Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Little bit about Alex
June
Indeed we are.
I think I will go first
Cooking
Kicking ass at
I have been watching nothing but cooking shows for like
Three weeks now and two nights ago
I cooked
A salmon fillet
And a stir fry
Perfectly
Salmon fillets
The crispy skin just right you know how hard it is to get the Christmas
F****** mailed it and I feel good about it somebody who generally for humor will
The insult you
What is this Behavior I should say and everyone should know that
Not new for you either like it's awesome that you're having this is fun but you've always been like a
Yeah yeah I'm over to your place for food before you make it
Some great ham I remember if it's at my head
You forgot that
A great potato dishes and a few times that I tried to make pizza
That were a disaster Fried Chicken
That was a airfryer first round was first round in the deep fryer
Oh yeah that one was real bad
Blame yourself too much for that
I'm glad you're having an enjoyment and
Can celebrate that little Victor
I'm feeling good it's between you know you've been we've been ordering out
So much over the past year-and-a-half
That it really good to like
We're trying to make that conscious effort to like go get
Fresh Food Eat fresh food
You know that kind of thing
Well congrats
What you're right but
Mine is actually you know I really appreciate
The fact that our audience
Is on
The ball
About stuff
I got an email from a guy Justin a listener 2003
We heard
Call to plug
The wilderness.com
Yeah I don't know I don't know what the f*** is going on
I get an email
This dude lets me know that
Roam the wilderness.com
Every figure that turns out it's a site those run by
Like some other 911
Some guys
The Wilderness and from the Wilderness. Come we're both run by Naruto 911
Venus.com
Another 9/11 guy who Alex had a fight with
Rmn the wilderness
It was just a survivalist
Site for the NRA that I thought midrash
Spot whenever people can be like
Bring more information to the conversation
Very cool then
It's at its Grey
That's awesome
Jordan
Today we are going to
Be taking a look
Apps
Some of the present
July 20th and 21st
Way I had it that's a lost art I got just the penalty
Five-second penalty
That was rubbing it in
Okay I don't even know how to tell you what's
Going to happen here
Crazyshit have excited I'm excited
The smile on your face suggests that Stevie peas might be involved
No
There is a gas
Okay
Now this is
To be tough I'm going to give you some Clues
About who they are
Okay and I don't know if you'll be able to get it
Okay
All the clues
Well I don't think I have much problem with that
Okay
This guy did 9/11
I swear to you
The problem with our show is that only narrows it down to like three kids
He has declared himself e
Sagami shows up during the show
Talk about his appearance towards the end
But also something happens that like
Legit blew my mind Alex Jones is an innovator
In the field of not doing your job
Just amazing okay I've been watching this guy for years
Like a laughing my ass off
This is art
Okay now I'm excited
We're going to teach everybody how to slack off at their jobs
Today you can get away with it I don't know if anybody else could do the s*** that he's doing
Open if you want help
Let's say hello
The crows call Thrice or this weapon glomma thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Sort of a reference
To Syfy thing that I don't know about
Next
My double chin is freakishly large thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Spider much that the ref
Did you and thank you so much
Thank you
The Emerick horror thank you so much you are now probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
CM Space City thank you so much you're an alcoholic
Like to say thank you and what up to Bram dirty dirty
Technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Also
Animal adoption news
We got it we sound effect
If you doubt these out a little bit
Nicole
Reached out to the World Wildlife Fund
YouTube Selena ocean for him
Unfriended now she can ride up on the blue whale to see her
My sincere hope eventually is that there is just a
The giant mural
It's a boy
Is ever expanding Nicole that is really really awesome
Yeah that'll be our Fresco it'll be deleting in the center with the Last Supper around
From Today Show
I got a second mind thanks to God
Okay alright
Okay
Is that
Good
Here's a restart on the 20th not good
But also a little little sci-fi
Parental rights being taken in your children
Sterilize as young as Age 3
In Phase 1
Helmet will be put over your children
Purse
Virtual reality
New way of thinking with
Direct General
With a I ever met
They call this
Direct neural
Intervention
Racism in the evilness of your child
We got rid of the left
The lineup that has children mounted at Birth
And the trial program
Yeah so badly in the future with your kids will have
Helmets put on them with AI overlords they will explain to them Teresa's
Picturesque look
What the Liberals are trying to do school for like 12 years of your life or you can get a home
Show me put on you in person either way you're going to be better off for it I'm fine with it
It's a little it's a little too late
Tell Susie program people to do cook salmon well
Great maybe you had a help with it on you when you were a kid
Cooking Grace's I was born was locked
So speaking of people you might yell bastards at
Every Project Camelot episode just one of those space soldiers bit like
Hey you know I had these regressed memories I've recovered them
How's the super soldier
Honestly
Veridian mazing I can't do it anymore but I used to be able to make an amazing bouillabaisse
Does Alex has a little buddy
At the beginning of the show just weird
They strange for him to have
Guest service associate
Real early on in the show and it's
Little gentleman
UK
11 a.m.
A Peter W call Joseph Watson comes in
Record store
Concerns this is silly
Restrictions with supposedly
90% of
The people I would say is still wearing masks inside shops
Isaura family
The year in the UK
Eating lunch in between putting
Taking off
Tons of people wearing masks
Outside
Week of the year
Being terrified I being brainwashed
I don't
People wearing masks
Now that now that it's not the
Purity of
Brighten underwear mask
And they're choosing to on their own
I'm so mad about that must be terrified into brainwash
Miss
They are aware of risk
Spinner bacon calculated decision
The air on the side of caution
Yeah I guess this angers ball
So silly
Yeah I mean if this was
Pre-pandemic
And people just started choosing to wear masks
For any number of reasons like including just
Having a mass culture similar to some Asian countries you know
Like
Then we wouldn't be a problem there wouldn't be this whole f******
How dare the government like we had a pandemic and people are like I don't want to give people the flu anymore either like just
You could see very easily a reality where Alex
Decided to go hard on like Chemtrails stuff
I was like you need to wear my underwear men block out the other than whatever it is falling from the sky
And you know that info Warriors my wear masks in public or something
Think I would
Considerate like
A crisis no
Maybe that's dumb
Whatever
I just
Is it has to take something out of here to be able to
Complain about that
I went on a walk yesterday and 75% of people wearing masks
And instead of going
Yep
This gets one of those standard Infowars and Paul Joseph Watson responses mermaid which is
Care
Drift into territory that's a little bit more into
We know they were brainwashed
We've got a document
This was the decision that was made of this.
Deviation
From the normal response to a
Every single historical
And instead they travel
By making them
More afraid
Of the threat the actual threat
That's just simply not
True
Princeton Cesspool think that the approach to Ebola outbreaks historically has been to strive for herd immunity
He was working at Infowars on the last big one happened so I'm sure he knows how that went. Don't you remember when that
Happened everybody was like okay lineup
We need to meet all of these people everybody needs to
Kiss all of the same time to World's Fair Michael Adams cure
It was also working at Infowars during the 2003 SARS outbreak and you must know that the goal in that case wasn't
Herd immunity
Toronto imposed
Strict lockdown
Community spread and other measures
Perused
In other places
For my article on the containment measures being employed from the May 2003 issue of the Canadian Medical Association Journal
Quote
Initial efforts to stop the spread of the disease consisted of
Hospital isolation of infected
Involuntary home quarantine of close contact contact
Home quarantine was soon expanded to include
Potentially exposed
Various jurisdictions including Ontario Hong Kong Singapore
In the United States
Have now invoke statutory powers
Permit involuntary Courant
In the case of SARS containment measures were fairly effective
Partially due to the different nature of how it was transmitted
Compared to the current outbreak
To be transmitted by people who had the virus but we're asymptomatic which made it much easier for people to self Courant
If you have symptoms you can very easily not go around people
And the work of isolating becomes a lot more sensible you know if your rational brain gets
Save MB
If you may have been exposed to the virus a week ago
You have no idea that it happened you haven't developed symptoms yet but you could be
Be contagious
Things are pretty difficult to manage
And so
The argument of acting as if
The worst case scenario is there is
Something that is
How do you understand we were there and that was not the case with
Organic difference between other pandemics
To the past and even so
In attempts to protect Public Health various efforts similar to the ones we're seeing that were used
If you go back and you look at some of the articles that were being published in 2003 you'll see the fair where the beginnings of attempts to make
Vaccines that would focus on the spike proteins of SARS
Absolutely would have been pursued more aggressively of containment measures had failed as they did in our present reality
Like you see the track
Already like there
This is exactly what would have happened
If things had gone South
Yeah it is this argument
That argument of appealing to this is it's not how we used to do things his self
That's
That somebody
F****** 200 years ago been like
Why are we trying to contain this this is God's plan and if you get sick you get sick
That's how it's always been that's how it always will be
It's a test yeah it's the same
The same s*** like no we should do it the way we used to do it no
Better than that
So when we go to the pastor when we look around we often see Alex being wrong about things
Most recently of course Bill Clinton being the Secretary General of the UN
That was a strange couple years 2000 wrong wrong predict
Japon Alex
Well one of things you see in the present
It's really fun it's Alex
Constantly talking about how
Vindicated
Everything you said has been right
Things he loves
To do is whenever you someone like Paul around
You get the real sanctimonious
Let me ask you how does it feel to always be right
This is one of my favorite things I love this shitt
Evolve
For 22 years
Makers.com
Keep it active since you were Niceville
I should stipulate
The blog is not being in the media we have a fairly decent audience for
I'm not positive that Paul has ever been
You're the longest
First but I've worked with on this
What is it like to be totally
Tennessee from
Research
What they were planning
And know that we're in their endgame
Accelerate it all
Autopia is
What is it like to be vintage
I mean it's kind of surreal because you
You don't want to believe in yourself
I've got great news
Wow just a nice little hand job of self-congratulatory b******* right there
I think it's really fun Tuesday like I was listening to this
I don't often listen to Paul Joseph Watson eat I don't
Think about him too much
But I was like wow
This guy's a worm
Deposition where he's talking about how like I do I told Alex.
Talk about Sandy Hook
Associate with a guy who get paid pretty well I guess
Paid really well it's outrageously really well
But I think that
That kind of editorial difference would be career and career-ending but like who would end your time
Yeah you would hope you'd think
Yeah and if you understood the ramifications of the decision
That you were opposed to your
Eating other people's lives in the victims families
The damage that was done because
Somebody decided to do the thing that you warned them was on escalator all
The other hand
In good conscience stay employed there
On the other hand
Most people
On in the states
It's work for someone who has committed crimes against humanity
Maybe not directly but the CEO
You know like everybody's everybody's working for evil now I I wouldn't be best friends with it
Or the direct subordinate I think you're talking about a different thing
I think really more
Realistically I think
Paul knows that
He's not employable
The rebel
Maybe you could get a gig at The Rim
Dance with the one what brung you a kind of situation
So
Paul's got another little boy to make it actually offended
Kay military is only supposed
Adversaries
And yet we have something
The 77th
What day did Alex at the start
Chinese government
Typing
The Hysteria
You remember those videos all the Chinese
Convulsing
Even though
Military
I would gchq
Social media
And through the combine
If the 77th Brigade which was
Responsible for disseminating propaganda that overhyped the virus and work to amplify the videos that alleged to show people falling over in the
If that was what they were actually doing
They could have had no better Ally in that effort than Alex Jones in the early part of 2000
100-percent easy to forget now because he's been doing this denial is s*** for quite a while but previously
Use banging The Different Drum
He was hyping the virus up in order to sell survival food and dump it
It's over
Humanity
He played all those videos that went around on social media people collapsing
He played unverified videos of streets in China being cleaned with trucks
Big hoses
He played the videos of people in Wuhan yelling encouragement to each other from their windows
Reporting it as been screaming in horror
You can hear Alex's giddy excitement
To get his hands on such a video as soon as Mike Adams brings it up
In this clip from February 24th
I saw a haunting video last night
Find us easily was in
Chinese
And it was just a
Video
Film in Ohan
Of all the
Buildings at night
In the background
The Scream
The Haunting blood-curdling screams from
People that mental
I want to see in their mind
I will yeah we've got the link
Is very excited
And not only did Alex do all of that
He also made up a ton of s*** to scare his audience at the thing that things were worse than they were in China
One of the Prime examples of that was how incendiary Alex that were being released
The number of people infected in China
Was secretly actually the number of people dead from the virus
He was telling the audience that it was his belief
That the number of reported that in China was being
Drastically underreported
I thought it was total chaos
This is a clip from his February 6th
We got to get ahead of this if you notice
Thousand confirmed we're locked in here a few minutes go 24,000
The internal Chinese numbers that leaked
Rapid publish in China by the people daily
24000 dead
Yesterday
They're doing is they're just
The number of dead is a number.
Alex engaged in all of the worst Scare Tactics he's accusing the mainstream media of engaging in
You just counting on his audience not remembering a-rollin
Accountable because they never do
What are the big things that Paul and Alex are up in arms about is how no young people were killed by the virus
Here's a clip from this week's interview from the 20th of July
Of Paul and Alex complaining about the
Melow twelve-year-olds be shot
There is no danger of K
All the side effects is that not.
But we have the numbers
People
From covid in the UK
Across a year. Two-thirds of those have serious illnesses so it's literally
In the UK
That's a fun presentation when you're trying to run an anti-vaxxer narrative grip but
What times are different like
Back on February 24th and you're trying to run
Different crib for you scare your audience into buying survival food and toothpaste or heavily implying can protect them from a deadly virus
You might have a slightly different angle
The number for coming out we know that
Killing healthy young people
What is killing a high number of those
They are in fact
These people are f****** creeps
And I want to make one thing super
Clear
This Gambit Alex and Infowars is running now is being funded by the money that they scammed off people with the extreme fear-mongering
The paranoia about covid
Which now they're pretending they never engaged in
And that's important
And something the people should not forget
I was digging around in the archives for a couple of these clips though and remembering a lot of the specific
It made me mad
I don't like
Mad mad little mad I understand I didn't want to leave this little segment here that we're doing on that note
So I thought it might be fun to remind you of one of my favorite things
They came out of Alex's early covid bulshit
This is the best
Like my brother told me I don't know where you got this
Bubble wrap because of all the air
Comes from China
Great point and more
Points f****** people are idiots comes from
China
Grateful
Great Point bubble wrap
Anyway I find I find this disgusting
Disposition
IMDb The Wiggles at Paul and Alex are trying to do
And Paul is he ever going to have to do a deposition or he tells people
You told Alex not to say all that s*** about the virus early 2020
We're going to have to pretend that 20 I was on the right side of that one too
Something needs to happen about that
It's f***** up
You know like I keep going back to the reports
F******
Jared goddamn Kushner is 6 months into it and
They're they're like
He had the chance to implement
The cdc's plan but they told him that to Maywood
Mainly going to be in the cities
And the cities are mainly Democratic so we let the s*** go
Like that is a situation where I don't know how we're not
Investigating that like all the
Cuz that's
F****** even even under ideal circumstances it feels like something
Take a long time to fully unravel investigation
To terms with
All of the errors that were made
Intentional or unintentional along the way
But Alex is errors
Very intention
Very intelligent
The archive of Clear Lake
Why it's a little more overt than I remembered that this was about selling food and pills
Yeah gross
Yeah I remember I remember that and I also remember
A good project
Camelot where
She claimed it
They were bored
Writing people up because they were vampires
Where's that one was my favorite possibly
That one was my favorite
That was a good one
David Johnson
And he's a quote-unquote whistleblower
Sure who's working with project veritas
He's a guy who
He eats pose that they were teaching
Critical race Theory at Hasbro
Sounds like a Mad Lib
Honestly
30 Chick-fil-A
Boy
Humanity
I was bewildered by this
So he decided to leave
After this Sinister critical race Theory thing
Whistle blew and now he has a GoFundMe thing with his $130,000 raise
Oh wow what a good scam
Pretty good
I think I could do Tsum that's at least a year's salary at wherever he was work
No at least
I guarantee I guarantee that I couldn't anyway
Quit the show
Call up
James O'Keefe
Do you think hard
You can make up any
Nobody would care be brutal
So this guy is on and I honestly don't think
Great care to take what he saying all that seriously and one of the reasons is this
Bonita
People based on
Their character by the actions that they
Sawgrass in the truest sense
Martin Luther King
One of my favorite quotes from
Generation
The circumstances of your birth are irrelevant
What you do with life
From
That's an interesting quote
Got a strange you didn't say what movie it's from the car makes me suspect that he's trolling
That's on the Pokemon movie
I don't know how old this dude is butt
Strong's
Suspicion that he's too young for the Pokemon movie to have been one of the most
The biggest movies of
Childhood
However online you can find a fair amount of memes using the
Misquote
I'm not positive but I suspect that
It's kind of part of a joke that grew out of the whole incident that the the GOP primaries where Herman Cain quoted the theme song
A Pokemon to a quote famous poet
Yes yeah I think I think that there's some of that
In meme culture that is
You know you can fly in
A bunch of
Inspirational
Posts
It is like Mewtwo also find some that are trying to attributed
Two other people
I remember I remember Thomas Jefferson in one of his letters
Route something
Just truly beautiful and it was just like
I want to be the very best
I like no one ever was
Write the Declaration this must remember the first time I read Federalist number 5
Gotta catch em all
I don't I don't know
He delivered that quote in the way that he's being kind of cagey about not
Quote saying what movie is not take this dude all this year I think he might be f****** with Alex
I don't really know and I don't want to over
So anyway Alex's big news
This is still like
The David Johnson interview still going on
But he has he has to let you know something okay
Big ass news
Bombshell
Because I
Documents
To show you this properly
I'll tell you about that either
Weather today
Special broadcast
I am at the hold on mr. Johnson let me break in here
I have breaking news
That I will tell you tomorrow
Breaking story up,
Breaking news
News eventually will break
I love it
This is not uncommon Behavior at all
So unfortunately Alex
Kind of tips his hand
Breaks the news
Last night with us
What's in this lawsuit
The first few days from vaccine
I've also got two more boxes
I don't I don't know what he's talkin to
What Lotto
I don't know he's in a workout
20th and 21st
Right and I don't know
You don't know
Dimensions that some people are
Suing
Somebody it's unclear I think he says that they're going to be on the show on Friday
But yes
Big bombshell that Alex won't cover is that 43,000 people have died from the vaccine
He has evidence of it and he doesn't
I guess on Mondays show if those people are on Fridays
Episode of History I guess we'll
Be able to learn what it is but we're covering the 20th and 21st and 20th
Houses that on the 21st he will be breaking this news
He breaks that news on the 20th
And then on the 21st he will not break the news any further other than to say that on the 23rd
On the 22nd 23rd he'll talk to the people
That are involved in this news
Alright
I need a calendar
So he talks to David a little bit and
This is
This is just one
Corporate I was like okay
I think I get a sense of what's going on here
When did they start when did you first then
That you were supposed to go through this
I'm very shortly into my time
I just saw the meeting for critical race theory on Mike
That was really the first time it came up
I've been aware that has Roy has kind of done
Similar things based
Critical race Theory before like I think they have
Monopoly before which
Kind of pushes the
Gender Theory
I gotta think that this
Guys f****** around
That does not seem like a serious
But then also was working at Hasbro for a short. Of time probably didn't like it
Hated it hashed out
Yelp
It's such a good scam
Oh man
I really like you
You know
You don't think about the scam until you've already seen it done too many times
Ansia no
Like at my old job I could have pulled this game it wouldn't have been hard
You just walk out the door and make bulshit up
Brutal
So Alex
Talks to this dude and I a scientist
Interview on
Convincing on capella
Another interview with Angela Stanton
King
Okay
She's person who ran
For office
In Georgia
Chi
She's already made clear that she's not related to Martin Luther King
She's the goddaughter of
Alveda King
Who is the niece
Of Martin Luther King
So we're not
Connected
At least you know personally connected
They can do a barbecue together Alex
This is this is weird praising on his part
What would
Martin Luther King jr.
I think that he would agree at all
Manisses
If he hadn't been assassinated Martin Luther King Junior be 92 years old right now
Here is a few people who are currently alive at 92 years old
Noam Chomsky Berry Gordy
Barbara Walters and Bob Newhart
I understand that he was killed in what feels like the far
Past but
Not that long ago
Blue f*****-up
To call Martin Luther King someone's ancestor
Yeah
Yes
F***** up really happened fast it really happen fast they turned a hero who died
Recently into Santa Claus so quick and they refuse to acknowledge all of the other s*** that he was
Clockmaker
Wow terminology there your ancestor is
Is bizarre
Angela Stanton King of the conspiracy person who happens to also talk a lot about supporting Criminal Justice Reform
I
Think that's great
Disagree with the notion that the justice system needs a lot of work I'm just not going to team up with people who Twitter qanon slogans
And his voice support for the idea that Wayfair is selling kids and couches
Yeah
Anyway she ran unopposed
For the GOP Primary in the 5th District race in Georgia in the 2020 election
She lost in the general with almost
An impressively bad
Number 14.9 per cent of the vote to her opponent
85.1
This was of course due to election fraud
According to reputable sources
I particularly those named Angela Stanton
Sure
So yeah
Hey
Did they steal the election
Just ask
Mead Mead
So here was something that I had to bring
Under the table
What is
It's on equality Act
Our children
In Harm's Way
Amazing
I can listen to you all day
Has not signed the equality Act
It would likely die
An identical Bill HR
The same bill was introduced into Congress before that titled HR 2282 and it died in committee
You're not going to believe this Jordan but same bill was introduced
The Congress before that title hr3
5-minute timer committee why would they keep numbering it different than everybody knows that it starts at 6
66 is the lazy game these scammers are playing and
It's getting a little old yeah the grift is really repetitive
It's disappointing
So Alex
I had some complaints about the media
I have to assume that when he says the media he means us
I'm guess
Cuz I don't know if I've ever heard anyone else but us make this
Compliant
Why say
5 / prepared for something
That's not a joke
The media always
I got too much to cover here
Yeah I don't I don't know if I've heard anybody talk about it but we talked about it incessantly
Is amazing how unprepared
And that is a documented fact
Insanely documented
Documenting things
But we have ever done
It might be one of the larger themes accidentally of our show
What can laziness do for you so Alex
But this isn't love
Beginning of the third hour
10 minutes left
What
What is happening
So this is what happened
This is where I was like
This guy is innovative I'm f****** amazing
Chelsea is all over TV and now everyone is regurgitating the LIE
That
Ninety-nine percent of the
I'm covid
You can spend 30 second
Can I go to the US
Government phone numbers
Almost 50%
Are in the vaccinated
Right
Fox and CNN and all of them
Repeating the same lie over and over again
Special shows
Emergency broadcast I don't know what we're going to call this
So I can go live
You want to just buy shove it
Okay see you again
What do you want me to 10 minutes left in the show The Middle the 3rd hour I don't know what's going on you're going to come back tonight you need to
What is happening
Here's what's happening
I'm impressed with Angela Stanton
And I'm invite her back
Text Mark Cummins
44 days
Amazing
Reschedule
They're coming back there was
Especially
Emergency reporting
I got Fox and CNN parroting all this b******* so I can't even get to her right now they're all
Call just parroting pouches and rescheduled
Doctors doctors appointment in the middle of the second hour to take a personal hour
Off of work
The work that I do
Yeah that is only 3 hours literally two possibilities one is it when the show started he knew he had to go to a doctor's
Appointment
It got rescheduled while he's on air
That's an amazing doctor
We can fit you in like that
And a really chaotic workplace
I think his needs better organization
It must be a very serious
If you're going to do and you didn't know prior to and it started
The other option is that Alex knew when the show started that he was going to be leaving
In the middle or beginning of
And if that was the case then you shouldn't have spent all that time digging around with the project Veritas dude about Hasbro
Having having
Critical race Theory nonsense
Paul Joseph Watson talking bulshit
Anza Angeles dance
Adam King just talkin more nonsense
Like I didn't get your f****** news he had all the time in the world
Seem like
The news that he is
Presenting himself as having
Which disagrees with all known available knowledge regardless
Vaccinations and death by covid
If that is 50
B15
That's the most important
News in the world right now
This literal most important news of the world
Well I like I'm not I can look into things as much as I can and I can
Find the stories about
Vaccines
Veritiv
Pizzava
I've been texting her hospitalization put like unless he actually covers the story he's refusing to cover
I can't do anything I don't know what he
He's talking about
Well I think he's talking about made up stuff
That is going to never come out
So we go to the 21st because
At this point as I was listening I'm sorry I ruined it already that I don't know what that lawsuit that he was talking about
Okay okay during about something
Yeah I know I don't know
He did
An impressive job of not talking about the things that he has sensibly wants to being a couple of of little Clues
Talk about this later
Yeah it's a nice annoying
Eli can we get some clarity on that
Would you not
But he has another bombshell
12 Monkeys
Play dram
In the world in London England
Bauer he went on TV
And said that the inoculations for covid-19
Pfizer
But he studies and runs the program on
Studying those are vaccinated around the world
He says it will get rid of your immune system and give you 16
The immune system you had previously
Oh no you're going to need
Every month
This gets rid of your
I'm HIV
But it doesn't
Destroys
Your body's immune system
They've committed
This bombshell story about covid
Match the clues about the bomb shelter
From yesterday
He was teasing
I'm getting pissed
It's very different bombshell
We've got a lot of Bombshells happening all around us juggling
There's this is the Blitz
Anyway this story is talking about involve some comments that he's taken out of context
A guy named David Bauer
Power is a researcher at the Francis Crick
Matutinal on-demand was leading a team that was researching the Pfizer vaccines at
Efficacy against other strains
But if emerged
The research was resort with centered around assessing levels of neutralizing antibodies that people had against
The strain
And I'm just going to read you hear from a write-up about his research in WebMD
And see if you can figure out where Alex took his bulshit from
Please wait until the the quote is done alright then raise your hand
Okay tell me where the b******* okay okay
This is a fun exercise
The team compared the concentrations of the neutralizing antibodies among the various
They found the people who lived
Fully vaccinated with to Weiser doses had antibodies that were six times lower against the B 16-17
Five times lower against the B 1351 variant
And 2.6 * lower against the b-117.
When compared to the original strain
You get the b*******
So what's going on is that Alex is taking the stairs research which is shown a potential concern that the Pfizer vaccine May provide
6 * lower antibody levels against one variant as opposed
The original virus
Alex is reporting that is this guy saying that covid vaccines Wipeout 5c
Six of your nudes
So total b*******
A fantastic way of two
Describing I'm sorry I didn't give you a chance to respond to sad
A very sad that is a day that the vaccine designed for the original variant
It's very good at the original Barrett it is in 6 times
Antibodies for new variants only up only of these neutralizing antibodies is it Pacific
Type of antibody that does not mean that it is 16
Effective
In totality again
These other stores
Nor does it mean that you have 1/6 of your immune system
No it's not like antibodies are one thing and they fight off everything
It's a rager
This is very dumb
Deep down in his brain
Alex thinks that white blood cells
AR
Basically the same little tanks from those Atari games that fired little
At evil viruses and that's all it is pronounced
White blood cells
At the best blood cells
I realize that this is why this doesn't work disorders like exercise doesn't work
At like a dozen an educational environment it cuz it
It's disappointing
It's a bummer
This is just pathetic levels of intentional misrepresentation
Sentation on Alex's Park
It's even
Disappointingly transparent
For him
Like I honestly was like oh wow this is
You would have thought you would have to be either incredibly stupid
To misunderstand it this way
Or both Craven and Incredibly stupid to use that misunderstanding this way
Shameless
To not think like
People can see through this really easily discussion of Bowers findings online
I'm going back to early June
This isn't news Alex probably just saw a tweet about it recently decided
Need to stop the goddamn presents
Oh my God
Let's soda
Pickleball
Now I will say
When I heard this I thought
I had a huge rainstorm yesterday and I did
7 hours of research yesterday evening
Bulshit
Until 3:30 in the
Diamond Princess
Okay so Alex was up all night researching
I know that mode I know that mine
I've been there
That's the type of mindset you love movie Alex isn't coming with some Dan on it solutely I think
Maybe Alex is finally learning he's listening to you are criticisms about his
Quote over preparedness so perhaps he's like you know what this time I'm going to do some Dan on this I'm going to have
Some real
What I love is that he was over-prepared
To do his show on
Tuesday
And you failed to get to any of that news
Now he's on Wednesday
Is over prepared once again about a completely different topic
It's crazy what a dick
You can use
Could you now I'm going to throw this out
If you were over prepared for one show
Could you not use that preparation for then perhaps the next to
You wouldn't even have to do any more work
No
No cuz you got to keep running
Well that's fair
These bulshit stories will not fly tomorrow
Only work today to your grandma today or you going to do whenever
They only for shelf life for the stuff is
Real short
So Alex plays the clip I want to play all of the clip that Alex plays
David Bauer
In its original form
You can actually even find it at the Raw
Unedited version of it where is like spell your name
It's clear he's being asked about variance
You can tell the clips
Starts in a particular place
So that context is DeVore
Here's just a small
Message from our finding is that we found that recipients of the Pfizer van
Taxi in those who had two doses
How about
526 fold lower amounts of
Neutralizing antibody
Gold standard
Private security
Antibodies of your immune system
Virus from getting into your cells in the first place
So we found it
Southwest for people with to do since we've also found that
For people with only one dose of the Pfizer job
They are less likely to have high levels of these antibodies
In their blood
And perhaps most importantly for all of us going forward
Is that we see that
The older you are
Don't lower your levels are likely to be
The time since you had your second job
Has that time goes on
The lower your levels are also like
That's telling us that we're probably going to be needing to
Prioritize boosters for older more vulnerable people
Coming up soon specially if
Disney variants
And
Wow
Wow wow wow
Just a big ol while guys
Completely out of context clip even within it has him very specifically describing antibodies for differ
Turnbury at that one specific
Yep
So
Wow
High tide has the flu will kill us all just don't even know man like
This is
This is pathetic
I know I don't want to like
Really just
Be overly glib
But even for me
You feel like
I'm punching under my weight class
Video2 deceptive
Oh well here's what's interesting about this
Nope that doesn't pass muster
To add insult to that injury
We had to open the show listening to them smugly describe how right they were about everything
Manor sanctimonious prick so
F****** b*******
That's well
I have to listen to me like how does it feel to be Vindicated
There's a lot of
Things that are repetitive beat
About everything
Charanda oh we got another one
If we get if we get a third we got a hat-trick okay
Well this is definitely going to be the most important broadcast of my 27 years on air
By the grace of God and your incredible prayers and support
We are still in
This position to fight back against these monsters
All of you
Yeah man most important. Cast of his career
Broadcast he was up till 3 in the morning and he found a weird clip on
Twitter
Cool boy
Yeah I can see him staying up till 3:30 just
Like
Down in a bottle of whiskey you just
Progressively angrier
Twitter clips
Sinbad life
Sure and then he's there for the next day
Most important broadcast man is awesome
I want to believe that this is true
Like I really want to believe that this is his actual experience and guy but I'm not positive I can
Canntrust
I want it to be
I got home yesterday at dinner with the family my daughter want to go to bed early the youngest daughter about 8 so I went into my office
Close the door
1 a.m.
When I went and got the bed
And then I
Could not stop
Stop playing
God said get back up and get back on the computer
Jumping around everywhere
And and
Information
Here today
I love this idea so Alex is trying to go to bed and he's laying there and he just
Can't stop praying
This connection to God will not close
Annie hears the voice of the Divine
The Divine reaches
Across the fabric of the universe to him and it says
Cruise the web Alex Cruz
Find something weird on Twitter
You know who else you know what
Here's a what practices that little store God told me to pay here's what happened to that
Story right before it began
I did a bunch of Meth
Then my job that's them what that's how you get into its 1 and I can't stop praying I have a where you get
I have a working Theory
This might have something to do with the doctor's appointment
I think Isaac baby I hope Steph
If you f***** up on this episode
These weird be prayed till 3 in the morning and that God told him to search the internet.
About anybody.
Reporting as I can
60 mm system
What's my password
Sometimes sometimes even
Even my cynical self it breaks
Through and I remember we live in a weird place
True
Here's some money or some big nose
I began to research off
Clip
Trudeau
Chinese dictator
Walk down up there
Forced booster shots
Why do pork brisket
They go back to giving you two year
Pause whatever quote Pfizer wants to put in
More research
I wonder who's your wreck
Acting this project
So I looked up
The project of how to Twitch
Cyber-shot
I found
Pfizer employee who heads up the project
For the main level 4 bioweapons lab in London England
They'll be telling you about
I watched
Videos
Doesn't
By the time I was done my job was on the ground
Alex did none of those
Clips on Twitter 100
Read dozens of David Bowers papers
You just making up
Is prudential's and like
Oh he's in charge of tweaking the vaccine
Nonsense I love his habit
Quote in in the wrong spot
You know like
Whatever quote Pfizer wants to put in you
What
Where
We're going to pull the quote Pfizer wants to put in you
Visors not really their name
Kaiser wants to put you
Cuz it says quote
So it has to be a quote
You can't be
Oh no I thought that the quotes were like
Quote-unquote Elites
You know like whenever you're saying like something isn't really what the
Quote Pfizer you think it was scared quotes
Right around by the scotch
The devil
Sarah quote
Alex gets into some mind-blowing chicken van
So
You don't
Canada
Can afford to get booster shots right
Tweaking the program whose
Squeaking
The Pfizer vaccine right in order to
Get everything right
It's this guy right now I'm speaking I will I need to find out who's tweaking I read all his papers and guess what
It goes so much deeper how much
Henrietta Lacks
That we told you about
Is black woman
They got eaten alive by cancer in one week
Stolen
And it's the basis of all
Human cloning
Everything today
The cells won't die
Herself
Are you oh my God I didn't know they cloned her
You 1966
In 1966
Alright
Okay we are
You seen the saying we're like jumps on things and eat some total at what age
I don't believe it's human
Doesn't have our genome doesn't work chromosome
Short another species
I'm show you Wikipedia and imma show you the actual.
Okay
This little Feller right here
They're putting Henrietta Lacks cells
Any
And one other
White baby that got a bored in the third trimester
Also 60
But she's from 1951
So
Ladies and gentlemen
Sid the Science Fiction movie you went to sit down and eat some Milk Duds and pop
Popcorn maker
Yeah that one's that one's Wild
Seems a little bit
Weirder than normal
Purcells won't die
Alex what he's doing
This is basically just would it's not worth it
When you talk to somebody who
Stayed up all night
Gatlin
A couple facts Miss
Like read them
About something and then just spun a while drinking ramble out of it to blow your mind with some like Elementary
Details about Immortal cell line
Set the most famous Immortal cell line is the Hela cells name for Henrietta Lacks
Scott African American woman who died in 1951
Researchers studying the cells collected from her cervical cancer sample discovered
But instead of dying as
Expected they would
Continue to replicate
Essentially forever
Never die it's okay
Concentrate
How old is breakthroughs in all manner of scientific Fields we're testing couldn't be done on hue
Subject
And one of the largest problems is actually Alex is right about it they did steal it
Like it didn't have nothing planned it's really f***** up
Yeah it was accidentally right about that
These Hela cells are pretty remarkable but they're not unique and they're not alien an orgy
There's a product of mutation which is not super uncommon in cases of
Cancer
There's a line of cells called The Jerk hat cells which began from a 14 year old
T-cell leukemia
There other human immortalized cell line
Plenty of other animal one
Comes to
The fetus related cells you bringing up our the HEK cells and those come from a fetus that could have been aborted or possibly
Play miscarried
Sheriff not entirely sure
That's all I didn't begin in the lights
60's hits
Was 1973
Alex's just like
I guess you skimmed Wikipedia article about this and he is just like oh my God they're going to put
These zombie cells in you
It's pretty silly
Love that
Love it I love it they clone Durand 19-6
56th and
They cloned ER
Where's my clock
That's not important
Will she die
Never exclude her from the immortal cell
Ourselves
Become immortal
I don't know
So Alex's makes up some details about Henrietta Lacks cuz I think he's just
Oh
The Henrietta
Backstory
Guess what comes out of
And the human party
Tuskegee Alabama
With everything
Is it made up on the spot
Henrietta was from Virginia
But you moved to Maryland after get
Getting married
Johns Hopkins
To have her cancer dealt with because they were the only hospital around those parts
Treated black people
At the time
I love to do with Tuskegee but Alex is just
Flying off the wall to pick up everything really sending it out
Of course this does lead
Some Grim prediction
Defense is right now for extermination
It's a powerful yahrzeit. Actually put this
I mean
And I guess we're going to join all the aborted babies now
Going to be at work
When the viruses in the mutation
Doing this to us
Sarah Goode die this fall
I mean
I would have done that LaFontaine voice
Oregon with it
This fall
The death of
No I think he'll leave that to Gregory
Has more of a voiceover things going on
I'm pretty basic misunderstanding
Things about these Hela cells
And here's another one
I don't care if you're in the Navy or you're a farmer
Military school teacher
I don't care who you are this is going to get
You're not getting out of this
Helium
Vaccine
Henrietta Lacks
Whatever ate her
That's whatever 8
Henrietta Lacks
Is all of the vax
Is pretty disturbing
So
Whatever 8 Henrietta Lacks
Text
Is in all the facts
It's the only way to interpret this is that Alex thinks that henrietta's cancer was in fact an alien ended 8
How the immortal cell line that came from her is that alien reproducing
Another Global as they're putting that alien cell line into vaccines for something
Nefarious
I'm going to throw this out
Haha
I disagree with everything Alex's said
About what he did the night
Before
He stayed up watching the trailer for Carnage
I'm just mistook Venom
For Henrietta Lacks is murderer he took some
Sunbeam had some fun
This is painfully dumb and I'm kind of worried that Alex should have just taken the day off
I have no idea what's going on why he went to the doctor but he seems
He was like
He seems a little different than normal
This feels like somebody who's just
Grabbing whatever like
It like right now in my eyes
His his brain is just a bunch
Lights
Rolling around and he's just grabbing whatever pops out
And he's just like this
This works
Throws makes less sense than normal
Whatever
Whatever 8 Henrietta
That was school's out to break with that
Alien
Alien ships going idiot I don't disagree
I think it's called
So here's how
Come back from break
Everyone's being injected
What cellular product
Mortal shell on black woman
Is that your biggest problem
Human cells
Different genome
Botanica
Ate her
In a week
Only found one of their human they admit
Aborted
Baby
Out of here with your War of the Worlds
True
Also I don't have the scientific credibility to discuss the actual process for it but you can create your own immortalized
So why don't you want to it's not magic or some kind of alien she just seems like it when you have
Haven't slept
It's just that simple
Yeah
Sunnyway if you forgot this
You got off on this
Alien
Tumor thing or magical world right now
Then I think he's used to
Dude I mean specifically at this at this episode he's living in a magical world where whatever
BoBoiBoy I'm concerned that he lives in that state
Much more regularly
He's good at disguising it about
You should beat like he should be listening back to the show while holding a brown bag and then like look at it and toss it in the car
But you know like this is the level of like
Oh boy these pink elephants are attic
Control
So if you forgotten
He's got off on talking about this
Immortal cell line
Alien origin story is this David Bauer guy
Who works at the Francis
Put yes
Caribbean system
Take me to Pfizer vaccine
Hey man I got to say
Course of this episode over trying to put a Target on somebody
He couldn't do much better job than he is
David LV
The program at the bioweapons lab in London England
Started the first shots
He studies their blood
See what happens when he has the project up
Telling you
Reduces your immune system
Massively
In the future
The key message from our finding
Just plays the same clip again here is that like
The only kind of attention you're going to bring
Towards this person
Is going
Going to be people accusing him
I'm saying the things that Alex is claiming
Decide which
He didn't
He will say
I didn't say that that's not at all truth
Now he's part of
The cover-up
And
Just it's just a really negative cycle
Perpetuated
The easy explanation for it is Alex
You're wrong
This is absolutely wrong
This is not what you said
Stop you need to
So long retract
Action isn't good enough
A lifelong Richard
Yeah
The next Republican escape this cuz it's just with the part of the episode where he says that
The people that the bombshell from the previous day or can I go now
Great love it love it
Science might be close to death though
Well that means the way you stalking right now it seems
No no no no no
You got a wrong
We're talking murder map
Pressure here
You need to go research the song yourself
How many times did I take the Rockefeller Foundation
Runs Gates runfalcon
Boys
Cuz they're losing right now
They want to attack but they know it's not going well
Rock Stepside
Now the big boys throwing up
And believe it or not right over the button and
You tell him it's going to make him bigger don't do it they're having debates the boardroom
And
That's fine
You're all going to be good so to anyways
I'm talking about all the Lister
You guys are right
Robinson
True Blood
Main reason
That Obi-Wan became more powerful in death was
As a
Assistant
To Luke
You know as somebody who can
Continue to guide him
Him further that's ensuring The Inevitable Defeat
Of Darth Vader
Rights
Now here's the thing
About
Debating whether or not killing Alex will make him stronger
His Luke
Skywalker is
Owen Shroyer
You get rid of him buddy it's all gone
Yeah I think that maybe there's a disturbing
Benson the force
Hasn't been picked up yet or something baby it is somebody out there that Alex's
Force ghost
Yeah I don't know I think
That notion of like
These shadowy globalist
S2r my Arch Rivals for the last 30 years
They just don't kill me because if they did it would prove
Give me right about everything
It's just dumb
It sounds convincing people who have already bought in
Enough to be like
Yeah you're right about everything sure you don't believe any of it
It's not persuasive at all
You know it's sitting right in the f****** boardroom being like let's kill Alex Jones
Probably think about no never
But even the even in his like just judging by normal human behavior
Even in the circumstance that the one point in time there was a boardroom being like sugar
That's a
One gomita
You know either you do or you don't
Alex hasn't done anything different in the past 20 years you know if they were going to do it they would have already done it
There's no point now you got a you got to think
Ya think
That would
And
Let's not forget
Did the people who would be killing our
Yes
Work for the
That's true
They have they have so much restraint
Call Jee advanced
From anything that we even know they could make this death look
Any kind of way they wanted to Henrietta Lacks at any point in time
Cancer blow darts
Emergency
Could be an army of henrietta's ready to kill Alex at any point in time
Stupid
Stupid and embarrassed
Yep so anyway Alex has some new money coming into the show
Isis Isis for you they are
Devil's children
Dream
The energy Lee Anderson
In Dark Crystal it's all an allegory
Tell me about a break I'm going to ask you all remember
Broadcast possible when you go to my pillow.
Tom
There are
They wanna promo codes
Okay so you get link on my pillow now
Brewery
Bruno
Both have fallen
Two windows to shake hands they both
Dig a little bit deeper in the air bottomless pit
Yeah it's
It's sort of the same as Nick Fuentes and Alex working
Together it's like
Possibly be happy about this
Geode swamp territory like they read like you have
To go into the dark.
Set the bar
IU bv3 monsters
Like a f****** Bigfoot's in the wild now by the way
We did that episode earlier in the week about
Nick Fuentes video about
Maintaining the white demographic little update on that info
The title on that video
Now it's the same video
The title says America must
Preserve its core demographic wow wow
You got to the bottom of what the problem was
They forgot to change the thumbnail
You know the thing you should changes the existence of
The video that's the major issue there because the title apparently not is also
Substance of Davido
See it is
Here's what's fascinating about this
It shows
But there is some sort of editorial review it Infowars
They did something there was a conversation about like
But instead of recognizing the title is reflective of the content
Maybe we shouldn't have this content
Alright our company murdered millions of people but now we're a different name
Grey-headed job Bandit video
Dickwad a culture is out of control why can't Nick Fuentes speak
Are you afraid are you in a war on
Are you afraid of the word white Alex
I feel like Alex is afraid of white p
I think I think he is just as well realizes that white
People
Just can't be
Never thought I'd see the day
So Alex rest a little bit here about David Bauer
It's not about seeing it's a gene therapy
That gets rid of your immune system
Only
Hell
And by the way that's not even tonight
Advisor
For the UK government
What is your 16 and what it was and only
Zbrush your life
I want a Pfizer comes up with
The study
The he heads up
At the most prestigious facility
UK
Probably the world
The Institute
UK's bio-weapon facilities there Fort Detrick Maryland
DNA
Along with a W and goddesses blacks on humans
So this is a really nice group of people
You free associating a little more than marble
Is in-between scattershot
So also now David Bauer isn't just a researcher at this Francis Crick Institute
I guess Alex is promoted into the position of supervisor or something
Feel like the way they sloppily throwing out random details should be a bit of a red flag he's also a player manager for the Oakland A's
He's busy
Like Danny Shea Graham
Rambus yes
Formerly the UK's big bioweapon lab whatever that means
Beef stew was opened in 2016 and if Alex
Cared at all about keeping his details straight
You should know that he's already established and Infowars lore that port
Down is the UK's giant evil by 11 lab
That's literally what he called their Fort Detrick back in 2003 when he's trying to argue that they'd released footage
Mouth disease
Also whatever to saying is not only out of context
It's also a complete lie
You didn't read any of these studies and that's why he's not speaking in any specific
It's about any of it pass yelling but he's ready
Studies over and over again up
These papers that were written by Baauer they're available on Francis Creek Inn
Institute website so
He wants that we're get into anything
Specifically I'd be happy to
Mix it up by
I'm not going to go on a wild goose chase
You'll likely scenario
He hasn't read anything I know he's
Read all of these studies I just assumed all eventually all figure out what Alex is talking about
Many studies that have never come in handy
I have
I've played this game many a time and
Come up wanting every time
Good War Games you know yet sometimes the only way to win is not to play
Generally also wanting our neck
Text gas shows up
Robert Barr
Dial God
Dammit
What is your dad
Subway has comes on to complain about Trump
Impotent social media lawsuit
And how they need to do more
Or something he's also mad at Black Rifle coffee
Because apparently they don't support
Kyle Rittenhouse
Black Rifle coffee
Talk to me Black Rifle coffee is
Is
I mean when you talk about mtch
When you talk about
I will you talk about what's destroyed this country there the essence of
That's all I'm saying is that
With friends like this we don't need
Anyanime Speedway
So what happened here is the Kyle Rittenhouse was pictured wearing a black rifle coffee t-shirt back in November
Immediately the right-wing
Insisted that the coffee company should
Sponsor him
They released a statement that said no
F*** that murdering piece of s***
Great and I was considerable backlash to them to be a company that would
Right
Recently one of the founders of the company didn't interview with the New York Times where he wrestled with his place in the mark
How do you build a cool kind of irreverent
Pro-second Amendment promerica Brandon the Maga Arrow without doubling down on the bog of movement
Not being called a f****** Rhino by the Baga guys
That's a real dilemma in my answer to that is you probably can't
Your community let those s*** heads in because
To do so is
The easiest and cheapest way toward gaining power
This is what happened yeah it's weird how everybody saw it coming
The co-founder wet on
The racism s*** really pisses me off
I hate racist
Proud boys people
Like I'll pay them to leave my customer base
I'll gladly chopped
All these people out of my f******
Customer database
I pay them
Get the f*** out
I apologize if the problem is dude is facing but also big mistake about it keep corded Disick
Exact audience
The cleanup His Name by Jesse Valentine
Which is great
Just probably take a little bit more work than this
Probably squeal like a shity snake charmer was trying to complain about getting bitten by a snake
I don't know how I'm supposed to care
But now Alex is going to
Virtue signal as far as Watson likes to say about how much he
Hates Black Rifle coffee
I am also make no mistake about this
Alex is using the
Parsley at the way to plug his own cock
Easy wind
We hate this guy guess who does support the Second Amendment and
That's right
Are you I have zero patience
Zero patience for a Nazi at a Nazi rally
Being like
You know this place would be great if there weren't all these f****** Nazis around
I don't care what you have to say about the Maga people being mean to you I think
F*** off I think that I do have
Enough empathy
If the person
Realization
Changes
If they leave
That rally
And recognize you got to leave the Nazi rally Buhdeuce
Hard soul-searching
And what have you been
Good on you I'm not going to this guy necessarily for have
Having these feelings now there's a possibility that in a few years
Do you know this process
Will come to his needs to go remember saying how the early branding and playing into the culture
Boerboel shed right all that stuff led to the point where he had the consumer-based
But he does that is full of s*** head races to get mad if you don't support Kyle didn't
The first thing that he has to wreck
Nice courses
He's here by because of him
And not because his audience
He chose this
That's how it work before did that
And it wasn't too that's really fascinating to me is like
Things that Alex is really huge into is like
Free association
Have the right that you have
One of the reasons
Libertarian types
It's often are opposed to civil rights
Type of laws
Hi because free-association just be able to do business with whoever you want
If you don't want to
Serve people of a certain race naturally you should be free to do that in the market
Playful sort that out
Of course
Free association is something that is at all meaningful to you
I don't understand how you can have a company
That was
Was pressured into
Possibly taking on a
Shooter
As a
They were sponsoring and they said no
And then you want to boycott them
For them not deciding to sponsor
Someone who killed
I don't understand how like that
Can be something
Make sure they have the right
To sponsor whoever they want
Fiat
They should
And the reason that they don't is because it makes these guys real butthole
Alex
The people who are mad at them want to force them as a business can sponsor
Somebody
There should be free association
For everybody
Well actually just for me
And then everybody else should do what I tell them to do and your business should be forced into associating with a
The guy who shot some people
So if I like him then you have to cuz that signals.
Correct interest that lets me know and you know that were part of the same
Tribes
Very strange
It's almost like it doesn't mean anything at all what they
Speaking of things that don't mean anything at all
It's time
Talk
Is Leo
He started the Church of Mesa
Fixing Zone
We have the Messiah. I forgot what episode it is but we didn't an episode we got deep on Leo zagami
And I can't recommend it enough
Excel good one of my favorite things that I have ever
Just the house music
Just starting at the house music alert Leo zagami was a rave DJ and Ezra
Currently house explosion
Explain how we got to here
Music
And it's not that bad
Leo zagami
Whaleyville is flexing its muscles it's making its big run against humanity and taking over
For every major institution we learn to trust and love
Join us waited Leo zagami Dan surprise
A war on conservative true Catholic
That came out of nowhere for me cuz Alex didn't
Tease this at all
Whoa
You didn't know they coming up we're going to have Leo zagami
Man
I warmed up
Well it's what he's big
Grape is about
Pope Francis recently putting up some new guidance about light
Yeah yeah you you only say it in Latin and certain time. Then otherwise you trying
The big change that he made was that
You have to if you're a priest and you want to do Latin Mass
You have to get
By the permission of your piss
And one of the reasons for this was
Because
It was being used its kind of a signifier
It was creating division Within
Catholic Community
Oh so the people who did Latin Mass where the Conservative Catholics in the people who didn't do that.
Them from kind of communicating with each other
Right and so this new guy.
Those put ours you need the permission of your Bishop in order to do Latin Masses
That every Bishop is required to have places that do Latin Mass
To cater to those folks
It has to be available
And
You need to have
Permission so it's not just
Being done
All over the place
Right right
So it's a very simple practical change that will have absolutely no effect on anything
Which of course means
Conservative Catholics are freaking
The f*** out of
Keep something that maybe is important to some people and I think there's an entry
Discussion probably but it seems like
When internal
Organizational Catholic thing
That I am not real
Really too interested Intel
Leo choking why they're doing it
I mean what does it mean and the Original Latin
Okay it means
Essential
Also for the exorcism
Is in itself
A form of exorcism
The
Francis has permitted
The use of their traditional Latin Mass
Yes
Yeah man
So the pups the devil
Lesbian
Demon can't hear Latin Mass
Do they
Do they know though
That at the Vatican
Where he live
Sometime
Look
Here's the deal
Leo's weird
I don't
Approved for my reading of it
Pope hasn't been
Latin Mass
Which is what
Leo Sayer
That's just not true
I do like the idea that he's selling it as it's an exorcism thing
And every church service is essentially an exorcism but only if it's in life
Yeah
I think we're in full-on magic words territory
God speaks
Italian
The guys God speaks the language of Italy in the past
When God was
Because that's where people started
I forgot so God only uses magical Latin
Just to be clear
That God started in Italy
Also Alex
Doesn't ask Leo about doing 911
Really weird
Every time Leo's on I'm waiting for that question cuz it's a hard-hitting question
It should be for Alex
Hey
Leo
You said you worked with other people's Health in Lawton
Who did 9/11
Thank you for it later you mean by that
So I said it was an inside job
And it kind of seems like you were inside so you want to you want to double-team this situation definitely
What was meant by Inside Job
Julio's
So what are the things that is really important
Here is that passports
Bear the mark of the bee
Sure until we have
Have to do coding Tulio is with make insulated community
We might not have that much time
What should we have for example ready in France in Paris so that is Kleenex throughout of course
Weed that excused they will eventually say we need to microchip you
And eventually we have 24 is related communities
They said there is no future
What's the time
If you don't know but
What's the time frame of the end
How are we going to survive
Serological Warfare the second cyberwarfare Defenders nuclear warfare
In the next nine years
So we got time here
So is point is
Is because people like him who hate vaccines
Are going to
Forge vaccine passports
The government in response to their inability to get vaccinated
Will then
Chip them
Because
Of their behavior
So they are at
Bolts for the mark of the beast
I don't know
I was trying to listen to what you're saying and I just couldn't
Stop thinking like
Leo got vaccinated
Of course he did
Are you going to get hurt
These people are all assholes
How do you know
Smartphones
Whoa
Smartphone
Smart grid
Wow sure everything well houses
Smart houses
Frigerators
Smart fridges the refrigerator will adjust the temperature for you and then you can check Twitter on it
I guess that sound smart but maybe it's not pretty smart mean something else
The Weeknd
Because all cities
Winn-Dixie
Eventually
CDs
And I've been saying this for a long time
Edema
Cool smart is actually satanic
Anything
Dady massmart
Is actually a nice service
And dependency from from Satan which ultimately he is the one behind
Our own
EStudio reality
Naturally
Of course in the Book of Revelation with you also cited
Is very important
The moment in which we have accepted the vaccine at the moment in which
We are basically at that point
So this investigation is open
Leo does believe he's fighting the literal devil
He believes that by holding the phone that he's talking to Alex on he's through the devil
Smart equals satanic
I don't know
How is he called
I don't
No it's on Skype
I think so I don't know if there's a boar
Succinct
Explanation for Alex's worldview than things that are spotted are evil 100% it is a very
Accurate
I owe man so they so the devil
Is behind our phones
How many days until chill
I like the devil
I like my phone
I mean
Straight play some apps on it it's good stuff
Play some
Play some games
Is devil behind
The devil is behind
Everything
Except that measurement
App that allows you
Need to see if Blake Shelton
That well yeah but only God can make things level.
That's true
So
We have the devil
Now I got bad news
There's another
There's two Devils
I was shocked to hear
From your research who is Satan what is Satan I want to say one
Satan and his Legion want our soul
So they want the soulless Society
After these three stages which
Describe
And it would be the materialization of Satan in cyber Satan
Daphne future inside the next
Starbucks
Increasing more and more
Dende
ISM play
Cypress
That's bad news
These this
This is this is
Liz's injected in my veins and
This dimension
But has to create a new Satan to exist in the Cyber Realm
Sure
Dumb but very dumb
I just I mean like
On some level
I can't believe
Alex doesn't like
Just go home
Kick himself over and over to my why do I do that now with people like Leo's about a f****** Steve
Pieczenik these people
The devil
Burping disrespectfully insane
Have a little decorum please
Wii U for my believing everything is the devil
Awesome
Think about public health over the last year
No it's everything's not going to be here till $20
23rd
Okay
There's a lot of stats
About
Moana
That has gone on measure
Until now
Possession
Literally possessing more and more pee
Sundae maker Grease
In the demands of 4
Exercise mat
Facing in Oklahoma
Demons demons or
True modern technology
In this book volume 666
Okay
Volume six points
Okay that's the Fahrenheit 9/11
Wrap up their interview and I
Alex goes off on his merry way
Just was
The introduction of cyber Satan into the pantheon is pretty important pretty good
Every appearance he's just got one that he can talk that sometimes he's got nothing but bad
That's not true
Interview that he's done that I have not been told you about all really
Generally will have one
That's what that's what I would say generally there's one and then desert Wasteland
Steve bats for the cycle
He's he's getting he's getting
Dreams on bass
Steve Stevens Stevens the Adam Dunn of b******* it's either gone or it's a
F****** bummer
So this 21st
Was strain
Energy was real weird and
I got a tip
From person who
I don't know if they would want me to use their name
I appreciate the
Cuz I don't watch the War Room
But
Alex showed back up
No on the War Room
Oh no the end of the world
American athletes shouldn't lose to another country at anything and now they're getting swept by Mike Nigeria
Australia and Sweden
Get woke
Dobro
But the Babylonian bee
As a
They think they know what's behind this
US Women's Soccer Team to boycott scoring until racism is defeated so clearly that's it
Clearly that's it Alex don't you think
Don't you think Alex
He's hovering
What you think about this Alex
Journalist could face up to 14 years in prison for stories embarrassing
The government
So at this point Alex's wandered up
Behind Owen
Geeking out
Behind him oh boy
Cowboy cowboy
Alright
Okay doesn't have a mic
Alright okay
We're having a little bit of fun with drug
Make a note for this because this is outrageous this is Adair special yes
Now they're saying they're going to arrest you
And put you in jail for 14 years
If journalists embarrass the government
I don't see anything
Yeah I can go home and feed him first so right
All right ladies and gentlemen
Never had it
Anything else you want to tell us
There we go that's what the crowd wants
That's what the crowd wants right
What are the cameras is now moved over to Alex he is off
On the side of the stage
Edison dark
Speaking kind of still see him
And what he's doing is he's moving around and stripping off
Button up shirt and you stripping out of it he's not wearing undershirt
Dancing around taking his shirt off
I'm on my way I'm on my way
Mama
I couldn't ask you if you want to go to dinner at the commercial break
I care I'm not going to get past turtle soup
Got a little bit last year
Right there and Alex Jones trip to you so you can only get that on the War Room ladies and gentlemen
You can only get that on the War Room
Not even on the Alex Jones Show can you get an Alex Jones striptease
Only on the War Room
I think he said drunkenly sleep in his office for a couple hours
East
Sleep in his office for a couple hours
But it sounded like you said drunken before that but it wasn't like
I'm not sure really make it out
This is this is
Just G
This is that no that's that's
The behavior of somebody
Who is
Enjoying
Behavior of someone who's super
Super concerned
About how a real high-level top scientist has just come out and told you
That everybody who's gotten the vaccine is going to have won six of their immune system and everybody's going to die
He seems like a guy who's like really
Engaged in doing the work
Really he's really taking this seriously and you got to trust him and he's right about everything at
Is it feel to be Vin
You know what else it's also the sign of a boss who has full confidence
Translate you are going to get your audience
That you have a show just as important as his
That everything you're doing is
Valuable valuable useful to the company boasts the other way it's the sign of a boss who knows
That you have any goddamn career prospects outside
Spell respect you and knows that you're
Wrapped hey buddy
Hey Owen
Say something
David B
This is unprofessional to my face on air do it I f****** barrier
I dare you to pretend that you have an interview at ESPN
H e r u
How does it
Feel that you would dissociate and think I'm your dad dad
I am a bad father
How's it feel that I'm on are clearly making fun of something in your personal life put by referring to it as your turtle
Maybe it's your partner or
Something with your roommate who's Peyton the ask how did how do you like that I'm making fun of your personal life in codon
Horchow
You know what's funny about this show on I can take it away at any moment
Hi fire David Knight
I replaced it with a baby
Just a f*** you just at like
Try and take your job seriously
Trial time
God that's embarrassing I mean I would want a quit so
Even though I know that I'm unemployable media just that moment of like
This is completely
So disrespectful I think if we've seen anything in the way that ex Infowars employee is over
I've been treated by the media
You never liked Josh Owens when he came out wrote a piece in New York Times
I think there is an over willing
People to accept
The negative behaviors
The people have been engaged in an hour
When they show some penitents
And understanding of the damage
But their behaviors cause
Is room
Society to forgive one
Promontory
Like if I were to leave now and
Going to be like look here's the deal
I think he could actually pull that off
But he couldn't be the third person to pull it off
Deep is closing in terms of people's patients for like Redemptive story
Yeah I think that there is still room
For that someone could probably
Sneakily get away with that
Anyway I think that this is
Atrocious
Hi I mean
That's why I
Doctor's appointment
Really really should have been
A weekend
It's really hard for me to not draw lines between
Alex having a Bazaar out of nowhere I'm going to leave the show for a doctor's appointment tonight
Super weird the next day it up till 3
Quote on quote researching the
GameStop prey shows back up on Owen Shaw acted weird does a striptease
Seems like something that behavior Doesn't Remind Me of anything so much
Chas myself on a manic episode
That is a thing I do
Gorgeous
Mike lindell's giving the money now so I'm sure everything will be fine as well
His doctor is giving him feel good
Do I'm sure everything's going to be worse
We will see ya and I guess maybe I will be able to figure out what the f*** happened with that lawsuit that alley
Text Bob cell.
Get well soon
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight and won't go to bed Jordans on Facebook
We are Facebook at the ocean
Please find a local charity or bail finding here
In your area to help out people doing
God's work
But out of respect for one of the gas today I am
Not Neo I'm not Leo imcx Clark and I am
And I must again
Advise you to not
Pop Arab
Stairs from China
And it is deeply
Bad
Great point
Alexandra Thurston color