Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody sit around and talk a little bit
About Alex Jones
What's up
Jordan is the family of celine's adopted children
Continues to grow as Ashley has
Adoption of a snow leopard
Can I always got to snow leopard a baby elephant
That's so good you're going to need
You're going to Sears the problem with animal drops in Tahlequah
The problem is all of Alex's animal drop related
Good stuff would be like
I killed this.
No no no message
So I'm very excited about this
Extended family that is growing
Snow leopard
Very adorable
Big cat yeah absolutely my partner and I are headed to
Scenic Oregon
We're going to head up right time to know we were thinking it's really hot here but it wasn't on fire
So we're like let's go to where it's on fire you know like like a real one you pick your
Traveling times
Interested
Yes to the West Coast
I agree we've been to the West Coast without the Northway
Pacific Northwest is a bit different along the north end more south
The West Coast
They different
Sort of Wildlife
Yeah we're going to go adventures all around the whole place we're going to go to
Are the coast we're going to go we're staying in a treehouse
Oh wow the middle of like real unplug that Hamish it like in the middle of nowhere so I'm going to win the whole time
I'm sure about how I don't have all my electronic tools
I wish I could play games
But
It's going to be a very exciting it.
Yeah if I'm thrilled for you in a little bit jealous cuz you know I like
Be in the woods
I hope you all have a great time
And unfortunately that leads us into a little bit of a admin base
Conversation
Trip of yours
Snuck up on me a little pickup
Me to time but has a certain way of being that way
Wanted to I knew that you were going to go on this trip and I wanted to like record episodes and
Advance in order to
Make sure that we
We keep the ball rolling and what have you but
The reality is between
My toe surgery and
Feeling bad
MN
Not feeling bad and then I guess what I feel like s*** again been there been
For last couple days
It's been really difficult so we're just
Going to be off
Episode
Some crazy inspiration strikes
And I record
Sing with feelings
Yes
Otherwise
Well you're gone
I'm going to be recovering and doing some admin work
Got a couple of iron
What time is it I take a Bic lighter to that
In my mind
I was thinking more of like
An iron used
To flatten your clothes and I'm heating it up with that
Cuz it's very efficient
With a crack pipe
I feel like that's better than cooking heroin in a spoon
I wasn't talking about quitting heroin I was talking about
Heating up an iron
Right
I forgot that part
Well I've got a lot of heroin
Episode to go over
And unfortunately it's not
There's not a lot
To talk about there's a couple of important themes that I think run through this but I do not have very many clips
Because
Luna Lee
This is June 3rd 2003
Go back in the past cuz Alex has been a little bit disappointing
I didn't really have much more to say I don't want it to
Just constantly talk about
Disappoint
I am covid self I don't do that every single episode
Things that I really want to learn more about
And you know if I if I have that option in front of me
Certainly
If I'm also not feeling well I would rather do that then
So I went back to this and it's just kind of
The boulevard
Check it's not great
I'm about an hour and 15 hour and 20 of this 3-hour episode
Is Alex interviewing a family
About a situation a medical situation
That makes
Almost no sense
It's has to do with
The mother getting a hepatitis test
Positive
Tested positive hepatitis Shoreham in something had to be done cuz she was giving
Birth
New Yorker she had a child
Better
Right and then it turned out it might have been a false
Appositive
The conspiracy somehow
I don't know
Most of these stuff that sounds really nefarious about the interview breaks down to
One of the
One of the reasons it's really difficult is because there's like four people on the line that Alex is starting to look for Mom the dad
Grandma and a doctorate is their aunt like you text
It's nonsense bad podcast control
I couldn't handle it
Anything that they say that even
Rises
To the level of like I don't know
About this
Is like one of them says that
The nurse said the doctor was like
We don't want your money
We just want your first born
Okay
All right guys or bring it back orphan trains to me I heard that
I thought well there's better
5% chance this is someone making an awful
Awful joke that's about 95% chance
This was misheard
I'm saying we don't want your money we want your firstborn child to be healthy
To be alive
Yeah we're focused on the health outcome
The money's not what's best for your child. We're not trying to get rich off your
Keep circling around this and Alex
Keeps pointing it out and I was
Listening to it
Does just
Nothing
That's brutal
XOXO
3 Hour episode and you got an hour and 20
Nothing
Well hurry up
So we get down to business on this year Jordan but before we do let's take a little moment
Some folks have signed up and are important
Gentleman scholar signs in San Francisco thank you so much right now if I was you walk
Nick Fuentes is better than his laugh thank you so much right now apology walk
Apparently you disgustingly said what
It does thank you
Next
Jordan
But not that one the one that makes a Beer by the river thank you so much you're not bazzi why
Next hot single rainbow dildo butt monkeys in your area thank you so much you are nopales
I just wish more people would say rainbow dildo but monkey it like just drop it in any conversation
Any conversation you can thank you
I've been finally come to Blue Ridge
Festival that you select your Nautica crap
Business
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
This honestly is not
Sponsored content
I was waiting for the next episode relax
Alright in the next technocrat is
Everybody drink Pepsi got
DMX
I reserve the right to say whatever I want about this Festival
I was looking over the other line up what do we got I haven't studied
Okay from Kansas City
Rapper
Tech Nine
Scrawled weight
Too far down
Director of Halloween movies
Limp Bizkit
Cover band how was it they were still like a unit
I thought they were all dead
No dresses like a TV director now
Sebring nobody directed an episode of House
Exactly that's all I know
He also directed that movie with Ice Cube
Where there's a young girl who played football
Are we there yet are we there yet to still not there
Bush
Bushes on their lineup Gavin Rossdale bush
He was great and Constantine that really launched his acting career
He was not great
Yeah it's Luda Ludacris pressure off his appearances
Van Luna has fallen far as he's co-headlining with bush
I don't think
You still headlining a couple love couple of rolls down
Cool
This plug may have not gone exactly as intended
You're already
Are you going
Jordan
Yes here we are
Sort of prevailing narrative that goes throughout the large
It's part of the show is about Eric Rudolph
Who do not remember him I remember the name I don't remember exactly what he did
He was the guy who was the actual bomber at the
Is it windy yeah yeah people remember
Is he was the first
Suspect
Right
Had a terrible time with that Missouri unfair
Really breathable
But
Eric Rudolph is the actual person
Fast
Ideas that were fairly similar to Alex
Hey did I do recall around this time many bombers had very similar ideas to Ally
Like this
Conversation surrounding Eric Rudolph is happening
Depressed
And
Alex is not very happy about
Because
Now they're pointing out
It's Eric Rudolph
Is somebody who has a lot of ties
Do Christian identity type group Sunday
Seem to be the
The kind of beliefs
We're motivating is
Is Bob
Yeah well you know it's good cuz we saw it we saw the real problem that it was going to be we address
Rested and we focused on Outreach efforts and education and now we don't have to
To deal with this type
Anymore right
Do you have to remember is that Eric Rudolph didn't just set off the bomb at Olympic Park
There was also multiple bombings of
Pain clinics
And
A gay bar
Fat people weigh with multiple
Yes he had committed other bombing
Things to this
Charge of everything
Those are other things that are indicative of the reason
Vicki did the things he did
And even the Olympic bomber
Mine was motivated
Well that's definitely a piece of it but it is more
Auntie abortion
Active
The targets are the
Sure if you read his confession guest
Socialist cultural mixing that goes into the Olympics I wanted to end
Embarrass them
Yep to there's a bit of that
Alex has decided that
He's innocent
And
He talks a little bit about Christian identity
This clip
And I find his awareness and non awareness of things
Possible
Tacoma existing human brain
Rudolph
I have carried all of this
Terrorism
Perhaps
Christ
Vaccination
Now I'm in a green with a parent
British Israeli
From
Babylon
Information
I want you to call
Call medieval
I wouldn't if I were you as well
First of all Eric Rudolph totally did the Atlanta Olympics bomb
People are guilty to the crime along with multiple other bombings which were inspired mostly by his office
Cuz I can do abortion
There were very strong indications that Rudolph was a follower of the Christian identity movement in touch with Affiliated militant
Groups like the army of God
This doesn't seem like a big
Stretch even if you are only judge
Judging from his own state
That said I find this fascinating
Alex simultaneously is totally aware of British is realism in
Totally lying
What it is
Admits to wake up with this in the past episode you made it to listening to an admiring David Jay Smith
Yep on the radio through his younger years which would be impossible
If he thinks that the description he just gave a British his realism is correct
It's just not
Possible
Bizarre
This is definitely an instant of Alex making a
Deconstruct the beliefs of Christian identity communities because if
She did so there be
Declaring overlap with his own blade
Desperately doesn't want to engage with the similarities between himself and someone like Eric Rudolph
Because ultimately
Eric Rudolph was bombing the Olympics and reproductive health clinics but he was also in the process pointing a finger
People like Ali
From his confession
Quote those who call themselves pro-life and who claimed that abortion is murder and that those who use Force to prevent Adorn
We're just as morally reprehensible as the abortionist
For these I have nothing to say other than that you are liars Hypocrites and cowards
There's no more fundamental Duty for a moral citizen to protect the innocent from assault
That is inherent in the values of all higher civilization
You have the right the responsibility and the duty to come
The defense of the inside when the innocent are under assault
Would you protect
Your children from the clutches of a murderer
Would you protect your neighbors
If you answered yes to both of these then you must support the use of force
I've just
Justified in attempting
Prevent the murder that is a Porsche
Very straightforward
Direct
I mean
Event they're all a bunch of Hypocrites and he's already or he's arguing that it is a moral necessity to support violin
In the service of
Opposing abortion
I suppose if you are
I mean yeah
If you are accepting that
Their logic
Is abortion is murder
And that Alex is right when he says we murdered
Millions of babies or whatever the brought the wrath of Satan the Promenade
I don't see how you can't follow that logic
Through and he's right if you do believe that and you don't do anything then you're a coward in it
Cuz it's not true I can disagree with Eric Rudolph
Alex
Difficult
Line to walk if he wants to disagree with what this guy is putting
They believe they agree in substance
And Alex's rhetoric implies
What Eric Rudolph believe
Robin Alex Cantone the
Conclusion of his own position I mean imagine Alex
He did this in his
Thanks because we were bored too many babies
Just like how yesterday I said we've aborted too many baby
Yeah
Eric Rudolph
Confession is essentially a call to Arms to the violence against
The government that he feels as illegitimate
Largely because of the fact
Abortion is legal
Another quote from
Miss confession
Quote 225 years ago our ancestors overthrew their government because they were not being represented
For purposes of Taxation
Tell me you good Patriots
The casus belli of
Taxation without representation more weighty
Then the deliberate murder of 50 million people
You lie and your lies will find you
That's a directed call out at people like Alex who you talk of extremism
How to make money but don't support the cause enough to do actual extremism
Someone like Alex doesn't have a good rebuttal to that argument
To the best thing to do is to insist that Rudolph must be a patsy
It doesn't matter that he can
Investing explained his actions in detail it's because they all turned it was a threat to Alex's self-image
Crusading
Hero of the right-wing
It's tough it's tough
Whenever terrorism happens and you are the person who's like man terrorism to really happen but I don't want
Terrible I don't want anybody get hurt
I mean obviously the only prescription is Terrorism
But I don't want anybody to go
Get hurt cuz I'm a good person
You should hurt
It's it's
It's tough to Foster the ecosystem
Create
And perpetuates events like this
Because in order to do it
You have to denounce
The actual things that you can actually denounce them
Yeah I'm have to rewrite them as fake
In order
To be like well yeah people should be
Blowing up a board we would never do that
We would never do that
The fact that this guy did that is evidence that he was probably the Fed
Right right
That's that's funny I do I just realized now that the right-wing probably does
Feel a little jealousy towards Isis
You know cuz they just get to come out and be like hey
Wheel of terrorism they don't have
How to play the game of being like terrorism is bad
Deal with it
You know they don't get to have as much fun now it's have to work twice as hard
Difficult line to walk with this stuff
With the Eric Rudolph
But even Beyond like that
Dumb game that he's trying to play he's also just like
Straight up lying
Like here is him like this is from the clip we just listen to but just the sex
Actuaries pretending to read a headline
Perhaps
How much is a do you think is the actual headline
Based on the tone of voice he's using
It sounds like all of that is from the article right but it's
Just got to just be is Terrorism tied to religious sect
Editorializing
It's part of that
Yeah why would the new why would the Washington Post be like maybe we should ban this Christian sect
You know the thing we can do
Not enshrined in the f******
Teen Constitution there is no suggestion at any point the Christian identity should be banned
And all of that is just Alex creating a more exciting story to distract
The main point of this article
Which is that Eric Rudolph did in fact have ties to Christian idem
Groups and it seems very likely that is act
Terrorism or at least
Partially inspired by his religious beliefs
There's a nice quote from Idaho State University sociology professor
Sir James Auto in this article
I would prefer to say that Rudolph is a religiously inspired terrorist because most mainstream Christian
Translate consider Christian identity to be a heresy Ajo said
Christian take on bridge of the juxtaposition of the words Christian and terrorists he added
That may give them some idea of how Muslims feel when they constantly hear the term Islamic terrorism
Especially sense
September 11th
I refuse
So Alex just has this whole life
A problem with
The idea that the
The term Christian is being associated in any way with
A potentially
Christian religiously-motivated extremist group
The good name
Of a peaceful religion
That has never
At any point in time engaged in random or raw acts of terrorism
Towards any people
Okay
So
Alex gets a little bit weird here cuz
He has to
Deal with the existence of Christian identity
Rather thing
Because it's part of the story that he
He's decided to cover and he's reading this
Washington Post article
Maybe because he thinks he's going to get to a point where it says let's ban religion
Doesn't
In doing so he ends up
Having to address the fact that
Christian identity adherents
Do
Generally believe
That white people are superior
For sure he has to be like
Why do wrong
This isn't great
European White
I mean, the army of God
Is it racist
Holyshit
Well that's weird
Yeah
I think he accidentally made a fairly cogent argument for the problem actually being people
Calling themselves
I think there is a religious
Tradition Within
Judaism
Of God's chosen people. Denote or imply to a Supremacy
And I think that that is something else they have to sort of removed from the conversation
Wendy's
These Notions are being used
As
Something to gain
Something for a community
Supremacy
It's not it's not an issue
It is an issue when it comes to
Supremacist ideology
Of the big groups that you're there are some black supremacist groups and I think that you can calls I racist
I think the supremacy part right
Muddy that water is silly
I meant
Secondly
Using this argument
Only serves
The purpose that Alex is driving towards
And that is
Make what
Supremacy okay everybody is a supremacist for their own
Group
Vines
Problem is that
People are judgmental towards
Other groups
And not themselves
Wait
That is the problem
It's a little strange position to be like white supremacy is fine because these others
Supremacist groups
Exist
I would say we could flip
This argument and be like no white supremacy is not okay because it is one of the groups that is like all these other groups also
Are not great
I don't know I would
Seems like
That would be more with
He wanted to he likes people who bleed red blood he loves everybody
Same moral argument is somebody who's like
Yeah
I just stole that guy's car
Everybody stealing
That guy stole cars
Why don't you go bother that guy
Right
F*** you I'm a car thief
And I'm better at it like
Define
Okay great
That one could argue that maybe Alex just doesn't know all that much about what these people believe
Doubtful
Yeah especially because he goes on to talk about how he hangs out on racist message
Taco Bell
Group outfits
Wow
Listen listen
What
That's like three Bob
People of John 10 bombings this is the best group out there
Very strange
Serial bomber
Say
I would say
In this
Territory for a defense drink trouble
This isn't good
What year
Comparing terrorist groups
I'm being like
Hey this one
Less
Effective worship
These look these guys are so tame some people they bomb a whole building think about the room
It's not a big deal time on
The you know places where
Virulent
Hateful groups
Commute to get together and they they
Discuss things and I got to say
The one that happen
To align with my belief system
Is probably the best of them
Works like that at the end of the day a lot of
People think they're the chosen
Microbe happens to be the best
So Alex has decided that Richard Jewell
Cgroups are still White
Supremacist
Like their white supremacist
Are even better at being white supremacist
Then other people are being
Other surprise
It seems to
Make sense attract
Alex believes that Richard Jewell was set up
What are the you was a Fall Guy
Because
He was getting
Too close to uncovering the plot by the Bureau of Alcohol Tobacco and Firearms
I don't think this is
Alex is no evidence that he provides to support his claim that Richard Jewell was blamed because he was getting too close to uncovering the eight
ATF
Conspiracy behind the bombing that's just
Trip from his imagination. Are you
Give a s***
However if you could really see Alex doing his job which
Has to do whatever he can to profit
From tragedy
Rudolfo super clear about his motivation and Salvatore to believe it that would be challenging
For him to cover
In order for this to be marketable for Alex
Lexi needs to make
It's a false flag
You can see him shamelessly do exactly that here
Rudolph was motivated by an extreme anti-abortion position
The story to be that the feds are worried about
Anti-abortion activist
So the makeup is demonized and no matter what the news ever says and no matter what he himself ever
Versailles
You can't believe that it cannot be in any way
Disqualifying of whatever my assessment of this is
Because he was probably tortured
And everybody makes up everything anyway
Yeah it's a dumb
It's really dumb
Yeah
That's frustrating
And it's frustrating again on a level of like
Man if we didn't have that f****** torture memo we wouldn't be tossing around torture is being
I'm fine all the goddamn time
Time you know like that
That's also something that when you go back and listen to that I'm like
F*** you you lying piece of s*** in at the same time I'm
Taking back to 2003 listening to
People be like
I think if you get the information
Orchard Supply
That was a conversation
Yeah like all the time
Yeah and it's like how and so if you if you hear that
Somebody like relying on that
Kind of emotion of like
They're going to torture the dude
Very easy to get overcome with that part because
People are saying around you all day
Yeah and I think Alex B uses those kind of Appeals
For his arguments that are are
If it's clunky
What does a disservice to the real conversation about how
Bad torture
I totally use it at
The prop a little bit
Yeah it's it's a real you know like normally when he
He's jangling keys
Most of the time
He's just made up the keys over here there
They're plastic and a bottom from a stolen from a child
This time he is jangling keys but that keys
F****** huge you know
That's a real goddamn set of keys
Yeah but it is also a key that doesn't go to this lockdown by solutely.
So
As far away from himself as you can
Go look at those over there don't look at the hell all my friends bomb people
Tell Alex
Bringing up
This one scene
From Fillmore road to tyranny 911
And it just got annoying at a certain point
Bring it up
Yep
Was a piece of gold because
If anything else
That particular sniffing on your phone 911 the road to tyranny
Is without any
Iopener
It's the biggest eye-opener
We've got
A90
Percent conversion
I mean wow
Iris
Hey you know that part of your film
The part that it wasn't true
That scared me so much
That fake thing that now I have discovered it all other reasoning or logic
Everything you say is fine
Well here's the thing I have
Do you know position that I feel drawn
Two things that
Are either going to change my mind
Right or I'm going to learn why it's wrong
Correct generally that's something that
Irene I don't think
I don't know how to put this
But at the beginning when we started doing this year I did not know all that much
Watch about
Like Alex's deeper beliefs and what have you
That I came in with a position of
I don't
Think he's right but if he is
I will have to adjust
A lot of what I believe
Of course
He's been wrong
Almost
Exclusively sounds fast
This is this is being listed as a giant eye opener
You know like this scene where they say that all Christians are terrorists
I feel drawn that like maybe I need to
Maybe I need to
Going now watch this documentary could be maybe I need to have my eyes open
I think I get ready to challenge myself again
Right
I think you're just describing what
Genuine curiosity
Like that idea of I am interested in this
Regardless of the outcome
Alright well yes but I'm not interested in this really
I mean I understand exactly from
I know how this propaganda works I do that when they say like
Yes the founding fathers are terrorists
I just got your nose
Yes they were at that time the British were the people are in charge
By definition
You can't not say that I understand that argument
Discussion that was probably being had in this
Bernat super curious but
There's more to it
I should apprise myself of it
Of course
Maybe I will maybe we've got that coming down the line
Maybe
So
Alex
Trying to wrestle with
The
The Eric Rudolph
And the abortion
Pain clinic bombing stuff
He's hard
And I think he doesn't really bad job
Everybody else out there on
Is the Holy Spirit
Eric Rudolph
Spiritual father is
Antecedent
Forum on his behalf
Because if anybody right now
Decent
He does
Bombing abortion clinics
Bought
The reason
They're going to use that to demonize everybody
Protesting
There isn't a number two and no
That is not why it's right
Bombing
It's in your own f****** book
Read your own f****** book for 1 second it's it's wrong
For Myriad reasons
Other than tax
Medical concerns
It seems to be the only thing
He's worried about the Optics of
Bombing abortion clinics
Leah inherent
Wrongness of the actress train
And you hear this caller
You saying we need to
Pray for Eric Rudolph
Yeah he cut him off before that caller was with able to be like I support Eric Rudolph
No no no but because the understanding of this is that he didn't do
The globalist
Globalist did all of that okay
Eric Rudolph is just an anti-abortion activist
This guy
Who's being pinned for this
Because they want to make the
Proud look
At the globalist of the 12 did hooker Bachman's and everything
Are croutons just a good
Christian man we need to pray for help
For I don't understand how you can live with the
Cognitive dissonance it requires to be like
That guy
Who did the thing that I want a person to do
Was obviously set up
Because they want to
Like the fact that I want that person
Listen to do things
And that's pin the blame of those things that I want done but did not do on my move my walk them done
Recognize that it's bad tactics and
The globalist would recognize that too and they would want to make it look like I'm using bad tactics as a follower
Christ
As we all know
Christ was like
Listen
Turn the other cheek
Because it's a great tactical move
And when you are on the other side you'll be able to come up with a left hook
That's how you do it
Boy
I don't like I never liked it when I agree with Alex about like
Conclusion and then he explains why he believes along with Moana
God dammit
You're one
Your you're
A couple levels off
Drunk
Yeah but I mean that's it that's the same reaction that they have till the 6th
Same reaction as the six like this was a bad idea
Because we didn't do it at the right
We didn't succeed so it was a bad I'm nobody who truly believe in our cause would have done this therefore it was fake
Nobody truly believes and they had the abortion
Instead they were making great progress with would blow it up because of the bad
Optical bad tactical decision there for the globalist
Dumps
So what
I just I got to say he's pushing
This
Road to tyranny
Clip this is Pacific clips
So hard
We have
It's it's
Incessant
At this point it seems like something
Completely enamored with
At this point I think it's
Good thing
Well I mean
100% evil thing but it's a good thing for him
To suddenly be putting
Everybody on the terrorist side
Even if he did do it which he did
We all know that was the idea who did it
He didn't do it
If he did do it
You know that you need to be on his side because they're
Claiming that all of us are terrorists
What does it matter if he is or isn't a terrorist they're saying we are all terrorists
So we should be on his side
Sort of
I think the argument goes more like
They were saying
They all of us were terrorists
Write in order to make it
Easier for them
To say that this guy did it
Because he fits some of the description right they were
Referring to as
As possible in
Indicators of
Membership
Open French commune
Well since you
Since you've restated it
I mean that are tied
Nothing I can say to that
Amazing how all of these like
Just
Long-term plans
These evildoers
Have have engaged in
Don't work
They never work out
It's almost like they're
Bad plan thought up by a moron
Almost
Alex
Will not stop talking
About that clip from his movie
But there's another thing that happen
Getting put in
We are going
You
Always
I love that
Happens
Totally
100% did
Exactly how I'm describing exactly how
Forget to put the thing that would have really proved my point perfectly into that fell
Did I kind of disappointed maybe cuz now we're I to go watch
Road to tyranny
I know that that clip isn't in there
I want
No it's not I was promoting that killing so hard on this episode he's really peaked my interest
What I wish that quit was in there
Like a trailer for a film that was reshot the movie
I would guess
This thing did happen it was people f****** with him as is almost always
Is the case with any
Scandalous video that he gets on the
I despise
Sometimes going back and remembering
How anti-cop
These people wear
And how
Like it boggles my mind how the cops have no idea that the people who are most likely to have
Have blue lives matter Flags
Are the people most likely to murder cop
If they come to their door on the wrong
That wild
It certainly is
Bananas God damn fast
So we you know the rest of this episode is Alex talking to this City's these folks
About to
About Vera's
Are there bad nurse
Who wanted to take her baby
And I just
I couldn't I couldn't make sense of
Like I was
I was trying to
Could not make sense of it
And I guess
Willow Lake
I've just not a you know
I'm not a hundred percent
Right now and Tuesday
Is tough for me to get another episode in 2003
I am so this is this is it
You know it bums me out about that call
What's up
If you are afraid
Of them
Saying
We don't want your money we want your firstborn child
Doesn't that
Suggest you think there was a possibility that they
They could have pulled it off
People like Alex do believe that happens all the time
That's true they wouldn't be like hey you have to get through all these
These places there
You can call somebody
The cops will show up if you they stole your baby low no I think
It's just a unique situation
Company would go after that
I believe that you have not provided over bubble to be joint argument that scare the document would have
How to get around giving birth but the family is not in the room
They're not allowed anywhere near the hospital so they're going to join
Disappear are they even are they going to replace it with a with a changeling are they going to give him a change
Evil store comes in
Stork
So what he does replaces your baby with a Vlasic pickle that's brutal
That's an evil f******
Stork
I like the idea of
Remember now to get to steal the baby
The Krampus of sorts
Should scare people
I feel a little bit better I think there's some really terrible time
Not feeling well around the same time that you're taking off
But
You know it is what it is will be back
Indeed we will
Until they
Facebook website
Twitter
Go to bed
Please find a local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people
God's work right until then
Dzx Clark
Robots
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work