Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge vype.com
You do not recognize how long that theme song is until you're sitting across the room for someone who didn't
No that was probably going to play as we were starting to show
So hate everybody here's the thing
Jordan is still on vacation
Until Monday
Who do you have an episode for Monday
And so I was at I was in a little bit of a pickle
And thankfully
Someone is in town visiting and
Is a person who
A friend of the show I would say I think that's fair
You been on before remotely over the first time
Well we've met in person on this trip someone who's
Brian stelter's new best friend
Just a recently unreliable sources
Jared Holt
Damn thanks so much she had been in contact through the years but here I am and HQ cats here
Tea2go I know that you're somebody who gets
Hangouts
Enzo like I wanted to really try and bring that energy out of you with the other theme song
Jared Holt notorious hype guy
Yeah you're like the DJ Khaled of right-wing
Spell researchers
Oh
Yeah I don't know about that but that's not the right example I feel like
He has gone from somebody who like was known for being like that the guy who yell on tracks to the guy who does not perform
Oral sex on women
I feel like his whole reputation changed in that
And that
Anyway we're off traffic
It is it is
Somewhat
It's it's always a
A little bit challenging to to figure out exactly what the show is without
One half of that you know whatever
Whenever I have a conversation with somebody else it's going to like
What word what would we do but I think it was going to be a little bit different since I think you and I have
Fairly similar mentalities at least similar
Worlds of Fun
Cuz you know we both look at a lot of the same kind of
Right-wing media landscape and do a lot of criticism about it
Sands
You know I think I think that that that
Provide a lot of interesting that insight
Yeah I hope so I mean you and I have
Kind of a similar approach where
We're fairly Clinic
Call about it
Where
I don't know it like it is very easy to get
Like upset or frustrated with this kind of stuff and
You and I both share
The gift
And curse of being completely dead inside
Volta consume this in and process it and hopefully help it makes sense.
I don't like that you put it that way but you're probably right I think there's a
Pretend
Maybe I'm not maybe this isn't totally accurate but I like to pretend that it's like academic detached
Like I can be pissed off at these things that RBM listen
What I'm hearing
But that's not going to help
My ability to convey the information
As I can be attached that from
The work
Or whatever
Yeah it it helps to think that your
Trying to do something about it
It does it does the bee that does make it
Less frustrating
So what I wanted to do
We should tell folks
A little bit
Pre-pandemic
Before covid ever came to Via word we knew about
You and I had gone back and forth a little bit on Twitter
And we were talking about
The phenomenon that we were noticing that was
Alex
Infowars we're becoming buddy-buddy with Nick Fuentes
And how bizarre that was
We had wanted to
Get together and have a little conversation about
How are feelings about that
Then
A worldwide pandemic happen
Kansas it kind of knocked those
Plans off track
I bet it looked for a little bit like
Their friendship or
There there's a relationship wasn't going anywhere
But now
It blossomed again
Yeah I mean Nick is
Hosting some of his videos on the Infowars site
Yeah
We consider that a pretty
Astounding develop
Yo Alex and Nick or both
Appearing at the same rallies working together for stop this teacher
And I mean they were together I mean they really
Grown closer together and it's
It's interesting we were talking before we started recording it's not really a perfect match
Like the whole creeper white nationalist stuff I mean certainly
Alex has broadcast elements of that movement or rhetoric on his shoulder throughout the years and
Various capacities but
Styling
Strategy-wise it's
Is chi like two different
Extremist world's coming together
It's really interesting to see
Kind of where that is machine and where it's not
I think
Interesting Lee I think strategy
You know like that is that end of things I think is actually fairly compatible
Because it is
Kind of
Attention-grabbing base
Dodge Stratus
Thinking alike at least in terms of on the ground and all of his followers will go and like disrupt
Turning Point
Event
And it would get a lot of attention and
Alex would go bullhorn people
And that gets him tons of attention to
But I think
I think what you mean is more like strategy behind like social
Policy
Google what their goals would be
Yeah I know so just kind of how they see the vehicle into influence and power somebody like next 20
Yeah just
White nationalist
Unless he's getting criticism that he's just kidding
Comedian
Complete coward by the way
Way more respect if you just own it but like
I'm not saying it's a lot of respect putting at least
A smidge maybe a very cynical way of loathsome respect
Yeah I guess that's the way to put it
But nixies his
Strategy as you know they do these disruptive events they go to Turning Point USA conferences
Are there a c-pack a few weeks ago as we're recording America on canceled
How did act like Dixon like
They get attention there's a ton of press it all the things they go to
And
Their hope is to kind of siphon off enough of
The energy that's going on with those
Cribs
To become
Type of
Stakeholder in
The broader scene
Dad demands
You don't if not
Respect at least some sort of
Like catering or compromise
Where is Alex I
I don't know that he's really
Scene
His goal as like
Mainlining
Into the GOP or like he hasn't
Particularly targeted young people the way that Nick has and it would like to
Yeah I mean I'm sure he'd love
Too but I might could have seen
So much
Coherent strategy
I know that's truth I've always thought of is like
Nick and Alex are very different in as much as I think that Nick has a political project he's working on
And Alex's just corner
You know like he has at like there's an ideology behind Alex and like there's but there's beliefs that he has and there's things that he would like to see
Put in place in terms of
Do you know let me eat some of it. Does overlap with Nick like immigrants sentiment certainly they both share
But Alex definitely
He doesn't have
The the same like a desire to
Really augment the GOP
He wants Alex wants the GOP to be weirder like him
Where has Nick wants to gain sort of access to the means of power
Yeah because
Nick
Unfortunately have
The experience of being one of the first people to lie
Like really critic
Kaepernick
Check in
Reporting for rightwingwatch
It's time
And
All he's wanted
The whole time
It's just
To command some kind of respect in the Republic
Looking party because he
What's this young guy based
Around here in Chicago
Don't rub it in went to school was anti-trump then was pro-trump then God dislike
Shity little gig at right side broadcasting network before it was anything
Think I can from that being like
For saying something along the lines of
Like I wasn't CNN anchor should be hanged
You know and
Just got bitter about
Got it you know and well and it he's
You know what his view he's doing all this stuff to support the
Did Trump cause it away that
Is truer to the Trump
Cosden
A place like Fox News my Shirley
And believes that he is entitled to some kind of throne
You know Tippy some kind of intellect
I think he's really bitter towards Charlie Kirk
Because Charlie Kirk is a
Bumbling Dofus should be Charlie Kirk you know
Yeah I think
I think on some level if you take away like how a toxic of people they are
I get that
Nick is better at this
Charlie Kirk
But I think that he's like I think that the problem
With that entitlement is is not understanding what the requirements of the giga
The fact that Charlie Kirk easy bumbling doofus is the reason he fits into that hole
The Pact
Nick has a
A sense of himself and feels entitled means he does not qualify for that role now
Because he would end up f****** up the game
You'd end up going off script you would end up
Advocating for some position that the
The people who are bankrolling everything don't want him to and then
Well
This is a problem
Yeah that's that's how it goes and not to mention that
Around
Geez I don't know 2016 2017 2018 and
For Fox sake the rest of the year
He's been toying with
You know what was
Call the alt right at that time
Mingling very close with
Some really Grizzly like white supremacist so Yad
Nowak away
Themes of Holocaust denial rambling on about anti
Jewish conspiracy theories
And it doesn't matter what he does or what he changes at this point
He has done enough damage to himself already that he is like never going to be the true
Charlie Kirk unless
You know
There is some sort of Insurgency type movement
Within
The younger GOP base
Yeah yeah and I think you can see that that is what he would like to incite
Yeah
Almost out of self-preservation interesting Lionel do you put it that way it almost seems like well
This is the only shot I have it relevance is to
Cement
Extremism
But I can ride the wave of
Yeah and
You know Nick wants to write it to power Alex wants to ride it to sell Superman
Male vitality
Keep himself afloat maybe younger and Alex's career he had asked
Aspirations
I bought
I don't even know if they were
As explicit as
Azadi
Nexar
Yeah yeah I would I would say so from looking at other periods and Alex's career I think
Enemies closer but certainly not to the to the degree that
But Nick is at
Like what is e22 now like
Now it's like he has he has a very sharp Focus
Young age
I'm your you're bringing up
Like I school did you ever have you watched his videos from high school
A handful here and that just enough to like kind of get the gist of what I was reporting out at the time just to be like
F*** is this
Because
Even
Years ago I mean it's probably
Three or four years ago
At this point
When I first kind of caught wind of Nick and
I was watching his videos I was like
This guy is Young
This guy is
Forbetterforworse
Sharp
Extremely well in like
Depending on what this guy dies it could be very potent
And I think
For the side effects of that potent
Yeah you're getting elected officials like Paul
Cosar in Arizona
Michelle Malkin very prominent
Calling this for decades
Throwing their weight behind
Because they see him is like the
The next generation of what
They do
Yeah
And somebody who has like the ability to
Be afraid
Of of what they do you know like he has the
The ability to enter hostile spaces
And Come Away with at least some modicum of
Like wow
That didn't destroy me
Argue with people who disagree with him
He's very slick
He is
I got the exact same sense from him the first time I came across him as well
.
Friend of mine
Was really into like those online debate
Unlike those that is what I want to just yell at each other and
Welcome to the political debate we've gathered
8 people
Each other room have an undergrad degree
Isn't there like alright we go now to base tonight
And then face 934 gets on there and it's just like
I hate gay people and then I was like that's terrible and that's the debate
It's 2 minutes like the rest of you
I would watch some of these and I believe this friend of mine was really into destiny
And so I watched his debate with Nicolette ass
And I that was I think where he first came into my scope of awareness in
I thought like this guy is
F*** it dangerous
He is really good at making bad points
And he's really young
To show his potential shelf life
Is a long long time
Things have gotten much harder for him lately
I don't know what f****** did it right but
You know
What was left of
His access to social media platforms finally pulled the trigger and it was amazing it took that long
Yeah it's
You could have verified account on Twitter until like it's like 60 weeks ago
And would speak like very explicitly Southern Poverty Law Center put out a report that
Took a big look at sort of
The problems with Twitter and how it relates to extremism
And inquire that
Report they brought up
What does an
They pulled this quote that I think
Like Illustrated sorta what
Was interesting here really well where Nick was like
Oh yeah you know I
I got banned from YouTube or I get banned from dlive or whatever and then I just tweet the link and then everybody goes and follows me on the neck
I'd like that was kind of his
Last really effective Mega
And now he's on telegram I guess but I am still active
About how much he hates Telugu
And like he's not he
We probably are terrible
Communication medium
But it's one way
Right yeah
So it's like he
Send a message
And it's not like his
Followers really like
It's not like Twitter where they getting their replies and they just like
People fight with each other that there's no endorphin rush
It's just yeah it's one way I guess there's like you count on it
If you opened up if you open up that telegram Channel where people who comments on it it would just be like
Like insanity I'm his phone would blow up
I saw that he's on Rumble
Like there's that video platform where people can just post s***
What are the things that I thought was really interesting as looking at
How unattractive that is
Yeah Rumble
Donald's
Junior's on Rumble that's where the flagship I think Dinesh D'Souza
Other great philosophical mind sure
Use Rumble
Sam heughan on people used Rumble for a while
I don't know if that's as prominent anymore but
Grievously
Dallas traffic previously by only interaction with it was
When Owen Shroyer did that
Caravan along the east coast
Verstappen the steel
I bet the person who was along with him was only posted
Thnks FR trembles as the only time I've been there
I've no real sense of the site they
I went
2 G preparing this episode I went to Nick's Channel
Very very low counts
And if I were him I would actually see Infowars as one of the more viable Outlets
That has actual people
Around and that kind of scares the s*** out of
The rumble and seeing the good view count
I would be like well at least he has his own thing off Alex's
Space yeah but it like on Alex's platform I was super skeptical of it when
And he watched it
But some of the videos on there
Pulling in hundreds of thousands of views I don't know
I haven't looked at
The buchanans fornix videos on there
You know occasionally you get a viral Banger on
Don Alex
It's not it's not super common if the numbers aren't like what they used to be on on like a YouTube or whatever
But it's still it's still more than
Then like
It's more than nothing
Nick's views art
Huge but they're better than on
Like let's say a rumble type platform
Which
Would you would be something that you would take into consideration if you're looking at a market
And one of the things that you were saying you were skeptical when Alex launched that
I was skeptical
When Nick came around
Because I thought there was no way that Alex was going to let him be explicit
And I was wrong
What Nick got into Infowars was sort of threw they like
At the time
Harrison Smith was having him on
Owen and him might hit it off pretty well yeah it's like he almost came in through like
The trapdoor
Bourse
And then Alex was like look at this picture
I always remember like when I was younger I was told that even if you didn't like
Graduate from high school even if you never took the SAT or act
If you went to to summer school classes at the University of Missouri you be automatically enrolled then
Next semester as a student
And that's kind of what naked with Infowars
Yeah
I remember to like the
The first like real
Indication that I had that something was like
Trouble
Was the c-pack from last year I believe
When Alex went
And
Got too drunk
And fell asleep before his speech
And then Nick was kind of just taking over the room
And like you could see
Becky had a farm or
Potent
Sway over
The audience then b y mean Alex was
Sleep
But the rest of the people there didn't have any kind of connection
That was close to 2 what Nick was bringing
Those those a little bit bad Q he took over
Alex's own is that
More or less
Yeah and I
That was going to kind of happen anyway I've gone to seapac several years I haven't gone since the pandemic
But that z-pack
I
Did go to I did not go to the Infowars event because of years ago right as two years yet
I didn't go to the Infowars event because at that point
I mean I'm a known enough quantity to this
These people that
It's almost nope I can't do reporting if I go there because as soon as I show up I just get like swarmed
And it
Yeah you become the story
Get out of my job
Yeah
I tend to just skip it or as like watching it or whatever but
C-pack generally as an event like
Certainly there's some donors that are around
Some older activist Xeno passionate adults
But
It's in it's like this for almost
Une major-conference ravent in d.c.
The pack the numbers with college
Like
What happens on the stage
Is for the cameras
And there's media it's like a media circus and then there's also like
The underbelly of all these conferences is
Bringing in young college kids and trying to rear up
The next generation of the conservative movement is the conservative movement
Has been so shity the last
Couple decades frankly at pulling in younger
Generations to their cause
Because Nick
The way he Styles himself being young personally and also
You know borrowing rhetoric and and stylings from
You're popular
Twitch streamers or memes and jokes stuff like that
Is resonates with the younger audience sure and I think
You know Pat an event like c-pack there's probably more people
Numbers-wise
In a crowd that
Could be pulled to somebody like Fuentes then
You know I don't know how many
DieHard Infowars listeners are just roaming around c-pack infect was a time when they go to see packets just to go be a thorn in the side
Until they get asked to leave
Yeah yeah yeah I guess that
That makes sense
I mean I think the
Someone like Alex probably has a difficult time
Connecting with
So you've because these don't care about
The Red Scare
There's a little bit of you're an old man
And I think that even like a lot of the insults
That we see thrown around
By Nick
Reply to Alex
That's another thing that I think is really funny about this incompatibility is that
On its face
These two dudes
Are like
Most of
What makes Nick brand work
Is opposition to what Alex stands for
Which is like Boomer 1776 taking America back Revolution
Nick on his own child care what color you are
Sonic show he he talks about people that
Use that kind of rhetoric
I mean I won't say what he calls them
He speaks very lowly offset
Yeah and then he goes on info or isn't it he's almost just like
Almost feel like you can see it in his face sometimes he's like
He knows that key kind of maybe
For his career should be doing this but like
Isn't
Incredibly down either
You just took happy that have access to large
Which audience to do
But it's like this is beautiful got to do it
You just got to do it there's a crowd there
You know just whatever
Yeah you get that sense of just like
Yeah I'm checking this off the list I'm just doing this
And the other thing too on this thing compatibility note
Is
We were talking earlier about
Turning Point
Feud with with Nick
And one of the big things that they used as a as a wedge
In those whenever they would disrupt the Turning Point events was Israel
Yep they would bring up Israel and it would be like a why won't you denounce
You know
This exact strategy
Could be quite effectively used against.
Yeah
I don't understand
Somebody like Alex
Could walk
What
Nick
And his fan base
Would have done
Act like exploiting Turning Point USA and not realize like well
Yeah like that's like one of the few territories Alex
Can't be a little hesitant to go I hate
There once or twice
But like you know generally
Softwalk
Very much
Very much so to the point where I actually don't fully know what is full position
I think that is probably on purpose
Keep it in figures enough that
Folks in the audience that
You know believe
In all kinds of anti-Semitic
Conspiracy theories don't
Drop it
Not specific enough that he gets in trouble
The other part of the audience that
You know it is supportive
The state of Israel
Yeah
I I think I think that that is probably a strategic
Move on his part
And probably wise for his his brand
But it's also the exact thing that someone like Nick would would be like
No
Have a position
Why won't you have a but that's basically what he was yelling at Charlie Kirk but all those events and I just feel like Alex should know that
Might be,
Down the road
From within your own organization now
Yeah I mean Boosie with
Nick not being on these platforms and
Losing access
Send
You'll be in a position where he has the
Potential to
Start circling the drain quite a bit
We'll see if Alex can
How long he can hold on
I am
Pretty curious
You know cuz
There's
Almost two ways it could go right
On one hand Alex is so cynical and
You know
It's kind of half
Consciously doing his show at the
This point that
Just like yeah whatever we're getting the numbers in this is about censorship this isn't about what anybody
Perfectly sane
And then there's
The other part where he's just like oh maybe
Maybe we can make host the videos but he doesn't
I come on the show anymore that sort of
Good thing it's it'll be interesting to see where those chips
Well I feel I feel like it's no matter what
Going to be bad
I don't feel like you can have these influences in the same like
Pot
Turn on a little bit of heat
Not turn into
Does utter chaos but
But we'll see I'm going to keep track of it and
I wanted to do was
I wanted to just
Discuss a little video that of Nick Fuentes is that he put on
Infowars something now Alex has to deal with
I
In preparation for this episode I wanted to go and watch some of his
Knicks
Platform
Work
And I was shocked how bad it is
Not even like a fence if I could have some of that stuff but it's just also
Bad
It's also just really doesn't seem like he's trying all that hard
Yet he's really gotten in his own head lately
And my I feel like half the show he's just he just talks about
He's almost pulling a Laura Loomer every time she opens her mouth she's like
I'm so persecuted is so terrible blah blah blah blah it just goes on and on and
For like 20 minutes and then at the end is like
Let's check the Super Chat I opposed text censorship
That's important look at a Google it and
Dia the one I watched one and
He was
Good-looking 5 minute rant
About how he wants to be a martyr but like not like Jesus he doesn't want to get crucified
He wants to cuz crucifixion would suck
You find being a martyr like he's on a no-fly list
But even if he was crucified he probably go to heaven so that would be great
I like
I don't know what this this is
Listen to Alex Jones all the time like I didn't I thought that was
Kind of
Uncompelling
Broadcasting
And I was this a******
Yeah
Yeah let's listen some clips alright this is a speech this is from a speech that Nick gave
It is on Infowars now
Is hosted on there
Is about opposition to feminism
Classic
Popular political position
Sure
Anti-feminism is a galvanizing
Force within some of the some of the Proto trumpian communities
The definitely
Fueled a lot of the anti sjw
Kind of outrage
I think that there's a difference between what you might call
Classical
Anti-feminist ideas and what Nick is bring to the table
And I will see that
Here we go we're going to
Give it a start
Now they call me sexy
That one is just
Portneuf Library
And it's almost half
Right wing
Women life
For example
You know Alex
Large
So I think this is one of the issues with
With dealing with like someone his age and
Baby
Humor maturity level and the
Trying to mix the issues that he's trying to cover with
She's ugly
Yeah it is seems almost explicitly aimed at like 14 year old boy
Who are angry
Yeah and that's like particularly what is concerning to me about Fuentes as he goes through the years is
He aims
Young
Why don't like a Crowder type like he's clearly
Somebody who is like I know
Once you reach a certain age
You're probably not going to be interested in this b*******
It's
He's like
Part
Stand-up comic
Even though as I try to imagine that set in like literally any Comedy Club names like
Alex Clark right in the audience
Who who the f***
I think it's in Shinto right-wing stuff and even I had to look up who she was
That she doesn't Instagram show for tpusa who who cares
That's what I studied about this is like imagining it as a stand-up said it's like
Also imagining it as like a serious political thing is also like
Where were you doing
Yeah
I got into a fight with this commentator for Turning Point USA
This is the Cornerstone of these this lecture that I'm going to get it's absurd
In both space
Yeah it's just
I don't know I just don't get it
Really
I mean I get it I get
What the point
But
The way he's going about it it's
Eats
It kind of makes me sick
A little bit to think
Like a mansion if you and I were putting out the show but
We are putting on the like hello it's
What's the meme like
How do you my fellow kids or whatever oh you have Steve Buscemi
Meme yeah yeah we open up the podcast and I'm just like
Epic dabbed and that's so f****** sick yeah Alex Jones he looks like he's got a
Is it for a head
It's it would be something worth taking seriously
There's some real political action to back it up
We have to take it serious about the Trap and that's the problem
And I think the understanding that trap is it's important to recognize that
You have this
ThinkPad stand up
Political thing
That is absurd but it also veers into that he's complaining about Alex Clark
And this is one of his complaints
But he brings up almost immediately upon bringing her up
Can I see these pictures
You ever see him
Sit there we go
You have this
Joke that's not a joke
Yeah exactly
And it's
It's kind of clever because
When throughout the years people like myself
Thor
Places like
Southern Poverty Law Center
Anti-extremism people
Have criticized Nick
He's kind of hidden under the it's an edgy joke it's a stand-up comedy you note when
20 years ago you go to a comedy club and hear this but
Don't think Nick is even old enough to know if that
That's true or not that's just like something some
One told him one time
Yeah he might just say Lenny Bruce and then never know who he was
The thing is like let's if you want take it from like the perspective of a joke
Like the joke here is
That Nick thinks it's gross that someone who's not black would be in a Jacuzzi with a black
I don't know what the joke is
Yeah it's not
Choke
It's just
Hate I guess the joke is
Like the only possible joke is him parroting being racist
For the sake of being
Anti-rape
And that's clearly not what he's doing
Damn this podcast is taking a turnitin thing could be Nick Fuentes Secret
Text Ashley
Inside job I remember I had a friend when I was younger who was pretty convinced
That Colter was a performance artist
I'm like all of it was an elaborate parody of right-wing
Stop and
I thought that was fascinating back when I used to smoke a lot of weed and
Damn bro I think they'd say if I were younger maybe someone would make that argument about Nick likes equally this is all parrot
Do you like no it's not it's just
Poorly thought-out
Bigotry that's being masked by like
A very thin sheet
Yeah
Very thin
I don't know how it gets
It's like a queen.
Right through it
I'm so in this next leap year
Begins to lay out with his problem with feminism isn't it relates back to
Clark
Clark a little bit but it actually doesn't
It relates to a friend of Alex Clark
Which is really weird
When your suprabha with famine
And don't say things like
Example
You know the first second every wave leading up to the
The reason they called me at Zach sister a woman-hater like Robert
I actually believed in real traditional value
It'll tell you what I mean by that
IC pachter against
And if you're Christian you have to be against
It really is your human being
If you see what they do
Go in there
This is Barbara
Andover it's Deepak they're opposed
I think that's a very standard
Abortion is kind of
Starting the story
Middle
Unplanned
So now here is where he gets into his problem
It's the way you have an opposition to abortion
That's starting the problem in the middle
That's like you have a problem
That you think is the problem and it's abortion but there's actually a problem over here beforehand
Yeah I mean
Beneath all the way
Weird jokes that aren't jokes in like
Almost
The openers are almost like
Stand-up comedy Reggie twitch streamers
Rhetoric
Knicks
Whole rhetorical strategy and
Yahweh
Extremes do this all the time
Used to present themselves as like
The trooper
You've heard this your
You're not in your head
But let me tell you
This is a stop
It does not fix the prop
In my head
Dissolution that's his whole
That is his whole purse
Presentation is the truer conservative because
That's what I was saying
He believes he deserves
Play some somebody like Charlie Kirk because
As he thinks he is a truer
Iteration
Trump
Which
As somebody who didn't
Like Trump too much I
Fight him on that you can take that mantle if you want to go for it I won't correct
Dubai
Yeah it's
It's interesting
Because this is what he's been doing for years
Yeah but the rhetorical strategy that you're talking about is definitely there
And I think the other thing that he's doing is
He's taking this thing that everybody in the room agrees on
And that is that we're against
Because obviously can hear from their response this is a
Anti-choice crap
So he's taking that agreement
And then he's twisting it into
Well
If you agree with this you actually also agree with this other thing that you probably actually
Don't and there's not really
Connective tissue to get you there logically
And this is where
Alex Clark's friend comes into play
There's apparently Alex Clarke was friends with somebody who decided not to get an abortion
And this makes
Snik mad
Somehow
You know there was a friend of Alice
We out a little bit
Twitter earlier this
And she went out on Twitter she announced
Hey everybody I'm not aborting my baby
I know everybody was nice
Wow Queen brazier
I mean all the dry percent is 2
Really
Good enough
And let's think about this
Woman wallpaper
Why do women having
Why does that happen
Why do abortion
They're having babies they do
You're having sex
Derek
And there's a word for that there's a word for that
Call Dad on cell
That's without
This is dumb
Yeah this is
Realtor
Taking the opposition to abortion and that turned it into like
Opposed to people having sex
That's why unplanned pregnancies happen
We'll just be like well
Are there other things that can stop unplanned pregnancies like maybe universal access to reproductive Health Care
Ida stigmatization
By way of a reproductive education
These biscuits
Clearly a track record that has shown that this does drastically reduce
Unwanted pregnancies
I'm so why do we have to just have everyone stop talking
Yeah and
This seems like a pretty hard sell to room a teenage boy
Just say that
Remembering myself as teenage boy and how
The only thing I thought about was
I wonder if and when I will have sex
It was on my mind
From time to time I grew up in a bit of a Christian
I should tell you that I did get a promise ring and there was a I'm going to save myself for marriage
Thing in my in my church I grew up in Arkansas but I didn't go that far
I wish that I had had the restraint cuz it was a bad. Of time
I feel a little bears looking back
But
Found it really interesting listening to stuff like this cuz there's an anger behind Whitney
Naked saying
And there's an anger to that women shouldn't have sex before marriage
Where is
As much as I regret and I get kind of
Cringey feelings about myself
Looking back at my
Past
I don't think there was anger
About premarital sex
I think it was a choice
That I felt I was making
And I
Didn't really care that much
About what other people were doing
Except
My friends in the church Community if they had already made the same decision as I had
Yeah cuz the
The premise of a promise ring is kind of a personal one it is
The person that I end up marrying I believe deserves to
Have Mecum
Destin Conrad
Committed to each other or whatever is what Nick does is like
He's essentially just like
A woman must be clean for
It's like
It's one thing for people to be like oh I want to do this for my partner who do whatever
What's another thing to be like
You owe me
Like that
Is a little fat
Yeah I think also just like a even just
Like ballooning out a little bit umbrella looking at it
The preoccupation with
With
Virginity your Purity or any of that stuff is a little bit unhealthy no matter what but
The hostility in the anger
Really just
Bums me out
Especially when there's just like is it if your problem is allegedly abortion
And your solution to it is
You know get rid of things
That lead to
Premier are unplanned pregnancies
Other strategies
You do not have to go with
People can't have sex
And it alternate Leaf you zoom out just a little bit
What Nick is doing is like
Some friend of Alex Clark was probably like f*** you Nick
Rightfully so
Probably disagree with her on everything else with her
He looked at that and said
Like oh she said
F*** you Nick
Krause she had sex
You know I
I really just don't want to borrow the language he's using
It's
Pretty
Gross yeah
And I think there's also even like if we take if we take all of this
The oldest content out of it
You still have somebody who sees himself as like a political leader
Complaining about a fight he had on Twitter
Bright
And that is sad in his gripe
They had sex right
And then something happened that was unexpected
And they made the decision I would want them to make
And I'm still mad about it yeah
Because it's still not good enough because
They have
Okay sure
Whatever
Nick also appears to be against contraception
As he lays out a little bit
Ensure
The Bible and Christian
About sexuality
That's young man and young women are
OSHA get married and then they're only supposed
Do it with each
What the Bible tells us about Mary
Hookup culture
All of that
Unplanned pregnancy
Where are the real
The story
Conservative values with
Theocratic Christian
Societal organization
Basically and even then
I would encourage him to brush up on his Bible a little bit. There are plenty of people in God's good graces
Got around Sherwood say
Jesus hung out with some folks who might have been looked down upon by someone like Nick spoke out in there.
Yeah
It's at you but you but yeah I like you're saying
The argument here is that the GOP should
Be the vehicle that
Yes
Which
Christian right
Folks would probably agree with what is something that our government is set up at least
On paper in theory
Not be
White Hope
Fingers crossed I mean the rate we're going now
I think that there's a difference between like wanting your religious beliefs to be respected
And wanting them to be Doctrine
To everyone
And expected of everyone to follow
And that is clearly what Nick is advocating for
Snake is clearly advocating for
A society where
He's particular religious beliefs are codified into what everyone has to follow
And that's not
Going to be great
Yeah I think for Nick and also for like people in the white nationalism that came to Generations before him
They saw the church
Even if the church isn't in total agreement with their agenda is kind of the fastest way to
Erase
Or or to get
Push the country away from the
Ideal of
A multicultural
Percy
By instituting some sort of
Theocratic
Control
You know
Mandating the laws of the government based on a
Religious philosophy
You can get more people to not along and also have
Like an esoteric Thing 2
It's not
You are not
Accountable you are just following the rules in the good book
Right
Yeah yeah
Yeah if you have like sort of a thing you can fall back on
That's that's like wow this is fun Quest
I want to be totally clear nothing against religion but I'm not really just what but whatever
You know. Helps
You do
Did you see this as a vehicle
And you know I think for anybody who's listening to the show that's like
Play person faith is something to be conscious of
The people are out there that would seek to exploit
You are Faith
To turn you towards something
Really nasty
Sure yeah I mean like I think you see that you see that a bit nuts
That's one of the things that makes some of these conversations a little bit murky
Is
You know
Trying to
Discuss that without
Coming off as
Anti-religious or anti
Any kind of safe
I think it's very possible to walk that line but people sometimes stupid jobs
And I think it doesn't help that a lot of people have negative
Your past experiences of their own that they bring to the table with
Religious communities in
You know that that's just a challenge we all have
It's hard to talk about it in a way that's not
Is my my tan for my promise ring showing my
My permanent
What is it's funny cuz it's on
Houston
Fingers how many promises did you make
I made a lot of promises
They've all been broken
I had a pinky ring and pinky promise ring
Oh I was going to have a gang
The pinky and the boys
Need to just jump out the window here
V
There was another thing that I was thinking about here to oh yeah that that's what it was
There's there's another aspect of this religious stuff that Nick is bring to the table I think
Really highlights
A distinct difference between him
And people like Alex
And traditional
Assertive anti-communist types
And that is a religious zealotry and fervor on both sides
But Nick is a
Catholic fascist
Yeah Mary specifically
And Alex is
More of a Protestant type
And I think that Alex doesn't understand
Yeah I don't know that he fully understands how those two
You been historically speaking perhaps
Yeah the extreme ends
Of
Catholic
The extremism but cyan
More
I don't even know what you would call him
Let me just
Christian identity kind of his is the
Vein you put Alex in
Yeah
No I think that's right
Because he
He sees it as something that he is
And I don't
Often hear Alex articulate like a really
Coherent like
Biblical
Argument
Stop it's like sometimes he talks about like
Space
In terms of God
He's weird
Yeah I think most things that he brings up about the Bible are like
Sort of out of context
Quotes about like Jesus ain't get a sword and stuff
The clown I'm not sure
I sure would have grasped you have here
Traditions of his community in his world in terms of religion are very different
In terms of Doctrine in terms of goals
Then text and I don't think that he realizes
It went they say
God or whatever they may have very distinct
The views
In their mind
I think that's another thing that could lead to a problem
Between the two of them
Yeah because Alex will undoubtedly
Play Fela.
Beat a stiff neck
Decides
Wants to apply it
Yep
Or
Alex
I mean potentially I guess could get uncomfortable by it
I don't know to do things make him uncomfortable
I don't know I mean like
Intel Nic does something that like his lawyer thinks he needs to do something about
I don't know if Alex would be uncomfortable
I don't think he knows
Like honestly I don't I don't think he knows
What's goes on his own site
I can't imagine that cuz I just
He has to either not care or not
Yeah and it is hard to know which
Which one of those days
Things like this would be very difficult to stand behind
Do you have Nick
Saying that
Abortion is wrong
He's got the room on his side
And therefore
Campfire
Cuz that's bad
The only f****** marriage
But also
This extends much
Further
It's not just about sexual
Morality is not just about the family but it's also about the
Opposition
Site
Who's having the babies
Does anybody know
It's the women that are having the baby
Yeah that's how that works
When I say
I don't think women should be in the
Frankly I don't know if they should be
And people say that
How could you
What is asinine
50s
The 1950s
Soon
Just to be clear for the
To the listeners at home we can talk in between some of these Cliffs but this is all from the same speech he has gone from
I got no
Twitter argument with Alex Clark
About her friend who did the thing that I would want her to do
Friend
And then kept
But you shouldn't have gotten pregnant the first place
Because she shouldn't have been having sex
By the way even with contraception spoke those things
Women shouldn't vote
This is spiraled out into this speech
Cutting out parts that make it make sense
This is the train of thought that he's on
Is these are the things that lead to abortion
Which it you need to be against if you work
Truly against abortion
If you're truly against abortion you need to be against f******
You need women not to be in the office. The workplace
Probably shouldn't vote
Okay
We need to return to the 1950s
Are the era in time
It was famously good to ever
Wonderful time for everyone
Everyone
DM
Thing is
If you if you look at that train of thought
What you really start to recognize is how much
The
Abortion has nothing to do with what he actually is advocating he's hiding behind that mantle because
Is it something that
Is people will obviously get on board with
Trying to make the connection between
Women voting
Having the right to vote
And being opposed to abortion
It's a long walk
But he gets there in like
I mean what is it 60 Seconds
Give or take
F****** an Olympian athlete
Spell Irene in a in a
Favorable ruling
This makes sense outside of his own America uncanceled rally
I don't know I don't know how well it would work but
This is this is what he's doing he's Trojan horsing
These other viewpoints
On to the the artist I would I would say that they're probably inclined to
Be angry and hostile towards women
To begin with
But maybe they wouldn't have gone to a rally that was a women shouldn't vote rally
But they might show up for a pro-life
Rally
Yeah I think I think that's definitely fair and it's
I mean like I said it's a whole strategy
Oh here's something you agree with
Let me give you the real s***
Like
And
With younger audiences and
Apparently at the favor of
At least one member
Congress
Like resume
Which is
Kind of terrifying because it's we just sit here and listen to it
F****** ridiculous dude it's
It doesn't make any
No and I think we're of the age where we lived through the Tea Party happen
Right I think that
In a lot of ways people didn't take that nearly seriously enough
And I think
You know you saw that
The effect it had on
On political discourse on
Normalizing ideas that were
Prior like I don't know about this
If we're not careful
This
Could be another thing that goes that direction
Like you're bringing up like the Michelle Malkin support the gosar
Support
It's
Not nothing
Yeah and Blake
These brigades from Nick
His fans call themselves The groypers and staff
The captain able to like
Kind of
Give tpusa like
Enough pressure for them to bend
Which
Is a mistake to f****** begin with because once you put that
You know you cannot put
The toothpaste back in the tube after that
It's like
A boy
You
You given to the bully you play the game and
Guess who's back tomorrow
How's the volume
Yeah and that's what I feel about Alex having him on
The the network
Even you know like
What you going to do
We got to kick him off
Good luck
Yeah I mean
Cheese I mean we'll see
It's it's a mess
But you work at the little bit a little bit race
No wait this is this is more just about how women need to be
I just making babies all the time
Alright let's do it myself I was a libertarian
High School
I never got it I don't think most people get it because
Nobody makes you
Why Nick why can't
I love it
Here's my favorite thing in the world when someone is like no one ever makes the argument so now I will
I love that it's like when I was like I'm going to get down to it I'm going to prove everything
Why does no
Nobody is talking about using your toaster in the bathtub to do it right now I'm going to lay a
Get out
I always always loved when someone sets the bar way too high for themselves and that's what Nick is done right here
Make the argument my man
Do you think they're incompetent
Yes
Entirely
I mean
But it's actually serious
If we're to have a traditional Christian
Sexual morality
Then when is you be getting married and
Alvinblox
That's just a natural
Is your following God's word if you're real Christian a real conservative
You're having all these babies
Who is going to raise those babies other than their mother
Yeah he's no one makes the argument so Nick's going to do it he's going to lay it out for you damn dude
I have never heard that one before God Nick made this argument
Yes women are things
Women should have children
What
This guy is breaking new ground all over the place church for the first time last week
I find I find this fascinating and I think you see it a lot with these types this
Is making really really old arguments that we most people have left in the past
As if they were new novel like
Breakthroughs
Like no one no one no one lays it out like me my religious beliefs dictate that women are acai
Essentially just
Biological machines that we use to create
And take care of the Next Generation
Yes oh wow
Wow groundbreaking
Mindfreak
Well it's just
I mean
Go back to the joke I made earlier I guess it's like
Imagine This
Any other
Contacts bright like
So
We used to put as best
This in buildings and then people are getting sick so we stopped
We realize that was
Not how we wanted to go forward so you know we moved on
And I just imagine somebody like this is the
Rhetorical equivalent
Of being like
Imma let you in on a little secret
There's something you can put in your walls
I swear to God no better insulation
Do call you an idiot say that you're going to go to the hospital when you're older if you do this
Why would my religion dictate so you must take the risk of
Going to the hospital
Yeah it's
It's not
It's not convincing
I would say 41
And of course it does we're into racism because this is Meg
Aperol and of course it does
We have a country now
Were people have babies in
What do they do
They have one or two or three kids and then they stopped
Anime send the kids
And the mom's working in the dad's working in that two cars at you car insurance at all this
And they send the kids to daycare and the kids from
The time they wake up
Hi Mommy and Daddy get home from
Are being raised by somebody else
Your mother
They're being raised in many cases by people that don't care about them
Maybe people
You're seeing people being
Mothers are too busy doing what
Spreadsheets
They're too busy making a schedule
This is not always does have to come back
Back to anti-immigrant sentiment in
Encoding the are babies and
You know it's also I think this is something that needs to be said
That is the Nick is 22 years old
And we know what he's been doing since he was in high school
I do not know if you've somebody that I would take very seriously
About what it's like to have a career or a real job
Two cars
Little kids like damn someone figured it out cuz I don't know if I'll be able to do that
Cars 2 car insurances
I'm right here is what I'm saying
But
Yeah he's not exactly the authority on the good old days you know I just imagine him flipping through like
1950s
Addition of like Highlights magazine and being like
This is what
They stole from
You keep Bucky's scrolled slurs in the word Bubbles and every drawing in the Highlights magazine
Yeah I know it's
It's
Ridiculous and also just this whole premise of like
Because somebody is an immigrant
That they would be in after
Caring for
A child
Especially if they're in daycare they're not in school yet
They're so young
Remember s*** anyway like
I mean by old despain is not probably going to stick around
Childcare careers are often people who do not hate kids at the most selfless people in the world
Obviously there's going to be
Bad people in any
Line of work but
I would think that the people that I know who gravitated towards
Backfield
Baby love
Yeah you don't do it because you get rich or you get famous it
Do it because
UCare
Are those going to be outliers in any profession
But yeah
And I think I think too. Just like Nick doesn't know what it means to have a job
He doesn't know what it means to have a career and therefore he
You can be productive
And stupid about like all women artists making spreadsheet so they can't raise the pain
So young
Can kind of work yeah cuz they don't know either
Yeah like if
If they got a room full of like
I'm thinking the tpusa donors
Aging Q-tips roundtables eating
Basil chicken
Starbucks on the menu
They just don't
So they've got careers they've got families that got whatever but Papa and I just imagine the audience being like
What's he talking about again
I just I don't
Think it would resonate with though
Older crowd
No no because he'd been essentially be looking at them and being like all you do is make spreadsheets
And everyone who's
Had a career or done work
Knows that there's much more
To having a career especially something that you love
Something that you find fulfilling something that is like
A part of your life
The idea of depriving people of that because you and your religious beliefs dictate that they must have babies constantly
Is this is bizarre
It's
Unhinged
Supremacist is what it is it's true
That my beliefs
So much
More important than you was
The person that they should take
Dictate your life
Yep Anza
It's now something that Alex apparently is either tacitly or explicitly condone
Yeah
We have one more because it's basically just him being like well if this is sexist then I
I guess I am
Yeah yeah I would agree
The best point he's made the whole speech accept the mantle kind of
Rhetorically what he's trying to do is be like this isn't exit this is just
Normal
And it's not
This is this is outrageous
I've said this before in a AAA think it Bears repeating
I don't think that I would
Spend time covering
Hypnic
I'm glad the people like you do
Because I think that
He's somebody that definitely people should pay attention to
And deserves
A critical eye
But I don't know how much he fits into the scheme of
Of what we cover on this show
But
He's on Alex's network doing this now
This is so incompatible with the message that Alex
Tries to sell his brand on
But I think
It bears like
Looking at being like
Really
This is now this is now in Fort Worth
This is
This is their their contact
Yeah I mean it's it's certainly interesting but it's
Yeah I mean at the end of the day I think they're kind of onto different tracks
And there's some overlap there
But
When the rubber hits the road I just
Yeah it is kind of hard to
To wrap your head around it
I think that they are fortunate that the rubber has not hit the road
And I imagine what it does
They will turn on each other
Incredibly aggressive
I hope so that would be
It is somebody who has had to spend countless hours of my life
Both paying attention to Alex and Nick watching them
Each other alive would be
Immensely
Personally entertaining to me I think there would be some schadenfreude
For sure
I would worry about how he could have the at like it could
Accelerate things for some of their followers
Yet if one wins the others audio
That's a bad thing
Yeah it would be it would be interested to see them take potshots
Especially because like
A lot of the stuff like
That's a bit Nikki use it as ammunition against people that he
Goes after
Are all the criticisms
The people in the right-wing have had of Alex
They all constantly said that he's a shill for Israel
They say that he works for Mossad
All of this is a tradition
That they could pull from
I'm just
Go to town against Alex what's something that Nick does for like
Everybody
It almost feels like he's pulling a punch
Without
Yeah
Let me just take me for
Right because I was on the first people that started writing about him
And now the people have questions about
People call me in like he has
Hold on let me just send you a document you
Off and on the record he talks you check all this s*** out
And you tell me what you think of
But I
Yeah it's pretty obvious what he's doing he said
It is failed with
Next
See straight through it but
So he doesn't like me
So when I was at Breitling watch
I was the Soros
You know I was working at Jewish
Oh yeah
And dumb
Now I work at the FR lab which is
Connect to the Atlantic council's and I work for NATO and now
I'm CIA and
What is the CIA but an extension of Mossad and
He always takes it back
Having some
Problem with you
8888 a very constant refrain on his part
And expect some of that in the future Alex
Well Jared thank you for joining
I'm sorry to have subjected you to this
This site is not fun
Listening to Nick Fuentes ever is really
Not a pleasant thing to do not a great use of an afternoon but
I appreciate you joining
So it's been a pleasure it's it's nice to
Being knowledge fight hqhq
As you can see I'm sending out buttons to The Listener is
And that's that's the return address
I will try hq0 nice
Jfhq
It's at it's a treat like I told you when we went out the other night and met up with
The first time
You're somebody who has been really supportive over the course of
What time do Don the show and I really appreciate that
And thank you
Oh absolutely I meet what you guys
Have been doing here for so long
Is important and you guys understand
Like a lot of media especially National media will
Baby
Go to Infowars Argota
Alex and cover
Angela
Mine
Detective
Origin tank 11 of like this is this particular crazy thing he
Tea set
But there aren't a whole lot of people just really like
Sitting with
And like
Watching the show Kansas
And you're really getting a feel for like the Infowars cast of characters
Sort of how the show works I can tell you why that is
I think you know why cuz you used to do that a lot
No
It's not a fun job
But it's
It's
Unfortunately Imports
In-N-Out yoworld you know
Maybe knowledge fight wouldn't have to exist but for now I'm really glad that
Well thank you I appreciate that and I'm glad that you're doing the work you're doing as well
Wicked people follow you to find some of your analysis and what have you
I know you're just on reliable sources God yeah
You can follow me on here
Alex might talk about you
Oh I hope so
Really you might do a segment on you hate stelter
Oh yeah it's
Sits I mean it
It's always a pleasure to be in the company of such a
Widely revered potato the most popular
O'Brien ticket guy I don't want to roast them too bad
You keep up with me at Jared L Holt
On Twitter
I don't follow me on anything else cuz I'm private on everything else
I've got a podcast my own called post called shitpost
With an! Right yeah it's s h! T
Etst because people on iTunes will let you swear
Yeah I typed it typed it in originally and I was like oh no I can't
What am I going to do and then I
Put an! And
Now I have to spend 30 seconds explaining to people to find the show I think you in the description of an episode one side
You put a swear word and I saw it it automatically added it
Wow this is
Text censorship man no cussing
Canceled
Yeah that's
That's what we need to talk about f*** Nick Fuentes getting kicked off whatever
This America
I want to say you know
A******
In the description of my iTune podcast
I should be able to do that
I shouldn't have to use the other signs
Where are you Ted Cruz haha
Is Ted Cruz on freethenipple
Will be back if Jordan is going to be back from vacation and so we will have an episode out on when
Wednesday where will check in
All with Alex
Thank you so much for joining
Oh thanks I guess at the end of this I'm supposed to say that I'm Bo hyung Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color