Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Surround
Attitude the Run
Bio of dudes
Apple David
The Peabody and Sherman of podcasting
I think that might be the only accurate way to describe us
So beware the Peabody and Sherman of podcast and we worked with the others lean and Doug little bit about Alex Jones
Doesn't roll off my tongue as well as I hoped it was the Peabody & Sherman
Peabody and Sherman
Dog
There's no way I'm mr. Peabody
Just skip that part
Jordan what's up
Dustin Poirier
What's your bright spot today
I hate don't call it a comeback
I guess my bright spot has been I really have enjoyed over the time that you've been on
Flygon
Making buttons I've gotten
None of them sent out in his
Is a ton more to send out
Course and I would just like to give this way with little reminder to everyone that if you've not heard back from the email
I can't respond to all these emails
There are way too many for a way more than I expected it to be more than last time but they're all be
Sent out
It's 1 I'm not complaining to be able to give
I give to Tom people
It's not like biting off more than you can chew it's like
Picking out a buffet and deciding that it's going to take a few weeks to finish the entire goddamn Buffet but yeah
Eat that goddamn Buffet
Yeah I kind of think that's how I'm looking at it
And give me the
Excuse to watch
Bunch of Survivor why you were gone and so I would like to say that
Really
Wow I thought you were going to that you were telling me that it was about to
To fall off the cliff you would seem the future coming and it was going to be a disaster they introduced Exile Island and then
And also they introduced the hidden immunity idol and he's are signs of bad things
For sure I will tell you this
Way too many twists
Start
Were they start throwing curveballs for no reason like you can't plan from episode 2 episode like
I don't even know if his give me my tribe tomorrow
It's outrageous that you're on The Bachelorette
But season 13 was the one that starts out divided by race
Ukiah and the
Yeah they start with an African American tribe and Asian American tribe
A white
Tribe
Wild
Edit
Not
Comfortable at first
It's 2005-2006 might get away with that s*** someone thought it was a great
Good idea and it like maybe it would prompt conversation
Yeah it doesn't
It's bad it's beginning
The story that developed the middle of the
The season throughout is
Maybe one of the mower
Compelling things I've seen all that show
I don't want to spoil anything but it's
Styx gets Highmark
I think a lot of people would hate it if you spoiled something
Sing from 16 years ago
Fair enough
What about you what's your birthday
You know I had a absolutely fantastic
Isaac Tripp
It was astonishing
Waterfalls I climbed
Goddamn
2 mi long
But it was
We're from here where there's no high
Yeah concrete everywhere
If they're up whenever I got up there I could
Could see other things from like further away
Reminds me of season of Survivor where they went up on a hill
Nobody was
Triplets great
Give me back my bright spot is I feel like life is bright
Yeah that's good
That's always a nice things to reclaim after a vacation
Dogs again I'm sure they were quite messy
A****** when they saw me
This morning pick them up
Jumped into my face baby been off half of my beard it was brutal anyway you got it
Folks
We when we last left
Serialized show
So are we going to finally figure out who shot Jr been not feeling all that well it was not
That huge of a deal I did get tested for covid never thing is all
-7
I am and what have you
And the only reason I bring this back up is because you never coming back here on a Wednesday and I really hope
That we would have been able to record some stuff
Before your vacation
And then have it too
Smooth
Things out on either end of it but
Because I was not feeling well we weren't able to and I appreciate everybody being understanding
I listened to the episode there's a delight to meet Jared
Sorry sorry I missed that
I had a couple it was weird listening to you guys talk because
I was listening as I was there and I was like who I got something funny
I can't say it
Brutal
Another thing that's interesting is
We might be witches
Alex
No
Nope nope unacceptable
I refuse
Then
Prior to this show
Prior to the show the number of coincidences
Coincidences per month
Very low
Right now it seems our schedules matchup in
When we don't really announce these things all that far in advance is upsetting Italy
I don't like it so yeah there wasn't actually all that much to deal with in terms of Alex last week
So would have been
You know
No-man's-land Dwight
We are back
Discussing
First one
This is the Sunday
Sunday
Episode
Very exciting
Stuff to go over but before we get to that door and let's take a look-see hello
Tyrus
Everyone knows you're actually a secret reptile and we are
Constantly watching everything you do thank you so much you're not apology walk
I'm a policy wonk
Guitarist
Caroline Jay from the Mohawk nation in Ontario Canada thank you so much
North Carolina Valhalla thank you so much
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
That was Mickey
Foley in Avatar
What's an avatar The Last Airbender there was an episode where they meet
Detolf the earthbending
First metal bender
They do a whole nice professional wrestling thing and Mick Foley
Plays the boulder
And does a full-on inov wrestling you got
Really excited that Mick Foley was a nozzy
I'm in the other Avatar
So how
I've listened to both of your god-awful movie episodes twice bring on more bad movies
Thank you so much right now if you want
So what's up
Quokka the games out
Money off that heroin
Is freakishly large
Transtech Walker
Thank you very much
Also
Update
It's two additions to selene's family
To say thank you so much
Fukt
Who adopted a blue-footed booby
Cuz it needed some feathers
Play exciting movie.
For every time we do something it whines
Spiraling out of control
I think this one might get us
To Arc
Levels of out-of-control eventually everyone's going to realize that
The only way we're going to make it through this is if we have two of every animal in the Gulf of Celine that's just looking to have to happen
Let's not let it get to that point but we do appreciate people adopting
Start here on Sunday here's where Alex is at
Big news
Covid bad news bad news
Go to front page of infowars.com you will see today's headline we have a live show feed
Jean King headline
The British government officially warned
That
2.6
Billion plus
People
Here we go
Whenever you're ready
2.6 billion
People
Die
As a result
The
Mutations coming from
The so-called
Covid-19 vaccine
What
We modified injection
India is
It really letting it slip wow wow okay
Did you hear this story while you're on vacation feel like you
You missed this week the British press has been like 2.6 billion going to die
Florida. Would it come out of nowhere that deliver the news
I want to just talk about an article here in the Daily Mail that discusses a recent comments from the UK scientific advisory
For emergency
Also known as Sage
They warned that the possibility of a mutation occurring they could make covid as deadly as murderers
Quote of realistic
Possibility
The part that Alex is completely ignoring about the article is the part where it also says
The sage report also claimed it was equally realistic that covid will mutate to become less lethal over time
So
Coming from the sage counsel future
Uncertain
Yes could be good that's fine
This is the paper that encouraged the UK government to that given to
Complacency because at this point there's really no way to know how covid going to evolve in the future
The part about vaccines creating
The mutations is just a simple misrepresentation of a single line in
Bastille email article that says quote
It at the outside of Britain's hugely successful vaccination Drive the team warned the country is greater levels of immunity May helps
Speed up the viruses
Evolutionary process
This isn't saying that vaccines
Increase mutation
That's just Alex's made-up version to what that means
It's clear if you read the underlying report that this is a ref
To the phenomenon known as selection
Compressor that occurs whenever you treat an illness
You wouldn't say that antibiotics
Create antibiotic-resistant strains of illness
But if you don't take a full course of antibiotics
You might f*** around and
Create antibiotics
Dial resistance
How many times do we have to
To discuss evolutionary arms races before people are like oh evolutionary arms-race is what's going on right here
If you do care to look for this and actually you can find the report
If you wanted look
The primary sources instead of
Of what Alex does is a
Skim Daily Mail articles
Breezy flight
That article are that tie-dye paper if you want
It's titled SPI
For the next few months
The frame of this document is really clear and that it's discussing possible circumstances that you cake
You could find itself in
But officials need to keep in mind as they embark on quote
The final step of Ethan
Primarily they list a key concern is being the quote
Any epidemic
Trajectory that could lead to unsustainable pressure on the NHS or other adverse outcomes
Would need to be identified and
Contingency enacted within days
They're board itself actually of the graphic at the bottom of it.
Explains
What they mean when they say realistic
Possibility
This is something that has about a 42
To 50% chance in their estimation
It's slightly more probable than unlikely and less likely then
Likely
All these contacts
Is absent from Alex's coverage because he's just interested in both representing headlines in order to scare the audience into whatever
Directions
Going to be profitable that day
Also
A 2.6
6 billion number that isn't from the report
This is just a calculation Alex
Or maybe you could even blame the Daily Mail for this week
It's just take
The death rate that you would have heard about 1/2 the inspection rate
It's that we see currently so it's applying it to the entire world population
The entire world population
Okay
Alright
All right. If that is a little sloppy you have is a Daily Mail report
Kind of
Not great in terms of the underlying primary source even further off course
With nonsense we have the British media saying that
2.6 billion
You know I think the big problem
That we're experiencing right now is a simple kind of error which is that in order to
To deal with this
We needed l
Who had the courage
To say things that people didn't want to hear
And then enforce those things as being necessary
System doesn't reward
Courageous leaders
It punishes them for sometimes being wrong or being right in a mean way
And I so instead we got a bunch
Ifucking coward
Is a mess
One thing I really always appreciate
About
Someone like an owl
Even if he is
You know lost tracks
Sometimes
He really knows how to keep his own stories
Straight
They have begun that long dad has these things that he's researched
And like
Gino's
Forward and backward
Too much yeah
Yeah like I got a really good handle on stuff
Williamston million views herself
Oh my God
Rockefellers another's
That would collapse civilization
And then the Crimson Contagion
128.
Document
Text Arianna crimson
Really sad to hear the way Alex is talking about these two exercises
He's made a ton of s*** about both to the point where he doesn't even remember which
The reality of either underlying thing isn't even something that he's connected
To any longer which is
Outrageous
Neither of these things that he's talking about were around by the Rockefeller
Dude with cheese
Dragonfly
Crimson contagion with a series of exercises went by the HHS
It was a government operate
Because it was a big elaborate scenario thing there were a bunch of governmental and non-governmental participant
Hitler report there's actually a list of non-governmental / 2
Just been to the Rockefeller Foundation
One of those
Bars with a scenario exercise those run by Johns Hopkins Center for Health
Security
These are two very different exercises in the fact that Alex can get them
Confused is a very strong
Indication that he doesn't know anything about them past their name
And the stories that he's made up about the
Crimson contagion was a government-run series of exercises about the fictitious discovery of a novel influenza virus
Not a Coronavirus
In Crimson contagion the idea was
The test interagency collaboration as well as collaboration with non-governmental agencies
And tribal leaders to see what challenges would arise in the course of responding to a
A new infection
Disease
Airport is largely about the things that they learned in the course of role play
Playing like quote
Response Partners lack Clarity on cdc's data-sharing policies in
Quote confusion regarding the purpose of and Target audio
For National Conference Calls a coordination among state and federal response partner
This is not like an elaborate scenario that
It's washed out with a ton of detail in this
Because they point the exercise was to have
A basic problem that require coordination to address
We could create the opportunity for people to
To test that coordination
In a safe environment and identify problems
Ahead of time
Conversely
Sparse is a little bit of a different kind of scenario exercise
This isn't something that was role-played like rims
Contagion
He's instead of document
Delays out of fictitious
Future series of events
Then poses questions about how
You could best
Respond to those develop
Esparza's exercise that is it
Explicitly about Messi
Messaging and Public Health
Risk communication
Doesn't really lend itself to role playing in the way the crimson
Contagion
Trying to explore challenges of Public Health messaging would be hard to
Do in a role-playing environment without a fake audience
To send the message
Just to
That makes a lot more
Sense to broach the issue in this format
Where you have like discussion questions
You got this curveball thrown at you like a basketball practice
Esparza's like famous
Messi football
Sure you know what I'm saying like the basketball practice you've got people playing you're running through the scenarios that might come up
Open a game the fantasy football years
Studying and you're taking Jada and extrapolating based on
Or maybe like
Esparza's like you would a chalkboard working-out a play
Sure whatever
Yeah Yeah Yeahs document is meant to highlight a different communication challenge that officials could face in
The context of a panda
Chapter 17 is about messaging surrounding potential vaccine side effects but the information
Alex is providing
Anyway consist
Any of that stuff
Yeah it's interesting
When you are basing things on reality
That have reference
You can refer back
Back to those
If you
Casino
If you makeup
Details
How about things and then create a completely different
Something based around 2 and then forget what that is
Go back and find it
Well you certainly can't find the thing that says the thing you said
Exactly
You can still say the name of the thing
Convince people you have Reddit know you're talkin
I understand the basic pieces of information that Alex is trying to run with here and it's all bulshit but
I literally drive home here that Alex doesn't even know the fake things he's talking
About
He put out an emergency Special Report on Saturday restarted to get into the stuff and here's what he said
You know what makes me even more concerned you know I'm really free
Breakout
Sunday show tomorrow
For 6 p.m.
Crimson Contagion
4 years ago
3 years ago
They saying there
But they're going to roll out of vaccine for a Coronavirus
And a year later
Turn out of kills about
Ella even
Disable Public Health officials will step down apologizing
They're going to have new that what you said
Why would they say that
Variance
That the mistaken
Failed vaccine
Creates the hugest thing it was crimson
Contagion on Saturday which matches basically zero of the details he's describing
So I would guess you're that I guess
He decided he was going to really push Crimson Contagion
Super hard on Saturday
Heaven sometime in between
Queen van and the Sunday show one of his in terms of someone's like
You got the document wrong
That's why you corrected himself
On Sunday show
Tahiry is on Saturday again
Still just trying to push it as
Backrooms
Contagion
You read
Crimson contagion if you read of it to A-1
If you read operation lockstep
Rockefellers
The Rockefeller Foundation
Now in complete control
World policy
Really
Oh
I didn't know they talked about how it's all going to come out
And how they're going to spend that through fear
Couldn't make you want to take even more vaccines they've created a are going to come to you
Who are against all of this who have the new vaccine
It'll protect you from the last vaccine
Now that was in Crimson contagion 34 years ago
I guess he'll date has been partially removed did not know that being in the account
12 tubing mid-level management and now he's out of the game completely I'm guessing if I were to ask Alex where he found
Papers or something
I would just
Run into a wall that would be a really interesting document to read if it while your reading rate
It's like
And then when people read this document will make them afraid of the document itself me like wait a second I'm reading
Nothing you're telling me I'm supposed to be afraid of now
It's a mirror in a mirror
I think it's really important to understand how we could grasp Alex has on these basic
Details about the primary sources that he's misusing
All these names are interchangeable for him because none of them actually are even real
According to him they aren't real
Over the course of his broadcast is created entirely fictional version
Crimson contagion to vent 201 and sparse
Onision
Completely fabricated operation lock
Step out of that Rockefeller
Methodist never read
These documents are real
And actually interesting to read
But not for the reasons that Alex and
They are fixed
It's all fake
Yeah I mean the problem is
Disease created so many b*******
Scenarios out of these two scenarios you know like he's
He's written
An entire universe filled with characters trying to kill you
And all of these things and it's like The Simpsons
But you know
You can't remember any of the episodes so it just kind of picks and chooses whoever shows up and you're like no that's not where
That goes man that's not where comic book guy is supposed to be
Comic Book Guy is back over there helping Bill Gates murder everybody
Bugatti this episode you know that I should tell you that I'm on the Saturday show
He does say that Bill Maher is starting to come around
So he might be working on casting people against type
Now we're back at Belmar
Yikes all right
So this is this is where I got worried
Sounds like oh man
Alex
You might have prepared
This information I study
I like six hours
Almost
Contemplative
Wow
You might have prepared today
I don't know
Oh man I was working on this for six hours and I got dizzy when I got busy what I said that was so intense
I got dizzy from the information
I don't know I don't know how
How much harder he could try to convince people that
For the past
48 hours in the last time that I stood up I lost one of my
I grabbed it and I put it back on
It's all because I've been reading
Globalist planned Crimson Contagion
And I would get into it but I
I've got dizzy the last time I learned about
So I can't talk
So he get Alex gets into a little bit of cigar called a little bit fear-monger
As he comes back
Break
Dependent enhancement
Real real well when your friends your family and you bleed out
By the near future
Who
Okay so everybody dependent enhancement is a real phenomenon that scientists
Do see it.
But it's actually really funny that Alex is trying to connect
Possibility to covid vaccine
Number of reason
The biggest of them is that the possibility of adee with
Absolutely something the researchers and
Experts were discussing in the early stages of developing a vaccine
Oh yeah if there is an active pandemic giving people something that will make them respond worse to contact with virus
Chris's is going
To be ultimately
Lee
And probably one of things going to check off
Early
The best way to understand Abe is by talking about the first place it was identified which is in relation to
The dengue fever
Therefore varieties are serotypes of dengue fever numbered 1
Through 4
If you get sick with Dengue Fever type 1
Anemone survive
Your body will create antibodies that protect
From fat zero
Should you ever encounter at
In the future
That's great news
However
The problem is that if you run into stereotype
Two three or four
Decent chance of the antibodies you have against Arrow type 1
Actually enhance the ability of dengue fever to replicate
Innovative be neutralized inside your body infection is actually really it's worth
Yeah yeah
The concept is a bit more complicated than that but that's the basic idea of what the
Concerns are about ADA
Impact studies there has been
Indications that SARS and MERS were two diseases whose treatment involves concern
It's about a DE
Since this new virus sars-cov 2
Is closely related to those two
That was an obvious question the people were discussing
You can find tons of papers on the subject
From early in the time of when vaccines are starting to
Come around
Because
The way he says
Is it to is like
Antibody that's a term you're going to get to know real well is your family's bleed now and
When is like no
I won't
Because they already learned it real well that's the point you're the only person hearing about it for the first time
Blowin Minds baby
Some early indications raised
Concerns that having vaccines that attack viral protein
Themes of covid epicenter
The cause adee
Which is one of the reasons that research skewed very heavily in the direct
MRNA vaccine
The targeting of Spike protein
Instead of the viral
Alright
I was just pretending this some kind of a big issue that everyone's ignoring
It's not the scientific Community is kept
The phenomenon willing mind and
Pandemic response is going on
And follow-up research on people who have been vaccinated that bro
Breakthrough infections actually shown
There really aren't signs of adee with covid
If there were 80 happening you would expect to see vaccinated people having more severe cases of covid-19 exposed
The virus but in reality
The cases among vaccinated people
Physically less severe
I have lied to last hospitalization
Which are very strong indications that lady is not selling
Just the fact that
The vaccine has documented
Effectiveness
Against
New variant
As well with
Just very obviously that it's not that huge
If it were then we would see
Increased or even greater negative reaction from the Delta variant if you were
Vaccinated again
Whatever you know
I was listening to this and I thought that it was pretty clear that
This is basically going to
To be how Alex
Explains away future deaths
People who are vaccinated who
Issues where they got the vaccine and then
They got they got
The challenge of
Being exposed to covanta near a global scale.
Whatever
So you're some big news
You don't think it's big news
Alright
This is a live Sunday August 1st 2021 transmission
What year was the big announcement
It is not debate
By the NIH
Bob again
IAH
National Health Service or any other world
Call covid
19 of a sedation for the baby
Johnson & Johnson
All of them
Make you get
Covid
Create
What's good to know that Alex has learned that AstraZeneca isn't an mRNA vaccine by this point
Work
Although I will say my Counterpoint all this is
All of that would absolutely be debated by any of the groups that I like
Waitlisted
This complete b*******
Yeah that's an insane thing to say about the claim that Alex is making this weekend
Parsnip
It's really stupid
He's saying that all these different covid vaccines one
Make you get
Get covid
To make you shed Cove
Free
Make you create deadly variants
And for
Don't work
None of this is true
How could
For be true
If 133 or
I get well that's one of my problems with actually the fourth point is like I don't know what
Not working
Yeah I mean if it's too nonspecific for me to take seriously so I'm not even going to
Not just that but I mean if it's the point of it is to get give people covered shed covid and then create deadly
Very it's any very clearly is working
Wow that's why I don't
Engage version of vying to be different
Is it very clearly
With .3 the vaccines make people create deadly various of the virus that just doesn't stand up
Neither
Came into existence
Before the vaccines were developed in in Venice
Mustard so
I guess unless
There's some other mystery variants that he's talking
Sing about him
Take us seriously either
Get the f*** out one just isn't Drew thanks
Don't make you get covid-19
Who does leaves a point to about shedding virus
Which is the only part that even comes close to
Some recent preprint studies of symptom indications
It's possible for people who have been vaccinated but end up
Sing a breakthrough case of the Delta variant
They could be as infectious as unvaccinated person
This is a matter that we are definitely
We need more data on before we can jump to any solid
Conclusions but it's something that makes it clear that we should all be
Cautious
These same studies
Is it suggested possibility also found quote viral load decrease Pastor the vaccinated group so
Either way there appears to be
Be concrete Public Health advantages to being vaccinated
Even if it isn't a magic Silver Bullet
And even if we're learning along the way new things that we were not aware I was earlier
There's serious concerns that married discussion
What about potential challenges we're still facing with
The Coronavirus
Alex is acting does he
Lead the service towards anyone's abilities engaged
This material
In a serious way
If you get information
Confirm him you have to sift through all this b******* in order to reach one thing
It's being discussed
Poorly
Which is the idea that if you're vaccinated you still might be contagious
Get the information that you need for better places without having to
Huh big through a pile mean
I can't imagine like an emergency broadcast alert suddenly breaking in while you're while you're watching
Sing some
Dumb reality shows like Survivor
And then the government like
You're going to die
Anyways just so you know that the possibility that breakthrough
Actions could be a problem
You're going to die you're going to die you're going to die
But that's what Alex is doing and I don't know how useful that is
The emergency broadcast system
F****** Moody as hell
Bad bad days
Happy care if you guys make it through this emergency
Hey maybe it's not an emergency maybe I'm talking with you who knows
Maybe I should join the tornado the FDR's Fireside Chats of just a moody ask
Alright so we're fighting this f****** why don't even know does anybody even hate the Nazis anymore I don't know
Depression is great
About that maybe it's a great
Depression ratings on my Fireside Chats are down
And I am
I'm pissed about it yeah that would be great
Courageous leaders I would love
The re-imaginings of
Like historical figures with the temperament of a moody Alex Jones
We would have never gotten anything done
So there's some side effects
And what have you
For vaccines
I do believe that Alex might
Be
Exaggerating
Conditioner blood clot the brain
You don't have a virus
You get given protein
What
Myprotein
Your body starts
Rolling
Animals of vast majority
Reroute self-addressed
You're going to burn to death
Barbie
That's why I'm so shocked
This is one hundred percent known
Feisty
Play my hand out of the table today
Alex seems
Like in
Intrigued by the idea of cause and effect
Kind of concerning me that this is
Blowing people's minds in his in his eyes he's like I need to illustrate cause and effect causal relationship
4 *
So you know what actually let's start with n
The universe
This is four-dimensional space and we are leaving
Spirit Style baby if you drop something and it falls to the ground
John mulaney's Ice Cube
This is Ice-T
This is a little bit
Much
I mean first of all just took
From a presentation standpoint I find it
Hilarious butt
Hundreds of millions of vaccines administered in the United States
The majority are absolutely not experienced heart attack
Strokes concert
Nonsense
Them also Alex is trying to make this point he does this clipping
Fully captured but there's this idea that they'd skip the animal trials
But he pushes fairly regularly at night
Prodigious were allowed to overlap animal trials with Phase 1 trials because of the nature of the public health
The pass animal trials with no problem
Largely ignored
We were more excited about the
Human part of it the one we were looking for
Boots
Paled in comparison
Open to the idea that
Even further progress is being made no I remember reading tons of stories that were like
Stokes good vaccine resulted in tested animals and I was like that's awesome
If the something had gone wrong with like the animal trials
As Phase 1 trials were overlapping with them
Then back to the drawing board
Imagine if something had gone wrong
And deal
Do you really think I would have expected it
Eye exam surprise
Many people it would have been an emotional blow certainly
But I think Abby will be like yeah
Yeah you try and it sometimes it works
Those would have been very loud they would have been everywhere and Alex would have run with
Them forever
So the fact that he didn't
Fruits that didn't happen because he didn't do it when it would have
So Alex is a study
Spell doesn't
I really
This is business roster
I got the actual CDC
Show you the actual study
Overhead shot Place why you can't trust
Flies from STP
Percent
Helping individuals
Azan in all the different sloughing off
Woodley
Say that part
They're not really accurate surrounding a cluster of cases that occurred in the wake
Quote multiple summer events and large
Public gatherings in a Town of Barnstable County
Chusetts
They're important questions to ask about this cluster and I would not begrudge anyone raising
I'm concerned about what this sort of thing could it
Imply
But that is not what Alex is doing
He's misreporting
And making leaps
Is coverage that are unearned
Princeton's the way you covering this story you'll be led to believe that this has to do with
74% of all Delta variant cases being among vaccinated persons
That's how he's
Speaking
What do you think the CDC has a report that 74% of Delta cases early
Liar so you know they're telling the truth what last time they are
The appropriate contact
This was just about
469 people who tested positive after attending events in
In Provincetown
The 74% number is definitely worth looking
It is a concern but
This study does
Does not involve a representative sample
You could extrapolate to the rest of the world
There's far more information we need to track down for the number
Could be understood and
It's really full proper Conte
If you read the actual CDC report you'll find a very important note that it's key to remember
Quote
Data from this report are insufficient to draw conclusions about the effectiveness of covid-19 vaccine against Stars Cove 2
Including the Delta variant during this out
As population-level vaccinations
Can coverage increases
Vaccinated persons are likely to represent a larger
Proportion
Of covid-19
Team queso
This is to say that if in this series of events
In Provincetown there was a 95% vaccination rate
You would expect a total number of
Infections UT on outbreak to be
Wow the total no
But the proportion of those infected or vaccinated
Would be higher
This is because no vaccine is a perfect
Effectiveness rating
And also that's just ask
Provincetown is a place in Massachusetts
That's well-known as a very lgbtq-friendly environment
And if I had to bet I would say that it
This place Utah
Pretty high vaccination rate
So if you know any event of an outbreak happening in a place like that it doesn't
Surprise me too much
Percentage of people who are vaccinated would be
That's what you would expect
Yeah I've read that I've read too many takes on that and very few people are applying the
Very rigorous
Context that needs to be applied before you can even engage with that information without terrified
It's still something that you should
Absolutely nothing
He's very
And if you understand it within the full context of what it is then isn't
Very interesting and something that needs to be looked at in studies
If you are just reading a wapo headline that you're f******
Terrified there's another there's another important thing and that is needed to take 800 number
B6 vaccinated persons having breakthrough cases in this outbreak
Only focus on that number you're missing an important figure
Which is how many vaccinated person
Might have been exposed to the virus and didn't
In the course of these
Public Gatherings and large events
I'm not saying that any of this makes the story like
Less a matter for
Concerned
Some people should be focusing on
What's just critical of these times take the stuff in the proper
Extrapolate this out to
Do 74% of cases or vaccinate
Yeah yeah I'm concerned quite frankly about unknown unknown
Obviously
How can you not be
I barely left my house this past week is Lollapalooza what's happening at this videos
Amass yeah I was stoked to be in the woods while all opposed
Yeah it's rational be concerned but it's irresponsible to behave the way Alex's
Doing it disseminate information that way
Yeah it's just it only can lead people to make dumb
Informed decision
So what
How do you say something like that
I mean to emphasize
I can't do I can't emphasize
Any more than
Alex G himself
Examples of cause and effect
Text to emphasize
He already did that
Call Hatchett
Still working on object permanence because Alex doesn't have that one doubt myself in a mirror the other day
Alex says
Do you get secrets on to another story that is about
A similar theme
That is like vaccinated people are getting
The wet what he uses as a source
Unbelievable
Bossman
Finland
Hospital
JCW's
2/3
70 + 67%
Partially or fully vaccinated with mRNA
I beg anyone who takes Alex Jones seriously to consider how sloppy and lazy this process is
Instead of actually looking into any primary sources on Finland or any possible outbreaks that have happened there
What you just heard
Is how Alex has decided
Story
This is Alex reading a tweet
Permanent verified account that's allegedly run by a guy wiederhold MD and Ms degrees
Where is claiming townhouses in Maryland in Mississippi
This is not how someone who take
Take their job seriously would operate
Alex is legitimately just reading the body of this guy's tweet
Accompanied by a screenshot and a link
I-80 surveillance article
This is not mean that picking or being an a******
Like Alex is not reporting on the study
He's reporting on a tweet
He's not read the study he has
No idea
The words he's reading what they even mean is what agency
Bwam
It's it's that great
It's at Great level of right-wing nonsense where you can just take a random dude with
20 followers tweeting there were three million illegals voting in
And turn it into the number one narrative that people throw around a fuk
Talking election
Play it's it's a mess and it's such a shity work that I don't even know why I found the study and read
But suffice it to say
It's another very small snapshot of an outbreak that happened at a secondary care hospital
When Finland in May of this year
45 healthcare workers in 58-page
Ended up attracting covid if you look at the data
What are things that jumps out
Is possibly most
Concerning is the people who were only
Partially vaccinated might have a higher risk
With Delta very
48 out of the 103 cases were among people who were only partially vaccinated
As compared with 35 for unvaccinated and 20 who are fully vac
Dynamics between the lake healthcare workers
Drastic age discrepancy variables
Keep an eye on butt
This is not the
Just a case study that you can read a tweet about
Assume that it applies to the entire like General
Populaire r0k studies
You can read a tweet about and then just extrapolate from me for this must be proved up all the way
Just take this belief added word
So
Alex gets back
Activities in Vista
This British article
I think
Thinks he hasn't actually talked about even though you open the
The show talking about
We got
Really
Big news the British
Official government agency
Come out ladies and gentlemen instead mutants from the vaccinated
What's billion people
Call wards.com
It's also equally likely that it will mutate into something it is harmless
Weather.
Sometimes you know
Part of this is going to blow everybody's
Everybody's Minds about here that you know like that
You know when you evolve
Like to survive and do like propagating
Discontinued and sometimes one way to evolve is to not
Kill your host and then just
Keep going
You know another way to evolve
So
When's the last time
You remember
Alex thank you figured it all out
I mean baby in my dreams it was last night
It happens a lot
Every
I like at least
Three four times a month I'm coming to studio and say that he's finally figured it all out
It took me a long time and I know I've said this before
So much that you might not believe me this time but I bet bubbly
This time he definitely has and here here's what's going on man
It's a nefarious plan is that amazing
It's a who's who of elite scientists this is insane
Whatever you're going to be dead
Really hurt you bad
I've always wanted
It's in our blood
You're like that'll collapse Society
I want to bring down civilization
Industrial world
Civilization
This is a psychological weapon of fear
1,000-point Plus
Thousand
I thought you were dizzy
That's why they did it
Define onto it
Trump
Nationalism
Defending it even as it starts killing everybody
You're cute that you're talking to you
Describes all the stuff that he did
You just described all the stuff that he did
It's
Very sad
Although it's it's hilarious the end of the clip being like these are sophisticated people after he lays out the stupidest
Over my love
If that's so annoying
That's so annoying because
He's making it up and then he's complimenting himself
Yeah that's the problem
No he's giving himself a
Compliment about how brilliant his enemies are
Because the plan here
Meet up for them to have
Yes
The plan that he came up for them with them
Is
Something about how like
His worldview and his god king
Are so important and so powerful
That the global is needed to use a worldwide plague in order to discredit him
Discredit Trump
We had to do
That's the man
That is the level of narcissism that's really hard to wrap your head
Exactly the word I would use
Yeah it's
So
Small-minded
Yeah
That's that's how you get to do that for a job
This must be about me
That's what I'm saying if you didn't have this fur if Alex wasn't doing this
If you was just
A person
Your job
You be like we need to talk
To doctors about you this is what needs to happen
Somehow you can just either
Okay either we all agree yugos
Go to doctors or you get a show
Does the only two things that we can do for people with your level of delusion now I should tell you that
Plane that crashed in Malaysia and somehow
This was an attack
On me
I could tell you exactly about
How this plane crash relates to me but I don't have time for that I prepare too much I got to go to break
Just know that they're willing to kill me because of this plane crash
And what I know about it
So Alex has proven his point
Stand
I think he thinks he still hasn't talking
Talk about this British British story
Is completely confirmed
Absolutely confirmed
Doesn't help you hurt you and makes you spread
All the scientists at over a year ago.
Wolcott in and I'll even hit the stage
2.625 billion day weather
Policy truth baby
Awful
I don't know I don't know what
He considers covering a story
Experience is about as
Deep is he get something to erase on some stuff every now and again
You covered the story
According to my estimation at least three or four times at this episode I haven't gotten
To this news I mean
In many ways you haven't
But
I suppose it by your definition you have
As much as he's ever going to
That's a good way of putting the number
2.65 billion
I love the idea
That
No one would do anything about that
That is like
As as millions of people are dying
Everybody's going to be like what let's just wait let's ride this out and see how many go down
Like there's even if it was this there would be a very serious reaction
Long before we ever hit 1 billion
People I mean
I mean
Do remember when
Alex
And all of his people
And people in his intellectual and political sphere were saying
Let's just
Just keep going and not do anything
I mean I can kind of Imagine That Could Happen
That's fair for
That's fair
So I was like all right I don't understand why Alex thinks he hasn't covered this story but
It was getting a little bit repetitive and then the exact opposite thing happened
Another was a story that I was
Begging him to get into
And it just
I hate I hate him
Heads of major medical school
Of the
Medical school
This is crazy and she's just
Today
I have no idea here what Alex is talking about like there's multiple Dean's
Different Medicals medical schools within Baylor
And I found one guy
Dr. Peter hotez
Has
He's had a lot of comments
It's about misinformation being horrible during the
Stand that make I'm not I don't think
That can possibly be the person who
Who Alex is talking about
That person
I don't know he said she though
In the Attic
The guy who I'm talking about dr. hotez he's the
The dean of the school of tropical medicine
School of Medicine the other school of medicine
His doctor Jennifer
Kris Jenner
We talked about her but I don't know what she said I can't find everything
But to imagine that you have this guy
Who's super anti misinformation about
About covid and about the pandemic
And then this other person who's like
Hey to all evil
Holy s*** that is diversity of opinion
That's exactly what the right says doesn't
At the same time like I'm listening to this episode
Without going on
Deep of wild goose chase
I don't know who he's talking about
I suppose if I was a vindictive propagandist
I would find somebody
Saying that misinformation was a real problem
To be offensive
And also Act
And so I would then include them in my misinformation
As an insult
That could be what he's doing I'm not sure and maybe we'll learn more as the episode goes on
But at this point Alex other guests
The General
Canadian weird
I'm too much as I can cuz he's a Canadian weirdo
Back in September of last year
Was extremely prescient looking at their own
Government documents
Weather talking about the permanent
I forgot it
Has that we need to stop people demonstrating
People going outside cheap locked
People talking
That's a clip is actually
About a Prescott
Easy
Is not right when you have like a claim that put lock down the permanent and the things you come up with to reinforce your
Say something it says the opposite
It's strange
Vindictive propaganda
Also Chris guy he's a real weirdo
He's a he's a fellow whose dad runs a successful real estate development business in Canada and he's mysteriously the
The vice president of said company
He also has no kids yet he runs a group called Mothers Against social distancing
I got arrested this year for allegedly threatened
You kill a bunch of people
This is a set-up
There's an awesome article advice by Mick lamoureux about his plan to
He's going to start a bunch
The Auntie mask schools
You might think that he was doing this with the money out of his like his own money because he's kind of heart disease charitable think so
GoFundMe
According to the article quote
In the enrollment agreement he shared apparent
Must accept that their kids might be taught by volunteer teachers with no personal accreditation
But with expert
Experience and education
That is a tough sell
Especially when you consider that in
Description section of the GoFundMe that he was using to start the schools
He misspelled public school as pubic
Welcome to Trump University because this is really fun here's another
From the article
Guy didn't respond to a detailed list of
Question said by Vice news about his project
Answer the questions were sent sky made several social media posts
Sabaton upcoming Vice news story about it
Hey what you implied I was a pedophile and George Soros directly ordered me to write this piece
Add shared my phone number to his followers
Cool guy
Yeah yeah
How do I give a flamboyant Auntie Mass character and he's got a cool neck tattoo so he's got a bit of online detention
For him until he's been hanging out with Alex a little bit
Thursday Island about
That is grounds for Parental divorce
If I've ever heard that would like if your parents are like a
We're sending you to Chris Sky school you can be like
I'm leaving you goodbye
I'm getting a divorce from my parents
So I can listen to
This guy cuz I don't really care
Beaches schools
On a press conference where he is
Peppered with questions about school in general I think Alex would give him the most
Adversarial interview on the subject but
I already interested anyway
If you just can be cookie
Qatar Auntie masks I can get that anywhere he's not that into
After he leaves
Baylor Medical
School comes
3 University
I've got clips of
Medical school
Top heads
Coming out and saying what shots are deadly don't do it it's a disaster
All these other top scientist
I probably watched
I'm just clips of medical doctors and scientists not track down there
Curriculum vitae
74% of the new covid cases
I don't like how the first step of his research was
They're not an imposter
Yep yep checks out Alyssa
Look at the picture ID
A real person
Also on the same show that he's leaving his reporting on the story from Finland with a tweet
So great
That 7 hours is paid off
Awesome
I still don't know what's going on with this Baylor situation I'm interested
I'm interested I want to know what he's talking about
You got me on the hook
So Alex talks about one of the things
That he does best
My predict
He believes they predict
The best way to wake up the sheeple out there because they come true
And then blow mine
And it's really convenient to do whenever you don't bring up all the things you've been
Massively wrong about
Trouble
It's really easy to make predictions
And get them wrong and then still claim your right whenever you never face consequences for your actions
Easy to be a sniper when you are allowed to use like carpet bombing
Absolutely everything around Pawtucket
Predictions are King because
You're already awake if you listen you heard it you do your own research
The predictions I made in Chris kaimade and Mike Adams made
All of which were wrong
Okay when I see it
Otherwise people are buying them cheap
Exploit them emotionally
And then they'll wake up to the things that are true
I would say this
Bill Clinton
Ended up being the secretary-general of the United Nations
And then president of the United States again after
Hillary had a two terms
I would probably be freaking out that Alex called evaluate everything I've ever known about anyting ever
Fundamentally shatter by understanding of human beings
Forever
So yeah
Possibly a bike
We forget those bad
Pretend that these vague things
He said
Or Acura
People always like to go to those Nostradamus
Predictions that are a little bit vague and have plenty of room for interpretation however you want to do
You bet
So
Unfortunately I have bad news
Mike Adams
Amazon
But actually
Thinking about it and I kind of enjoy Mike Adams appearances now
Okay
I kind of understand him better
Okay just a dramatic
Like
Adolescent
Yeah he has
Almost I would say the emotional maturity of somebody who's
In
Maybe not a senior in high school
Like a junior he's one of those people who got rich enough where they don't have to grow up
I don't know I mean I'm sure he's responsible in like
She holds down whatever his
Is his businesses are inside
Play Ernie
I just think that he comes in and it's just everything is so over-the-top
And I kind of enjoy that
Is this fun narrative do that's going through the pandemic with him
Big Alex's best friend at the beginning right and then Alex tried to see if he could hang out with David I could David Icke was saying that there was
Is norovirus right back Adam got mad and went away for awhile
Now he's back at I wasn't hanging out with David Icke anymore
Jesus
There's just a weird fun high school thing going on with you
Frustrated with this Betty bulshit also comes along with High School drama
It also David Icke still has a section on Alex's website where he is
Posting videos
For no one to watch about how there is no virus
Which is great I'm glad platforming app
I do
Temp sensor anybody
I got you could he's much more easily with David Icke
But Nick Fuentes
I think
Anyway
A year ago
You may recall Mike Adams on coming to
Fragrant
What year ago
They're saying hospitals were full
Yes they were
Is Welch
Right but now
They are
The hospital
Cheer
I've got friends and family organ ospital. Crew twerking Hospital
Full of people dying
Inoculated
They've done it now here
This this is this is an interest
Sing reality that that he has us living in
No
I reject it
I rejected entirely this is unfair
F*** that f***
That so hard
F*** that
We remember that Mike Adams
Escalated over humanity and there would only be Lone Survivor
A ways back
He hasn't Newport
That made
Rival
I don't know
Deescalate from it's over for Humanity
A little bit silly
I'll sit here right now today
Events have already been put into place
Going to see millions of people dead
In the next 12
36 months
Because of these vaccines
And it cannot be snowy
Many people today are Walking Dead
It cannot be stopped
What a predictions events have been put into commotion there you know it within the next couple years
Millions Dead from the vaccine
That would still be way better than if we didn't have the f****** vaccine
Conceivably
It also
Is outrageously inaccurate
I would guess this is one of the predictions that is going to go in the
Bill Clinton as Secretary General basket
Open forget we did
This morning they're going to let that one go
So
Mike blue my mind
For a little while
He seems to think
But there's a bigger
2 plan
Going on
Bright
All these news reports that are coming out about how people are vaccinated can
Still you know the Delta variant might be transmissible
Find it the really trying to
The trying to cause
The tried to cause a reaction
The reason they've done this and the reason that they've admitted now
Over the last week
Vaccines
Don't work
And that they're causing
Of these so-called Delta
Want
Uprising
In America
This is bait
They want an uprising even among those who were vaccinated and then are now
Angry and coming to their senses and saying
They want a massive uprising
Cuz they need adjustment kaisha
Foreign military
Martial law
Crackdown
In order to cover their tracks
Because their entire
Globulus system is about
To employ
And many of them are going to go to pray
Prison order
Tried under Nuremberg 2.0
Yazoo apparently apparently
They are telling
Everyone that the vaccines don't work in order to
To try and get people
Go to
Freak out
Sandra Bell
The Maccabees put down by a military coup or some sort of
Martial law
Distract from
The fact that
Tabaxi
Don't working
I don't know
A really sophisticated people if that's what we're dealing with we're dealing with
Genius is a fun story
Not
It's not that funny story
Define
Story
I wouldn't read it
What kind of Uprising over there what kind of Uprising is a look
Looking for you know like do they have a boot
Teak Uprising that they want that would be optimal for them or do they do they want more like a
Graduated in
Insurgency kind of thing do you know that burning down a police station isn't enough to bring in martial law so I don't
I don't know what they're trying to
I mean not even
Trying to overthrow the government installed martial law
Yes
Anyway
Mike believes
That if you've been back
Vaccinated
And this is actually something he's been saying quite a bit
I remember hearing him say
Even though our ways back
He's basically like
You're a biological weapons Factory
The people who been vaccinated are walking
Intubation vessels
Weapons
It's all happening on
Purpose
Therapy injections which are highly illegal
That's right that's right
Hellboy
Better not better.
Explore this logic to its to his conclusion
Where is for the sake of protecting everyone you might have to kill vaccinated people
Scrape
They're there at this place now we're there
Like they've taken Karl rove's
Do you know that that
Turn a strength into a week
Miss that Swift boat kind of thing you know you're a veteran so
Destroy that credibility
They have just turned that on reality itself
Just a come
Complete like
If you're vaccinated you're the one who's incubating the virus and spreading it see hahaha it's definitely not
All of us unvaccinated people who spread it around all the time because we don't even f****** believe that it
Spreading the disease
What's work with Jerome corsi for years voters
Rex attack on reality
Right at the
Face of reality not trying to avoid it or even allow for it to come into a
So f****** intense
So I gave Mike a little bit too much
Credit too early
I told you that he was blowing my mind
Those clips that played or not blowing
They weren't doing much
We're going to get into
Mike bring some heavy s*** here
You might notice
Littlest woke
Corporation
All these corporations that are like really
Woke
We'll have the ones
The donated to Trump campaign
No other kind of
Okay they're making their employees get back
Yes that's very welcome
The real shocker here has have you noticed over the last week
All of the so-called
Woke Corp
Reparations
Have now demanding mandatory vaccines among their own workers so we're talk
Google Twitter
Disney Walmart even the Washington Post and many other corporations like that
They know that they are ordering the VAC
Maxine Slaughter of Their Own
People
And you ask why why would they do that well at Google and particular
And by the way Zack has been explaining all of this
Google
Humans have been
Teaching
Google machine Learning System
AI systems for the last
5 years
How to no longer need humans in the loop
Thompson moderations Corporation
Lower the drawbridge
Always gets executed by the army that takes over
I got to say I think
I think that might be the first time you stood up laughing
I was a big one one got you I wasn't ready for it I want ready for it
I wasn't ready for him to respond to that like the Twisted of sci-fi movies
Show Melania
Ocean's 11 where they reveal the Bland of the end what are you guys talking
Corporation employees with vaccinations
Or
You could kill the ball
Okay
Okay interesting strategy from Google we're going to see how this one plays out going forward
Deserves an
Whatever
Hi Mike cool cool
Anything else
The globalists are now
Acting as if
They have knowledge of
Global level
Mass extinction
For threat
Probably one that they're going to unleash
They want to make sure that there are billions
Human beings around
When that happens
Because they can't
Control billions of people
When people realize they've been lied to
And they been poisoned
And they're being killed
Third-dimensional chance
Very desperate
Yeah but my apologies I
I do tend to just leap ahead because you and I have a knowledge base and your listeners have
Set the average American
Is just clueless
What about soy
Look man we are so smart
But sometimes I go a2c on you like a way out improv troupe
Big leaps
Oh man
So I was a little
Confused
Yeah
Thankfully Mike
Mike is it does nothing is not a teacher clarify this
Let's just say
Giant asteroid we're going to hit the
Never going to happen in
Tell the people
No
They would never tell you
You wouldn't know until you see it in the sky a giant
Flaming Mountain
In the Book of Revelation
The reason I wouldn't tell you is because the globalist need
The infrastructure
So they can
Continue to stop
Pile food
Fuel and all the things
Teton there private islands and underground cities okay and everything
BattleBots
They have everything now
They have it all
If they told people that
Everybody Woodstock
Everybody would go home
And decide you know how I want to spend my last 500 Days on this
Probably with
Family or something.
Oh my God
We can infer
From their behavior
Why are they going to the private
Why are they
Building underground tunnels
This is wild
This is watching nine-year-old argue over a book report that neither of them did
Describe his authority
Experiment is if you're like likes experimenting with
He's really trying
He's playing third dimensional chess I will say that
The bike the globalist
Never tell the public in an asteroid we're going
Going to collide with
The Earth because they need infrastructure.
Continue to exist
Until the last minute so they can
Can stockpile resources and their bunkers are whatever
If they told people you know with all in the public that they had x amount
A time before imminent demise
People just stopped working
Families which would hurt the globalist ability to get those last minutes
Supplies they apparently need in their bunker
Wow
Parts
What what a great
Like here's the best part of that
Is the best part of that they truly believe that and extinction level events
What it would be like
Listen guys
We got to wait
Three business days before the money transfer over there
We can't end the world yet
My food is
Oh God we got to wait till the world ends hold off
Push it back supposed to be in my bunker without
Fresh fruit
Oh my God
Fortune reception is all I have in my bunker right now do you really think I'm going to live out the end of the world with that no
It's it's amazing Jesus
Simultaneously though this entire show and makes initial Point has to do with public messaging around the pandemic shifting to the globalist
Submitting that the vaccines don't work in that everyone's going to die
According to bikes only thought experiment the globalist are acting in a way that they never would if a disaster
Truly working
This s***'s about to go really bad and if that's
The case there would be stories about breaks
Suitcases on the Delta Varian
Stop I don't under
Understand and honestly
This stuff is the most infantile nonsensical garbage
I do kind of like listen
Link to this
Alex and him really seem like they're having a good time that's a problem they're both they're both like
Bouncing off each other like a great bulshit we're sitting right here this is the good stuff
Nothing like
To blow each other's minds
You don't want Alex says that someone's hit like
In this episode he says that like Mike Adams has a hook and always a farm here in Texas need a good friend
I believe that
Makes me sadder that he couldn't
Come on the show and Alex's pretend
Tecovas
Healthy to have a good time with each other anyways that like
Steve pieczenik is a power imbalance
Alex abuses a bunch of other guests
The talks over them and doesn't
Give them a chance
What's to say stupid s*** like Mike
I think human women like actually are probably friends yeah
Yeah he and Mike have the relationship that Owen thinks Alex and Owen have
Yeah
But Alex knows that Owens is little baby boy
Cohen can't reflect my camp
Coming up with this good stuff
Never going to get up
Mike has more thought
And out why do they not care that they are at
Absolutely destroying the rep
Mutation
Of the CDC
Vaccine industry who
Itself
Answer because none of those things
Existing their plan in a few years
Anyway
Okay so then
The next couple years all this stuff is going to be gone according to their plans and dollar is gone
This is like the grand unified field theory of s*** I don't know
That's just what they're just like okay all the stuff that I don't know I don't think they care about the banks isn't that crazy
Do you think I've ever heard anybody say they're not concerned with the reputation of the thing I've been
Smearing for years
Insane
Insane level of s*** where they can say this and their brains don't
Explode
It's mind-boggling unfair it is it's unfair
Great transition what are the things
We do these episodes in 2000
And one of the reasons I want to know if Alex
Thought he was fighting the literal devil in 2000
And the reason that I want to know that
Is because he's made it abundantly clear that he does
Enterprise absolute
And stuff like this
I just want to
Throw a brick at
My computer
Fleming's other analogy
2 years
And they just got a deal they get the spaceship but they don't kill us quietly and
You know I'll make sure nobody wakes up and then challenges
They're acting like
Everybody's dead
Unless they basically call us off
Can't talk behind that I'm not saying that this is what the what's going on to what they believe he's a
Illicitly multiple
Multiple-time said that this is what's going on
The devil is behind the globalist to give them their marching orders
Bulshit
B b
Come on man
No no
The cats out of the bag of toothpaste out of the tube you think you're fighting the f*** it saddle
Let me with anything that isn't ultimately about the devil trying to corrupt
Don't try and like
Retain some veneer
Some credibility of like no I don't actually think I'm fighting the devil
It's like a dignified the devil
So now
Predictions
Yes
That's how you blow the mind of the sheeple
Mike
Has
Some
Prediction
I have have it on
Bad Authority that he's on fire today
These are
Not good prediction
I'm intrigued by this
I'm trying to shut up
Short Circuit
You know you're in trouble when Alex starts ends with this
Clearly when there's bars a million dying which is already starting to happen
They're all going to go to prison they're all going to get destroyed unless they know something even bigger coming
Add a magnitude much bigger than this you agree
The most likely scenario to primary scenarios what I think's going to happen I'm sure both of them would you hear the first one
Talk about
Fastbreak
Where they're going to engineer a
Collapse
Freezing of the entire global
King system
All transactions
Frozen
And then
Where's the dollar
Watching and then this will unleash
Which would justify
To come into the United
Actually, he's Chinese troops
Under the UN Banner you are
Humanitarian
Emissions
Scenario 1
Executions
AB concentration camps mass murder
That's even
For those who survived the vaccine
Okay so that's
Option one
Wow
Let's Be Cops
Sure
Collapse of the dollar
Troops under the the the guise of you of any folks
Execution
Tina this is also point out that if
We Believe other things Alexei
5/6 of your immune system will also be wiped out everyone will basically
Be dead
I don't know
Probably trying to
Spin a few too many play
The thing of the thing about it is isn't it like you do I get if you're listening to the show and sometimes you see a coincidence
Playing in the Twisted in your like maybe Alex is right about the
This sometimes or something like that
But if you're listening the show would you hear that why aren't you just like
What the f*** are you talking about
What cuz the cuz
Horse from any contact you don't need any contacts for you to just listen to that and go
That doesn't make sense
. even in my conspiracy world and Jordan what if I were to tell you that that clip I just played
From Mike was 5 years old
Same thing
I would not know it's from this episode.
Things all the time
When you said what if I told you was 5 years ago my first thought was
That makes sense
Dammit Daniel
It would not be impossible
Select the first scenario scenario
Is a little bit underwhelming
When that's the first scenario
A second scenario
Remember this is a very Dynamic situation this
Also play out
Is that
Gearing up
Flip the script
And say
Oh my God
These are true
Vaccines that are killing everybody
Trump operation warp speed
Push
Pharmaceutical companies
He puts the FDA in the CDC for emergency authorization
Going to say
Trump's a mess
Killer
From the vaccines
But the rest
Watching it
Lego future ex-wife saying don't trust him
Yep
Exactly but he was lying all the time
This is making the other scenarios at 80%
Scenario
They are trying to then save
Vaccine industry
Play the CDC by
By turning against Trump
I'm putting all the blame on Trump
Again this is that same a narcissism like this month
Must be about my hero
Wow
I hate Trump as much as the neck
Text person
Probably
Maybe a little bit over average
I think that it would be ludicrous
To imagine people blaming any problems with the vaccine on Trump
To imagine that he had any direct
Involvement with the medical
Outside of doing things
That he should have done
Like
Benno buying
Surplus about to vaccines in order to make sure
That they would become available
The expedited process isn't
Things like that probably should have done more but
Gordon liquid imagine that there is something that
Comes about that is a
Expect
Consequence
The unforeseen
I don't
Think that anybody
In the right mind would blame
No
That would be a fundamental
Lack of understanding of
Let's say
Cause of death
Sure
I know a guy with a lot of examples
Might clear that up
First scenario is kind of fun
On Thursday
Dunno door-to-door executions as its Financial collapse
Sure. We could use the Alex in this but I'll let it go
Xcite Hotel
What's Argon
Definitely be still in play if we're going door-to-door
There is an excitement
Into this
In terms of like a sci-fi movie plot should I enjoy it
It'd be bleak
B shot
It's dark
Cormac McCarthy could write everybody would be dirty
Might get nominated
The second scenario
Trying to save
Science
By blaming the vaccines failures on
Trump
Trump was mixing up the vaccine with a spoon
Borderline Trump was
Going to view the factory where they make the vaccine and he like elbow something stuck up to a giant f****** sister beans
About
I just think this is what a kid would say
This is so stupid
It's so sad
It's so sad that you acted
It's on it's unfair
For me
And it's unfair for them like the imbalance of
Ability to interact with reality
Ezion fair you know like it's it's
It's a privilege in some ways to just be able to go outside and see
Look
There is a street
That's what it looks like and that's what it is
And they don't have that
Did Street probably hate Trump
Ligature
Get it
Sad
But we have our own sort of
Things we need to
Concerned about
Family that we live
City
Every major city in America what's this
Top picks in every city
Becomes a death
Zone
A war zone
Wallace chaos looting rate
Sandy that you can
They will be unsurvivable
If you're not bugged out of the city already or if you don't have a
Before this happened
It will become your tomb
And this city is going to be your tomb
Every time
He says
Every major
Every time
I mean it's
Everything that is going to happen
Will eventually lead to
Every major city Willock
Explode
At no point in time
I know playing time have these
Stiffy cities exploded
Now they just keep going
And sometimes their pockets of unrest
What happened with it
10 cities around
Particularly
Resident event but the cities don't end up
Becoming everyone
Cool Math
Or whatever I'll give you a good reason why
Everybody lives here so we don't want to burn it down
That is a piece of it I think
I don't really fully understand exactly what
This obsession
Comes from
This desire to f*** with people and make him leave cities like I don't know if it's
It's trying to like
Like if it's a long con
To try and get more population
Into rural areas
Greece representation
In the house
I don't know but I think it's just I think it's just that
Cities
AR
Less homogenized
Then
Rural communities let's just more than your head then it is actual advise anyone to actually leave the
The city he just wants the people he's talk
Can do who don't live in cities to look at
Cities as if they were deathtraps exactly
Play because they're not
But not all white
Yes I do
Really do believe that those there probably is a bit of that
Because every and growing up in rural Illinois to extremely religious parents is like
You get the constant drumbeat
Be of stories of people who went away to college you went away to the city
Come back and they have all these different ID
Ideas and stuff
And that's just
Because they meet
Non-white people
Give me people who aren't the same as them and they go oh you're still people cities are a
Visitation
Of looking at people who are different from you
And calling them
Your neighbor
Life experience or even just different ideas
As your peers and
Equals
Yeah yeah
Better is a piece of that
So Micah goes on his merry way and
I mean look
It wasn't his best outing
But I honestly think
The realization that I had of like
You guys actually are friends
I think that's fun
The juxtaposition of those two scenarios is unacceptable
It sucks it does seem like one of them he put all of his eggs in one basket
The other one was very under-baked
Yeah it's like somebody who's like all right I got to pitch meeting in the morning
Nothing up all night getting this elaborate
Plot for one at Main.
Is it going
Half an hour laying out this
Detailed scenario on the second one
Guy falls in love actually going to pick up that one
Little disappointed you kind of
UE
You know maybe we were going to pass on the
Second one anyways but now I think we're going to pass on both. Get out of here like
Alex talks about the people who got the first
People who got the
Pfizer shot
He might be wrong about
Call screen
Watching them snuff
Oh my God
The first person who got 250 shot
The first man
Okay you know you did say that
The first man to get the Pfizer shot you know what his name was
William Shakespeare
I wish I was making that up that's really was Bill Shakespeare in the UK
Swear to you I would have turned him away
Could be the first
You can be number two
This is not we're not going down in history as Bill Shakespeare being the first to get that f****** back safe
The conspiracy theorists have a field day with us
This was last December and he did not die of month later
He passed away in May of this year of an unrelated Illinois
How to dress fudging the details of this stuff because he knows that the reality these stories isn't salacious enough to justify his abs
Search injectors
Calling this
I f******
Snuff film
Ridiculous
Course the first people to get the vaccine we're also the ones
Closest to dying
Anyway
I read about his passing away
It was one of
He was incredibly proud of being able to be a part of
And it's just a real tragedy to see
Granted Alex
Know his name but he's not really piss merch
His memory
That much prettiest still using his death
That's gross he's exploiting somebody who who really believed that what they were doing is right
You're one last clip years has Alex decides
The end the show
Again
Brick
Through the computer
Sunday live in the ocean until Sunday but Sunday lights the next 2 hours
I'ma come back and play all those.
Collapse
Medical Dean
You were coming I'm single shots on safe
This is big
After Club
F*** you
Actually Jordan we've run out of time we are going to talk about those clips that I was played on the other show but we're going to
Have to do it another bill actually you
Spent so much time with those clips
That you have
Too much information to impart
How are you
Facebook
So transparent
It's legitimately so
Embarrassingly
Clear what he's doing
And it is like okay there is a sea
Sensational headline that I'm going to
Teased throughout the show
That is broadcast on
Some radio station
In order to actually cover the story or whatever I'm going to force people to get it on my own platform
8 some of this away from
My own
Market
Or maybe part of that I don't know if it is necessarily but like
I did notice when I went to his website but there is a lot more my pillow ads on the other website
Maybe maybe not on radio shows
But on a on his website Mike lindell's seems to be getting
Involved
And advertise
Oh man that's like him
Okay
I got this clip that's going to prove everything over to say Ed brother
All right and then
You you want to hear it okay
Petco Coco
I don't have to do it but
Yeah
Really really frustrated
And I hate it
Every scene the strategy
Play out like
A bit
This this this weird like the other show
That's so annoying. I hate it
So you know this episode was was
Was real dumb
You mean like
One of the things I find very fascinating is the
This
Idea
That Alex had
First of all done
6 hours of research
And somehow got dizzy because he had so much
Information or whatever
Any gets on Aaron one of the primary sources
Diseases is a
Thumbs down time to find that tweet though
Thumbs down
Even did
20 minute
Of preparation for the show he could have found the underlying report that tweet was referencing
And not been a guy who's reporting on a tweet it would not have been her
That would have been probably the thing that anybody would do take care
Anybody
And then he talks to me
Mike Adams
About bulshit
Forever but they
Phone
He's talking to that weirdo from Canada
Who wanted to start a weird school should he doesn't talk about the Weird School
He doesn't have time to get to Spanish
I'm sorry I was having fun
Riffin with my buddy
About imaginary scenarios that
Can't happen.
It's just unacceptable if you imagine
That he's serious about us
Like if you ask
Actually think that he thinks there's value in getting these stories to people
This is
Nonsensical
But on the other hand if you recognize that
He knows that the entertainment value was having like Adam scare people right
Then you kind of get the like o this is what Drive sales as opposed to
People being disappointed by
New stories not living up to the way your t
It's it's him not
You know it's like
In the
The way we view it
If you cared about your show
Then you would
Take the things that you say
Evan
If you cared about your joke that would work on it
You would prepare for it you would make sure things sounded good you would get a staff that can
F******
Keep your phone calls on are all of those things I would honestly suggest that if Alex
Approve the things that he claims he could prove
He has a moral response
Possibility
To do his job
Like you do
Just have like
Of the financial incentives
It is a n
Imperative
But he do it
If you can't
And he doesn't
Auntie
Here's the bigger here's the biggest
Alright
Because he can't
Won't and lies about it
Right
Then it becomes our moral imperative to f******
Talk about it he's making us work for him that's what it happening
Open system of morality
Because we think about it that way
It's nice to have a boss again
I feel a little bit Rusty
See this time visible longest time we've gone without recording an episode or seeing each other for a while
I feel like I'm a little off my game I'm excited for next episode of think we'll be a little bit more in the groove
A little bit
Feeling happy is good to do the show it's good to get back home for sure
Absolutely it's one of those things
Man
Vacations great but when you really love what you do
God if you miss work
Weird
I mean.
It's because I don't do much
I can't wait to get back to the office where I do nothing
Hey
When you get a good job you can't be jealous of it real
Oh you're going to kill me now
Where will be back
Back on Friday
We do have a website about right.
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight and I go to bed Jordan
We are
Local charity or bail Fund in your area to help out people
Doing God's work
I am emotionally unbalanced
Stand Moody General Patton
Giving a very wishy-washy speech
Alex
Birthstone colors