Damn important
I have great respect for snowledge b b
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Everybody look like knowledge around
Where's the altar of Sweeney
But about Alex Jordan
Question for you what's up
Today I guess
Is Ivy
Watching Laura Survivor
This is going to be for nobody but myself I guess
Survivor Gabon
Okay and there was a guy named Bob
Country Bob's the map
Kabob okay
So he's a physics teacher and he wears his buff like a bow tie
Dumbass
Alright
Looks just like an old
Nate Burrell
A friend of ours
The comedian okay have a great dude he looks
I'm picturing it and yes I can see it looks like an old physics teacher Nate Burroughs with a bow tie
Delivered
Gabon
It's so weird
Some reason Nate Burroughs is a person that I can age in my head
Instantly like I just see it I was watching the season
Instantly was like this
Is my guy I realized
Solberg yes I enjoyed that
Finally saw the movie event of the summer F9
Okay
Furious 9 little bit of a John Cena can I watch Suicide Squad
John Cena was also into a Scott Suicide Squad
Back-to-back and I was like maybe they're in the same movie I don't know if that could be
It could be shared Universe fantastic but I do have one huge problem with it
When am I
Obviously this is not
Spoiled if you went into this not knowing the Tyrese
Go to space
Wow
They go to space
Would like the record to show that I didn't
Spoiled that was all George
You didn't they go to space alright
And then they get rescued in the movie lineup at the drive to the space station
That is the wrong move 100% what they do
They sacrifice themselves Armageddon style during the regular movie
Post credit scene
Oxygen-deprived
The Russian Space Station
Can pick some up that's fast
After Furious 10
Luda and Tyreese
Fighting again
It's the Toretto family
I was thinking that a good way that they could have done it is just like
Leave them out of the red
Cast of the movie Emma
After credit scene
The two of them bickering in a car in place
I got cuz I would have been
Good comedy movie where they like
Not worried about it
Then they have the whole fourth-wall-breaking character Shield Banterra that's always annoying but
What you going to do
I enjoyed it but the further I get
Get permit the amor
The excitement about it where's the
The f*** off
F****** know you are God
God dammit
So Jordan today we got an episode in the old present day when we talkin about August
Fifth
Cornmeal
Yeah this is Thursday's episode from last weekend I decided I would check and see how things are going
The baby seem like we have some bad things happening
Within the next week for and
I regret to inform you of some of these things
Say hello to some new Wong call that's a great idea
The first met Godzilla thank you so much
If blank
I'm a policy wonk thank you very much
Morbid mediocrity thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Disseminate
Thank you so much
Journal
I'm a policy wonk disseminate bills
Thank you so much
Also out there I got a little bit of an adoption certificate from well
Basil or basil
Opossum
What a great addition to celine's family
Fawlty Towers was at John cleese's characters might have been something like that
Either way also
Come to the family basil or basil the opossum
Lovely contact drops
From Today Show here is the first one
Of Christianity is a very flawed
Ohio
Quit riding the Moonlight Sonata
Is that Beethoven urbach or god dammit
Why don't I remember anything while he was up in space
That's what they were think
That's what they were thinking
Somebody's
Bulshit
Like maybe a valance cover good from a commercial break
Instrumental just music and then
The human implementation of Christianity has been deeply flawed
What you going to give it an extra lecture on the subject
So I hear that the other atacante
Little bit different in tone
What's the clear
Heterosexual
But but
What
Alright
Anyway
Restart this off here and
I generally don't get too excited
About Alex's shows
He's going through the motions
A lot of times
There's nothing nothing too exciting when he said this I was like
I cannot wait
Does he what he does
Country
Barnesville Beyond
Talk about the legality of the big announcements I'm about to be
Okay what the fuc
Fucken up
Okay baby announcements I'm going to make
Rmp
Whether they are legal
We need Barnes to come in here and weigh in on whether or not what I'm going to do it
I heard that
Yes
We absolutely do not have nor bad
Determine whether that would have
Is legal
You wouldn't do that again
Uno
I hate to break this to you
I want to be like a weird
Artisans
Not deliver a payoff supper
Isn't anything too
Barnes going to be in
Bounties are League
Let's begin
So here is the big news
Did Alex leave
The show with
Infowars.com
Show
Headline
For the broadcast today
And this is a pretty big deal
And somebody might want to listen
Exclusive I'd known as Nationwide lockdown on August 11th
First saw Jack Purcell
Definitely
Us intelligence agencies by the naval intelligence
He said the shatter is there looking to do it on August 11th
All that
2 weeks ago
So we got to August 11th
Biden's going to put
Country into lockdown to look forward to
Premier future and I've been recording this on the 8th
Yeah we got a few days only a few days that we would be
Well it may actually be
It might actually be and there's actually
A secondary
Conspiracy that Alex has to weave
Is instrumental in
Surprise Walk Around Heaven
Federal
Emergency Management agency and the Federal Communications Commission
Internet takeover drill
EAS alert
On the
I'm a type of guy
But knows when to do something that big
They're going to have radio TV station owner engineers
Do test before
Make sure it also knows out of their platform
Cuz I've been ready on TV 27 years I know how that works
Asian phone calls
And they said indeed they're told there's something big coming on the 11th
I do enjoy the fact
For that first step that. That other Cliff we we we just heard we both have such little respect for
We didn't even need to address the fact that he's being listed
It is one of the sources
In terms of this deal we got this this emergency alert
What's going on
That's going to be the the flash-bang okay be like we're now in a lockdown
Tabac in June
They were going to run a drill of the emergent
The alert system on August
What's going to happen on that date is basically as follow
Consumers who have opted into receiving text messages on their wireless devices for emerge
Warnings will receive test
Emergency warnings
But say this is a test
Of the national wireless emergency alert system
No action is
As needed
A secret code for
Yeah let's say it is
Simultaneously there's going to be at the
The bear
Or the standard emergency alert system with a
This is a test type messaging broadcast on radio in
TV providers
This is scheduled to last about 1 minute
Starting at 2:20 p.m. Eastern and it is not a takeover of the internet
So what is it Alex's starting this
Conspiracy Jag that he's you know
Getting into early and they're talking about how there's going to be another lockdown
I'm starting on August
But then like
Biden
I'm going to take over the airwaves that day and that
That's martial law
I don't know how scared
I mean what's he going to say
Just like lockdown
That's not that big of a deal if he overrides all communication
Since devices in the United States then well he's going to declare martial law
And I think Alex does later at clarify that he's also
Climate
There's going to be a whole bunch
Just a feeling on.
Things to make and apparently
The military of the military
Captain resources last night
Yes they're told Biden will make a big announcement on the 11th
Well
Anytime
Insurrection as within calling protest
I can tell you that
Whitehouse is writing a speech right now it will be on the 11th
Okay alright
B o u g
Just talked to Jackie
But this all coming
Just from
So when Alex is doing here it is painfully transparent to preempt
Do storyteller
He knows fully well there's a large faction of qanon weirdos and Maga dead-enders who have convinced
Themselves it's something big
Is about to happen
There's a considerable contingent that believes the Trump
Is going to be reinstated as president on August
13th
Friday the 13th
Very powerful day for the Illuminati numbers
Much of this is based on random online bulshit that's gotten out of hand
Of course the meddling of Alex's new sugar daddy Mike Lindell
The my pillow guy
Since the 2020 election Mike
Has been banging an incoherent drum but how he had absolute proof that the election was
Stolen
He's released multiple entirely unconvincing an easily debunker
Couple documentaries that he claims lays out all the
Approved for everyone
Sleep
And for the last few months
Contracted
Attention for his beak
Cyber symposium
What's taking place
August 10th through 12th
In Sioux Falls
Mike has insisted that the information and evidence
He's going to reveal that event is go
Can be so convincing that this
Supreme Court will vote 920
Put Trump back in
The office I am excited for that day
Leaving aside that there's no cost
Digital mechanisms
To do this there's also a huge problem that Mike them that s*** for evidence
Is it going to be an embarrassing
Flop
What how does that day go
John Roberts is coming out just like hey
Trump's the president now
That's what we could
I imagine it would be like the Vatican
Well we got to give it to I don't want to believe you
So the fact that this is going
To be a disaster and a flop
Mike
Can't prove anything
Machine of the extreme right-wing from getting into action
A lot of these folks
Are fairly excited
You might remember when they stormed the Capitol Building to try and stop the election results
Certified cuz they believe that if they did that
Staying power
Every month the media tries to
Make that a year
An extra gear in the past
Alex knows all about
She knows all of these angles
Mike Lindell pays forever
Advertising time on his show
Like he's a he's an idiot
But he's not an idiot
Sure sure sure
They're people who are actually holding out hope that the
His last-ditch Hail Mary attempt
Truthout is going to
And when it doesn't
They won't realize that my
Proof is b*******
Still insist that the Hail Mary didn't work
Because the game is
To Rick
Desperate people mixed with disappointing
Making a volatile results
And that's why the dhs's warning that they've seen quote
An increase in calls for violence online type to election-related
Conspiracy theory
They're warning to law enforcement entities didn't include any information about
What specific threat but it did say that quote
The timing of these activities may occur during August 20
Folks folks
You know how they did all that s*** in the lead-up to the first time they tried to overthrow the government
The same shift happening now some of that same talk has happened I know the results
I'm paying and getting the same results
The combination of the election based nonsense
Conspiracies about the emergency alert drill
Combine to make this weekend
Murky
A key.
Personally I'm not overly convinced anything's going to happen but I do think the ingredients are all there for
Trouble
Nothing may happen
But the universe is true also
Something may happen
And what we see on the show gears Alex attempting
Infront of appetite
Centrally harmful story
If you pay close attention to Alex to see him do this kind of thing a lot because
The really powerful strategy
Strategy to use when you
Kind of want to make domestic terrorism more likely want to pretend that you're not doing that
All I'm saying is that if these people don't get exactly what they want which is a 90 Supreme Court decision they will almost
Certainly commit acts of violence
And since we and everybody else
Knows that
I'm just going to let you know it's a false flag before it happened
I mean Trump being made president again
This coming weekend
Is being
Told to
A section of the Bible
This is what you're entitled
If you do not get this
This is not America anymore violence
Supreme Court
So I
You know
Mike lindell's
Wasn't coming around quite a bit
He's been showing up on the show and I noticed there was an influx
Soap commercials
On Alex's show
And now apparently they're running
On the Genesis Communications Network
Hello I'm Mike Lindell and I'm coming to you with the most important commercial that I've ever done
The last 5 months
It might efforts to bring the truth forward
Cyber Symposium on August 12th
The runs the commercial for his cyber
Kristen poziom
Does he still sell s***
Yes
Really feel like the whole
Prison is part of his
Not existed anymore
Why what is happening
I don't know it's going to be a new marketing strategy like the CEO of temper
Eric is going to start coming out and being like
Brazilian
I find
It's very strange
Yeah I do know these still selling stuff OB
Because Alex
I have a promo code
But he gives out multiple times man for my pillow
It was really fun because he's like
All of you out there listening know what my pillow and myself have been through in the last year
So we knows now that
Biden is going to declare martial law by way of taking over the airwaves
On the 11th
Of course I'm here's where we get to the
Climate emergency of it all
I have this friend
Research
Because I know what the club of Rome and what
So I can tell you what to do
Climate emergency
20 years
How many senators
Governors
Move it to the 14
We're talking right now
6 days
Roblox
And all the suicide
Bankruptcy
Do like
I don't know what Alex imagine
Would need to go in
Into the implementation
Mission of like
Elegiac
Martial law thing because back on a William like 3 days
Pretty important for organizing a lot of this stuff
It also still has to be on the f******
Can highways before we can get there the reason why he's doing that is B
Because this is all bulshit
And
He needs to also create a backdoor for himself to slip out of
That's great he brought attention to it so now we averted it
Very specific prediction Elizabeth doesn't
Come through
Hooray
Trump doesn't become president but
They made a deal with Biden
To stop a second locked
That's my that's my guest narrative or maybe to avert
The climate of her
Something like that
So Alex
Get this mother
News
He's talking about how like they
Things are really bad
But there is a way out
There's a way out of some headlines
Is it over like really inspiring as one of them
I got several articles together that illustrate the way out of this
Let me show you these articles
Few days ago zerohedge.com build is the biggest newspaper magazine in Europe
Apologizes for fear-driven coverage
I'm coming
And says the police are beating men women and children this is all overblown the numbers were much exaggerated what
PCR test for fake we apologize we were wrong
I thought I thought I would have heard about that
So this is about Julian
They do have the highest circulation of a publication in Europe at least that's what they build themselves as okay
Definitely not the most
Respected Outlet
It's a right-wing nationalist tabloid
That isn't really all that
That all
It's a prop for American extremists like Alex
Text to use because he knows his body
Has no idea what publishing is even like at all in Europe
Pieces of paper is the most respect
Adele just
I love the idea of a far-right tabloid because in my head it's like
Marine Le Pen who she dating we've seen her at the beach with me
Also this story isn't new
Julian's comments were made back in May but I assume Alex just a viral tweet about them now so it's
Kind of like it
Just happened
The video was Julian apologizing for this
Play Snow coverage of covid
Particularly in regards
Stew Howard effect
Two children
I have no idea if he's talking about his own coverage or everyone else's but honestly
I care about this just about as much as I would if the editor-in-chief of the Sun
I had made these comments
I don't care I don't care
Transcript I can find his comments there's no match
Should have any of the stuff Alex's
Talking about
PCR test being fake
I'm telling you what the
These are counted as details of the story that
Galaxy
Does adding into these
Comments this guy made three months ago in order to make
Get fit into the narrative but he's already selling
Imma to it also I'm going to give
This is a free piece of advice for Alex
Before you f*** around
Drawing book
This dude does Julia know that guy from build as a gas
Alexandra know that on January 7th
Julian wrote an op-ed titled the quote
Donald Trump will live in Shanghai
Baby travel
You know I do appreciate Alex trying to give us a little bit of an uplifting news you know like hear the way here's the way
Too many broadcasts are always so depressing like I like to read the intercept
What is the most depressing thing in the history of the world do you know like give me a give me a positive
Way out
What story every noun
The editor-in-chief of this tablet is apologizing for covid coverage
You should know about
Build okay I don't know you know this
Snowcap there the mouth of the establishment
I don't know
Type of activity of people that are in the system
I mean build at the end of World War II
What
Paper
Everybody
The Germans ever really got control of
Build is the mouth of the established
Why would it be saying that because
I don't know
Alex's saying it billed as the mouth of the establishment
Because he has some
Comets
You asked him the day before the sepa
Episode who the mouth of the established
Boys I bet everything I own that he would not have said build
He would never have heard of you would have said Colbert FF
Yeah
Has the claim Alex is making the build was taken over by the OSS at the end of WWII and then was run by the CIA
I'm not sure where you pulling that from
I don't think it's a
Scrutiny
The first reason I'm skeptical of this is that the world war ended in 1945
Yes I remember that bill didn't exist
Until 1950
YouTube okay well it was after the war ended so I'm still going to give Alex that one
Also after the idea of the paper was run by the CIA I find this tough to believe to
The CIA actually release
Correspondence
Spies in the reading room from May 1982
Is a letter
Hey did we run your paper
You guys up to you having a good day it's a letter from Charles Wick
The director of the United States
Information Age
Agency William Casey
Event director of
The CIA
The letter was a request
For William Casey to be introduced
Do Alex
Axel Springer
The man who founded
Set build
When he was going to be visiting in Washington
Pretty clear from the letter that Casey did not know Axel Springer
Quote we look forward to hearing from you and to the pleasure of introducing you to a gentleman who is doing all he can
The strength of the ties between the United States and Europe
Bags
Picture of
True that Springer and early build had a pretty staunchly anti-communist stanchion
The Foreign Affairs they would align with folks like Reagan
Pretty close
Still not enough to establish a
Anyway the
The paper was run by the
The CIA
In fact it looks like
Pretty compelling evidence
That it wasn't
Accusations that the CIA funneled money to build early on
But there's no proof of this
Of the people pointing to the tabloids
Support for US foreign policy objective
But even that isn't
Something that's consistent
Any of his nonsense
But it's just
Fun I guess the height of the Cold War
American Spooks are just emailing f******
Newspapers like nothing suspicious about us wanting to meet you no big deal
Jesus Christ
I just think that Alex has an inability to prove any of this
I guess this is why three months ago
The editor-in-chief
Who bailed him out and apologize for
Sensational coverage
Covid
It's because they run by the CIA
Defecting and rice
Is the good news right
Good news
I think Alex a timeline quite
Fits with the
True no
But there's other good news
As a headline that's good news
I watched it last night
I got home after work
Bombshell
Freddy Fazbear whistleblower confirmed
Ginger poisonous bio-weapon
Dr. Andrew Kaufman
And she just goes over the patents
He's designing
So yeah I guess one of Alex's dum-dum 4th our hosts interviewed Karen Kingston
She's very excited
Very exciting if you heard of her
No have we talked about her before now.
So Karen works for Pfizer apparently but it was just as a quote
Marketing cardiovascular therapies to healthcare providers in Manhattan
Choosing sales and marketing about how much of the scientific end
Things like Alex and all the folks were trying to imply
Yeah I know those types you went around
Hospitals and she bought everybody love
Also she worked there from 1996 to 1998
If you were born after she left Pfizer there's a chance you can legally drink
Can the United States
Here has been making the rounds claiming that she's uncovered evidence
That the Pfizer in moderna shots
Contain a poison called graphene oxide
Reuters asked Pfizer about that and they said this is not
True
So here's an explanation of this whole conspiracy
Alright
Kingston laser research process of the interview which makes it easy to spot how and where
Either distorter
The information or arguing
Mint Restaurant
The messenger RNA and covid-19 vaccine
Is protected by a lipid nanoparticle layer that also allows it
A the non-nuclear Porsche
Turn of the South
These specific lipid formulations used by both Pfizer and modernity
Both include at least one chemical classified as a
Deg
Why why lated lipid
Regulated lipid
Such weapons have a polymer named polyethylene glycol added
Kingston's argument rest
I'm too deeply flawed to search
That the only company in the world that produces Pig liautaud
Lipid
Is the Chinese company called Cena pay
And
That documentation on Cena pegs website proves
The graphene oxide is present
In their products
Neither assertion however Bears any resemblance to reality
I think I think
Bobcat
Man has a video of Reagan getting Peggy
Alright
So
Yeah she's made this very
Varidesk
Connected argument about things that are in the vaccine
Hearing a large amount of things that I absolutely do not understand
But I hope somebody
Play this conspiracy has something to do I think even with like
5G stuff
It only makes sense
So I look forward to her being on the show
High level
+ 98
Marketing department
I do like the tenuous
Directions
Alex's pretty opposed
To the moratorium on is it
He thinks it's unconscious
Institutional
Or something
It's against the law
The CDC has no authority to do this
Yeah
Since when do they have the power they tell you how the other
Under civil emergency
The bacon do this
Martial law
Only abide this dictator
You see they haven't been officially implemented not all of them yet and that's what's going to start on January
January
Next year in my view the country going in the complete Banker
Obscene receivership
Fuel economy again put into cardiac arrest
August 11th
Declaration
Also declare war on fossil fuels
Drive anybody else
I think he said January by
And then he just
Additive
Betts Betts
Kind of Fantastic Beasts like I messed up and I said January
I could say August but I can never be wrong I think I'm going to have to I'm going to have to
Roll with it
What's a person's back to next year so I have to talk into the phone
Roll a die
High stakes for August 11th
Let's try this means anything if you could just make a
Speech A Day to Remember like either played stage
You got all these headlines out there all this news
The Delta very all day
Scary no one's talking about the real issue
What
Colorado
Vaccinated
To the Vudu app
Saban is the blaming
Non-vaccinated people
Force Delta
Sure everyone should be talkin about the
Play get really disagree
Route me to
So the media did actually very much
Cover the child who died in Colorado with you
Whose death was linked to the bubonic
Play
What are the reasons that you don't see the media going
Saying about it is because outside of some animals this is not a human outbreak of
Like Mike
Squirrels and chipmunks
But we got to be worried about
Because not enough
Okay let's go
Also it's something that's super treatable with modern medicine and most likely the reason this child died was because they can
Condition wasn't identified or diagnosed
Early enough
Is very sad
The plague is carried by a number of wild animals like
Like fleas and various rodents so you do end up seeing a few cases of people getting
Disease each year
Between 2010 and 20
2050 people tested positive for the plague in five of them
Media Outlets like CNN USA Today in Forbes all covered
The case of the child in Colorado but Alex is mad that they didn't
Continue covering
Recently didn't is because there's no reason
To continue to cover this story unless you're trying to use a headline to scare your audio
When a person gets the plague or God
I forbid they die of it
It makes sense for the media to cover
Because it's an interest
Story and it provides an opportunity
I need to teach the readers
Viewers a little bit about precautions that they
You should take around Wildlife sure what
Symptoms might
Indicate some
Kind of potentially very serious condition to useful story but is not one to use
Naive
After that revisiting the story over and over when there aren't any development
Is pointless
Counterproductive
Spread
Still not happening to a lot of people
TuneIn later absolutely
Are there easy separate but sort of related
Kids story that I actually came out
This past week and that is the
Mid South Lake Tahoe was closed
But for service
Have they found the plague was being carried by some
Some of the local chipmunk
This is a temporary thing
Camarillo
Just don't let you
Two dogs off
Police around
Areas where the plague could be endemic
Yeah it's hard
It's hard to do still
Get the plague
Harder than you might think
It can be done
Stampy
So we got some other
Some bad news out of the
East Coast
The Alex
Alex Hudson
Some breaking news
Play go no
Sure
It's your fault though
That's another story
10-second clip
Is his coverage of this story
Told You So This is an article out probably hasn't read about New York's
Excelsior pass
From the New York
State government website about the program
Quotes
Participation in Excelsior passes volland
At businesses and venues where proof of vaccination or a negative test is required for example at Large
Indoor venues that seat over 5,000 people
Individuals can always show alternate proof of vaccination or test results like another mobile application
Or paper form
These passes
Excelsior pass
They were rolled out in
So it's now
No it's more or less
What stores are naked
Covid test
Proof of vaccination of the QR code
The participating businesses
In stamps so they can effectively implement
Public Health precautions
Get to get into the Cubs
This isn't news at all in place and working
King pretty well for
The past five months the new news stories about the rollout of excelsior
Plus
Which is just the same app
But now it can also be read by businesses that use QR codes that are part of the smart health
Card app
The story here is just greater
Convenience
About to try to make this the mark of the beast
I'm afraid that boat sailed
Sale if it was in March
Is everybody dead
Antichrist
The headline as he's reading it is New York is rolling out vaccine pass
And by his definition I think they did
That
Months ago
Yeah
Hautboy alright sloppy work
So at this point the show Alex has a
This is actually pretty exciting to me because I put a clock on this
I I saw them rise to prominence
I guess they did a video that went viral
It's only a matter of time only a matter of time
And seapak
Fox
Censoring going on everywhere
But not here at the dreaded evil Infowars
So this is ivory
Hacker ivory
Jeezy was I guess a local Fox affiliate
General assignment reporter I know this lady yes she was definitely going on
Jesus from Houston she went viral back in June when she claimed that she was being muzzled and that she was taking
The proof to project veritas
Have you do it you did that in a live remote video
Release of her bombshell info got way less attention because it was just a
Sweet.
The most relations salacious of the revelations that you provided a versa
Censorship with a video
You captured of the assistant news director
Saying that he doesn't
Greenlight stories about B
Going because it's not something that would be relevant to the interest
Of their five viewing audience
Censorship
Don't know
Unlike Infowars
Just having anybody at the helm
Really poorly research pieces about Hydroxycut
Comfort their news director
To tell Ivory that
Quote failed as a report
Alright that's difficult it's all very embarrassing us expose lived up
Go to the O'Reilly's
Sensational buildup that they did with her going on air live
Yeah that's why Ivory's now on Infowars
Yeah that 11 viral marketing
Stunt isn't going to give you a career
Nope she took her shot it was an airball and now the only team desperate enough to give her time on the court is Alex
Lego very sad honestly for both of
Yeah yeah
I feel I feel bummed out
But also
A little by little
Laugh a book a single viral video star within a week of their
Viral video
You are low on the totem
Project needed the first bite at the Apple
Do they have the right
To release the video see any traction off it
But now she's at going into business
Versailles
And now she needs a whatever helps you
I can get today released a video James okay
Keith was like you have
Failed as a propaganda
Probably
So
What you working on
Plugs
This is live in about
But what you're doing right now how you're launching a new major operation today
Upload uncensored journalism there
I'm going to cover all the topic
Didn't want me to cover I made a Blog
Yeah but it's not just
Blog
The paywalled plug
Goddamn you go to her website there's no actual content on it it's just links
To get you to sign up so you can
Can see the contact
If you want to see the news that was
Was too hot for the local Houston Fox
Affiliate to cover
You have to pay $5 a month
Oh my God she is she is skipping a lot of steps or no
Is it going to work
Her website is just
The template offered by secureserver. TV
What is a platform designed to host
Sinalau direct monetization of
People's videos
They offer their services at a at a
Price like it's not a free service so
She needs to have a number of psoriasis
Drivers in order to offset the cost
For every business you start the first couple years in the red it just happen
She paid for hosting of all right
No shame that although it is
It is weird when you go you cuz you can find a bunch
Which of these different sites
Better all through secure server.
TV show
Jordan sather
The Cuban on weirdo in Legion
Okay I'll disown and they all look at
Exactly the same sure the landing pages all look identical
They can that get you to sign up
You know you don't go into right-wing propaganda if you want to work
I think this is one of these Sammy
Popular platforms that the people who've
Kicked off YouTube inside
Are using
I don't know
If having a cost of Entry
Is going to be
Conducive
To like
Just getting off the
The ground too early
You're too early in the game
Reason that YouTube work for a lot of these people never wanted
The number to the algorithms of Drive beep
Evil towards
Content that they probably wouldn't be
Going towards
Otherwise
This has neither of those advantages
Are you sure you don't want to learn more about the proud boys
This is this is
Not free
And you have to search it out
I don't know how well Ivory Hecker is going to be doing
You got to spend a lot of time going around the circuit
You got to go on
On TV you got to get the word out before you can ever start getting a paid
Serviced
Sorry I was pretty interested in this
Secureserver. TV cuz it
It does seem like this
Is very strange
Cookie cutter
Fill in the blanks
Thing for
People with bad ideas to make
Secureserver.net TV scruples
Why
I started digging around a little bit but
I got to bummed out until I decided to stop the only people I could
Could see talking about it we're people in like
Really f***** up message voice
Great great good news good news
You can be judged by The Company You Keep
Alex's tacos
The ivory and today
Huey's
Eastside
Who built up this idea that she was censored
C-pack
You heard him say that in the introduction
Did say that unfortunately she's not going to allow this
Fictional story to be told every
You go to sleep
Fox is a sponsor that
What a dumb move to turn your microphone down
Stanford you again
Oh yeah that only hurts Fox
If they're cutting my feed and then look day
Austin turn my micro
Phone down because it did I mean c-pack was in charge of the mic and
Camera
Nation I was told by
Viewers in the audience
Fox Nation cut
The feed
When
About your specific microphone
Oh this is chain
This is why this is why she's not going to make
You yes and anytime any censorship
No use trying
To be too specific about what her narrative was a busted Alex's
Herbal idea
Your narrative doesn't matter on Infowars you just need people to hear you talk
Yeah I think she doesn't know how to play ball with Alex
Deletes Alex having
The correct himself in a very embarrassing waves
Beginning of the clip
He was saying that all this stuff you saw and everybody knew is
Navigate
I hate that we know how to be
Way better right-wing propaganda spend 99% of these idiots article in The Daily Beast
Something to add
Conversation
So Alex was saying that like foxes a sponsor of z-pack so they cut the mic
Apprenticeship
Ovaries version of it is
That nothing happened
Itzy pack because
Controls Xbox
It was on Fox Nation
Exactly turned off
4 ft 11
Quote
A spokesman for Fox Nation
Jen said the feed was never cut and it's
The service had already stop streaming the event
If I were a betting man which I am I would guess that
Maybe Ivory heard second or third-hand that her speech wasn't on Fox
This got turned it
The fox shut her off
Because this perpetuates
Cancel culture narrative that these losers are so obsessed with
And it's the only way they can bark
Subscription-based blogs
And so this is the version we've gone with
She doesn't realize
Silver dialysis version
It's a lie but you got to pull off the lie you can't just
You can't just lie
You got to play the game with the LIE
Why I don't have a whole lot of Hope
She doesn't have the staying power
She doesn't know where her bread is buttered and that is
Making sure the people know that James O'Keefe is real cool
Cool guy
Yeah
He's great I I really am
Respected journalism
He shows video and audio people in their own words being that's where we got to be at with journalism
So few people Trust
What the news is saying so if you can
Video of what people are really up to
Audiences want to see now they don't they don't
Trust
The written word is much anymore there's just so much fake news out there
I don't want to read in order to make my mind up about something
I want to watch deceptively edited video of
Somebody drunk at a
Bar having a conversation that maybe about something that sounds weird
That's how I'm going to make up my mind
The media has ever tried
People in their own word
Before
Or like
Quotes
Or maybe even
Full broadcast of speeches and interviews things have been done
Yeah but what they tend not to do is with James O'Keefe
Which is secretly filmed them in the deceptively edit the footage of making a narrative funk
Looking for him man you bet
But that's the good stuff
So
Ivory sticks around for a while but Alex goes off on a little bit of a Jag
Sure
Because
He's finally found
Taking the Olympics
Is alright with me
George Orwell said in a world of universal deceit
Telling the truth is a revolutionary Act
Real quick
It's not in Orwell quote
Us Olympian proclaimed her love for her country
Miniature stock
I want the big wrestling competition gold medal
Completely normal it's your country for you to go there
No it absolutely did not
Cultures and ideas
Melting Pot
Instead most people here
Big corporations
And
The nation-state there
Challenging the Monopoly power of big corporations that are bigger
And most governments
Well I do believe
Balance
Braces becoming the government
What is a short clip of what she had to say
Revolutionary I just won the gold medal
Why is this so
So I meant to stock won the gold medal in wrestling
After she won she said she loved representing the United
Red States of America
Try as I might I cannot find anyone saying
But you shouldn't have said that or that it was weird that you did
I think it generally normal people saw that and responded Haygood
Good for her
We're proud of our house really cool congratulations
However if you look around just a little bit on Twitter you might find some
Maybe
Slightly racist sounding responses on the right way
Princeton
And there was the Daily Caller sports editor David hookstead
Who tweeted this
Quote
This is what real patriotism looks like
LeBron James
Colin Kaepernick
Could learn a lesson from her
I
Can't understand a little subtle
F******
I mean
The Gulf
The f****** golf
LeBron James's what your daughter f****** metal
God I hate
Can people I really can't find anyone on the glass
She was somehow offended by
It's Mira's interview
Pride in
The us but that's an essential thing for people like Alex to imagine
Didn't exist
This is because they've been telling her audience that these other athletes who make the
Statement that they do are actually concerned with the cause of the bring attention
They're actually just against
America
I have the people who support these woke athletes only support them because they to hate America
Any idea of countries
That's when an athlete celebrates their win and says
They're proud to represent America
There has to be a backlash or else none of this makes
If we're cheering for the people want to destroy America we must be furious about someone loving it
Right
When that backlash isn't there someone like Alex has to imagine it is there and
Respond to it not exist
Austin point of no one's
Not a revolutionary Act
For an Olympic Athlete to be a proud
Of the United States
The same way it's not treasonous for an Olympic Athlete to use their platform to advocate for social
Whatever even then within the
Context of them advocating for social change they always or at least often
Say I love my country as well and that is why I wanted to
Sure
Jesus is a small-scale and very transparent
Instant about that right-wing media strategies essentially based on manufacturer
String outraged about face
Endure running they just have too much
They just have too much time
And it works too well as work too well whenever you create an imaginary enemy that people have just decide
Cited is real you can say
Anything
And they just believe it
So Alex plays the wrong clip
Of this this Olympian
When it's happening
Well he thinks he's playing the clip where she talks about loving America
And she went on to say another interview that she loves American she's proud of her country
And the left actually attacked her son but I don't like this image cuz they think they own women
You're a loser
Friends really
So
I'd like to I'd like for him to
Groove anywhere
1 Tactical
Single
Generally Paul Joseph Watson will at least show up with like a random
Complete some assholes
He's tweeting about how about black lives matter
I'm even a little bit like
If he about myself using
From this guy but
At least he's released
Sports editor for the Daily Caller
That's where they don't think that's indicative of a universal opinion
Piece of s***
I have no specifics but Alex was giving
Anyone who said anything about
No
Just do that he is only speaking of this one
Other athlete who is strength
It's a weird
So
Alex
Yeah it's a little bit defense
People have been
I'm saying that Michael
Allendale
Is paying out
Wow I mean my pillow guy
Maybe not
Okay alright maybe it's worse
USANA
He runs the ad with us
Alex Jones
Are liberals do that mean
He doesn't completely
Gold Ranger
Idiots
Okay
Paying me I don't work for that a******
We're sharing the profits from the things that I say
Fell for him
Give me a cut of the sales that I direct
To his website profit-sharing program or unaffiliated I don't get paid by his
Money for him to advertise
What's up with the people who liked me but they should buy his product course at the end of the quarter we figure out the
Prophesy get a cut of those words about that there's a financial arrangement
Draw time chantaje
Sales and he gives me money but I
You fuking idiot
Not only that
You're an idiot even more because you thought I was just getting paid for it by him
Like I didn't give a s*** if he succeeded or not know this is a profit-sharing so I need him to succeed
I honestly think that the
I think it's worse for
For Alex like
Flat rate
For what you charge for an address
Okay
This is Mike Lindell being like if you don't sell anything for me I'm not giving you connected
You are naughty you are an independent
Contractor is there Lee believe that advertising with you would be worth it
No
We're not going to do this on spec
So anyway Alex
Understand
The
That
It'd be better for you yeah you should definitely have got hit lateral
Glendale
No wonder he is playing that very add on his show and not where the ads Gus
He plays the entire ad on his show
Instead of during the commercials almost sponsored content
Is that like is assault
Just because Ivory wanted to
Respond to it
Exactly
Since you mentioned it
Temptations
Are those hats ladies be able to enroll
You want to respond to
Hello I Mike Lindell the most important commercial
Very important
Commercial
So they play this
Here's here's Ivory's
Geico
After work this is
Hear it
Fascinates me why woodfox
Down an ad for a symposium that is going to
Floor
Truth about the election
To the bottom of what really happened with the election here's the thing we know Fox
News is in a huge lawsuit
Dominion Dominion voting systems is suing
The Wazoo now if you're being sued
Buy Dominion wouldn't you want
Get all the proof she could
Got Dominion did commit fraud would win the last night
Is she High I don't know
She is really struggling to get through this concept
It's a yeah I guess it would her argument is like she
Fox News should be paying Mike Lindell to get the
Yeah absolutely they should be running that
Because
If you're getting an independent investigator.
Confirm
Why wouldn't you want Mike Lindell to do it for you
He's already on the way
Maybe you're a giant
And Company at you
Maybe been able to have your own investigators
Maybe use more rigorous approach
DJ's then someone like Mike Lindell of looked at this and Blake
Oh no we're f*****
Yes. Realize you answered your own question with the question that happens a lot by wouldn't
Fox 12
Get to the bottom of this if they're being sued
Perhaps
The very concept that you never
Considered they are wrong
And they don't want to lose a billion dollars
So this this is this next clip kind of bummed me out a little bit
Meowth
Yeah
I don't
I just
Especially the way that
The ivory tells the story of like her
Her ambition to do a story about Dominion
And then what happened
I also tried to present the documentation from the Secretary of State's office of Texas
Best Gators found in January 2020 that Dominion
Was a no-go because
It was
Susceptible to fraud
My boss is on again acted like they didn't care man assigned to me to cover
Sidewalk chalk art instead
I said I can't keep I'm being used as a tool of narrative
At a certain point you kind of have to ask yourself if maybe the boss is assigned to you
Thule report about sidewalk chalk art
Because that's all you could
Could be trusted to handle
Possible
Just not that good at through being a reporter I
Feel bad
Maybe you're sitting baby you failed as a reporter
That's I've heard that from somebody
Her boss
So the Secretary of State of Texas is actually Thrice reject
Did certified Dominion
Machines for elect
Inside in the state
First time was in 20
B12 and the other two were in January and October in 2019
Respect
Not 20
These machines make it harder for us to cheat
You can find report
It's very easily about their find
Three concerns that were raised
In 2012 there was a wide-ranging series of issues largely around them not being able to
Conductive full enough review
The technology
So they decided not
How to sign off on
We don't
In January 2019 there were concerns about me
Maintaining the secrecy of ballots
And whether or not the system was quote
Capable of permitting
Straight party voting
That initially seems like a weird thing for a voting software to not be able to do
But it turns out in some places
It's not allowed
Reviews
Straight party voting
I didn't realize that when I was first Reason by one-size-fits-all
And because it's outlawed in certain
Places
Concerns about that
The October 2019 report is the closest
But I can come up with
It's to whatever you say
System was quote
Ephraim fraudulent or unauthorized manipulation
That's certainly interest
But the fact that Texas had
Concerns about that
Doesn't prove anything to finish
Nope
I want to learn a little bit more so I went to check out the more detailed
Report on this October 2019 task.
The specific problems with the Dominion system
This report lays out really mostly breaks down
Being a pain in the ass
It's difficult for people to install
Bear
They also found that something could be
Be plugged into the second
USB port
Work on the machine but it wouldn't be
Right
List of needs
Specific ways that I could be done this was Dean Vape
Potential vulnerability
And the realization was like
Seal it up instead of trying to charge your phone on the machine just
Cover the US
Yeah yeah
Every state in the country has the right to determine their standards and how they want to run away
That's just how it's done in the United
For Better or Worse
Not confusing at all
This theoretical
Concern could be enough to
To get Texas to pass on using these
Machines but you can find analysis
From States like
Pennsylvania to Washington that reach
Different conclusion
I suspected this kind of thing is why Ivory ended up on sidewalk chalk Duty
If you look she read a headline about
The Texas Secretary of State decided just
Debaser reporting on that without considering the larger scope of
The story
Colonel tells you tried to run reports about hydroxy
Quinn while ignoring
The nearest Aldi's
A massive pile of evidence that it was a miracle cure
Or like how she wanted to do stories about Bitcoin Gold Rush is only local news how can
Considering the audio
This is just
Yeah I mean it so
It's such a sad thing for her too because she's ruined her life
Yeah because of this
Spell f****** delicious Avenue
Totally been one of those reporters who handles sidewalk chalk
For the rest of your life
Soft news on the five
The other building to that I think about it is like you know there isn't there is a pesos that we can feel
As much as like well
His media career is
Is.
Except for as much as you
You can do it
This right-wing
Just parallel reality
Some traction you can get there
I also like
It's not that much pesos
No that wasn't
There wasn't much more for her to do know that's true I don't know I don't know if there's chop
No she's in a lot of people who work
Oh your career is ruined
What career would you imagine
Yeah I mean before you even started this I'm sure you failed as a report
Sorry
The chance to get better job or something she could have learned that if she starts with the softball puffs
Places maybe some
Pretty cakes are under a wing she turns into an actual journalist
I didn't set her life
Her career and media is over and right-wing media isn't going to
She's too lazy and she's too lazy even for them
I don't know
I think she could get with the program but also
There's a there's like
A million other career paths
She could probably go down
Maybe
So she was censored
All over the place
Things that are the boss
Their boss said
Kobe black
Texting Story song
No
What is a camera right there
Your boss told you Xbox
Yeah my boss
Fox
Told me do not report
Thousands of deaths after vaccine
Nation
What is that what are we hiding
I've been working on a character
You like me to do my new character
Let's do it my new character is
Ivory's boss okay
I've got this break she'll story
Okay everyone hoot
Takes the vaccine dies
Alright look you can't report
The people who died after getting the vaccine died
Because of the vaccine because that's not
And you can't really support that
They claim it all
You can discuss deaths after vaccination in a proper
Contact so long as he explained that there is no proof of causation in
You restrain yourself from making
Ridiculous insinuation
That probably takes
The fun out of it for you so I guess
You should probably just pretend
Stop you right there
I don't like
What you're telling me
Could you pick up a clear head of it
Cancel culture
So she takes her exit
And Alex
I get back
Do scary
People
About sure
August 11th
Airplane vaccine passports
Inside we've got that Biden is set on August 11th
Credible sources
Very dangerous time to be alive
Great
Okay so
Future
Be tomorrow could be anyway
The beginning of an inescapable hellscape where all right wing
Christians will be
We taken care of shoulders and everyone.
Could start
On the 11th
Right now the plan has been the sources I have
Gold standard not just check the soap ever
Now since I got the wrong so many times
It could be not bad
With a grain of salt
Hey just in case you were wondering
Pictures of fortune cookie
Keep your eyes open for this lucky number
The last hour of the show
Alex has Barnes
This is where I was really excited I wanted to know what Alex was going to do that he needed to do
This is the big is the Big Show
Doesn't happen what does it happen
That
How can it not
Appliance
But he does have a long
10 questions
Okay
There's a series of
Over a
Minute-long
Conquest job
Okay okay
I started to get like really disoriented
In the middle of this review
Like I don't know what it was but like
Listen to the whole question of minute and 17
History
Bum rushing my corporations by the UN by The Fortune 100
Force experimental injections I mean
You're really smart Astorian I really respect you
What are they
Desperate
Insane push now they admit it doesn't work
Same thing here they're trying to suppress that
Find that out I mean
This is like
Watching insane Gremlins burn down a building or something
Why are they doing it cuz they're going to destroy themselves the process it's already falling apart
I just I just cannot find any even from a criminal
Criminology logic
What is this
Grabber
Wanting to punish the Westford
Aegis
I'd like
It's very strange for someone to like
Ramblin Lee ask a question that they answer
For the person in the
Process of asking the question
Here's the direction I would like your answer to go in
It's a long Quest
Actually that I
I counted three question
And within there
Bandit in descending order
It starts with why are they
Acting like the bad
Right then why turned out with Hitler
Why are they doing it
And then
What is the
I can't really explain everything that is that Alex's make
Picking up in just about everything he is trying to
Solve the mystery of
Long minute
Questions
Is
They almost always boil down to a yes or no answer
You've given it why are they doing this is it just because they want to overthrow the world and take over and suck everybody's blood
Yes
Go to answer next question
Barn
Here is a little bit later
Pretty close
Succession after this
Alex
The Moon
Because for a minute and a half
Yeah oh my God
Azima Global idea that cost while talking about
Why did they name
Something
The National Institutes of Health in
CDC
Are you asking
Do not
Vaccine for the spike
Will basically kill mammals
Proceed with Extreme Caution
Inhumans
YouTube
Get the power get the control make you by vaccines make you be tracked
Sprinkler World ID
Right up front
People get hurt
What
The doctors
Are you high
I started putting a poison
Kill Everybody
No no no no
Upfront
I just get everything you wanted once in a blitzkrieg attacks
Total War
Yes I end
Okay
What yes or no answer it happens every time
That's exhausting
I do appreciate that he always disagrees with his fake terrible plans
Supplies that even worse terrible plan
As like the
Is the SmartThings
These idiots
Are not putting out the placebo first they're killing people when we know they're killing people what I would do
Is kill people later the skies are so f******
Stupid the fake baby sugar water
Barnes are they stupid
Alright
Iodized
I was listening to this
Barnes having a coughing fit or something like it's Alex has a mute button
What is what is the explanation for this Behavior
These are the type of free association questions usually come with something in the nose a little bit earlier
Scott
Just let me go Daddy-O
Sense of likes
I know when he
He's going to stop step aside when a master is fed up
When Satchmo start Bluff
Dave Chappelle drops in your not doing your 5
If you're not going to yell something out in the middle of his disrupt that rhythm
Nope not going to happen
Knows better
I'm going to say that if people don't like gross things
They should skip ahead
Text Glen okay
It's pretty gross
Okay baby comes out of nowhere as much as
It's going to
For you that sounds about right now
Disgusting
Alexei on the show
Like that for this
You're having sex with your wife
Imagine your wife gives you permission
Whataburger
Menu
Come on
That's how many people compared to
Vaccine
Things are putting
We are genetic
Sent to you
That was discussed
What the fuk was that
I could have gone my entire life without hearing Alex Jones a ejaculate
The fuk was that
It was unfortunate that's what that was
His response
What the f*** did you just say
Alex
You just said that
Oh my God Alex you are
You're asking me
Ask Dave link questions
If you're talking about
About to
Hey Alec
Did you just say
You know how when you ejaculate inside of a woman and she doesn't want you to
She gets mad
Why did you just say that to me cuz I don't know how that feels I don't know how that feels
I don't know how that feels I don't like
Knowing that
You know how that feels
Let's meet up in the head
Now we're back to Nan gross programming
Is Christ
The edl
Apparently is calling everybody who doesn't want
Medical knots
So yes I'm to come in
To the world you are calling those people not
Because he doesn't want medic
Nazi ironic
That they would call the knots
These Nazis when they themselves are the Nazis
I bet this clip
Ends poorly
What do you make of the ATL
Calling anyone that doesn't want this Nazi law over us Nazis
Two-month-old terrorism policy put out my mind says You? Down
Eagle terrorism equals CIA will be Unleashed on you and the Liberals aren't
Alex Wisconsin
Oh boy
What in God's name is happening on this show
Vic Fuentes is rubbing off on him
Holyshit this is
This is aviraj Alex just tossing out real our is a mess
Yeah wow
I don't know against the Jews
Why are they doing this to us
Why
Why Dad are they doing this to us
Why are they
Doing this to us
Yeah Alex
Is
I don't know
Why
Are the Jews attacking white people is what I didn't
Actually say
But I'm very heavily implied
Great
So Alex
Another
Extended Quest
Barnes this is one of my favorite Alex
Text Jones
Saga
Paul
Well I thought pjw was on
He has it what's it like to be Vindicated about everything
But this one's even
Okay
What is it like doing all this
Physically
I'm not scared Appleton
Cell
What
Level Washington
Upside down where we going
We are
No.
Terrifying time of what the
They're trying to do
If you if you're paying attention to wave this question
Started is
Barnes there are not many people who know as much as I do and
Do you do what is it like to be as smart as me
Yep
I don't know how a human being could not respond to that
Messing with Siri
Get help
Please
What are you talkin
Did the underlying things that are said
Two people
Like barns
It's pretty rude
Yeah that question isn't it
Itself a little bit
Dick head
Also of all the thing you know
Types of people where they give you that one sign
I would like almost immediately to where it's like
Listen
I know how to
Control my body of course
And you look at them in your like the one thing you absolutely do not know how to do is control your body
Do you feel like saying that
Timmy is an acceptable thing
Feel responsive
Forgot
What are you f****** talk
Talking about
How can I sell you a pillow
Looking
I actually can't tell you why
Code override
Oh my God Michael Dell's website
We got one last clip in
Alex bringing everything back
Into the center
Full circle
Got it ready
From a lot of sources while I'm jacking Celtics
Stephanie Claire basically civil emergency climate emergency martial law
On the 11th when they see is alerting all the rest of it so
I'm telling you man this is one hell of a time
To be alive
So the 11th
Is B
Totally going
Hbms
According to many many many many many sores
Does not just Jack Pacific
Yeah baby walk
Bye because Alex will do it
And you should know that Alex is reporting
Is totally accurate
Nothing happened
He's still right
Right now
Only changed it because he's so right
What is it like to be as dumb as
With me right now
This is this is the game you how I got this is why I like
Like predictions blow people's minds
Man
Cuz maybe it'll happen if you behave this way
But maybe
What little load of s*** happened
That's my prediction so Jordan This episodes a little infuriating mostly because
Cuz it started with the promise of Barnes advising Alex on the legality of
Some sort of
The plan
This this check-offs
Plan never
I wonder if the advice was given by a text message
And the answer was no don't say that on your
They could have been
We will never know
Yeah and then we got to the 11th
Be worried about
I mean it's going to be really weird whenever they surprised us with it usually they're like we're going into lockdown event
Actually not like
Outside today if you're caught outside dialects with guns
Surprise
There's going to be that emergency alert
On the 11th
That's going
I'm sure sure
Just going to be the second day of my
Glendale's
Does asterisk
I'm calling it an advance but away
It could be not
Cyber summey revealed
If it's not it's because we are calling it possessor
Directly right
Yeah I don't know I don't I don't I don't
Baby b
Some sort but
I just I think this is
I'm going to be a disappointment
Maybe
I don't think there's any way
That Biden
Wood
I don't know
Maybe they'll schedule the speech during the terrible stupid Symposium that's going on but I imagine people will be
Yeah I know I would be morbidly entertained by it I see there's a livestream I might f*** around an atom project
There's no way that you're not going to see something that you'd be like there's no way that this would be on a professional broadcast Allure we will find
I don't think so
Probably
Not I would've what they should do is they should have
He should have like a Supreme Court Justice
Just tracker
During the live stream like
We got we got one
Search does not here is going
Going to be the real test for Alex
If he's at Rockville
Does Mike Lindell air commercials for Infowars
During the Cyber Symposium live stream
Oh no because if he doesn't that means that Alex has a one-way Street
That is
Is it better than
Dominant move right there you are somebody else's not good
Anyway
Will be back
What's going on in the world
What's new with the 11
Yeah
I hope all is well
We are infinite and I'll just go fighting I go to bed Jordan
Please find a local charity or Bell found in your area to help out people
Omnio abellio I'm dzx clerk I'm Daryl run this this is
By far than
Commercial I've ever recorded in my tire career
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color