Damn important
I have great respect for snowledge B
MoneyGram
Fight.com
Vaseline and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Jordan
Russian for yes up
Vibrate spotted a Jordan is we're back to the button
Brightspot BBs
That BBS button Breaks by alright something different this time around
A little update
Hundreds more have been sent out
Hundred more to go if you haven't received it's probably still coming we will
You're in line you like a Brit
Who is Alex Jones by play Patriots
Along those lines
One of the things I didn't do last time but I decided to do this time was I wanted to keep track of where I'm sending them to like
States and countries in
And just for fun
Just because I was curious
And we officially now have sent button
To every state in the United States
Oh that's cool do you think the whole that was really the last one was
You know I want to say
You know it seems like it would be obvious that it's like Alaska or Hawaii but I feel like the real answer is Utah
No you told me that you said the number of buttons
Alright
Disproportionately represented at Utah escape the Mormons listening to us
Peoples in the middle Idaho
At this point there are two states
With only one
2 States with only one
Oh man Vermont
No Vermont's doing alright I don't even know if I know all 50 states now
New Mexico we had one
The last one to get a check mark on the board Delaware
Bucking Finance Lovington
Avoiding text
Who's on my
Taxes and avoiding buttons currently
I'm very thrilled that there button
Now in every state
I would be more fun if you said
Something like their butt
Is it all 50 countries
He said those are the ones we recognize beyond that no more buttons
Definitely more countries than I would have expected also
What is the best country
Supposed supposed to answer that
It's just a fun Quest
You like total numbers of
People
That's certainly where the most of the buttons are gone
Internationally
My bright spot then is going to go with a double Brightside cuz I got a real short one
It's where you stay up till 3:30 playing Mortal Kombat together
Oh Wonder
Middle School
Exactly and it felt so good to just do that again you know just to be that kind of person
Is it a situation where one of you was winning every match
No, we played the story mode and we just kind of
Switch controllers that you know that way you don't have any hard
Feeling Jersey game that was like
Mortal Kombat but you could play was like a two-player thing
Like you run around and you would do that one that almost like a platformer I think so remember he's out there
There are three in the morning or whatever
Yes and will get back to work on this was not on Super Nintendo
Come on well that's fun
Who's my guy was a fighter in Mortal Kombat 11
Jade
For sure she got the Longbow staff she can get it from across the room she's got the whole package
That's the way I go I don't I don't like to get up to close
Get scared
I get really scared I go with glacius
Cyberwolf
Nightwolf Killer Instinct
I do remember Inferno
There is definitely the store doll that was on fire
Red Dynamite or something like that smaller than the T-Rex
I'm over glacius Latios for sure
That was the monkey that had ice powers right
No
Primal
Outrage that's what I'm thinking of you
Damn it I don't know anything anymore
Gerard came to fighting game straight
So old
Alright
Oh yeah what's your spot is just a shout out
To whomever was
Handling me at the dispensary earlier today
Who
Took my order and then said in the most chipper and kind way
Wow that's a fantastic order
To the point where I
Moment for a brief moment I felt compliment
I really did he was that good
Now I remediate Lee went back to being cynical and reminded myself
This was a
Transaction however
For that I got to give credit where credit
Sabrewulf Savor wolf oh my God
I had to look it up just now remembering killer
That was great
Yeah there's some
Some fun if yeah. Kilgore
Yeah it wasn't in the first 10 just
The bad pun
Name sabrewulf
Vonnegut also a playable character in that one it was on walkable but like a Bill and Hillary Clinton were in
Tournament Edition
So Jordan today we got a new episode to go over there any talking about August
This is
Sunday's episode
From
This week beginning of this week
And you know
Some people might say hey
You're doing a sneaky snake episode here on Wednesday and I think it's essential that we do
Cuz today is the dreaded
August 11th
Starting back into Levittown
That Marshal office
One of the things that I kind of thought was that like you knows
The trip to the FEMA camp is probably going to be like an hour and a half for most people
Episode
Chicago
To be like in Des Plaines
It's going to be a long drive for a while
Figured it'd be good to have some new content for books to enjoy
Fat boarding
Traffic on the Dan Ryan is backed up with a lot of people headed to FEMA camps today it'll be an extra
Add 15 minutes to your DriveTime commute
Alternate route 6 Corpus Road
Hello
Also has a birthday coming up
Very excited I'm not a rapper
Secret space program chief Master Sergeant Richard Petty thickness
Journal apology
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Lupron
Free secret of the Reptoid clone thank you so much right now policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Hello to and that plays the non-binary stoner Drive
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Heroin
Is freakishly large
Meganplays
It's also it's a it's a blessed day Jordan because we have another member of celine's family to welcome
Wonderful thank you too Patrick from Germany
Adopt a gorilla
Now we got muscle
Now we've got the whole team for protection we've got to shore up the offensive line I think I think there was a gorilla
Primal
There are a lot of gorillas gorillas somewhere in Killer Instinct
Sure
And that serious
Who's that
Nevermind
Strensiq of other arcade games
Here is narcotics drops
Road Rash rash
Constantly control myself
Not to us
Because I know it's God's play
Godzilla
I want to hit people but I know God's going to hit him that the only reason that you wouldn't hit people because God's going to do it for
Maybe not like Compassion or at
50 or like the thought process that perhaps a person also has feelings and existence I don't want to put I want to ruin this fight
I forgot later
Jesus said other people do unto others and then you're just like I got to kick his ass for me no big deal
They wait till it wait till my big brother God gets here
My daddy
Bigger than your dad
So are we start up the show and Alex has some pretty big news
Here on this
The skier episode as he does every day which is always
Disappoint
Sitting here just minutes ago I was I was riding
Post for Today Show
I was looking at
One of the largest newspapers in Germany
The largest regional newspaper
3 German states
Weather headline
That the largest
Medical Union
In Germany
The pathologist Union the corner Union
Gals know what kill
40% of the dead people
That they're seeing I've been killed by the vaccine
And then it's eating or body switch all the studies show it would do
Oh boy
Alright
This story is not about some pathologist
Union and Germany although I do love how Alex always is like
Whatever newspaper he's talking about his biggest newspaper in Germany
It's everything they say is right on this is about one pathologist named Peter Schumacher
Who's coming out with some concerns about that that's after vaccination Maybe
Under-counter
Hamburg Germany to do further work assassin
Cause of death for both covid related deaths
And people who died after vaccination
Schumacher estimates that 30 to 40% of the
40 people who died after being vaccinated who have gotten autopsies quote
Died from the vaccination
But this is absolutely not an opinion that shared by other
According to the underlying primary source article from osterberger almanyam
The federal Association of German
Pathologist
Did not actually agree with your markers opinion
But encourage more autopsies
Spectrum
You know you were the reasons it is because that's the only way that you can disprove or prove any
Conclusion or any claim
Such as this
So they're finding was
It's fine Devin
Johann Friedman the head of the autopsy work
Working group of the Pathologists Union
Federal Association for German pathologist
You don't know anything yet
Yeah that sounds about right
Other groups like people are licking
Institute and other German doctors who were interviewed did not
Share schirmacher is
This isn't interesting perspective that your marker is bringing up but at this point it's not based on any hard data or prove so it's not something that should be
Reported as fact
But Alex is doing is actually worse
He's not just assuming sure baugher's position is correct
He's embellishing on it and exaggerated exaggerating it.
A completely fictitious headline
How to report
To guide the coverage
Today's Show
Yeah that's
Actually gets way more fun later holy
I can't wait for you to see where this goes
If your
Contention is that 30%
Of
40 people who died
Died of
The vaccines
Specifically
Then
He's making an estimate
Right right
But I mean
You put the numbers across there there been
A lot of people backs
Trueno so
Those numbers would
Suggest we would see
Apatis
Being carried around with bring out your dead signs yes
That's kind of number is
It seems like a number that would be really difficult to extrapolate to larger populations
Is true
Would probably mean that this select group of people have something about them
Write that would make them
Allergic to the vaccine or something or the estimation is incorrect
There's an others of variable that's being missed
Something
And that's why I think
That's certainly this person isn't from everything I can
Yeah some crazy person
But the the perspective that he's bringing is something that needs more examination before you can really
Really yeah
Take it ride
Like different
Skipping that step
Save it at the most prestigious paper in the world and this guy is one of the best
Yeah it's important to remember that it does not matter at all what it it like
The guy could have come out and said like I think 30% of the people died of the vaccine specifically
However I will admit the 40 stab wounds and each
Was it
Contributing factor Alex was it will be like
Kelly people comorbidity
Article to talk about today he also came across a bill
Was in the bill Friday evening
Promise my wife and family I was not going to come to work on Saturday
Given the Saturday crew the day off
That didn't happen.
4 Hour forts
When I saw this on Friday I had to come in
Responsibility
I'm an accessory to murder
You're an accomplished what I came in
Is the infrastructure bill
They found the enforcer
Thousands of page-long infrastructure to help
But he hasn't read
No no no
Yeah that sounds more
More accurate
So we'll get to his take on that but before we do
There are some things that are actually causes for celebration in my life
Okay one of them is
When Alex
Has a new song that he likes to rant over
Whenever we discovered you belong to the city and Alex's amazing day
I think that there's a new contender in
In the clubhouse for another song
No
Angle my friend evil will fail
Slowly building power
There's a great Flash
Asteroid
Rolike poison Prion
That's once again
Until the break
What are universes
Minions in prison
One with God
Amazing
What is it about heaven and 80s
Inspired Bob
That just makes you like it works
Like I mean I want him to why isn't he talking over Fascination Street
The Cure is his
F****** Zone man I feel like it must take him back
To like the blow Hardy Daisy 1213
Pontificating to your friends over there at the radio hit
I enjoy quite a bit
Pop Plus
Alex's
Weird I just like autocrat
Jeff compilation
Commercials that you can like that at 2 in the morning
Always with you
Crazy like every time he should just have one of those can you believe that all of these hats are together as one
If you believe I think I talked one of those commercials
Recently and it blew my mind because
Dude
Technology once I get
Back then
How are you going to get all these songs
All-in-one place now it makes sense
Tape to CD
Very exciting
$0.01 for $0.01 for 10 CDs there's no way this will come back and I thought that that went away
People still can't
Directions
Swing of the internet
It will bring us all together
And apparently that will lead to the
The singularity
That's not the singularity that Alex is talking about in his neck
Text clip I think it's
Just the devil
Broadcast then just to say it upfront
Everyday
Singularity
Everything
Become an instant everything
That's Titanfall singularity
What
What's Singularity of
Evil
Evil has taken completely over and is operating on all cylinders
Assault
Everything
In creation and trying to overturn logic
I just common sense because that is it odd
I would have Carson
Mechanic
So there's three singularities here there's a lot of talk about
The futurist version that
Is what we understand as the singularity
The devils
Fake version of God's real
Singularity
Different version
There's a third one
Just talkin about
And that is the evil is banging on all cylinders
And destroying Lodge
Jake or something
You know Dion
Words
Words words words
The word
Itself
Defeats
His conversation
Sing
You Larry single single
Clarity X
Singularity
Go back to Germany now I am here's here's how the story is developing
So let me tell you what's coming up on this live Sunday transmission
First off the largest German pathology Union
One guy
That's corners
People study disease
Oscar single dude
That come out and said months ago the vaccines are vaccines are killing people
Didn't say that
Right now
Some months ago they came out and said a vaccines you got to stop
And now is the time to bring that knowledge to life
Ridiculous
Breaking news
So apparently everybody
Who's
They're getting covid
They're all blacks
This is sort of the essential shell game that's being played by people like Alex and a lot of the right-wing media
It is as
As greater numbers of people are vaccinated a higher proportion of people who get sick
Will inevitably also be vaccinated right
It is an unfortunate reality of
How
That's how it is but it's something that can be misrepresented and misused in order to create perception
Oceans of like
Everybody who's got vaccinated is
He's getting sick and that's just absolutely not the case
Describe this is
Is really actually kind of funny
You have to understand that he just makes up
Like
Listen to this
If I get a national reports of 95 to
Israel in 95
Australia it's 99 and Indian
Other countries
Chili's only 20-something percent
23% of Australia as of this morning Ice Age been inject
99.9 per cent there's one person in
Australia
Can a hospital tested positive for covid
Batman shot
One person one man alone
Fighting against
Thanks to the tyranny of not having the disease everybody else
Is vaccinated and they got sick except for one guy there's just one example
Only one
I don't
Show any proof of this
Just one guy you know how you know how you can be confident it's just one guy because in a continent and
Country filled with millions of people
Rampaging pandemic always just one guy
Yeah and I'm like yeah in a New South Wales there is a bit of
Bit of a resurgence
Yeah little bit of an outbreak going on
What are the reason
If you read about the articles
But there's one of the reasons that people cite
This being
You know what what
Contributing factors let's say
Is it Australian had a difficult time with the vaccine rollout
They've had supply shortages they've had
Under performance in terms of local manufacturing of the vaccine
So there is there's a number of issues that have
Slowed vaccine
Coverage
In Australia
Everything I can tell literally the opposite of what Alex's Hangout
But button
Itsfunneh
It's just so frustrating that they can use
That
Bypass of that emotional just respond
Lots of just like that lives are stupid
Because if
If you could stop for one second if you're on the right then
Can you confuse
To be like
Okay at the beginning of the pandemic
They said it was
Going to kill all of us
Then they said it wasn't going to kill anybody
Then they said it was going to kill some people
But it was fake
And then they gave us the vaccine
And now the vaccine is killing people
But then
Now that people with the vaccine are contracted covid now the vaccine does
Do anything against
The people
With the covid
Like
The Narrative has changed
And twisted around on itself so many times it has short. Of time it's hard to keep
Keep track of your heart
You forgot about that short. Of time where they were dipping their toes into is there even a
Didn't stick around too long
Did not work how can you not just look at that and be like okay
The other guys have said the same thing to her
Varying
Degrees of the same thing
And also cautious
Yeah
The fair amount of caveat of like this is a developing thing we don't really
Have all of the information when I made it to learning that information
Confirm
Repetition
It really is weird
I think that some of the messaging that's been done obviously by the Light
Like the normal media hasn't been ideal
Obviously other profit-driven to
But yeah the message world
Is absurd
Let's get to this little clip hereabouts talking about the infrastructure bill
Thought
I'm usually tomorrow's news today
Louisville
Talked about for months yesterday before but I had no idea I thought was just be
Infrastructure plan
Has in it stops at when I read it in the bill I couldn't believe
My God
Okay
So
Breathalyzer
Assistance by law
I don't know
What
That's the Holy Grail
Always known this how is he not happy with this
Because he's so mad whenever people don't wear seat belt
He is a seatbelt
So this infrastructure Bill does include a requirement that the national highway traffic safety administration
And come up with rules to require alcohol monitoring monitoring system
In new cars
This is specified as a passive technology so it by definition wouldn't be a breathalyzer type thing
It seems like the sort of thing that this bill is
Disgusting
Really be feasible unless there were self-driving capabilities for all new cars
Since it would aim to quote
Passively monitor the performance of a driver of a motor vehicle
The accurately identify whether that driver may be impaired
A a tour limit motor vehicle operation
If an impairment is detect
Is someone swerving
Great you've identified a possibly impaired driver but in that situation
It's not like the safest thing to do would be to shut off
The car
Figuring out exactly what to do is probably going to be
Real challenge
I suspect the reason that the language in the bill is pretty vague and it's just about getting the highway traffic safety administration to come up with
Rules is because there isn't a definite solution ready to go right now
Maybe some of the Technologies are at the beginnings of being
Minnow on the way but they're not there
I'm not sure what Alex is talking about in terms of retina scanners but I imagine if that's real it has something
Do it like me
Making car theft
More difficult
I imagine that I would have had the same like
Like concerned if it was like when they introduced
Kyiv
But what
I think these types of bills that are over like a cow
Open pages long
. that seems off-topic sometimes
Kind of worst
At best they seem an efficient and it worse the way they cover these for ranging topic
Excuse the appearance
Do politicians trying to sneak things into bills that could
Couldn't pass otherwise saying
That's said I'm not sure if Alex's argument make
If this whole thing is about spying on you and your car and like having
Some kind of database
It doesn't really make sense that the bill also repeals the national driver registry advisory
Exactly counter to the conspiracy Alex's pitching
But whatever
Right
This is terrifying overwhelming government surveillance they're watching all of us but if you
Told any one of those people we're installing Jarvis into your car
And if you are drunk you walk in your car and you say Jarvis
I'm s***-faced drive me home every single person would be like
I want that in my car
Everybody would do that
Yeah if you could give it a character people would probably enjoy
Okay my retina Jarvis of course I will you're such a kind person
So here here's some more stuff from that bill that is
Criticizing
Transgender singer in any bathroom I want with children you name it
Mendon feather women it doesn't matter
Everything else
Bornstein from there
That's an infrastructure bill that's just mad libs
Just throw it out yet
Spaghetti at the wall
I'm too or the ability to read that entire infrastructure Bill do some word searching
I will tell you that we're bathrooms not in it
No only time the word restroom comes up in the bill isn't a section about provide Grant
That's for gas stations that provide access to Electric
Charging state
That's great
But it turns out the bathroom
That's a consideration in terms of their ability to get a girl
Great
No I think I don't know what I'll just talk about
I think about Kaepernick
No
Weird
That Kaepernick is invention of the infrastructure bill
Yeah
So it's kind of gave me the impression the Kaepernick was going to be very heavily and I think I was
Not a whole lot of analysis of the infrastructure bill
Broadway button
Sure is that but that's because Alex is mad
Esau picture online
Obama dressed in a baby blue outfit with a big
Platinum chain around his neck
No no no he's an African god
Super spreader
Palpatine
Hollister
We got about strain
They want to stay lockdown and you should stay locked
North Korean style worship
True Jim Jones style worship
So I want to ask you a question about like if you hear clip like that what is the story that's even being cover
I mean I guess
Yeah
Obama's an a****** for throwing a big ass party
Congrats
It seems like that
The story
Seems like it would be with the news item
It's not
It might appear that the story is at the lives or hypocrite
I don't follow their own Public Health guidance
But really if you look at the way that this is being reported that
That's not the story either
The story as it's being presented by Alex is about how the left
Worships people like Obama and allows them to get away with the things that don't allow people like Alex or Trump
To get away with your
That's the story that's interesting to me
Hey don't forget it's also a story about how black men wear jewelry
And we need to fear ants African god or something. It's very important that we mention
That about Obama feel like later coverage of the story will get more racist but
The underlying story here is that there is a picture of Obama from his 60th birthday party that got released where he's dancing around without a man
Mask on
Obviously Alex can't be outraged that he's not wearing a mask
Because Alex doesn't think anyone
Find a different Lane to attack
From apocracy angle that's more of a Fox News kind of ploy
Yeah that's kind of
Sweet tea
Second-hand suit
Criticism
Yeah let him have that I will say that everyone
On the left are cult members
Who want to be locked down to pick up Mama's special right
Yeah that's
Right right right
I think certainly the Optics of that are bad
Oh yeah I haven't having this party I think that there there's Fair criticism there
I think that Alex is
Being a little bit of a dick
Yeah
I also think that there are marked differences between
This kind of
Bad behavior perhaps
Sore Maybe
Unwise behavior and certainly bad
Publix
Responsibility
You do have a certain amount of responsibility
Republic when you've
You know your robot
Yeah I think there's a difference
Between that and the kind of irresponsible ship people like
Trump
Alex do
Around the virus
Around around public
Yeah that's why I refuse to even accept any kind of
False
Equivalent
Between the two
The bad faith argument I can say is that while still having some criticism
M4
The bad Optics
The unwise decision making
Having a party that doesn't follow
Right
Right right
Hey this guy's driving around
Swinging a baseball bat in people's mailbox
What an a******
That isn't
Exactly like Hitler
All right it's the same level of crime
Yeah it's
It's it's not difficult
Quotes
They're not difficult
Thomas Jefferson Thomas Jefferson
Hello Institute quotes are difficult
Service here is Alex doing a doing one of the old
Sambuca
Thomas Jefferson famous by French reporter
What is the level of tyranny in which humans will except
Lee said the level
That's the level that people take us to
Lee said the level you will except
Very simple
Sounds right
Death of Frederick Douglass quotes
Do things that I want to bring into Focus here is
The way that Alex is telling a story he's now added a French reporter into it and famously this was
The reason that I think that this is important
Just craft this this year
French reporter in there
Speech at other point that yard sales around this don't matter
So you've already decided that you're going to erase a black man from history so you might as well add French
Hoverboard
I don't even think it's
Conscious on Alex's bar
He is
His politics would
Erase
Frederick Douglass in favor of Thomas Jefferson
But I think that it's
Just that
He has this
Little bit of
Trivial grasp
To this this
That this kernel of information
Then he just wants to flush it out with details to make himself sound like more of an expert
That's all he does is like his version of quoting a
Exactly deadline Dash 1109b section 111
It's an act
I was it was
I think poor
Taste for him not to try and do an offensive Fred Jack
Exactly
More headline
Becoming fauci says
In full FDA
Will inspire a flood of vaccine requirements
Play that next time cuz it's
It's not enough to just read the quote
I want to
I want you to hear it for yourself next time
Flutter vaccine requirements
These comments were very specifically about how after the FDA fully approve the covid vaccine you're likely to see a ton of
Any local level regarding vaccinations
This isn't him threatening mandates he's just
Just expressing the Sun
The many areas probably already want to put in local mandates but are reluctant to because full approval Azan
Immigrant
In the same interview fauci said that further lockdowns were unlikely but I expect Alex is going to ignore that part seeing is that
Predicted that August 11th
Today if you're listening to this
The beginning of martial law
Weirdly hasn't come up on this episode yet
I wonder I wonder what Alex is thinking about that
It's it's so funny to me how many
How local restaurants
Can put in a vaccine mandate
And then immediately be like
Oh I also got rid of all the customers that I didn't like from before
Is that weird or also the assholes that I hated who came to my restaurant before I think it's real
Really strange to how like
People of Alex's politics
Don't believe
In like
The Civil Rights Act
You should be able to ban people from making their cake
Homosexual requirements your religion
No you can't have a vaccine the little strain
You can also tell by the exact wording that Alex is using there where he's getting this new story from
That headline is from a newt from a Nigerian Outlet called The Paradise
I switch is just reinterpreting a primary article from USA Today
The headline on the blog is far more Sensational enough Alex is going to tend to cover that
As opposed to the underlying actual article Which is less useful
For his purpose
Yo
You know it's fun to always like
Back
You're not reading the paradise.
Website
Get out of here
You had to put it back
Text through Google translate twice
It's okay you're not you're not reading
So what we got going on now
Is the culmination of like a century
Evil plan
The globalist
If they were 10 years
True
Got a lot more coming
Today
My friends with
First thing I want
Before we go
Emporia you to realize how
This is the big Global smooth
This is a hundred years of Robber Baron planning this is
Everything launched
It's not going as well as they wanted
They're just going to pour on More Steam Moses going to get
Very destructive
Very Reckless
Very very dangerous
And so does Tobin
We don't have a choice
To do whatever it takes
And that's where we are right now
A piece of cake
There are 23 years that
Population
From
Because the devil logic
Even those being killed one admitted if that's too scary they have Stockholm Syndrome
Okay
Population
Is going to be dead
Soon
You know it's fun
It really makes sense
You know that after January 6th
Not doing anything
Solve the problem
And there's absolutely no way that a propagandist like this saying that it's
Open season on all of our political enemies
Could lead to a repeat of that event
It's so amazing how doing nothing
Worked it certainly
Alex comes back from break and wants to play this clip
Bill gay
Although this actually is
Was just eclipse
Anderson Cooper
Bill Gates
Cut it off before Bill Gates
Sorry about this but this is apparently now thing we have a streak
This is the second episode in a row where we're going to hear Alex say the word ejaculate
Play this clip
This is Bill Gates
Is on with the
Other globalist
Fortune
Anderson Cooper
Cooper is Shang
Well we should just deny
Social Security benefits
Social
But if you don't take the deadly experimental shots
Doesn't even work in the majority of the dying
Wow
Well then you'll just ended Bill Gates start smiling
Like a pig and you know what
Erdos
They are saying
You have to be vaccinated in order to work at a corporation is that something you support and
Do you think
Federal government
Or
State governments
Federal government should mandate
She want to get on the airplane afternoon vaccinated if you want to get
Social Security you need to be vaccinated if you want to get
Whatever whatever benefits
They give
You need to be vaccinated
Therefore is that something
Anyone on the say yes but
Why didn't you let him
Gates looks like he had a funtania see Jackie
Special powder
Billy baroo
This is a big one ballet
Just
You could have just play Wyclef
If he had an organ
He had buried sarkari another globalist on CNN doing everyone a year-and-a-half ago
Lisa
Engage did the same thing
He's an orgasm on air
You can play that quick
I think I think he's
Trying to be funny
I guess I think
Is that it
I don't know
That's bad
It's really tough to tell him because he's said this
A lot
Yeah he talks about Bill Gates
Jesus while talking about tyranny
He goes to
Semi-regularly
I think I mean you could
Be better
Just thinks he's got his hands on a good bit
Wow I guess you could
I can't tell ya no
Nonono dwell
You have the
He has the intonation of somebody who's like actually saying that this dude
Just came at 100%. Like Eddie pepitone zangri with that kind of Limbs
Musical rage behind it it's just
Yeah it's confounding
I mean I can't tell but I am willing to believe that there is a
That his intention is humor
UK
That is about as little criticism as you can
Can give anybody trying to be funny
I am willing to admit
It's possible
You were maybe
Attempt
Humor
AMC Hulen
But again I apologize that you had to hear Alexei jaculation
So Alex
But this is this is also one of my favorites
Thanks there with
The times that he finds a new song to rant over
What he says something like this
F****** love it
You do not going to play the head of the US teachers union saying
4shared
I love it when he's a quite approved
To prove something cuz you're making claims dude everybody knows this
That is my proof
Sodium the teachers union did voice support for vaccine mandate
But
Alex doesn't cover it
And he seems angry about proving any
Your whole thing is proving thing
Iris
Zent's
You
Forcing me to look into the things that I am making up because they are not true sir
Another thing that he is
Not refusing
It's the story of Germany
What are the major German newspapers highly respected
Hi largest
Medical Union of doctors in the country
All your top doctors is one guy right
Union came out
In March
Looks like these vaccines are killing a lot of people
Now they've been doing spot checks on her finding starting to 40% depending on where they look
30 below 40 Bhai
35% of the death of Germany
About people they're giving autopsy
Wow
Way to tell the story
But now I want it I told you that you're going to love
The hilarity that ensues
And this is where
You may remember that when I was
Breaking down with the story is actually about
Did the original article included some comments from people
From the Paul are looking
Who were saying that this doesn't match up with anything that we're seeing
I assume they own the Wuhan Laboratory
Okay Alex
Makes a crucial mistake
Eugenics organization that calls for worldly population
Paul Ehrlich Society
Has come out in
You're not at your not epidemiologist
Your environmental organization
Cuz you're not environmentalist
Environmental organization, environmentalists
Bill Gates
Never heard that before
Open
Because they wrote the battle plan
Alec doesn't talk about Paul Ehrlich all the time but he does bring him up sometimes mostly it's John holdren.
Ecocide derelict was also the co-author of that
Institute is not an environmental organization
Text me part of the German government and it's a biomedical research center
About the polarity
Society
No
It better
Alex is confusing Paul are like who the Institute is named after with Paul are are like that fell off
No no no
Maybe this is just embarrassing obvious you have no f****** clue what you're
Talkin about
For this log
No idea what you're talkin
Pretty amazing
Wow Paul Who The Institute was named after was an immunologist who cured syphilis
He died in 1915 a good 62 years before the other Paul co-authored
The textbook Alex him
Sure just amazing how f****** stupid Alex amazing
Again this is one of the things that's like it seems like maybe we're just nitpicking
Reality
You have to understand how Alex processes information
When keys
Doing these things about headlines he writes a story in it and he just
I have extraneous details to stop
He sees the name Paul Arabic
Institute is like oh my God I know who Paul are looking up
And he just decides to write a story about it based on like oh I have this
This textbook that I've made everyone afraid of
They're the same person no they're not you have no idea what you're talkin about
You just just presenting things with the authority and confidence of somebody who knows what they're talking about
When in reality is just a
F****** idiot
But it's not it's not nitpicking
If he misspoke
You know like when he plays the clips
Does Nancy Pelosi misspeaking and all that s***
That's
A mistake
This is a foundational element of everything he believes
And he just has no idea
No idea
It doesn't matter
It doesn't it's like with the it is one guy
It's one guy you know like he's basing and now he turned into a whole you if it was like the f******
If it was like the octopus that picked world
Winners who is life just picked out of a can like maybe it hurts
He be like the entire Union of American Pathologists Eric
But he's insane but what's he
His version of it if you
Like it makes sense
So like Paul are like
Beholder
Eco science
That apparently has to do with how you kill off a population using vaccines and blah blah blah
So yeah it's it's in there it's
It's great it
If the planets
It's a battle plan the original battle plan for 1977
It gets implemented in
To the world right everybody is doing it and now their plans are coming to fruition
Visa vie
The covid vaccine
Korloff everybody
There is a guy
Germany
Who's trying to say hold on now the vaccines are killing everybody
And the Paul are like
Institute is the one who tries to debunk that it makes total sense
Except for the part where there's poop all Airline
Reincarnate
No
If not
For that
Very important facts
Civilian Tire Roofing makes a great story except for
Blackjack
Yeah yeah yeah
Critical it's like whenever it's like in that eleventh-hour situation where somebody finally
Confirms your Alibi after you've gone through like
15 days of
See
We've made our case and then the person's like where there's one problem though
He was not there to do that they do the different person with the same name
Almost got him though
So Alex gets back to complaining about Obama's party and he doesn't seem to know that it was a birthday party
I find this very weird
Bananas work gets a little bit more race
Play It Again with audio Barack Obama's in a baby blue outfit
Big rapper chain
Look at the list who's there as much balls scum
People are all going straight to hell
Something more
Disgusting in this
What do they celebrate
We overthrow the election
We overthrow Trump
We Trump vaccine
Celebrating Obama's 60th 60th birthday that they're celebrating
Inherent
Disgusting racism here of like only seeing non-white people as being able to be used
Birthing
That's how that mentality is pretty disc
Hey hey this guy works
Community organizer in Chicago
Found a bridge of Senator then it became the president United States
Obviously doesn't have any agency of his own by the CIA
Absolutely
So
Another another thing that we we notice all the time
In Alex's coverage
Is that that that Razor's Edge of it
Extremism which is
You have to constantly be winning but also losing directions
Alex takes.two
Parody
Level here
Welcome back we're now into our number to evil is always going to make a run at good
Gonzales pro-opposition
It will launch a Full Assault
What you doing right now
I'd rather take overall sneakily but
Open pedophilia is good World garbage good
Unapproved inoculations are good censorship good
This is real desperation
Astrostyle
I use the analogy of Blade Runner the original lyrics
Issued
When she realizes she's
That's what's going on right now
Question is how many of us are they going to Dragon the hole in them
All these nuclear weapons a bioweapon
Almost Maine releasing
Any by any stretch of the imagination
They are getting their ass handed to
We're just
The Lust For Freedom
A good word the Bible but it's a good word to me
You understand that
It's my goddess
Freedom is his goddess I mean
He understands that the point of lust is that it takes away from your work
Bishop of God
I don't think he understands a lot of the nuances of
Of religion
Truth is freedom
Well that I mean God is actually
If part of the point of
His religion is
Is to become a servant before God
Lust after Freedom you're literally didn't INB exist
Would dig
Satan
Oh man his favorite thing is when God said do what thou wilt
I'm telling you it's false flag
He's been saying the whole time could be
So Alex is presenting
Like we're kicking the s*** out of these gloves but look out they're going to Nuke us
We are so powerful there won't even press that button
Maybe a bad day from one of these Global it's and we're all f***
Deadpool
So Alex gets to talk about how Lady Lady freedom
And it leads him to get a little bit mad
About the idea of bowing down to lesser men
It's first and foremost it's it's it's it's
It's my goddess
Amazon
The goddess worship
I do like two things.
Creative but you get what I'm saying
Northstar unfollowing it's real
See there's my flashlight
Felicia
I want to burn in hell before I did I love you Jesus help me
Point is I will not
Now about Trump
Let's get in the big news here
Joe Rogan
Amazing the big news
I know.
There's a progression here that is
It's so goddamn funny he's screaming about how he's not going to bow down to a lesser bad
I will not
Let's go to the news
Alone is hilarious
Wolf Blitzer screaming about how he will not bow to a man
Newscaster
Speech that Edward armero gave where he just
I just went
Off on Eisenhower right just went off on Eisenhower said that Eisenhower the worst president ever
F****** he's going to
Light himself on fire before the Vietcong ever even f****** tried it he is going to kill everybody and then of course
If you're going to go back to the Dukes
Hilarious
Let's get to the big news and it's big news of The Joe Rogan
Joe Rogan
Jotaro vs. might guy
It's a one-two punch that I I just
I love that
Tilex is mad that people are critiquing Joe Rogan
About is vaccine stupidity
I like how we had a theory that maybe this isn't so not
On purpose this it maybe this isn't
So on
Unintentional Rogan's platform anti-vax
Is like
All right now
Yeah I see it seems like he's
Vietnamese dipping his toes further
Hope
Spotify feels real good about their investment real good
Is on that same path feels like that
18 year older like 14 year olds were on 10 years ago where the YouTube algorithm
Like all of his friends just keep recommended Hayes
Here's a good guy here's a good guy here's a good guy and then all the sudden the guy from news radio is now like
I'm going to say it
We're going to have to get rid of the black population in your life
Yeah I think that there is a dark
Possible future where Rogan
Is essentially like
Another Ali
Yeah yeah
A passively redpilled assholes I think that he's too old
For it to be like really effective
It'll take a while for him to
Really break hard
To the extreme as the presentation of a naive dope
Yeah kind of is a protective shield
For his hundred million dollar contract
I think the
Saving Gracie has is that
Republican politicians and far-right figures don't do a s*** ton of drugs all the time or at least our open about
Where is he's just like
I am high all the time
What are you going to do follow me
Get out of here
Alex plays a clip
Rogan talking about this up
Episode cuz I do not have the time for that
Unless Alex is on
But I think there's a really Elementary
Thinking errors
That you can pinpoint
In Nairobi
I want to play the club but I want to show you
Just a small snapshot
Small snapshot
Organization sayings
But the system knows what he says true
They are simply
Hoping you don't look at
At the information
So here's what he had to say if you guys going
Vaccination can enhance the transmission
Highly virulent pathogen
Right so this is a scientific paper
From 2000 and
That shows
If here's it's that there's this one import
Vaccines
To keep the host alive
But still allow transmission
Strains to circulate in a population
So
Vaccine
Kill the virus
Vaccines
Like this one things were finding out about
What are calling brakes
Do people who are vaccine
We can still get covid
And they can still transmit Kobe
Is recently
Vaccinated comedian
Gave
Cloven vaccinated some of them not
That
Situation where the vaccine just
Text you from Sirius
Damage
Protect
Text you from really being
Like badly
Hospitalized
But doesn't stop
You from getting the virus
Kompas
Sibley lead
Houghton virus
So these
People that are saying
So it's these people that are responsible for the variance
Actually scientific
Sick papers
Set point
Two singular very
Covid-19
By having so many people
With a vaccine that
Doesn't
Tilly's
It actually can lead to more
Viruses
So it is
It is true that the fact there are some breakthrough infections that that's not ideal in a perfect world vaccines would stop this
Of any illness
However there's a critical thinking errors that Joe Rogan is making
In here that required for this argument to make any sense
He's acting as if the vaccine has no effect on whether or not a person will
We covid which is
Is not true
It greatly reduces transmission even if it doesn't do so
Completely
Ozark Mendes essentially him taking the present circumstances and comparing them to a perfect
Vaccine
In that context
Yeah this vaccine doesn't look so good
Some people will still get mild cases of the virus and they have the potential to pass it along
The other people
What really should be done however is compare this vaccine to the actual alternative
I wish things would look like with
New vaccine
Even though we do have to stipulate that some people can transmit the virus even though they're vaccinated
The alternative is people who are not vaccinated who spread the virus a lot more
In reality Rogen's argument against vaccinations only makes sense as an argument in favor of vaccinations
If his concern is the potential for viral mutation in transmission
The risk of that is substantially higher the lower the rate of vaccination isn't
The community
Also in the front turn of events Andrew read the scientist who authored the study Jose talking about has come out and said quote
Joe Rogan is getting this
Wheatley wrong
Sounds about right
Yeah I don't I don't I don't know I don't know
I don't know if this is the breaking news The Joe Rogan
Open Smart that Alex wants to
Okay
All I'm saying
Is
If it doesn't solve
All of our problems immediately and
Permanently
What we should do
Is
Wait a little bit
See how the science looks
Let several hundred million people died
And then I'll think about getting vaccinated
I think I think they went when you create
Sort of
Bizarre alternatives to comparison something to eat you can always make that something look either really bad or really good
And that that's
Kind of the mistake
I'm willing to believe that Rogan is making
Just like a mistake there
I in some in some way like I think he just hasn't thought about anything
Some people are not pointing out
That with scuba gear is
You go too far down
Sometimes the
The pressure will make a
Did not work
And that's why we should never go in the water
This checks out
Waterford why won't anybody you can't go lower than 1200
So Alex gets a little bit heavy and he starts talking about Bible verses
I think it
This is another instance of a thing that you eat
I think he doesn't understand
Bible
Talk to ya
You understand that your son everything in the universe
Give my people the people that love Justice and good
Wannabe good
Which are called by my name
Shall humble themselves and stop playing God
13 day was about his own hearts
David was a man after God's Own Heart because he had unwavering faith in because he was repentant
No not from that is not supposed to be the god also wants to f*** his
Joshua
That's what the takeaway from that
That story is
Daily that God's your bro man
David the man after God's heart because he like to sling ticker rap-up
That's bulshit you're going to tell me that God doesn't get it
I
What you think Zeus didn't f***
Well I mean the problem really that I guess I have
Is that just one
Well
I always forget to apply the same level of bad reading comprehension that Alex has for the news
Brother just tags have thing that he cares about know why I always forget
I'm talking about this
This Bible verse
Excited about
It's not unlike
Like Isis
In many ways
Barack Obama party
Or going to a
Chuck Schumer party
Bill Clinton party
A party is a Chuck Schumer party don't stop
Bodies in the world
But you just pull off the side of the highway and some old black church
White Church some old Hispanic
For real people are
Satisfied
You feel real
Everything they claim they are
Billiards
Stop worshipping
Allentown to oven stopped working out of this stupid ass
You're going to lose this thing
11 this damn flush given all your power
Oceans on it
Captain all day
What is God's Temple
But if you lose your body in the service against evil that is a blessing
Alright
Yeah yeah that's
Hey hey
Just so you know
That as long as it look
You're going to die anyways
So you might as well die in service to the Lord
If you die fighting globalist
The blessing
Twice as much heavy
You get the most happen
That's upsetting also What potions are you putting
In Harry Potter what is happening people
Play into many Adventure video game
Season ocean
I don't understand the lotion he's actually specifically referencing I high potion which
Florastor 500
So Alex gets to talk about his commitment to the Infowars
Andy says something that
Kind of surprised me
Fortune
Becoming that's coming up
And I will have all the stuff
I'll just say this right now
If I had two or three times the funding we've got I could have done a lot more and I'm not bitching
Completely
Sell my house
Which is not even
Hard decision to make
Everything's in
Alien laser
So just go to mypillow.com man
God that's
Against
Globalist
Talking pillow
Percent
Cut out of everyone
Ouch
Okay
This sounds like just
A rerun
Listen if I were a better businessman I would have been able to do more for you but I'm not that good so I'm real
Rub buck and ripping my pillow now
I will tell you I will tell you that we overextended ourselves in the info
We bought
They told us it was stupid to buy tanks made out of diamond baby
Maybe it was a bad move
And I see now that they might have been right
But would you consider buying pillow
Let me know the time and I was working at that f****** coupon place
And one day everybody is
Working and he's just like the owner of the company is just like
You know what
I'm going to turn the third floor into a coffee shop you know it's going to be like a Starbucks nobody will have to pay for it
I'm giving you guys again
No
Hey
You a******
Pictures of very Groupon app
Yeah you're a bunch of dick
Yeah alright
This little part of the offices decorated like a
Tree
So it's like a little Forest that you can go do work in a bunch of Lacrosse around
Why am I still a temp after a year-and-a-half
Exactly the a****** how your f****** dick
Alex Quebec to the Germany story
And what now that we know
He has the wrong air lick
It's kind of funny to recognize that that's
Basically his entire angle on the store hun real unreal
That one of the leading pathologist in Germany
He's done his own study of a bunch of that bodies found the same number
30 to 40%.
Bodies
34% of bodies there now autopsy
The vaccines
Where's my book
What I do in my house
Oh no
But don't worry
Who's in the article
Dr. John B holdren
Institution saying was no evidence is not true
When he wrote
The science book on depopulation
Poison vaccine poison Florida and everything else
It's playing finally got it.
Man
Just embarrassing
Just I mean
Could not bet like sitting there I felt like I was
Was handing him a rope
Slowly
Dislike
Here you go I guess you I guess this is all your decision I'm just holding the rope man I'm not doing any
I'm not moving or just my walking cane
Get on your desk
I don't know I always find it interesting to imagine the audience
Listening to this
I am still taking him seriously
What are the reasons that they can is that the information that there are two politics and Alex has no idea what he's talking about that never
Never penetrates
Infowars
Contact that never gets on the show
And if you were just passively listening to this
It's really easy to assume that it is the same Paul are like
Cuz why not
There were people are like Institute
Make that two this famous scientist
Oregano
One of them
He's a guy whose work was in ecological
Concerned
You know
It's a little weird
Baby weighing in on the science and Germany about like
You know it would biological and
Illogical the only thing that you can do that you're like
You know what maybe there is a
Italian for sure
Oh and yeah maybe there is this German Paul Ehrlich Institute just really admired Paul Erdos at work
And so they named it after it maybe he endowed the beginning of the end
2 / Middle School named after him
Passively listening you could be like I am make sense
It is the same and it's not and Alex's building so much of this conspiracy on the idea
But it's suspicious
Because it's the same person
It's not as if
That's not good
Alex even just reporting on this story you can't help it
Themself
Adding lies
Received support from
Association of German pets
Autopsies of accident people who died within a certain time frame
Nation should be performed
Depart at airbnb's Alex
Editorialize article
Because the rest of the stuff makes sense
The people
Kalologie Union
Look at more people should dad be
Okay I'll talk to you
Please cuz then we'd have more information to go on
12 out of 40 is not the sample size you can use to draw a conclusion
Is about a large
Population
Even
Thirty-two 40% of those people who are being referenced in this article
They did not prove
That they died vaccination
So there is more information that is required
And that is what there's call for
More
Alex adding that other detail onto the story is what he does because
The actual text of this
Article that he's reading is underwhelming
It doesn't match zika
Conspiracies
But he's built up around
Hey this guy's got a concerns maybe let's find out some more stuff
Right
Oh okay
So I got to
I got towards the end of this episode
And
I was
Kind of
Feeling
Empty
Martial law begins on Wednesday
It seems like that would be more important
For Alex
Not knowing who Paul are like
But there is
You know
Last episode
Pretty intense
We're going work with happening yeah there's this emergency alert system thing that's going to be
Cover for the internet takeover
Biden's going to
To put in this
Martial law and also maybe a climate emergency but maybe it'll happen a different day going to happen
Does he realize that his sponsor
Is holding a three-day-long talkathon
To overthrow the
The government
He does
I was I was
Concerned that it hadn't come up
That yeah come up on this episode
And now it doesn't maybe we shouldn't worry about it
Maybe maybe the 11th of February
Maybe but I'm not
I'm glad that the boom operator
Mention this
Real quick
This boom operator
Nose without the production credits
Absolutely no proposal
Explain the blue ball Creator brought this up
It's staggering
This is what this is the VIP of Infowars operator
Cuz it is not their job to give a s*** no and apparently they're coming through in the clutch
And telling Alex hey you forgot to talk about this the only member of his staff who is never f***** up his mic
Has always sounded good but he's wearing like a lapel mic
Cover today
I said last week I'm going to head to my bad
Santa Clara
Obama
Also known as a
Reporting slip was actually real
When the president Let It Go
Still at Meijer
Passageway
A lot of dependent clauses there's a lot going on a lot of we've already got a little
I didn't say anything weird
Beatles rights
Always gotten so far
Fully intended
Election to the country again
Domestic Security Forces spies
Contact tracers
You have an emergency alert system
Modell's
Putting it on
And I'm not saying for sure
Bible do it that but
In the White House meeting
Drawing of a plan
Call
Show emergency
On the 11th
They may not do it but
Emergency alert
Maybe maybe it's not anything and maybe it maybe just like the end of the world
We listening to this on the way to FEMA camps
I don't know maybe maybe the entire day's programming that I did those who pursue
Sensational
Maybe it was nothing
Now you know but we got a few sales out of it so goddamn the tip of the spear
Almost Happy
We would have been at that beer
Stabbing what's happening
This is kind of impressive in some ways
I mean he's given up on this narrative before it even like he is
Cut bait
Easy 100%
Smartest move
I think it well yeah I guess if you were just trying to
Push sales that is a smartest move
Smarter move
Bigger picture
For the help
Book Society
Is don't do this
That would be the smartest
Yeah that would be the acting this way
You're making termite lintel
Is not worth it
Now
No it's not
Speaking of Mike Lindell
Alex
Going to be on location this week
I'm going to be in Sioux Falls
South Dakota
2 mi from there
Is it is working for
After all of that
You sound
Defeated
Confidence
The after this
72 hours
We will have a 90 Supreme Court Justice
Holyshit
The delivery of him being like Mike's got a lot of evidence and no he doesn't
I also think that there is like
Alex
I think is going because
He might be realize like that like
Mike Lindell is not going to be able to
The fun things after this
No it's a last-ditch effort I don't I don't know how deep
These pillow bags are
The pocket
Pillow Pockets that laundry is running low
Can't
Possibly
Go on forever
Alex
He may be
Alright
Imma take what I can get here
I'm going to head over there to do some chalk
And then I'm going to try and
Double my speaking fee for Friday's episode
What I was thinking about doing
Is the episode about the end of the world this app
No
Cuz we've already
So I was thinking about doing something
Think about Mike lindell's stream
But man I don't know where to start it set like 3 days long I don't know
Where to start or end it's going to be a stream-of-consciousness rant and he's planning on doing it for 72 straight
I've seen some people posting some nice Clips on Twitter
And how well it's going
Insofar
And I appreciate that but what I think I'm going to do is check in on Alex's
Cara vanity project part 3 think we're going to have to
It's not really a caravan I need another Pawn
You come up with something okay
Sssniperwolf
Sabrewulf
Cyber Symposium wolf
We could
Could call it my road trip
Now
I want to make a my pillow pain but I'm
I'm drawing a blank right now
Brutal to my Thriller
It's not great
Tropical Falls
Sioux Falls but like getting sued false
Footballs
There we go I don't know how to spell that
Doing they're out on the road
Very sad
Sounding announcement
For him here on the Sunday episode
Leads me to believe that his coverage is going to be a little bit mopey
Anyway we will check in on that but
Tell them Jordan River website
No it's not, but it didn't knowledge fight we're referencing died in 1920
Me too I'd found out.
Go on Twitter @paul Ehrlich
And at Paul are are like
Facebook
I love you
Until then amnio and Lido MDX clerk I'm Daryl Rhonda
Robot
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work