I have great respect for knowledge like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guy
Monica
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Everybody
At the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
Indeed we are.
Jordan
Fashion for Yahoo
This might come off Patty and maybe insulting
Sing to you
But it is a bright spot
You can take that or you can take a bright spot that doesn't sound like a bright spot
I could get us to a brighter place you like
Bright spot like a workplace evaluation dismissed this system that is not good not good
Onodi the petty and possibly a wanted I've been doing all these but
I am sending buttons at people and
The emails
Taking people's addresses
Insolvent
I'm not going to say exactly how many I've gone through but I will say it's in the low four digits
I got I forgot one the other day haha
That was addressed to you
Literally all the other puppies
Almost all of them are like damn I know you're the one
There was one only one out of all of them that was addressed to Jordan and then said something
Like say hi to dance
Whatever that is
Gets
I don't know I'm going to send you something
Special that's what's going to happen I thought that was really amazing
It's very funny
I mean it's it's something to start from every Journey Of A Thousand Miles begins with one
Email
The other the other maybe not a bright spot a better place
Is
I have a message
To KitKat
Shut it down
Original.
Regular ones fine with these flavors
The fruity cereal one
Key lime pie
Shut it down
It is it is funny how it seems like what happened with most of these candy companies are like McDonald's or something you've
See what they do in Japan or something here like
The race ball flavored Kit Kat what are you talking about that was 10 years ago or like
We should try all these flavors and now they're here and we're like stop it
Shut it down maybe there is a way to do a while I may be in Japan
It's being jonuel
And maybe that is the case
It's not being done well here
Will be in a better place
If you just stop it stop it stop it calling you out who loves novels and things
Stop
How about you with your breakfast is the challenge has returned
MTV Challenge by one reality TV show that I have somebody who's spent
Hours watching Survivor
Season upon season I must shake my head at you
I don't know why those stupid idiots I just I just love him so much
The only problem this year is for the past few years
I've been tracking
My new favorite character I've let you know remember young CT
Of course just crazy that guy absolutely eyes bloodshot always ready
New Years for a few years
He's been fat CT it's been fantastic
Apparently something happened my partner insist that he just got divorced but
Because he is back to being
Right here if the guy also back to being of violently abusive
No no
Completely different like he's a weird dad
The younger people are having trouble they always show up next to him and he's like
Like I ain't know what you got
You got to see what happen
You know like he's just
He's just this weird Buddha
Is a drunken rage if he was really big
And now he's gotten
Back I bet he's off his meds if he's definitely more likely to drink
Thought about you to be having these
Experience and excitement that I had when I was
22 watching CT
The little Unbecoming for a thirty-year-old but whatever
How do you say again maybe somebody was watching
In the past 3 weeks
Still watching it until I actively don't enjoy it
That might be a theme in my life
Alex Jones
I don't like it and I
Alright therapies on Wednesdays
Really weird so Jordan today we have a episode where dipping back
Cancel last week
India at the end of last week where we did is we put out
Reposted episode of bathtubs
Just came out the
He was sort of behind some of this information
The Mike Lindell was going over a person poziom right
And I kind of realized we need to do now
Disable Symposium is over
Is it we need to go back and look at this as a snapshot
We need now we have closure I never got ahold we'd know for sure
They Trump did not
Cymbalta
He was an open question at the end of last week
There were some people who really did think
Who really do you record on Thursday so we didn't know what was going to happen on Friday the 13
Is very important in numerology
Bickley to the global
The occultist
No I would finally believe in all superstitions regarding Friday the 13th if suddenly Trump was
Reinstated as president I would be like
I guess they're all true
I guess there we
If we
Had a 13th floor in a hotel after Trump got reinstated
If I were Trump and I got reinstated on Friday the 13th as president
Take to the podium
At my first words would be
Bwahahaha
Straight up dr. Wily call it a comeback or something like I do something funny
Oh man
I don't know if you get cleft would say that if you get elected on Friday you will owe me
Almost certainly be assassinated on Saturday
Let her be gone till November
Go go that don't make him a Halo no
Do we do a show
Are We Done Yet
August 11th
1012 figure middle of the week for Wednesday we can
Finish off the Cyber symposium
Love it because there's that there's a good amount
Through
Really
Really delightfully
Funny stupidity
Does new walk
Do first
My opening argument is this knowledge phytest
To clean up I'll 45 but I'm tuckered out
Thank you so much and I apologize
I'm about to shout outs going on in there
How much are nopales
Full circle map
Beacon of Hope For Humanity and everybody knows it thank you so much right now bazzi why
Then we got a couple of texts
Gretzky
Founding member number 9 of the official Stacey Q fan club
Thank you so much you're not like Stacy
SECU
2 of
Hearts
Two hearts
That beat as one
You should go check it out
Money off that heroin
Check out that Stacy
Does a gym Banger for made gym playlist
Pretty regularly get the doctor to a podcast but I'm here for sitting on Jerome corsi
Space that's what I'm about
It's as important as making sure everyone remembers
Stacey Q
I'm Amanda also got some Editions
To bring in Scotland
There's a placard on it that says
This tree is dedicated to saline all hail the great Saline
So now there's a tree in Scotland with saline slacker.
To leave a legacy
Benches or some s*** no way we got to Celine on the tree
That's the way we do and then also Marcella got in touch
I wanted to shout out for the pet rescue
Are the Mendocino Shelter Pet Rescue
Are there helping animals that are being
But like maybe their owners have
Medical fees that they can't take care of
Yeah another pet rescues like this in many many places around the country
Countries
They do very important work
To make sure animals are
Killed absolutely if you are near a pet rescue please help
Please help
Let's talk about August 11th first
This
Maybe the David
This is the day that Alex has built up as the David
Biden is going to announce martial law
Right now maybe it'll happen
But maybe it won't and if it doesn't happen it's because he's scared the globalist
Until you try to walk that line here on the 11th
I want to play the puppet in Chief
Nationwide
Band-Aids for masks
Non-essential businesses
They were talking about
Day
But I stand by my sources and Jack stomach sources they were looking at
As the day to announce new Nationwide man
Last night
Biden said he's looking at the wall
Violates the law
So maybe it's going to happen
Start today
Alex also has to know that the emergency alert test
Going to happen while he's on there
Yeah so
This is a weird
He's putting himself
In a barrel
You shouldn't do this
List yourself you know that eventually
You're going
To be on air when the thing doesn't happen
That you said maybe
Sure but have you considered doing a little bit of soft shoe and saying X
Stage left
Maybe
Well we will see what happens okay
But before that that deadline hits
I don't have some time to fill and so he does it by
Complaining about math
Stop versus another particula
McAlister's on the back
This product is
Product is not a respirator and will not provide
Any
Protection against covid-19 Coronavirus
Coronavirus
Want to read that again
Not
Not a respirator
And will not
Provide any protection against covid-19
Coronavirus coronavirus Azure contaminants
Let's just read it one more time
Not
Not a respirator
And will not
Not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not not
Any any any any covid-19 covid-19
Coronavirus vs. other viruses viruses or other
Contaminants
I'm not trying to get nauseous here
I need him to read it again
I didn't get that
And you know he read it so many times it's like when you say a word too many times and it loses all meeting shovel
Shovel
Any shovel
You kept saying I started thinking about belly buttons like you don't need to eat or not doing this well
Yai
I think that was
Poor attempt to not be obnoxious
If that's truly is invention
Sat
That is to doing his show what
Increasing your font to
20 is to writing a paper
Do you know what I mean like
I'm going to waste as much time as I can sing as little as I
Yeah that's also like
The equivalent of
Putting something in all caps and thinking you're strengthening arrabbiata
Just from a meme that went around last year early in the antimatter
Ask days
It's my feeling that the messaging on mask
Has been pretty clear if you're actually paying attention
And not a knee-jerk reaction Dairy a******
Masks are an important part of the pandemic response but doctors and health experts I've seen
I've been pretty consistent
Getting across at the way that they help is not by making the wearers
Super safe from things getting
They helped by limiting the amount of droplets
That escape
From the wear themselves
By limiting the amount of possible virus you could be
Spreading you in effect
Protect everyone around you by reducing the odds of them
Coming in contact with the virus themselves
How to pierce to be arguing against a straw man here namely that the reason to wear masks
Check yourself
You can repeat that warning labels
From a boxer
So masks 100 times if he wants it just doesn't mean anything
He's arguing against the wrong
Yeah it's
It does seem like there has been a lot of resources spent trying to
Confuse people as to what the
The point is you know like
If you would
Explain to somebody if rationally without
The influence of everything that
It's about protecting others
I think it will not be hard to convince
The problem is that trillions of dollars
Accusing people into being that's about a combined effort that has a
The cumulative effect absolutely
So the text that I was reading is just from this meme
It's not the packaging of an n95 mask
It's just a box of
Standard cloth masks
Who's Isabella's in all this s***
And repeating it over and over again
Because then
He's hoping it will Drive-In
To the mines
Of his listeners
Zambia compelling
All caps
Yeah you might as well be like this is not scuba gear you cannot breathe underwater with this
Breathing underwater
That's some bad advice
At least
Say about advice
You got to smoke in the water
You better have goggles on
I don't try it at home
Very long this is useful
Useful conversation
Just giving you a pointless piece of information
And said that it's super effective but it also kill you
Hey this
Just so you know this is how you make this
Function right
You will die
Go to it and this is route
It'll work for a little while but also you'll probably kill yourself
Hey don't go back into a burning building
Wow now hiring
So Alex talk some more about this this warning label that's on the back of these Mass
About belly button
Censored
Wait the warning label is warning label is that
Any media that wants to cover it
It's answered
Except for the media that Alec
What is sighting in Taka
Think about how
That's trouble
Look at all these articles
Wul article
Verified fact check why the face Matchbox says it provides no protection to the where
You try to put this out on Twitter Facebook YouTube Google any of them
Apple let you put these articles out local news national news
Happy that's not
True
This article itself you can post
Anywhere
Explain to me how there can be all these articles
Which are assumably posted by and hosted by these Outlet
And yet also
All these artists
I'll be suggesting that there are a large number of
Octopi
Social media
I don't think that maybe some of the articles that are on like really dicey blogs
Maybe end up with her like hey this is improve warning
Right maybe that is something that happens if you try to post them on social media
Maybe
But this article that Alex is talking about the what is it the the USA 9 the wusa9 local
News article that you can post whatever you want it part of the reason is because
It is
Where Alex is seeing this meme
Image of it but it describes
And explains why this meme is sending inaccurate information
Context it's writer Asian
And I don't know I don't know what I don't have
But
Compelling
Feeling about this being a sensitive
Yeah I'm going to go with no this is not censorship
There are all these articles
So now also be surgeon-general like
A year ago said Don't wear mask that cuz man
Surgeon General
Which was true
February
See how that works oh
See how that works
That's a headline that I was reading
From February of last year when the Surgeon General dr. Jerome Adams came out and asked the public to stop buying all
All the matter wasn't it because people were hoarding a s*** ton of masks barbecue couple issues
One of these uses that there is a fear that the public could make a run
Nan masks
It was possible then they
Medical professionals will be unable to get
Protective gear they needed
Do their job
Another factor it's super important
To consider that at this point in February twenty
T20 we didn't know what we know now
This is prior to the understanding of the novel coronavirus could be
Be transmitted by people prior to them developing
Symptoms
If you're operating under the assumption that only symptomatic people are contagious then widespread masking isn't really all that important
People have symptoms should stay home or where I'm asking that's largely cut down on a lot of the transmission
However it pre-symptomatic and asymptomatic cases of the coronavirus or able to cause new infections
Leave a completely different scenario on your hands
Now if you
You don't have symptoms
You may not be sick
But you might be pre-symptomatic or asymptomatic so even if you feel completely normal there's a chance that you could begin
If you're going out in public
Without a mask
This Dynamic is what change the government official guide
Amazon widespread mask
Understand
MedExpress was possible there really wasn't that much of a reason for people
Both wear masks unless they were sick
After that aspect of the virus is better understood game critical for people
Wear mask
Not to protect themselves but
To drastically reduce transmission to other
Alex even knows all this in his willingly misleading his audience about very important public health issues
Or he's really unable to
Breast basic
Concepts and probably shouldn't be trusted
Interpret information
Yeah
Yeah it's kind of interesting that far right propaganda usually boils down to
Future could be anything
Past can be seen 2020
Yeah
Yeah really f****** nailed it and so much of this
If you
You get down to the actual details and
The fact of the Imp
Information that there
Disseminating
It really does break down into two possible paths
You're too dumb to understand what you're talking about
Or you're willfully misrepresenting this
And putting people
Greater risk
I don't know
Neither is acceptable
Yeah I mean you know you can be both too dumb to understand.
The greater context but understand just enough
To distort it
In order to make money
I think I just explained America
So you up buddy
His name is Randy
If my best friend
Concerns that Rand Paul has been censored
Bye
All sorts of media
YouTube
He wasn't concerned about Rand Paul's wife using information in a little bit
But yeah Rand Paul Valley was giving a little bit of a
About how
This this meme
About masks not helping people
Look at me
Look at that mean there's nothing to look at over here
Intuit
Complaining about it
Here's his response video Indian also taken down
Recently I shared a video on my YouTube page
It was an interview between myself and a journalist
We discussed a variety of topics including
The science behind wearing masks
Apparently would you care to contradict dr. fauci in the government
YouTube has removed my video
If you want to see the video it's up on rumble.com does not censor the news
What's unpack here
First it recently came out like you mentioned that Rand Paul's wife box talking
Gilead Pharmaceuticals in February twenty
20 which is only disclose the
This past week well past the 45-day deadline
Supposed to report this
He's kind of purchases at
I would assume that she just bought stocking Rumble
Was well huh
He personally 45 days after his wife stock purchase happen
To be right in that sweet spot last March when Kelly loffler and David Perdue
We're getting very serious criticism
From the Press about how they may have used Insider information
Gained and briefings to make stock market
At least they didn't face any consequences
Is 4in but it also sounds like
Exactly the sort of time that a man with Integrity like Rand Paul
Yeah I wouldn't want to step up and create any kind of appearances that he was doing similar ship
I bet he doesn't want to debate
Whether or not people in power
I should be able to buy stocks or not
Probably not
This revelation of Paul's wife stock purchase and it
It's very delayed disclosure amount
The problem
The first is that there is the appearance of insider trading
There may be no insider-trading going on and it's
Plausible that Miss Paul Bop
Let's talk without any information
France
Okay so it looks really bad
The second problem is that this means that Rand Paul had an undisclosed financial interest
Austin government policy as it relates to covid response
Weather naughty Act
Did the further those interests
He stood to gain
Four more people getting sick
And from there not being a vaccine
That is widely available
Because they pop Gilead
Produces rendezevere
There may be no malfeasance here but there's a giant cloud of Suspicion and I would like Grandpa to debate you on that's okay
I would too
Also it seems like Rand Paul might be promoting Rumble
That was a little bit
Declaring rumble.com
They don't censor your information
Mbele
Raise an eyebrow except
Week it was reported that Rumble was signing up people they deemed
Quote thought leaders to promote their platform as an alternative to you today that's good stuff the big names
Glenn Greenwald in Tulsa
What's wrong with those
It's enough to make you wonder if grandpa is another quote-unquote thought leader
You certainly seem to have a difficult time making
Timely disclosures of
Conflicting interests I guess maybe we'll know in 16 months whether or not that was paid
Spawn confer Rumble if you got into government to do anything other than grift and make
Money I don't understand what you're doing and
What else is it for Dan
So Alex had an intention
On the show today
Remember that song by Afroman
I was going to pay you my room but then I got high
The only song I remember
I was about to go live today
Articles
Where you at
Last night and this morning
Doing research
This morning
Man versus
Self
I intended to come in today and write a headline about major victory in the club elixir in trouble and
Came out and came up
Forgot about that
More coming as we speak
But martial arts
Reminded me
The martial arts
I was going to do a show about Victory but then I got scared
I
Remember
Today is the day that martial law is supposed to be announced at all we've got is a day about victory
Okay
Big victories of the martial law happen
The only one that matters
Yeah I think they're one of the
Primary things that he considers the victory
In terms of things he's going over is that
Number places like the military have
Confirmed that there are religious exemption
Right
It's like that's not even something
It wasn't
The case a week
To go
We knew that Vic
Grateful victory
Thank God for
For small America
Any discussion of forgetting about having
To do a show by victory
He's talked a little bit about
Women
Are going to poison people or something this is strange
The women just start poisoning everybody
Could I have a
Reference
Domestic help in East Los Angeles
Take really good care of him in
Real tide at night
It really sounds like he's telling people to kill
Made
Killing
Alex is very clearly saying poison
Poison Poison
If you have access to them
I mean like a lot of billionaires are getting divorces these days because most of them were friends with Jeff.
Epstein
I mean who's better poisoning the next why it's always the spouse Dan
I don't know what side of the law this is on but it doesn't feel this imaginary poisoning
I don't I don't think this feels yet
He's he's saying that you know like the women are going to come in and poison people because that's the stage rack
Cuz man who
Not done the job or whatever fall of Rome or it was
How to play every single culture throughout all of history this is what happened right after the play
Pyramid or whatever
The Zhou dynasty that fell due to all the women poisoning all the Gemini remember that's with humans
Sacrifice
And the meat Supply
80% human meat
Black Pyramid
And then women poison folks
I don't know
Call Montana
When you're not going to boys
Anyway
The killing is going to
And Alex
A little bit of a ramble here about how he's
Pretty good at
That stuff
Revolution
But not the one of the comics
Convert everything
We've all got red blood
The blood of Christ
Freezer meals
Call
The Red Terror
With the red blood
Assange
You sent you scare us with your red star going to spill our blood
We're more than happy when the rubber meets the road
Killing machine organize Focus reading
Don't want to kill ourselves or to steal something or feel like we're men
Only kill to protect
When the killing starts
Killings going to go for a long time
He's having a bad day and then blank
Those are the reasons that they want to kill and then he's like to protect innocence in your light come on
You know that's not your guitars there's nobody we didn't tell you what reasons we thought you wanted to kill you
You were telling us
So one of the reasons
The kill is because he believes that covid vaccines
Are killing off everybody and it's part of this
Globalist
We're all dead
Anti-conservative is he has to lie
A lot
There were the same number to Destin illnesses last year as the year before
This year
Dudley I got the forces
Various horrible covid
The world right now
And it's not the covid-19
That was the exaggerated virus
High protein
Swapping off and shedding
And spreading
But the majority
The shot
Alex does just have things anecdotally
By the way
But even he knows that that's like anything's I got to pretend I have
Stats
But I couldn't possibly have
Also says there's the same amount of illness and death last year as every other year the year before it and that's it
Completely
Journal of the American Medical Association put out a paper in April that looked at excess deaths from March
2020 to January 2021
Impound 520 2300
68 excess deaths
Took place during the
Yeah.
According to the CDC 2854522 resident deaths were reported in the United
In 2019
It takes a while for concrete numbers
Come out to that report wasn't formally released until December
2020 and as such we don't have a formalized number two
Recite right now
But the CDC has released a provisional count
For 2020
The provisional number of deaths in the US that year 2020
3358800
The stuff hour to talk about it
Bulshit
Like there's nothing
Thing to back up what he
You saying cheese areas
A lot more.
That took place last
Yeah
2 + 4 I mean
It's good to have the numbers but we all knew that
Anecdotally
Alex
Anecdotal
No no
Yeah it's ghoulish
Like this this kind of denial over
Hub.
Now that's massively
So nothing is f***** up is that Alex didn't go to his new bosses symposium
He didn't go well wowowowo
They're not he's not paid by Mike Lindell okay let's
Let's get that right out in front of the gate
He doesn't take money from Mike Lindell unless
People click on the link
He will put on his website in order to get a referral fee
In terms of the people that Alex's latched onto who are money
Folk
This is probably the most
She's like Tyler Anderson created
Career Center
With his gold sale
Money
I meant doctor group took things to a whole new level with the supplement
Right and what have you this is
Who this is
I don't think this is going to last
Now his involvement with Mike Lindell I don't think it's okay
Going to go on Long
Just
Transform products
Leica if you've fallen from gold
Fake pills
Down to just
Best pillows
There's almost a narrative tolls go and get the excited there's a gold rush
You go out and you try and do try and make your money in the mines
And then you know you need those pills to stay up and chip away at the the or
And then I take a pillow
And it's exactly like splitting his career to bed
Gold rocketed up to the top
Too many trucks
How is this
Yep
So he didn't go to the symposium
Symposium
I want to go it's so jam-packed it's a lot of great information
Cam
So I just decided to stay here
With my family
It was an omen
Plane broke down when broke down
What you going to do
I mean I don't know when the last time I heard of
The plane completely breaking down and get another flight
And you couldn't get another flight within another couple hours I a man
Gaslight
It's from Austin to Sioux Falls
Real small airplane
Real book okay okay
I don't believe that Alex doesn't have the kind of money that you can Charter a plane or something
He took a
Helicopter to go hang out with Steven Crowder
To be a
Tank plane
It would have to be a plane that has full armor plating all over it it's got to be it's got to be in style
Michael and Al promised me a jetpack it didn't come through
Butterbur Glendale promise
To be honest
Alex talks about how you know there's a lot of good news
That's true
It is true
But there's a reason
And then Alex start
Spiraling off
Send to
Nonsense
I see so much positive news everyday but I tend to only give you the bad news
One thing I won't put up with my crew
But I want no bad news yesterday
I don't want to know it later
I want to see it
I remember
15 years ago
Off record
Obelisk
A well-known age Lebanon
Okay
Alright Alex always the same speech
Don't you want to be a star and cinnamon Crusade you're going to fail the bubble
You'll never be able to save them
Don't you get what you put in all this bad news you just Karen demoralizing
You will
You are kind of people
Really cuz you don't feel like mine
Feeling
Here's my theory talk to me exactly how I talk to myself in the mirror
Furthermore even
The devil respect me
If there are
So many f****** globalist
All the time
You're my people
Maybe he is
Baby what they're saying to him is that you're never going
To be what it is you think you are you're exactly like I
BRB the ship
He admires
Secondary theory none of this
That's a good thing
The reason I believe that is Alex gets into how he's had eight meetings with the globalists
Over the years
Number and one of them
Gives us some details on
It doesn't
Sounds so much like a meeting with the globalist haha as it does like maybe he was getting interviewed
By somebody sounds right and
Abu
Calendar phone
Monthly editor coming down here
I don't California
That was terrible
The reason this is important
Alex you're just scaring them
You think you're in powering them to fight
Back
You're actually scaring them
Not going to fight now
Ali saying
Humanity
Horrible this is
They're going to wake up and decide to fight you instead of being slave
Pretty telling that Alex thinks that being interviewed by someone at the Atlanta counting is it some kind of meeting with the globe lights
Scary if you count meeting with a guy from Atlantic Monthly
I'm guessing one of the other meetings that he's referring to is like that time use on Piers Morgan show
9 include
It must yeah and Hot Springs
Kamillion meetings with global Civic out every time he's run into somebody on the hike
Bike Trailhead that's a fourth tier Global he doesn't get those I'm guessing the people who have interviewed Alex in the past
Blasted why you spend so much
Of his time scaring his list
That seems like a really obvious question
Asking if I were a journalist that might be a good place to
Start
Alex experiences this as
The globalist telling him that he's scaring the audience
Send that to submit to there
Allstate
Believe
30 bring them bad news in order to wake them up to reality and spur them to action
Really cute thing for him to believe
But it's all based on nothing and it's b*******
How to make the audience scared in a very specific way
Away where there's no productive outlet for your fear other than things that Prophet Alex
Personally
There's no real action items at the audience
Check off a list pass promoting Alex's media Outlet
And buying products
To make sure that Alex's media out looking
Continues to exist and if you are a Service employee
Poison people
Call fees are other
Beyond that there's literally nothing you can do that's going to make it
Take for example Alex's insistence that operation lockstep is a Rockefeller battle plan that was written a decade ago and is now
Being put into action
Which is what the whole covid
Pandemic
Been about
If you're in Alex's audience
What can you do with this information
Obviously you can give Alex money to keep talkin about it
Or you could spread links around to your friend so they see Alex's videos talking about it but
Ultimately what
What can you do that's productive
Even Bill Cooper was like let's buy Turner Broadcasting
You can't do anything
Because this isn't real
Do you try to band your neighbors together to have an anti operation lockstep protest
Do you write your elected officials and demand they put a stop to operation lockstep
Do call the news on demand that they look into the evil
Operation lockstep
You can't do any of that s***
And have it mean anything
Because the thing that I was just making you afraid of it isn't real
Putting together protest is a waste of your energy
Can any elected official or media entity worth their salt is going to look into your claims and immediately realize that there's no story there
The underlying documents misrepresented in weaponized
Be something it's not
Anyone
Who's not also
Just trying to get in on the grift
Isn't going to give this the time of day
Alex build his audience with empathy
We are an outrage
There's nothing they can do to proactively work
To resolve the unsettled feelings that is Goosebumps
What coverage of headlines creates
This is the business model
Because Alex knows that as long as he pretends to be the tip of the spear
The audience knows that their primary job is just
Keep him in this Bay
Big fight
Where this gets dicey is what you kind of brought up
And that a very small percentage of the audience was a very different reaction
Ultimately realize there's no productive outlet for their anger in
And Alex also caters to that
You know he fans those flames
Politically right
Plausibly deniable way or whatever I was speaking metaphorically
But there is a small percentage
That end up
Succumbing to a nihilist
Nothing is ever going to work
And part of the reason that nothing is ever going to work is
Because you're fighting
Well I mean and not
Just that but it also creates a feedback loop
For you where you believe that you will never be
We listen to
Imagine if you do send I'm going to send a letter to my elected official
Which is what I'm supposed
What to do in that letter is about all this b******* I'm continuing wall
And then they don't respond to me so clearly there's no reason to go through that the other thing that he's recommended his violin
You know like you can't
You can take send a letter to your state senator that's like we demand an end to the Griffin screeching into
Good morning and then like I don't
What are you f****** talking about people don't have time to patiently explained to you
Why is the thing you're angry about isn't real
Fiercer gryphons are mythological
They're not to be right
I know it's a hippogriffs on the map
Excuse me
Even though you sour shouted Wingardium Leviosa things are not going to float around you I'm sorry indeed
They are not
It's time for Alex's still record
The new segment on a show where Alex tells a long-winded story if it's
In this
Addition of Alex's story Coronado
He gives a woman up the Heimlich
Somebody else did it
Madeline
French restaurant
Not a fancy French restaurant just like this
Chain restaurants
Almost fast food
Wife
A year-and-a-half-old
Rex
Woman
Batwoman
White sandals
No one's helping her
She's turning blue
When I go to the Heimlich maneuver
Don't look at me like I'm a space alien
Back then I was in really good shape
What are you doing
Huge piece of bread comes out of their mouth
Huge glob she was turned out she was down syndrome
What's up
Just happened here
What is happening
And
Thank you you're a hero
Let's get out of here
That's the spirit of the left
This is weird
That story is weird
That is a weird so I can identify at least three or four different points where I think like
The story did not go with the way Alex is presenting it
I mean this is the type of story where it's like
Somebody else did they send you just
Have remembered it in your brain to where you're the hero
That's what's happened really possible or like people
Might be alarmed by the way Alex
Interact with people
And not want him charging
Now their loved one who might be choking
Person with Down Syndrome
I don't know why you said any of those word leave it leave us alone
Please stop hitting your child
Yeah maybe she wasn't choking maybe she was maybe this did happen maybe it didn't
But I don't know what any of it means
I guess that Alex has decided that they were going to sue him if you didn't leave
Which is based on nothing cuz
I know that they said you were here oh thank you so much
So he had to bail
Cuz they're going to sue him for saving her life
We got to get out of here that those people call me a hero that be there about 2 that's the spirit of Alaska
Rambling ass stories
Nothing
The entire restaurant gave us a standing ovation you know they're about to kill us
No one likes me
Valex gets to a conference mother headlines
And here's that you the first
You and the globalist arriving in UK for climate Summit
Moltres covid restrictions imposed on British citizens
But not
Private corporate leaders and government leaders coming to set up the world.
Isn't that just special
Sounds kind of fudging some details about this upcoming climate Summit taking place
Glasgow
Call the COPD
E26
Precautions and rules
A little bit
The people coming in for the
But that doesn't mean they're just
Ignoring safety measures all together the way Alex make
Cloud
For one thing delegates coming in from countries that are on the Red List will still have to isolate and quarantine Hotel
410 days upon arrival if they've not been vaccinated
In 5 days if they are fully packed
According to the BBC quote
They're also requirements to self-isolate for 10 days for those coming from a countries who are not fully vaccinated
The approved programs in the UK us or Europe
You went beyond that the summit says quote
They will have strict
Covid testing protocols
Open place including regular testing to ensure the health and well-being of all
Allstaff attendees
And the public
And
Quote there will be further Public Health measures in place at the
Cop26
Including cell
Something face coverings when delegates are not seated
And a comprehensive
Set of hygiene and ventilation measure
Yes I mean there's still tons of
Precaution being
Into account
It's just
How are you going to strike a balance between these very necessary climate Summit
I bet that you know
Clearly
Important oyi
Two reasons
And also take into consideration
Covid
Concerns you can't just
You don't want to say okay nobody can do
This at all
They already postponed to Summit from last year
Yeah if you want to stretch and say that it's unfair you've got a point but
If you're mad about it there's so much
Childish it to go I'd like what
It does seem to be from like everything I can tell they are going out of their way to still be as cautious as possible
Yeah yeah there's yeah
So Alex is another headline
Yeah this one's a little bit
Other folks are fighting bad parents are filing complaint against Atlanta Elementary School for segregating students
Classroom
Black classroom blacks their communist
Recently Kila Posey mother of a black
Accident at Mary Lin elementary school in Atlanta filed a complaint
Alleging civil rights violations on behalf of her daughter
According to the telling of the story she was discussing which second grade teacher will be the best
For her daughter with the school
Principal
Hey what you brought up one teacher that seems like a good fit the principal told her quote that's not a black
A class
Celebs that
Of the six second grade teachers of the
The school only two more options for black
At this point I can
Can find these allegations and I can also find some indications that other parents of students
The school feel like these allegations are under
Found it
Multiple of them to school yearbooks as evidence that there are not black or white classes at the school but I haven't
Seen the pictures of these yearbook sure I don't know exactly
I feel like this is a bit of a difficult situation
Since I don't know all the details in it
It's really hard to figure out what's actually going on
It only makes matters more
Confusing that the Atlanta Public School System released a statement that said quote
APS does not condone assigning students
The classrooms based solely on race
When we learned of allegations of this content occurring during virtual instruction at Mary Lin Elementary School in
August 2020
The district conducted a review and took immediate and appropriate action
At that time to resolve the issue
That kind of reads as if there was legitimate segregation going on but
It's also not specific enough to be able to determine what the
Exact situation
Right
I feel like as this civil rights
Complaint progresses we will probably learn a bit more but as of right now
I feel like this is
As much as I'm comfortable with conclude
But I can tell you that no matter what the reality of the story ends up being a
It's definitely not with Alex's
Reporting
He's playing with his classroom segregation was being done to teach white kids that they're inherently evil into packets to be communist that would be
Be very weird thing to do
Ultimately his version of the story has the focus being with the white students are the ones being was victimized by this
When it reality if he allegation
Are accurate this is a case where educational opportunities are being withheld from Blackstone
Solely based on their race seem like historically at least segregation has not been about
Spy disadvantaging white p
People in any way
It doesn't seem like that story is an indication as any indications of that either
This guy is kind of an essential piece of Alex Jones's races
Gasoline station will desire
The Coop the oppression that other groups experience and secretly being about oppression against white people
It's honestly really sick
Yeah well I mean
What you were doing
Is taking the thing that you've done to other people based solely upon race
Claiming that they're doing it to you
In order to justify
Continuing to oppress those people
Not just sick
It's f****** insane that's more or less than the game plan
If you were to be a coach
These headlines in any of these stories any realizes like
Man it was really fun talking about how I
Had meetings with
I should talk more about that
So
I was thinking about something
But I can't
Because
Non-disclosure
When
Show it to me
Fruition
Closure
What are you f****** talking
Let me just tell you this way
I recently met with representatives of the cobbler
And I told me
As if I didn't know that
We are criminals
You know you seen the Godfather movie
We control things
And our job is to destroy you
Do you know
Just so you know I need you to know this
We are criminals
We're on everything
Used
Rod
These people like I look like you just
The NBA's are like magic or something
Disclosure agreement cannot involve
Being on disclosure of criminal activity
To keep
Criminal actions are
Confessions
Secret
Because of an NBA youngboy Al Capone
Sullivan's Witnesses
So there's nothing we can do I got to say is NBA is Ironclad
Families of the mafia
Always sign and do you know how easy it would be to have a
Conspiracy a criminal conspiracy
It's so childish it's so stupid I don't know I would I would guess that maybe
Alex is talking about a deposition
I don't know
One thinks it's really fun is like event starts struggling to try and understand why these globalist
What do the thing that they're not doing like
Why
Why would they
Why would they do this why would they have a meeting just to tell me they're evil possible to understand the behaviors of
The creepy monsters in my head
Like we're criminals we're going to destroy you
YouTube
You mean to tell me your bell we didn't think you knew that
Smiley face
At the end there I was at
Jobe
From Arrested Development
Yeah I mean
Oh yeah
If the other
Yep that's bad
Lattice
Underground
Exactly what's going on here
The globalist wouldn't have a meeting with you just to say that they're evil
Because you made that up
Pretty simple
Wow shampoo
So he's killing a lot of time seem like his front is gone all the way up to size 45
Wasting so much time it could be using to talk about victories
Thredup forgot the
That's what we are. But unfortunately I think one of the problems is that
His staff is interrupt
And pretty regularly
They want it they need to tell him about like
Breaking news
Of course
Every 5 minutes they come in and give me a new article
Another hotel another wedding venue
Where you can't go if you're not injected with a poison akkala vaccine
Even though
When you take the shot
Makes you shed your admittedly
What's the business owners
I love women
What is there a good start
Sunday teenage movie
Women
Sounds like you're about to tell us otherwise you know who every person in Austin is shut their business, take a shot
Who want to be impregnated psychically by Bill Gates
Jeffrey Epstein
Okay
Alright
Hey listen
State came for the vaccine
For the wedding venues that I said nothing
Because I wasn't getting married
Hey man I've done some research into all of these businesses that
Are coming into me every five minutes from my staff which seems like
Waste of their time necessary updates
And all of these businesses are run by women
Because they want to get psychically impregnated by fauci and Bill Gates
Right
Has he ever noticed
That many of his gripes about women
Center on the idea of
If Mannitol allow them to get out of pocket
They will poison everybody and run the world like with vaccine mandates
And try and f*** Bill Gates all the time
He's a mess
So it did
We're getting to the point in the show where the emergency alert
Is scheduled to happen
We've all been very
There's a pre-announced time it's going to happen
Trying to play a game
Well it's about 7 most telephones and cable TV radio system
FEMA and President Joe Biden
Roll20
She unfolded
Politicians are 20-30 minutes late
As it all unfolds
So there's going to be this emergency alert test
Nmn buy milk I'm out 20 minutes later or something and
Psych
Martial law
Okay
Okay alright
Do you know
You know how when you plan the
Concealer
Downy really scary
Could you know exactly when it's going to begin countdown clock and everything
You known about it for months
You know it's no big deal
And yet still you're telling me that on the day you're going to announce
Martial law after this
Months-long planning
You still going to be like 20 or 30 minutes late like what's going to what's going to hang you up from
Firing marks
Biden weird guy was late
Got to go to blaze up before he goes out there and declare martial law
Are you ever declared martial law on Wii
If it was set to happen at 4:20
I would I would be like okay that's a fun martial law
Martial law
So Alex
I think that he
A little disappointed cuz the alert happens and it's not really anything
But he's got to sort of like
Okay we're in that space where it
It's happening
Around the country
I'm going to just vamp
A little bit
The Pentagon
All these evil guys
25 years ago
Mike down for this
This is phenomenal this is just outrageous
Again in Mainline Pentagon documents 25 years ago about
We've been passed by DARPA and the Rockefeller Foundation is the Carnegie Foundation to end War
Have a plan to put humans in tanks
Computer systems
People will live in peace and we'll be able to have a Mainframe computer
And the power of their own heat
Computers
That was a theoretical.
Made the movie The Matrix
Is right now
Emergency alert system
Telling us
Atone
We are the tones I can take over the Scramblers
That's not the town
The old system
That would launch tones
To check out with the radio or TV station
I want to fight
You can show the image of it
We can't even show you the emergency alert
Twilight Zone
It's like a year-and-a-half ago during lockdown
I told you it's all Bs word essential company
We can stay open
Batman
When we got here
Am I allowed to show a video of this sub
Attempts to divert wild king Obama attempts to divert
That's not good
That spiral into a whiny tantrum I don't know
Can't play the Biebs
Because of course
Cuz the engineer or whoever's the producer is concerned that playing those beeps over the radio stations would over
Verizon signal or something
Sure that is the technology that
It's still used but I don't know what
Size radio stations Alex is on around the country
Antiquated Radio Systems
Seems like a legitimate concern if you're a producer to have
Better safe
Ansari
Alcoholics
Freaks out
I love that they're like
Play whatever you were
I am a man babe
What I listen to something like that
The first thing that comes to mind is
Professional
Sure
And if I were the globalists
I would meet with this cash
I am the devil watching this guy needs to be on my team holyshit
Tip of the spear guys of number one draft pick
Giada actual violent confrontation clearly all we need to do is presenting
A minor annoyance to him and he will walk away yet it seems this seems like
Achilles heel
I Got A Car
This really hurts
Whatever you want
It's not actually my cut of mild irritation
Oh man
I think I have a little bit of a reaction
Haha
Why
I work for him I would not let him
Come now go away go away left the show you're done you're done
Like there should be that kind of level of like that
Who does work at Infowars apparently
You quit you're a quitter
You're not going back on the air today
No you don't get to have a tantrum and then come back up
Pretend nothing happened would you accept this kind of behavior at a little league game
Absolutely not no
If you're the coach
No
This is disgraceful Behavior
Hey hey
Okay I know you made an error on that play and then stormed off the field and we had to replace you with a new short
What's a butt
Now that it's a couple outs later of course you can go back into the game
You yelled I'm not mad while throwing your fat at the opposing team
Umpire has to have knee replacement surgery
Valex comes back with a very exciting enough
I can trust rated because
Covered
20% of what I was ready to cover
A lot of
Today
Great
F***
You stupid
How to do a job a lot of your time on my show and now.
Time on somebody else's show spend a lot of time lying about nda's and meetings are globalist
I did have a little baby freak out
Bad I left the show
You
Baby freak out
Don't you forget that I do all running everything. We don't tell anybody. Everybody was
Said that
I like the idea that
These two things are
Geniusly crew
Alex Jones is the most
Important truth-teller in the world he has a singular ability to understand the globalist right away that nobody else
In human history has ever been able to over two decades
That's the first
The second thing
Is he
6 minutes
Plaid Justice
Vine
Did let his
Engineer decide what to play on it
Brittany stores
Play whatever you want
Summer intern
But he has higher just some random person
Their instinct is going to be as good as mine
Coof
ISO
F*** Alex I'm not going to listen to the war room for him to come back and try again
Absolutely not
So we we go to the 12
Call Pierre and
You know we didn't
Didn't have martial law break
That's true
And also the Cyber Symposium the bike on Dallas putting on his
Mighty display
Here's where Alex is at
But this is a softgel weapon
Differently
Absolutely so evil and so well thought-out
Premeditated
Verizon
Hydrogen bomb going off you know what
Bud
With this because it's a slow kill
Because it's a soft kill
People don't know
What is hemp
Silent weapons for quiet Wars
That's not a pentagon report
Document
Alex
Real
Amazing
In the year of Our Lord 2021 Alex
Is such a dumb dumb
He's willing to site silent weapons
For quiet Wars
Amazing
These guys
Do they think this one is
Going to be the last one or do they think they're going to be able to
Do you know what I mean like
Eventually it's going to be a year from now
And the people who have gotten the vaccine
There will be more of them and they will all still not be dead
So what did they do then
I think that what you do then is you pretend that all
Bullmastiff
Is being covered up
And you make a mountain out of a molehill anytime there's any kind of adversity or event that happen
I think that's probably the the strategy at that point
I don't trip but I mean this one is just so big you know it feels like
You can't wriggle out of
Hey
80% of people are going to be dead
In six months yeah
If you know
I agree with you
It in terms of like rational mine
I think that
I think that you and I can look at this and say like
There's no way out of this
There's no there's no doubling back
Yeah but
I would have said that a hundred times over the course of Alex's G I have said
On this show even like
But he's f***** yeah
How's it going to get out of this it's a dead-end narrative know you're right
Bigger than anything I've seen him try to pull off in
In the past
But I don't
As long as there's money I don't know
What
I understand how old I am 34 now I have not gone two years of my life without some Christian cell
Telling me it's the end time
So of course they're willing to just
So it's not this time
We'll wait until the next one in this time
It's the end times
Yeah I think I think
Vets
Alex is the Arbiter of information in
And so
In Subway's
As long as
He's able to feign confidence
In whatever way he walks
Back stuff pretends that he's not actually wrong
Right
I think that he was able to
He'll be able to keep up some amount of the auto
Yeah you're right
People who
Float away
As long as there's money
Ill Bill tricks on people
If I were them I would be working on my walk back strategy now started a year ago
How are we going to pull this off it's going to take us a lot of nights to figure this one out
Is the sort of thing that I'd have a flow chart for multiple steps ahead
On the 12th
There was a bit of
Stuff going around on social media about one of these nice Alex was right about everything kind of money
About
Judicial Watch
Center for Medical
Call progress
Release of some documents about the University of Pittsburgh
Procuring
Fetuses for Reese
Sure okay
Fun it's not really a bombshell in anyway but Alex
Of course because people talk about how he was right about everything
He's got to cover it
Here's Fox News
Here's Associated Press
Today
Criminal investigation by the justice department on whether major universities
Did they deliver 3rd
789 Montana
Peter poor women sometimes it show up at the hospital
And and
So this is Billy inaccurate
But it gets worse
What was Elvis in the documents
That they wanted
Minority babies they don't say why in California in Ohio and New York
Illinois
We want black and brown
Hey buddy if I say the wrong thing on the right swipe
Harvesting
So like I said this story is just about to documents released by Judicial Watch and the Center for Medical progress
Both of these entities are pretty Usual Suspects on our show and Arkham
Complete should have they should never be trusted
The one element of the story that stuck out is this second
Appear
Folks
They really glommed onto it's this specific details that they're these great documents that require
Some of the fetuses percentage of them that they take in
Abba need to be Democrat
Ethically diverse
Anyone who's not a s******* grifter would be able
I'll tell you this isn't an attempt
The target minorities
Keeping in line with making sure that the studies that they carry out follow property
Distribution pattern
So SB reflective of the general
Just like with Dennis Montgomery
Judicial Watch instead of medical progress or names
That you should the Akira X to a story and you should just ignore it
There's never going to be anything worth wild comes out
Every single time that I've heard their names associated with stories there is a simple explanation
For how there
Intentionally misrepresenting something
Push-up political am
Yeah
Every time
Project Veritas
Course all of these names
Ignorable
Exact
The opposite problem that's
Like the problem that's being addressed is far larger which
What is that most
Medical testing over
Our history
Has been done on white men so we know exhaustively
What works for white dudes butt
Medications for women and for minorities
Have been under understudy because they're not a milia concern problem
Finally trying to do something about it and of course
It's turned into an evil f***
There's just no there's
Nothing they can't f******
Speaking of which
Here's Alex messing around with
Photography
The major national gay pride organization just gave their highest award to an image
Of a toddler child
With men in bondage uniforms
With sex swings
But they put themselves in
This is with a two-year-old child
And they're all lined up
And then the messages were about to g*******
Weird message
Pdsm
There's a right-wing media outrage cycle those k
Kicked off this traces back to a tweet
Does posted by Andino
Who's another name you can add to that list people
You should probably just
Signor
Apparently during pride in the Netherlands
There was a contest taking photos that capture the years
Theme of celebrating diverse
50 photos were selected and this one was one that particularly stood out
According to the post-millennial which is a source I generally would never site
But no one else is covering
In the stone story
The jury's out of this picture quote
This photo in a
Its composition child in the foreground men preparing for
Canal parade in the background
Everyone busy with their own activities and fascination
Sublimely depicts what will hopefully remain self-evident
That we unhampered by prejudices and almost unsuspectingly
All met and can exist side-by-side
I seen this picture and that seems like a pretty decent take on it
Certainly that's closer to what I experiencing the photo that Alex is interpretation which is just
Disgusting on
Yeah
There's just no way around if that's what you think is about to happen that's cuz you're.
Yeah you're a monster
Reminder standing
The picture is a child
Holding a swing
Yeah like I'd like a
Playground swing
Swing
And then there's people in leather
Behind right there not like all looking at her anything girl minding their business or like getting there
Stuff latched going to have you and any picture about how prejudices learn
Yeah and the situation to was that the child mother
Had let these people change
To go to the parade
At her home
Answer
It's done getting ready
Need to go to the dealer
We're going to
It's just
No that's because you're that's
If that's you
That's what you get
You are disgusting and you should deal with that
I am sick of having to deal with the fact that you can't deal with
Anytime there's an adult and a child in the same room that you don't like them
I have a difficult time with these projection
Yeah
Yeah so Alex
WhatsApp
What's the one word that Alex uses
To describe
Doctors that he likes pennies
No
Doctor
I would have to go with well-respected top of his
Field close close
Damn it that's that's his favorite word
Talk about a prestigious doctor
I am.
Another prestigious dr. Fleming
Vaccines are biological weapons
When
This virus
Is a man-made
Gain-of-function virus
Paid for by us tax
Taxpayers dollars including
Money stacks
Department of
Defense
Del bigtree is an anti-vaxxer lunatic so if someone's being interviewed by him AIDS
Pretty safe bet that they're not on the level
In this case though out to sing with this guy is really
Prestigious
I thought I'd
Thought-out short
As it turns out Richard and plumbing is a bit of a career scammer
In 2002 he billed Medicare Medicaid and Blue Cross Blue Shield for quote
Falsely represented medical test
+ 2,048 submitted false data after being paid
Performa clinical study
Call me health benefits of a sweet chip food product
This all Legend being sentenced to five years probation and six months house arrest along with being forced to pay restitution of
107,000 $244.24
Hey man you can get jail time for stealing bugging out of Alexa
Yeah I know you stealing from a f****** gas station B of A years-long
Scam 5 years probation
Sure that he would probably say that he never admitted to anything and he's totally innocent but he needed
Well
Swimming is no quitter those who decide to keep trying to put that studies which ultimately led to the FDA in 2018
He was disbarred quote
Look for 10 years from providing services in
Any capacity to a person that has an approved or pending drug product application
I know it takes a lot of prestige to get there
This guy is a doctor has no specialty in vaccines or epidemiology at all
It is somebody who's been charged with multiple fraud-related felonies
I'm going to go way out on a limb here and say that that's not the resume or somebody who's one of the most prestigious doctors around
Yeah
That somebody who's I don't know
One of the most
Prestigious doctors around it took him 10 years of not being allowed to practice by law
In order to
The game the level of prestige the TV prestigious Maverick at the fda's.
Afraid to have him
Put a legal injunction against him because I'm in India
But also if they didn't
Stop him
From being involved with these studies in these like trials
No other doctors could get work
No that's why the FDA had to step in and just borrow
Cuz he wouldn't even be doing everything to good
Stupid
Good
At doctor
So what are they
Is that Alex has been
Dancing around with ease
When they said the hospitals were in
Pool last time
It was all bulshit the house
Little branch
Right now hospitals are full and they are actually
Do they get to go both ways huh and nobody's going to stop them and we're not going to have any consequences for this whatsoever
This is not the argument that Alex is making
But it is
A little bit
Unnerving
How
It's not being treated as at much of an emergency this time
I'm part of that maybe
What do you mean from the society at Large
And I don't know if this is in part because
Vaccination
Prevalent so I don't know if it's
Because of poor messaging
Maybe could be partially or could be the exhaust
The comes from recognizing that
If you are going Alyssa
Like you can yell all you want about the hospitals being full and it being a very severe situation
I think that the
Right to do
Been talking to change
Governor DeSantis his behavior
It's not going to change the people like Alex's Behavior at all
What the thing that you wouldn't
In order to address
The problem is an impossibility
I don't think that that justifies not
Treating it like
The type of problem that it is so don't know what to do
Anyway that's a real thing Alex's fake thing
Is that they were pretending the hospital.
So now they are full because they're filled with vaccinated
People people are actually the ones we're getting everyone
Prairie right
Topsy-turvy world but it'll mean we don't really need to deal with this too much
Because Alex kind of
Gets distracted in
In the middle
Talking about it
Hospitals around the country I could check statistics
Last year at this time the hospitals were empty
What do all the real Carolina
Hospitals not operate
And then
Appreciate
Awesome
I guess you're awesome
Actually I got her.
Very important
I need a Mac and
I'm just going to stop right there
Play whatever you want
To set up your own ear
And have literally thousands of documents total admission
You pour gasoline on somebody you like them on fire going to burn to death
Gets back to causal relationships
Hahaha now we know how
I get a little worried about myself from time to time
Things that prompt
Worrying me
Is that I think I can understand Alex a little better than I should
Because I heard that clip
And when he's breathing heavy and then he's like I have total admission total proof
I like
I know what happened
You got distracted by something you forgot what you were saying
You forgot you were talking about the hospitals
You are being empty before but they're full now and approve everything
He has no connection
Intuit and he just
Like I don't even know where I was
That's usually where he'll have a
Breakdown and storm outside
Yeah but in this case he doesn't he tries to to hold it
Together power through
And then
In like a minute after this
He basically admitted
Exactly what
I suspect it was
Too nice to just fly over with helicopters and gases
Lacoste fires explosions
But if it is a cold attack
People want to rationalize they don't want to believe it's happening they don't
Wanna believe it's taking place in their lifetime
Calm down and try to come back
How can I guess somebody came through and I forgot I was going to say if I got mad
I got what I thought. After while
Imma try to reset imma try to come back
Do you want to hear about him keeping a little kids alive
Alex doesn't want to read those studies because they don't say the things that he needs them to say in order for these new
Narratives to buy
Stand up to scrutiny
That's why he doesn't do that
I forgot what I was going to say
So I got mad
And then that's
Mad is a medical problem
I think that
You know
Acceptance
And self-awareness is the first step
In terms of make
Making progress
And for Alex to actually stay on air I lost my train of thought so I got mad
It is certainly better than them storming office
True
I don't I don't know I I worry about myself though cuz as soon as I've heard the first clip of it actually happening as I can
I would love to try to call you getting mad
This has looked back then
Thankfully I have candy
That you got a nogga to cut it up. Candy and season the Survivor that I'm not enjoying
So I'll be okay
These doctors that Alex
Looks like I'll hop
Sober
Jordan in his prime
Michael Jordan Nike Jordan Allen
About 17 playing High School baseball
Call Jordan
Made it to the
Pinnacle in my profession buddy
This is Mississippi
Give me like having Dale Earnhardt
Pride
In his prime
Enterprise
9 or something
Tell you
This car's got a problem if engine is going to blow
Don't put it out on the track
Michael Jordan in his prime
That's not a good player I think you should cut him off the team or I don't want them out here with me
The real quick I want it I want address both of these example
I don't know if Dale Earnhardt jr. is the best mechanic
In the world
Maybe he wouldn't actually be the person you'd want to talk to you about the car itself
You know something about driving up
Necessarily know everything about the car
And Michael Jordan
Is a notorious assholes who said exactly what Alex said he said
He also wouldn't
Be the best judge of the best player
If someone
Is 2 good
Murder them
Good players were complementary to his singular good
Right Right Alright actually be a very
Bad person
Listen to take Staffing advice
Scrum
Yeah I haven't watch The Last Dance
And also having watched
Jordan's career as a general manager and owner has players
Like both of these examples are bad
Yeah
How did Dale Earnhardt
You know what never
You listen to Michael Jordan
Michael Jordan
Earnhardt
Tom Brady
Another notoriously piece of s*** please was going to happen
I am in the Twilight Zone
This morning
He wasn't trying cuz I
You do it I'm not going to hurt anybody
Attacking
I'm not confident boy
I mean you know
We already know you want
How to kill people
I read these studies and I have tears of murder
You don't baby the thing that is a metaphor might actually be very good
In the opposite direction
He's thinking about
Because I listen three of these people that he is reference
Are people who are in
Credible
Where incredible at what they do
Better than anyone else ever has
But if you ask them to do something outside of that
You are asking the wrong person no matter what you are doing
Sure you are asking
If you are asking a duck
Shursave who is Ben
Maybe the best there is ever been in committing fraud
Fraud
Yeah
Yeah singular and that's kind of why when some of them go away there's a real hole in the shower like Steve
Around more
He is
The Michael Jordan
Of crazy big brag absolutely
Larry Nichols being dead is
Kind of unfortunate
Because of the
Hole that's left there he was the Michael Jordan of Clinton conspiracy really was
He just had them
And you know you lose those
You lose those people and it's tough
It's tough to staff
And according to Leo zagami he's also the Michael Jordan the basketball
He's the Michael Jordan of Illuminati Insider
Championship
It doesn't hit when you try and Slot these other people in who are just diss
Disappointing weirdos
They wish they could be
Sprite
That was for a 90 wasn't on the Bulls
Sixth Man of the Year repeatedly
He was a starter for a while though
Great
Good stuff
You're talk about Vlade Divac
Another bad administrator great basketball player then he became a general manager. Right
People who aren't
Good at what they're asking that they
Glowing basketball
Terrible
So look
Cyber symposium
How did it go
It's going well
Mul-t-lock
It's a cold
Living in the future I do remember that
At 90 Supreme Court decision did not come
This is a beauty Berry
But
Mike Lindell still hasn't money life
Well and I admire him he's in the arena
You still fight
This
Next clip
It's so gratifying
Okay
Okay Selma
Rihanna
Medias attacking with a cyber Symposium calling it a failure
A really big success
Courage and honor in will and Truth
I watched a lot of it
And reel algorithms real proof shows in real cases of fraud
Warren Lyndell privately and publicly I said
In the classic setup
Even set up a pentagon
I said you really oughta move away from that
I said okay
Overshadowing that it was just random.
Alex is trying to throw Dennis Montgomery under the bus but refuses to say his name because he's been a sorceress
So many things on April 4th
Oh man
Oh man I wore died Warren
Mike Lindell not to listen to the dentist Montgomery's information like I have so many times in the past
Alright I created an entire months-long cycle out of the fictional idea that
The truck was being spied on based on
Montgomery information
I can't really throw that out his name
Make it too obvious that
But I believe all that b*******
I tried to warn lundell
He's good guy
Things going well
This is Dennis Montgomery is the Nigerian email scammer
Stories like I told people you know it happened
Some people named me listen to lunch time
That's cool
Oh man that's really gratifying for me
Bike
Even Alex has got a cup
Montgomery Lewis now
Mike Lindell
You know this is Venice
Success in a lot of ways the updates honor all the other ways other than the ones
Wyatt by which we would measure
It's a party
Participation trophy is what Alex
Would like to give
For Honor
He's Miss Congeniality
So Alex
Gets to talk about the the old vaccines
Of course and
He's not learned the name of
The first man
Who got the Pfizer shot
First man eroded William Shakespeare
The first name William
But your mom
William Shakespeare
First he died
Rabbi William
Do you want to help everybody
If this dude has descended William Shakespeare it's got to be like
Make a really bizarre distant relative
It's got it with the kind of relationship would be meaningless
William Shakespeare had three children
Only one of them retain the surname Shakespeare and that was his son Hamlet
Haven't had no children
Because he died at age 11
Shakespeare two daughters both married and took on their husband
Open surname
His daughter Judith Mary Thomas Queenie
Children all of whom died
Before having kids of their own and all before the age of
His other daughter Susanna married John Hall and had one child named Elizabeth
Elizabeth had no children and is widely known as William Shakespeare's final descendant
I was just all the name William Shakespeare and decided to write a fun story about how he's a descendant of the playwright to make it more compelling for the
This is something pretty important to recognize that Alex's process
It very regularly involves him just making
King stuff up as he's cold reading articles
Also if you read any of the articles about this guy our to know that he's very strongly prefer being called bill
Most likely because of the discomfort
Being named Williams
That's somebody with the last name Holmes nobody has ever called me Shirley
Block so I don't understand h a
Chicago called H H Holmes
Is it really is most people don't like to reference famous serial killers when talking
Aurora shooter
The world government
Haha
Going to take over
But there's one
Achilles heel
Memes white people but he doesn't want to say that
The whole world government rollout forced inoculation program
Little bit of an Achilles heel
Western Europe in the UK and Australia and New Zealand in
Supposedly have election
Those countries have democracy
You're able to put
Sure thing list
Countries that Alex's saying are the Achilles heel of the globalist
It's because there were
Publix
It does seem like a very
Ties them together feel like
UK vs rights bit of a misstep
Since the UK is considered a
Constitutional monarchy
Don't generally considered a formality today technically
In order for any Bill to become an Act of Parliament
Required to get Royal assent
Which is the monarchs
Approval and literally stories have come out recently of the monarchs themselves changing legislation
Can using their influence this actually like at the Royal assent not being granted to a bill hasn't happened since the sea
And if it did today would almost certainly prompt
But in terms of the law and how the government is organized in the UK the Monarch has the power to override everything
Any elected body does
The UK is not a republic
How funny would it be
If
The queen just finally did that one time it seemed like the perfect everybody's like I guess we have to
Killer now that was a strange way for that rule to end and guess what Jordan
Elizabeth is the queen of Australia to
Are there laws redacted with royal assent as well although it's done by the Australian
Governor-general
The governor-general is not an elected position it's a
Appointed by the monarch
This is one of the heads of state and they surface
Pleasure of the British crown
Canada
Stupid world do we live in
Stupid
Bulshit is this
So f****** stupid
It's kind of bizarre like
I think that they're still like effective governor
It's able to
Take this new constitutional monarchy
But it seems like something we should just do away with
Heads of state who are kingma's in
And queens
Who
Technically on paper control everything if they want to but yet
That's where we're here to make appearances
Live extremely lavish Lifestyles at the expense of all the poor people around us as we learned
From Trump
Norms are not
Set in stone
And if there is a norm
That the monarchy does
Give Royal assent to everything
That's not setting cell
The only as good as the monarch
Hey well and not just that but we're seeing a Resurgence of a lot of far-right monarchist at the moments
If there is a monarch who decides to say remove that event
And has already put together a large group of supporters many of whom are very violent these days
Took the countries that Alex's listing aren't Republic
Interesting leads do that list
But he gave his
Really similar to the countries that Kirk Lions noted Neo-Nazi lawyer
Listed is the ones where the white
Majority was under attack
Do use the acronym
Cause which you used as the new name for his organization which was formerly known as
The Patriots
Defense Foundation
It's better than the white people only we love white people white people white people
Alex
Don't care about these countries cuz they were public
He cares because he believes that there the places where white people are in danger because his intellectual roots
Orion extreme right-wing racist ideology
Whether he's aware of it or
So
The thing that I love
About this
Episode in
Secular
Is that Alex has to rationalize
That the Cyber Symposium is not going
It's not going
But it is going well
You have money and I have a promo code everything he's ever done
But at the same time it looks pretty bad this is not going
And it's only because Dennis Montgomery set him up
Globalist
But Alex has to say his name
We knew how they did it they sent out all the
Balance
I sent out tens of millions album
From North Korea
Put on a boat
Glendale
Theirself
But just like I told you to was control
How do you
Shredded
Somebody that's actually out there
Trying to expose
Will stop while you tell him
We've got all the files of all the election
Symptoms China
Prove
So now Dennis Montgomery
Giving this information to Mike Lindell is a plot
The globalist
To discredit Mike Lindell
And the guy pushed
To overturn the election
Amazing
Does he not realize
What he just say
Probably not
He rarely does
Because what he just said
Was that you can give
Mike Lindell
Fake information and he will put it out
Because he does not have the ability
The tell the difference between fake information or real in
Yeah that is that is definitely a piece of this that is
Is going on examine
Yeah and Mike Lindell will make multiple documentaries about this risk a 1.6 billion dollar lawsuit
I mean
It really doesn't get that what you just said is that we don't
Don't know how to tell the difference between real information and fake information
Yep no way of verifying whether or not the ship people give us
Is true yeah and
The fact that this information is coming from someone who is a career scam artist
Pause
Past behavior is not a predictor of future of a
Also I love
The premise that Alex like
Is like I'm not going to say his name cuz I do want to get sued when I gets
He goes on to s*** on
Montgomery Sommore
All that smile he said he had
Individual that gave it to him but said that
China
All the files and did it
Obviously you can't have all the files at once
Individual
Courseworks for the mccratic party of the biggest Democratic party Law Firm
Affirmative quarterback
Operations against me
Oh my God
But Linda listen to me and that's okay he's a good guy
Level
He'll remember what I told him now
Exclusive
Modell's planes in China
Election
Who gave Michael until all this information is NPR headlines
Call the Pentagon
Politics in
Kind of messages on broadcast TV
Report
Summertime CIA Pentagon into buying
Artist
Involving Judge
Have you ever talked about tennis
We have
All of this information
Yeah that
That seems really absent from his analysis of this is the conversation of all of the
Fraudulent
Based on this
Guy who's in
An obvious scam artists
You know it's it's fun
How many times people are like Alex was right but we don't have that like you do when a cop gets caught play
Planting drugs
You know and then they have to go back and revisit all those old
Convictions and toss them out
Because the cop is clearly a f****** cheaters like Alex should have to go back and revisit all those dentist
Gomery cases be like well this one's from a Canard
This one's from a con artist this one's from Baccano
Right I mean even the basis of this one Alex is on board with a hammer and scorecard stuff
He definitely was promoting that was
Straight up Montgomery s***
The problem is
It was too big
So people paid attention
Yeah I think it was easier for him to
Assertive pretend he wasn't aware of
How much of a hoax artist
Montgomery was back then
You know there was a
Trump was President there was a good chance
G.i. Joe Arpaio pardon
No
And the tides of change
Montgomery is a
And everybody knows it
I won't say his name because I don't get to
Or
I don't want to trigger something in people's memories
I remember you talking about this guy
As if he was the Super snowed in
Didn't seem to recall somebody saying super Snowden
About somewhere Bunch times
So Alex interviews this talk show host
Name Katie your Kate daily dolly
I don't know
That's fine
Cheese
I would say that she's somebody who's talks in Infowars content
Okay with a Fox News delivery
I got you
Junior varsity
She is not
Did Michael Jordan have
She is the bill wennington
That's not great
Luc Longley
It look like we was great
Yeah it was pretty good that's a bad example
All over my boobs now I can't think of any other people who were on the boat with that point
B.j. Armstrong but he was good BJ was good
I was asked by Michael Jordan which
Proves our earlier theory if you get punched in the face by Michael Jordan you're probably pretty good as some other players on that bad
Give me some other players from the bench yeah man that's not going to go well no
It's been awhile
It's been too long Stacy
No not Stacey
Yes yeah I know I know
Nevermind
I can't remember.
Alright
Who else we going to Bulls you love them
Their interview is not very interesting it's mostly to
Just about
Basic misrepresentations about covid vaccination
Seems like we talked about a bunch
Although we do learn something
And that is that Rob do was in the hospital
Oh no
Dumb f*** I'll explain if you tested negative no matter what that may be possible but barely got some kind of pneumonia
And then he had to escape the hospital
Which is fun
Okay
I would probably just ignore this and be like whatever I give it to you
But
Listen to Alex
Call Rob do a friend
And there's a little bit of a
Pause that made me very sad
Call Goodwill my best friend's Rob do
Add covid-19 in went to the hospital and they weren't giving him IV
They weren't giving him vitamin C
You do
Escape
What do I goodfriends Rob do
Already had covid
Thought he had covid what a my best friend's Rob do
That's not like a
Giant Paws but it's
Meaningful
It feels
Pointed one could call it pregnant
I'd also love VIP
Subdued
Just basically being like what Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest
Getting out I see I see Rob who is Crunk
Ocean theme music of the escapes I could see that I could do that
So he refused this Cave Valley
And I don't care
Partially that's because
We have another guy
Use outbrain
He's very traumatic
Any other surprises
Also we've been able to get dr. Richard Fleming
To join us at
Power if that's alright with you he's
This is what people I've ever interviewed this is the fraud doctor we talked about earlier
The most brilliant people I have
Ever interview
Yes
He's great
Happening is that
Halfway through the third hours
And let's Mike
Like interview this other doctor
I like oh my
My God
Breakthrough
He's one who who has ideas
I like the way I made that song
He is one who has one who has ideas
Yes
And he has idea for the day
The office
Personnel
Backpack that happened right
China got all of the psychological profiles
All of everybody.
And now they're using it
Kill the military
Would you believe that no
Remember what was in those files they had these psychological profiles
High-level military leaders including high-level
In their interviews when they're being interviewed
Do you have multiple sex partners
Records are now in the hands of the CCP
High-level officials in
With the people's Liberation Army
War
Against the United States military to then
Military
By having our own troops with Spike weapon
In the name of vaccines
While emerging Global Center China
Spy Car trips
Poison them
As an Armistice as a sign of submission
Love working together
Spiritual
They're good they're Jordan and Pippen
I said something crazy even crazier
Love the way you're not
It does seem to have a little bit of a
Chocolate and peanut butter Vive 20s
Oh man you know like
You take the content away from it there's something really delightful about the
Cute it's just
I mean
Doesn't it seem too much doesn't it seem too much to return your anti-vax
Bulshit from
You do like
It's it's
Reasonable to trick people into thinking that something you some kind of birth
Defect or something can happen because of vaccine
And then a kid riddles
Pretty easy to present like
I have a can
Concerned about this
Concern is legitimate
There's some science that I feel is unclear or whatever
Deams Lake
More on Shaky Ground and this about 70% of the population
Has had at least one shot
Yeah right
So now you're going to take anti-vax
Bulshit out of the realm of that and turned it into
All of the people in our military are being murdered by the Chinese Army
Used
Psychological profiles of everybody
That they hacked
Yeah they know how many people are f******
And they're able to use that in order to get them to vaccinate
The troops so they die
And here's the point
Here's here's a quick question question
There's No Pigeons Chinese military been vaccinated
And if so are they being murdered as well.
Okay listen
Here's the deal
Where's this weed
I suppose
China invading
A lot of details to share here but
There are people
And and
I'm not sure about
But for those who believe that Trump might one day be reinstated by a Supreme Court decision
Erratically
Trump would inherit a weekend
Military with probably hundreds of thousands of dead and injured troops
National Security level
Which would mean the US couldn't defend itself against
Invasion
Better Connecticut
You nailed it
Invasion
United States
Is the most unavailable country
In the world
Every child
Huge margin do you know what we don't need a military whatsoever
Cuz we have so many f****** nukes
The idea of somebody being like
Let's go take Utah is insane Beyond Reason
The idea of a staging ground being possible would be really difficult
Well I mean if your
Boat
Maybe in
The Northeast coming from
North Korea going to land in Mexico and then
Travel upwards with what kind of insane person I said
America can be invaded
If you believe that that's possible then you have to believe that either Canada or Mexico would be on board
Bored with the invasion
Or that it would be somehow possible to do a maritime Landing
One thing United States coastline
The United States coastline
Thunder under cover of dark
Yeah it seems a little bit far-fetched but if possible
Troops get back
I mean Jesus Christ
We've already been invaded in the
These people are
Really fun
Mike is fun
I guess as much as like
I abhor all of these people's beliefs
At least Mike is
Trying to walk that line of like
I know
That it would sound really stupid
For me to say that I believe that Trump is going to be reinstated by the Supreme Court at some point
But
The Chinese military
The brass
Into injecting
The troops with vaccines in order to weaken them so when Trump is reinstated by
If you won't have the military wedding pallet ideas
That makes perfect sense
Text that makes
Perfect said what a f******
Mdec unreal
I'm still actually worried about the country being invaded
That's a real thing that people are worried about his troops
Autumn arrogance Oilers other things to worry about to like societal collapse
Well that seems far more likely
Well not this version
And there is a critical Tipping Point
Beyond which if you have a certain percentage of
Then Society the complex society that we now live in ceases to function
Because you lost the redundancy and the know-how
The people who can run
The power grid
Who can run the manufacturing
Machine for the transportation system
If we start to lose twenty-five 30% of those were vaccinated
There may be a Tipping Point Beyond which this entire system suffers a
Cascading systemic
Collapse from which we are not able to
Yeah I would say if 14 people in the country dies
There will be a massive reorganization that will be required
Twenty-five percent of the population of this country.
It's always fascinating to me
It's always fascinating to me how these guys are
Capitalists are always like off
If 20
5% of the people with know how the engineers you know how to run the power grader bills
People are taking away
It's never like
If 25% of the owners of these businesses die
It'll all fall apart
Here's another thing to help Mike historical society's going to collapse entirely
To the 1800's interim
The technology of 25% of the population dies off
Right
Meanwhile
Essential piece of his analysis conspiracy is it the globalists are trying to kill off 80% of the population
Ninety percent of the population
I guess the goal was to want to live in a world of 89 technology or something
They love horses and buggy
None of this makes any f******
Mike interviews with dr. Fleming guy
Hear what he says
No I don't give a s***
If you had your license revoked for a license for being involved in the study
Disbarred
Primanti Vig
For even like
6 months
I would be like
And this was 10 years
Has he committed multiple
Bullfrog related felony
Yeah
Sia I don't really care as you're saying the same kind of standard Infowars covid conspiracy is it just like oh
We have a new face to repeat after us we have a doctors saying it
A prestigious doctor
Don't look at them don't don't worry about his
Is as resume
Prestige is actually how
He leaves halfway through the third hour and then Mike
Who's hosting
I listen to the rest
For the third hour and I'm not losing you another hour of Mike Adams
I turned it off
Only thing I even came
Close to being interesting as this
Of Plumbing
There's very clear
Evidence that serves Kobe
2002 was actually the
Their first bioweapon
And this isn't
Version
Bio weapon isn't something
You really are good with what
Kill the enemy
Slowly but surely demoralizes them
Arms
Damages their society and their
Economy Inn
Causes slow malicious diseases
But doesn't make any sense
I mean I guess the best weapon in the world then was George W bush
Cuz he destroyed societies
And cause all kinds of masses
Diseases in
Yeah
I mean you know I think
If you look at
Particularly
Prominent
Biological age
Yeah you looking at things like anthrax
Yeah
Doesn't count
Hold on
It demoralizes
Don't you remember the biggest threat
From anthrax was how demoralized we'd all be
A lot of biological weapons are actually targeted at crops
Yeah a lot of them are things that are like fungus is
End up killing crop
They don't demoralize props starving to death will demoralize you
Well that's true killing people they're aimed at
Plants
You still ain't killing
I don't know I don't know
That sounds more like a propaganda strategies I would like
This guy too
Explain what you.
How
Clear based on the evidence
Bitstarz
Was their first attempt at a biological weapon
Remember
We got it from Dennis Montgomery
That guy
Loving but also
Pretend I never listen to him
So where are we
Do I owe some enjoyable stuff here I was trying to dance around the
Rebecca this is
The bosium sucks
Utterly embarrassing blow up with the emergency alert
Just what I thought of shifts beautiful
I'm just that
Tip of the spear
On the next episode will finish up
Reply with the Cyber Symposium disappointment
No work shopping
We'll come up with something
Don't give it away for free
Compresor on Twitter
We are there any local charity or Bell funded your area
Emilio I'm dzx Clark
Gunbarrel rundus I am the Rony seikaly of doctors
Holding
Alex
In color