Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about Alex Jones
What's up
My bright spot today Jordan is I think that I've coined the term you think you coined the term I think so think you've invented
I didn't cuz I don't really know exactly how it would be spelled I feel like I could smell it
Days Inn
Misses other way I also do I checked in with a couple friends
I might
What I decided to do the other day was at 1
Okay right alright I called it in Munich
I've never heard anyone say they like you know that
Take me to night to yourself
That might be cleaned
I don't know I feel like it's impossible but it hasn't been in some kind of Pop Culture thing a Time
I'm stealing this from like it would have been either in like a trendy show like Parks and Rec
Comedy show at
Before evening is a winner
If if in the next two weeks this breaks into the Zeitgeist for real
I think you win like I also came up with a pitch
For like how this is going to go
Like I've come up with this term evening and it's going to go huge
It's going to get so popular and then I'm going to rename your comedy show comedy
It 2 Fandango
Cuz they want to sell tickets post-pandemic Schulich freeway
Either way
Encourage solo going to the movie and social distancing
This is a whole new thing I think this is really going to catch on in like China where the male to female population is
I'm so scared there's going to be a lot of movement going Saturday to me
I have a problem with no dates
The problem evening I think
Been this excited about something I thought of sense
Many years ago I came up with
If you are agreeable Gray g
Black hair salt and pepper
But for a bearded should be called cookies and cream.
I thought that was really fun pales in comparison to a winning
Although it could get out of control whatever I go home
For Holiday Inn call it a m
Batmobile
Yeah you know what though
Predict what's actually going to happen
Is there to ever put this episode out of me to get up
Flood of people telling me that this is
Coined it I will I will find all of those and block them before they ever get a year
There will be a complete Code of Silence around you be offensive line
You created me evening
The end. It feels good
I am I'm getting another tattoo
I set up an appointment to get a tattoo
Wednesday very excited
It about it that seems fun I've been wanting
To get another one myself today I still am not
Entirely sure if I feel
Get back into the
The game the longest stretch since I was 8
What are you getting
I'm going to close the loop on this thing you know how I got this this whole flower right there
I'm on the wrist area I'm going to flip it over I'm going to do the exact same thing on the other side and color that one's in
Grayscale
Close the loop on it'll make me have a nice little wrist thing
Bracelet that bracelet for it
Exciting
I'm looking forward to seeing how that turns out and also
Myself
We're going to be The Tech Guys
Undertale
So Jordan today over and we're going to do this episode
Pop-up last week shortened the end of the Mike Lindell cyber Symposium price.
In between the release of our last episode and getting ready for this one
In the world
Taliban
Honestly I'm not a hundred percent ready to cover that
Into on Friday's episode
I will
No dip into
Alex Jones is coverage of all that
So today we're going to be looking at
Friday
Of of
Of last week
August 3rd
This is the 13th falls apart
The end of the road it's a we will also be talking about a special report Alex put out on the 14th on Saturday
What happened and I have to say that
This might
Only be
An episode because of
Maybe I found the best out of context drop
That I've ever found in my life
Nothing else will release the dentist Montgomery episode
Nothing else this out-of-context drive
Is worth its weight in gold
Before we get to any of this business evening and the comedy gold out of con
Text dropping one episode
It's an embarrassment of riches
No could be at the last cuz I'm going to play is pretty gracious good good
But before we do that says say hi to some new walkthrough
So first
Millworks exhibition
Honey badger
I also
Birthday coming up and
Vaccinations for this
The young Nate
Posey walk also
If you want
Listen to the John Rappaport episode while training to be a psychologist and was ethically obligated to give you money
Journal policy
Thank you very much thank you
We have something very special Avenue Raptor princess out there in the world
For this
This person Alex Jones is the neighbors fence
Spawned
Very
Cause
You know we talked a lot about things like animal rescue jail so I'm sure
Don't you think of
Poor people who live next door to Alex
But you need a big
Events there and that's going to come into money
Ross who said good fences make good neighbors
Neighbors fence fun
I'm a policy wonk
Barbecue your ass
It's over for Humanity
You're Beautiful song
They're coming for your balls
It's all over your God
Very few people
Pulitzer babies
Make it a practice
Calling people
The garbage when they are
Jesus
Thank you very much excited news
Joiner of the
Cult of saline
We kind of do, this is interesting
Okay family members for Salina Public
Scotland
Sneaky Bojo
Came in with something that is a little bit
Upping the ante
Do we have a star
We do
Guess what is now it's star in the Leo constellation
Cloud app
2B adelio cat is named the altar of saline for a start
That sounds like a Science Fiction made for a star where they like all we got to get to the altar of the lean-to restart civilization
Oh my God I would have had a field day with the altar of Celine so now we have a lot of
Refugee animals
We have a lot of
Trees
And something to keep them warm damned a star
Wild
I love it so thank you sneaky Bojo thank you very much
Is great
I can't over-hype this
It's so good
You're fighting for your life
My life
So good
It still good
It's too good
My life
It should be that easy that easy
Writing jokes
Tried to be funny and it's that easy it's just that easy everything that I've ever done trying to
Alex saying I'm flirting for my life is pretty funny
Really makes it funny as the pause the pause where he's at goddamnit
Power through
It's too late I just said I'm farting for my life
Love it so good
So good
You could do to take
500 something episodes in we have
Farty farty lightlife
It's just that here is Alex on the 13th
Don't want to believe this
I want to be wrong
But I'm sorry
David Rockefeller the globalist
Real world depopulation
Preparing the program
Launch
Program
I guess you and your family
Broadcast
God it's so empty
Yeah
Yeah that is now time to declare war on the globalist we've been thousand time
I think in his mind
Since price
So we don't need to declare
3 Briar
Sizzla Dawn Of Man
I don't
Care like
I can't imagine anybody in his audience
Like listening and being like Oh my God it serious
This time we have to declare war
I think the only time it would be serious if Alex
I would take it seriously if Alex
Seems like
No more blaster
Just get on your knees and die
Justin
I have done that already we're all dead already
There's just no Escape
The only thing he hasn't really done is like
It's time to start shooting
I mean you know it would be more fun if he was like it's time to do community outreach and like
Build
D.C.'s do that
But the community outreach is promote my video
Jimmy Carter and you've got space and money you could just
Bill
You know
No get to sell his home to fund a war it is not going to be building anybody else any Hall
Do Alex a pre-recorded himself ranting and reading a couple headlines
Samantha the beginning about the first 20 minutes
How's the show on Friday the 13th
Spartanburg weather
It is pre-recorded so he could have it's pretty funny like he's doing
Cinestudio or he's put up a bunch of shelves full of books
On the projection screen behind him to make it look like it's a study
Oh God
So fact that there's a segment that it's a pre-recorded think of Alex on the phone
Is the audio
Hahaha but with a picture of a callus on the phone until because they
Have accused
Videos
And they play seamlessly very clearly
Free produce
After that Alex is actually on the phone hosting for a little while
A very short segment
And then Owen Shroyer comes in and takes over
It's super weird I have no idea what's going on
It felt like it was planned
Recorded stuff but it also felt like they were scrambling
Cuz there's three different versions of Alex
That appear
In the first half-hour like
It felt like maybe Owen was late
Or something I don't know maybe it's like maybe it's like when you get one of those things of chips
You know and it's got like laziness got Fritos in
And it's got Doritos in it we're just getting a smorgasbord of different options of Alex
That's what we're looking for
Well it was bad
I would guess
I mean if I'm writing the story of what happened
I mean who knows what the actual reality of July like to imagine that Alex is really depressed
Yeah because discipleship ozio bad real bad
Failure to stay home
Smartmove yeah
But I don't know either way I'm not listening to a full show of Owen Shroyer
God I would give anything for them to have tried having
Owen
Talk to the
The pre-recorded phone call
Got to be so good I wonder if Owens Florida prison life
Anyway we go to Saturday
Because Alex put out a
Special Report
Special Report on Saturday and this is going to be a little bit of a shorter episode of our show
Just because
This is
When is Wednesday first of all
Iris Sneaky Snake
Snake episode
And then
That looks didn't come in on
I'm not quite ready to cover the
Response Afghanistan no I'm not at all ready
I'm
When Trump
Took office on Friday
Last week
I
Thought it was
Going to really work out terrible
But since Friday
Everything's been going great like
Covid-19
It turns out that was all a hoax
Get rid of trump and now he's back so we got rid of that I haven't had to wear a mask at all
All since then really great
What else
Just
Just good news all around since
Trump was reinstated on Friday of last week
It all went down exactly as
People thought
Here's the opening
The Saturday
The 14th Pastor 30
So
The shares
An emergency
Saturday
David Morris
I come with grave news but also goodness
Good-news-bad-news
Constantly all the time every single
F****** moment is good-news-bad-news
I was kind of curious this is only like a half hour long
Special report that
Even do this
What's
The point why is it what is what is so Monumental that you need to come in and of course
Yeah I guess you was trending on Twitter
I got up about 5 for
45s morning
Turn my phone
All these text message
You're blowing up on Twitter
You're blowing up on Insta
Blowing up everywhere
How did you predict
Kicked it again
And what did I see
I saw this image
Apologize
And I saw 10
And I saw the comments
People saying it's not
Real there's no way it's
Real
Other people later found the DHS document Lego no
Here's the NBC News it's true
Minnesota,
How did Jones do that
He's one of them
It's not about defending myself
Before I cover this
I'm going to
It's about
People understanding that
You can do everything I know
So there's some big news people tweeting about it
I feel like all of those Twitter things that Alex
Talking about our stupid
The
Someone being like Oh my God it's fake
Okay I'll Alex predicted this
Must be one of them
Also.
All of it all angles are
All angles that exists within Alex Jones's
Assessment of the side
Are dumb
There's no reaction that isn't going to be stupid because
The fundamental aspect of it is stupid
Simply being around it makes you dumber
It's fruit of a stupid tree
Between Good and Evil
He said what
What does DHHS tattoos
In June
Puppet Biden put out this new report
Terrorism strategy
From the Press
The number one threat are people that question the election
And or people that question lockdown
And those people are terrorists
The full word
I probably covered this
200 * 2
Obsessed
They come out last night on ABC NBC CBS News art
Tcnnf
And they say
Screenshot on the videos right here
Potential Terror threats opposition
The cupboard measure
Claims of Alexa
Fraud
Believe Trump can be reinstated
911 anniversary and religious house
What is even confused himself there
Whs put out a bulletin on August 13th I was essentially a warning that becoming. Was one where they can
To be a heightened risk of terrorism in the United
Alex is reporting on this and pretending that it's all just by putting a Target on his buddies who are Auntie covid measures and they won't overturn
The election
It's actually a little bit more complicated than that
The bulletin does discuss Alex's crew and the threat that they compose in terms of quote
Grievance based violence
But the picture is broader
One of the main element to this bulletin music
Concern about the upcoming 20th anniversary of 9/11
And the fact that lk2 released
Cocottes first
English language copy of inspire magazine
Andover for you
Your soul good for them
The. This bulletin is covering includes the anniversary of 9/11 as well as a number of religious holidays which is relevant
Because the report points out that
Many mass casualty domestic
Violent attacks
Target religious gathering
Thanks and that's something to be aware of us.
Country reopen
In terms of the stuff Alex that involves Alex's world I honestly think the report pretty accurately sums up the situation
Quote
There are also continued nonspecific calls for violence on multiple online platforms associated with
Domestic violent extremist ideologies
4 conspiracy theories on perceived election fraud
And allege reinstatement
And responses to anticipated restrict
Things relating to the increasing
Covid cases
This isn't about calling anyone who wants Trump to be president again a terrorist or saying that anyone is opposed to masks
There are terrorists
It's more about have a level and actors are exploiting those things to advance their agenda
They're sort of wedge
Yeah they've infiltrated so many of these
Communities that it's
Hey you know it's not the anti mask
The problem is that the anti Basque
Issue
Has been overtaken by Nazi
All of the Crystal new age people who have turned anti masking and more violent now are like
Well we have to keep an eye out for the crystal people is like the crystal people have been fine it's at the Nazis info
People traded those Crystal people and now they're terrified
It's not it yet and what it is is it's the miac report all over it
It's just the exact same intentional misrepresentation of
Summer
People who pose a threat
For domestic violence
Exist within this community
Being presented as this community is entirely terrorist
And that's just
You know that that's the game that he's playing and it have you seen it play out over and over again
Cheryl's
Yeah it works
Well yeah if you they had enough successfully mobilize against the miac report 3020 years ago
Maybe we wouldn't be
We are right now it's it's a very simple
Fallacy
That you can get people
Go to accept
Pretty easily
What's going on here so that the new version of Alex's right
Which is excited him so much
This morning but he decided he had to
Special Report
DHHS
Report says
Is water wet
Newscast
She found the actual
Homeland
Security bulletins
Put on screen
Were they go into more detail and they say
Terrorist for putting out the dish info
That lockdowns are bad
Emmett mask
Don't work
So they can recruit people to blow stuff up
Don't listen
I just want their money
Sherlock Holmes
Character
He says
His assistant Watson
Deduction my dear w
It's Elementary my dear Watson
Obviously when they said two months ago
If you oppose future lockdown
You're a terrorist
Preparing
That's obvious right
No
Very much anel
You don't just get to say something's obviously
I will accept this is dumb
Like let's say that more people you know back in 20
15 black Alex and Larry Nichols they were concerned about Obama
Revealing that he was a secret Muslim
But he was going to stay president for Everton United States at 2
A caliphate
Now what city
Bunch of people
Took on that that's ordered
Conspiracy theory has started
Did the mobilizing Maybe
Some folks
Took over the capitol
You know it maybe
The intelligence agencies are DHS might put out
Some kind of warning
Better
Hey some people believe that Obama is going to start
The caliphate
These people have of maybe a potential Terror threat
Obama is about to launch a caliphate
No
You know I think this is a situation where somebody who's really good at it
Explaining causal links
Could be invaluable right
You know what I'm saying nobody was a real grasp of a happy day if you go outside
And the sun is out there you will get a sunburn f*** you man that's you came up with that example
Because I got a thumper in the other day
I don't keep things in my brain on a hand they just show up when I made that was an attack on me and it's not an attack on
Yeah I just I just think that this is stupid
I mean like that this is a
Pretty basic
I think this is how Alex thinks
And that to me is
Is a real problem
Whatever anybody could be warning about is
Actually secretly them telling you what they're going to do
And that way if you fight against them your Prius preemptively labeled
That's just dumb
And now what the bad guy does of course
Is tell other people that
The other people are doing what they're doing in order to justify what they're doing against the other people
Divide the other people not act
What will be my aquaport again
All over again Nouveau my Akrapovic whatever
Doing biak report.
Myactivity Street
Not bad but it didn't include any french so
You're not wrong
I think this is all flimsy and the guy was going to take him the day off
New plane coming in to do a
Special report about this
But
I was right about everything I'll be here for the next half hour
Tower commercial
But huh
Resume content makes Dan and that's where we're trying to take that meat off the bone
I need to ask you this question because you are somebody who
It is taking a lot of involves content you understand some of the
The story is your
What do you is
The plan
For depopulation
Like what how does it actually work
What is the mechanism by which people will be depopulated
So first thing I'm going to do is get rid of the most obvious question which is
Which way
Because
Alex's elucidated Soma
How many different possible ways
Does that mean are you kind of
Kind of hit the nail on the head there
My ears my like overarching single single idea of what Alice
Truly
Kind of like ghosts
Dolphins
Which is reproducing Alex Turner I'm trying I'm doing my best channeling
I do not need to do funny voices you could
I could
The globalists are releasing a soft kill agent that will kill 80% of the population
Shouldn't the rest of which they will use as Serfs
In order to maintain their lifestyle
And that's my
General gist
I understand that but you actually even different angle that I was intent
What is
So it's the soft kill weapon
What's the vaccine tonight it'll kill people off or possibly
Makeup unable to reproduce
And do we have a new one.
Now I don't just need doing
Engaged
Deduction
Also engaged
Criminology
I've studied the globalist and their white paint
What they said what
An operation
Lockstep
Literally hundreds of other
What about animals
Prestigious organization
They're going to use the threat of a virus to bring in World Government World ID
The track-and-trace will
You do too
Cut your resources off
You so poor you can't afford to have children
Repopulate the planet
So now it's
Already so far we can't have enough children
They don't need to the rug Ruby the virus
Yeah it's so now apparently it's impoverishment to make it so you can't afford to have kids
They started capitalism up again about $80 in the eighties and now we're all f*****
I just find this to be difficult to square with all the other things I constantly hear and fear mongering about
I don't know why this is the plan
I mean was the plan Reagan closing mental health hospitals or let's say Reagan allowing a virus to go unchallenged
Check through a specific minority Community or any number of different possible ways
Exactly what it is
It's so tiring
It's really tough
Try to maintain some semblance of reality
In such a constantly nebulous
Fake space people in order to make them
I think I would break Union
I think my main goal would be to break and Airport Union
Birthday reggae
Well we may have some agree
There
Coming now
2 + 2 equals
They're getting ready to Stage major
False flag.
Magistrate
The blame those of us
24 sanakya
Against new lockdown
And that are against me
Not essential
Incredible Tarot
This country
I think Alex just kind of recognizes that the folks on his side have reached a fever pitch
And there's also the
Amen
Disappointment of Mike lindell's stupid cyber symposium
The
Hopes
Did some people had
The Trump is going to be put back into office
Has been dashed
Yeah
There's a lot of people who are probably desperate
And disappointed
And that
Tim could bind to
Something pretty violent
A good
Lead to a cataclysmic
Cataclysmic that's overly dramatic
Some kind of
Terrorism in today
Sure Alex recognizes that because
He and his Goons
His
Not boss Mike Lindell
Have gotten people into an emotional state where
This kind of thing is more likely and
Now then
Need to
Shore up
Any possibility that they could be blamed for
Yeah I mean it's
It's like
Hey we spent the last
2 years
Blowing up all these balloons
Another full
And some of them are going to deflate and some of them are going to
And I Mike lindell's Symposium has made a lot deflate and it's going to make some pop
And so that's what Alex is respond
Yep yep
So the CDC has some plan
Berryville AR
Official CDC document we covered last Monday
Is actively discussing the possible necessity
Of shielding high-risk individuals
By putting them in Corinth
Azure green
What say that again
People that aren't sick
But that might get sick
Being put in Camp
Whenever Alex has let's say it again
I just think of Cisco
I wish
God I wish Alex would come in with his head
Just like spray painted silver what day of the Great
So
This was something that got some traction because Candace Owens tweeted about it
Media went out it's making up stories about how everyone
The right-wing was going to be
Vindicated
Oh
Osher Holocaust Museum ya think it's offensively
Doing this
Nothing comparing this to the Holocaust did Nazis know we were right
They're going to put us in Camp the whole time
Unfortunately the actual document isn't about any of that stuff not surprised
It's a discussion from last July about how do you know when they're outbreak
People who live in places like refugee camps or
Particularly vulnerable
Due to compact living conditions and I levels of interaction
Between people
This document is about
Strategies that could be employed with an already existing refugee camps and areas housing displaced persons
And how in that setting it could be wise to separate high and low risk population
In order to offer is much for
I can put them as possible
It was an attempt on the part of the CDC to explore ways to best protect vulnerable populations
Soon only make sense of his taken by malevolent liars and turned it to secretly being a plot against them
It's amazing
Yeah
Cheese
Yep what a bunch of
And the CDC to f*** you
Q
You didn't put prisons in there just let B they're letting people in prison
Do the same f****** s*** I hate
You know what I bet I bet their prisons would be something that would be
I mean it
Anna and a good world
To be taken
But maybe that was a baby that's the focus of a different
Group within the CDC to study that
I do think that
To residential patterns
That exists within prisons and within Refugee communities
Rrr different
But different
I could see you in some things not being
Totally over laughable Interpol report
Is
Is very fair
Not enough consideration being taken
Tzatziki prisoners
Another thing that I would Springs up a bit is
Is there some applications that are being seen
That there is some potential IQ drop
It's being seen
In children that are born
During the pandemic
During the lockdown
And one of the there's a lot of conversation about what could
Could possibly
Account for this and some of it is probably down to socialization some of it is down to
Stresses and
Things that are experienced in utero also I don't think there's enough information on this
To really
Bully
Discuss it
And I don't
Don't know exactly
How accurately measure this is of
What is going to be the experience of these
Is children Isaiah's weight
You're older and so
So Alex is saying that like
Wearing masks caused a giant
Dropping IQ in all this
There is
Some
Information
Goes into that
It doesn't
It's not appropriate to save the masks
For causing that
Is an underlying real story but I don't think it's possible to know enough
To really discuss it so I'm leaving it alone
But I want I wanted to
Pointed out as like I'm not ignoring it entirely
It's just I don't think that
I don't think it's something that we can have a full discussion of outside of
Hey this is this is
This is an interesting
I think to be aware of about that and
That's a very
Yeah that's an interesting study and I think it would be a good idea to follow
Children born during the pandemic until they're 25 or whatever cuz it's not like we
This type of time in quarantine
Before
It's not like we have a large
Dataset of like
These are the children of born in a pandemic in This Is How They mature differently than other thing so I think it's a very
Valuable thing to study
But I'm not going to say that we should draw
Conclusion
And so I'm I'm leaving that aside for right now
Now the varus database
Do you have the vaccine adverse
Events
CIA database
Of course
Is a thing
Exist
So and does not prove in any way that any of these things were
Caused by the vaccines at all
But it is a very important statistic
School thing for p
People who study
Vaccines and study
Public Health in order to be able to better
I'll provide
I think so cause less
Adverse effects
Information
However there is apparently a doctor in Hawaii
A lawyer in Hawaii
Causing a second lawsuit
Against
I guess vaccine makers because of
Vera's Beto
It's not going to go anywhere now obviously
And I'm only playing this clip just because I think it's
There's a really important
Huge lawsuit
Hawaii attorney who's
The top lawyer of Learning Ally
Just coming back season
Killed nearly 45,000 Americans
Courtney his analysis
Aver
He's finally a massive class action lawsuit
Against it everybody is the top
Everett everyone's the Michael Jordan of
Hawaiian lawyers
Spell lawyer off
It was it's like the Miss America pageant
You know America to Miss Universe
The quarterback
Like challenge
You have to defend someone who clearly guilty
You have to solve three cases you have to litigate three cases while doing an Ops
It's like American lawyer woman for no reason at all 3 point contest
Yeah I just I find it annoying
Everyone is the best
This lawyer later find out was the top lawyer
Why can't it be somebody who's just like a middle-of-the-road guy who stumbled upon something huge
Do you not like that's interesting story
The way that Alex does this where everyone is the best lead to me to be very suspicious that some of these people are very not good
They're not the bad
I'm going to go out on a limb here and say that this lawyer is not the best lawyer in Hawaii probably not now
So Alex has been on a long Crusade against fact-checkers
Because he doesn't like it when people very
Accurately point out that he's wrong about everything
April snow
Is something that has been
A constant Target
Now BuzzFeed recently put out
Report about the
Yeah now this story about that is David mikkelson
Dirico founder of Snopes
He was found to have plagiarized
The number of articles
And so they ended up having to retract 60 articles
From the website
And that's
But it's not
100% counter
Do what snopes is about
You don't saying
Ethical lapse
And certainly
Be consequences and Nicholson.
You know that's no good
But
In terms of fact-checking
It doesn't really do
Like it it's not like they're making stuff up for stealing content
EXO
It's not
The big dunk that Alex wants
He's going to play it as if it it says it's ultimate vindication
Snopes and
All these other fact-checking
Groups run by Bill Gates
George Soros and other
Media Matters
Are going to come out and say none of this is true
No one ever died
No one ever got sick
Joe Biden won by record
World
Communism
But how many times did I tell you
Here it is out of
BuzzFeed
Snooze itself
Attacking their own
The co-founder of
Plagiarized articles
For the fact
Checking site
That's what he got caught
Employees are gone public
Say he would order them
Adjust plagiarize whole articles
And put their names on
And of course
She would falsify
Much of the information
We already know that about
But here they are
Eaten by the wrong
A total
Fraud
And now Snopes
Been so discredited
The globalist removing on D'Amore
Fancy
Fact-checking
It's just Snopes but wearing a top hat
I would like your finest fact-checking table thank you notes with a monicals.com
Yeah I love this the employees have come forward and
Said that he forces them to
Yeah I plagiarized
The other talking point that Alex has very routinely about Snopes as it's just a guy and his cat
I think
What he accidentally revealed is
Such a like crucial
Reason to trust
Everybody bought him with that far right
Infinitely more
He describes
BuzzFeed
Finding out that the co-editor of snow
Is the plagiarizer as attacking their own
Right and not
As quality control
Research or Jessica approached
Do journalism it's the way that things are supposed to be done and that he thinks of it is attacking
Their own just makes
If you're in the right-wing media sphere you don't attack your own all of your grips are bulls
Yeah and that's why I looks is still on this position of like
Hey look
Mike Lindell got
Taken in by con man
Anthony still good
You still going to do good
Not like the editor of Snopes
Not like the co-editor of Snopes
Not Meijer the co-founder whatever yeah
On the right
You don't attack your own until they become
I'm so much of a problem
Bad
Alex doesn't actually operate that way
It's people like one back yeah
I mean the larger ecosphere the larger ecosystem do kind of does have that like eventually if enough
Enough of the Sharks gather around and they're like this person
Got to go
Then they all
Dialogue
People are bullying
Glenn Beck is certainly in that camp
So you just gotta say no to
All this stuff
Write all the
What's good covid rules all the mass
You just got to say gnomon Tipper Gore
That's right I hate it too Live Crew 2 Live Crew and
Denver
That's Gallagher Jesus Christ is it I'm pretty sure
Weird
Anyway you just gotta say no
Just say no
No
And there's too many people
I'm not calling for violence
States are on false Flags
And blame those of us exposing
Their violence against us
But their lockdown
And their tyranny
Telling us we're not essential
Aw down and bankrupt us
SMS suicide
Better stop
But I don't want to be office of a violin
Opposed
As victims
And an outlaw
But know that they're coming with the false flag
So yeah
Know this
If you're listening to this
You're probably one of the people going to do one of those false flag
I mean the false flag
False ones
Hey I don't want any violence I'm just saying that they've committed a tons of violence against
I have been able to believe they are going to commit violence in our name
The in order to
To justify more violence against us
I mean it seems like not
Doing that is
Falling into a church giving them the upper hand
We have to commit our own violence before they can blame us for it
Weird
So there's some good news remember at the beginning this Alex out there was good news.
Stop say the good news
I was out
Today
Going for a hike
Like
Middle of nowhere
Outside Austin
Country Road
It's all Xfinity
They protesting
Globalism
And the great reset
Oh thank God 15 weirdos were protesting in the middle of nowhere are going to make
This
Change
And the New World Order
And then I was driving
Tomorrow office
Valdosta
And I saw more peep
Protesting
The legislature
They want voter ID
So we don't have
Criminals
Voting
EXO
The good news is I'm seeing Just Right Live
Massive push back in
That's the answer
The globalist
Probing
Testing to see what you'll put up with
And finally
I can't do the shows and I
Take care of our off
I can't do the
The work that needs to be done without you
Complaining
We've proven ourselves
We've proven word that on
Proven we do the research
I don't
Believe that are based at pivot this is the Hope
Activity
How much is a lot of fun
Oh man I saw some
The people on a country road
We're at a voter disenfranchisement
So
Stupid please give me money so I can help keep this up there were 20 people outside yelling
What a victory for the far-right
Women's March photos what are you talkin about Soros
When I was younger I would protest
Against the the Iraq War
And my parents certainly even more than I would
Every Wednesday they would go out to the corner of Providence and Stadium. Stadium
Providence is Providence in the goddamn
Get my brother cross street
They would go out there Broadway
Because Broadway in Providence okay we'll go out there every in Columbia Missouri and they honk
Peace
And you know it be that the hippies
Hang out in the basement
Against the Iraq War
It was meaningful in Subway
Like look at that and be like
Haha we're turning the tide
That's good news
I can sell hit Bayside that
Kind of the equivalent of
You know
15 people on a country road
Columbia 15 people on a country road
God this is going to
You know this is this is the good news that we've been waiting for
It's something and its people having a principal in
Against helplessness yet
Absolutely you know whatever but
It's not going to actually end the Iraq War
No I know
2 million women March
Didn't and s***
Does that hope bass tab pivot
And it's really weird
It's very strange because he gets into selling some product
And then it goes way off the rails
Please.
Mypillow.com
Promo code
And father
People that are in the arena
Need yours
And by supporting us you are the
The men and women in the arena
I thank you off
Opportunity
Please review
This news
Others
It's all just so
Joe Biden
Sure it's one thing when Alex Jones goes hey
It's in this document are going to Clara solteras
And I get people wouldn't go looking up at thought I made it up
Screw you you're the globalist terror
Socialist
Whatever you want to call it
Tell me an American
Essential
Another lockdowns coming and I've got to put up with it
Experimental shot or I can fly on an airplane
Job
F*** you
I got plenty work for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Yeah man
You're getting into it
You know that was the best swearing I think I've heard from him in 5 years
He pronounced it without saying it all weird like he normally does it was a little repetitive on the f*** you through but yeah
Yeah it sounded like a human
Yeah
Stevenson
Where is the best way to win the horse you rode in on
Is a nice little thing to throw in a nice little ATM
Don't know why you got all Angry so immediately shorts
What to do I
It's important that you go to my pillow and use my promo code also
F*** you
Very weird
How
How can you the day after
Day after that three-day Symposium be like
Mike lindell's a good guy you should still buy pillow I can tell you exactly how
You still a sponsor how is there no fall
There's just no fall for the right way because you're already all on Rock bottoms who else is going to sponsor Alex
He's not going to get a promo code at 22 she
Or manscaped
He's not going to he's not going to get one of these on it
Sponsorship
He probably couldn't switch to one of those sex toy ones either Adam and Eve
Steve Cash
No he's not my pillow or nothing
Vibrator
Type italics
That would not be a good day one thing about the Infowars we prioritize self-love
When I say f*** you
I mean you need to go fuc yourself
You could have been a duel at every direction of God
That would be really funny though to imagine like
But you know all these podcast have like you know
Put on a symposium where they tried to overthrow the election
Weather
It was such a disaster ended up Aerosmith
Heaven people still kept advertising
Ceo.of keeps as like here's what I'm going to do I'm going to reveal how we overthrow the Australian
Government and you like what I still don't want to lose my hair
So I guess we'll just keep going
Look I just your check is at don't have another option
If it works
What you going to do
So one thing you might notice there was some swearing at
Little bit of
And one of the reasons that this is kind of okay is because this is a special report doesn't on the radio
Ugly butt
Still a family
It's Alex does have to Apollo
I apologize for family viewers
When I put this out of the satellite over radio
TV
Proposing a ban. Video
The other day
You know what
Be offended by me saying
Bill Gates
People injecting children with deadly goddamn poison
What you going to do about that
I'm asking you right now
Yeah
I mean that apology went off the rails apology at all
That was it would almost say I would almost argue that was not an apology
I apologize for swearing is a family show but also
Bill Gates
I mean there's a little bit of like
I'm sorry for swearing so much
But if you don't like my swearing
That's what it was he Lady Sovereign
He just said like I'd okay for me to do this so you're not apologizing
If you love me then thank you
If you hate me then
You
Yeah this is a pointless
Episode
Of his show and tell by the photo show
We got me evening and I'm pretty stoked with the puppet Biden I'm enjoying that
I'm back
Fighting for my life
Oh man I'm fighting for my life cuz I'm scared of a day job that's common my friend that's what the heck
I'm farting from my life which is
Code for I am still taking Mike lindell's money
That was a like
Thing that we invented
For just taking Mike lindell's money
Take it like a what's Santorum
Like that
Spartan for your life your life is taking Mike lindell's muddy
It is now Canon
Shooter episode today will be back with taking a look at Alex's
No coverage of the Afghanistan news
I just want to
To check-in and
Let everyone know that I was too. Have a robust analysis of the end of the week and I've cyber symposium
Nope still on the payroll fill on the bed
Carver's life
I hope you all out there have a wonderful evening
Twitter
We are there a local charity or Bellefonte in your area to help out people doing God's
But till then I'm Neo I'm Leo and bcx Clark
It's been awhile but I'm also Daryl Rhonda's Ice Cube
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
I love you