I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Looks around drink that with the altars
Jim
Better made out of Selena authors I think that's what
Does it still write in July on my checks plan I cannot
Get out of autopilot sometimes
Stop
Yes yeah Dan
What's up what's new for you I've got a question for you
Sure what's your bright spot today is not Buzz Marketing post office
Not spawn Khan
Okay
I'm sending out all these buttons killing Santo fun look at these damn Mike
Cappuccino cappuccino stance
There's like a bunch of coffee drinks and I just got these ones that are people tap dancing
It's because
It's clear you can tell Moshe
Static picture
It's not moving at all because there's movement
Yeah I was in the Highlight is this one
Sun science
Oh that is actually pretty cool
They're like a kind of shiny even like they reflect light if you move them around different
Looks of the Sun
I'm cool son
Drinks for you to get some
And start really going for the stamp collecting
I'm going to get
300 stamp
By the end of this year I mean look dude one of the things that is definitely true is that I do have a collectors
Impulse it true I used to collect
Certainly basketball cards
A little bit of football card mostly basketball
Marvel cards
I was a little bit
Too old for that I paid my tab my timing was a tiny bit off
The Gathering I would have but my parents found it demonic
You got right in that attractive to me and
Inside I wish that I had the wherewithal to like stand up and
I'm going to have a secret collection with me but I did not
I had a weird situation I put I went to a magic the Gathering tournament at a
What's it called the
Masonic
Lodge
What am I friends
Is that
This is exactly what my parents were saying
It's so that the Masons are involved with magic the Gathering
I know I did not do well
It was only my second time playing but he was very interested and then they took 12 oz of your blood
Exactly
Losing
I don't think I'll get into
Leaving Sam's only reason is because there's too many of them
882 there's 88 been too long they been making them
Acceptance Now now is not the time
Like a long time ago with
Century your gold
Urns for a collection of something
Start diving
4 doubloons
We should collect
Doubloons
I can't tell you how it is and I am on that
Do it
Play some buried Sunken Treasures
Lights
Next vacation
Let's go
Alright
Books
Treasure hunting
I hear that there's a clue on the back of the
Decorations
You should go check that out
It's called humankind I think is the name of it
Pretty sure but
Basically civilization
You know it's really really good same but different in your life
Okay I realize that this is almost exactly like Civilization 6
But then while you're playing at your leg
I don't know if there's any other way to make this type of
Does game though like that's how
Incredibly valuable civilization is
The games like sort of like
City and state simulation
You start out in the Neolithic age and some of the cool things about it is that you can change your society and evolve over time and said
Just being stuck with like
Joe Empire
And now you're going to stay like that until the future
You can grow and change and you can have different kinds of different
Everything's going on it's actually really really in
I am looking it up and I'm seeing that it's just on
Computer is now so I am
Apologize for that doesn't really fun it's really good I do find that I enjoy those
Those games a little bit more than I thought I did
And coming up
Simulation games
It's kind of like
Took
Took a real backseat
That it's a nice if you've ever played Crusader Kings 2
Or something like that where the
Level up
Complexity is such that it's so
Impossible to like
Hey just start playing you like you have to read through Reddit for an hour
Just to figure out how to start
The game you know how do I walk
Exactly
But this one has like that good mix of
Difficulty and simplicity can find it
I'm so Jordan today what we're doing
When is we are talking about August
This is the day that the news broke
Taliban
Entering
Kabul
So I thought it would be interesting to check-in you know like these days that things happen
I always am interested in the snap
You know the day of
What is Alex's coverage
He's the tip of the spear
The capital has fallen he's tomorrow's news today
So
Today if something's happening
I guess you should be
Way ahead of
You think cuz he didn't cover
This yesterday or the day before
It's a
This day's news wasn't covered yesterday today's news is today
Right so let's meet at I want to see how he covers it
So here we are August 15th we'll get down to business on this
And say hello
New Wok so that's a great idea
Dwellsy
Thank you so much
My bad
Netflix and I apology walk
Chesterfield
Text squid muscle thank you so much
Thank you sweetheart just quit I'm not sure that's an interesting question
Jesus Christ
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Thank you
And also thank you to Samuel
I got I got two new member for the Williams family
An African rhino there be messaging here is to the destroyer of local
Municipalities swear undying fealty
D2 the altar of Celine okay
And then parenthetically I know I'm copying the good person who adopted the elephant
But it's a good idea
Pick it up sometime
Evolve outside of Eureka
Control ended
Looks a little scary
The Ivory Tower
Where is start off here in Eric.
Get into a little bit off the Jump
Taliban
20 years into Point trillion dollars
Break this United Nations Utopia
Love and kindness and goodness
Really
It's all been a Giants game
Dollars
In rare earth minerals
The country
Replace United States
As the new Empire
Bill just simple
Play buy off
Taliban
Didn't we try that
They're trying to blame Trump
For what has
Withdrawal
This is been a
Almost as if they wanted this to happen
On
From the US Embassy in Kabul is the Taliban
From all sides
I'm sure some people are trying to blame Trump
For the current situation in Afghanistan
I would agree that
That's kind of looking at too small of a picture
I would say the same as people who like to throw complete blame onto Biden
I think it's
With the Limited
Scope
There's plenty of blame to go around to a whole lot of people but I also kind of believe that assigning appropriate levels of blame isn't
Something That We're capable of doing on this podcast
So I don't even want to engage it
Alex is in a really tough situation here for his narrative
Just because
The Taking of Kabul is the direct result of the United States
Withdrawing troops which is something that he's champion
For a long
Time now
In the lead-up to the 2016 and 2020 elections Alex presented Trump as the peace candidate
In opposition
Clinton and Biden
HuHot
Seeking Skippy's conflicts going
Indefinitely
He was a major selling point for Alex
The Trump wanted to bring the troops home and for what it's worth
That's one of the territories where we were
Closest to agreement the positions that Alex
In October 2020 Trump announced that he wanted to withdraw all US troops from Afghanistan by Chris
I'm not sure what qualifies to Alex has a gradual withdrawal but considering how long the war dragged on its
That's not
Super graduate
Right
The Taliban celebrated this announcement mostly because it was in keeping in line with Trump's obligation under the Doha agreement
Which was signed in February 2020
Do you need added States
And the Taliban
What are the major points of disagreement was the US quote
Committed to withdraw from Afghanistan military forces of the United States allies and Coalition partners
Including all non diplomatic civilian Personnel private
Security contractors trainers advisors
And supporting service Personnel within 14 months
Following announcement of this agreement
After his election
In April 2021
Biden gave a speech where he laid out his plans as they related
The Troop withdrawals
From Afghanistan
According to the Doha agreement troops
We're supposed to be out within 14 months or by May 1st
Biden decided to begin the withdrawal then with a goal of being out by sea
September 11th
Fun symbolism
In the past month
Many of our allies like Germany and Italy have withdrawn their troops
And as we've withdrawn the Taliban is coming in and taking over the Capitol and every
Thing is
A real tragedy
This is a hard thing to wrap your head around from the people who were in Afghanistan right now to the veteran to a wrestling with these
These developments
Send their own
Personal relationship
To the people who
Staggering
People who are suffering
I I just
I don't
I don't know
I die. I'm not I'm not capable of
Over having to write
The position.
I mean I think the only major thing that I can say like with 100%
Certainty is that
The amount of people
Screaming about George Bush and Cheney and the military contractors in 2001
Is not large
That is
The TV fundamental issue from the very f******
Beginning
And that they're even talking about
Any other government
It's beyond the first one first
Who gives a s*** about Biden or Trump or Obama at this point we have to deal with the
Original f****** problem which we never even bother
Yeah I think I think there's something to be said for that
I think there's something to be said for
You know the maintenance of the war is your is is also
Something where
But again we're getting
Getting into finger point
I just
I think
I think that I think that there is an appropriate amount of that
It can be done
It's not the most
Pinpoint right now I don't
What I mean
I suppose
The most important problem is that we owe
A country
Two people yeah we stole it and destroyed it and then we left
And said here's the mess
And unfortunately our best
Attempts that week
We could make
To pay back or country
Would be
Well I mean it would be making everybody that wanted forever making everybody that wanted
United States citizen and giving them f****** Utah
We owe them a country
Metaphorically giving mute I suppose
Wee-wee-o a lot of
Folks certainly
Citizenship amnesty
It's too big of a
It is
And
One of the things that
I think it's really
Difficult one of things that I can't really understand even as much as I can
Can read on the subject is
Is there any point at which it would
Have been a tragedy at
This point
When we withdrew
Would another year
Have made a
Would six months has made a
Wood
The extent to which
There is no really good solution
Right it doesn't end up
In a messed up place
I don't know
I mean it seems like a
Fairly simple tactical problem that
If you have an Insurgent Force that's willing to fight
Until every last one of them is dead
Then you can either say that the only way we win is if we kill all of them or we stop
It's
Kind of the
Central issue there is like
If you leave
They're still there and they're going to fight until they all are dead
And it's something that's really weird to in as much as I think they can
People our age
Certainly
A little bit
Teenage I'm a little older than you
Spy like
This was really the
First disillusionment
Of my adult life
Yeah was the
The Iraq and Afghanistan Wars
The aftermath of 9/11
Was something that
Really brought into Focus
Political dis
Disappointment
And
Protest
That kind of
Involvement
And
To be now
Pushing 40
And
Here we are
It's
It's disillusion in all over again
In a certain way
I can't imagine what other people are going through and I like
Obviously whatever I'm experiencing is so minimal
Compared to
The other folks but it's
Yeah it's
Is a very messed up
No I mean that was immediately following
It was the first time in my life where I saw
Adults
With that much
Bloodthirst
Open
Just straight-up New York Times headlines let's
Kmol
You don't like it
It's that kind of level of
Jingoistic
Murder
I've been called for
And I had no idea that adults would act that dumb
And it's just been
Will put Abreva coronavirus exactly
Play yeah it was it was just insane
It was insane to watch
In real time just to
Some other news
What's going on in
Taliban
Ready to declare Islamic Emirate of Afghanistan
Recognize
Not true
China about recognized the Taliban as the Islamic Emirate
Or anything
How is it is making that up because it's part of what allows him
To fit everything into his tidy little
Conspiracy
Breyer news reports suggest
In the China would be willing to normalize their relations
The Taliban if they were to take Kabul
But that is not happy
According to an article in the Associated Press from August 18th
Quote
If we are going to recognize our government we will have to wait till the government is formed foreign Ministry spokesperson.
At least John
Said on Wednesday
Quote only after that will we come to the quest
Action of diplomatic record
So that's not even
Something that they have
They have.
I was just making that up
Yeah that I mean to see
To even say that it's like
Imply that things are done
Like the situation in Afghanistan is just
Well they finished it's over nobody's going to be opening up very normalize diplomatic row
For a while
Yeah and I didn't like when the Taliban was in charge of the country prior
Did 9/11
Very few countries recognized
The Taliban
Baby concept of it moving
Forward with many countries
Recognizing and normalizing relations
It seems
Fairly unlikely
I mean it's not like we're you know
It's not like everybody's trust in America to not change their mind into years or whatever it is you know like
Who is
What makes you think that
At new president
In two years wouldn't try and start another for
F****** War somewhere you know like it's
It's ridiculous to think that they would
Uno's
Sub to me I think that this is probably the
Top of the top news story that's Alex could be covering here on the
Absolutely
It's not
Okay let's just plowed right into the big scoring
Honest and it snow
Electric
Civilization by Design
Globalist
Their post-industrial agenda 2030 plan
I've been warning of
In the middle of
So here's the headline
Infowars.com
DHHS officially designates anti-lock
Protesters at
You know read the whole article
Case study that I'd like to make I want to make this
Super clear for everybody
The headline of this story on RT is
Quotes by Administration Warren
Brett from anti-lockdown extremist
A sympathizers marking 9/11 anniversary
If you read the article when it's reposted on Infowars you see a completely different headline
Quote
Biden DHHS
Officially designates anti lockdown protesters
As terrorists
The headline of the Arty article is fairly odd fairly accurate as it relates
It's the content of the article
But the Infowars version
He's not
It only gets worse when you get to the sub-headline it's been added on Infowars
Quote Biden's attempt to establish soviet-style dictatorship and Now official
Okay that was quick
This is absolute next level of violating Turtles
Stochastic
Not only is Alex been found to have not gotten permission to riposte other outlets articles many times
In the past
Very clear that his website website is transforming other people's work
This headline does not match the Arty article and whatever credibility that a website viewer might apply to arti
Is being stolen by Infowars and subverted
For their own purpose
It gets worse to
Within the body of the article Infowars is inserted multiple tweet
It's one by Paul Joseph Watson which do not appear in the body of the Arty article
Weird there's no editorial indication that these tweets are not part of the original article
Line on the article is Artie
There's also multiple ads for Alex's dumb pills and embedded video of someone owing
Troyer interviewed by Pitzer
Let's concerning in terms of directly misrepresenting content then
Embedding tweets
Alex nobody's willing to work with us anymore we kind of burned all of our bridges
I got a plan
Steelix
Take out one contact and a little bit
Does anyway Have you listened to
Come on
Considering how concerned Alex was about the co-founder of Snopes
Plagiarizing some articles
I would suggest he get his own house in order
Cuz this is amazingly on ethical work
I think it's almost like he saw snow
Oops plagiarize article
Cousin
I could just plagiarize article cuz this is this
Kind of practices going on for a long time
But I just think that this is an interesting instance of
Is it a very transparent
Transformation of a word
This article and Artie and Alex is completely changing the headline
Adding a sub headline
Throwing in some of his own content in the middle of it
Last night
No I wouldn't be happy with that if I were them
No
I probably
Seasons assisted letter atleast
Fair to them
I'm not usually on the side of Defending RT but here we are.
Did you shouldn't have to put up with
Your stuff being
Misrepresented like that
Do you like somebody just reposting one of our episodes with knowledge fight guys prove that they are socialist
Monsters and then cut it their own ads into the episode
So Alex gets to this what this is all about
Behind look with all behind this
The calling lockdown protest
Chester's terrorist
National strategy for countering domestic
Terrorism document
Nashville strategy for counter
Policy
I said any narratives of fraud in the recent general election
Impact of the violent breach of the US Capitol
Conditions related to covid-19 pandemic
Conspiracy theories
Almost certainly
Want to try to engage in violence so
So you're that little stutter-step there at the end and what happened was Alex's cold reading this paragraph So he
We came to an abbreviation dve
And he didn't know what it meant so he just said someone
If you actually read or understood this document in any depth he would know that that means domestic Violet extreme
That abbreviation is actually explained on this
The very same page of the document like four sentences prior to Chinese reading
Way further up
It is
Alex is sort of reading this correctly but he's not quite giving it the context that requires to be under
Understood
Here's the larger Passage
This is from
Quote
Enduring dve motivations pertaining to biases against minority populations in perceived government overreach will Olmos
Will certainly continue to drive dve radicalization
And mobilization to violence
Newer socio-political development such as narratives of fraud in the recent general election the emboldened impact of the violence
Free to the US Capitol
Conditions related to the covid-19 pandemic
In conspiracy theories promoting violence
Will almost certainly spare some dve
Do engaged
In violence this year
The document lays out today to primary varieties of domestic terrorism that are on their radar
Are racially motivated an anti-government
Related
But even with that being said they point out that quote
Other demands
The terrorists may be motivated to Violence by single-issue ideologies related to abortion animal rights environmental or
Involuntary celibate violent
Extremism
As well as other grievances or a combination of ideological influences
In some cases individuals may develop their own
Syncratic Justice
Applications for violence
The Dubai ready categorization
This document doesn't label Trump supporters are any anti lockdown protesters to be terrorists
It honestly barely even spend any time on them
It's a broader picture
Sure but
Just can't waste any opportunity portray themselves as a world's biggest target victims
Boring
Yeah especially whenever it is been proven over and over and over again that these types
What's the things almost always wind up being
More direct
Acted towards leftist protesters than anything else
I think this is
Honestly
From this distance that I could
Get from it is
About
Bigot viola
Yeah but there's most noted in this document
I suppose my problem with those documents is always like whenever they're talking about bigot violets they're not in
Including that most of the DVDs are also the people trying to investigate
Protests
I think I think that if you were somebody who is
Incline towards
Bigot
Bigotry
Related domestic
Violent extremism
You might hear something like this and think
Southern border is completely wide open
There are people coming across the Bubonic plague cases
Spring all over the United States
They are
Cross with
Hundreds of
Diseases that are extremely rare
Whiteman in the tropics
Better now spreading all over the United States
But they're going to tell you that your five-year-old needs to wear a mask
Celtic evil lazy
Teachers union wanted to swing
They're filthy
That's so it's not reminiscing
So does not say derealization
Who played certainly not like something we've seen
Never let the genocide before
It's just I've ever quite a bit is equating disease with
With immigrants
Other population
And said he doesn't like
Yep and that's disgusting
Also does bubonic plague
The storyline is got Nautica
Control
Do I wear still on
Apparently there's
Transmission of Bubonic plague in four states now
Which is not true
And also
That's all Alex's
Traced it
I guess there's an index patient there was
No it was actually it was actually a Capuchin monkey but then they you know it's Fred from there and Alex would you
What's your guy who sold the cat
What you don't understand is that I need to sell so many supplements and dump
Is that we have
The state-of-the-art last where we do research
And figure out exactly where the plague came from
Steve pieczenik my friend
Of course it is
He cured it himself
Too I know that I know the first case of very well
So great
Sia
Alex's being
Disgusting
But
You know he's also
Really prepared
I'm not complaining
I spent
Children are gone right now
So I've been studying
12 hours a day
Working 12 hours a day
I studied about five hours Friday I studied about not 14 hours yesterday
Saturday and blonde guy drinking our today
Let me let me just calm down
Comeback
Okay I'm sure you are
I'm sure this is going to happen
Start from the beginning I've done a million hours of studying in the last day
I said it for 36 hours
In the past 24 don't know if this is a weird quibble for me and maybe I've even used the term in the past
Somehow saying studying
Hits my ear weird
Studying cuz usually like you study for something
Get ready for a test
Get out
I don't know why studying
As an exercise doesn't
It seemed like
For some reason it doesn't that doesn't feel like the right word but
I like he's really married
Researching seems like
The correct word
Investigate
Eating
Reading wood
Be very simple and easy to say
Think about the word
Imagine if you prepared really hard and really well and then this is what happened
Like
I would love to see Alex try and defend his Ph.D
Oh my God I'm at sincerely
Do you did
I'll prepare and then you like
Completely f***** up by preparation
No I just it's just been a habit for my whole life I know everything but I fail every test cuz I pray
Prepared too much is just failed every test
You were in that
Sort of position
Is that was what
Come to you then I can understand why you would learn to never prepare
I've never read it
Does what he does prepared gets into this headspace
Happy's terrible
I'm so
This makes Clippers another
Thing that I wanted to use as I kind of a teachable moment in the same way that looking at that RT headline that Alex is
Completely changed
An added to the body of the
The text
This is another piece of rhetorical technique that Alex uses
But if you can recognize some stuff like this it is very helpful
In terms of penetrating
His b*******
The Taliban are caveman
And they are terrible people
Something actually
It is kind of cool
Dungeons are all over
Adenoma sexuality's about 90% in Afghanistan
50%
Grooming gangs in England what the f*** are you talking about
Kebab machine
Conrad's
Indicative of his style and it's a perfect encapsulation of Lights
Kind of impossible to even
Think about talking to him
Clippers a minute-long it is probably
I'm going to give you an incomplete list of the different claims Alex would mean to substantiate before I would allow him to say
Play another setting okay here we go
The Democratic party said an internal memo that it's
Kind of cool that the Taliban keep children a sex away
I'm going to need to know who these
But who is this
Democratic party and Democratic party. Com
Okay
Go to 90% of Afghanistan are homosexual
I don't even know if I can fake a reason for that what that is definitely not true and I can find no indication of where Alex might be pulling
This picture from
Patricia Grossman the associate Asia director for Human Rights Watch told the telegraph quote
Same-sex relations are punishable by 5
Go to 15 years in prison under a law that bans all sex
Between individuals not married to each other
Afghan law specifies that marriage is between a man and a
Yeah I was going to say
What world would you get that
Anonymous
Three fifty percent of the population of the Middle East is homosexual
Come back to self to save his life
For some contacts in the United States a recent Gallup poll showed that we were at a record of 5.6 +
Set of the population who self-identify as lesbian gay bisexual or trans
The proportion of the population of the Middle East that Alex
Display my Robin cycle is absurd
Butthole children and meat kabobs talk about a little bit
Once yourself ever
We covered that overpass episode and Alex came back up that story at all
I just do the case of Charlene Downes who was a girl who went missing in 2003 in the UK
Two men who ran Fast Food Spot were tried for the murder and in the trial the prosecutors allege that the minute.
Discuss dropping upper body and putting it into the
The kabob
This was never proven and the main were ultimately not charged and released
The prosecution was working off covert surveillance that was quote
Handled poorly and unprofessional
To the point where the detective who was in charge of the case had to resign
After being found guilty of misconduct on a disciplinary hearing was called
To review the how things left
Look at what
Shenzhen country that hold
I wouldn't let Alex proceed until he accepted that this was a story that he couldn't prove it all
Sandy's just yelling detail points
Yeah
5:30 takes live babies and keeps them alive so we can scout them and put their hair and brains on crack
That would seem to come out of left field
That's just
Stuff that's dumbest representations of the new Center for Medical progress that came out
Substantiate any bastard yelling about it
Scalping is self esteem
They're training people and beagles up and putting maggots in their heads to eat their prey seems overly
Complicated
I actually have no idea what Alex is talking about
This is such a wide swath of points about completely unrelated topics I would take a really long time to actually discuss
And when you took the time to do so it will become super clear that the version of these stories that Alex's presenting is not real
When you shoot them off like a Gatling gun what he's trying to do is create too many points
Trulicity
Even consciously take in
Let alone routine
Flood the market with v
This is a tactic to demagogues in bulshit artist use pretty regularly
It's kind of a self-defense mechanism because
On the one hand it makes them appear to know a lot of stuff
And it also makes it so the most critical people probably wouldn't want to engage with them
If you're trying to debate a point with Alex and he responded with a word salad like that
Who be really difficult to know what point you're supposed to respond to which is intentional on Alex's fart
Nonpoint on the road stand up to scrutiny but if you string enough of them together
You might be able to Bluff it
And make people just
Too disoriented
Two to argue with you
This it's a dishonest
A manipulative debate tax
Yeah it's
It's black throwing
Sand in Europe
He's just being
Now debate
Like in blood
Sport
This is the Jean-Claude Van Damme of
Propaganda
See ya
Alex gets
Two talking about
The covid-19
Queens
Why there's the plague
It's a good point
Why are we talking about a made-up leg whenever the real Bubonic plague is in four states now Dan
Yeah I would think that should be a bigger issue if Alex
Believed his own b*******
You should be leading every show with
Remember what happened last time
Show me people to wear a mask
Oh
Your narratives are working at cross-purposes
So Alex starts talking about operation lockstep
And this just isn't
Let me explain the Playbook
Permanent world government
Rockefeller Foundation cooked up landfill operation lockstep
Listen to mop song
Loosen up sign
Three successive approximation of the world ID card
Mobile carbon tax system
Your phone
For gene therapy on a monthly basis
System wants to put into you
No more FDA process
No more nothing just Absolute Total tyranny what's fascinating to me about that is like
That none of that stuff Steven
Ian
Document that Alex calls operation lockstep
It's pretty remarkable like the the the distance
From primary sources that he's gotten
And how much of this really just
Is
Based on him repeating the stuff over and over again and building up the narrative
Snowball goes downhill at Thrifty grabs twigs
All the sudden your
Tiny little kernel of truth from a headline is now a snowball of b******* about
Fauci scalping
Babies
Where did this virus come from
Make sure Alex underneath baby's head
Will be serious
Mysterious
If you're out haha virus
Wuhan Institute of virology
Fauci
And Obama in North Carolina
Because
You keep it in the United States
A long-standing
Narrative the main one
It's about to accidentally change
20 hours of unwholly
In December
And we put out a
Emergency everyone's waking up to us
We're just giving backseat Montebello Melinda Gates Foundation
Forgetting wobbly
We've got to do something and I sat on her one but that document came out those videos came out
We learn about until January 2020
I said this
Covid-19
Out of England
That's really rabbits out of England to the US
Give me the Chinese
Bio weapon cook
Monday I don't know I must have missed that
Sun never set on the British
I think Alex just accidentally said the co it came out of England decided to run with it cuz there's
Just missed it and then I suppose you could say it was developed
Down something says that's the big bio-weapon lab that he has in the UK
Alex didn't watch 20 hours of this un
World Health Organization conference
We covered it back when he first discovered this stuff but just for a little refresher he's talking to at the global vaccine safety some if it took
Alex didn't watch all of this nor does he understand the issues they discuss
You just saw couple Clips The anti-vax Lunatic Del bigtree posted
Herman Alex wrote his own story to flush out the rest
The details
Whatever this narrative comes up at
It's just a matter of me waiting
To hear him say the word wobbly
But we only hinge word he has to remember this tortillas
He always says wobbly
The only way
Jog is memory
That word is actually used in speech by dr. Heidi Larson
The director of the vaccine company
Project
Dr. Larson Davis Beach on the second day of the conference at the Biltmore complex in the way Alex
Presented
She does say that there are doctors who were expressing less confidence in vaccine that I visit
Is the problem
But she's not saying that those doctors are right
Reports on this conference like
The World Health Organization getting together to sound the alarm but doctors around the world they're catching on to the scheme and that's what
What's making them wobbly now it's more like doctors are losing
Yeah and people
Have
New methods of
Communicating misinformation or a complete information
In reality dr. Larson
Speech was about her trust-building is an essential step move move
Forward in society
Here's a clip of her from her speech that you're never going to hear on Infowars that I think it actually pretty well captures
There's a lot of her point
One of our biggest challenges
I think now
Is getting rid of the term anti-vax
Getting rid of the Hostile line
Language
And starting to have more conversations
To be open to question
To make people
Feel like
They shouldn't be judged
When they're asked
Crazy as those questions might see
Same to you
As stupid as they might seem or as ignorant as they might seem
This is an interesting perspective that she's bringing
Oh wait
To proactively build trust sure which is trying to diss a big you ate the people who are
Driving the propaganda from the people who are effect
Yes people who have like sincere and legitimate concerns and questions they feel are being answered right
And people who are willfully misleading people
Cuz if you can separate those two groups you can make a lot of progress in terms of building Trust
With the people who have questions
That maybe
You would
Instinctually or as a knee-jerk reaction be like your auntie Vex weirdo
And respond with hostility or derision
Maybe that isn't the right approach
What you saying
Makes a lot of sense especially from the person
Yeah the position that she isn't sure no of course
And you know it the same time you can definitely see you.
Doctor is having like his 30th
If parents come in the same day been like
I don't know if I should get my kid vaccinated and he's like
F****** stop reading the internet and then turns into an a****** like I'm going to be exhausting day
Apple clips from this summer they were put up by people motivated by a very
Specific political agenda
The big version of that summer that he's established on the
The show is now like
It has been for a bit but it's the explanation for why the globalist needed to do covid
Story but it's just
Not real
Vaccine is premeditated murder
Sure
Of course you are
This is just
How old
Premeditated psychotic murderer
They're going to stay this winter with all the
Imagine this winter going to be sedated
Martial law
God
Supposed to do it on last Wednesday I thought it was already done
A man again
Again if you're listening to this show you got to have that feeling a lot
It's kind of amazing that you can just keep stringing me along like that
Oh going on fifteen years
Another another explosion, Nayana Kill Everybody
Next week
Okay well I'll see you in a couple weeks you want me to pencil you in for next year too
Your reserve a spot for biting to kill everybody
That's going to happen
Camping
So Gaston the show now this
Classic name
He's
Comedian from the Catskills
But he's from Aurora Illinois
They make good people in Aurora
Kinda fella
I don't know
It's a hundred percent
Vaccine
So why globally was this done
Warfare
I want to hear from somebody
Specifically who's got a political parties
Having some success
PPL Electric
In Israel
For medical
Freedom
He always comes first with the medical
4 minutes left with
Gordon
So yeah like I said this guy is Israel
Just outside Chicago
He is not politically relevant in Israel
Regardless
Alex is trying to put on that
Unlike major political party but this is
Really true
In 2018 he put up a page on a crowdfunding website to run for the open
Primary three
The Slate of candidates for a party running
Prepositions
Ultimately raised $162
It's from four backers one of whom was Anonymous another of shared his last name
Wow I would hope so
In the crowdfunding page he discusses how he's a member
Of the zahoot party which is a
Very hard right political party in Israel
Sure they're super into expanding settlements
Location to show up on Rogan sometime soon
0 seats in 20.
I don't know if I would rank him as one of the main political parties
He's willing to talk to Alex so that means he's got to be Prestige prestigious
Any moment now they're going to get all the way up
Between one and two seats in the knesset
Is against vaccines and is against vaccines
Passport
Alright plane crash proof of vaccination requirements Uranus that's Tuff
He also seems to be pretty against the Reform Judaism
It's a weird conversation and I'm not interested in one of those weird libertarian internet people
Do just like have a hodgepodge of things that they're against it for no reason to be honest Alex seems a little bit
Thrown by that kind of
And also
I think Alex is is is
Going to have some
Some trouble with Nick Fuentes
And I always got this
This hard right
Israeli guy who believes
And what have you I know that
Nick Castle
Thoughts about Israel
So I don't really care too much about this interview
But another Gaston
Canadian weirdo Chris sky
I've got you wanted to start his own School remember Chris guy
He is now Alex's
Favorite guy
Latest information on
Is about to join us
He's the most successful the most prominent most actor
I'm sure he wants to be a clipped by you
It's about survival humans moving forward
Exposing medical tyranny
5th generation Warfare of depopulation
That is moving against it because all these cops are saying
This is going to be a depopulation weapon
And now it's happening and now
They lied last year in the hospitals were totally empty
The virus itself was just a game of function thing they own now
Now what's in the vaccine crane the prions
It's what's causing massive illnesses all over the place
And when you go in they don't tell you you need Ivermectin any vitamin c u need zinc
Chris Kyle
Absolution
Italian Hospital
And they just wait until you get worse
And then they play
Then later on you until you again
$3,000 for
Wow
Hospitals are murdering you for money
Yeah I would say congratulations Chris guy on being Alex one of Alex
Unfortunately that does not have a lot of longevity
And doesn't it
No typically you end up forgotten
Or maybe
Disgrace
Definitely that one
I think that it is going to be fun
Time to get together a support group
It might be a good idea might be a good idea they have a lot to talk about
Similar stories
It would be a mentor
I don't care about Chris
Skype
But also this interview is kind of Interest
Elements to it
Chris guy's phone
Keeps going out
He just had a large rally antimatter
Type of rally
Can you point out we don't need leaders we have to be the leader but you imagine
Governor of Texas the governor of Arizona a governor of Florida
Glad
So I think
Is the governor of Texas Greg Abbott is a little bit busy
Right now
Covid
I think you should leave that rally and breathe on everybody who shows I think he might be might be in bed
Wooden things that I
Enjoy bike
He's high-minded
I'll bet his auntie UMass can T-Rex nonsense
He's also incredibly Petty
He seems to be airing like personal grievances on Alex's show
Like there's one guy he just does not like
In Canadian politics
8 planes by kamelot
Oh and also apparently there was a booking
Website
I got to call out somebody right now real quick
The international covid Summit
Taking place in Italy
I was invited there
Invited their months ago they may be promoted
Two weeks ago they made me register for the event as a speaker I have all the evidence of this
Make me go on a zoom chat and they told me that I was going to be there
15 minutes
And I was going to be getting an award
They told me to start booking my
Supposed to be there on the 13th
Can I get a call
It started getting
Pressure from somebody as soon as they
They call me back and they said
You're not allowed to talk about
Vaccine
I said
The wholesome it's about alternative treatment
They said that's great
And they call me back about an hour later we go have another chat
Okay
Bayside Walk
Say anything about the vaccine
You're also not allowed to discuss
Any form of God
Government civil disobedience
Is all tabs if you take money
And you did agree to promoted you
Yeah it definitely would
Yeah so I guess you failed that test
The funny part about this is that the international covid Summit
It's supposed to take place between September 12th and 14th and Rome
GoFundMe page
Oh how's it going
$2,000 about out of there 50000 gold rays
A comedy though
It's not what's funny
What's funny is that the URL
For their GoFundMe
Is gofundme.com help and censorship
Here's Chris guy telling me that he was
Rudely censored by the
Kid I talked about the resistance to the government or vaccines
What gives man I thought these people they hate censorship but I mean they are
I've been used
I checked out their website looks dicey as hell
Yeah one real big red flag is it there's no list of speakers on website
But it's in Rome so if my boy Leo isn't there I'm going to be.
A big missed opportunity
Officer Chris guide said in that to that clip there
He has a cat
Praise
It's United
I thought it was boom shakalaka
Booyah
You know you know what
What you want
What's people to do
What's that unitedly non-compliant
Which means
Form a union
More or less
He's calling for a general strike
All you got to do is
Very simple
Yeah go on strike
If your Apple
Stop it's our doctor lawyer
Frontline worker
Teacher
Student
Xcetera
The work you don't show up to school
Simple
General strike
General strike not for this reason I'm fine with it we'll figure it out afterwards we'll figure out why
After everybody is just struck
We do for their first things first
General strike
The opposition
Withholding labor
Advance
A cause that these people have
It goes completely out the window whenever it's a minor inconvenience
Slightly sometimes indoors
So all of the posturing I've done and organized people
And how strikes are evil and how they're stealing money from people I'm going to abandon that I'm going to say it's time for
For a general strike Forever by
So Chris has an event coming up
Of course he does
He wants to promote this
Seems a little bit
Craven
Turn on the 20th
I'm having out of
Private event
Social media
Anybody in Canada
Power
Resources
And wants to see this
Is finally ready to get off their ass get off the sidelines
White
Can you show up there
Yeah man
If you're in Canada money and I'll power
I want to hang out with you if you have money and power
I would like to
Con you into giving me both money and power thank you very much. Please come to my event
I am a hyper charismatic weirdos
Kind of
Right in the middle of his attention cycle right now and if you want
You want
Give me my lunch hour
This is a test to see if you would do it for money and the answer is yes of course you would
So Christmas
Phone difficulties and what-have-yous Alex
Length of a little bit
Are you gets to
Talking about some weird s***
This is where things broke
Broke real strength
What percent of Saudi Arabia
The Chinese
This was for Canada
This was for the UK
This was for Australia New Zealand for America
Anglo-Saxon ethos
Wow
All white people
Don't do this
Yes it is talked about
Getting rid of Magna Carta getting rid of the Bill of Rights getting rid of the Constitution
Idea
Wow Roundtable
Amazon at the head of the table
I can't believe I've had to save us so many times on this show
But King Arthur wasn't real
I'm Blown Away by
By using King Arthur to justify white supremacy
When's the new one
I like even his qualifier that it's like
Not all white people are
Supreme
Green people are white
I don't get why you think this is racist
So leaving aside the King Arthur
Alex at the 20% of Saudi Arabians are vaccinated but that number is actually 47
1.6 %
And according to Reuters
Alex said the 10% to is in India and I figure is actually 20.4%
Time is it about 67.5%
This districts that are available or not of total people vaccinated but the number of doses administered and then you just assume that people get
Two doses
So factoring in the windows vaccines these numbers could actually be
Be higher
At the same time there's some people who get one dose but not the second dose which like a Pfizer in moderna so
That could shift the number a little bit here but the point is that Alex is just making up numbers and using them to justify his bizarre wife
White supremacy
That's that's
That's just real fun
Target
Places that are descent
Of descendants
Right
Yeah
And as we all know from Reading history
Prior to King Arthur
No leader had ever listened to the people that he was leading before
Never
Never had they thought they were
Equals there zero civilizations that have grown up in places outside of white places that have
Created democracies and republics
Publix in the lake
But also things
Didn't end up working out so great for that Roundtable
Fine I guess you still lost
His wife
Geiger kill them
Look King Arthur
Dot-dot-dot
Great
X Also let's not forget
King Arthur
Technically still on his way back
Caswell is King Arthur's coming back
Okay
Warren LifeLock
The thing is
In history we have
Going to way back
King Arthur Round Table
America
Straight line
And if you are somebody who's like
I don't know
Not white
Right in America you should feel bad
You should feel lucky
What is Western Society
Give me black
But because you live
Syrian
Rothchilds another
Evil took over King Arthur
Syrian spirit
Create
For a few
They are seeking to overthrow it
And kill it
The world's not being targeted
Okay
So
Alright
This is an interesting wrinkle 222 Alex's
Historical
Lure
Yeah
I mean
I guess he's a monarcas
So that's
Do you like the presentation I guess of a benevolent monarch
What's a monarch
Pretending to listen
Yeah that sounds like what people who believe in God would want right
I guess basically the same thing that they think God is
It's just a guy who's
It's like really nice and run say
So I guess
Pictures of reward
Jean Arthur
Is
Almost did
Deified
Figure
Well yeah I mean he is coming back in the Arthurian Legend
He does resurrect later on
I mean c.s. Lewis YouTube
I think it was this present Darkness
Is there something like that it is out of
The Silent Planet
King Arthur comes back to life
Modern-day England or whatever
King Arthur's coming back
Man I don't know I struggle to fit
The pieces together of this jigsaw puzzle
Just it's a mess
So King Arthur
Round Table
Knights
Equals
White people are superior
Alex must have really hated Monty Python really struggling for him
Okay so
Chris guy come
Comes back
Any Elena
Comply with this vaccine stuff
You're all going to die ever this
But if you don't
Utopias
Comply
We could have
A golden or what they're going to call
Crystal age
Society
1Weather
People have
Total control over their lives
One where we have a much higher standard of living with a much lower cost.
Fabletics
Much less centralized
Control
Control of resources from
A few people
This is what
They don't want
Because they lose their wealth they lose their
We will
We'll all get
Good life
They've been enjoying
So how do we do this
Call United.
Compliant
Simple
United
I don't comply
Chris guy is on fire as usual we're going to reconnect with him having turn off the stuff on that laptop
His phone went out again
Yeah I mean like this is a little bit pie-in-the-sky ish
It seems like
Very nice
Specific
We're going to enter a wonderful age where everyone will have everything they want
A chicken will be in every pot
Yeah
And also
There's not a world of difference between this
And
So she know it's exactly that
No it's kind of it's kind of funny that he's described
Accurately the problems
A potential solution
And the way forward and yet
At the same time
The people he works for are the ones who are continuing the
Status quo that he is
Yeah there's a there's a desire
For people who have
Has been
Left out
Control their own destiny to a greater extent
Democratize the workplace maybe income inequality is out of control
Yeah.
General strike is a good idea
I think so but I don't want to do his he don't want to do his either
That's the amazing thing that they
That they manage
To do like that Fox News and Alex and all of those people
Like yeah man we income inequalities out-of-control yeah we don't have control over online
The government is f***** up and can't
How to tell if whatsoever yeah
I agree with you in a general strike
Is a good way to send a message
But we're not going to take this s*** anymore
But the people that you are agreeing with are the what do I default to the problem in the beginning
The bus
How did they do that how did they trick you into thinking that by work
Looking for them you will be working again
Them
It amazing
I don't know and I have a headache
So Alex starts talking about how
When you hear smart cities
It is I thought it meant like charger
Alright
And then it leads to an ad
Development
Nazis
I think Beyond Nazis think absolutely being starved
In control
We're going to make it harder and harder by the way
Stay on air so I need to remember
Tell the listeners of this broadcast
On this Sunday evening
Without your support
Thousand percent a trillion percent
Infinity committed
What if I don't remember my t-shirts and buy bulk sand
My films
We won't be on the ear
We're more important than ever
I'm not trying to brag my phone
Sure
Leaders of God
All the major talk show
Probably call me up
Real blessing to me
And I'm looking for other people to be in that position as well.
That's how we win
Is rising people up
You have a spirit
I need money to fight this so
We got a big special
Okay
The Oracle has a special
The Oracle table
In the early days of the Trump presidency Alex is like
Yeah you know Trump around the way. He calls me the Texan
Yep he always like I would have the Texans
Man
I remember the Mirchi is to be able to get it delfi
It was just
Rideable hey what's going to happen with the rain
Then she'd be like I'd love to
I'd love to tell you
But first here's a gun part
You're going to have to buy where to hide
A a bucket of food
Alex comes back
And
Chris guys now on the phone
And the outside
Alex
Say some stuff
I get into his
Repeats the same think you literally just already sore
The human Spirit Rises
They'll be facing millions of us
We got bad blood
Ready
Real quick I want to talk
Talking about the concept of
Facing a million Alex Jones is
I would rather fight 1000 Alex Jones's than one
Because they could never get along
That's true
Find a way to hide it like at the top of a
Retrieve you'd be safe this what you do if you got $1,000 Jones's you just be like
You guys have to fight in a tournament
Ed only one of you can fight me
Like I said your week that exactly other Allen
What is Big Mac you hate that guy don't you
You controlled opposition
Probably won't even break
Just started whisper campaign but they were just
Big fall like dominoes
Not coexist
Did you hear that that one married a non-white person was
Awakening
Sky
Doing a great job
Great activist
Chrissy
Repeatedly asked
He wants to
Start over
What is analysis
What's coming next and how to stop it
Chris Kyle
We got it on phone now so we got back up audio so this time they can't cut us out
They
You either comply
Are you doing
Comply
If you comply
This cold
Vaccine vaccine
Which each one for them at the checkpoint
People dead
More laws broken
More freedom
Taking this is the exact same thing as I give you comply you die if you don't then we have a Utopia
Just saying the exact same thing over again
I'd love that
They are they are cutting off my phone look outside of gas station man
Calm down
What you did we did you got get a phone call like 5 minutes before there was like we need you on it for words right now
You can't you can't just leave it everything is some evil
We'll plan again
Text you you could have been at home
Hardwire to the internet man what were you doing running errands
I got to get some
Some gas and I'm on Infowars
The same time might as well just head there now
So Alex is a very important question
Jennifer Chris and that is what would Jesus do right now
Oh I thought it was how much
Can you bench
He already asked them that interviews back
Quite a bit
And then we get our little bit of got to give it up to the Somali pirates, cuz
You knew it was coming
What would Jesus Christ what would Jesus Christ do
Right now
I can't say with Jesus Christ will do but I can tell you what I want to do and that's
Red Lobster
Compassion
Come from a place of love
How can they demonized you how can they pretend pretend what all you're doing is advocating for free
Choice
That's assault
If you
People in bath
Edit aggressively hugging them
Without permission
Punch me
Or leave
Do not try to hook back of a pretend were violent we are invading their personal space
Tell them you love them
Doesn't mean I still believe in the back
That's why they want you to be violent they wanted to look fine. They want us to look crazy
Violence is not the answer
How do we start literally they're preparing a false flag
You got me
Take on that
You just have to have the numbers we have what kind of violence can I use against 300,000 people to line up the army
Everybody down
You think the Army was going to do that the Army would turn their guns on the government before they turned
They're horrible people but there we go
The whole biggest military in the world can't stop
How can I make
Germany
In France
And Israel
And the UK and Canada the US and Australia New Zealand
Martial law
When it's a fake vaccine is poison
Stopped
L an arrest
That's all we got to do some close to me
If somebody is wearing a mask
Give him a hug and then
Take them with you to the Hague to watch fauci be hung
Also buried in there is the you got to give it up to the Taliban
To the Taliban hey come on
If you're if you defeat the United States military you got to give it up to
The Taliban
So is that nice moment of
Look I'm not defending the Taliban
But Hey listen
I hate the Taliban and I think we should stop him however I do agree with all of their governmental choices they're banning a boy
Similar to what I want
Yeah that moment of realization that struck some people
So Alex end of the Show screaming
And then there's a juxtaposition of the actor that plays right after the show
I want you to make down for this cuz
FedEx
It's shocking
Owen Shroyer with Sunday live coming up now
Would you like to breathe in Freedom wherever you go now you can with the amulet Shield based on space
A technology annuit shield and it's positive ions and Surround you with a forest fresh scent wherever you go
Oh boy
Psychic Alex
Like
He ran out of things to say about four seconds
To earlier that you just yelled out of fun
It's a lot of fun
And then you got the amulet Shield
I just like I just like him screaming and then the neck
Text words being like
Do you need to take a breath
Video commercial caught my attention
Barely Alexandra
Communications Network are taking add money
From a company that sells a portable air freshener
I'd like to look at
Into this a little bit alright
Their website claims that quote this Sleek wearable air purifier repels particles such as
Bacteria viruses molds
Spore allergens and other pathogens from your breathing space
For a personal 4ft
Queen Arizona
Is that
Works it seems like everyone should have one of those are inefficient from what I understand they don't work as
Well is Isaiah you expected
A lot of ionizers
Is it that they run the risk
Of creating ozone
Which is really dangerous
This website is all over the place
The address
4 at the website is Project pillow-talk
Gmail
The contact email is info at remember the law of Moses.com
Okay, remember the law of Moses
Has he got Usher
He got checked out that website the place that sells lawn signs and bumper stickers that have the Ten Commandments
Because apparently displaying them will save America I forgot the ten
The project pillow-talk
Is two sections on the website one is for this amulet Shield
Any other is a section where they sell pillowcases
They have the Ten Commandments on that score to super weird
Of the Lamb
Jordan
Again
I might have to ask you to make down for this because it's amazing
This is the audio that plays on the website whenever you go to
Do the pillowcase Auction Sales website
A project pillow
Let's get right down to business
This nation
America was founded on
The ten
The one-room schoolhouse is used to
The teacher
It was the
Curriculum in every
School and every house
Call the Bible
The law
He says if you love me keep Garden
Do my commands
You say you love me you're not keeping a garden
Doing Michael
Does not in urine
Now that
Let's go for
Proverbs 6:23 the
The Commandments the lamp or the law of God
Is the light
He commanded us all to be the light
Now
If it was the foundation of American every Schoolhouse and ever
Treehouse
Perhaps you'll have these
Face pillow cases
Under your heads
Immediately
Remember it's in the Bible twice with
Jacobs
Pillow
That's right
Jacob's pillow and the pillow that
Slept on
The middle of
Now do you think these
These plagues are going away it's at
It says in the Bible there's going to be plural
Play
So we'll talk about the amulet
As well
That's in the Bible twice
So you're supposed to
Teach your children when they rise up when I lay down
Do you know the command
That's the problem
Can you say the right now all
Ten
For sure
Well you don't have to have in order but you better have them
Written all the tables up your mind
And your heart
The only way to save America is to win this spiritual war you got a
You got to clobber those demons
You're not going to do it with a gun or freeze-dried food
Florida underground bunker
You cannot
Walkaway is a coward now
You have to be equipped
The equipment you need is step one
Project Pillow Talk pillow cases
Underneath your heads
It goes on from there it's even longer if I do like
Pillowcases the rude
Bible verses
Echo is in the audio to like it's it's
Do another take
I would have probably there seems to be a couple points where
Things Fall Apart
Maybe he was going if you want to save America you got to go up to the next
When you see and say it
Clobberin time
I'm at him with a pillow
Pillow fight pillows Direct
Play is this a pillowcase I didn't think there's any connection with my pillow at
Itself
Curious
I think that this is working on the assumption that
It's like there's some kind of an osmosis that happens you sleep on East words
Other work so I'm not entirely sure what's going on here
But
From what I could tell I
Think that this is all run by a Christian fanatic
Dentist from Louisiana
Why is it the dentist
To wind up
Getting either work for the CIA
Almost don't really care exactly who's behind this I just think it's a really good snapshot of the sort of folks
We were willing to pay Alex and gcn4 add time
Point this is what they're down to
You've got
Discount rate
The sale of at least four pillowcases to cover the cost of an ad spot that sell a magic aired
Necklace
Zealot pillows
Alright
First thing you got to do
A pillowcase
With the Ten Commandments on it
ASAP
ASAP otherwise this country's going
There was another pillow case that they sell that has
It says
Beer scriptures is the name of it
But I couldn't
Zoom in on it enough to see what the actual scriptures about what that means but I guess it's
Scriptures that make you scared
Scriptures
The f****** you're going to die
Yeah I would assume that something like that
Good people to be
Literally in bed with what I would are they
The Ten Commandments father and mother
Don't take the lord's name in vain commit adultery
Honor the Sabbath
Oh yeah
That's a good one
Wait why was honor the Sabbath
Part of
The founding of the United States
Did you ever wonder that if America was founded on the Ten Commandments
It seems like we could have chosen like 6 or so
Yeah
Anyway
Get a pillowcase
To honor thy father and mother
So we'll be back
On Monday and I'll see I think I was probably going
To do a bit more
You know he's going to get borin
Afghanistan stuff
Show the map
Interest
On this day
I'm waiting for him to say that America is installing the bath party a two-run Afghanistan
A matter of time
Oh yeah it's it's
It's a little bit strange
To me that's
You know you supposed to be a new show
And so much of this
Episode was
Just dumb kovacic when there is actual news
Is that you should be
Interested in discussing
Intimate Expo
Burston
According to himself
But until then
Go to bed Jordan
People doing God's work
But until then I'm Bo I'm Leo and easy Explorer come Darrell rundus
Robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work