Jordan
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Do you like to sit around cower in fear and fly over
A little bit about Alex Jones
Every year is just like allowed planes
It happens like this is annoying
And then
Your passes and it happens again
Yeah you know and I always look around and see people without
Houses and then I see the billion billion dollars flying overhead and I think thanks Chicago you bunches
I mean it's loud
Coronavirus
That's true that's true and it inspires the sense of jingoistic
Which I think is what we really appreciate right and I think sometimes I will be lol like Lookout
Over the lake I'd like to do that
I remember I saw would float like daughter years ago and I was like wow
About my day
What's going on
Dan I have a quick question
What's your bright spots
My brakes but today Jordan is I wrote a joke
What's a rotor joke joke
I mean I came up with a joke
And
I didn't look it up I don't know if someone's tweeted this
It could be derivatives but it made me laugh
Dictionary s*** again so I'll just have to live with it
I think a lot of people like to know like
How did this happen
How did
How to get inside the creative mind
This Dojo came to me when I was doing laundry
Okay
So that's sort of the sort of the right setting
It was a joke
Dryer sheets dryer than what
Criminal Just repeat that alright
I like it
I want the driest sheets
I have to admit that would be that reminds me so much
Like a fantastic Mike Wiley joke telling the joke and no one laughs and there's just me in the background
I'm just going like
This might be brilliant but I might be the greatest thing I've ever heard
Just losing my s*** the entire audience turns around and likes
Why are you doing this
Good
I'm sure that's a joke that someone has made before but I tickled myself quite a bit with that
My bright spot then is
I was walking over here
As I normally do
And assemble back upon that great Jessie Ware album
And I'm addicted to Spotlight while I walk
Down the street singing along very loud
Realized
It's time for me to get back into disc
Okay
For a while going to listen to a lot of discos
Italo disco.
When I was growing up I was part of that
You know Aiden
My town was
20 years behind so they have just figured out that rocking disco were fighting it like is a 9
Okay
It took me like 10 years
Till I watch
Documentary has like oh yeah it's entirely about race
Rockin disco the height the hatred that rock people had for disco with
Well
I think there was a lot of that I think I would that did underlie alot of it
I think
Some of the ACT
We're kind of corny too though
Square a little bit
The Bee Gees maybe lacked a little Edge
There was that the same time that was all of it would be
Do you like some of those Circle things that we're going on
I give you that disco get down with your bad self or
Get on down get on down with your bad self
Today we are going to talk about
A bit of time from last week
Alex's show
Are we talkin about
The 18th to the 20th
2021 B
That was too fast
I mean
I can't I can't not address the elephant in the room charged regarding
January 6th protests
People have given
A lot of
Hey
What do you guys think about this type messages
Am I I've surveyed some of the landscape of some of the commentary that's going around on social media time
Disappointed
No I think
What what I wanted to do was I wanted to start on Wednesday and go through Friday Wednesday through Friday
I think get us 20in troyer's
Charge this might be our first how not to cover Owen Shroyer episode
But I realize that I think there's too much anticipation
We're going to start with actually Owen Shroyer war room
Show from Friday
Alright back in time
Experience Alex Jones has passed through the end of last
Okay then in that case
I demand you do one thing at a certain point
Pause during the middle of one of those Owen Shroyer clips and then say
I bet you're all wondering how we got
Advent Advent
It has to happen like that how about I El kabong you
I'm in you wake up kabong
And then you wake up and we're talkin about Wednesday though
Little moments
Some folks who are walking I think that's a great idea
Sinjin
Desiree thank you so much right now.
Text Desiree Heart full of spiders
Rapture princess versus Obama Decepticon
Thank you very much and also big shout-out to Brian in honor of
Vaseline and the cult
Brian made a donation to The Seal Conservatory
Need
I love this
It's amazing to me that somehow once again we have done something that we can
Fall behind on with Jeff
Yeah yeah definitely
What if we just did what episode
45 minutes to The Testament to how
Generous and charitable and wonderful people who listen to the show are credible
It's a real
Humbling
Anything to be
Have
Animals that are backed up on
Other people have like
Oh Joe Rogan fans will gang up on you on the internet they're all I got and our fans will be like
Adopt an animal
Jordan
Yes
I know that
We've already
Ruined
The news
So don't try got charged
For the January 6th
Guess who's coming out
Theoretically has to have reported
Perturbed
We will learn more on this this episode that he hasn't held Monday morning
To show up at the Austin Police
If he does not demand
The trial by jury
Fiore combat
Absolutely
I'll fight anybody from Alex's show before we go
Owens business
Linden
The Clown
Jose
What is the code for today
It's not a nice way to Colors Jose clown face
What are you up to say send it
It's very uncommon for us to cover and Owen Shroyer
Episode
And part of the reason
The only reason we are is because he got charged
I wanted to see how the actual episode itself was
Because a universal clip that's going around
On the social media the like little clip of him saying that he's going to declare his innocence
As much as I could of course I would still give more information than necessary
We will listen to that clip but I wanted
To see what else was going on on the show
State of Mind
And here is where we get
Start Capital Has Fallen
Not quite.
I'm in Hawthorne Troy with you for the next 3 hours we have guests joining us today
Joe Biggs attorney
Joe Biggs a political prisoner being tortured in jail right now
Because of the big Live January 6th is attorney Dan Hall is going to be joining me coming up in the next segment
Who makes the announcer that there's a warrant out for his arrest and I think Biggs is a lawyer
Another guy who worked at Infowars who got arrested
Cuz it was a
Certainly did different things during
Actually was inside the capital of this with the proud boys
I would have you
Mina pizzagate hadn't happened you might still be working at Infowars and he wouldn't have had to
Join up with the proud boys
Absolutely correct pizzagate
I think so much all goes that
Pizzagate honest I was thinking like this guy might be your lawyer
It's not having burns on your show
Yeah
Burnt bronze medal made that choice for
Clip of Owen discussing how there's a warrant out for him
Alright so here's the deal
Ladies and gentlemen
Couple hours ago
I was informed by my attorney
Will be on the show shortly there is a warrant out
For my arrest
With allegations
Involving
January 6th
And I will have to turn myself in
Monday morning
There's a lot of questions
Some I had answers to some I don't
Yes I was there
Yes it's not going to be getting into more of this today on the air
And
I plan on
Clearing
Innocent of these charges
That's the deal
So I'm not going to I'm not going to comment any further on this I'm not going to take any questions on this today
But again I was informed by my lawyer
There's a warrant out for my arrest right now and then I have to turn myself in
Monday
That's just
That
Probably shouldn't even be on here right now but we're going to go ahead and do a broadcast anyway
Yeah I think he's been studying at the Alex
Pausing Academy not talkin for scratches
Talk about a big dramatic over to understand
Charge for his actions as it relates to January 6th
That's joining rainbow personalities caught up in this fall
That piece is that he almost certainly wouldn't be
Beginning charge
If you wasn't already under a deferred-prosecution agreement
At the time of his actions on the sick
This is something that is absent from almost every little bit of discussion that I
Seen about this
And it's so critical violated his parole
Back in December 2019 and got up and chatted a bunch of bulshit attempting to disrupt a session of the house Judiciary Committee
Stewart's cousin Trump
Impeachment
He made a plea deal where is prosecution will be deferred and ultimately dropped on the condition that he quote
Not break any laws and perform 32 hours of verified community service
Apparently never did that community service
According to his charging documents
From this this charge
This current one
On February 5th
2021 Owens lawyer provided documentation that
I completed 30 hours
Between January 19th
2021 in February 4th
Which means that on January 6th
Owen had not satisfied any of the conditions of his plea deal
And thought he was still under a deferred prosecution
Part of his plea deal included him agreeing to quote and not parade demonstrate or Pickett within any of the Capitol building
He also quote agrees not to utter loud threatening or abusive language or engage in any disorderly or disruptive,
Did any place upon the US Capitol grounds
Or within any of the Capitol Buildings with
Contempt impede disrupt or disturb the orderly conduct of any session of the Congress
Or either house thereof
Unfortunately he was doing those things on January 6th which means that he violated the terms of his plea deal which he
He had agreed to
These actions on their own might be the sort of thing that would result in a chart
It's because he wasn't involved in the actual storming of the capital as far as I can
Can tell because you was essentially on probation
What specifically to do with them not allowing being allowed to protest
Disrupt
Government process unreal
He had over a year during which he could have done his community service or we could have realize that he was barred
Protesting at the Capitol but
He's too stupid or the Allure of being part of the identity 6
It was just too enticing
Here we are
That's what's going on your honor I declare innocence
I do I do understand the charges now
I did not read the plea deal
Nor did I know that that was part of
So I am
I would like to stipulate that my lawyer is Robert Beltran
Not guilty
I don't think you even had
Barnes probably wouldn't even give him the details you just like sign here you're like
Do some community service
I've been pretty consistent why position the drum the available information that I have I don't know if what Alex was doing on that
Constitutes criminal Behavior
It really does seem like he was trying to exacerbate the situation and intensify people's feeling
Until things got out of hand and then he tried to get people to stop
I'm going into the capitol
His intentions and actions were
Destructive and spiritually bear some responsibility for the events that transpired
It's hard for me to breathe
Do the gap between bat and him having legal culpability
Oh and on the other hand
Did this to himself
I still think that this prosecution if it goes forward probably does more harm than good
Whatever punishment Owens facing is probably miniscule compared to the
The potential this has the fuel Infowars oppression and victimhood narrative
We'll see what happens but as far as I can tell
In this case the government of straight up trying to give Owen
The get-out-of-jail-free pass for the 2019 disruption case
I need didn't care enough to complete his end of the bargain which were
Was just him doing a little bit of community service 32 hours that's on him
Yeah that's his fault
Yeah he had a year
They are so incapable of doing something for not money
That he couldn't even do it to avoid jail time
Yeah like that's how it wouldn't it would result in jail time unless he violated these Pacifica
Her prosecution and he did
Yeah
Your honor in my defense
If we had one
You wouldn't be charging me I'm so even with this like violation of it
Still can't see him having
Any kind of
Punishment coming his way
That would get him to
Rollover on Alex
What is there for him to roll over on nothing as it relates specially as it relates to the 6th
I don't know
Iuic
I see a bit of this on on social media
I think I
Think that it's always kind of unwise
Really care too much about what random people are tweeting
Oh but I do see some
Barely larger accounts and people who some people listen to trying to use this
Alex might be getting charged
In the future I think that's probably a sign that someone selling you a bill of goods
Anime might be Griffin
I think that
Ignoring
I think that anybody ignoring the aspect of the story
Videos
The only reason Owen got charged
Is because of the Deferred prosecution
They're missing the entire Forest
For the trees
Because they're trying to say that Owen and Alex did the same things they were at the same place has frightened got charged that means Alex can get charged
104 a prosecutor
Alex didn't go and disrupt the house Judiciary Committee
And so
Owens too stupid and too young
That's what it is
And I guess Alex whenever he was pulling these stunts has always been smart enough to go right up to the edge of the line
Like right up
To the edge
So close to being prosecuted
Has Decades of practice yeah he's just really good at it
Who thinks seems like he's a Believer to which is why he would go a little bit further than
That Alec
I don't know if I would chalk it up to being a Believer I think it would be it's more he has something to prove that I like
Text doesn't
He doesn't have a name outside of Infowars
Like if there was a headline Owen Shroyer charged
No one cared Infowars reporter Owen Shroyer charged now people are like
The guy works for Alex Jones
Have an actual identity outside of that that means anything
He does have to go a little bit further
You know try and disrupt the proceedings
Yeah and he has to he has to impress his daddy Alex and Alex doesn't have to do that because you just hired his dad
So it's a little bit of a
You know he's got to be like hey did I do a good job Alex to
So I don't
Don't think this is necessarily going to be the biggest thing in the world
Interesting to see how it plays out
Phone may be gone for a little while
How to do 38 hours of community service have to see the info
Chart get adjusted a little bit
Talk to Robert might be getting called up from the bullpen
Brutal
I wish I was still curious like how's Owen State of Mind
Here's where he's at
Let me just tell you this
And back I'll go to these clips now
Boats
Devil
Worshipping cults
Run the planet
Okay
Time to just get real about this
Got to get real about
People run all the water Satanist
People that run our government or satanists
Lot of mainstream media people are satanists sure
So that's why you look around at all this and none of it makes sense and there's all the inversion and there's all the lying
And there's all the backstabbing
And there's all the degeneracy
And you disable the none of this makes sense
No it did they all make sense once you realize that Satan is running
I get it now mr. running thing so he violated
Did the terms of his deferred prosecution and was caught
And you did it on camera to which was
Oh yeah and there was like a promotional materials that advertises he was going to be doing it
Is very exciting
What media
The cops
Just been waiting there at the 6th and then like hey
You're here
Goodbye we're going to take you in Augusta
Yeah I know I don't I don't know if that would
Deescalate
Situations
It's probably good they didn't
And also I probably better and this is probably the reason it's happening now in August
Probably cuz it easy
Very low priority before they finally got
Nobody saw it was like
Goddamn
I thought maybe somebody who was like on the case of his like
Deferred prosecution whenever we like looking at pictures
Scooby-Doo
It's probably like a series of coincidences that lead to this
Probably
A long line and also
All Owens fault
This is one
Hundred percent his fault
The world is run by devils
No it's like he had a restraining order against a f****** Meijer and then he went into the Myers and was like
And then
So
Get some bad news
About his
During the Middle the show
We're back here on the Infowars war room we had Joe Biggs lawyer joining us he can no longer join us
So we will no longer be conducting that interview
Alright
I wonder why
I'm sorry he said what
Okay no
My lawyer is going to be a bad idea to talk to do a big as a lawyer on air right now
Joe Biggs and lawyers lawyer has advised him it's a bad idea to talk to you right now
Set a little bit of a sticky situation let's just avoid that
Play the little bit more about Satan Sheila and Satan worshipers and what have you
And there's two things to keep an eye on whenever
People like Owen
What are they use the terms like degeneracy what they're doing is they're trying to attack
Lgbtq plus Folk
Without using specific
Plausible deniability to the
Having sex outside of marriage and it's like no your base
Basically saying that sodomy is wrong
Better if you're trying to say
There's a heavy overlap of that and they're trying to save those things
Without
Without saying
The piece of that and then the other piece is that this is where I
Realize that Owen Shroyer believes in Illuminati bloodline
That's why all of this stuff is robbing you of your Humanity
The mask
The force vaccine
The degeneracy
The p***
The drug abuse
All of it
All
Satanism
Satanic cults
Of the World Elite
Illuminati
Controlling the planet
Ringing in
There
Oneworld satanic government system
That's really it
That's it
This is underwhelming
I would I would even say that
I mean
If the X
Explanation for why Owen is getting charged
Is Satanist
Run every
Alright
How does this further Satan's plan
I mean
Owen is the right-hand man of the only person who can take them Satan
I mean if I was saying I would look it up and be like
Beneath me
I wish
I was listening to this and like
Everytime Owen has these pauses they don't feel the same as Alex's posit now Alex's bosses are either
They're like very seriously dramatic
Intention
Pause Act
Cuz you can't
This it almost feels like it any minute on my be like
Guys I'm full of s***
Nightfall at any moment it just like I can't do this anymore
I'm going to prison
Does war room Have a Gimmick
You know like dude is there is there a gimmick that separates
Alex's show from war room just like every episode of the War Room
Aerial combat
See now that sounds great
I would watch that one Infowars employee sacrifice at the end of every episode of the war
It's like it's like Doug Loves Movies chatting and then they fight to the death the winter comes back for the next
Three straight
When
There is no gimmick to the war of it's basically the same thing
As Alex's show but hosted by Owen
And maybe
Skews slightly younger in terms of some of the reactionary guess
They have a terrible
So
Open talks to
This woman from Australia about how bad covid lockdowns are there and it's I don't care
It's a long interview
It's very boring
But
It does lead to some calls
Afterwards
Amanda
They seem to have a very interesting perfect
Fat lady that you just have mystralia I think I would rather be under Taliban rule
And those Australians right now no I mean like it it's not a joke I mean I don't say this ironically like
Hey hey
Taliban it's obviously not good I wouldn't want to live under the Taliban but they're not making them wearmaster not making them taking
Taiwan
And we got our own globalist Taliban we're dealing with here
Isn't one of their big complaints about Islam the idea of like people having to wear a hijab
Isn't that like
Do they call like
Covid masks
Facebook burkas
What are you talkin about that one is
Pretty egregious
Listen they're not making people wear masks they're making them wear full-body
Suits dum-dum even
Even Within
Iiii
Don't have
The same relationship
With
Islam that
Let's say Infowars does
Reality
This doesn't make sense
So and Owen believe that the January 6th
Was the globalist reichstag
Coronavirus Georgia
But you can't really talk about it
Because the cat is it good
PCAT
Going to get arrested
Whatever
Whatever term
We put
The group of criminals that are running this country when it's all said and done and the history books
Just like the Nazis reichstag event
January 6th will be known as
Whatever it is Democrats globalist
That will be there false flag reichstag
And it's sad that I have to sit here
A firm believer in free speech
Affirm practitioner of free speech
Nn
I'm afraid
To speak my mind today
Okay
Cuz we no longer live in a freak on
What a mope
What a f***
You know what
Here's the thing
All right and this is like one there's the propaganda of course of being like if we take responsibility for the 6th
We're f******
You know so we have to say that it's a false flag
But
Just saying that
Makes you realize that
Everyone Towing
Is f****** stupid
And so is
Really really dumb
Like you have to know that you are
So stupid
If you're really going to say
That you went to the 6
And saw all of your friends there
Burned black lives matter flag the night
F****** before screaming in the streets
False flag
Yourself
Insane
Yeah insane
Also
I tried to put myself in Owensboro session understand that there's a lot of steps that would have to lead up to me being in that position
But I imagine if I Quantum Leap into his body and let's say
And I was I got news of this charge
I would feel so disgusting
If I didn't
Present it honestly
Two people that like look
I had a deferred-prosecution I wasn't supposed to be in the capital.
This is a bureaucratic thing
My actions on the six
Actually have nothing to do
What what I did or didn't do as nothing to do with this charge itself right I just was
I agreed
To not do the thing that I hate
Told him I probably could have
Been there on the 6th and gotten away with it
Maybe no charges but
I'm too much of a selfish prick to have done my community service a gout in a timely manner
Hey until I was still under this agreement
And look it look it
I understand why you would want to take this as some kind of a thing where there's
Devil's around or whatever this is on me this one's my fault
We could talk about how
It is it right for me to have gotten arrested for disrupting the house Judiciary Committee or we can talk about that
This time I agreed to the terms of this thing right violated better
That is my
Every man if you care about
Contract log Intergalactic lie so much
I think you have to care about contract law here is well and if you have a green to the stipulations
And break them
You don't get a say
What's your belief system
Atmosphere
So I wouldn't take another call and his guy
He wants to bring back an old Villa
We all know is falling
Strings now laughter
Coolers mating with Trudeau
Maybe the evil one Hillary Clinton
What if you just meet with your now
I didn't see that
I was too busy even walking
Hillary Clinton might guy
But yeah it's
We know what I mean look at this brain-dead
Don't be that we have in there
You think he knows what the hell is going on at
I mean he can't even stand up
He's literally
You can't even run a controlled
Press conference but he just he literally reads off the script
Says the name of the reporter that question their supposed to ask when they go off-script he's like hey what are you doing that's not the question I have
People
Uvalde Forum how can
Can you see this crap you know like
How do you make you feel I want to know
I'll let Democrat or a liberal field right now
I convinced that
They are just fully demonically possessed at this point and anything that causes you pain they enjoy
They don't even care if it causes pain to themselves
They didn't is long as it's causing you pain they like
This is this is the conversion of the doing anything to own the libs
Yeah those are trying to reverse that around
Remember how student loans and any number of different things were involved
Getting biting elected here we are so no
We are not happy
Yeah about s***
Yeah
I I don't know I
It's it's so weird to me to have like
Hey look in the mirror Dems
You love Trump
He talked about having a big
Dick on
You know what are you talkin about a if you are mad that he can't run a press conference
You can't do 32 hours of community service
That's another issue
Should be able to
So yeah this is this is the sort of vibe that we're getting
From Owen show
And not good
Museums
By boring
Melodramatic
Yes I am OPI and a giant piece of s***
My big point that I wanted to make on all that he's this
Deferred prosecution aspect of it
If this is something that is
Blade out in the charging document for this current charge
Scorpion so I think
Video Wellness of this dynamic
Is something that
Is
Essential if you have red
The underlying information
Answer when people come to you and they present this otherwise
Probably a good indication that they haven't actually read
What this is about
And what's funny about it
Is not that somebody from Infowars was charged
For their part in January
What's funny about it
Is that it's entirely because he's a lazy piece of s***
Owen Shroyer
Could have done all this stuff
And none of this would happen
Entirely his fault
And it's hilarious
So are we go back to the 18th kabong
Here's Alex getting into
Same kind of stuff that I wouldn't believe and I was like hey look I don't like Italian
But compared to the satanic New World Order
Compared to the globalist compared to what they wanted or children
Well the Taliban pale in significance
Doing what they do From a Stone Age caveman like
Perspective
Oh boy
Wow what a f****** wild thing to say
Of all the things
Yeah
I feel like he's being racist I'm offended on behalf of the Taliban
What's happening
Yeah
Wow
Yeah it's it it's
Bizarre Bazaar line he's trying to walk
Deep-seated respect
Exit all of these guys have for anyone who really tries
At the Dominate women completely
You know they're like
You're going for it man we were trying to do it here but they're just too strong
They're just too strong you guys are f****** doing it
Another thing that seems to be going on in the present-day is Alex's talking quite a bit about
King Arthur
Actually saw the Green Knight a couple nights ago it must be it must be
Because of that
I have not seen that I guess I saw a trailer for it but I'd forgotten about it but I was always a fan of going
Man it's great it's really good it's a great movie one of them nights that I always enjoy maybe it's just cuz of the name was fun I don't
Remember anything about him
He was like
You know what he was kind of an Owen Shroyer typing trying to impress his dad a lot so he
10 / 10
I've been trying to make up for his mistakes
He loses
Gala gala
Who else you got
Maryland's in there who else do we have
Starting out old and then aging young Merlin or you talk about the Merlin that ages
Done with the magician
The magician
Anyway Alex very much believe the King Arthur's real
In Australia and New Zealand in the United Kingdom and Europe
The US
Is if we forgotten
The Anglo-Saxon ethos
Of the Knights of the Round Table
Son of Uther Pendragon
Wait one round table
Of the Lord
And the Magna Carta
I'll save this as many times as needed to be said King Arthur's a real person not a real person
Son of Uther Pendragon has no evidence that Luther Pendragon
Know if he's the son of someone he must have existed obvious
Obviously
Like how
You realize that Luke
Is the son of Anakin
Do you understand Telugu as a real person
Poor boy guy that worried BPR leave abandoned even then
Nobody ever really did the Roundtable
No
This is generally very very top
How they organize governments during the feudal
So
This is one of the harshest add pivots
I've heard in a long time
So I'm warning you ahead of time
Five presidents have been murdered
By the way
Africa
Because they said we're not taking this experimental shot
You saw what happened to them show
This is a big big big
Yesterday for x29
Every percent off because we're about to run out of it
Fuk was that
Nuts
Wow so Alex is just kind of repeating a little blurb from a meme he saw but I couldn't even name the countries in
Africa that he's talking about
What are the recent deaths of an African country's leader is the prime minister of Cote d'Ivoire
Hardibacker Yoko
He died of cancer and was an enthusiastic
Supporter of the vaccination
Campaigns are being held by the World Health Organization
Murdered by satanists Ambrose dollar meaning
I was the Prime Minister of St
S14
He died after testing positive
Difficult
There's no evidence that he was that his death was suspicious and anyways
Assassinated
Pierna Grande
The president of Burundi died after heart attack
Okay
Then there was John magufuli who is the president of Tanzania
He was pretty out there in terms
Covid stuff and he was the guy that he
He claimed he got a sample of a papaya tested and it came back positive
He died of heart failure but there's no evidence of Foul Play at all
And there's actually been heavy speculation that he might have had covid which was a confounding factor in his heart
Condition door
The reason that Alex can make these kind of outrageous pivots from talking about heads of state being tortured to death
And then discussing his pills are on sale is cuz he knows that nothing you saying means anything
These leaders work
Gildan Alex knows it
Tell me just the window dressing that he needs to scare his audience into buying a pills
Yeah can you imagine how you would actually respond if you believe that leaders of State
We're being tortured to death
Because they refuse to accept vaccination campaigns
That were bio weapon attacks against
The population
Like you wouldn't be like oh yeah and also Hey look
Reason style t-shirts
It's a comedy to believe that that's
How humid should behave
Nonsense
My God
That is so funny he can act with such abandon
And like
Not really care about the pack
Text Nikki saying that these people were tortured to death because he doesn't actually believe that they would you don't have to have empathy for murdered heads
The state if they were not murdered and you don't know who they are and take them out of the equation
That you would know about the world that were in right now
No One Is Safe
Might be murdered in a moment
It does not matter
Yeah it just
It's nonsense
Anyway
Mike Lindell some Posey
Is Cyprus a ghost
Didn't go Grace
Inca Gods
There was a problem
Who have the trumps president again he can pardon Owen
Oh yeah
There were some problems with the symposium
One of them was that
His information was bad
Yabby and slid into his DM
That was Montgomery gave him some dirty dossier
And the
Alex is going to try to pretend that this whole Symposium was great
It was full of evidence that
But everything was cool and that Trump
But
There was the poison pill put in
And that was the
Little tiny bit of the big lie the big lie is that
No problem is
So much
Of
Mike lindell's
Argument rest
To all these fake packet captures
That were what Dennis Montgomery gave him
It's not that there's a
Tiny little thing that people are focusing on its that the underlying
Keystone
Right of his argument
Is from Dennis Montgomery and it's b*******
But
You still spot
Answering Alex
So Alex has
Kind of you know
I still like Mike
Mike still good still sponsoring Alex we would see Alex doing the exact same Owen Shroyer thing like this was
The false flag attack
Against the rest of us like yeah might just not talk about it
Loveland OH
He's doing
Will get his take on that where he's going
Don't forget
I would be in the red right now weather for my Glendale
What he's doing
A whole lot of
Pillows ground-breaking pillow groundbreaking pillow supposed to be heavy pillows
I like I just
It's it's
So boring
It's so boring how like
The reason the coverage is happening is because of the
It's not it's not that you would be covering
Michael lindell's Sowell
And like as a hero
So happens
I don't believe it
He talked much about Mike Lindell before you became espanyol
Interesting
So I find this next clip to be a little bit
Confusing and
Homophobic
Great perhaps
Cool
But more than that confusing I'm going to need you to help me on the other side to assess this
They're doing it as a poison to sabotage the culture
Thomas China bans all the George Soros
Men and women together
Homosexuals in prison
In China
My point is is that they say that's not allowed here we're strong
They want to be
Because I know that's a strong system
What
And Destroyer
Because multinational Banks own our government
They want to consolidate the government and take
So
Is he
Imprisoning
Gay people
Seem to be saying that it creates a strong Society
Well I mean
He's specifically saying that trans people are
Poison
Yes so ugly transphobic
So I'm saying that despite him saying I'm not suggesting
Prison I'm just saying that they're trying to be like 1950s America when we were the best country that ever been
Now I'm just saying
It's not good it's a good thing
Yeah we're getting real close to Alex siding with a Chinese about human rights abuses
But not economic
Skip
Taliban have good social policies
It's
Become a parrot
Yeah it is it is very very at mean it's it's just so much like
Look into the abyss the abyss looks back all the people who were like
We need to go to Warren Carroll all the Islamic
Hey you got to give it up to
The Taliban they know how to run an evil organization
Can I'm just saying
That their policy choices are fantastic I think there are some people on the right who you could categorize that way
But just for the sake of
Total
Clarity
Alex was not a super harsh warmonger
He's weirder than that
Yeah
So I'll take some calls waiting for Michael and Dale to show up cuz Mike
Who's going to be on
Anymore
And this caller has an interesting theory about what's going to happen with B
The Alex
Does his
That's his
Trademark
You bet
I called in I think it was Harrison just yes
Yesterday
Honestly
False
Flagstaff
Everything going on especially Afghanistan now
Vacation I mean
What's
Stopping them from one Daisy
News headlines
Biden was poisoned we hadn't even seen him in over a week
Crazy crazy
There's no there's no protections we have two presidents
Brother's Keeper
Again Alex can just say that he agrees with this collar is ridiculous
Stop. Because nothing means any
I agree with Ida probably what's going to happen if a false flag assassination
That we predicted for every president since we started
Problem
And here's another thing
That doesn't mean anything
And again even drugs report
Headlines
Butchers in September vaccines declining Effectiveness against infection
Is it ever going to get
I can't believe that Alex expects
The colors to go along with this kind of a roller-coaster s***
Flicka last we heard from Alex about drug use
Telling us for the website had been sold off to the globalist
Speakers
Bruno
Going along with the election fraud stuff
Now I guess there's a headline metallic likes on The Drudge Report so maybe he's back in charge running the website how would that even work
He broke into the offices
I got to get this one had lineup
Nothing Alex says means anything
Judges of villain and a sellout on the days that he saying things Alex doesn't like and he's a hero when he says things that Alex
Sounds like
Bill Maher is the mouthpiece of the globalist until he says something Alex likes and then Alex has a secret
April long
Bill Barr is a crusading hero when he's helping
Entropic struck investigations and eating and Shady pardons
And he's a turncoat villain when he won't unilaterally overthrow the election results now
Trumpet power
If you pay attention to how Alex interacts with people in their positions
Print starts to emerge is worth noting
Alex has to live in a world of absolute
Daughter black and white
It's tempting to say that
The part is part of the view Because he believes that he's fighting
A literal devil on behalf of God
Trying to find a middle ground doesn't work there
But that's not what I
I think is going on
I think Alex is just almost
Embarrassingly lazy and he doesn't give a s***
It's much harder to deal with people as three-dimensional beings that are able to make decisions and hold complicated sometimes apparently contradict
Reposition
On different issues that it is
Just to make people heroes or villains depending on what they did or said that day
On another level if you make people into sellouts and villains when they fail your bizarre purity test
Kind of just the way that you don't have to end up looking in the mirror and judging your own beliefs
Decide not to support the election conspiracies because he knows their b******* and he doesn't need Mike lindell's money
He did it because he sold out to the global
At least he did
Intelli pool something that's already sold out of the globe was never opposed
Then he must have wrestled back some kind of control
Sure it's just
That's nonsense
It doesn't it that none of this means anything weird
Weird lazy narrative
Fiction
Yeah it is a little bit like
The
Like
Embodiment of Twitter
You know like that like that idea of there's a main character on Twitter everyday and you can
Matter it just doesn't matter and then the next day we everybody moves on
You know it's it's just that kind of like
Today's
Topix
Today's heroes and villains like it's
He doesn't do a serialized show
Yeah yeah there's there's
Discontinuity all over the place
What you can't do
It's jarring
Any expects the audience
To sort of live in
That
Space as there
Conception of reality
I mean that's awful good
So I think that Alex Jones
This is a liar and it is a fraud
But I also think that he has some pretty dangerous perspectives
Visa V religion
And
I think that his view of
His
Is there a Christian identity conception is a mess
And
I'm against it while he was famous you know he did quotes
Jesus in Mark 21
54 when Jesus said do what thou wilt
If you recall that was a big one
Haha
So
When
People talk about
Brogan
One of the things you would like the idea of platforming
Platforming hours
I think that there's one part of it that is like
You're giving an uncritical interview to somebody who is disseminating bad information
You're not capable of pushing back on him in the way that would
Expose that this is bulshit
And by doing that you are accidentally supporting or intentionally supporting
Everything
But he is lying about right
Now there's a secondary
Danger
And part of it to the platforming
That that
Maybe is a little bit
Less obvious
And that is that you just have people who get it doctrinated and exposed to Alex through it and this collar is one of the
I just wanted to
Say thank you
First time I heard you was on the
Joe Rogan podcast
Inherently
As a
Is waiting for someone
Tap into that
That God has for us
And you definitely did that for me
So I thank you for that
Hey Brogan's essentially helping out with Colt
Recruitment
End
You know I mean like another part of
Unhappy with
Is that
You have to know that Alex is coming in to exploit
Before you even wrote them on your cereal
If your Rogan you have to know that he's coming in
With an agenda that has nothing to do with you and is
Pretty much insulting directly to your face
You know like it's
Ostensible your friend
Like I can't believe that you don't have the self-respect
Necessary to be like
Hey f*** you
And if you were to present information
That was counter to the nonsense
But Alex was trying to pass off on your show
You didn't stoolie not be his friend anymore
Yep yep
Alex might be out for blood again that you wouldn't stand up for yourself
That's what would have happened
100 million dollar contractor
Right now
So Mike Lindell shows up and his
Looking symposium
Everything Is Awesome
That one little tiny thing
Anything
About to guess we've got with us for the next few segments
My pillow
Dot-com
Big American dolls American employees
Products here in America and sponsoring
Integrity in elections
Nationalism and patriotism
Conference last week for 3 days
Parking for Tuesday Wednesday Thursday
In Sioux Falls South Dakota
I watched it at all these scientists and engineers
Logarithm showing the proof showing
You're all this and then the media focused on one issue
With one file he was given
How they do it
Is underlying
Information
Problem
The foundation for your house right right
What's on a
Lake yeah but overall the route
They're underwater really well construct
Short know and I can see that if I go underwater
Plumbing
Installed very well
In so much water
Salvation
Problem
Writes this is an interesting line Alex is trying to walk
Unfortunately
Mike Lindell does not want to play ball with this
And I'd like to get into all the big discoveries that were made in proven
That got overshadowed by the media distracting onto a few things at 100%
Paisley manifest
But I don't know what you're talkin about as far as
They focused on a bad file
They out there was no filed focused on is it icing but
What's going on here
Is the Alex is trying to save what he can from the wreckage of this conference understand that it's time to
Abandon ship
Community recognizes that it's time to pretend that the conference was actually total proved election fraud
Damaging to the globalist that they had to focus on how the fake packet captures that Mike said the election was strolling came from
Notorious fraud guy Dennis Montgomery
Mike doesn't get the game and he seems to be refusing to accept that he was defrosted by Montgomery
So this is this is a dicey start to this interview cuz they were there
Working at cross-purposes Alex's trying to help him
By attacking
This one like
This whole
It might doesn't realize that
Boats going down you want to you want to get out of here we can just get on the bed
It's just the two of us
So we can get on the lifeboats there's no women and children there's nothing
We can just get on the Lifeboat
MP5 will get you another boat ashore trip over to that other boat right there
All of your supplies are on that other boat with moved
You don't have no reason to stay on this bus
The boat is very well-constructed
Not giving up
Triad my own team
For five months
Spend millions of dollars
White hat hackers
From all different all different.
Walk the light I mean that they're not they didn't have diverse white hat hacker. My information and got all these terabytes from Porter
By the way including
Dennis Montgomery
Validated
Everybody data is data
Episode of podcast for YouTube
Alex
Mike just talked it out there
Yeah but he he's he's still holding onto like it it's valid it's good
Information
Unreal oldies
Scooby's hackers
Is that he has work
Confirm I wonder if one of them is a Nigerian prince
Anybody spending millions of dollars on
Getting another phone call
The whole premise of Mike cyber Symposium was that he was going to bring these like Tech
Pinnacle Minds together and they were going to see this evidence and it was going to be irrefutable
Gyros Supreme Court
Mind-blowing
Now that didn't
Sure Mike's got a different angle on it and that I didn't show you all the information
I got to keep something back in case they try and kill him
Billions of dollars
And this is taking months for all these people to verify
Write my how could they possibly even dis rarefy it in the
Three days in Bossier
Impossible
That's so funny yeah
When you see somebody who is really that delusional
You're at your mind boggles you know you're like
Can you survive this long like this are you a millionaire you're absolutely nuts
Are you controlled by a robot everybody
I have
All the Cyber data from the 2020 election
In my possession
Okay
I'm not going to go get
Ogo validate this it took me
I don't know if 66
A people
Didn't know each other
Validating data
Invalidated it took them for 3 to 4 months
Can I search for these guys there's no sense I already know it's real
Over here for the Supreme Court when we need to get when we going to get there
You're not going to get that
That's kind of is a betrayal of the entire premise of his big event
Yeah
It was supposed to be like I'm going to show all this evidence is going to be irrefutable
I'm not going to show you the evidence cuz I already know that it's real and there's no way
The you would be able to even verify it in the amount of time that we have cuz 6
The eight people took four months
It does seem like what he said was
Okay
I said I was going to show you the Smoking Gun right I did
Now unfortunately wasn't the gun that fired
So I've kept that one
This was like a model of the smoke
Nose like a is like a
Reproduction of Lifetime special
Sir that's a smallmouth bass okay now I understand but have you seen it
Sing
Hello my baby hello my honey
Got a Looney Tunes frog on the Supreme Court Justices death
Doing a little soft-shoe
Advocates
So in this next clip
Mike Lindell talks about how he's on a
Crusade
To keep the media honest
Sure and part of that apparently involves doxing reporters
I put out a report and you don't have calling out all bad media I'm calling out bad
Bti even games
This guy that put out the report with associate press
I gave his phone number on Alex
Because I'm not going to take these guys doing this bad journalists anymore
But one of the things that happen is
Trunews I went out there and went out her True News.
Find out there a great ministry
I called up Rick Wiles
And sure it we both find out we prayed together this morning, both setup
Oh my God
They just really don't read the Bible
I just don't
Just don't
Rick Wiles introduced the guy who famously said that the
The impeachment of trump with a coup
I think that might just confess to a
Yeah he did say he just released a journalist phone number
Retaliation
I mean according to his own internal sense of morality I think he was lying so I can release
His phone number to the world
And that's fine
I don't I don't subscribe to that morality
According to him
There is nothing he can even say to me that it's a bad argument
So Mike has a little bit of a plea that he needs to make as Alex's going out to
Guilty
If you go to Crime. Frank's beach.com everybody
Crime. Brightspace.com and you're out there and you've been you've been threatened
Are you at the evidence back in November December of with updates machines or whatever of this cybertech
Go there fill out the form we will get told you my direct team
I will get your tree I will cover you
I will cover you I will just like I got Tina is fighting hard
No
He's not file a lawsuit that makes him
We should all my look back. I don't think that anybody should but I don't think it's a
Impossible that that is not going to
To be like in favor of you
Like people just
Putting fake email addresses in
It's just a
Moth to Flame.
Speech.com I believe
I think that this doesn't sound like the actions of somebody who has
90 absolute evidence of election fraud already I don't know why you need to add
Why would you gild the Lily by trying to solicit whistleblower
I mean I think that's what you would do with all your evidence was s***
And you needed to start from the ground up again
It kind of is the smell that I'm getting for
Not many prosecution's have like
So we presented our case
To the judge and the judge is declarative guilt
Now
We need to get a lot of ideas about how to get him to declare this guy guilty
That doesn't work we got the guilty charge
We got this
Now let's come at this from another angle about super guilty
Have you thought about super duper guilty
Go to the 19th
Yes
This day was Friday
Haha Thursday
Is disappointing Alex Ross
Oh no cigarettes
They must be misspeaking no
I was actually read the UK government studies
That
Doctor's name was on
Lab coat in lab
Operation
Abby
You've all seen it
You all heard it
Literature
You don't just think when
I was sent that
That's what I thought about it
People are asking
What is this what do you think so I said well let me go look
In the world in the UK
Undisputed
Don't put that. Back on screen weekend
And
Pizzas
6 times what it was almost
Blood cell.
That's nice that's the doctor
Exposing white blood cell count slower
Broadcast
Santa Cruz fault I reach the level of being upset now
Too much information
This is a mess that's bad
That's embarrassing
Dr. Bauer is the right doctor
This guy from The Francis Crick
Institute
Has no idea what
Narratives are which
He seems
Swae Lee
A little bit I'm just going to rebroadcast he does
Actually doesn't go to broadcast
You take a little break
E4me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
I'm going to start the show over at that point
And David have all the information for you it's going to be beautiful
Beautiful man
This is like
13 minutes into the show to like it never started over after a quarter of an hour
I love how many people call in and I like Alex you're the leader we need you're a leader you're the one who's doing
Like the idea of going over the hill with him Alex be like
No you got didn't charge the right way
F*** it I don't even want to do this war anymore I'm taking a little break e
Alright
Another started shelling US1
Sounds like a like
A baby that's still drunk from the Night by
Before with a lampshade on his head got to take a little break
Got to take a little break
I got to get some fluids
Overly
Sigillo Breaky break
Yeah that's what the rest of the episode does end up getting a little bit morose little bit of a bummer
It's overwhelming it's mind-blowing that they actually did this
Exploding they have hit us so hard
By this winter
You probably need to stay home
Annabelle Stacy we told you when everyone's reminded on
Five-year-olds
Sexual pedophiles
They just created by 11
You'll take the vaccine you become the bioweapon factory
People are fighting about here's Matt Baker of San Diego
So Alex is really into this guy Matt Baker at in San Diego
Cancel Coronavirus
Alex is really into this dude
No possible way
Alex YouTube Eli
Well we f***** up with this auntie mask thing
I was a bad move on our part
We just blew it
We were you know we got it right
At the beginning
And then we tried to own the lip
Into our own.
So that was a bad move
Could I could have made some different decisions it's some other points but now
The globalist have killed us all
Now let's watch a guy yell at a city council meeting much like everyone to know that we take no responsibility
Ability for our own actions whatsoever
Nope nothing we have ever done is that not this next clip is a really great
Encapsulation of Alex Jones's journalistic Style
He's going to play a video of someone
Crying and saying that their child had died
After getting the facts
Sure
However
12 year old 50 year old 18 year old
Taking visor shot
I can't verify this video that I'm about to play for you that is incredibly emotionally charged
I can't verify that this is real
I don't know
It seems to be saying the things that I want to say
So it's feels real to me
Here's the hairdo that here's the clip
Of the president of the United States
Pushing a terrorist
Out of his
Here we go
And it's Harrison Ford
It feels real
Feels real I've seen a lot of real clips of President it seems like
How a president would respond to a terrorist being an airplane what else you going to say like get on my plane
Absolutely.
Yikes
I think you just need to do better than that
I I don't I don't think that when you have a large platform like this
That
Stopping to the fact that you have no idea that you're playing is real
I think you shouldn't play it then
I can't tell you how many times I've heard of a journalist
Who is spent
Weeks
Days just non non-stop time trying to
Run-down asaurus
Trying to run down and verify a fact because it's so good
It's so good that it needs to be in there and people need to know
And in order to run it you have to be able to confirm its veracity
And then they couldn't
Run it
If you can't confirm it you can just not
You're not you're not you should
Fuchsia
But Alex doesn't
Care all about
Just
Whatever
Who gives a s***
All these African presidents were tortured that I have bills on sale
So
Alex has been expecting a false flag
As We Know
And so there was that guy with the car
They said he had a bomb
Right.
Expect
They've been staying online that by the
15 to the 20th
Trump would be reinstated
A dyad
Screenplays
A man in a big black truck pulls up
On the edge of the Capitol sidewalk
And then just starts yelling and screaming and expecting that he's there for the insurrection
Just like we got a million people out there on January 6th
Eclipse
Ellipse
And then I'm just outside with Mark the capital peacefully
A few
600 go in
We're all terrorists were all criminals ever that
All the other people believe
And so now there is a man in a standoff
On the capitol grounds
Watch the video mocking are at all
Supposed to fold cam
Turn off on doing I hope you have a good shot
Add
Tampa Police that he basically threatening them and now he's saying he's not
We're just going to watch this as it unfolds are so the headline
Capitol lockdown policing ocean with man in pickup truck claim to have explosive
Device
I'm just here for the overthrow I mean
We got sucked in by the cute art stuff
Communicating with police
Using a whiteboard
Hear what he has to say
This is the derangement of the key brainwashing
How can people think it's a joke
They cleared the block
I'm calling nine-one-one three times
Who's my wife
I'm not entirely positive one
Journalistic value there is to Alex playing long stretches of this guy's
Video
I think that there was a hope that I like it's like
Maybe playing it with some of differentiate this guy from
What Alex believes
No
Sounds very much
Yeah and I don't know what I don't this is not a good false flag for Alex
I don't think obviously it didn't
End up in explosion
Which is good
Sure
Absolutely better than the alternative
I don't think that it has the
Needs for
The false flag that said he wanted to profit off
There's no real spectacles of Isuzu
Is it going to guy got arrested
Hudson bomb threat
It's kind of Alex's Hearts not even really in it that much
This isn't that kind of assault
He needs to take a nap
It's take a longer break
And so we're going to take a break he can go to the 20th
Cuz
Alright alright
Intolerant
So the 20th is Friday and this is the day that we talked about Owen Shroyer show already where he's announcing that he
Use
I didn't do my community service
Is all my fault personally I made all of these choices and then I am now paying for
You know if somebody
Near me
Could explain cause and effect well enough perhaps I would have realized that my car
Effects when should have been listening to Alex's show along
Causality is his main focus
Owen could learn a little bit about object permanence
Stupid
Like whenever this
This deferred-prosecution agreement isn't in front of you it's still exist
Still there
So anyway Alex is in a bad mood
On the 20th
America
And the birth of the new second Dark Age under the cyclotron
Technocracy
Is all the leftist and all the scum are going to be judged only the first
The Dalai Lama
Cool
But everybody that didn't like America then like Freedom it didn't like Jesus
Self-defense you're about to get
Front row seats to your own destruction
This is the very Twilight
Final minutes
The final
Second
The death of the Republic
Hollywood and its accounting minions are going to take their time without
Slowly bring the country down and splicing into little chunks
We're going to go into bondage just like
Like those little babies
Never got to talk about their mothers breasts never got to learn their first word
They just got their brain
The operating table at nine months old and they were lucky
What popular not taking delivered alive till University facility where
Battle shafted unbelievable things to them
They were just ordering line fetuses for liposuction
We're just trying their hearts and livers on
You know they were doing more don't you
What national Canadian television Centre they just got in with her
Satanic ritual on TV it's all about letting you know
Time
Ladies and gentlemen
Yeah that that really upset me
What are they saying
I guess maybe Satanic rituals
I guess it's probably would
The doctors are doing such an approachable.
In Australia there was a newscast era day
Peace
Of a Satanic ritual accidentally
But it was just like at the Satanic ritual is people in robes
Just waiting on a stage going like
But like so scary
The ritual sacrifice
Guess
What happened
By somebody who worked at the station
Or it's entirely possible to that someone was working on a story about the the satanic
Example that a clipping light because they
The satanic temple in question
Has been making a lot of
You know he's about
Them not being allowed
To teach Satanism in schools
Is basically just trying to
Confront the idea that you are allowed to teach
Other religious stuff in schools
And in so I could see somebody at that station
Working on a story this is some b-roll from that accidentally got into a
Story
Because it's
Like basically local news
Is it could happen
I could see it I could
See it happening quite easily
There's an accident
Aspect of this
It certainly not proof that
They're trying to normalize and
Throwed demonic rituals in your face
You know it is kind of funny
Tumi
That
In order for these types of
Quote unquote Christians to like
Maintain their belief in God
They also have to give
Satan worshipers
A powerful religion
You know what I'm saying like
Both in order for them to justify themselves
They have to be afraid of something
That
Is just a bunch of people's cone
Like you've created a fear out of
Nothing and a lot of the people who are doing these things like I want to teach Satanism in school
Are doing it not in order to teach Satanism in school but doing it in order to make it so you can't teach your
Religious beliefs
Do people in schools
Satan is just a your belief system
It you're looking at Satan and Satan's like
You're a hypocrite you idiot and you're like
Pure Evil
Right
It's
Just
I grow weary of it
I think it's a probably there's a lot of incidents of this like local news
Things they've just have the wrong b-roll but a lot of them are probably so
Boring
You never hear about it
Child riding a tricycle
It's Ono I was doing the story about
Please and there's a beer all of a kid riding a tricycle
That's never going to you never going to hear about that
Because
Dum Dums
So the Taliban
They have
Made some moves
Afghanistan
He's not talking about this
To too much
Sprite
Look
You know who get who get this he's only complimented the Taliban
You know who did it though
Who it was a Taliban
With it they had help
Satan
Obama
And somebody else
Ladies and gentlemen pay 100% of the Taliban to take over that way
100% Fat Joe Biden
This is
Obama
This is Kamala Harris
And it's just our plan doesn't mean by none get in trouble doesn't mean he's not terrible
My point is we need to put the blame on
The bureaucracy that Puttin me on
And the media that said he can be a president and then help him steal the election
However Obama and
Kamala Harris having
I was thinking
That thing but they are both foreign policy expert
They not white is that
To not white people who have
Copperview executive
Person that he's a patsy he's not a******
I mean that's amazing
That is just an amazing amount of unexamined racism wow even your number one villain you're like
Well he's a white man let's not go crazy okay
Sure he worships Satan but this one this is not a white man
He's a doddering fool you being used by the
Yep
Unreal
What a massive
Sucks
So
Alex has gotten that headline
I bet he wants to cover
And this has to do with
The FBI putting out
Statements
That statement but some sources with the
Klein Forest
Manaphy I saying that
Rodger Stone and Alex Jones didn't have some elaborate plan on the 6th
Break
Figured out exactly how he wanted to cover
Emily forgot
You know it's hard to tell him Willie Nelson story and I get into something like this
Because this just really really a big deal
And I don't want to say things about this that are wrong
I want two times when I get ready to say something on here
During the break at all crystallized
And I have the perfect explanation
English Spanish
Battling spin like a politics but then like him
Cool
Billiards
Information
Give three more examples really clear and people get the nuance.
Take a phone call and forget what I was going to say that I said hey I'll cover you next Eggman
What I am is Fatima do now
I like the I like the music I figured I would like is really
Concise
Perfect nuanced way to say this thing and then I forgot
I'll talk about it next time
I'll get to it I had this really important
I'm saying that I made sure that I understood clearly and could communicate effectively
But then I took a phone call and because I have the memory of what people think of goldfish
I completely forgot what I was
That being said
The right after that clip
Alex has
What I would call one of the more
Poetic description
Of what it's like to feel
Forget something
So the one thing that he is an expert at
I mean this is pretty good
Alright
Take a phone call and forget what I was going to say and then I say hey I'll cover the next segment
Which is what I'm going to do now
But just as soon as I try
Grass that fire again flickers away from me this
I tell you I'm really surprised that the establishment I mean it's one thing to plan this new world order
Play in the end of America to bring the planet bioweapon release
It's one thing to plan injecting people with
Program until they die
And express treatments
Another enchilada baby
I'll give it to fauci man what are we doing
Bad motherfukers
Bad hombre
Nothing on you
You vampire bat
Creature
But you know what
Schwab and Bill Gates dish out
Versace
This is honest where that we deserve the weekend that's what happens when you
Serta forget what you were going to talk about you end up giving it up to fauci and
Plus Rob lesson you guys
You're evil
Top notch
Likes Final Fantasy man you are good evil
So we've got the Somali pirates
The Taliban
And the global
Now they have to give it up
Yeah yeah
Cool it seems like the only person you don't have to
It is
A badass motherfuker
I'm so Alex finally get back to his train of thought
Flickering flame but he was trying to grab
Yes like
Prometheus getting his
Throat checked out every morning
Grabbing
Get the hold of it
This
Is nuts
Alex's found out that the FBI made the state
But that like
Rodger Stone
Again
I keep saying it's a state
It's not
There's just a
An article in Reuters
They have some sources in law enforcement
They say that there is scant evidence
But there was
Overarching
Planning
Behind the January
Which is not news
Well I mean if you go by Occam's razor all of their other plans have been poorly put together
Almost non-existent and have been ineffective and kind of
Resistance is the model
DD right-wing in the extreme-right organized
As for decades
And so there would never be
Elaborate
Organization
No it's not the mafia
That's about how
The folks
Community
Alex takes this information
In a way that I could not have
Possibly imagine
It's
Wild
I'm going to cover it
I would have left the story today
E5 a.m.
Wedding brother punch in the stomach
Ninety-nine percent of the time it's some horrible
Fishes playing
Okay we already got to stop
So Alex wakes up at 5 in the morning
Google's himself
Yeah
Is 8 hours of research is just putting his name in Google news and then hitting refresh
I sat there
Toilet at 5:30 a.m.
Stomach
And there was the
I was thinking about what does that mean
I think I know what that means
It's actually a positive thing
Not for me. I don't need myself
Sign my life over a long time ago
God
Traditionally you make a deal with the other
Forgot to save me a lot of the right things to the glove with cancer my family
They can't do it again me to sell out
Campursari
I'm not worried about myself
But
I really wanted to sink and Noah dismiss I caught a lot of people are respect
Different ideas to different views on it but
I know what it is
MPI being smart
A lot.
And I and II establishment that America the small vestigial group
There's a question of life
Is is the New World Order really a suicide pact
I mean it screwed
Your power and taking over really
Really going to be good if you're destroying the process
The answer is no so that's why they're not just about all
So he's teasing isn't talk a little bit more about it but the essential thing is that he's
He's interpreting this headline
Is being the FBI deciding they don't want to go along with the globalists death called
Anymore
Of course
This is a sign that the global FBI
There's dirt parts of it that are cool
Because and I think
Part of the reason I think he went that direction
Is because
It preserves him
Being smart enough
To have apple
With Rodger
Cursed out
Whereas
Because
If that's the case then he's
Still the leader of the resistance in the tip of the spear and all this stuff
And the FBI is helping
Cover for
I think the reason that he's doing this is
Because his name is in the story
And
It's fun
Yeah yeah
Although this is another
This is another drop in the bucket of my belief that he is actually himself a Satan
We keep going back and buy all the noises that he says Satan has make here's to the one that make them
You'll steal the deal you can't make a deal with God that's the point
Yeah God didn't go down to Georgia sell your soul to God
Fields it already
Yeah
Took the essential thing here is that Alex thinks
This FBI announcement
This headline
Events Stark
Contradiction
The Department of Homeland Security's strategic
Document
What's the smartest Minds out there people I respect
Versus the national security policy of the president
Even exist
Now doesn't
5 million Islamic refugees from Europe in the US right now
No they said opposition to cover measures question the election
That's the main Terrace
MPI
Verses that
We're giving a final report to Congress I've already seen Italy Publix to
Weatherscan
Evidence
0 Island
A shadow of evidence
That anybody plan an attack from capital
Even if everything ilex was saying about
All of the underlying documents in
Underlying sources of
It still wouldn't
Be accurate to say that
The what the FBI's announcement or this Reuters article at reversed or contradicted the dhs's 42
Only cares about this cuz like I said the fact that his name is used in the article
An unnamed former law enforcement official said quote
Ninety-two 95% of these are one-off cases
Plenty of 5% maybe of these militia groups that were more closely organized
But there was no grand scheme with Rodger Stone and Alex Jones and all these people to storm the capital and take off
Unified percent of the cases here
That's not no one planning
The article even points out that approximately 570 people have been charged total and 40 of them have been charged with
That's about 7% of the arrested who prosecutors feel have
They've enough evidence to charge with conspiracy
I'm not sure the stories about Michelle and anyway the actual information that's in the story
Or about what
People have
Ben
News
Acting rationally
Alex is shocked by how accurate this the FBI sources are
And of course when he
Says that he then has to embellish
Everything that they say
About 5%
That they did think they were going in the capital to take over
Alex is just
Writing that story
For himself
So this is
Astoria
Is Reuters story it's bitter
Then the FBI just covering their own ass cuz that's what some people think
Right some people think
That the FBI is covering their eyes cuz they don't want investigations
Into these militia
Two groups because they do they'll find out that they're all run by the feds
Brightree want to limit that
But it's not just that
According to
I think it's bigger
And just
I want an investigation of the provocateur groups
Now it's about this
It's about the national strategy for counter-terrorism
Listing gun owners and veterans
And
People that question elections are lockdowns
As terrorists
What's interesting is that Alex is combining his miac report and
Strategic document
The gun owners in veterans
That's a holdover from 2009
It's
It's interesting
The way his brain works
Spend as much as it's not
Nothing at all
A war in the FBI had any self-preservation any common sense
MPI would not be led
War with the American Linden
Can you imagine the left
Is it going to fight this war FBI agents
A1
Federal Marshals A180 fa1
Bureaucrat
Craft one
Soldiers
Men
To go out and fight
Other men
A Dalmatian and
Simple party is if you're not under mind control
I don't want to fight with the FBI or the US Military
Wouldn't help America anyways
American I'd rather reach out to wake them up and they're like
Maybe we should start saying no
And that is what this this
So yeah this is the way Alex is interpreting this
Trivial news story
It's a sign that the FBI
Dad doesn't want to fight on behalf of the left against gun owners and Veterans and Patriots
Wow you know the reason that
The FBI
And the bureaucrat
That's in the likes
Should handle this
Because this is not a war
No
You are just your guys aren't ideologically aligned to save the country
You're just a bunch of idiots women
Just like everybody thought
Give me a potential Criminal
Well the ones who've already committed crimes
Criminals
The ones
Who are idiots
They're on their way
There's something there on the street
Anyway
Alex gets off this topic
After.
Bizarrely interpreter
Because the other guy
Okay now this guess
Someone is very
Somebody else
Okay this is a real get of you know this guy
Alright
From
Going viral for yelling at a San Diego
Back at it like a crack addict
Alex finally got ahold of the guy who yelled at
The San Diego board and went viral
Matthew Baker I believe is named
You've been on Owen Shroyer show multiple times
Somebody said my God just got sounds like Alex Jones 2.0
And turned out I didn't know his brother Warren twice
I know you look familiar
See if somebody was on Ellen Show multiple times
Aspiring the right-wing sugar in there
Anyway he's just somebody who
Alex
He's a big fan of Alex's
He's just repeating the things that Alex taught him
How to pair it
At this board meeting
Video goes viral man Alex interviews him about what was it like
To yell the things I taught you more less
Stupid
Ouroboros interview
Happy here with Matt
Well it's fantastic to be on the show Alex and you know I am a massive
Fan and what people don't realize is I might not always be screaming and yelling but
When I do with fur
Humanity
Who
Very much
Fringe
This is why you guys aren't
Going to fight a war
Because what you got right there
Yep
Yeah but I have to introduce yourself to somebody for like the third or fourth time
You had that had a friendship before that started
I swear to God because
Both of us
Thought we were doing that at the
The same time both of us I don't think we'd ever met before but because we were comics
And because weird
Kind of generally seeing each other around you
We just kind of started talking and both of us were soaking
Confused and weren't sure if we had already met the other person
That we just became friends for a couple years
Like it wasn't even like we just
In the friendship was entirely based around not wanting to be like
Hey how you doing I'm Jordan and then have them be like yeah we met the last time that was the only thing the
It started our friendship
Just assuming that we already met before similarly one time
I became friends with a comic book
Because we just went up to each other and let
That's not as far away
So I deserve this clip of
This guy who
Basically just indoctrinated by Alex Jones and then now is
A drone
Drone with John out
Go to these meetings you'll meet real hatred
Right-wingers people Asian people
Girl shoes
I was always talking about you know I have a saying it's called
I married
I can't go to Patriot eventone River clothes off and people even know this
While somebody just stand there like why are we living in a world full of pus
This is this is
Great while
Wild
Gold coin
Angela Patriot rally and get your dick sucked come on ladies and gentlemen if you want
Fight For Freedom you're going to get that dick so this is just like PCU
Anyway I don't care about this guy just basically like
You are being interviewed about how you believe Infowars
Stuff on Infowars
Or some s*** like that it's like of course you believe the same s***
It's a it's a pointless exercise
But
He has another guest at the guy named dr. Vladimir zelensky
He's got his big into hydroxychloroquine and I would have you any eclipse
Because
I don't really care and she also talks about how
Now there's a war spiritual battle and
How do I think it takes away some of your scientific credibility of your
Talking about how the devil is
Upon us
See a doctor in
I'm not sure I see there's a problem
But we have to end this
Episode on a high note
Of course
No we don't know I don't know what's happened with her when I was recording
But there's only one
Hinode that I can
You can think of
That will satisfy us
Mike down for this
If you can
Oh I can taste it I certainly
Because the whole galaxy just a city
I'm going to get off this planet together gospel and you belong in the City Yuba
Belong
Are deducted the failed they already sign.
The wrong energy
I know they're cut off that's why they're so angry
What do you think about it Galaxy is just a city
I want
God damn it it's good it's true and you know what the only thing that unites all humans
All Humans regardless of race Creed background ideology religion
Dope sack that's what you mean you just need a good sax solo
That's all you need
Man
Man oh man that trouble sex I thought you were going to say that the one thing that unites everybody is loving
Alex Jones rambling / You Belong To The City definitely
Connect sleep stream
I hate Alex Jones was even I couldn't enjoy that and now it's clearly loved it
But I bet there's a bunch of people in the middle who wouldn't find it as interesting as I do or as fun
Dammit that was a good one though
Concern
How I can taste it
I don't know if I could listen to that song like casually
Without
Filling in my own Alex
Bulshit heard it at the store the grocery store like a couple months back and I
Pretty excited
Feel it
There's nothing
Better than I do I
Giselle
But there is nothing better than that
The Galaxy is just a city
That's
Crocheting
What what else did we get him
Compare things to just played any song cars with the Galaxy
She's a lot like a car my car
You can whip you know in a lot of the ways we have to
Whip it good
Mufon I can whip it
Yats
Just think that I wanted to stress on this episode
Is really that
Owens
Charge
I have no faith that he's actually going to see the inside of
The jail cell
It seems like it seems unlikely
And the reality behind it
Is this
The Deferred prosecution
Alex has a not in any
Real trouble
Of any sort
Not this all falls on Owens
Dumb show
I do think it's funny though
Because
The as we've gone through this like stretch
Trip time
You see Alex.
Seeing this coming at all
Having a warrant out for his arrest
You know the 20th Alex is responding to this
News this Reuters article
About him being exonerated
And he sees this as
Bfbi deciding that they don't want to fight with the globalist
An hour after that
Owens on are saying well I got to turn myself in
Yes we are bad guys losing control of the
Drudgereport again
Kicked him out Ono the FBR villains
Look
There's not
This is stupid
The stretch of time is stupid
Owens dumb should have done his community service
That's nothing
But I know people really excited to hear our take on it and there it is
Jordan but until then
It's also showing
Owen.
Crime. Badka
Realtor on Twitter
We are
You could please find a local
To charity or bail find any real help that people do
Got to work
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work