Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
A couple dudes like sit around and drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
And his effect on the world
Today
Salted caramel mocha
A company that
No but
A company that may or may not have been involved in a scandal
Starbucks
Known for making some weird that store available products
And this one is it was Mark limited edition that means I got to give it a try
Do the honors
SAU
Tastes amazing
It's a cake
Supposed to
Drake we had last week
Which was
Edible drink
Picture editor
Wondered what it's like to
She would drink
Give it a go I don't anymore
So I don't know much
Very refined our dynamic
We're going to be the 2015 president
I should tell you
That Alex Jones
On today's show
This is recording this on Thursday
On the 29th
Who speculated that the globalist the kidnapping children
I'm sending them to be slaves on a Mars colony
Okay well one
That's the
My bad
Terraforming it and then there's children
Terraforming
Yeah
Pro Bowl
Well in terms of
Like
The present and how violent it's getting in terms of Alex's rhetoric in his tone
This is very well
This kind of stuff is at least like it's Philly
I said they're going like
Oh you motherfukers watch Alex I think Alex got to come
Insulting credit on that thing
Liberals are coming for you
Bully just keeps calling
That's so scary
So also the other thing
Not American you might be thinking there a Mars colony that these children are going
Right
He's on Alex Jones Show
He has some
Supposed military history so you know he knows things
Sure here's how I know he's in Val
Not in the same conversation where you talkin about
Otis Mars colony
He also talked about how did he die
He's pedophile globalist
I have to terrify the children to Adrenaline eyes their blood
Adrenochrome narrative
Such b*******
I don't know
I do it's cuz you have to get whack your locker or else you don't get attention
You don't mean like they're hit up after this point was like
Buck
I do like the next I'd like their move
Is there
They're doing monsters.inc basic
What is like
The global is if they are terrifying the
Maybe they discovered that they could get even more adrenochrome
Yeah right before the show started its very hard to make a comedy
Before we get to Today Show in earnest
Hey what's up
We appreciate welcome Patrick
If you would like to be a policy wonk
You can go to our website knowledge
The support the show length
In a monthly donation
Format
Songs from now and
We will have
Cindy's sitting on falling apart
Do jumping the time machines
Nope on our last the show
Last time we were back in 2015
We ended on August 16th
Alex
Hit heard Donald Trump
I mean
Maybe Trump is the guy we need
Because I speculated to you two things
Yeah I made a bold prediction
The first
Was that this was not a full payment
This was just a warming
Of sorts and Alex was not on board with
Prediction that I made
Was that Larry Nichols was right around the corner
Okay I will tell you this
On August 17th
Larry Nichols comes back the next day right around the corner
Dammit
Larry Nichols Rock in Elizabeth
I'm not going to play any of Larry Nichols parts
From the August 17th show but I will tell you
But he provides evidence
That the clintons killed Evans
We need to call and ask about that
He provided a memo
State troopers
I don't know also could be
Alex is like how did you get that document
Cuz I got stolen
Just covering up for your
Your secret
Agent sources
That's right
Nah I'll be honest
Things just show up in my mailbox
Are your f****** home address on Alex Jones Show who knows how
How many radio shows that you're on
Soliciting money for your medical bills which would be covered under Obamacare
Join the winning
We're all going to die
Very bad time this Thursday
Talks about is how he thinks
Clinton
Hillary's private server he thinks Obama setting her up
All right that's not a narrative I've ever heard
The most in
Intriguing narrative
Both because Larry Nichols believes that Obama wants to become the last
President because when you're the last president you become and if
He will immediately turn the United States
Leader of Islam worldwide
It's okay needs to get the clintons out-of-the-way right there the only Force
Powerful enough to take him down
And stop his islamification
Playing
So he's got to make this server should happen
In order to set up Hillary take her down
Then there's nothing stopping him from okay
Here's my counter
I agree with the premise
Set up Hillary Clinton
Revenge on America
Has been
Treated worse
Yeah
And now it's time you know what
I'm f****** out of here
Done with you
Guess what
Welcome to Trump now you finally appreciate me
Have a hot plate of trump an a****** how good is Obamacare
Declarative
Trump
Is Obama's Revenge it follows like human nature but at the same time Obama's not nearly that petty
Well
Did you did you read the
Story Wright
Maybe Obama could have revealed all the info
He already knew
Maybe he could have told us maybe
What happened
I feel like that comes into legality though I'm not entirely sure about all the Dynamics
Be that as it may
Eddie
It's all over
The fuk on the Larry Nichols was coming
On this episode
No but I'm right all the time
But also I'm right about the other thing I suggest
Here's where Alex's hit is that at
Thea on August 17th 2015
As it relates to Trump
And say that he's an operative completely
And now I moved from 50-50 on trauma
260 40
What is that mean
Because what he's doing
Hurting the established
The imaginary team in my head that I'm again
Hillary
Peach Paul Watson did last week
His perspective
At the bottom of the hour
But then I'm going to go over why Trump may be good
I'm not endorsing Donald Trump
Okay alright
Ultimate
I'm going to wait until he sells people out
Nauseous myself
I'm going to make sure he's politically and financially punished
I'm going to hold you to that
Beyond Trump
So Alex is right
First off
Jon Lovitz
This is the ultimate
Credit
That's just that
Is that all you have
2nd Peter 3
Except your hand on the cake bottle
I took it
This is real this is Revenge
This is Revenge for the replica visit
Fireworks
Alright go ahead
He's going to wait and
Salespeople out
What is that
How can't but how can you be 6044 Trump and still be like
Yeah he's going to tell everybody out
At this point it's really talks about like 2 months later
So let me know
His numbers
His loyalties are meaningless
Yeah yeah for sure
And Elsa as the course of this episode goes
Speculation that a lot of this was about Hillary's probably true
But I found a new leader in the clubhouse of what's going on
Obama know Larry Nichols is not correct
What are the news stories he wants to cover is about how there's a sorority
They made an adverb
He's already done
Very
There's a sorority that made an ad you have no idea how dumb
And the reason is because it's an all white commercial
It's all white people in this roraty
Is it all white people in a very
We love all white p
Sorority that's like let me be clear I didn't watch the video
But let's get Alex Jones and take on it
Racially home
Homogeneous also I want to give one little bit of a warning
There is a jump cut in the middle of this audio clip
It's the first time there ever will be one of those on this podcast
Is it the last time
As well not maybe not I'm not sure but I did that because you talked about the video into chunk
And in between was a two-minute commercial for prostate guard
So the commercial
And just put the two pieces back
She just love the
Position of
Sorority girls taking making a video and then
I do like that
Sometimes
Isaac Prosper guard everyday
Why are you taking all your pills you're riding your braids out also there was that report that came out about how
Gwyneth Paltrow's goop
Blog recommend
All these three ladies bikes
I was reading through the article that had all the comparison of her product her like a hippie bougie product
Versus Alex
Forest Products
And how they're all pretty much the same
And one
Something that I didn't realize is
The the iodine
The amount
B in the pills
But Alex cell
Is substantially over
The recommended amount that you should yeah
Covid-19 everyday you are
Weigh against doctor's orders
I think it's like
700 micrograms
More than what doctors recommend is he
Feeling
For what
So taking that much iodine could actually be dangerous
Yeah that everyday plus processor guard
Goof
Super female vitality
What else does
God dammit
Selenium
Boat field
Leave him what he says
He's taking
Subway
It's gross
I wonder if you can afford it.
Bars
Boston
Alex Jones
Because he's supposed to give you any other people don't want to work with them that's racist
So that's where the that's where the jump-cut is
One of the things that Alex
Is doing is really unfair
Thing where they grow up in a certain
Segregated culture
Segregated
That's not a good argument
For anything but it's also not applicable really to like sororities and fraternities and stuff like that
Regulator
You know organization
Like Greek life organizations and if you have
Abe
No black
People
Fraternity
That's a systematic
Problem has nothing to do with
I gravitate towards other people of my race
Institution
It's very much impossible to prove or disprove
Unless you go undercover it's just like the
The movie Soul Man
No I mean just like the housing
So the people who are working for a regulatory agency
They'll have a wipe
People are are white woman black woman
Both go try to rent the same
And they consistently find that
Black women are quoted
Much higher rent
They're systematically discriminate
So you can't prove that this
So sorority
Doing this because of this
Video
But also
You know
It's not necessary it's not necessarily that they're not doing it
Either
Distended
An undercover college student
Need to be like
Sorority
Skin color
I don't know
I don't know how to unpack the idea that there are like
Fraternity
And things like that
Because those do exist
Really see that big of a problem with it somehow
But all white
Fraternities and sororities
Dulce like a problem
Why is that
Well because you're awake
Here's one of my big
Issues that's why I just answered my own question.
Am I happy
Exclusionary history
Alright it wasn't done by these other disenfranchised
It is a problem and when they have groups
That are inclusionary to themselves
As a support
System seems like we have to
Unite to fight back
Cuz they if we don't then they're going to pick
Pick us off one by one or less fight each other
That yet again what is my route
It's like we're not allowed in there space
Right
I think that might be more why it doesn't really
Well I think
I think
It is
I think you're right
My thoughts on it
Built around
I think
The way that Chicago is so segregated
Like I think one of the biggest issues is that
If we're this segregated it is very much
You're not
You're still treating people as the other
Like one of the big things that they did change things for
Alabama immediately following the Civil War is once you have a generation
Kids that are fully
Aggregated
Earnout
Fully integrated
They don't fear black people
It is very much and inclusionary thing
Everybody gets pissed off whenever you try and do it
But I think integration
Even if it's forced
Integration
Ultimately wind up being a much
Situation for
For everyone
Forced integration is a bad way to put it
It's almost like his
What will it be
I think it's a better way to phrase it would be like
Immersion therapy
For people who are afraid
Just desegregation like
What was the school system of other than Force
Integration
Call desegregate
Which is still inaccurate
Moniker but
I think
Again I'm always
Frustrating tights Alex's.
So Alex is not done talking about these sororities
And his video weird spin
Why are you so racist
Hispanic
Races races races
Does it get more indicative of white privilege
That that
Can I join your family Barbecue can you think of any situation where
Alright
The most glaring example of white privilege
Dude we're just trying or maybe there are four super inclusive this is a big argument that white supremacist
Make about the idea of diversity actually being code for like white genocide
There's these all-white organization but you never say that you need diversity in
All black organization
And some stuff like
Which again
It's a
It's the
Between the oppressor and oppressed
Currently the future as well
Because it doesn't look like
Sounds like you're gonna be wrong.
Not really
Yeah tell me what's wrong
The only thing about this
It's a bunch of really good looking women
And as we know modern feminist for whatever reason I have their initial studies
Are three times fatter
And tell women what to do
Lesbian
Are lesbians who just won a pimp
Sarcastic
Some of the dog ugly women short haircut
Juan girlfriend you know he's got her nails done just right
Police report
I mean
Girlfriend looks like
Next week Playboy
Also
Horse
So that was some nuance
You are so mad
You threw down your pain in the middle of that
There's no way that it see that's that's
The problem like
Anytime there's a
There's like a fictional meeting
Between me and Alex Jones in my mind Alex
Said something like that
And I just
Begin to break down and
Scream. Like you're you're a mean guy just like yelling directly into his
Space for an hour uninterrupted screaming
It's going to
It's going to get so much worse
Hypothetical framework of this meeting you're going to have with Alex
UPS
Okay
And of course
I would say the only person
Could mediate
Between the two of us
Who sabotage
53 you have a beer
Alex might have six Alex
Alex just is like
Hey man I'm
I'm really just a
The character
You know I'm really just
Amping it up to 2
You know playoff fees
These dumb dumb
Who buy this product I'm just in it for the money
I'm like no I totally understand that
But
Let me ask you a question
How do you feel about all white sororities
Who's lesbian
So mad cuz they're ugly
Few years of the past
None
Do you know your drink is espresso
Yeah
Okay this might be an issue
This is my break now I'm amped up all the time
Sensitivity to caffeine
Every single day
Okay
Wow all right let's get through this
The next clip that we have from August 17th
Alex talked a little bit about Hillary Clinton
And then I left this in
Mostly be
Because
On the last episode the trend of
A very positive feelings towards Russia
This next clip demonstrates some of them
That they are the men now
And she should be proud of that
Country girls
Baby
I got Larry Nichols
Hillary Clinton
And Bill coming up
Speaking of the devil
Let's go to this clip
Hillary
Talking about how
He's like the guy from House of Cards
He does
House of Cards guy is a manipulating crook
Who acts like a sweet
Keller 8
Here she is saying Putin
Is House of Cards
You talk about
Wow
You know
Well with a gun
Look
Straight-shooting murders journalist very few of the journalist that have been shot
We're shop more than two or three
What's FairPoint
Also whenever you have strong arm leaders
Don't like their approval rating look
Just got forced out
97% approval rating
That's that's
The sign of a happy
Cialix
Completely buying into Russian propaganda RT button
It like that
Like I reference
How old are
RT
Is Eastside
You watch Russian profit or the propaganda
Have you seen artavis propaganda shut this is good stuff he's like how you watch Russian State television and it's like it's
Call Alex Jones is on there there's a reason for that
You should you should look
Hired in a Russian mirror
You know I hate tyranny I love freedom and everything like
Strong leader
You got a great approval rating
The straight shooter
He's not manipulative
Alex
Alex Alex
Is old
He's mad
Mary Tyler Moore or Murphy Brown
We've already established this is fine
Women who work whenever that make sense
About ladies who lunch
Unbecoming
August 17th that was most of
Nichols
Also Jared
Gerald Celente comes on to talk about how the end is near for the economy also buy gold
He says that the economy is definitely going to collapse by the end of the year
Daiso by gold or implied because the last episode maybe Max
Maybe one of our own cryptocurrency
So now we come to
I think it's still available yeah
Jordans
Go to August 18th
And I will take up the rest of our show
That anytime 1 episode in the investor
Takes up the rest of our show.
Something big happened
Do you remember couple episodes back Alex Jones got a call from a literal White
Yes
Told him you need to have David do conure
F*** he has David
He has David Duke Show
You Daddy hours
Most of the show me listen to
Former Grand
Former
Who can prove
He actually has some negative things to say about the clan
Weirdly
Yeah
Control
Like the administrative services
No it's more like being Grand Dragon because it's more like I was one of the good ones
When I got out
Right whatever
Yeah I know
David Duke
Is
Resoundingly a horrible horrible human being
I don't need to go into detail on it
And I don't want to repeat a lot of what he says
On my shelf
Cuz we have control over
The show I'm not I've cut out most of the
Flaming bigotry that comes out of his mouth
But I've left in some stuff that is important for our investor
Because
This interview does not go how Alex Jones wants it
Okay
We've established in the past
The terrible interview
Heath
But he's bringing David Duke on to the show
It's going to be a
I got you
I'm going to ask him about abortion
Planned Parenthood is genocide I'm going to bring up all my narratives
And he's not going to have an answer and then David Duke is going to be humiliated on my show
Goes very different
This is an astronaut all over it
It's way worse
Except instead of somebody
He's gone into space
Pale blue dot
At the world
Instead it's somebody who
Russell's underneath
Rocks
Caterpillar
Poisoning
Millipede
Which one is the most
Either
Chimera of them
I'm not going to like I said if you want to know more
Look up on your own you can find some
Some really f****** horrible things he's red
You can find him being very supportive of the Nazi party
In America you can find
Any always counted it behind I'm just trying to protect my own
That sort of thing
Which is dicey
But
Before we get into the interview
Here is
What
Alex Jones
Didn't do his research
And he doesn't know how much he agrees with David Duke
Corsola
So all he knows is this guy used to be in the KKK
He pushes race
Politics
Soleil
You're like a white version of these minority groups
But I hate
You're like Barraza
Which he thinks is a
He's like you're like
Farrakhan but for white people
That's his promise
But he doesn't realize
Is the David Duke
For all the horribleness of him
He is way smarter than Alex
I believe
Basically
Except she says
Instead of globulin
And there's a reason for that
Alex Alex's entire philosophy is built around
This
Build up
Brahma Italy late 1800's on
From the time of the protocols of the Elders of Zion
You get through to the creation of the Federal Reserve
Stuff is the foundational aspects
This massive Jewish conspiracy
Are controlling everything
Designer
And what have you
Which is what globalism is
Fear of globalist
Is that
So
Di-dong
Comes out thinking he's proved
He's not eraser
Yeah
Turns out
He proved that
He is a race
No the same time believing that he still proving
No I don't I don't think you have it quite right
What I think more happened
Alex is caught off guard
Having to agree
David Duke says
And all you have to go back on
Is
You're obsessed with Jews
And not much
So Alex gets
Basically on his own
Like an out-and-out white nationalist
And I think
That this
Is demonstrative of the future
Alex Jones
Ba like this week is hell
He starts to see
Some of like
And then also
David Duke
Uses a number of arguments that Alex Jones ends up event
So in the same way that Alex Jones would take information
An integrated into his theories
I can see at least three or four points in this interview
That he worked David Dukes
MN Within
Episodes that I've heard in the future event
Alex just mirrors at identically
But he says global
Like I said
I tried to cut out as much of just the out-and-out hatred is possible to we don't need to sit through that
Is that all you have to
And make
Out-and-out big
More acceptable is
Change
So Jordan
Further Ado let's dive into this interview with David Duke here's how it starts
Ask you so much for joining us today
Well I hope so
A real discussion about some of the basic issues because
I would like to get down to the bottom today about who
Country
The world that is truly as you say
Their nana play of all mankind and I think
Even said this as well in the first part of the show
You said they want to in some ways go against European people because they want to control the West End
The power
Of the West
And I think that's why
In the Middle East Billy Wars for Israel
And Wars for the globalist up hours
But I'm not I'm not
A carbon copy our mirror image
Sharpton
The truth is that
There is
Racism
Ben dominates America supremacism
Against the European American
And as far as Eugenics to respond
Limiting births
Throat population explosion black people have
How much higher birth rates and white
Mexicans have a much higher birth rates and even African American
European Americans have about a 1.6 Birthright which means a quarter of our people
Every generation of population explosion the world
A statistic
Showing that in Africa by 2050 Bill be one point
NFL most entirely because the massive Birthright so
I don't believe that worked all day because of Africa
Are African Americans or whatever
The truth is that the only
Nation
No
Amazon
United States
Canada Australia every European nation today is under attack
Just
Not careful with his language
That he's making the same point
The globalists are attacking
All these European white Nations
With emigra
To listen to one
I did not sign on to listen
To Alex Jones's agree with each other it's really important
I know it
I know that
No one wants to listen to David Duke
In terms of where we end up
This is crucial if you are still mad
Okay
The control the West
The goddamn f***
European Americans of the mean is
Europe
In North America
And what you really mean is
North America
And what you really mean is the United States
And then what you really really mean
F****** white
People
Everywhere close enough to wipe so visually pass
Intellectual bigotry of a David Duke
Now he's
Less careful with his language than Alex in the sense that he
Is
Out in front about it that he thinks that
He's
Alex fears those sorts of things
But it's a little bit more couched in his language
But I you know
David Duke
Wouldn't be as dumb to say
White
Behind
You can hide behind
Can't really hide behind White
There's way more you got to be worried about what we were angles of attack
I'm fine
You know what
David Duke
Play well every
Immigrant
Has patented has anything
You no longer get to you
So that's
Better route
That's the one blog that if I was
If I was any kind of King
Of any sort
And I hope you guys all eventually elect me to be the autocratic
My one law is if you think
That it's white people you only get to use
I think it's very reasonable rule
We we proved everything that
Everything
You use
Like pretty much all
David Duke
Likes to pretend that he's real smart
I've got a lot of sources for things
One of the first sources that he cites
About his daughter
Jewish Supremacy Over America
Infowars article
No it's even worse than that
And then I'll explain what the source is
How
It's not european-american Christians my friend
Largest Hollywood Studios of movies and television are all Jewish
Control I can give you the name
Demographic hear of a Jewish pendants like at the Los Angeles time
Who is
Where he boasted you totally run Hollywood
In any article he list all the leaders of the Hollywood Networks
Any sense is insulted when people
Try to argue Irene even
He's proud of and he goes on to say I don't care people think we're running the Federal Reserve
International banking Wall Street
The media and government all I care is we keep on running them
That's pretty bad
You know what happens in the middle of it
They flash up on screen the graphic
That that you send along
Do you know Joel Olsteen
Logan Everest in Huber Heights
Yeah
Pundit
Like a boy
If you're taking that a Joel Stein article as your proof that like
You got a problem that's not good
That's like taking a dingleberry column
More or less
That's what you did
Yeah
Your f****** hero give you some medication about the level of thoroughness he does in terms of
You know verifying is sources figuring out
Making sure he knows it
Exactly what he's talking about when he wants to make
Claims on a radio show listen to buy millions of 80th
And here's another
When we're running low on food
We
Eating
For Irish babe
Small group
Right
That
That's just a fact
AAA
Has a sort of problematic history
He's written some things that are pretty f***** up
But
All in all at least especially at this point in his career
He's a humorous
U b
Make some bad points at some point time
And it's
He clearly just picked up like
Some quotes
Amazon
Bruce Almighty
Like that needs to be said
But
They going to do a little
Humor
I don't know
I think I think the West
The British
But they're right
List all of a sudden
It's like a violent language
The espresso
Yeah so in this mix
Single-payer healthcare
And I don't want the Jews to have it
What's wrong
Ava Progressive David socialist
In the first clip of David Duchovny played
You could hear that he
Agreed with Alex in terms of
Immigration stuff
He agreed
In terms of their being
The globalist force
But they were up a
Slickly threw it in there as like a
The globalist
Globalist first as like a little
Candy and stick for Alex Jones
There's a large that's that I think David Duke is trying to get Alex to recognize that they agree on
But in the next clip
Is another indication of
True things
Well I don't know if I can trust him because he's been involved with the zionists and he's one of these guys in the Republican debate we got to control me
Even Fox News is like
Controlled opposition Orwell was so great about that in Orwell
Talked about the controlled opposition and it is great
But he talks about the converter opposition for some reason
Name the controlled opposition Emmanuel golsteyn using to Jewish name
And I think that the Jewish extremists can set up a controlled opposition
And if you saw the debate it was like of ambush
And I got against Donald Trump and was because he was talking about the fact
That European Americans are losing the right the people who built this great country gave us the foundation
Sins of our Bill of Rights
Only thing they believed about it being replaced
And here's the problem I'm again I believe
And having a kind nations were all people supporting all people
I am at 4 instead of expectation give example the media so powerful they can just make me
I've never
Ever been a white supremacist
I believe in equal rights for all people I've always stated that position even back in my clan days I was a young man
Boy that's a tough
Even back in McLamb days
Kill the Jews
Need to kill him equally but you know what like all people should be treated equally
Macon in my young wild clam days
Cuz he wasn't an entry-level member of the clan
G Dragon which is already the dumbest thing that you heard
Slater
But
He doesn't he can't play that game that's not fair
Alex
Thing of like
I'm referencing movies
Referencing Orwell
Did Rude Jude the Jews
Yeah it's a Jewish name
Gordon pieces of Alex's at least his current
Framework and I think they're
Piano pieces
That are intrinsic to him
The day Breon
Distrust of the media that the media is full of s***
And the Trump
Can't really trust him because
He's been involved with Zionist
Oryza
Alex
Framework you've been involved with the globalist
It's exactly the same thing
Right this is this is a meeting of the minds
Two men who agree with each other but don't want to agree with each other
Does Alex
Admit
He agrees with David Duke on just about anything
He is now
With David Duke
Agrees with Alex
He has to
Give up
The pretense
We have to give up what makes him what made him famous which is
Being as I stop by
You know what I mean
Dallas cuz that's surrender
What is philosophy
I think a lot of him
Bring
Alex to
Yeah that's what I say
Men trying to disagree with
One man
Trying so hard
To not be racist
Given
Given today
Come on buddy
I am and I ain't
880 wildlife
This is a damning portrait of Alex Jones is a human
Defiant
Himself a little bit later and he tries to
Put up some sort of a resistance to
David Dukes
You know what
Here's the thing
I don't know if it's wrong to have David Duke on your
I don't know about
I don't want to I don't want to stay I think it's everyone's right to choose
What guests you will have and will not have on your show
I will say that it's wrong that Alex
David Duke
Savory things on his show
Already did on challenge
Cuz the only real rebuke that I get
Is
It's all with you that sort of thing
That's it there's no like real pressing back in terms of
Like
What do you want
He said
I just I just get bogged out I think I think
It is very much
Just like
The the all white
Sorority versus
The All Blacks
Anytime a white purse
Referring to all white
People immediately immediately like
Oh you think we're all going to kill so
Yeah everytime black people refer to every black person
As we it's always
2 things of solid
White people refer to Olive White
People is waiting
It's always a vial
It's always we're under attack
Need to fight back and the reason that you and I might be more
A verse that is that there's an implied lumping us
How to push back a little bit and one of the only things that he keeps doing
Is he keeps trying to get
David Duke
To say something about Hitler
He keeps
Alright
Hitler
What is your view
I have
A lot of German writings as well
I mean the Nazis really weird death called
They really were all sorts of weird ceremonial Magic
Call Todd
Where is Hitler
MetroWest
They double-crossed
Give me see again the West England British intelligence along with
What setting things up I mean take Prescott Bush
Butler I mean there's all that other stuff going on
I think this is
I'm sorry but I believe that the information you have there is false and maybe it's planted by the people is just business
That is no evidence at all
Western Nations supported the rise of Hitler rrna
Gentile
Establishment in America magazine
Yeah that's that's a little wild
I love it I love it
Alex's
Main issue with Hitler
Is that
They were a weird death cause
By then and then again
What's the who's the West now
Of course
It's hooked up
But yours is even more f***** up if that clip first of all Alex's
Wanted
Rule the world
On the other side was like
Alex is trying to bait David Duke into getting into how he doesn't believe in gas
Chambers and stuff like that
And that was the that was the thought I was I was thinking he was about to say
The truth is
There were no Jews killed in the hallway
David Duke that in a conversation
Games are not going to work
But here's the other thing as transparent
And it might just might just be because we have listened to so much of him and we have like a familiarity
If David Duke is such a monster
But there's a
You kind of pulling for Alec
Don't
Don't make me say that
How its breakthrough your condition a breakthrough your programming a good rooting for Alex
You hope what you hope is going to happen
Is it Alex Jones is going to come face-to-face with David
Who sang the exact same ship that
He says but about
Hayden juice
Alex knows that hating Jews is dumb and based on
Bigotry
Itsuki will you hope
Hope
Then he will see this be like oh no everything I think is wrong
Oh my God
I've been wrong the whole time
Have I been like him oh my God I would go for this interview is
Is Alex gets
That's all I really want I want Alex to genuinely
Angry and be
You learned you can choose for no reason
I don't
He's not going to
He's he's already 20 years
Spoiler alert
Now neither of us get our wish
Be angry
Alex
Well I think Alex
Tries to get a little bit crafty and it doesn't really work I'll explain that later
Should not Alex did not try and rely on
His craftiness
So
Stick with his bread-and-butter which is screaming like a loon
Explain why in a minute
But
Alex is against
This idea that Jews control every
Videos for the idea that globalist
Control every
Naturally
Don't be a contradiction inherent there
In this next
Really trying to have sophisticated
David isn't sophisticated
I've just heard all this over and over again
And I've also experienced
Nation group
They give
Just like super powers
Sky
Mama
So yeah he's an idiot
He doesn't realize that he's using the exact same thing you the packing to build up his globalist
He's trapped
You should never have agreed to do this interview
Imagine
Here's a Here's a thought
We take
Get transcript of this
And we just transpose
Globalist
Oh man
And then we transpose
The same
No it wouldn't be because
And I think most of
The facts
Seaside sarbak
But he has a lot more information
Ben Alex
Okay he comes in with names
He comes in with actual pieces of tidbits
Worry about
Next clip
Did we do a good enough job of explaining that I was an idiot
Attacking
People who think
Tablets run the world
The fact that he said
You ascribe superpowers
To whomever it is you think
Think of the anime
You just want to shake
I'll remind you that
In 2017
He allowed someone
Pretty much on challenged on his show to say that the globalist
Hoverboards colony
Those are kidnapping children to take
Godlike powers
So
You dumb
You real dumb
So I told you that Alex cooked
Start yelling at
They have
Clearly setup parameters
For this conversation
Alex Jones made a lot of
Concessions to David Duke to have him come on the show
He said
Early in the interview I didn't I don't have the clip of it
But he says
You agreed to come on the show if I'd be nice
And it's very clear that David Duke made
Time
Limit thing
Like I'll speak 45 minutes then you speak 45
And the reason this is clear
Is because they bicker about it
At least 12 times throughout the interview
Comment about how I kinda need my time
There's like I'm giving you your time
They end up fighting
Throughout the entire two hours
Mostly about time
I did not have time to get all of the clips cuz I'm telling you it's
Like
Isolated like
Here is an example of that
Them arguing about the time
Who's talking
And then Alex
A question that he thinks of the gotcha question
About abortion
And Planned Parenthood
Not he just doesn't realize everything he's doing
Is what he does
And is helping David Duke
Listen to the way the davidiuk answers this question
Realize that
Is the worst
He's the worst he's the literal
Worst
And then he didn't answer the question for 10 minutes
I want you to answer this question
He's going on so how do you square up
Behind the scenes
The Democratic Party
She loves him
They don't accept them love you
There's something else going on here is what I'm getting at
I'm glad you're giving me 10 minutes
I got your whatever
We can go into that's all I think I'll go to the end of the program the next hour or two because you're right this I feel like the only way I can
You really get a clear exposition of all my position
But his issue about that experts off
The KKK was not the author of any sort of Planned Parenthood
But I did and I was in the house represent by the way let me make something really clear to you so there's no misunderstanding
Spoken and completely opposed
To abortion
I also put my money where my mouth is and the House of Representative
I voted for the strongest anti-abortion laws has ever been passed
Legislative States of America
So it's really clear when I stand
You just forced himself into a situation where he had to compliment David Duke
Of course Alex is so bad at this
Why didn't you do any research I bet you didn't even know David was in the House of Representative
I didn't know David
House of represent
PPL Electric
Yeah
To the house of
At a certain point in American history
Wow
I mean it doesn't seem like too far of
Longshot for the future it's almost like you have to
To go back as far as
Now
To get another former KKK member inside the house of
Maybe noted
Justin anti-semite
Jeff
Who is in the Senate
And is now
Wikipedia list David Dukes political affiliation is
American Nazi party before night
Scene 75
I don't know if that's true maybe that's not
Not fair I don't know
President
Didn't work out
Riveting stuff here reading the Wikipedia article
A special election for a seat in the Louisiana house
House Representatives
Representing
Louisiana in 1989
That's the
Even though especially
Still real
Locked up
I can't imagine
Fukka I can't imagine it was long
Like I said
The two men
I bicker a whole bunch
Yeah About Time stuff
This clip
That was
Sol pass
Progressive that was amazing
That was I want to make a 94 cut
That was like
I remember
I remember I the God camp
What I was
14 for about a month
And that was
Every
Single
Dorm
After like
Day 4
Just like you know it's no big deal
Stop leaving your
In the shower but that's
Like
Those are those are 12
Starbucks
We'll wait for this next week
What you even
Doesn't really take care of the people to die and don't they are never able to reproduce or whatever
Give me my 10 minutes please
David talk about birth rate
Please bear Alex's interjecting trying to be helpful f*** you give me like that
Here's one where they're bickering more about time
Do we have
It really affair
Playing field in this country when the same media
That promotes the Jewish state of Israel is doing everything they can to destroy European Americans
Majority and and really preserving our European
Earlier
Do some stuff like that
Criticized
Implying I'm not letting you talk more than I have
Dish hour
Unless you count the ads is my time
Ion radio show
O'Reilly for sure
I would just talk more than other shows
I might say something I don't want to be polished
Polish
I love it
Why do you say
Because why
Food you say what you want
PR spin
Just masking the white elements of it
White right
White
You know what it is you get to
F****** quote Orwell
And not
Get new speaker
The main part is making language mean f***
Nothing that's just part of it
The trick that Orwell was really talking
About there
Is that what language has
Meaning
You can say whatever you want
True
You can say whatever you want and people
Believe there's no there's no like
Like this
TV
Boxers
So it's going to cover more peep
Say that
God is my my role model
How is it
How is it that
Media critics
Stupid
Geared towards letting me
F******
People being lied to
Is lying to an audience
That I really dislike about that clip
What I don't dislike is them being petty as f*** about time
Is awful is the David Duke one of the
The point that he's trying to make is that white
Will no longer be a majority
And that's really scary
And here's an idea
That
White people
Art supposed to be the majority
In our home country
Warhol
European Americans
Our home
Country songs about tons of countries in Europe even say about Alexa
Various other countries that have
Germanic
Alright hubby how about Africa
This is their home
Its own country
If I'm to be a majority
I mean
Charmin The Wonder of America really it
Never should be a majority
Should be everyone is a minority
We're all cool with it
Kind of the
Big
Course
Why do you think
Like because of the Jewish plot
Right
Are you solo
Afraid of not being them
Majority anymore
Cuz I think he thinks that once we become them
My minority
Maybe the real fear of whiteness is we're going to get with
Coming to us
That's not true
I think that
No but I think that's us projecting our minds into
I think
To be the subconscious
I would argue that maybe it's not fear that motivates primarily it
We need the majority so we can kick their ass
In case we need
I think they might have a more proactive angry approach to it where is Jose
We did a lot of bad s*** in the past
Totally afraid
Yeah absolutely
It has to it has to be
That like their hats
To be a
Awareness
Because why else would you insist
Endless
That white people have never done anything
And that racism is
Curaleaf
Function
The Jews controlling plot
To do all of this
People have done wrong things in the past
But
The white people
Have done wrong things are dead
No
No they were gentiles
With the Jewish power
Do you mean like globalist
Collaborator
I would be I guess so
Yeah it's absolutely
But that's but there has to be
Knowledge which is why they insist
Endlessly that there is an
Rite Aid losing the majority
Purely because
They think violence
Is going to be visiting
And that means that they think it's Revenge
And that means that if it's Revenge
They are aware
That their s*** to be revenged upon
To feel guilt
Five people expressing their life
Exactly
Yeah I don't want to hear black people stand up for themselves making me feel guilty
I don't want games
Public
Make me feel guilty and weird
That's
Just
Guilt because of an awareness of
That's wrong
This exploit Jordan
Conflicted feelings about this
Text clip
And here's why
I don't think that it's ever necessarily wrong to be rude to David Duke
But Alex Jones
Was pretty rude
In this next clip
And I think it's inappropriate
No punch Richard Spencer punched David Duke
I think it's wrong because of the host
Guest
Dynamic
You know even if it's David
He's still a guest on your show deserve this kind of rudeness
Based on how he's treated Alex in the interview
Here is
Here is the game here
I'm going to listen to the level of rudeness
Measure it against
What I think would pop
My level of rudeness
You f******
Other issues you want to cover where you think the world's going economy but
Explain to me seriously
Goblin Cyclops stuff come from
You are goblins Cyclops Dragon
Never was a goblin never was a cyclops
I think that's a little rude
What are you f******
What are you f****** because of the names of cake
Take a position
Do you know that was the point of the Superman radio serial in the 50
I would like him to his f******
Face
I get that I believe though the grand
I was not your scales
Did you have those surgically implanted
Is your belly the weak spot
Should I if I were to shoot an arrow into going by first of all
Let's start at the beginning
What type of dragon would you consider yourself to
Are we talkin about
Lord of the Rings you're about your about to learn about fire breath
Please dragon or a Chinese dragon
Are we talkin about a gargoyle
Situation
G Dragon
What type of dragon are you
Honestly I think that's less rude
I mean look I'm not that he deserves better treatment
If you have someone on your show that you've clearly made confession
Sims 4 like he's clearly
Been like okay you get 5 minutes I get 5 minutes
We'll set an arrangement that
You clearly unpleasant
Come to me as a broadcaster
Because I want you on my show that badly
It seems like the wrong kind of thing to do to
Ynobe reductive
And insulting about
Write something I've already talked about this a little bit I cut it out
He talked about how like
Yeah I was in the KKK when I was younger
And I realize that the organization I couldn't
Control the actions of
All the other members of it
So I decided to go and do something that I could be in complete control of
The idea that you're like lynching
Which is great
I'm glad you were gone you pull up my computer
David Duke
I'm going to show you
22RE
Scale of how
And it would
Surely be
Black cock
Tire inner
We agree to this
Before he was a grand drag on
And he was a rapper from the Roughriders crew
Much forgotten rapper
Second row Brady Dragon songs
Duke
Richard David
Do you know if x
X is going to be the ticket
Custard
First
You stop
I need drop
Oh
No
It's a Ruff Ryders
This next clip
Video guide
We've been talking a lot a bit about
Various things that are clear
Points of agreement
Between Alex Jones and David Duke and here comes another one
Americans always respected and loved Robert Ealy
Today he's been called The Traitor he wasn't a traitor he's a traitor than Thomas Jefferson was a traitor George Washington was a traitor
Any attack on Southern Heritage will be nothing more than an attack on entire European Heritage cuz now there
Play talks about taking down statue
Thomas Jefferson
They talked about taking George Washington's name off Public Schools they did that
New Orleans saying he was unworthy because he had slaves will half of the great Heroes of the entire third
World order slaveholders including an awful lot of Jewish Heroes for slaveholders is read about Jewish history
Brittany apocracy is unbelievable in this country
So there is some more bickering about time there again
Go f*** yourself there's a really funny point when they're about to go
Go to calls
And David and
We're just going to talk I don't I don't care
Have you
But because
Lick right there
That fits perfectly into Alex's and Tire
They're trying to ban the Confederate flag
The Confederacy
Was actually not that bad
The Civil War about slavery narrative
Write a match up perfectly on that
Is getting incredibly flustered by the like
S***
This guy has more information than me
You sound smarter than me
He's way more put-together than me
He
Dancing circles around me making the same arguments as me but just
Saying that it's Jews
I don't really have a good argument to come back against that
I do
Me personally
Damn I do
I would never activate David Duke so
Never never
Show him cut for
About drywall
How
This is this is something I'm becoming more and more
The worst thing that the North
Dad was
Go to war with
If they just let them secede
It would have been a failed state
Yeah probably the problem is of course
Slavery first
So
True
I don't know but this
That
Robert
American Hero
Is so
F****** stupid
Well today
No one in the Civil War
Wasn't America
There were no heroes in a war
The most Americans die
That's not a hero Scituate
No
I would agree with that
Yeah I don't know but it wasn't
Raggedy
That was the f******
Iliad all over it
There's no there's no
Good team
Pretty cool
School director some good dudes
Among the Greeks
Hector was a pretty awesome dude you just happen to be on the side of Troy
They were there at the whim of the Gods
And forced to fight each other in a war that neither really wanted to be fighting but had to
The globalist forced us into the Civil War
Quite frankly
Consider the possibility that there are
That the Greek pantheon still
What is the Greek
Nailed it
I thought about it
I made it would make sense just using us for
Entertainment
Back to me makes the most sense
The gods are immortal
What would you do if you are immortal
Layla
Ford
Right
That was the Greek pantheon they were just f****** board and they made
They make people fight for their immune
Like that's the only thing that makes sense of the world we live in
Subway situation where God knows everything
Sing it is everywhere
Controlling every
Makes it seem like there's one dude
Who is Jeff Dunham
Biggest f******
Yeah
If you're dealing with the Gods
It's just like
They got nothing else
To do
They're human characteristics
I don't think we can get to the bottom of that
Let's get to the bottom of this
I am putting out about
$10,000
If you have any information I'd
Give us a picture Idaho
Gmail
It'll be a picture of cat
Clip
Alex is trying to rebuff
The idea that
Jewish Supremacy
That is a problem with the world
Sprite brings up
John P Waldron
The book
Ketoscience that we discussed our past episode
He brings it up to lie about how it's about putting stuff in the water
Amy wants to ask David Duke
Are these Jews
Those people were white
So here is that
It's it's fine David people can go to davidduke.com
Most of the other people of your ilk
Really trying to understand your worldview on things
Where you see things going before we go any further
Major League
White House science our population resources environment
And reduce IQ
Because that's not what they talk about in the book we went over there and I cut it out cuz it's
Long but David Dukes respond to
Disrespected
Just those words
He should have looked at whether or not they were just having a very simple response will do do cuz like the air licks those are
Well I don't know about John holdren
I am so at that point
Because Alex doesn't rebut it or have any information
That's the fact that stands on the show is losing every single point
That is being like
Keeps
Giving softball serve
Thinking he's spiking
He's doing a terrible job
And letting
Basically
A white supremacist
Anti-semite convert people who listen to Alex Jones through his caused
What is f******
Dismissive
Yeah but
But the dismissiveness
Was because
You can see it in his face there's a lot of visual stuff in the
He's defeated
Alex Jones is like
All right you can see he's just like
I know he knows what's happening as it's happening
Because earlier in the in the episode
David Duke said I'll stay I'll stay with you for an hour
Alex kick him off the air without being like
I do I want out of this
So he's stuck
Yeah
It's it's insane
The only way the only way Alex wins is if he gets
Really really ain't
Kicks
Eddie can't do that
Because
Argument
So here's Alex's summation of the interview so far
Maybe like
The reason he is such a bad interviewer
Because
If you come on his show
No no. Stop.
That's what I'm saying if you come up
I got this
I don't need to do any research
Yeah we're used to being attacked
For everything he says
I'm so wow he's wrong
Citing things like
Joel Stein
I think it's serious
Call Miss brat
Using that as a kind of like
Example
This kind of thing Seaside
He still has information
He still has like
I can
Defend myself against attack
I'm I'm ready
Is really funny
Because Alex sums up how he feels about the interview so far
News on the phone
But Alex Jones uses an expression I use very frequently
Myself I just don't want to get stuck
Thought-provoking
Discussion and debate with you
Ask you this question
Pushing out in the future
Where do you see the world in 20 years
These forces you say that are running things are successful
Versus the type of world that you
As a leader
Would like to see because
It's true that what they call Angie
So there's a real
F****** help
Well that's that that's one thing that's really important first what is called semitism
Slightly just
But then second
Keno's
But there is a rising tide
Of white supremacy and anti-semitism
Babies growing in the world
He can't say Niger
Everything way that we found that clip where he talks about knowing the Trump
Is Mob connected in 2015
Now we have evidence of 2015
Aaliyah wear
That there is a growth
The community
Even though he
Sister
The races
Is still Direct
Well
He would maybe say that
I mean it's a false flag
Semitism is just ask
Dividing us
Bigotry is really just a really
Sponson white people foolishly falling for globalist
Call stupid
But God.
A really every single time someone asked me how something's going
That's literally might dismissive answer when I don't want to talk about stuff
I would not
Very much
Little general
Superman
I wouldn't even give you a 37
Grade might get a non complete didn't finish the assignment
Also in his next life like I've been saying
They are
Very similar in terms of philosophy
David Duke is going to see some stuff
And really just imagine that you think
I think it makes things
Pretty clear
The real problem we have is not Isis threat me when you can have the Isis threat
Accept the fact that organized Jews
Appointment for the propaganda and the direct organizations and troll the critical
Clinical process
That literally opened our borders how much does that sound like Alex
Like especially that last part
Yep that's
Literally stuff that he would say
The globalist
I've opened our borders they left us open to attack
Isis isn't really a problem is the globalist to promise to us
Literally the same s*** he says
It's not
Man
Really
A lot how do you hate
What like I love it I love that life together is like
Love you
Yeah
For all the time
Yeah history has shown that might need to help each other
I want to make clear is the David Duke tries to also play this game where he's like
But they just propaganda and all Jewish organization
Arduous supremacist organization
All the banks are run by Jewish supremacist
Essentially it comes down to every liberal-leaning organization has Jewish Supremacy at its core
Which is what Alex would say about globalist
All liberal organizations are basically just
I didn't know
Try my best
To avoid
These people
Very hard
Because
Perhaps
The response that
You guys have seen
Yeah you're fluctuating between extreme anger and just staring at me
No you're not getting
Alright
Oh man
How can you say
I don't know
I've never
Everett
Experience
Even
Rid
Jewish supremacist
Things
Did the imagination
F****** ass
Well I think asked as he denied the Holocaust
That's cuz it seems like he's
Seems like he's in the intellectual
Holocaust denial tip
Like there were no gas Chambers
Not 6 million were killed
And why do we talk about all the other people who were killed
That sort of
That's sort of his cam
It's called denial but it's not like it didn't happen
Like what it like like 80 million Russians
Hitler was bad but why do we got to talk about the Jews all the time
No proof of those gas Chambers
Mom
Unfuk
Yeah
I think
That you grow up in a very bad environment
When you're 18
Joining the clam if you're in a situation where joining the
The clan
Is a possibility viable
That means you're not in a great place to begin with
So
That sort of environment breeds
Ascertain
Type of mindset
And then I would say that although David Duke is high-functioning
He's still not really all that smart
And in the same way that Alex doesn't understand things
Textbook is advocating for putting stuff in the water
David Duke is probably read a bunch of History than thought that there was something nefarious in it when there wasn't
So I think it's
Probably a combination of those things
Terrifying
Argument
That
That product
Have your
They're like
Terrifying
Because that
Forces you to look at yourself
What would I do there but the grace of God would that could that be
So much as I can
I think I have a better case for saying that I would be against
Because I already grew up in a cult
Right
Already got out of that one
But
Could be
F******
Anyone
Separate
Because they're not going to be
Nobody can make the Aldridge end up in some sort of militant black nationalist group
There are certainly those groups out there
I don't know I would rather join
I think
That
882 complicated
Equation
Cuz I don't think anything is strictly
Environment
You can just be born David Duke
You can be born with the potential to
David Duke
The surroundings
Could lead to a date
What time you got to
You got to do a lot of that work on your own
Yeah a certain kind of
Crafty
Yeah as opposed to any kind of a
Intelligence
It is
Base cunning
It'll be fascinating to me because I would never do this
I'm not going to
Yep
No
People donated to the show
I would never do this so don't even suggest it
Okay has his own radio
If we listen to it as much as we listen to Alex
We would find that
As a ten-year-old
He was trapped under a house inhaling termite fumes
I guarantee if he's as Lucid as language on his radio show
It makes everything make sense
I think there's probably something like that he had some sort of
Play frankly
Can I go on
Like not David Duke
I could listen to him
More than I already have
Now that I think about it
This close to quitting the show in the middle of this only got a little bit left to go then we'll never have to deal with him ever again
Alright
Yeah
Look
Alex Burton set up Alex bring that up in his responses
Choosing my name was my parents
Change it
You f******
Garbage
Pile of s***
David
But I'm still lost and thought about what we would do if Alex
Come down
They're still years of his show we can go through so no loss for
Continue reviewing
I give it a big
Clip
Alex Jones
It says something that I
Very strongly
Disagree with
Celebrity
More modern
Nope
Is
Bizarre
Flaming Lee corrupted
Jim Jones cult
So I just opened but I want to butt in here because Alex is very wrong
And if he wants to make the argument that by far the number one perpetrator of Terror
PC stuff is a problem and like you were saying about the
Interesting argument to be had there but Alex's examples that brings up her always lie
And this one is that same lie about
You can't say boy or girl you have to say Purple Penguin
This is the story out of Nebraska there was a gorgon
Justed
The teachers
But if you're going to be arbitrarily calling groups of children gender
Because you never know you could have
Send somebody
It doesn't say
Presented like they're outlawing boys and girls
That's not the truth of it at all
So he's basing
His
Letting white fascist groups off the hook
Because how much scarier PC culture is on lies
About this ascent
Of PC culture
Stupid
And other dangerous
And more arrogant
Left finally reaches
Clare gold
Huh
That's the
I'm sitting here talking to surreal
And you know why it's giving him a headache
He's
But he's f*****
Yeah
He can see it
He's giving a he's getting a headache because he's like
Goddamn
Bore base cutting
That was I think that right there
Is very least
Heard up
What
What do you mean
That idea of
People are talking about who owns
Or who run
As opposed to
Yeah
To me is that
Especially at this
Time that work
Covering this
That to me is like the moment
Trump starts
We're going to take the country
Yeah that is
Together they could be it could be
Cuz we're really seems like it would be a strong
Motivator
So you brought up political correct
I didn't Alex did
I mean in the context of Orwell
Whether or not
Arguments
And I would ask
Okay I think
One of the big things that
Michael correctness
Is
Trying
Accurately
What a word mean
Like because of that
Additional,
Like train
Like
What your what Your
Granny
Is if you are a
Good person
Yeah or if you're just like
Person who's using the word without malice
Lycon
Brightright
Means
This purse
Right
But if you are
One of them
Men
Who have
Really really
You use the word tree
And to you yes
It means
Transgender
Bright
Is
Victor big human
Inhuman
About political correct
You're really just adding
The connotation
To the word
I don't disagree with that at all
Yeah
But I think
V
I was the way I was approaching it is more the idea of what the other side would say
I like the premise of the other side
When I say there's a
Discussion to be had
I'm more memes that like
That's something I've endured
Oh yeah if the communication idea if there were someone trying to make
Said argument
We could have that conversation
I wouldn't agree with them but I am not going to be like
F*** you you're an idiot
Everything like that
Strongly
I talked to Alex I wouldn't
Record it secretly played on the last about how much of an idiot
Impersonal
I don't know I don't know if I have
If I genuinely have the balls
To do what I say I would do probably not not a chance
I don't know man
I'm very angry
Worked up into a frenzy probably
Do you not know how easy that is
I've noticed
But there's such a low bar to frenzy and then also a low bar
To get away
3 G of coffee and a little bit of credit
I'm so this next clip
Godot frostguard
It was next clip David Duke
Very literally makes an argument that Alex will use in the future
And it is
Just another complete mirroring of the two men
Americans and Canadians in European Europeans are literally being Jen
Genocide the real threat
Yellow people to Chinese people
Vance 1.3 billion of endoscopy 1.3 billion African this more than European
In the world while Europe
America and white countries are banded clock
And I'm telling you that it's not supremacist mm
It's not racism and hatred
To defend yourself from predators
And as you said earlier in the show if a tribe is being attacked by another tribe
And I try wants to
All the women kill the kids take over
Put them into slavery whatever
That tribe has a moral right to defend themselves and that's what I'm talkin about here are people
Are facing real genocide replacing loss of her own country
And most Americans most Americans watching this
Broadcast right now I'm absolutely sure you can have two
Figure out whether you agree or not before Father's is being totally write it out
You know that we're losing our heritage our values our traditions
You going to the store to go into the
A communities of our society you don't even look like you belong anymore you go in with spares of hatred against you
Maybe you'll get stairs of hatred because you're a very famous bigot
Maybe publicly
People look at you with hatred cuz of the things you said
Antibodies
Alex right there
European
He's just said why
The argument about
Tribes
And like of a neighboring tribe is
Coming in you got to kill him
He's made that argument very literally
And then all the stuff about the cut this country is not like our forefathers country
It's not our heritage
Alex uses terms like Birthright
And Providence
I'm stuff like that and it did just synonymous
It's they're making the same point
The same vision
The same arguments
With the only caveat between them being
What do we call the bad guy
It's it's so
It's so amazing
This idea that
Own
Americas Value
Like that's that's what I see so often
With all of these
It's always
It's not our values
The America
Cuz value
Which is such a lie
Rick
And that's that's
To me that is
The that is America
Regardless of our history
Which has been
Nightmare
It's trouble
The values
Were there from the
That that value
Even if it was not a
Applied
Which it most certainly was not
But that I value of all men are created
Americas Value
Government
Life liberty and the pursuit of happiness
Do all those things
Are really great idea
That
That's the value
Yeah
How many people have
That's America
Has been for so long that Kai
Kind of Beacon of like
I'm going to go to America
Because I've been a pretzel
Yeah cuz
I think
America is where I finally am go
Because of that ballet
Yeah
Our heritage is
F*** over everybody
But the idea
Control our values
Talk about the ownership of that space
As they say in the business world
It's really f***** up
I am I mean by this point
Alex is headache is probably getting worse
Are you going to see him just being flustered and being like
I do
I do recognize those words I think I'm going to stay in the future
Yep
What you talking about I hate the way you say it
But I love I love what you
I will probably just know that I agree with anything you say I will say right but I will
Stay warm
Now you need to put down for this one because Alex asked
David Duke straight up with the world be a better place without Jews
Do not play the
It's
Every society
I think I think absolutely these problems wouldn't be here except for the fact that because they existed
Because we let them take over but they didn't do it openly didn't say look we're Jews and we're going to control your Society
Deceit
And even an intelligent man if he thumbies puts poison in his food
He can be killed and that's exactly what they did with us
That's terrible
That is just
Terrible
Absurd that Alex
Who's letting him say these the
Michelle
I'm going to go pick my backup now
Sorry
Oh boy
Silent treatment
I'm trying
Yeah that's crazy
Advocating for killing all Jews or anything like that
Do you think that are they all
Jews are
Aaron Trickster
That money lenders
Implied inside that statement that he's making
There is a sense of inevitability that they will try and lie to us
To take over
I'm so
Even though he's saying
I'm not
A better place if Jews weren't around
I'm playing that inevitably they're going to get sneaky
And so yeah obviously
They shouldn't be around yeah
And that's really really really bad and the fact that Alex
Shining
Beacons of nevermind
Has ever lied and colluded with a
The foreign power
To take over
Yikes they're taking over our
News breaking
Probably as we record this podcast
I'm so
The thing is like Alex
Like I said earlier I'm not sure if it's wrong to have David Duke on your show
I don't know
It is very wrong to allow him to say stuff like that
I'm knocked out
And not be competent
In your rebuttal
And Alex
Is not
Is absolutely not
He allows David Luke to get away with saying these things
And
If you want any kind of estimation
How bad Alex is losing
Listen to this
They end up taking calls
This is the first caller
The calls in
Is defending himself a little bit
Remember you take the first
Call
I am
Missy
I don't think
I've never said we should go out and start killing black people or anything like that like they should have inside of them instead
Sebastian's not really
Louis Farrakhan
He said something I agree and I agree with any black person that wants to preserve their own heavy I will come on overdrive I'm going to spend
Whatever time we have a lot more to discuss.
Let's do it I'm ready to go
Via Skype you're on the
Hi Walter Williamston conversation and dialogue between e26 and fascinated
In the past year
Illegal immigrants
Miracles this year said that Germany population of 89th and take on 400,000 people from North Africa
In the middle because I'm wondering what the doctor thinks about this
I would love to hear his opinion about letting recruiting and lastly
Alex I love you man
I listen to everyday
What's the time in half you been super politically correct
So I just want to say that
Read
I appreciate Alex Jones having having me on
And and I I really do and it was
It's a courageous act on his farm
The Power Balance is entirely flipped
Yep. Callers are turning on him
Because
He had a good outing outside
Supremacy will Alex can't defend
But he can't stand up in this argument because it's abundantly clear that the only line of
Demarcation between them
Is
That
David Duke is willing
You to say what you mean
And Alex is
Alex Alex still has to apply it to caught up in dog language
Bring his peace
And I don't know maybe it is maybe it's not
They are well
You can see it with
With f****** Trump the real supporters
AR
Out now
I want you to say white people are better
Campaign they won't stay radical Islamic Terror
Right
But you know that's not that being politically correct
Didn't say anything
Errors
You know
People who we've murdered their families
Slipped and
The caller the way he presents things first of all that becomes Alex Jones is is like
It didn't straight mirror of his narrative
That all of these invading immigrants are taking
Places in our in our civilizations they shouldn't have
It's the caller is
Mirroring and
I had a Alex's narrative a little bit
David is so
Yeah he's so like
Listen I'm so grateful to Alex I am so happy that Alex
What do they take him out
I'm glad Alex let me
Come on and show and beat him like a b****
Yeah I've completely destroyed you on your own showed a nice pat on the back
I don't have any more clips
What happened because it's a mess
But
Alex
Tries a different approach
Because
He
Has failed
Though
He has a Jewish employee
No
She brings him out employees
I think Alex think
David Duke is literally afraid of Jews
Because he brings them out to make some points about Jekyll Island
And about the the Federal Reserve Bank
I'm stuff like that the big point that he tries to make is that like
Not all the people who met at Jekyll Island were Jews
People who ran all the big six Banks weren't necessarily all Jews
And it's not
Successful line of argument
You can see that Alex is like I can't win this
I'm going to bring in hired help
Yeah and so he tries to get
He brings in yet another unprepared person actually does a better job at least saying
But he still ends up looking like a
Cuz you can't you can't
Spar with David Duke
Come out looking good
It's not it doesn't work
He brings you down
Whatever level you been
And if you already agree in principle with the things he's
You can't win it all and I don't want to win
So how is
So that's one of the things
I
I think about
When we talked about life
Jakari Jackson or this guy
Like how do
Do you not
Get
That he
Is a Mastiff
The biggest like is it just
Like is it a gig is it just like
Is it like a pterodactyl in
It's all living like what it what is that
I think a part of it might be pretty strong contract
I think you might sign a two-year contract just
Nothing like that that's very difficult to get out of
I think also people
I noticed
The trend of very young people
Is like a early twenties when he started
Lee Ann McAdoo can't be much older than that when she started
RAB do
Actually Radu looks much younger than he is he was in
Is 30s
David nights
Just an idiot Jakari Jackson
With under 30
I think
People think that there's an opportunity to be had here and we're doing journalism
Play sign a contract get in
Realize f*** this is
Completely ruin my chances there's no way I could get a job anywhere else
And maybe they just assimilate a little bit
You know how whenever you're at a job that you're doing and there's a lot of negative things about it just kind of acclimate to it
You're like
Look what the bird until you start to like blind yourself to all the s*** that you don't like right
Just filter it out
Or Hugo native I think some people
Start to I mean Alex is for all
His problems
But your money
He is pretty
He is funny sometimes
And I bet off air heat there's moments when he's pretty nice
If you're young journalist
Aspiring journalist
It probably would feel pretty good to have
His approval
Maybe
My theory is a media operation
You can't create something like that
Without having some sort of charismatic
Pole with people
Well
Immediately following the crash
In 2000
As we all know
Is very tough
For young people to
Sure
And I mean
Fresh out of college you got a lot of college
Toothpaste
See this Infowars gig you don't really know
About me like a man
I got to get work
This is Oprah
Corset
But you're also both are discounting the fact that a lot of people
Do believe
Alex
And don't think that it's bigger
Because he pays lip service to we all bleed red blood
But that's not taking into account how
His action
Are very different
Covers
Like if there was
Criticism of an all black sorority
He never would have said the sort of stuff that he
He wouldn't care that wouldn't be on his radar
He's talked about it cuz it's defending
That's perfectly at encapsulation of
How has coverage work
But if you're already on board with the infowar
You might not see that
You might just be like
Another story about the Liberals run-amok
Maybe you can check yourself
Maybe
I like how plenty of people trick themselves into
Believing that the merchant
Sure
Or the Bible
Never rest
Parts of it are pretty bad
Great books like I said
Makes a big L
In terms of this interview
Better
But
I started listening to the episode on August 19th
Does the next day
Post game
Where are you trying to save a little bit of
And here is
Alex describing what happened
On the 18th
By David
Hillary Clinton first
But getting back to David, show for 2 hours
Less than 2 hours
Yesterday and
I wanted to have a serious discussion
You can't come on if I was civil and polite nice
I want to get Eman
Illustrate is lessons
Then what match yellow Raza
Racist black groups are saying
Northwood
It doesn't inside even just that sentence
Not as race
Racist
Aren't as bad as their race
Including
But you said larraza in there
Actively advik
Perkasie group for Hispanic
Populations are not a hate group
They are not a race
This group at all they provide Legal Services
Ford
A disenfranchised population
Them in
With the likes of David Duke
Is also very white
You betcha so anyway
Respect
What I came away with this
Disingenuous
What came away with was
I'm terrible at dinner
Making points
Okay so he says that no no
I almost did it
During the breaks out there
When he wasn't on area look like
And it really was creeping me out
Little Angel Eyes sweetie face
The dude
Help everybody
Are you cutting me short
And I'm not going to answer your questions are on the spinner
Pedophile
Looking
He wasn't playing mr. coetzee
Talking to some business people
I'm going to get into it last night
Oh yeah David
There's more than meets the eye with David
Oh really
What is it the
What do sweetie I is that enough real bad
Is
Has business interests in Austin
And even if the end of there that indicates
Like a very
Unprepared Alex Jones interview
If you didn't realize that David Duke was very successful
What does he know
That he knows he was a member of the KKK
Wizards are funny
Right that's about it extra
I'm because Alex
Dumb people
He allowed David Duke to be on
Lose an argument with him which only makes
And his listeners got
Mad at
For not agreeing with
If you were taking the temperature like
Interview it
You know you do wrestlers do
They come out and they take
Take a survey
Of the audience
Wrestlers do they come out like back in the NWO days is going to do like
Scott Hall would come out
How many people here love the NWO
I meant you could get a sense of what kind of crowd you were in front of
Is there people who were like
Cheering for the bad guys
And that sort of thing
If you take a poll
Basically or take a survey from that
Episode
The only answer that you can really draw is
Pretty much
I don't have the other Clips but the other callers were fairly similar
Like they were mostly you to agree about everything
I hate to see people in the alternative Patriot movement
About everything and disagree about a little bit
Not getting along so if you take that as
The survey
The audience
Like David Duke more than they like Alex absolutely
Butchers real bad
But they would do probably doesn't talk about chimeras a bunch
So Alex
Keeps his opposition
I don't know
That's
That's a powerful man
White supremacist
Sarah Haider
Done make him president
Why I insisted that we go over there
Even though I knew it was going to be bad and you were going to
And I'm sorry
The reason is
I think
That
I don't know I don't know how to put this exactly
At the beginning
The 7th
Alex is still on the I don't really trust Trump
Even though
He is now attacking the clintons and that's great
He's still
Literally saying I don't endorse
He's still there
He has an interview where he gets cucked out on his own show by David Duke
And he's forced to I'm telling you
Don't watch it
Cuz it's really long
And David Duke says even worse things than we played here
But if you do watch it and you can watch Alex Jones's face
He's having a miserable time
Because he's faced
Too Faced with the reality of his beliefs
And whether he realizes that or not he internalized something
David Duke was one of the first people that came out and really supported Trump
I think that there is a
Conscious thing that happens
Possibly
That wants David Duke starts advocating for Trump
And
Using a lot of
The same arguments that he makes on Alex's show
That we live in doing this episode to support his belief in Trump
Something resonates without
Yeah do you not think it's more likely that it's
The fact that he
His listeners
Steamed Berry
David Duke
Maybe that forces Alec
Move further to the right
It's possible but if I were Alex
By the way I do mean right
In saying that
When you get further right
You're a white
Yeah really far right are there
The farther right Hugo
Eurowise
No
Here's what is i r Alex
I would rationalize the callers Away by saying
They knew he was going to be on my show that jam my lines or something like
It's pretty simple to to rationalize that
I mean I know he couldn't rationalize
If he were explaining it
You know that
But I genuinely
Just in the same way that
His sources are caller
Yeah I think he's pushed
Buy collars
I think whenever a caller comes in buying the goddamn pills
He's a big dumb idiot
True like
Whenever I'm Taylor
Whatever color says
You've been very politically
Alex
Yeah I love you but you politically correct
That because you just
Accused Alex
Something
He hates more than
Amman
That he's
Not
Politically
Right but I think that's a way that he can get through that and gets around that it's the next day on the 19th him saying
Kind of being a f******
Weirdo
He's creepy and he scares me
Brett so he can be like he was being manipulative and I was creeped out
Again
Talking about what he's talking about on his
Fright about Alex
Who's running his
But I still think that he could feel that
Like I think you could feel the
I got it back by making fun of Duke the next day
Okay
I think so but I'm not sure I do understand what you're saying
And you may be right
I don't know
That hurt you
Poseidon
Alright
You win 10
I don't know man
And when we started this investigation I certainly did not expect that we would run into a f****** to our interview with David Duke
Is not what I was expecting to
Discuss but I really wanted to do this and get it out this week
Yeah because this is been impeding my investigation
I really have to yell at you
No
I knew that this was a hurdle we were going to have to get over it was stopping me from
Being able to enjoy whatever happened
So f***** up
It's so f***** up
Anybody with any insight
In Alex's position
Listening to David Duke
Say the exact same things that he believes
But stay
Jews instead of globalist
Would have a crepe
Or
Would expect
And have a good argument to rebut the fee
Be closer to the prior than the latter
But he's not really doing either
Cuz he doesn't give up on the globalist narratively f****** know that
He didn't defend himself well
Right
Question
That I'm I'm
Because David Duke
Has been on
Yeah he's been interviewed plenty of time O'Reilly
At 5 and
Even if you are pushing
Like
What what is better
Is it
Is it a don't feed the trolls approach where it's like
Just don't have them on your f***
I think so
Like even if you
Go line-by-line
You fuking idiot this is why you're dumb
This is every single thing that
Not only debunked
But can
Condemns and destroys all of your
And
On top of that
Your
Personally
A bad
And I mean that
In the sense that
You are
Evil you are immoral
Dammit
And hurting other human being
Exactly
From this episode
Giving his
Thought
A
I think I've January my response to
The Megyn Kelly Alex Jones
Before we were doing that in our preview episode
I was kind of on the side of like
Well maybe it is a good idea
It's a kind of shed some light on this
And let everybody in the world know
Look at this
Idiot this is the avatar
Star of the alt-right
This bubbling
Mereba leaving months
Easter seal
Hate the real face
Behind all of these people that we are afraid of be
Because their violin
Stupid
There there
You're f******
That
They're just petulant children
That we should just f***
We looked at the Meg
Kelly interview
Yeah but I think that not giving a platform is the best thing to
To do probably because
I was reading an article about this and it made a really good point
And
It's essentially a situation where
Respectable people
People with
Journalistic ethics
Are not prepared to deal with people like this
Because they don't have rules
Any rules
Ratso
Megyn Kelly comes and it talks to Alex Jones revamp
She didn't
Expected he would
Turn it into a whole Narrative of his own
She didn't expect that he would Bluff that he taped the whole thing
And start lying about it
You know it
You like
Alex Jones didn't care about the interview itself
Like we've speculated
There's something on that tape you was worried about
Yeah but he didn't care about the interview
As much as he cared about these the interview was done allowed him
To create
A giant narrative Arc
And
Megyn Kelly was making a story
Alex Jones was making
Story was making hay out of that
Of course Megyn Kelly got 10 minutes
That were pathetic
Nobody wanted
The funniest home videos
Whereas Alex.
Weeks upon weeks
Program
Lyrics to pain weeks at Fordham Court
Mainstream media's full show
Alex
Definitely one that one
Alex defeated Megan in the way that
David Duke defeated Alex
I think they probably have comprable audiences
David Duke and Alex
There's probably a very interesting very circular Venn diagram of that
Jakari Jackson is the only one outside of the bed.
So I don't know I don't know if it is a thing were denying him a platform is really irrelevant
Concern
But I think that the more the better thing that I would say about it the more accurate
Is
If you let him on your show
You stand a chance of losing to him
And then
You've lost
Cuz I know that I could
I think I could conceivably make better points
David Duke
Yeah I think I could
I would never debate him I would never talk to him
Be in the same reason I would never have a serious debate with Alex Jones
Cuz they're both slippery
They're both due to lie about
And if someone if you're in a debate with someone and you have a bunch
Back view of your argument
And they throw out some historical fact
That's really
Skewer and probably alive that you just haven't looked
And make a huge deal out of it
Do you might end up appearing to lose a debate
You just
David Live Well I mean look at the
Mediate covers truck
Like they're unprepared for somebody who doesn't live even Within
Doesn't give a second
Society
They can't deal with a president
Tuesday
Intrude like they've been
Trained to respect
The office
And they can't deal with somebody who
Couldn't give less of a s*** about the
About you
You doesn't care about the
Truth
F******
Care they don't get that so to them
Okay our job is to cover
The Press
Wooden reality if you're dealing with somebody like that
Your only real job
Fox them
Force them
To abide by your rules
Can't understand
Right I think there's a chance that you know David Duke wasn't forceful about it but I think that's what he
He did a little bit on this episode
Are any any
Aware and decently smart
Observer
Would see that
See Alex Jones essentially
Having to admit
But his beliefs have roots in it
And we've said hola
So here's my thought
Blind-spot
Can closing work
That's all right.
Here is my plan
If I am
If I'm in control of the media
Here's what we do
All of this s*** that Trump is doing like we're not allowing cameras into the depressed free
Taking all of that
Stop covering Trump
.
No tweet
No nothing
You only talk
To the Senate
And the house of
About the healthcare
What's about
That's all you do
How long before Trump
Explode
He has to have attention pretty quick
Yeah and he would end that would be only move that's your only
But you're only plan of attack against people
Who cannot help
Cannot be
Held within those bow
Your only plan of attack
Is 2 take away the one thing that they care
And that is
Attention Trump it's just that
So what about Alec
How do you take away what Alex wants
OU
Or you just can't
Recently tweet at him is that him and Gwyneth Paltrow agree about supper
Yeah maybe
Hey Alex you know what you're selling your selling your selling poop yeah you're selling like mungias or what
You're a trendy
Right oh my God
You're a
Liberally
F****** trendy a******
But just with a different name
You are a
Exactly
If you want you can check us out at knowledge fight.com
College underscore fights
Facebook
Well Facebook under knowledge fight
Leave a review it's always nice to get reviews
Also it's one of those things where
It's super cool.
VR audience grow
And one of the ways to do that is just by leaving reviews on iTunes
Algorithms Fuqua
You can leave a review on Facebook that helps somewhat but who knows
It's all a mystery to me
About
Look globalism is not the same thing as antisemitism
To me that argument is dead
Agree with David
Yeah
That
Do you know what
What is one thing that is not dead
What is not dead
Before we do this B
Wait wait are you saying we were setting up a bit
Okay I just wasn't completely natural episode of
WTF Marc Maron
Okay you don't listen to that show regularly right
Yeah and I've lived a long time
I didn't realize that the end of
WTF
Marc Maron scream Boomer lives
No s*** no that's alright
All right now we got to figure something else out I was going on
Is 2
Pro Skater rapper Korean Tampa
He had a song called it was like
Couple rap songs pro skater
Wem
Okay there's a reference to that I just realized there's a podcast in reference people think
I got so scared when I heard that it was like
All right we'll do you know what are
Rapport
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work