I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge
Monica
Knowledge fight
Nick.com
Text Joe
For you
My bright spot today Jordan is wrong
This is our after Sesame Street
Episode
Okay there's something in life
Sometimes things are going to worry about it then it's not really that big a deal
You start doing stand-up one of the best things that can happen is your first bomb
And you're really really worried about it then you do how do you do it how do they live like this you go through it
Experience how horrible it can be to be on stage in be like
They hate me nothing is happening here only hating me person then you go to bed
Wake up the next day and you're fine
You know like it
I have a reminder that experience
Are you think
The people who caught this because it
Cripplingly embarrassing
What our last episode Alex was
Talking about North Vietnam
And I swear I could
I heard him say North Korea
And I responded as if he had 90
Oh my God that was embarrassing a I went along with you so eggs on my face as well
Q&A bad helper
I'm here for support
He's not getting in the way I've tried to like analyzer
Next happened
Dolittle
Trincity North Korea
I think I've been listening
2003 South Andes
Singularly preoccupied with war with North Korea
I think I was
Is this North
Going to be North Korea
It's pretty remarkable to me
Experience
Realizing
Oh my God
I couldn't hear him say the right word
Yeah I know it's weird
It's okay
Nothing
Nobody's nobody's hurt
Everybody's everybody's doing just fine
The folks who emailed me about another bright spot
Everybody was like
Hey I'm sure this was a normal accident that
We all make me
Mistakes all the time Turtle transparency I'm bringing this up now because I cut it out of the past
Episode of the last episode reposted
Because I kind of felt like
I know how this goes like I'll still get emails about
Chumbawamba
I don't I don't want to correct they thought they were
I guess we got there the next episode
Yeah I know and I just don't want to have more lightning rods for that so
I just called myself episode
I said what's your B.
My brights Montana's I got my new tattoo
It's really really great
I was this
So I'm probably
15 to 20 somewhere in that range
Whataburgers like eight or nine different artists
This was the first guy where I was like
Oh this is not a guy who does
Just tattoos is not a tattoo guys are they
He's at like
Sponsored by people in
The guy
And as he was doing the tattoo you don't have sometimes you're like
What's that but there's not that much of a
Difference between yeah that kind of
This is a 95 mile an hour fastball I get to 80 mph where you're like okay there's a whole different world
I got it
Minecraft yeah yeah yeah
Is my guy now here
Amazing
I'm still still great I love all my other tattoos to break out
I love all my other tattoos to their fantastic but this guy was
The alternative would have been
You're not happy with it
That's implied that
This is the act of the follow-up
Because what I did was mirroring the other side seems it was
It's fairly simple to just go okay well he wants
Something like that bird on the wrist
Bird on the other side of the wrist
And then but the way that he just handled
The coloring in the shading in the way that he put all that
Just so good I'm excited to see plastic comes up
Today we are going to be talking a little bit about
The present-day of Alex Jones Show
24th
I was so ready.
How old are you
Quiet
Quite the Machinery whatever the answer is
This is this is this week
I wanted to check in and see how things were going.
Tuesday Alex's
Coming off of a very disappointing
Trump rally
Yep where you said the people to give axe
Happy about that
Hayden Lake Jackson
Simultaneously Owen Shroyer is turned himself into the
The feds
I don't know
I do like I do like the idea of trump being like in this headspace of like
What are all these idiots mad at me I just told them to get the vaccine like clearly having no idea that this is entirely
He's like what are you guys
Can't believe it
So
I mean you encourage an audience
In certain direction and then you
Directly contradict what they believe you to believe
And then sometimes they're going to be
We're going to get to business on the 24th but before we do Jordan let's
Take a little moment say hello.
Some walk first
Zebra one thank you so much
I'm a policy 101
Actually we forgot the
The sort of subtitle
All of their name
Oh yeah it was North
Zebra
Nam no no no no
This is Rapture princess versus Obama Decepticon and then the tagline or the subtitle
Roommate mix
I'm a policy wonk this is
I will be really funny to hear me drive
So thank you so much are podcast Blanco dealer Nueva Ultra Direct
Director I was so close to really doing great
2 km
But most people abbreviated
The chaos but I'm not going to judge
I wasn't the KN in bed and now I can't fall asleep without dance
Some Jordans
Money off that heroin
Ashley large
Stop listening to go to bed
Ocean waves occasionally
Punctuated by a pterodactyl Screech
Hold on hold on
I'm going to do something
Sweet dreams
Go to sleep
You're at peace
Thank you to someone who is selene's family
Type beat
Has adopted
I have two I wrote it out
Phonetically
What is a Pangolin
Pangolin
Sounds like penguin
Not penguin old
For some reason whenever I see that word I want to add like two syllables in the middle of it
I keep finding myself
Penguins win
Play y'all know this is
AOL
Yeah thank you so much for 4
Adopting
Define armadillo creature
I guess what you say
Cute girls
All God's creatures the represented
The leads through
Here we are on the 24th
Here's where Alex is at as we launch
We set sail
There is incredibly beautiful opposition to the
84 proportions
SIU Place cross the world
You're going to find out who's for slavery and who isn't
I don't lionize Bill Maher Bill Maher
We had listeners take over
Do it I'd order
Wife
Eliza
I supported
Take over his life studio audience a couple times
If I was blown up
When you get things right
Don't block Ivermectin
Internet down
I really be curious
To know if when Politically Incorrect I cancelled Alex
Was speaking out on behalf
Abbeville mall that you should Wonder
I don't know
Increase might not have been on the air
Yeah
I don't know I'd be curious about that but I don't have any of those those episodes
Maybe he wouldn't have even mentioned it
So this is one of these instances here this clip where Alex begins of thought that he ramble so much that the second half of the 8th
Then statement.
Totally lost
He doesn't like Bill Maher but when he says things that Alex perceives is true
Alex's got to support it
I fully agree with that under normal
Circumstances
Princeton's
I think Alex is a lazy dumb fraudulent buffoon and I hate his worldview with a passion
But
I do agree with him about civil asset forfeiture
We may arrive at our positions differently
And we may never actually be able to work together toward
Opposition to this thing that we
We share opposition towards
I can understand that even the person I think is the worst
Can be in alignment with my beliefs on occasion
It's possible that a fundamental level
The government shouldn't
Steal from you seems very obvious
That's not what's up with Alex and Bill Maher
I don't believe the Bill Maher is one of the main mouthpieces of the globalist conspiracy on the media
Alex constantly claims that quote
The last door
The globalist
Have made some announcement of their
Plant and the only thing he has to back it up is a clip from Bill Maher's show
The entire narrative that the left wanted to crash the economy in order to punish drop
I just got a bad joke
The bilmar made
And I guess maybe a bad dream that Alex had
The explanation for why Bill Maher is now saying things that I look
Disagrees with is not a simple matter of someone you don't like has the same perspective as you do on a point
If anything Alex says means anything said bilmars on the global
The payroll would never be allowed to say the sort of thing
That Alex is now applauding him for saying if he was saying those things
He is a shield for the global as soon as can
Controlled opposition there's simply no way to trust him
Because he's working for the global
Perhaps
The issue isn't as easy to dismiss as just saying like I got to give it up
Bill Maher has larger contradiction and Alex's ignoring in that is
The bilmar works for the devil
Devil remember all those times whenever people would like
I know gurbuz does a lot of that
He's really said nice things about me so I got to give it up
Sehitlerimiz
Who's Alex says like he's the official mouthpiece of the globalist
What is trying to say is I don't like
I suspect that Alex knows that he showed look really pathetic if you replaced all the ink
Intrigued and supposedly documented
Conspiracies
But just him whining about how he doesn't like people at certain ideas
That's pretty much what's underneath
Need the entire show it's pretty remarkable
Examples
The people being mean to
Now I will tell you why I don't like them
There's a document in the white papers that I think this guy's pretty
Cool guy
Is this clip from Bill Maher show that is like pretty encouraging
F*** are we doing
Now they want us to do all boost
The boosters Wichita
Xander
I mean I don't want a booster item
I never wanted the vaccine
By the way
You know doesn't get a lot of vaccines
Millennials millennials
20/20
I don't want it they wanted they don't think they need it they're probably right
I told him I didn't want it either
Took 14
But a boost every eight months you're going to put that s*** in me I don't know about
Maybe I don't need one
I don't want a one-size-fits-all
My body may be different in your butt
Nothing screams hip like a 65 year old dude who knows a lot of millennials
Oh my God
Chesterfield billion on I-20 roads are millennials
We're old now
Also there's no reason to just conclude the booster shots
For covid-19 48-month
A lot of times people are recommended to get booster shots are vaccines on a two
Particular schedule like
Like every 10 years
What's going on here is the bilmar is falling into the same trap that the right-wing media is exploiting where they take the
Cdc's announcement
The people who are 8 months
Their point of full vaccinations
Could be eligible to
To get a booster shot
Mmm reporting that is if it means the people are going to need booster shots already
Slots forever
That's a lazy conclusion
To come too and I understand life
Hypertonic conversation that plays on Bill Maher show
His whole brand is like trying to be edgy
Sort of funny and
Gently iconoclastic so
This is exactly how he would have that talk
Just not a serious point
Department Health and Human Services put out a press release discussing the option of getting a booster
Rashad and it's exactly that
An option
It'll offer greater protection but there's no indication
Mission for the text to anyone's going to be required to take a
Some people
Like dr. Celine gounder of the
NYU medical school
They're little bit wary of the booster
To plan but not for the same reasons as Alec
And some dump dump
Bucktail bar
Calgary plane to NPR
Vaccines need to be thought of
Population-level interventions
Also from the article
She argues that getting a higher percentage of people that
Animated wheel protector
The community board
The giving already vaccinated people Edition
Because it provides
Community immunity
Which reduces the amount of Ira
I think she's clearly forgotten that we don't give a s*** about community and I only care about myself give me
Protection and no one else
Another voice criticizing the plan is Doctor Mike Ryan the head of the World Health organization's Health emergencies program
Writing makes me very solid point that there are tons of people in the developing world who are in need of vaccine
Enterprise
Planning to hand out extra life jacket
It's the people who already have life jackets and leaving other people
The brown
There's a lot of intertwined issues the touch on this planet have booster shot campaign to the United States but
All of the actual reality
Hastings have nothing to do with it
What these idiots
Alex
Bill Maher make their careers
Complaining about
There's there's real There's real discussion
To be had
It's not these
That's such a great analogy
That's such a great analogy because
Is it so f******
Airtight like I imagined somebody
Hearing that guy say it to their face
Isn't going like
Why we try me when you put it like that it does sound bad
Okay
Food with other than like
Yeah you're right
Buck
I think the best argument you could have to that it was sort of like
Staring at the person quizzically
Closed
The door
Little bit of yelling
He likes to
Animated for
Kids having
Underwear mask
No it's not no no I mean it's directly there.
So you're holding us hostage
You're the Reason
Two-year-old got to wear mask
People through you
We should count in law there's enough of a pause there that I bet somebody in a
Is your peace just went
Yeah exactly know if somebody's like
Alex if you would
Include that in the in a f****** trial and they're like wealthy he said it at the end
F*** you
You you know he didn't mean that f******
Sojourn
I have a question
This is time for knowledge fight Infowars quiz
So what's the plan
Okay
Everything you know about
The covid conspiracy that I
What is the
What does it lead to
What is the end goal of all this
For the global
I believe the globalist want to wipe out 90% of the population and then
Quipe utopic
State just for themselves
After the devil
What station is
Settled
I'm not even positive I'm going to do they want to get off-planet now
But I don't know how permanent that is forever
Solution
You got to get off
And they're working with
Extra dimension
No beings who I assume have promised them
Take it off
So
Yeah they're just trying to get rid of us
That's so towards the end
The covid thing is
To kill off most of
The population right
No no the code thingy to get us
Take the vaccines
Taqueria La famosa
The population
Right good clarification
Apparently not
Apparently this is all just to cause a financial collapse
Government on TV
Only God cuz they're getting ready for a total
Financial collapse
We really should just talk about that because
Tomorrow ization is poison shots
News today
I don't even give that to you tomorrow
What's coming next to the total collapse because
Brazil time to mitigate how bad it's going to be but not much
What
Yeah man so it's apparently all about the summer of Rage
There's still time to mitigate
Bunker I don't know
This is just
This is nonsense
Yeah like this is secretly actually
About
Precipitating a Global Financial collapse of his head for a while
The vaccines and the killing off of
The population is a financial collapse
Misconception is that the financial collapse is supposed to cause civil unrest which allows for a Crackdown
To the extermination of the population
That's
You can't have
A leading to be but you also leads to a
Let me let me try and visualize this better for you
So
This is like a perpetual motion machine of
Conspiracy
Alright so he's got a pot
Apocalypse's every morning
Lined up
The starting line
Write like a horse race
And every morning whoever wins the horse race
Is the globalist final plan
If if it's like
Well we got the appointment everybody
And that's the day
You know and then the next morning
It's a new race
Did you ever see that web series Brody Stevens interview challenge
It was as if it was a web series where Brody Stevens
Pennswood interview
And
There was a mysterious man
Who was pulling the strings who would give Brody Steven
Challenges
But he had to accomplish during the interview
It's like
Brody Stevens so great was he couldn't let Pat and eat bread
And there's bread all around there's bread all around
Set up to make for warriors as
I like to imagine that maybe
Alex wakes up every morning
There is like the shadowman there
The apocalypse today
Cockatoo make
I like that show point that reference
To Brody is a good one
Alex plays this
Bill Maher clip
And that takes up a good part of the beginning of
Another clip
It's very important
We also get
Its 2 here in this sub is open
Info that the vaccine is safe
Activate needed and is
Matter
Courage Your
Coronavirus vaccine
No
Get the vaccine
I think that's a matter of choice
All individuals
That's why we live in
Don't trust vaccines
Hey lady when's the last time you visit your gynecologist
Keep your medical records
He's got his medical record number your body your choice
My body
That's really weird I'm going to go as a reject that
Cherry picking stuff from the CNN interview with Brett Favre
Instant Alex's conveniently cut out this little nugget
Get from the interview
And in this is from experts experts
From both sides
And
The vaccine or
Maxine
I've been has been administered it within the last
What's 6
Didn't go through
20 or 30 years human trial study
FDA
Requires
So
We're sort of
Trials if you will
Alex probably doesn't
Want to play a clip like that because it makes bread sound like what he is
Ex-football player who doesn't really know what he's talking about
Trying to Bluff his way through a fairly polite TV interview
Also
It's probably in Port
Brett Favre wasn't on CNN to talk about his vaccines
Suspicions that was just something that came up
He was on because he recently put out a PSA urging parents not to let their kids
Play tackle football
Because of concerns about CT
Teehee
In 2018 far-field Megyn Kelly that he probably had thousands
Concussions over the
Expand his career
This leaves me and really if you territory
On the one hand I applaud far for speaking out and trying to
Protect the Next Generation from suffering head trauma and potential brain damage
But on the other hand I think if he's doing it while he's also spouting b******* about covid vaccine
I worried that he might not be the best
Concussion awareness ambassador
Big picture I'm not really sure I care about what a former football player says about medical advice on AT&T
TV show that I don't watch
Apparently for Alex Jones the most serious chronicler
The collapse of Western Civilization
This is big news
I can't stress this enough
If you are someone
Who is played
Professional football
And has received the number of
Concussions that Brett Favre has
Which is astronomical
He said when I was when I watch football he was playing and yeah
I believe it
I believe that kind of number from him
He should talk about concussions
Do you know what somebody who has had thousands of concussions doesn't know about
Vaccines
That's just how it goes
I'm fine with that
Amount of
Feeling on my part that like
I don't know how much
That was what he planned to talk
So maybe that's
Just on a poorly structured interview
What he thinks about that at all not relevant
What you think about a post route
Concussion movie End Brett Favre
This is kind of embarrassing
It feels like the headlines on out to show her just kind of boiled down to improving Twitter for a few clips of things that are
Kind of in pop culture
Lenny just yells about them for a few hours
Like imagine the opposite version
How seriously would you take an ostensibly left-wing truth-teller who insisted they had all the details about the
Nefarious plans of the right-wing
Weirdly took most of their time on their show Court
Points made on like Greg Gutfeld show where people are trying to be funny
I am celebrating something like I don't know
Randall Cunningham or John Elway saying that vaccines are cool
If someone took their time like really thinking that these were important like these are headlines we need to really focus on
You look pretty f****** stupid
Yeah we're staring down the barrel of
Climate change extinction level event
First I got a s*** ton of guys on the morning Zoo crew
Look
90 am up my butt
Red Wings got some really in the Feria things but in good news
Dan Marino likes to recycle
What
Oh damn
Next clip Alex
Teases that he has a guest coming up
Exciting
Political prisoner
Owen Shroyer
Will be joining us
Coming up
Is he ignoring us 45 minutes of the
4th power
He was only in jail for about 45 hours in the federal jail
Yesterday
And the judge put some restrictions on him
Two people involved January 6th about the
Okay
How do you use a talk show host everything you did is on body cam
So what we did is he is giving his all right
This is not good
I'm a good idea
I think what are you should
All right now
And you're going to say no
Stick with me through the end
Okay then
Stinky does he comes out
Any places a million-dollar bounty on whoever
This is work
Yeah I think
This is such a testament to how minor the situation with
Petfinder
Go back on TV
No one cares
What a political prisoner gestapo State we live in where
He had to be processed
A couple of hours and then
He is free to
Go back to work on a propaganda you know it was really strange when I read about it that
Cuz we all know the story of Nelson Mandela
What was so strange is that he only had to go to jail for like 45 hours
Like most political prisoner
Yeah
It's fighting against the power but it's often forgotten that's what the Mandela effect actually refers to
Dude against the guy that's kept him
Under house arrest for two years because he fought against they're destroying a population
But you know what
He's still allowed to go on his goddamn radio show
Yeah but I hate
And I think one of the other things that really is important it is going to come up whenever Owens on
Michelle
Is that like
Whatever
The cases
He's being allowed to profit
His arrest
If you're Alex
You have to get like some
Bad news
Your boy got popped
He's going to that he's going to the clink
Going to be doing a hard bed
You tell me I'm Alex you tell me
Hey alright you can be out
Text Alex
Just real quick I just want to let you know I was arrested
And don't stop
Stopping the nose
Yeah anyways I was arrested
For January 6th
I am going to do almost
0 jail time
Bring me Lee Ann McAdoo
Replace you demented
Alex Jones
No I got to get this bad news is maybe going to be in
Convenience for a couple hours
Not going to make it
Your son's
Baseball games to make matters worse you have to see the last
Sono Bella braided on Twitter
Celestron very upset
Very very very upset
To learn
Owen
I was not
Taking away to DC to be put in solitary confinement there's
Literally it is named trending yesterday so did mine
In the top 10 of a Twitter
When the people wishing for his death
Evil wishing for his execution
I don't even hate these weird people on
Another word for excuses all the time
Sorry for because
They are such a Thor attarian
There
Like a mob wanting to exact revenge on those of us
I'm just simply trying to save the country is very sad
Wow could you get more protective
Then that
It's pretty fun
Wow
Again it's just it's just it's a remarkable thing of like I saw a random tweet
Maldives the doctor in position of the left
I know I know but to stand next to the
The people on the sick
When that happened
And then to turn and look at the left and say
They're just a mob
Wild
Wild s*** Wild
Do you know Alex Jones you know that he likes two things
Talkin
Going off air
Powerful
John bowne reports they've been doing lately and
I enjoy talking on the show
What's the same time we get really really powerful reports and things in
And so we're going to play August report right now
Play I love I love to take a little break
Is not doing
We'll be right back
So Alex
Covid news
Here's one from Forbes
Mustache
I done lost it
Pfizer shot just 39
Percent effective
Against, now all my gosh 39%
But you heard it work so well first of all I just love the way Alex answer
Surprised by articles
But he sees that headlight me like oh look
It's like you found something
I mean you know for somebody who does so much research
It's it's always nice to be surprised by the research you've found something under a rock
Excited
Second this isn't the new article
This is a month old piece that was going over some data from Israel where some indications were showing that the Pfizer vaccine was about 30
39% effective
By protecting people
From covid
Including the Delta Fair
But Alex is intentionally only telling half
Story
The same Forbes article also covers have these included a finding that the vaccine offered 92% protection against off
And 91% protection
Severe illness
Intentionally ignoring
The part of this article that
Discusses the other research that is
Conflicting numbers on
General efficacy
Of the VAC
Do not adjust Alex's cherry-picking
The detail from a month old article and ignoring the rest of it in pretending that it's
Tomorrow's news today or a month ago news tomorrow yesterday
It's tough because what you want the headliner the article.
2B is the Sun
So you know like
90s summer percent chance that you won't get sick or die so you know what maybe the vaccine doesn't print
Protect against the virus forever perfectly but you know what you're not going to get sick and die so
Pretty good overall
And that's just too long for a headline
It's it'll be tough
Get that into like MLA grammar headline is what that
That is yeah so long for
Specifics talking about specific
Because there are the things that you're able to really
Assess more than his
Fauci should be hung
Whatever
Just drift into the
Can't believe those bloodthirsty people on the left a loop
Want violence to happen gross unbelievable
25 seconds
Specifically
Is it conspiracy theory that mothers
PetSmart not a selfie
Natural
Colostrum
Most births are cesarean
Asleep
How to make
Two statements
The Weeknd
Here we go most people give birth by C-section
And most people don't breath
According to data from 2019 C-section rates in the United States are approximately 31 per
Does a bit shy of the most people
A lot of folks I can find commenting on this Tuesday that the rate is too high
And it's very unlikely that all of these represent necessary
C-section
In many cases
They're absolutely necessary but apparently it's also an area where there could be intentional or unintentional
Applications
At the medical
Conservit
For one thing
Many hospitals have unlimited space for people in labor
And in the interest of making sure that they can cater to all their patient
It's possible that some doctors could do more C-sections
Gyms that are strictly necessary
In order to keep
Space open
So maybe those stories were it's like
28 hours and labor are also
What they're leaving out is that that's because the doctor didn't have anybody coming behind base
And if he needed the space maybe I would have been in labor for 6 hours and got nafisa
Maybe maybe is a
Just saying that that's
That's now in my brain
Before an article in the Atlantic points out how data seems to indicate that a lot of the prevalence in C-section
Can be attributed to this type of behavior
If there's any doubt that the culture of individual hospitals can have an effect on a on a
Choice of a C-section
One only need observed that hospital C-section rates vary from 7% to seventy percent
Differences in patient
Complexity
Cannot account for that spread wow wow capitalism to the rescue again
Issues that are related to fix
Hey Mike the doctors get for performing as opposed to a vaginal delivery
Apparently C-sections net around
It is much as 15% more per surgery
So there are some
Confounding factors that are
This is this is where we go back
Back to the ship
Mayonnaise
Face level of corruption it would be as easy to f*** around
You know some of this is
Understandable even possible is
The subconscious corruption doesn't even need to be like
Intentional scam
There are things that people could
Just said
It just said operational pressure of not even not being told ever once like hey we need this bed we need to get
Get this out you got to do the C-section but just like
A constant awareness
We're running low on hospital beds
There's all this stuff going on the budget's tight
Hey all this stuff is in the back
Is mine and that happen
Humanity
What is the culture of individual
Okay thanks
Some places may have more
Pressure
The effects
Treatment hey when the bottom line is profit treat
When's going to supper
A lot of interesting issues to unpack as it relates to the issue
C-sections
Completely wrong about the numbers and he's also wrong about the idea.
Child
Breastfeeding
The CDC releases an annual breastfeeding report card for the United States
Do that a thing like that existed or why
You can find the 2020 report card and if you do you'll find that 84.1% of Americans who gave birth
In 2017 breastfed over 25%
Exclusively breastfeeding
For the first 6 months
The call the action on this report card includes both quote
Celebrate state of treatments and breastfeeding and breastfeeding
Supportive matern
Ready Care practices and quote
Bring together partners
To promote and support breast
It's so weird.
The CDC will be
Be saying I sent there an evil globalist Behemoth and they want to kill everyone
So weird almost
Everything Alex says doesn't mean any
If they didn't say
And if what they did say actually confirmed
The opposite like I shouldn't trust with Alex's
Also just for fun the top seven states in terms of their score on the m
Pimc scale
The maternity practice isn't
Christian Care
They're all blue
Stop California New Hampshire Massachusetts
Walking Rhode Island knocking it out of the park with the score 95
Take me home
Swear if Alex
News
Like he actually do it
He would have a complete different angle is like how dare these blue States come and tell me how to raise my kids my breast for
I believe in capitalism and I support the formula industry
I want more C-sections because the bottom line is suffering
Mike Lindell has a my formula he's putting out
The point is nothing Alex
Complete to be saying at the globalist
The man and the government they want a breakdown the relation
Humans have with each other they don't want you to breastfeed I want to make you a dumb
Oh that's just based on nothing
So this this was my thought was pretty funny
More more
Information
We should talk about the spirituality and God and
How to get out of the trench in
Ways to break
Conditioning
What whether you're old or young or black
Wife
Are male or female or where you live
Real thing is
It's a growing process and I'm not perfect either
Respond to bash liberals it's fun to get mad at a minute
Stupid they are but that's a reflection on us about that
Wow
Other than conscious demons
A funeral Gates
Very top of but mostly people
Are scared to belong to something
And I know deep down that it's a fraud so they're shared
11 nice way in
You know try to get people
Our side that way
Because I've had the big Brash approach that's been successful a lot of people
Dodge related on my heart
We need to just get back
Really want to be bullying
We'll evaluate Humanity really caring about everybody
Realizing that
Love is the answer
Love Is The Answer quotes Alex I swear to God
I swear to God
I'm throwing baseballs at everybody
55 G
That's insane you know what I
Here's the other thing that I just that just occurred to
So the people who Alex
The people who follow this far right
Specifically
Like
Do they realize
How close
These people would
C C-section to abortion
Like very quickly
Like if they got rid of abortion
They're going to have to pick something else
Unnatural and Unholy
And it's going to eventually get to women
There you go
Yeah probably
To put that together and be like a natural birth is what it should be and you should always try and save the child's life and not the mothers
0 *
Yeah yeah
Loves the answer
Also I just got to say that if Alex thinks
New Direction
Temperature should be
Not covering the news and talking
Think about rambly pseudo-spiritual
Great idea
What he saying is he wants to lower the
I can't stop
I welcome that
The pretense is annoying and it's very annoying
So Alex doesn't like Rim Desiree
Now
Bright cuz he did before
Right
But he still like hydroxychloroquine
Still kind of like Cybermen
Sure
He's another one Eli
Likes now
This rendezevere
That we've been seeing getting pushed by
Has less than 8% efficacy
They cost a bunch of money they made money off that didn't help people
Regeneron
Create a bunch of Clone white blood cells for mice
Prisoners or something their blood
No side effects
Cleans everything out
No shorts
Turn stop
Change your body it's in something in
And then you urinate and defecate
Is piss out the cloned cells
Okay
Does snake sound like something Alex would be again
F****** Christ I would never put
Play Shannon that the FDA has approved
Now
These rats themselves you just piss him out this amount
Just passed them out
It's really funny that Alex is promoting the use of regeneron
Complaints about the covid vaccine for these people is that it wasn't FDA-approved
Although that's
No longer true for Pfizer
Something like that
Which is also not FDA-approved I mean none of his s*** is FDA-approved
Cuz it doesn't have to
Bright but that's not the case we
Emergency
To use authorization
And it does seem like fwiw there are some indications that getting
Four injections of this cocktail of antibodies
Can be effective
And helping reduce a person's risk
Hospitalization
Hey I don't want to get a vaccine they're going to stab me with something that I don't understand
Did you stand before times you know it's
Yeah if there are some indications that it could be effect
But it is not a good pandemic control strategy
It's only useful for people who already have covid and it's effective only early on in a case so that could be a tough win
Window to hit for most people
Stop being sad
If you go to their own website to the
Regeneron website you can see
That it does have some side effects that Alex maybe should be concerned about
Serious Adverse Events reported in 1.6
6% of patients in the 2400m group
These included quote pneumonia hypo or hyperglycemia nausea and vomiting
Point out this
Can't be used
Conclude that the regeneron
Treatment
Actually cause those side effects
Alex
That's how I would report this let you would
Say damn
There are short-term
Side effects of associated people who were in The Trials choy
Bye
Pennywise the only reason the people like Alex are promoting this now is because
Florida Governor Ron DeSantis is open
Attempting to put a bandaid on the covid problem in his state
Of course this is really dicey because we're generon is part-owned by the hedge fund Citadel
And their CEO
Kenneth Griffin is donated over 10 million dollars to do
Who campaigns
In 2018 and 2022
Well the drug cocktail itself may be promising this whole thing has a very
Strong smell of corruption duet
It's a little bit worrying
Is f****** Banana Republic
Chet right there
That's straight-up like
Anybody is anybody watching
I think the argument that
I saw that the Santa's had was
That there were two possible antibody related treatment right
One was Eli Lilly one was this regeneron
And the regeneron showed more ethic
Perkasie in relation
The Delta variant and that's why you chose to go with it
But maybe a hundred percent proof sure very well could be
And brightest in itself could
I have as much promise as it appears to write
Zach said
Haha
The circumstances surrounding the sale make it
Really f****** dice
Well and there's the fact that he's
Still profiting off of
The death
So people in it
Also as you pointed at Alex
Trump in the right-wing chorus were all excited about better than doing any of that other stuff
Blah
Get ready for him to come over genron for a little while
I hate it whenever it doesn't go well
And then probably will see
A lot of those
Rogan types
Also
Probably promoting a pretty hard
I can't believe they do this s***
You know he's not going to advertise my pillow for free why are you doing what are you doing advertising regeneron you should get a cut
Give promo code promo code for Toronto
Serious about make
Money get out
You got a Hustle
Alex loves his talking loves is going off air
Is Tac
He's like a f******
He's a genius Sister George Jetson baby I love technology
Eminem liability protection
An image transparent
Glass
End
Authorized
Regeneron
For no profit and it doing that
This is a bunch of nonsense
The company owned by kenfucky
Griffin is a non-profit
Million dollar investment
In general
But also that the cocktail that regeneron has is not any more than any covid vaccine that Alex
So that point is
Second blade the whole issue of liability protection is not to protect the
Necessarily
It's protect consumers
The entire system
Paying people who could have been hurt by vaccines to set up to make it easier for people to get settled
Never be able to reach the burden of proof
Required in an actual Court
Companies that produce vaccines are also protected because if they weren't
No one would ever take on the risk of developing treatments that can save Millions
The Flies
It's a collective good
So the state takes on that burden
Next total
The word liability protect
Feel like a slam dunk with Alex but they're really not
Thirdly Alex says things have to be transparent
And what's the definition of transparent
It seems like there's a giant conflict of interest involved in
Florida's
Stop operating
That is large-scale Virginia
Screen Prince parents
I don't know what this glass
Do you mean physically try thinking means physically transparent and opaque things
I mean he would like his phone but it can't
See through it
It's not boats
CC
Point of
Treatment
They're charging
Consumers for regeneron shots
That doesn't mean the company isn't making a profit
But one thing
In late 2020 they received at 4
50 million-dollar contract for the federal government to produce
And in January 2021 the federal government
Bought all the companies supply for a price estimated at 2.6 billion dollars
Sometimes you just
See this corruption in your really like man
We're just not doing s*** our way we're just not going to do it
I mean so it's just not going to get done
We're just going to live like that also if you're keeping
Score these Governors like DeSantis
Is the federal government do Alex hate so much and is full of demons
That is paying for this to be able to
Have people get at the point of because if you're smart you're not going to pay for it
Make the government pay for it
That's why your smart if you don't pay
Taxes
And keep all that money for yourself it makes
Fix that makes total sense
This is all just such
Bulshit
Jetson baby hello technology
If it's these three things
Let me know
Can call before you tell me your George
Instead of accurately discussing a story that he decided to cover on his show he doesn't prepare at all and he just chooses to make up
Details instead
Regeneron is supplying the rejection that cost out of the goodness
So their hearts
Same
Test your might as well just give me a
Yeah if you're a conspiracy theorist
That listen to Alex
Text Jones
Even Alex saying that a corporation would do something for no prob
Would have to
Temeku razor
Tears up a little
But like it's a little silly
You're going to go with these
Billionaires
Are not trying to make money off of this supposed to believe that every billionaire is it a secret
Design to make money off of my desk
Who's the theme that develops got over the show and that is this like they're trying to take away these these human elements
Of Our Lives
Like a breast
Speeding that day
Sure
Here's the deal guys
Biological system
Mothers can't get milk to babies
Doesn't work
We've got to put you in a bubble and control your life
Mobile.
Don't talk to your neighbors
This is really happening this is the pod people
They're trying to make us the bald people
Do you want to fight tyranny you say you want to fund the second American Revolution
Got cut off
Got caught up at break there
Yeah that was passionless
Yeah that was not
Heartfelt like a
His emotions were
Felt like he was replaced by
By subway
He comes back from break and he wants to
Explain why everything
Is going all topsy
Teeter B
The world is in
The state of Chaos
Writer Isaac
He knows what he's talkin
Do you think so
Michelle
A lot of this is because
The top Rothschilds have died
Top Rockefellers have died
I know a lot of people that know
The top people
And they are just involved torturing and murdering people in Devil worshiping
Eating bats
Shopping channels off and torturing themselves
I don't know why you're laughing
Some very serious
People eating
Is Ativan
This is deadly
For one thing if he's Loveless or eating large amounts
The poop you would expect for a lot of them
Constantly being a state of Heaven
Food poisoning
Norovirus rotavirus and hepatitis A can all be transmitted through oral fecal meme
And that's not even taking into account the tons of bacteria and parasites you risk exposing
Yourself to better make sure they got clean ship moves back
Exactly it ruins the fun
Brother hamburger
Fresh organic
Farm-to-table
You know one of the big reasons that there are signs and every restaurant bathroom that have employees have to wash their hands before returning to work is because
Gulfeagle contamination can lead to outbreaks of
Nicolai or shigella
I'm no doctor but you got to assume your risk would be much higher if you're eating poo by the vet
Yeah you know it's super weird how you can identify all of our oligarchs by how they died of
Poisoning every
F****** day
Alex doesn't say these things for shock value
Play kind of suspicion that he's teasing his audio
Like yeah I can get you to believe this s*** let's see how far I can go
Showboat
Look-at-me showboating propaganda
So you Dum Dums believe
Also I'm going to do some
Dribbling between my legs how about that
You impressed by that I don't
So now that Alex has sold you on the van
How to poop
He also wants you to know that the global
Don't want you to look at
Sunsets on Ybor
My mother I told the story 20 years ago
Just last year
Another said
You look at
At the sunset
The water and the waves on the beach and you know it's beautiful
And you know it's good and you commune with it and you spiritually connect
Through God's creation to God
That is a form of worship
Electromagnetically and spiritually to God
God made us
Experience this with him
And what are they come out and stay
Australia New Zealand
Do not
Look
Sunset
Statistically if you look
In the morning and at night when it's low on the horizon that's not bad for your eyes
The massively boost
Your IQ long-term
Picture depression United
You don't look at it
Horizon
Something in your brain
They're trying to take away
Because these are Satanist
Uggs go
Dawn and Dusk and stare at the sun no they don't
That sounds like a saint
Nah man then I'm still looking for a
Nah they don't do it
Nope
They don't do it and they don't want you to do it either
About WhatsApp
Don't go outside.
Don't go outside dark dusk
Start alarm
Don't you dare look at the Sun during a transitional phase when it's
It's you know that the Liberals are
Tried to take away your son's that's all my God
You have a good day
Get on get on out of here something like don't stare at the Sun
If you stare at the Sun for a half hour you're going to blow your eyes out
Tell me what
Right now this is the demons trying to get me to not look
Sunset
Because that's how I connect with God
Alex look at the sunset
Directly into the sun
For as long as you possibly can enjoy a sunset
Sunrises
The more power to him
That's it
I don't have another qualifier
So I found this really fun because this again is another thing that's harder than that same train of like trying to take away the
Human thing
Like that
Speeding at
Sunset people by slapping
What are they going to do about the northern lights are they are the Aurora Borealis still okay
Don't look at the Aurora Borealis the Elder gods don't do that
Alex says he needs we need to take action
Collective action about sunsets
You know I want to do a human ritual with our listeners
Human ritual
And tomorrow night and you are the sun might not be clear the sky
Only
To join me in
Jay-Z at God's incredible creation again
Gives us life and a celebration of life
And I thank God
The meaning of spinach
They're telling us don't go look at the sunset don't look at the sunrise
I would like to
Pledge
Jerstad
Sundown Central that has matter where you are in the world
Sundown
You do out for 5 minutes and just pray to God for Global Awakening pray to God for healing
And in love and any good energy in the world
To get people courage to stand up and
This show is f****** weird
I agree I think what we need
Good deal
As a society
Is get rid of all of our
All of our TV shows all of our government
And all as a
The country focus on creating a
Truman Show situation
Text Jones
Where we all just do this weird s***
All of us
But he's insane
And we're just humoring a bit because I do want her
Him to walk outside
Some Nights
And just be the entirety of America
Staring up at the sunlight with him
Beautiful
I was going the other way with this I was I was thinking we would put him in as all of us
Truly tell him not to look at the subject
No. We all live out his negative fantasies as opposed to his positive
I want I want to live in a world where what Alex says make
Make sense
He has to like nothing
It's like it's like him hitting a
Wallet
60 miles an hour
Whenever all of a sudden everybody believes everything he says
This is true what will happen
Interesting because you would have to
To start complaining about something else
Fascinating to find out
Like how is
Ya survival
XM
We're all looking at the sunset now now what now what are you got now
We're all here
Call Cindy we love
The Tampa Bay
We love it we love it at Savannah what else every state passed resolution
We're not taking your guns
Actually want to hog all the sudden
Yeah
He's mad that everybody wants
Takis onset and is
Breastfeeding away
Famously
Very poetically said
Mama titties
It is
Cool life Falcone
I think it's a little bit mad about this taking away of his Humanity
Take our lives our bodies over
What do you want us to do
The good guys
I don't want power and don't want violence our kids up in our lives up
My father's brother's up to make this go away
No it makes this
About what we're going to do
Volume this murderous all day
Cerrone
Videos of Nancy Pelosi and Barack Obama's party
It looks like a bunch of trash and a bunch of unhappy garbage are losers
I didn't want to go anyway
Also in terms of the blue cities being full of feces
Preseason that's lunch
It's like those those regions in the Appalachians where they all eat raw meat all the time
Do you like
You people
Gotta stop
You got a
Stop
Baba to that Alex
Is
It's kind of like
Yeah we are going to do something to you don't worry about it like a people are worried that he's not going
Yeah I was worried
Pretty convinced that
Anyway the Democrat
Everybody on the left
It's all just Satanism now
Undercover
They talked about how much they lost
Then there really
It's a bunch of really soft
Weird nerds
No Satan rules the plan
I just want some petty power
We also make jokes about all that doesn't exist
Charlie Staton ism
That's how they suck everybody into a true control of the island after the
Porsche rally baby
I love Satan
Then they're just demonic
Rabid dogs are some
This is what they don't love men they don't like women
Special judge
Super super ultra viral
Videos up on
I hope that you are Cher
A video by doctor Shaun and Brooks
PhD over a million hundred thousand views right now
Really have the floor
Please do not forget
Fusion
So these Devils they want to kill kill kill I have Tang for sale
Satanist
Quite jarring
Doctor gas
Yes and Alex has been presenting him as somebody
Who's the doctor
That's
What he says
I mean you did name him
Doctor
You would not be
Wrong to assume that maybe this is a medical doctor because
Assuming that
And now you're concerning me
In my assumption you would have assumed that because of
It's about like medical issues
You would have an idea
Talkin to ask
God's School Board
You kind of think that and I think Alex probably thought the
Yeah
He's wrong
Ono and maybe he learned
Producer
I went to that High School
And I was there
I'm a well-known PhD in education
A doctor for monster
I know you are a senior riding before and I've heard about some of your book
I really want you on the sugars during articulate person
A PhD in education
I said
Bushes for a living
We're all humans
Chewing on and speak out
Yeah man
Sure
Not only was I aware that you are a PhD and education who lives in Oxford
Didn't go to Oxford I know that I was fully aware of your writings and I love your work
B******* instant crash course
And that this PhD had of like
Oh
I realize now that they're going to think of a doctor from Fox
Yeah
That's not good
I don't want to misrepresent myself I would like
Give you an opportunity to bail on this interview
That's what he was saying to the producer
I know why this is happening I didn't intend for it I'm not going to play along with that and that
Education
Mitzi from the city of ox
Oxford
Now this guy in his video that went
Mega Uber viral
You don't sound a little bit on him
Snapping your RNA
Anymore
Now here's what's going to happen in the future very quick
15 seconds
Alright so we need to be alarmist about this because this is a big Loveless moment everything he says you can.
This is a really tough Waze me to find out that I I and you
Yeah and almost everybody I know we're no longer human
I mean I think a real
Quick question to that would just be like a
What is a human
When you're stupid piece of s***
Give me a definition of my quote-unquote RNA gets broken in half
Give me a real explanation of why a full
You are a human if and only if your are and are not broken
I like it it's like a game like you don't
So we don't have to treat you or I guess the flip side of the argument is that everything has human rights
I guess this is going to be a dangerous road for this doctor of Education
Doesn't want to have that conversation
That's fine cuz I don't either
Have you ever considered
That if
The definition of humanity definition of humanity is more a social thing that we've all agreed upon
More people have broken RNA than have not broken our an egg
All the sudden we are the humans
And you're the not human how do you feel about that
Do you see how your logic might make you a fuk
Moron
Have you considered that for one second sir I don't know
So you going to be coming in here in a minute before breaking news
Welcome back I'm your host Alex Jones massive news has broken since we got our guest on let me message
We're going to take on to get back to the huge
Information he was just
Laying out
Bourbon on Salazar
Member Israel Australia are The Cutting Edge what's coming or not
Is realtor Grant Green passport
Why
Restaurants
Israel
Only
At worst you got to take
Unbelievable
The green passports in Israel were rolled out in February
Now it's been a little while
How'd they do it
It's just a convenient way for businesses to check out a person's exclamation status if they want to require vaccinations to enter their premises
Israeli Health Minister Yulia eidelstein was quoted back in February the Jerusalem Post
Whoever chooses not to be vaccinated has his right
There'll also be no personal sanctions against someone who is not back
It should be understood that getting vaccinated is a great privilege
That has been given to us
Something that many countries in the world has not attained
The article continues
The minister added that there will be some areas that will be over
Open to everyone even for citizens who have not been vaccine
And the possibility of these areas will be
Depending on the rate of immunization of the entire population
So now currently the the conversation is for these things are already out they will apply to people that boosters
Story is not
Alex's snow I heard I heard actually do Alex hasn't heard
This yet this is new that I'm breaking
Forehead has started requiring White
That
You have to use
And you have to
Tain
In order to move in a car from one place to another
Can you believe that you have to
To get a
Driver's license can only go places with these cards I mean it's bananas
Dial this work and you can only drive certain
Special move as fast as you want to drive
This is
Martial law Banning state
Gone mad
I think I may have even misspoke a little bit doctor he's on the line
Just getting into this news
Announces he has to get into before
We we really dive in with Sean
And that is
We got to get into dumbass gate
Will you do
Did Alex call Trump a dumbass
Everybody saying
Call President Trump
A dumbass do I said
Just showed you to spend a days at Pfizer says it's 139
Visors
But don't worry he's got new ones
I just said days before he said that
On Friday
Prophet said it looks like a scam by Pfizer with these boosters
Trust that you're smart
Yeah I stand by that
Okay so if I'm hearing Alex correct
Call Trump a dumbass
Apparently with Alex medbio comments was that
He doesn't think the Trump is a dumbass
That's right and then he must know what
He's doing
Sure which is recommending people get a vaccine that he presumably knows is a scam
I guess I was a dumbass as much as he called him and Evil
Fraud is trying to kill his followers
That's even better that is what you would rather somebody hear you say other than dogs I want a dumbass that's
Insulting things
You say what you should call them
Is a mouth
Please for the enemy that you have been fighting against your entire career and feel like a complete
Sell out in a piece of s***
Tivoli killing the people who put him in power
Here's the clip that's been going around I'll let you judge for yourself
What Alex's meaning
To say
Decided to call Shadow dumbass gate
Medical doctors on a play for you on this when we come back
President-trump
I believe it's a good person
And who I really care about is why I want to see a lot of the Republicans elected the midterms and who I would love to see him run again
Cuz he came out last week on Fox and Friends
I really am suspicious of this boost
Four shots in this supposedly work so well why did The Butcher Shop
Because you got lied to Trump
Advocacy
We knew it wouldn't work
. it's a fraud it'll create mutants
You got Trump
You got signed on to a fraud
Restart the economy
I understand why you did it you believe in science
These are Bad actors sir
Real quick I just have to break here because
If Alex do anything about delivery in m
He would have repeated sir
Yep it was begging to be put up
Do this sir
Yep
You know like that yet
The right tire how you do it
Sir
Now they got you signed up
And you are seeing and come downstairs
Seeing it snaps her fingers
Tim suckers snaps his fingers and Trump
Quick steel and hops
There Trump in the Alabama yesterday
Where you got to do what you have to do
I recommend
You got. That's okay that's alright
You got your freedom
If it doesn't work
You'll be the first to know
Okay
But it is working
BS
Trump that's a lie you're not stupid
Just two weeks ago they said it was 65% then 40%
Someone ever put out by about 50 shots
37%
Cuz he's going to take it doesn't work
Pappadeaux
Shame on you Trump
Seriously
Hey
Disable yourself
That's okay
And you'll be like you
My God
Maybe you're not that bright maybe Trump Taxi
Dumbass
If I were in charge of deciding how to cover this story I would lean much more heavily into how Alex is very clearly saying that
Trump knows that the vaccines are a secret plot to kill everyone
And that he's recommending them to his audio
Know what defensive is that
Dumbass
Write the headline here isn't that Alex speculated the Trump is a dumbass
Evil
The Alex Trump will-they-won't-they storyline sent the election really isn't doing anything for me
When you get right down to it really
It doesn't really matter
The Alex either
He doesn't like Trump
That's not a problem
Because he probably never did
Trump has a useful tool
For people like out
Is an impressionable malleable chaotic
Idiot who they could use to take over some of the levers of power
In this country
If I was in the press and I decided even
Touch this clip
What angle would be would be that Alex is turning on Trump
Scooby-Doo play up this idea that Alex is saying the Trump is either stupid or evil
And not
Good
There's only two WAP
Covering the story as Alex called Trump a dumbass misses the point a little bit and just
Makes me think that the reporting doesn't have much awareness
Of how often Alex says mean things about Trump when he's mad at
Like it's it's
Not novel
But I think there's maybe some ground you could
You could gain by
Bye-bye
Really positioning this we're like okay
The bass is really crack
Right right
You have a foundational issue
That the leader of the cult
Is unwilling to go along with
Which is telling everyone not
To get back some
Yeah
And I think that you could probably
Exploit that wedge
Pretty hard
No it's a it's a
Perfect
Like it's such a great teachable example of something that happens in human history all the
Which is that
The leader of the
The group is the leader and they will go along with whatever the leader says
As long as they tell them what they want to hear
And if you tell them what they want to hear guess what you can add
Whatever the f*** you want
Dove Court yeah
You tell them what they want to hear and then you can destroy their lives because whatever you want
Whatever you want as long as it doesn't violate one of the other things
That they need to
And then in this situation you would think that Trump would look at that and go oh
I was just
Able to
Bought them I was not actually leaving the group and run the group
Will do anything if anybody tells us what we want to hear
Everybody should learn from that and be like maybe we're both stupid on both sides here
And this is a negative feedback loop that is repeated itself throughout history
I think the negative Craven
But manipulative jerk
We learned something from this and that is that
Alright you can control this Cult of Personality there's a limit
Yeah really knuckle up and say whatever they want
So maybe the next person will just be like that
F*** it don't care don't give a s***
Cuz that would retain
The control over
Whatever whatever amount of
Influence you have
Yeah there's two lessons I guess there's a good lesson don't do this again and then there's the
The bad lesson
Do it again the butt
Never ever ever ever ever
Not once
Yep so talk to this doctor
PhD
So he he talks a little bit about his going to this
School Board
Meeting in
Yellow bunch of dumb s*** at them
Becoming the
The favored media Outlet of
Weirdos now
Because they are going to be on TV
Maybe a lot of them have had their social media accounts
Yeah so now they can videos
Taking of them yelling at people
At 2
Public meetings
Yep
Now this is a new art form
School boards are the new reality TV show
Good way to get attention if you're really weird
And so I went when we
Get to any like actual points
Sean wants to bring up
Because of bad handle on some
Decisions
That have to do with covid regulations
An Indiana University is another example
Over the summer
Before summer
They said everybody who works here and everybody who comes here has to be jabbed end of story
Countless students and parents started to sue Indiana University
Involved
The judge sided with Indiana University and said they get to do what they want
I could have that wrong but I think that's right it is to how that ended up settling out so
Everybody who attends now
Understand how this case went with Indiana University at all
What happened was that 8 students at IU which is not a countless number
They sued the school because they announced the vaccine mandate that applies only to the fall 2021 semester
Zoe this is mandated the school offers many options for folks who can't or don't want to
I get back Senaida
They offer medical and religious exemption
They'll let students take a semester off without penalty
And they provide online option
For completing classes
These students have asked the court to enter a preliminary
Action to stop the mandate
The primary
Syria that would be used
Give that injunction is whether or not there is quote
A strong showing that they will likely succeed on the merits of their claim
That they will sustained irreparable harm
And that the balance of harms and the public interest favor such a remedy
The US District Court released a 101-page opinion explaining how they did not feel this case brought before them status
Injunction was
If you read the filing all but one of the Apes 2
Either have a religious
Exemption to the Mandate or would qualify
But haven't even applied for washu or who hasn't replied
Maybe she would
My point is that this is kind of a farce
The fact that seven of the eight students suing the university over a policy that is so Taylor to them
Qualify for it not to affect them
Is the very definition of right-wing victimhood mentality
Problem I don't have
My other point is that Sean Brooks has
Annoyed
Idea what this case was actually about because
The details don't matter
What's important is the Optics of victimhood that he's able
Go to present using
This case as a prop
When you're trying to have a serious conversation about issues that matter
It's generally not a great idea to bring up an example of a court case that you have such a week
Grass pollen that you have to
Admit on are that you might have it wrong while use that as a defense
Answer why you're right don't do that
That's a bad luck
Alex is bringing up Amy Coney Barrett because after this injunction
The students
Pull up Mike Lindell and take things to the Supreme Court
Has assigned to the seventh circuit currently which includes Indiana so on paper
It was her who rejected the request two-stepping
And overrule the district
Court is not the relevant judge in the
She was foodie right-wing media decided to get really mad at though since she was a trump appointee
The presumption was that you would be up for any
Why aren't you a rubber-stamp doing whatever and I thought you'd be up to be real weird
Point Isabel of appointed you
Was that you didn't know what you were doing
And you do the dumb s*** we say
How dare you act like you have any experience that was the deal
I mean I am I get it
Like I would be offended if I was on their team I wouldn't get I wouldn't understand it cuz
Cuz when you get down to it right
Okay
She doesn't get to act like
She's acting like she's on the Supreme Court
Because she should be on the Supreme Court
And she is not there
She should not be anywhere near the Supreme Court
She's there
To do this dump
If I were them I would be furious
How dare you act like you know what you're doing
Let me text you probably does know what
She's doing tuna
Next
Probably maybe not on the Supreme
Baby a little baby batting a little bit outside of
What punching out of the weight class I believe Izzy
Is a sheep part of the deal and if she doesn't get that she's wrong
Like I understand I'm also pretty grateful that you
She's wrong
In the real world this is a great this is great news
Scalp
Who's listening to this Sean fella
And I got a weird vibe on him
You just made the hair on the back of my neck stand up
Yeah you really did he was
Freaking me out Hellboy
Part of it was just like you see me
Educational system
Education you will get mad
Mad in a different way than other people
Tell your partner's a teacher and we've talked a lot of times about Consumer Cellular
Absolutely passionate with it
Public school systems that often
Make things better
I didn't get that
From healthy that sounds kind of where I was
I got an angry vibe from him
This clip kind of made me laugh a lot
We've always known
Did the Rockefellers in the carnegies have had every
Nothing to do with
Xbox system
No different in higher ed
The exact same
Control
They control the minds of those individuals that don't see
Think for themselves
And again when I was in college
Or the ones that I went to the bookstore to buy
They were not the ones that the university said will you need to read this and you need to read that
I look at this $300 text
And say no
I'm not reading that
Glance through it I'd write a paper for the class and then that be
Bookstores existed
Goodbye
234 bus
History events psychology sociology
Anatomy physiology and I would put all of this together and I read on my own time
People have to self-educate
So I understand that some people are
Just too much of wreaths
Thinkers for this kind of thing but the reason the classes have textbooks is because their teaching a specific thing
But the teacher presumably is a much better awareness of them the student
Typically the teacher will know about the subject ahead of time and the required text
4 best
Enabling
Students get the handle on the material
That's usually how this works
I hate like the idea of Defending
Pieces
On education
Informal question we ask this if everybody it's not even affect anything
Did you ever read any of the books when you were in school
No I read Robinson Caruso
Surprised that discount goodbye
I agree that there's problems
The textbook industry particularly as it relates to Heather essentially an instrument
The price gouging
Colleges
Expressing here really is
Just that he's a blowhard and he's an authority
I kind of guy whose streak has gone a little bit off the rail
When I was in college off in the required text
Four courses wouldn't be text
Per se
The class could be a novel in academic writing or possibly like a collection of photocopy newspaper articles from the Earth
Early
Book The Professor wrote
Themselves sometimes yeah although I always a little suspicious
Just about that that was a little bit like to come on by yourself dealer
Only trying to sell his own s*** to the school that sucks
But maybe there was good
Oh now he's mad
Also my dad's a professor and I've spent my entire life surrounded by Academia
Never once in my life encounter to Professor
Or teacher who is discouraged reading
Parts on the syllabus
Typically people in Academia love talking about their subject
Cuz they're really worse than it and
You know if you want to read a book that run
Counter to their take on the subject they know a lot about
They're going to be excited
Discuss that book with you and explain to you why it misses
X Y or Z point
Already suggest
That you've spent
Clearly a decade of your life focused only on this one kind of
Subject of course you better want to f****** talk about it's your favorite academics might be
Powermadd psychopath that are bent on making the big bucks and work
Open the minds of the youth
But they're nerds for
Yeah before I would believe anything
If you told me that they weren't interested in what they were talking about your ad say
Ultimately
I love this conception of like
You know they they they
Give you all these
These are the indoctrinate you if you're not afraid
Thinkery
What in the textbooks
Did the non freethinkers a remember
Like what was it exactly
From like history textbooks
Science and math
Victory was
Retained by making it sound like I'm mad at a problem
That doesn't exist
Kind of now an end I will say that being mad at a problem that doesn't exist as a thing that
I'm mad at
A problem that doesn't
If you're the sort of person who so narcissistic and Oppositional Defiant that youth
I think you can create a better syllabus than a professional
A field of x
40 East
But maybe formal education isn't
I'm at school
That's totally fine
People can be self-taught I believe that and I've got no disrespect for that it has degree
Just that it's a lot harder for external observers to know exactly how well a person has or has not taught them
Degrees are generally helpful because they did note that you learned a subject
From someone who understands that subject
And they were able to help you understand it
There's no way to can
For the same kind of thing with self-education
That's why it's a little bit more
It is
Also it's so funny that this dude has such a weird bone to pick about education win
He himself kind of
Intentionally misrepresented
His credentials
In the video himself at the school board meeting
That went viral
You barely does have a Ph.D but himself to this
Quote
Dr. Sean Brooks
PhD Oxford
I have 48 Publications including 23 books
Anatomy and physiology for approximately 21 years
Book
Like I said you didn't go to
Oxford he's from Oxford Ohio
A f****** is degrees from Walden University
Justin online
However there's more going on here than I would like
There may be a reason that Sean is
Is mad at the public
Look school system
But he's not disclosing
Will does his pH
If you give him any access to
Teaching positions
According to heavy they were able to track down a person with a PhD named Sean McCullough Brooks
Oxford Ohio
They were able to find a teacher discipline case from
Florida that was against a person with the same name
Which resulted in a reprimand and probation after Brooks didn't confess
Didn't he was innocent but also agreed not to contest the accusations
I'm not going to get too deep into this because it feels really f***** up but
The issue that I was behind this disciplinary action
Had to do with him posting videos of students discussing
Really personal issues
On a public website without the student
Parent's permission
Some of the stuff
Involves like
Pretty personal stuff
Just
Creeps me out
I was concerned that this
But possibly not the same dude who's here on Alex's show but
First of all Shawn McCullough bruxism
Pretty specific name
Specific
The documents for the teacher misconduct case
Included 2015 letter of reprimand that's address to Shawn Brooks
Whose address is in Oxford Ohio
Any idea for Alex the screen is guest in the future so it doesn't end up in this kind of situation
Where G7 devout for this guy just cuz his video went viral
If you're talking to somebody about Heather
The school system is evil
Kind of
Into the conversation to let your listeners know
But they may have a big old chip on their shoulder
Informing their positions
It it might have to do with them being real weirdo so they were teachers
It's not personal it's about protecting the
Don't you understand that the Rockefellers and the Rothschilds won't let me post weird videos
Yes
Also what a weird thing whatever like
Textbooks at-large held hostage by f***
Texas Bowl
You know what I'm saying like
You're really going to come after 2
Textbooks whenever a half
Half of them just because Texas doesn't want to admit it
Say that slaves came here on a lark
Like what are you f******
Talking about
And there are very real issues
What a dick
So I feel like these kinds of disclosures are important
Because they allow the audio
Chance to assess the information that's
To them
In a responsible light because it is very relevant
So
You have things like this
You can't you can't do this
Institutions
I've been writing about your speaking up
He's complaining that he's been shut out of higher education
And
Maybe it has something to do with this disciplinary
Stuff that he has
Maybe his response to that just
Plenary action
I don't know it it's
It seems like you can't
You can't have someone be like I've been shut out of higher education
Because
My my ideas are to verboten or whatever
And then you defended without knowing anything about the case
Ripe
Just it's
It's not respectful to the individuality of the audio
Information
Nope
So Alex
You know he's covered on this episode
Bill Maher
And now he saw something else recovered on this episode
3 people
Talking about things
But they know absolutely nothing about
But have the expertise of being good at something
Completely different and with no relation to that
Alex decides he's going to cover something you saw on Tik-Tok
Tik Tok video
Somebody sent me a bunch of weird stuff.
Brian Williams who says he was shot down the helicopter
Nobody was shot at Noel driver got shot at it's a lie
Brian Williams
That's not true he didn't say that his helicopter was shot down
That was shot at
Alex is lying about the LIE
A convicted pedofile run your preschool
Adios equivalent
He brings up Sandy Hook
All we talk about Sandy Hook
15 *
7/8 years ago the internet questions
Set the mass shooting
Was Smollett
What is your name
Did they fake babies in incubators to start the Iraq War
Did you get John Cena
Show footage of the Knob Creek
Machine gun shoot
People blowing up villages in Syria
Question tag
Free speech
Not on purpose
Unlike Brian Williams
No but you have said that you have prophetic dreams
Sears Automotive things are equally embarrassed
He's had a paper a lot of abortions he slept with over hundreds of women by the time I'm 17
Yeah yeah he's made a lot of claims that maybe I wouldn't
Want to
Yeah
Even if all of those things
Accurate
Babies in incubators jussie Smollett
Sure all of it
Even if everything
It still doesn't excuse his behavior at the lights
Said he has literally nothing to do with what he
Yeah
I guess he's just laying out f*** that one up
Which is actually an evolution in his position
I mean it's about as close to just
Straight up saying
I am sorry for being wrong
As I think we forgot
From him
There is still application they're still trying to deflect
It is a little bit more like
I did that bad I mean to do it a lot I only talked about a few times
Dip my toe in there I only did all this stuff you know what there's other things that
But sometimes I did f*** I only paid
4/2 of damper dondi's flight to hold a newton
Dutch on it is all good
When's in buddy cowboy
This is great here we go
It's always there when Alex plays this
The studio
Is
So
Good
Okay
Soen
Is going to say
Hey man
Listening to that Brian Williams clip
I heard six
Lies
Alex makes
Huge mistake
He's like
What are they
No
I think I counted just
5 or 6
Layton
Lies
Brian Williams
Live
Can you imagine
Sometimes the crew will sit there and and you know you'll go on a great ran or something wrong
Imagine the crew behind Brian Williams like wild
Nobody's business to imagine approved
Could do that
Why the whole world
I don't even mean
Everything he said pretty much was a complete lie
Oops
Shouldn't shouldn't attack again
Specific
Hey come on man you're ruining the scene the scene as we just make s*** up what are you having
The game we were playing in
Imagine if we were able to get away with that
Course I didn't know what lies
It's just a general feeling of things to tell me what's up with the lies where
Listening
Everything
That's all I everything is alive
Go to antibiotic
Just want to know how jail was
Minoan
You were giving some rules not
To talk with other
What happened I don't know how they do that when you were talk show hosts
Talk show host
Body cameras on video
Usher weird about
What happened on January 6th killing our
Story straight hair
But I want to know how jail went yesterday and
Honestly Alex keep saying to like everything is on body Cam and that's actually evidence
Against
Cuz
The problem was
He was
Breaking his is
Prior agreement
Is that his deferred prosecution
I mean maybe he's just saying that like
We know there's a guaranteed guilty verdict so we don't really need to even talk about the case because
Cuz he did that s*** it's all our body
That could be an interpretation
This is all
This is 100%
We just before we recorded this
I'm not sure if it will
When it'll be out
Guest appearance on opening arguments
Case of the nature of idiots
Not a big charge
Even if Owen word
He found guilty community service it'll be something minor in a fight
Fine it's not a big deal
But Owens trying to raise a quarter of a million dollars for the dreidel.
Obviously you're trying to raise a quarter million dollars for
If we find it we are fighting it
You did not break in the capital using physical Force
He's been charged
Urine present when I can let that happen
Dollar Tree Legal defense fund
Great want to get under 50000
An open-and-shut and now you've been charged based on a lie
You should know you don't want to do them
Well and we may look into other lawsuits going forward when when some of the smoke starts to clear but yeah
We have an executive order here
Governor Abbott
It says you cannot mandate masks in any public building
And when I was in the Federal Building yesterday
I couldn't go in without putting a mask on
He was being
Arraigned and processed yet where I'm asking you
This is the realest
I thought it was cuz they were showing Eric
Adults movie in the courtroom
That would be offensive
Tia Alex is lying was charged
Because of the
Of a Huffington Post article
Is charged
Actually I think that might be Alex
Maligning The Huffington Post
Anything to do with Owen making that deferred prosecution agreement
To do community service The Huffington Post
It would show up in
Slapping and break
His foot so we couldn't do any
Screw the human personification of The Huffington Post Arianna Huffington
Bushes
Blow dart in Des Moines with sleep.
Anyway
Is our last pipe and it's just to show how like
Tough Alex's
3 strong
That's what I think of
Fivefold from the three years ago in Blue City
I'm a tough guy
I will not go downtown now
Unless I have to add a meeting and I bring a bodyguard
It is literally
Like a lunatic asylum.
That's amazing
Soto
Fivefold increase
Crime in blue cities is amazing first of all
Sure
I don't know where that's at, probably like him
To substantiate that
Second
I've been to Austin my parents live
Fairly close to downtown Austin
Only safe place
Like a safe or unsafe or whatever but like
Is the idea of needing a bodyguard to go downtown
Is absurd
Except for the fact that Alex has a celebrity
If your
I don't know somebody who's just like
Who's who plays
Superman
Henry Cavill
He needs a bodyguard
20 year old be Millennials until you know how the rise and fall of beam came with
Can you do nothing
Pavel
Needs a bodyguard
Not because any place may or may not be safe because he's a celebrity and people
What a bum rush
Right
When I went to see a
Cavaliers
Lakers game
When I was like
15mm game
Aqua shooting
Free throws
Pregame
Of course
It's because he's a fan
Atmos not because Austin is such an
Unsafe play
And even then you don't
I mean like
If you need a bodyguard
Bodyguard
Then you probably earned that
You know I'm saying like Henry Cavill may have a
What would be more like a bouncer of just like
Hey man I know there's just so many people that want to get up to him at the same time
We just need an orderly line
But if you need somebody who's got a
Gun
And it's just like hey man if anybody comes at you I'm going to shoot them
That's because you're an ass
The Alex has a team on the roof
He's got ninjas
If you're if you're if you're a politician walking around with a f******
Bulletproof vest on it probably
Because you have it coming
Or at least you've done something to earn
I don't know
Bite my feeling is just that it's
It's a little silly
Sorry we come to the end of this and
I think
Owen is a political prisoner who's able to make
Tons of money
Misdemeanor
Nonsense
Unreal
Misdemeanor Budd Lake
In trouble
Tons of money
Quarter of a million
Sense of what it means to be a freedom
You know it's really important
He's doing the big work
What meanwhile
Alex
Is back in studio anchoring this s***
The real serious work of talking about
Belmar Belmar
Talking to a weirdo about education
Yeah cuz we had a viral video I was just very cool it's why you got to get him out there
And then
Bickering about whether or not he thinks
Dumbass in whether or not the media covered it correctly
Who was in that meeting
Everything is pointless
That meeting there had to have been a meeting
Where
After Shroyer
Turn himself in and probably be on Sunday before Schroeder tour
Before Shroyer turned
And it's Alex
Edits
A couple of lawyers at least I'm sure Barnes is on the volume
Yeah and they're just like
Okay
How do we make
We're going to be rich what do we do what's the capital
We said on that like cuz that's the
That's a conversation they were like
Okay no we can't say a million dollars nobody would believe we needed a milli Riders
But if we say a smaller amount
Is it still high will reach it and then get a
Beyond then we can add like
Extra stretch goal exactly
He totally legal fees of the 250
H500
RAC
He going to be okay
Okay that was never a question
How much profit
Is the potential for this ruse the right number.
Consulted
Actuary tables of actuaries
Yeah it's really disgraceful and pathetic
Exactly what I would expect from these
Ding dong yay-hoos you got it
Jordan
We will be back
Baby I would love it if I do next time
We record
Owen Shroyer has been since 2:30
Every photo pretty funny
We've decided to make a
An example out of
Shroyer
We're going to charge him, clean outside of the potential punishment
Absolutely what he did
Yeah but
Wellsfargo.com
Oh that's your life
Idessert
Please find a local charity will be offended. How about people
Omniome Leon dzx
Clark
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color