Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Hey buddy
Alex
June
Indeed we are.
Jordan Jordan
I think we talked about the recent episode
Survivor no collector itch
Oh yes
That got into my head a little bit
And I started to think about
Card Collector
I do I don't want stamps maybe I do but I don't actually
Just trying to think of like a way that I could productively and not like a belief self-destructive lie
Explore some of these tendencies
Got a game
That's like a deck building game
Okay okay game called
Okay
It's a lot of fun
I think
I do brakes but I guess is like exploring these genres of games that I'd never really played all that much and
I dig it
Yeah there's a lot of this lot of fun
Different play styles of games up there that
Attacking but can bring a lot to your life in
I don't know I'm
I'm really worried that I'm going to end up finding
Some
Really in-depth deck-building game and then I'm done
You're just going to get way too into online gwent
And then it's over it's possible I mean that was
Is one of the first like
They thought you had no no like one of the first instances of like who like
Just do this for a while
Like when I was playing The Witcher
Holding lady totally this is a sub game in the game tonight
Kind of like more
I've gotten too good at this there are
Players in the game that I can actually
It's not satisfying
Hundred hours like yeah it's not
That was that was the start of the root of it could be the problem
Blossoming into an addiction will find out help so
How to keep with the theme you've got your cards similar
We got a new board game called wingspan
Okay it's kind of like a it's like a resource game like Settlers of Catan and all that stuff
But it is just
Gorgeous
Just like it is
Hand-painted
I have anybody you know this like beautiful artwork
Cupboards and and it's just about
Collecting
It's gorgeous it's just it's really really cool
It's better than what I thought it was going to be in
Wingspan is just like
Hold your arms out long
Get out of there
The fun game out of there
I'm going to set a fire just to make sure that you mean it when you jump out of the window
So Jordan today what we're doing is we're going back to
The past
So this is a recording
Couple days before
We would normally have right so if anything happened
In the very recent
We don't know about
Yeah cuz it hasn't happened yet
When we recorded
In some ways you are hearing us
In the past
Talk about the past
And that's we are even
Less capable of responding to the usual yes
We're doing we're going back to June 11th
Three continuing on our path through 2003
Does he believe in the devil
I have to say to his groundbreaking up
I'm very excited about this episode
It is unlike anything
I've heard it listening to past Alex
And I am
Humped
Alright to discuss it
Man thank you so much and I apologize why
I'm a policy wonk
My next is it goes to refer to sharks as Chum slots that you so much right now if I was you
It might be his ghost the word
One of the worst
It's a word that's not the only word to describe active
Healthy cake San Jose
Emergi from the happiest country in the world in Orland
Thank you so much you're an alcoholic
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much for rubbing it in
Technocrat in the mix we got a little bit of a Halo what's up
Going out
Do mist
Patience of a flood thank you so much you are now attacking
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Freakishly large
I know that's a Biblical reference
But it
What's what
I thought it was a the name of the jars of
Play album
But I don't think it is I think it was like Grace flood or something like that
I was not a Jars of Clay head no no no no my jars
Is where made of porcelain what other materials do you make jars out of
Google was just called
Flood
Just cause one of my face
Raining for days
You lift me up so
It's hard to imagine
That not
Tickling my fancy
I didn't even realize it but remember the lyrics
At least three different Vibes alright
Okay I thought so it was Grace flood
Not it
I wonder if that's something
Another
It sounds like a hard boiled egg
Active great flood
I'm here to solve your goddamn mystery
I'm going to give a shout out to
Who adopted a sea otter daughter hanging around Selena very excited
Yep yep solutely we have a pretty cute
Crew my biggest problem so far now is that we don't get
To hang out with all of these animals at the same time when I sleep
I dream of you
Be cool family disagree with you
Jordans
Dreams will Factor heavily into this conversation
Hahaha
Alright
I listen to a couple episodes
From 2000
3r not covering
Because it just kind of got bored was just mad about a recent interview did on a radio station
I really want to find this actual interview
Stanley compare it to
Radio interview for 2003
So that was a real frustrating thing and it was is boring otherwise it
Caribbean Market
People disagree with
What was it like in 2000
Free when everything was intense
Italy archive
That's forever
Yeah so weird
Have things
Tell me things were lost
February said even mean
So
I turned on the 11th
June 11th
And
I immediately got
F****** pump
Blanco
North Korea
Call Robert
Died on the operating table
Holyshit
Can you die multiple times and go to heaven to go to heaven each time they what are you doing back here
Balls of the Pearly Gates
We told you to go back there are no Pearly Gates according to this story
I adjourn this honors like this does not sound like
Annie episode that I've heard from this time. A particular where Alex is very
Calmly
Big we're going to talk to a guest about how he went to heaven I do like that I do like that
This is
This is absolutely a
Huge sign pointing toward believing in the devil
You bet we work makes considerable progress in that investigation
Call Brad
But I love the dress
Exposition of this are used to the car we're going to get into the Iraq War and how the globalist want to attack all these other countries also by weird
Greg Roberts went to heaven
Ensuite that is
Two of the most
Stories happening today yeah so Alex is not
Unfamiliar
With this kind of thing
Dying and coming back
Paranormal
Wait about 20 years
Job
Knocked Up
Believe
Medical don't believe
In the afterlife
Really excited when he get into some of his experiences because based on
To the present day stuff
You've got to have a lot of stuff
That should have already happened a few years when he was younger
Was tried to tried to induct him into this High called
Yahoo satanism
He had God give him a panoramic 360 view of everything
It was going to happen that they would guide him through his future
I'm excited to hear him
Say exactly what he says now she isn't that right I'm really excited because this is some
World-changing s*** and I will remember it forever if God literally came to me and you can either
You can either make the argument that if he doesn't get into a lot of the stuff that he talks about in the present then
Either he doesn't want to talk about it on air because he's all comfortable with it
Right
Or he's come up with all that stuff
Since this point backstory
Benefit of the doubt
Going to say that he's yet
5 years
5 years into this show you certainly should still be giving him a bit
Jeff Fairman so
Craig Roberts is one of Alex's weirdo friends
You forgot who died and came back
He's a guy who
I don't ever hear Alex talk about anymore
Never knew who this guy was until I started going back to 2000
3 and he's everywhere that she was lousy with Craig Roberts in the past
But he is not somebody who
You even be really familiar with
Gation no I don't know if he's dead I tried to sort that out
He died by his own
Storiesig
Wouldn't be surprised if it happened again I wonder how many times you can come back before you have to
Just say okay that's number for you're here for good
Yeah it's a three-strikes-you're-out policy
This is better what happened
Weather for when I worked at the movie theater you know like if you want left the theater to go to the bathroom you get back in
With your stuff you know
What are somebody's going and out of the theater like 10 times
Is it I feel like heaven father the same way
So
Craig Roberts died and went to heaven Alex's uncle
Also had a little bit of an
Experience and if you thought
These not the numbers were weird
Okay
His job
6.
When he was
Died
On the way to the hospital
And I
Zf6 times man six times
6 x 6 x 8 long ambulance ride
Way that you do not walk away with permanent brain damage from that
Have you Larry something along those lines
I guess what kind of lens
Credibility to
Dying 6 times
Dying six times are coming back
In a ambulance ride
That's ridiculous
What counts as dying
Definitely don't
I want to know I need specifics on when you know your daddy's their brain activity or is it just hard
Is it what are we talkin about
There is a
There's no scientific
Which kind of does make it a little bit more difficult
I do believe however that the proof is in the Stars
Edit is in the leaves around us
That obviously this was full brain-dead
Alex's uncle's in the
The
The ambulance
Humble
I'm back
3/52
So before we get into this interview Alex does have to talk about some
Now that I think about it somebody's in the ambulance
There's a there's an emt-b really said I just imagined the band like at the beginning
I will bring you back to the number 6
Jesus Christ I don't even know if we need to do this anymore Bruce Lee pmt's in there that like
I am
Magic's
Everytime I touch this band
How does a B-2 get your next
Person you're picking up who doesn't come back
Configure
So there's some
Quite alright
Real world issue
Use the even get to before we get to heaven
One of them has to
Do with
Taxation
Of cars
Albion radio
So Alex is making a prediction that within a couple years the entire United
What states will have
Tracking things in cars so
There will be a system
The text
Cuz you buy them
Sure
I don't think that
Maybe I once managed to save the world from this one cuz it did not deny.
2021 article in the washer
2 States currently are trying out this sort of the policy as an alternative to taxing gasoline
He was just a decade behind on his planets
The question is why would a
State want to explore the possibility of Shifting have taxes are levied and measured
It's because of emerging Technologies and things like the idea of hydrogen powered cars that hypothetically
Don't need gas
If he's become larger and larger parts of the market space
What ends up happening is the
Midstates face
Huge financial
Cars are still using the road
What's the upkeep of which
Is funded by tax revenues but the drivers are no longer paying gas taxes
Which made up a large
Which part of the pot
Their number solutions that have been floated in terms of how to deal with this inevitable issue but the mileage based taxation is one of the ideas
It gets talked about the most
Partially because it covers a lot of the relevant variables
And the plan seems like it could be implemented in a way
That would cost the average driver app
Approximately the same about
Has gas taxes ended up in Keurig on them
No granted
Gas taxes are levied against
Do you like wholesalers
Amana trickled down to the Geico commercial
But the amount of expense would be fairly similar to most average drivers
Just buy it are people who drive
Like
Completely fuel-efficient cars
That much
Gas tanks
Sure.
Utah and Oregon I've already put programs in place to ship things in this direction
And there are folks working on it in various places around the country but it's nothing at all like Alex's describing
The Oregon program was launched in 2015 and it was voluntary
To participate
According to the Washington Post
Legislators and Salem are considering a bill that would make the program mandatory for new vehicles with a fuel economy rating
House 30 miles per gallon or higher
Starting in 2026
But still even in the future even like a progressive
Gas tax
If you will
You could look at it that way
How this article
Explains the system as it works
In Oregon
Quote
Participants in the state have three ways to sign up
Privately-run systems and one administered by the State Department of Transportation
Private companies send drivers a device that logs where and how much they drive or pull the data directly from
Vehicles
Then they send bills
Turn over the revenue to the state
Drivers get reimbursed
For gas taxes that they pay at the pump
Okay
So that's the way that the system
Right there trying to eat their trying to see if it equals out or if there is a loss
Still or Thursday is
And then they're like concerns you know about privacy obviously
People can opt out of having their information
Capital
A reality that
Technology is advancing and non-gas consuming cars are more fuel-efficient cars are becoming more and more prevalent
Simultaneously the system we've built in order to keep our roads
Safe and driveable relies on tax revenues that come from gas sales
The discussion about alternative modes of Taxation or just a discussion about how we can adapt to new better cars
Will simultaneously continuing to publicly fund
Nothing cards
Need to drive on
Even so even proponents of this kind of plant except there are real challenges
In terms of putting it
In place
For instance like I said the gas tax itself has collect
Wholesalers
Minutes passed down to Consumers indirectly
Where's this new plan would require many more employees to be in like collection type position add a lot of
Exedy to the
The way that this was
Collected anybody even proponents of the plan
Don't recognize like
That's Tuff
The infrastructure on this is going to be difficult to figure out because we're creating it as we go it's a brand-new system
That nobody's ever even tried
It's going to be a challenge doesn't mean it's impossible they're probably some hiccups
I guess it's Alex would prefer maybe there's a
About
Taking blood making up attack somewhere else
Second property or sales taxes
Poquito for those plans either
I think he's a
Against
Taxes
A plan and that's fine on his show because if you're listening to the show you actually haven't heard Alex
Explain what the problem is
Why people are discussing the ideas he's ranting about
It's fine to be opposed to this
Proposed system but it's
It's not really okay to just pretend there's no reason
Did anyone would want to try it other than
To track-and-trace everyone
Yeah that's not
Did the relevant
Part of the conversation the entire reason the conversations happen
Right yeah I mean
My plan would be to probably
Forcibly dissolve most oil companies and then reallocate those resources that I have take
Taken 2
Employ the employees that used to work for them as well as rebuild
See I don't know is that necessarily is a self
Perpetuating
I don't know if that's going to be a renewable pot of
Time to figure out the renewable pot
It's all about buying time right now that's what I'm about
Actually made me think of
How Alex
Was talk talk about the bubonic
Plague in the present-day he has a bit of an another Health scare
Betty wants
People to be aware of
Confirmed
The outbreak
Abilene report
To give you some context
SARS outbreak is still currently active at this point
June
The World Health Organization didn't announce who was
Contained until July
So
It seems like
Monkeypox
Look over here
It's weird
This outbreak in 2003 monkeypox was interesting only because it was the first time an outbreak
Kid ever been reported outside of Africa
Investigators believe that the outbreak traced back to a gambian giant rat
Who infected a shipment of prairie dogs who have been gone on
To get some people
God damn those
Gambian rats
There was no human-to-human transmission and no doubt
The CDC did their job at Raystown the animal shipments and put out guidance
For people who may have come in contact
Prairie dogs recently to keep an eye out for symptoms
Since this outbreak there has been one case of
Confirm monkeypox in the United States
And it was a person who travel to the US from Nigeria this year
Where they've gotten sick initially and I come
Yeah it is much as it offers an opportunity to learn about public health responses that might
Go unnoticed generally
Or it could even be a good chance to discuss other needs to be better regulation in the exotic pet trade
But ultimately this is a low-priority story
You have no idea why Alex is spending so much time he is liking reads almost this entire article
I mean it's I guess because he likes a monkey box
That does sound reasonable to me it's kind of fun to say monkeypox
You have a decent Theory
It's as good as anything from him yeah I was confused because you did seem to be spending a lot of time on this
Disgusting
I realized
Did I have found
A hole in the space-time continuum
Emma government
Dallas to Denver
We will lock down
Will forcibly inoculate you
We will go to Red Alert you will be considered an anime
A martial law
Carpal
The program
We've got the funk
I can't find the article are the interview talking about
Save these cities were
We're going to be hit with
Smallpox sure there was a risk of it
Like I can find interviews and speeches that he gave
Dating back to like 2001 where
You know the idea of someone release
Smallpox is something that is a fear of hit
But larger picture
This is just the exact same story Alex is telling in the present day but with the
The details swapped out like it's a madlib
All this just overlaps with the present-day in a way that does
Bolster Alex's credibility would actually
Anyone who thinks he knows what he's talkin about think
Twice
The claim that 99.999% of healthcare worker is in
Cops and whatever
They'll refuse the small pack
Fox vaccine
That's the inciting incident
In the 2003 version of this narrative
This isn't true
We talked about it on a recent 2003 episode
Rizzoli Bush Administration initiative post 9/11
We wanted to vaccinate 500,000
Frontline worker
Workers against smallpox
Ultimately only vaccinating about 40,000
Because people didn't see the need for it as
People with autism
Although that number is low Alex's figure is way off
The present-day parallel this is the 2019 vaccine safety Summit where Alex claims that the globalist doctors
We're worried that the jig was up in the Frontline doctors were getting suspicious and wobbly on vaccines
These two events are severely misrepresented by Ali
The reason that the bad guys had to act
Now
They had to do this now
Because everyone was refusing the vaccine right in 2003
And in 2019 the word the doctors are getting wobble
Explain the events
Did Alex's now covering his news
The source of monkeypox popping up
How to scare people in 2003 is the equivalent of the initial covid outbreak in 20
The inciting incident happened which required the globalist
What are plans in motion to scare the pub
In the back clip
Alex even uses the same goals videoscribe to the bad guys now lockdown cities Forest vaccines martial law
It's tempting to look at the consistency that exists here with his fears and convince yourself that he was onto something
That's missing the bigger picture
This isn't a prediction that Alex amazed that he ended up being right about in 2021
It's ridiculous Megan involves his interpretation of the world in 2003 and he was
Wrong
Total b*******
When you see him repeating the game of the present-day that's all he's doing
Except this time the stakes are way higher because covid was a big deal
And it wasn't handled as responsibly as other outbreaks
To the past that I was his fear Monger to Boughton profited off of
In 2003 Alex knows the monkeypox
Smallpox aren't real threats mostly thanks to widespread vaccination campaign
And that's what works best for him
That's The Sweet Spot
It needs to be not an actual problem
Business works best when there's no actual pandemic there's just the insinuation of 1 and Rising vaccine rate
Happening which is what the globalist
The ark
2003 is almost certainly would Alex always wants yeah
2020 and the way this is gone is a mess
Steak
For him
This is this is no good
It's also really really important to remember that
The reason he's describing the lockdowns and all of that stuff
Is because that's what you
Have to do
When an outbreak gets out of control at all we've seen it to be embellished exaggerated version of what you have to do
Exactly
And
That didn't happen B
Because of
Anybody
Other than the people who listen to the people like Alex Jones
It's it's self-perpetuating in some ways were so encouraging if they
You didn't act like they idiots they are so it's it's not that he's right about something it said he
He's very worldview
Predicates
This happen
Well it's it is really bizarre thing that I'm thinking about as I listen to this and it's like
The thing is that
Works the best
Is
A functioning CDC people following Public Health guidance
Alex yelling about how it's b*******
Joanne retainment
Newton on the folks who are
Arise wide-open and
They gave him money for his dumb s***
But they live alone
Weird people who sponsored
So you have that and I think that is kind of
Of balance
That can exist
Probably would
Think that's a preferable State of Affairs because this is easy to go back on
He's right here in 2003
When smallpox and Munch
Monkeypox don't end up becoming a big deals I don't become
Something that is a a massive outbreak
It's great cuz then you know people are getting vaccinated and you look at they tried to scare you into it with stars
There's no
Lost that wasn't already lost
Like you're just going to
I don't know
Convince anti-vax people to be anti-vax
Stable
In some ways
But now in 2021
How do you go back you can go back
It's too late it's too late
I mean it's just
Just that
F***** up like
Everybody
On the far right
Is so much better off whenever they're nowhere near making any decision
We talked about that like a very early episode
Sing about s*** that isn't a problem and you can bother yourselves yet I think I think a big part of that is that
Last couple decades in particular but also
Yeah going back even further than that I think the conservative
Sort of
That the media sphere especially
Has been characterized
Just that they've gotten the most traction out of
Being like
Agitating and opposition does not really work all that well when they're in
Aether there's power
It has to be against something
Right I mean you can't untie the like
Late 70s Rebirth of the
Conservative dumb dumb
As as
Thought leader
From
The beginnings of
Which people going all hog-wild and trying to exacerbate income inequality
And as you see the quality of life go down for these people
They get more and more Angry combine that with
A media sphere that's feeding them
Terrible information and making them angry at the wrong people and we see
How
Billionaires in babe
Billy Brown over the past summer years
You know it's just
It's babe it's created
It's manufac
And then it's perpetuated by itself
You know
And the other the other point that I wanted to make two is that
Like what I hear Alex doing dozen 2003 and think about
Like the way he's behaved
Like
I see it as like a
Just a gamble that he does it always paid off in the past
And this time did not
Yeah they this time
There was an actual
Real Public Health crisis
It was mishandled
People responded to it poorly
And
In the past
That is not been the case
It's worked out
To maintain
Balance
Before and this time
It's just completely out of whack
Yep
Yep the whole world sucked
Well
The good news is we learn about heaven
We're not there yet
Alex's Pizza
Who calls before Craig Roberts shows up
Atlanta this one caller
I wonder if you can answer this for our
This caller asks if Alex
Meditate
What do you think dance
I'm going to say that the answer is prayer is meditation my friends
What do you think
The most power
And
No I don't matter
The reason I
I can see
Will
R-Truth
And
My whole life
Afraid
The man or whatever you want to call
In my opinion the truth
No matter how
Strong someone else
Never impose
Real control on me
Like maybe
Translate
Shut up heavy
Everything you believe it listen I think you're coming at this from a good place but everything you believe is Ben
Alive meant to trick you
Meditate all you f******
I believe in self-empowerment but only if you're gone
Great if I wanted to breathe in and breathe out I would be
We doing it while I'm at the firing range so here's here's where we get to Craig Roberts
Colonel Craig Rob
This is comic
Akon
And I want to talk
The government
Cars
5 hours driving
About how
So this is just
Hilarious
And in many ways
The big thing I think is really funny is just that side-by-side
We're going to talk about geopolitics
What it's like in heaven
Yeah
Yeah yeah yeah
It's a little bit difficult to take anybody seriously whenever they're due
Netflix
The religious local news version of like that's
That's like in and after this we've got the kitten that can't be stopped
Get that kind of think I want to be clear to like
I think it's a lot of people have
Sort of
Maybe we could call it Mystikal
Experiences or something
Transcendence sure means a lot to them personally impugn anybody for whatever they take
From whatever experience
They have
I would not
Take seriously bickering
About
Like
If I hadn't
Experience have you had an experience
We went to a place and I had a detail about
The place
And we argued about
I think
That that's
Dumb
I like getting into too many specifics or taking anything to literally is kind of dumb
And
I think that's what they're
Yeah I mean somebody sent me some of that that clip of what's his dumbfucks sayings
God can't hear prayers through a mask
Sono
If you if you are at the place where you have to say
God can hear prayers through it
You've already lost
Yeah I think
I think that I brought this up in the show before but
Twice
My grandparents
Gave me a book
For Christmas
That was a tourist guide to heaven
It was outrageous thing
Zika think they had like
The question-and-answer like frequently asked questions
I'm like are the streets really made of gold
Totally
That's not my heaven Dan I don't know why but to me it always seems a little bit like
A waste
The time
Oh yeah 22 engage in like
Trying to put
Physical
Details on
Something good spirits I don't know
It seems silly and
Enjoy it existing on Alex's show it's really hard to shake
From a lot of people's minds the image of God as that old white guy with a beard you know and it's like
Really two are we there
Streets are lined with gold
About why are you going
Is there an economy that was the point in heaven is their scarcity in heaven
Yeah that is going to be the angriest day of my life. Life is honestly I think streets lined with gold
Would look tacky
I don't think it would be the best
Joyce Emily I don't think it would be the best choice
Adidas not a good metal to walk on
I don't think it is there would have to be people who were cleaning the gold streets all the video
Oh my God
Anyway Alex and Craig Roberts
Talk
Do you want to cover first and I think Craig Roberts is totally right okay
And
Or do you want
Need to hear
The after-death experience
Killearn that they do not
Everybody's like
Okay I did die it several times
Went to heaven saw doll but first
You really need to talk about troop mobilization as we go that like the logistics we need to get into the weeds
Cuz people are listening
Okay
People need to know that we've got to get two clicks
So I think
You know we're very interested in
Knowing it's Alex
Thinks he's fighting the literal biblical devil
In 2003
And I can say I'm much more confident saying I think he thinks he is
But I can definitely tell you that Craig robbed
Thinks that there is the literal
Workforce
To do will make you rich
I forget what happened
You know you're probably going to be
Basically yeah
Minded before I do some
Regroup
Get out here and it doesn't matter
And they killed and they step on
The fascinating clip because I
Did Craig Roberts sounds like he almost
Kind of understands the teaching them as a child that if you did anything wrong you go to hell
Abusive then Scare Tactics really does seem like he almost gets
Can't make it all the way
The jump
There's a good chance that Greg is right
That is hellfire and brimstone upbringing did instill in him a bit of self-accountability and that
You may have
Consider his actions more than he would have otherwise but
Because he was afraid of going to hell
If that led to him being a better person I suppose that's good but I would
Strongly dispute the position that
Fear of hell is the only way to create self-accountability
Teaching kids that they're going to hell if they don't behave well might be a way to convince kids to pay well but it's also a really good way
Way to mess with their head
And give them enough baggage they may take years to unpack it all in therapy
And there's all kinds of detrimental effect has beaten as a child and I turned
Great t.i.
MMA pot
There's a
I certainly in my own life and the life of many other people I knew growing up in the church
This idea of
If you do bad you're going to hell
Is much more detrimental than it is helpful in terms of creating
Self-accountability
I did one of the big things that it does
Is it creates
Intense
Feelings of
Shame and
Guilt
Because
Messing up is human
You're going to make mistakes
You're going to do things that are wrong and evitable Aid
And then if you've convinced yourself ahead of time that you're going to hell for it
All you're doing is guaranteeing that you'll have some kind of
Intense guilt
But you'll need to
To deal with somehow
That you don't need to have
And
I don't know it just seems like a dumb
Beer
It is one of those things where you know when you're in school we should spend more time on like understand
Standing idioms in metaphor
And you said you like
Pull up your Treasures in Heaven you're like oh that's a metaphor that he's using it because
Material things are valueless and then other people are like
No
He means that if you do good in heaven you get a fuk
Bucking bison
Yeah right
Equal system
It makes sense it wasn't that a brochure
About heaven that I got
I mean you're not
So when you do go to heaven you get a bike
And
You no longer have to worry about socialism nice
Right now
And yes
We are judged on how we
And yes we need to plant
Future Ferrari
Prison camps
Perfect North
Whatever
Now's the Time
Well my uncle
Therealak
Which brings up his uncle again
One of the guys I find really interesting is that
Ask Craig keeps talking about all of these
The experience
I only keeps going back to his uncle
That's just alike
Can we talk about my uncle like I know you haven't experienced
You're my guest
Yeah
It's almost like the radio version of somebody asking you a question because they only want to tell you the
Their answer to that question or like
Would you play the million ducks are a million billion.
My God you're you thought about this and I have not had a thought
Well but also Alex
I think he thinks it's one-upping
You know like six times in the ambulance
And he can't make the story about him personally so it has to be about him
At the very least 81 situation
Uncle who died a bunch of times
Amen
We get a revelation
That I have been waiting for for a
Very long time already knew but not heard Alex Jones
I actually layout
But yeah
Rebellious one my dad was the older son the
Victorian
Finally Alex
The case for a very long time no your dad
The super into the John Birch Society John Birch Society
Beaches okay now we've gone from
My dad was around John guy who maybe had a few books
Books on Earth
We had a lot of books
And it's like it wasn't that big of a
The f****** furniture from way back
2deck
Games ago my dad was
The f******
Monster High reviews
He was given speeches for the John Birch
Obviously deeply involved
By Alex tries to pretend that he wasn't because he knows
Coconut
Point the
The label of Bircher is
More baggage than he wants
Soylent is uncle died about
Sometimes and then he went to a place
Where there are Crystal City is
Grown
The waiting room
Went through toll
Ena
Praying for him amazing
Wow
Wow Crystal
Cities
Getting scolded hey
If if I
Have been doing
Boy Crystal series are what I think of
Heaven
I love it
Wagon
So a story about is his uncle and now it's
Craig Stern
To tell his
Experience
And I got to say
Too much
Preamble
Ono Ono
He goes on and on about his tumor
And stuff I'm going to the hospital and then like
Hubris
The interesting part of the story it's the heaven
It's not the bleeder take for granted that you had a bad time and then you die
Cancer was bad
Yeah if it can't be like well I was in the hospital for a little while and then my wife came to me and we talked to the doctor
On and on and I think that even Alex is getting a little pissed
Nobody knows people who've Gone to Heaven Bryce what I want to know I think you can tell
Come on man
Rooms on the gurney
I need a living will I think
Your hemorrhaging is hurdling
We don't have that
Financing
Make through the night before
Robert
Buble
I think I was a little pissed that Craig threw it to break break
How
Dare you know that you can hear the music
Professional
Oh how about you go lead some more army people cuz I'm working right
Right now
We go back
From
And we get back and Craig's I can go back to Alex Jones's show I hears the host Alex
Every great he does not but we finally get
To hear about going to heaven
Amanda
For whatever they were going to do
Play
I was
To another point
Large
And
It was around this because
When you get there you just know
You know
Receive or
You have this ability
I know what's going on around you
Music downloader
Cool
Feels great
Also there's a second
I do like that to you I can either put the tube in my nose and instantaneously a Zoomer I was almost like I was on a drug
Almost like they I mean they had me count backwards
It's from 100
And I remember making it to 95 and then God
It was definitely God
Had nothing to do with men Mannitol
So Craig is alone
And this big waiting room
Thai place
And they're too
Two-door like in Beetlejuice
Somebody standing right behind
I don't feel like this is a bad boy
The good place
It's probably the size of a
A medium-sized
School auditorium
Inside
Some type
Entryway
With one that I would leave if I was taking off the office
It's pretty standard I think you
This kind of picture that you
An image that a lot of people have
Yeah you know what kind of like the architect in Renee Trick
We talked about this before when I was working at a God camp everybody used to make each other pass out
Cuz we couldn't do drugs
A disorder stores a.m.
What they would say is something like
Oh I felt like I had lived in entire other life and I felt like my dream has been for 20 years long
And all of that stuff and your Lego you were only out for 5 seconds or some
Something like that and it's like
Yeah man the brain does that s***
That's how it works
That's what what are we doing are we doing with a waiting room why does heaven have a waiting room
Yeah that does seem a little
Seeing weird human thing a human thing
God is like a listen we got overflow
Can't handle it right now busy day
Yeah I think I think the other thing too like I mean to you no dreams you can have
Dreams that feel like they go on very long though in in
Actual time that's not very like that
On a very basic level thinking
What about that
Time experience
That's not some divine
And if you've ever had
Sleep paralysis you still chemically shutdown in your brain works perfectly fine you feel like you're
Hallucinating and going absolutely crazy
So
But when you're in heaven in the waiting room
There's that there's someone behind
Charlotte School
It's a good guess what your young again
There are new
Really matter
Elena
Family
Everything that I was feeling
Young
Now you understand heroin you just figured it out
Is that yes
Yeah it is almost like
You were
Heavily burdened by
Your physical body collapsing and then
You were
Experiencing relief from all that sort of
Some sort of
Really
Notice that I was worried
I didn't even look at my body
Right behind me
What's going on
I'm a burger
Does he think that
You know
People like
Indigenous people don't use the bathroom
Nope no idea
Nope there's no clue until you explain it to them
They have no idea.
It's a place where you do.
It's like it's like what you do now but different
So this being
Who do you think this is God
Noah camp
Niger hanging out behind you
It's not God behind you
Knockout
I'm going to go with
Let's say green dragon
Green Dragon green dragon I'm going to go Game of Thrones God is a huge Game of Thrones fan green dragon
Missed the mark by a little
I know
Playmate
Backyard fence
Vietnam
The kid
Bear
Like a picture with a celebrity
It's okay I'm with you
Anna I'll be with you
That's it
Imaginary friend
Broderick
I do like
The idea that Alex is there I hope
Gheenoe
He had to have known that imaginary friends are real that have it right I mean he has to
The presentation of like the pre-interview is when Alex
And Craig Roberts
Went down to Kansas City to do that babe radio
Feel like it
Probably could have come up
Although I would also believe that Alex wasn't list
Cuz you wanted to talk about how his uncle died about
Alex
You speak very good
If he hadn't internalize this part of the story
Yeah boy I can't imagine having somebody that I taken so seriously tell me that imaginary friend
Pens are real in heaven
I was in the waiting room
Behind me was
1 ft tall version of my childhood
Imaginary friends are real and having guys
Waiting room Imaginary Friends
Socialism is it there Heaven is capitalist
But also you should know that
Your childhood Imaginary Friends
Also your guardian angel
Everybody I also knew by the way this is my guardian
Sky
Attorney lot of time so I could
Everything you do in life
Like this track
A remembrance
Everything
Information everything
How to make one point
Very clear
If Alex is concerned about the surveillance state
He should be really concerned about that
If there are aliens or angels with
What's the number to Lee record every good or bad
I can't imagine with the NSA like I would even come close to comparing to that
They have been secretly killing and Reviving people in a flatliner situation this entire time
Call modern technology has taken from that waiting room
According to Alex's own in
Higher career
What's being described is
This darkest
Culinary school
Oh boy
Can I really want to go back to how many jobs
That Craig Roberts
This ad
Where he has been in control of people living or dying
Do you understand that that
I don't like this I don't like this and it's like that kind of thing like if it if you have
This belief system
And that helps you get through the day
Find
I don't want you with a gun I haven't done enough look
Looking into
Colonel Craig Roberts
So
I don't know what positions he's had or not
I take everything with a little bit of a grain of salt super soldier as well
I don't know I don't think he's ever been on Camelot
But
You know
You tried the best friend who is imaginary is your guardian angel and they have a chip in them that recordes all the good things you do
Religious
So
Actually answers a really
Deep philosophical theological question and that is
There's so many human
How does God know all the good and bad things you do because at the end of your life you've got to be judge
Whether or not you can go to heaven
Remember thinking
When I heard that it was
Does ineffable remember in the Bible we see through a glass Darkly
Sure you know that Kai
Ineffable impossible to f
I do not say that
Don't have that ass
Some f****** computer chips literally affable
Is a f****** snitch
Okay in the end we got it
Came before there's no way that
Alex cannot abide by this
Can or cannot do what's the point
And we're arguing about whether or not your imaginary friend is a snitch or a witness
This is if you replace God was Santa Claus it's the same conversation
It's very similar
Outlook
I being a little disrespectful
And some people may think
But that's not
Appropriate
Sure
I would like
To present to you
An argument
I'm at is that
Alex
Could not be more disrespectful to his own belief system
And his own ideas
Listen to this s*** when they come back from
Alright
Back on
Ladyandthetramp
He interrupts the story of going to heaven to do a water filter add
After bringing his water filter sponsor to talk about like this special that they have Man story of going
Heaven is not
Finished by any stretch
They went to break
It was a cliffhanger of we're going to get back to your
Experience in heaven
Do we do not
We get into a water filter commercial
What are you going to do
Whenever the app whenever your holy book very
Clearly states
Except Marion Commerce and religion is
Is a great idea
Whenever the person you've named your belief system after
Has
Explicitly said to you
That rich people will make it to heaven
Every time
When you know it's a good idea
This twist happened
I literally
How you say this
Sincerely
Had to stand up
Walk around the room
I put my hands on my hips
I'm sort of breathing a little bit
Can't do it
I can't I can't make a joke out of
Like
This is so disrespectful to the idea that you're having an interview with somebody about like
You went to the afterlife
And you're trying to present this as a real thing
And what you do in the middle of it is slip in an interview with somebody else
Who you're selling their ship
As we all know
Crazy Jesus
Said buildup that I treasure in heaven
And if
You are in heaven
The number one treasure you want to have is this water filter buddy
Big Berkey Burke well you know there was that time that Jesus
You know
He went and volunteered at the money changing tables
I would love to do this
Money money guy
I even told him there's a scratch scratch and dent sale on this water filters
Panda
Take advantage
One of these was about a year ago
Last time
Weather filters
Dial ticket
Alberti products
Okay well first of all with the
Little bit more scratch
If I were this guy
I would probably be mad at Alex
Because
I'm now being presented his own who's
Interrupting the story of Heaven
Scratch and dent
Sale water filter just remember that this is your last chance to get these we're not going to run this sale again just
Just like this life is your last chance for salvation in the next ladies and gentlemen we need you to get these water
Filters stored up in heaven
It's like a it's
Like a scavenger
Like a parody of
What Alex is doing
It's insane
It is insane it is I love it
It's amazing
It's just that that like
If you see this this is almost another part of that weakest link in the chain of right-wing propaganda this is the way
Weakest link in the chain of Christian propaganda of just like
Once you see how glaring this s*** is
There's no way you're not going to find smaller versions of that
F******
Everywhere it's just remarkable
How old little care Alex take
Separate these kinds of
Except his show
Like I think there's a way that you could sell water filters and interview guy about going to heaven on the same show
He's probably shouldn't do the ad in the middle of the story is going to have an unreal
Unreal it's a little tacky
We're careless
This is twice we've achieved the story fro coming up
We're teasing a heaven story through commercial but that's just a reality of
Stories are very boring and we have gotten to some of the
The details like
From childhood was behind you
Snitches on you're not going to be able to get over if you if that's part of your belief system
Good luck to you then if I were Alex I might have gone to an ad to
So a good boy when the guys lives
Your imaginary friend is your guardian angel and he tells God all the bad and good things that you've done
Maybe I would bail too but I have to go back
Yeah that's
The difference
Phelps
Tell you
Tell Santa what is whether you've been bad or good
Santa check his list here's where we break off because Alex
Instead of being done with this
I clearly
Bizarre interview at this point
I decide to go back
After the water filter at
Promoting
Gun
You use it everyday
Recap
Are you
You are
Angel
So that's a set
The table pretty well we're all caught up
You're in heaven
I would have preferred you said imaginary friend instead of guardian angel
We got to keep this
Respectable
He got some info downloads
Which is interesting about the NSA we've always talked about our modern technology
Nobody is thought about death
Sure Alex
I was receiving information
And this information
Acknowledgement that I was there
Take me on
Later
Is it
Isn't it
Your house is going to the other end
I don't know
People that are running
Down the road
What happened
Very very interesting
I felt like I hit
Gone
Maybe free
There
Because
And
Call Alyssa
Hours
3 minutes
Long-winded
Wow so either he goes on to say that
He was dead for like that 3 minutes later
Interesting because
Lead me to believe that there is a concept of time cuz he said within the human clock it was like 3 minutes
There is a
Yeah
His own telling of it is like whether I guess time is still real
I don't I don't I don't know
This info download thing is
It's fascinating
Tomato
You know
I think
It's it's kind of Fairly obvious and I feel like more people telling me stories
It seems like
Heaven is limited by your imagination and not the other way around
You know what I'm saying like
It seems like
Maybe your
Creativity or lack thereof is the limits of how we're going to get into that as a related
Info download thing
In a second
Where's we have one specific
Check from the saddest vision
Specifics
I got one of them
Chemotherapy after that
Better
It was all worth our time Coronavirus
Wow
So don't listen to doctors
Apparently is a good medical advice
From the vision
You know
You were
You were dead
Before medical science
You want to stay that way
Also you probably weren't actually most likely just dropped out
Put into an induced coma and you are f******
Confide
At we get this
This this message here
I'll get a little bit more information about the message
That he gets
Get sent
He got sent back
I was sent back
Information
Years my research work
Fire start I was gone
You have to live right now you better live
Correctly because
The New World Order
Grounding
There is a part of me that as I was listening to this
I think Alex stole the store
The info download the the beginning a message that you have to fight the evil
Like II reminds me of stories that he tells now about getting Visions from God when he was at
This time. Younger
Yep nope definitely younger
No you're right
You think God giving him his mission and such like telling him
Hit a big package
Get downloaded it like
Xenia
Panoramic view of the world and everything
Like I
Would expect
That if I were Alex
And I were having this conversation with this guy
It seems like Oye I would interject with my story very similar to yours if it is
It is that similar and you're willing to discuss anything
Seems like that would be what you bring up
I get a real very strong scent
What's that maybe one of the reasons
The Craig Roberts
Isn't around his get Alex's
Take a note store
That's
Yeah the details of this
Astoundingly similar to story
Alex tells now about abs
About himself Smith
This one
Piece of
Resistance to my own suspicions
I'm at is based on like what maybe you just wouldn't want to talk about things publicly
You know like maybe you would have some discretion about Llorona
Experience
But Alex does bring up how he has psychic dream there we go
So it doesn't mean like
A penny in for a pound of clean literally talk to I guess his imaginary
Right and I believe this year that correctly or did his imaginary friends say to him
The chemo
I'll kill you
No no no
Get all that stuff is going to kill you
Get off at
And all healed
Oh okay I heard it as like a man
Interesting Guardian Angel that's not the way I heard it I don't think that's what I said but
Yeah they sometimes the ears hear what they wanted
When you have
A guy who's presenting himself as having a like this
Divinely originating
Packet download of information that was super in Port
And Alex on the present-day says that this happened to him at the beginning of his career
You think that he would
Commiserate about this if Alex is willing to talk about anything
And he is willing to talk about stuff
Like I said
Either profit
Pinstripes
Once every two years
How do I get on the air
Intuit
New York
And I have the information but
Where I saw
The tower
So I think that all the 9/11 truthers and the we are change folks and I everybody was like Alex.
Gerald is always right
You know what year
What you're really reinforcing is his
Yeah he's a he's if you say Alex is right
Then you are taking on
That he is a psychic
Who can see the future
Not someone who is understanding the future you're not defending somebody who's done a lot of research
And knows things and understand
Like
Still stand behind things like loose change
Disproving it totally cuz know this isn't based on
Any kind of
Actual report this is a
Based on Bible
We've that 9/11 was an inside job
It's not based on
Proofer
No dents
It's based on the fact that I had a prophetic dream ahead of time
I knew this
Well I mean
It look
Doc Brown didn't worry too much about all those facts and stuff
He had a dream when he hit his head in the bathroom and the flux capacitor came to be
Interesting differentiate this
Dark brown is real
At the fake store say you're going to tell me King Arthur is real
Absolute Madman
John degrandpre son of Uther Pendragon
Has come to Legend
That is true
I find this all very dicey and sketchy
Alex should
2 because he wants some specific information about taking formation
Is that the great God
Well if it's from God I would want
Pacific Steel yeah but unfortunately that's not the way this
More knowledge
Was that
Information
Music
Kill Trump
Oh that's super convenient that really is super convenient convenient
Love that because now you don't have to give any specific information to people
Could judge whether it's accurate or not or
Anything you can
Just give yourself
Built-in
Credibility whenever you tell anybody anything
This particular thing I am telling you
Is from God
Now I didn't know this like 20 minutes ago but it was in that filing cabinet that God gave me
And I can't confirm this order
I didn't know it before.
No but you have to listen to me baby
The courts and now is the time for me to tell it to
This is almost like
Scam artist
Body armor
Yeah yeah
You know it's been the same
F****** Playbook
200 years
This
Exact conception of the information that I don't have access to until I need it
That's what Steve Quayle says also about this like Vision that he has
The two of them both have
Exact same explanation for why they don't have information the court until they need it
Divinely-inspired
And you know why
Cuz cop out there fun
Yes
This is a really Ironclad way
To never have to
Show you're at space
No and that's why I mean
You know I imagine that the very first reason that we invented a divine anyting
Was just because somebody got ask a question that they really didn't want to answer
The equivalent of
You don't have to do voices when you Channel
Explanation built into the store
Yep it's
I find it I find it suspicious
You can't be preemptively defensive
About why you don't know
You know like if your preemptively defensive that
It suggests to me that you already know you're wrong
So I think that you can have interviews like this are not disrespect
To the person you're interviewing
Like I think
Sharing a
Experiences of
Likes things
You have
Subjective experience of
Discuss those things at end and not
Necessarily pass them off as
This is the truth of the universe Shore
The same time not be like you're dumb cuz you think
You went to a waiting room
I think there's a way that you can
Recognize the subjectivity of it
Recognize what it means to the person you're talking to you without
Universalizing
Right right right Alex does not do that
Sounds about right
Is Buena verse Eliza
When do a coma for weight
Happened to him
It really does happen
The problem is
4 people singing for 2 seconds
Yeah this is
This is him saying this is all real this is all like this is all truth
Everybody knows it that's why I said devil
Created scientist
Explain to you that
Drugs do things to your brain
Yep yep
So when Alex said
I think now is the time to talk about some of my experiences
I thought well obviously he's going to get into
How he also had an information download
He doesn't talk about a prophetic dream
Call Herbert
And at one of those dreams
Don't you
New York
I learned this when I was young
That you're a psychic
Do you have prophetic to
There is
The other side
And I have been
Seen it
There's there's an interesting
Sing
I just
I can't accept
Somebody who is
Is like I
Make reporting based on profit
That I had I have dreams and this is going to
Affect my coverage of the new
Right
I can't accept that
Living simultaneously in the same space as someone who like everything I talked about it documented
You can't both have because here's what happens if you both have all the evidence
And you have a prophetic dream okay
Okay
So maybe you were dreaming about the
Or
Why did you need the evidence
You had the prophetic dream
Or
Who cares about either one of them
I think that
I think it's an inability or unwillingness to choose a lane
I think it's because Alex realizes that like
I don't actually have prophetic dreams
If I tried to do that I'd be wrong on a lot
So I better Edge everything with fake evidence to
If you're hedging then I don't believe you
I mean
In this kind of circumstance
This is an all-or-nothing situation
You've either been to heaven or not so you've either proven that heaven is real or not
There's no other way around
I don't
I think it's appropriate for like a magician
Let's say
To do magic
Insist their magic
Right I've been also explained how they
There is the problem
I could handle that kind of an act
So we're getting closer to Alex
Being
Against the literal.
Well I mean he's already said that
That's how the enemy
That's why the enemy has all those quack
It's right so that has to be the end
I do feel like
I am very close to being able to say
But Alex does believe he's fighting the devil
In 2000
Experience
Connected to that
Let that world
Okay
When your dad your dad
There is a spiritual war
A war going on all around us right now we may not be able to see the spiritual or
And your imaginary friend
Doing right here
Against
Nobody
Gary Ridgway
This is not the world we lived
Right now in heaven
So
Robertson saying that Satan's globalist socialist
Crowd some people just won't listen some people
Sand
Physical War
Well the physical Warriors
Information was why would that be the war if it's the war for heaven
Exactly
I think that the way that Alex is responding to this
Leeds 12
Suspect that he believes
It's not him
Explicitly laying out that I'm fighting The Devil Ride
But it's
Nuages closer
It's swimming in the same pond
And being like
I like this Bond I'm on days where I
Feel comfortable was the only the only thing
Do is
That I mean yeah the only question then is
If you
Received message specifically from God
Then
The then
Does your Christianity include
The devil
Cuz if it does
Then
You believe you're fighting a literal devil
The only way he's not fighting the literal devil is if he doesn't believe that the devil is real
Yeah
So
He's fighting the literal Christian do I think so I think his entire career has been predicated on
Trying to trick people into think
Making his political beliefs in reality he's fighting
He's just
I think so you know what if that's the case
You've done a pretty good job of obscuring
Yeah yeah he really has people do not
Think of him as nothing more than a televangelist
I think I think that he's made himself so weird and
Interesting
On other levels
Pullo's
Byzantine Mazes of bigotry
You kind of don't don't think of him primarily as somebody who
Is preoccupied with fighting
The literal devil
Pretty fair to say I'm still going to keep looking around to 2003 watershed
Yeah this
This it convinces me
Beyond A Reasonable Doubt I declare
Guilty of fighting the literal Christian devil
I think I tentatively agree with your your verdict
But I still want
I still want more information
No I want to say I'm fighting the devil
And also like
Going back to 2003 and finding episodes like this it's like there's gold in them thar Hills again
Yep this is the problem with what you believe
Nobody wants it to be real
You can't go about making it real getting Trump elected and all that chicken whole world
Just learn your f****** lesson
Quit beer and it's Alex
Complaining about two TV shows
Selling
Witchcraft
And then I think Craig Roberts
Might be
Not cool people be
The New World Order
Colonel Robert
Then that were seen
It's okay if you're almost
We're getting into
Working art
Wild wild
Just got to get that Hitler in there sooner or later
And maybe education took over the
Yeah that's the problem is a problem
Probably the thing that he hates most yeah
This episode was so
While
To listen to It's So enjoyable on a number of levels
Compared to a specialist present
Do you have
A guy who went to heaven
And I was trying to interview him
Am trying to have some semblance of like
This isn't a ridiculous interview
Meanwhile the guy is talking about his
The imaginary friend from childhood being there behind him in the waiting room without him
And then Alex Goes to off
F****** interview with this water filter sponsor it's just
Onion of parody
That that him
Having the gall to be like you know like those fake Christians those 501 c 3 Christian right is like
Are you just mad because they don't pay taxes
Because you're doing the same s*** man
You went to a f****** water filter
Interview in the middle of a story about heaven Christian
With their money all of these Christians obsessed
It's a great price at MSRP but this
Is 140
Yeah
So I think we have
More reason to believe that Alex thinks he's fighting very literal devil and has forever
We will dig deeper and
And find whatever we can find a 2003 cuz it's
Indeed we will
We have a website its knowledge buy.com
We are also on Twitter is that now just were fighting at go to bed Jordan at Imaginary Friends guardian angel
You're my guardian angel dad
And when we get to have it I'll find out you've been imaginary the whole would be weird
Imperial laughing at nothing
But Garfield without Garfield knowledge fight without
Randomly laughing at my own f****** jokes
Yeah that be brutal
Gastodon a show and
We had to record our end of the audio to send to them
And I've gone
Listen to the whole thing or anything but I will check your ex or the audio sounds okay and it is bizarre
You're just one into the conversation imagining your audio isolated
God that was when we were when I was attending the D&D show together I was I was isolated
Everybody's individual tracks
And you
Could just pick out weird sections whereby just wanted to clip that
Without context
Beautiful everybody sounds insane everybody sounds nuts
Indeed we will until then neon Leon dzx Clark
I'm Daryl rundus
And now here comes
The sex robot
Holding