Damn important swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Lean and talk a little bit about Alex
June
Giordano Giordano
Look I don't know a lot about a lot of thing or at
I know a lot about some very specific
Specialist you're not a squirrel
All things that I'm unaware of
And I believe is on our last episode I mentioned that I was starting to play like a deck building game
Yes indeed you should try Magic the Gathering
Cuz there's a way you
Can play it on a computer
I didn't know
I wear underwear
Me too I didn't know that thing existed
And
I started
Goodbye you roped me into this s*** to you dickwad
It's been a couple days of like
You going to dabbling around
I don't really know what I'm doing exactly
Because it was demonic
Scratching a lot of inches
It's scratching a lot of inches of the like
Card collecting
The sort of bizarre magical things of course of course creatures
Are you love Byzantine rules basically like logic puzzles
In a game for because there's so many conditional things about like
You can only play this if and only if these
Conditions are mad
Yeah
It's it it does tickle that a little bit
It's like a it's like a
You've just had more imagination and you didn't know what the other player had
Yeah
Yeah it also is really making me feel a little bit of like this reclaimed
Stuff from
When I was younger the stuff that I wasn't allowed to play
Eminem you know it makes me realize that I was also the one who decided to accept that rule when I was younger
I couldn't play it but I can't
We are playing another kind of wish I had
That's really cool that I could be online that doesn't make a mess
What is my house worth
Yeah that yeah that could be real trouble
Considering the number of Magic the Gathering cards there are if you got to Intuit this whole place
To be f***** it's over on it so I don't lose
Myself into the Otherworld
Of playing that
I'm struggling we played one match after I dragged her and you murdered me so bad
But now I'm like in the back of my head I'm like
Don't get too into it
It's not that big a deal I know there's a part of me is like
The next time you played and you better beat the s*** out of him or your dad's never going to love you I'm never going to play you again just so you can't
Appreciate
Great and I appreciate the people who recommended that and
To basically inform me that it exists
Cuz I had no idea
Well done
My bright spot it could be I could go with that cuz I have course
Began dabbling as well
Said I'm going to go with be under spoken about album that has just been released it
Very good
Is churches
Churches Olivia
Fantastic
Do like them quite a bit
A couple of standouts and then you got roberts-smith Gaston what being a sad boy for a yeah
Simpson sad boys that's what you should have named the album summer
I also why were the topic of new albums
Do you have the rapper iodine gives a new album called a little above Loki
Listen to it enough
Till I fully Digest
And have strong opinions
2 hour but I enjoyed
Manziel
To go take that up to the lawn
Overwriting Spotify
Sue Jordan today we have an episode where we're going to go back into the past again
The reason is I just need to put Alex on timeout and while I was doing that
I just I felt like I was
Falling down a mountain
Like just like or a staircase hit mystere over and over
Superfund
Honest-to-god
I didn't sign up to
Do an anti vaxxer
Podcast
Hahaha
That is the one thing that I really didn't want
What is podcast
I didn't I didn't sign up when we started doing the show to talk about
Bizarre and stupid
Conspiracies about vaccinations every single
Go around
Otherwise I would have started a podcast about like Robert Kennedy Jr or something
You know into
I just
Why president stuff is
The bomber was trying to find anything that
Could be another angle and I came up with a pretty decent angle that I thought
Would be
Teachable and interesting
And that is to go over an episode of somebody else
Talkin about
Alex interesting interesting okay
The ways that you can
Highlight
Unawareness but other people have when they comment on Alan right
Right Right Alright transparent
Poison which they falling for the tricks that Alex
This is an evolution of our how not to cover Alex Jones series
Snapchat
And so I want to do that I put a bit of time at
Couldn't get over the hurdle of feeling like
I'm being a huge a****** to these people really feel like before you even said it I was like oh no we're going to be dicks.
These people I don't want to be mean kind of impossible to do that without putting
Specific
Person on blast Yahoo maybe is certainly
Small YouTube channel to give you a performing
Prince review exactly
I think there are things that you can learn from it and I think the
I need to find a better way to present that information that doesn't involve Kik
Taking some small YouTube channel is it just feels dirty
We got a we got to do some blind
It was a a Time sink
Yeah for me
And then of course
All my all my efforts and everything get interrupted by Joe Rogan getting
A fuking idiot
So Alex is pretty thrilled that Joe Rogan got covid and he cured himself with Ivermectin
Yep that sounds about like how it went
Yeah I think that people are really missing the forest for the trees on that story when they reporting that he took Ivermectin
Because he says a laundry list of things he took
Yeah he said he threw the kitchen sink at it
Doug z-pack you bought a quadrilateral antibodies
The prednisone
But he was taking tons and tons of stuff
So let's say that any of that help
That's my purse of the Ivermectin helped at all
I think that's the funny thing about science
Is that you can't draw
Conclusion
Unless you
Isolated the variable
If they were just get there going to do it's like
A study and they were like
Let's just give this group a bunch of s***
And then let's say give this group a bunch of different shapes
That would not have learned any
Anything no
No it won't be two different groups of s***
We can maybe make some wild speculation about
These different piles
Do people has better that Pilots yet sure
Maybe when we do it again it'll just be a different file s***
He took all this stuff and one of the things was Ivermectin and it just made me think of like okay
Yeah
I had an infection so I
I took like
Some antibiotics
And also a gummy
Total yeah that sounds about right
I don't know
Cena this is why this
What we missed
Was a real opportunity
To find out if hallucinogenics would cure covid
That's our control experiment for this if Joe Rogan
Gets
Covid he doesn't get to take
Any regular medication
Just rooms
That's what he's
If only he had a commitment to the public health but the science
What we're here for
You know trying to prepare an episode and I see a headline Joe Rogan has covid
Woohoo
Didn't see this coming
That's today
Alright
So I'm sure they'll learn a lot from this
This and that
Everything will be fine
Hahaha
I've no interest
Ms the most sarcastic
And devastating thing you can say to somebody knows just missing their budge
I just saying I'm sure they'll learn about
But next time this will go a lot smoother haha
Enzo all this all this world together and we are left with
June 12th
June 12th 2003
On our last episode of 2003 Alex interview the guy who went to heaven
That is the day before this
Correct
So now he's back
Nubian real Siri
The day before the day we're about to speak of
We had a very serious
Home
And
Just
Discussion about what was in the waiting room to heaven
Yes and Alex allowed a guest
To discuss
How it's your snitch of an imaginary friend that you had
From childhood
And he did not push back on this light
So that means that I'm assuming that
Today I will be
Taking him very seriously
When he complains that the Bass party is still in charge of Iraq correct I will save there are no updates on the back party
Going
Exactly as they have been
On that front
But let's take a little moment say thanks
Send hello to some walks carsick thank you so much and I'll probably want
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Opening arguments
I'm a policy wonk
Andrew Bird
Liza's not a policy wonk but he plays one on patreon thank you so much right now apology want
Value play White
Say what up to so Ross beef
How's your 401k
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Large
Come to the family of Selena
On behalf of Matthew abroad to brought a tree kangaroo into the mix
Kangaroo in the tree or are they is it a type of tree
Depends on if it's
The animal or the magic
Jacquard
The tree Guru
Completely different
Restarting here after Alex stocks
About going to heaven
I mean I guess he's gotten back to Earth now
U.s. can't rule out
North Korea
Reported story
On the border with North Korea
Alex's pretty preoccupied with the idea that we're going to go
Start a fight with North Korea
This point
Easy saying that this leak leaking of the battle plan is an attempt to get
Get them to attack
I got so weak
Can have a war with them
I'd like to point out that none of this
No.
But
That was
What's the plan
Right and I think there's a decent chance that be
Because Alex covered it on his show
He averted this
I mean I didn't hear anybody else
Think about it at the time
I can safely assume that
By talking about yeah it has been all Alex
Save the world once again
By himself this is a little bit you know I guess fear-mongering a little bit putting
Putting more into the the idea that we're going
Going to go to war with North Korea there
At least it's
Cut it like it's on Earth
The problem about when you introduce somebody who has been to heaven
And then the next day you're talking about war with North Korea
All I want to know is what does my imaginary friends think about war with North Korea because he's the one who's going to be keeping track
How I failed
Whenever I go to heaven
Why are we talkin about I think your imaginary friend is
Is against it
Then I can't go to war now can I guess you can
Yeah yeah
I also think there's a big difference between someone being like we're going to war until I'm saying like
All options are on the table
And when it's like Rumsfeld
Assistant or whatever
Anybody has reported on a mean to say
Report directory
So we got to
Unless I'm too along with heaven
And we got a little dose of monkey paw
Yes we did this
Is a preoccupation of Alex
Says oh my God
Gearbox
So much
99%
Medical workers
Now they seem
Everywhere
Well you just might have to have
So there was no attempt
Soar initiation program launched
To try and get the general public native for smallpox
In response
Monkeypox
They should have used Jeff Foxworthy
Because monkey talk
Wow that's not bad just might need a vaccine
Yeah the CDC advises that a very limited set of people get
Smallpox vaccine during this 2003 monkey pox outbreak
These people included people who investigated the monkeypox
Cases people who are in close contact with patient
You got it
And people that directors
Contact with an infected animal
The only way to make it look like an attempt to scare the masses of the public into getting smallpox vaccine is like completely lying about the details of the
Story in exaggerating
Ridiculously which is what Alex is doing
Yeah if your warning is like hey
Have you been around anybody with monkeypox recently or an in
Infected animal
Then get vaccine
You're fine
That's not scaremonger
That's just like a regular
There's a flood around
If you're nearby where the flood is half
Happening
Yeah it's
Doing the least
That you can
Help people make a
Yep good choices
So
Alex's said this
This the
Narrative
At the beginning of it is the 99.999%
Of folks
Rejected the smallpox vaccine
And that's why they needed
To do the SARS and they needed to do the monkeypox over to scare people in order to get
Presumably which would then kill them or something
I guess yes
The covid vaccine real but just
Planet of the past history repeats itself
Yeah and one of the interesting things I've learned this episode
Is that Alex
Made-up let's that
That sounds right
.
But if you've got
Scott
The police
Well
This is not have stats work and I'll Alex the saying is that he made up that number that he cites his me rate of excellent
This was only a plan to vaccinate a total of 1000000 people
Well half of them were in the military on the other half who were Frontline workers like at the
Over 500,000 soldiers did get vaccinated but in terms of civilian
Only 39200
30 + gacha
I was just taking straight numbers that he saw him by
Like who knows what local news Outlet
Presumably about low turnout at
Specific vaccine station
Extrapolating those numbers to be representative of the entire story
No one with an actual vested interest in reporting stories accurately would engage with the
Sick this way cuz it's
Just meaning 100,000 members
Oh well then everything that I like said
Is
Pointless in
Stupid write a dead they're fine
They all got the vaccine they're all fine
So why is he saying all this other s*** there was 500,000 people who got the vaccine at 99.99%
It doesn't make any sense cuz half of them got it
No I know but you can
If you just like
Read a local news article out of Connecticut and you see if there's low turnout at one place and then you try and do that math
But you know you just use that
Fraction that percentage
If in the next five years everybody dies of Monk
Epoch something to be real mad at the military I think the odds of that are love
So yeah it looked
Do you need to understand
About the world
And
Please tell me there's so much
Well here's the thing everything everything that you hear about
You only hear about
Because the globalist want you to
To hear that all that's scary formation
Yeah yeah yeah
If they didn't want you to know about the monkey pox outbreak
You never know about
Noah Brown
Medical journal
Depressed
Call people
Morning
Smallpox
I just think that this is a
The dumbwaiter engagement
I got with
Information
Yeah everything that they tell you is curated and I must
Must be deceived
I suppose that's easier to
I suppose that's an easier thing to come to an easier conclusion in like 2003
It's not the monoculture it's not like you've only got the four channels or whatever
But now if somebody said that you would the only information you get is
Is curated
You'd be like
Dude
I got information coming from everywhere always all the time and it doesn't matter
Doesn't matter
But I think that some of that was true in two
732 I mean the internet was obviously not as
Is it is now but there were there were elements of that
And I think of it like if you're just going to say that
You know even with just like the news channels the mainstream Legacy News Channel sure
If you want to say that everything that they are covering
Ever
Is highly curated because it's what they want you to be aware of or whatever
That's just a lazy way of advocating your responsibility to
Like engage with news
Figure out like
What
There are some things that are probably likes
Sponsored content
4 /
You know you can have a responsibility to to dig through and figure out what's what
Yeah and it's also a good way of saying
You can only trust me never trust anyone else ever about anything especially if they tell you're not
To trust me because again I'm the only person you can trust their lying to you so if they point out all of these things that I lied
I didn't actually know anybody who went to have and all of that b*******
You to know and what I want you to know it's not that
But different than what the heck why they're going to shut me now
I don't need your money
My imaginary friend is broke
Imaginary Friends imaginary car as is a
Blew a fuse
I would love to pay him back but I owe him twenty bucks so man we're all screwed here in this case adjust a mountain
That he's got imaginary loan sharking
That guy
The imaginary Lonestar
Do you do not want to f*** with that
He's too good
Sharks are somebody's friend
The imaginary must be somebody's imaginary friend
Shrew
A real sad day for the real said day-to-day life of the imaginary LoJack friend but what if I cure it
Wild in the mafia or something like that you might have an imaginary love sucks
Possible
Because when your Kik you look up to
To your father doesn't matter if your father was a brutal lodestar
Protection rackets that's not what's important
What's important is that he's your dad
I think we have some bad predictions so far monkeypox seems like
Bigger deal to Alex than the rest of the world Trail
The somehow he's thinking that's going
Tube used to give everyone
Smallpox
The nuclear war with North Korea thing is
Also apparently the draft
Coming back
Also I'm mr. Rumsfeld
North Korea
Wind-up do you and your family and you'll be all for it
Aunt Tara
1/4
That is really condescending for something that is
Love that smug tone
Call boy
Shout out to everybody who thinks Alex is right about everything
On this episode nobody has been to heaven
I will say that
But
Alex does have Aaron zelman
The guy who runs
Jews for the preservation of firearms ownership
R a
Support at this point
NRA
Brighton 2003 but he's in favor of this organization and then gunownersofamerica
But before Aaron zelman shows up Alex takes
Call
Batman is call is so funny in 2021
Warrior on the air go ahead
Alex
Talking about
Cragar robber
Work yesterday and
I like that was
A very good
Like even though
Some might consider that a
Materialism
No
That you do have to do so
Look like there again
Was that
Nothing
Against DIA
Send your family you still have to try
Because you are going to answer
For what you do
I also wanted to
I just want to host
Pics of aliens
He's robotoid
Come across Ciara
It's important to me
Maintain credibility in NatWest
Patriots
Idiots
Proven
Oh really don't mix it things that can't be proven like your imaginary friend is waiting for you to snitch when you get to heaven
Man that clip really f**** me up
I don't know maybe I'm dumb
Maybe I'm done listening to that clip because they want
I think it's a powerful delusion
Being mutually reinforced
That clip is funny the day after he talks to someone who went to heaven
It's also funny considering where he's
Like what type of s*** that Alex covers now
In the past
Would look at his jet like if you modulated The Voice
Of Alex's show in the present-day so we couldn't tell it was him
You might not even be able to tell his voice his voice
A pitch adjuster you play it for him he be like this purse
Trying to make the Patriots look terrible
Hundred percent would be like this guy is
Is f****** killing the movement destroying Alex
Been the president
Would be the
Perfect foil for Alex
Yeah but I mean I feel like Alex in the present would have a pretty unbeatable argument which is
Is just like
Look at how stupid that guy is
What he was saying is
Tone it down so you can be credible in the real world
What one
What's going as far and as
The hardness
Loud as humanly possible
True
Maybe I feel like maybe that guy's an idiot
I mean I know he's in
There we go
I was looking in the mirror when I said that I think I might be the dump
One here
Strange hits
Really it's really straight
Cuz it seems like he's making a really reasonable point
But not like that what you was trying to differentiate himself from like David Icke
That's what you would say about him back in the day and now they're best friends
A sort of
Timing thing
Nina
Duet
Go crazy at the right time
Don't be David I can go crazy too soon
When the going gets weird the weird turn pro
What you got to do
You got a running president
The going is getting weird
Money wins it's all over
So Aaron zelman comes in and I don't know
Inasmuch as
Somebody just like wants
People to be allowed to own guns
Vine
Sure but he troubles me in other ways
Picking up a spider
And
The master
Long range rifle
I would have to peel an onion anymore
Coronavirus
You'll learn how to master
Range rifles
Cancer spread
OK Google
Disappear
Holyshit
Cut that level
Sierra zellman's coming in and he's like big I'd learn to f****** use a sniper rifle
Self
And it's going to your going to have to be on a rooftop shooting everybody
Why are you even saying sniper rifle you don't need a scope
Holy
Yeah that's upsetting
That's a great little bit of a little bit of a
I hope I don't have to
The people that own anymore
If I say what I think I think I'm going to commit a crime that's all I really want is to imply heavily
Leave it everyone else should committed
Crime
It's about implying come on
You got to get
Capable with a sniper rifle
And part of the reason is because
Everybody
The cops everybody's out of control
What is state is Alton f****** society look like if everybody's good with a sniper
How do you go how do you go to f****** stores somebody's got him beat on you yeah
I know be really dangerous to use instacart
You sure it's not going to show up
Yeah
Elaborate body armor suits might become more popular
Anime instantaneously
I love it
Bruce Lee underground tunnel
I do like a good underground tunnel we might become the morlocks
It's Alex I mean
You got to do something
That's a good rewriting of
The Time Machine
There's a reason for getting into sniping
And it's because like I said
The state
The government as evidence
Let's buy this third-hand story that has K wants to tell
New York
But the distance
Situation
Is this the best
Example you have I mean
Listen I think it's b*******
Criminalizing just hanging around is a good way to destroy the poor
What you do I don't disagree with the long rifle probably not
Probably not I also don't know if this story happened
As it being told the lawyer in charge may have been
Related to something else
Be completely made up by this person that Aaron zelman was talking to
There's a hundred like Wyatt why are you even bringing this up why does this rank
There we go
Nazi again
I think it's wrong
And I'm sure if regardless of whether or not this story is
Exactly true let's go with that mean if you were not a racist you might just go with the stop-and-frisk policy
Even bothering with a third-hand story from some a****** who doesn't know any details who may have been loitering and you have to
Admit I just bought I don't know what happened
Datavac hang up stop Aaron's almond expect something like that to be
Like is it really
I am not convinced
That
The government is out of control based on this story
Now imagine that
That's right so you are hanging out on a hydrant
And a cop comes up to your knees like a
Can't loiter here and you're like no I can absolutely order here and he gives you a ticket
Right
You're long-rifles not going to do much in that situation you don't have the speed
To close down
What's the point of a long rifle if this is your example of how we have to
Fight back against
True
1 timeout stop nose for this one time I was skateboarding.
And I jumped up onto a hydrant and I spun around like a
If this a weed
Cop punched
I fell over
The police are out of control
Control this was in a video
How to tell Aaron Belmont about it he's going to tell Alex
Bellboy
So yeah Alex is this thought about the drug war
Audio
The more I learn about Alex's positions
About things that I
In fiery thought I agreed with him about
The more convinced I am that I'm not I don't really actually agree with him
All that much like legalization of drugs
I think is one of the
And you had
Look for low-level drug
Live now
I don't feel like I agree with him
And I don't feel like this is the way I understood his position
Yeah
I would say the reason that I felt
To place I've come to with never agreeing with Alex about any
About anything ever
Is because no matter what it is his position is
What I know now is that all of his positions
Have conditions
That can change on
On his whim and only his wings
It's true that whatever it is he thinks his position is or is presenting his position at
Given the opportunity to do something about it
He would change the conditions to whatever it is he wanted them to
Yeah yeah I think I don't think you're right on that count
Oh I think that
Decriminalization is something that's really important
Because
Many drug
Issue should be dealt with as medical issue
This is something that's not necessarily
Putative
Approach is
I don't know if it has
The best
Cheats for for helping p
Right
I suppose what it has the best chance of doing is
Creating more slave
ABS California to use
To fight their fires
I don't know it's a primary motivation for wanting
Drug legalization
Listen to happen
Is because the globalist make money on drugs
That to me is empty
That's what happens when you reduce everything down to Capital isn't it
I guess the wrong people I mean
Choose as a consumer
Do not let all of these millions of people get
F***** over forever but that's only because the wrong people make money off of it if I was making money off of
The drug war
Yeah of course we're having the driveway
So on this collar
Because in
And he wants
To know why
Aaron zelman
Is telling people that they need to
Sniper rifles
This made me really
Recommend
Do you do know about the weapon
Do you want to be
Far away from the enemies you can
Can you tell me why
Call Tom
Sheree we're not going to say go kill people sir
You know that's what we me
You you know that the answer is you can't get close to high-profile people
That we would want you to talk
Be quote-unquote 12
That's f***** up I mean what he might as well have said is
You think Kennedy's getting his head blown off with a short rifle in oh
Alex later then goes on to be like in obviously
Chinese troops Landing or landed Vision sniper rifle would not be helpful
Against a land invasion
I mean
Alright
China storm agar beaches what are we going to do alright we're going to line the border with 10 million
People with sniper rifles
Fire whenever you feel like it
Strategies metalman the Revolutionary War
So I feel like
In the same way become a little bit disillusioned with Alex's
Dunno is is
What would seem to be an agreement
In terms of
Drug
Policy I feel like I've also become disabused of the notion that he and I actually agreed about bush
Either
I think that he was using George Bush as a bit of a political tool
Down exposing a corrupt
Liberals
Convert
Look at you
Okay YouTube
Sia buddy
So it's only the Liberals need the program
And you were able to achieve this
Bye
Hearing sane by criticizing bush
So what you're doing is essentially trying to gain credibility for your
Extreme right-wing positions
By throwing the middle right under the bus
That's what you're doing
You're trying to appeal
It seemed reasonable
I mean that's what he's doing now with the the big box
Churches kind of
You know
ACH
Throwing the
Mainstream Christianity litterbug
Throw them under the hood
That kind of b*******
Christianity and all this nonsense we're waking up all these liberal Christians
Killing everybody we don't like
That's great
Yeah it's
It just seems like an intentional strategy
Yeah it is absolutely an intentional
I think I think part of that might be because I
Maybe he doesn't have much hope of actually converting all that many bush
Or like.
Conservative-leaning people maybe
Maybe maybe he's aware of that
They like that that's not that's not a fruitful Pawn for him
Deficient
Yeah I mean that
I guess
I guess it in that was born out because they came to him
You know he didn't he never convinced
Neocon still love him all the sudden they just started going f******
I'm crazy and then
He was there
Yeah he was ready and waiting for those
Dumb dumb dumb people to show up
Dora tea party event Trump eroded everything to the point where
Is normal
Is like a f******
Bilbo
Hobbit situation with Bjorn
Dwarf showing up one at a goddamn time
Can't Stop
Sorry that's a weird Hobbit reference for no reason
They got there
So Alex could take another call from a guy
And this service fellow would like Alex to speak at the University of Austin
Do UT Texas
Is Austin better be an interesting day
Yeah I'm going to tell you that the booking doesn't seem likely for me it doesn't seem like he's going to get that book
But there are some conditions upon which you would accept
Stopwatch
On table
Donald Trump
Krowd
I'll come do it
Well I can do a bullhorn
Invicta Viper smoking at UT twice before
Visited my dad's office I said hi to somebody
I've spoken of UT
I would say go f*** yourself with it if you can get me a big enough crowd also
You went to Kansas City to feel like a opening of a tire store local radio
Fly across the country to open a grocery
Restore
How do you open a grocery store
Like mask
UT got him two people
If you take out of a
Sandwich
So there's more calls
Most of the rest of the show is called
Actually not a whole lot of
Meat left on the phone
But
I don't know if I like that lesser more than that
Cuz it seems like he doesn't take too many calls
Yet
It's not as
Facts about taking calls now
A b a b
Elephant doesn't happen
I meant also
He has like just the same
People calling
Yeah in the present like this guy Carlos calls in all the time
Pretty much every time though
Phone lines are open that doodle get in there
Yeah it makes me wonder if like
There are just a few people who call
I don't know I really have no idea
I think
Vets
In terms of my listening
Enjoyment
I prefer it like this in 2000
Sees it feels like a radio show
I was thinking that about this from like a purely enjoyable standpoint I prefer being in the past and these colors are are
No I'm suck and are boring
But
It's still like at least
There is victus input of the listeners and Alex has to
Yes and with them a ramshackle charm to it
And I don't know if I would like that now though because I don't know if I would be able to handle what the
Callers would say now
Yeah you know like back then
The closest we got was that guy being like hey what do you think I should use this wrong long rifle for
That was
Right now if somebody called in I feel like they be like
No no I didn't ask you what should I use it for I said
Who who do you want me to kill with his rifle
I don't want to live there yeah I think I think you're right I think
If I were Alex I would be aware that
It might not be a good idea to
To trust a lot of the audience with a
Can open phone
That could be that could be rough
But then again I probably wouldn't trust most of the people he has on his guests to speak
What's this color
Hellboy
I mean obviously this is a sovereign
Sure
There were a lot more of them in Alex's audience
At this point
I would say
You know I mean I'm not like Alex I don't
Does makeup stupid
Explode say 99.9999 percent of his callers or suffer
Okay that sounds about right
It's about four out of 20,000
TimberTech
This person believes
This lady she believes
Yes
Is that
According to God and the Constitution
She does not need a driver's
Because all right
Her husband owns the car
And he gave her permission to use a
Which makes sense
Alex how are you today
I'm pretty good people how are you
Being followed
Monday I took a trip to town
Aaron's hours
Pulled over by
State trooper he was doing his dad
I don't know what
He never gave me an explanation
He was just pulling people over
They were standing in the middle of the highway
And after
Going to say their driver's license
So he had to a gentleman on one on the other Saturday
Black and his wife
Anthony told me
Waited
Give him
And I said no sir I do not have one
First mistake
It came back
Umi
My son and I
He said you want to tell me why you don't have a glass
Everything I said yesterday I believe in the car
United States
Believe in the Bible
My husband is this track
Give me permission to drive it
So therefore unless he tells me to get a driver's license
You show me where the
Selena
The state says that I have to have a driver's license
Or a license
At all
How to operate
Thing that my husband owns
And gives me permission to you
Then I'll go get one
Cetme
And the funny thing about this story
Teas that it ends up with the cop letting her go with a warning
Goddamnit she's actually I think she's totally right but in the wrong way like she says that
She probably wouldn't have been
Been treated this way if she didn't have her kid with her in the car
He's saying that you would have gotten roughed up
And like Tina beating up for being a Patriots fan mad about this kind of thing
But I think she probably was treated differently because she had a young child in the car and the guy probably
Just get a really
F****** their day I'm just going to let this go
This is going to be
Too much insanity
To try and beat through
What's that what's what's going on here what
Know if she calls in
To Alex's show to tell this nonsensical story about how is your husband owns the truck and he gives you permission
Then the constituted could drive
Ed Dudley the cop was nice and let her go and then they demonized him but I wanted to beat her up
Crazy
To think about
I imagine being a
Like whenever you ask people
Tell me why your
Do this
You don't want to hear him say like no I'm not going to tell you
Like that's going to be a lot of work
But if you hear him safe
Yes I would love to tell you why you're like
This is some Sovereign Center
It's about to happen the only people who have your like
Do you want to tell me why you don't have a
Sansar like yes I do and the Constitution like no go just go
Go go get into an accident
A pull-down on like the
The Duru for that car it's a screen
Projector setup I have a present
Temptation ready to go
Excuse me ma'am you need to understand this question was more rhetorical
And I have no
Justin the answer the problem is you don't have a life
Pushes in at 8
This presentation is a soundtrack
Put a lot of work into this officer you will listen to it
Excuse me officer
Would you be happy to know that I have been waiting just for this exact situation with a lot of
Props
7 hour and I am going to open the door just to do a little soft-shoe
There's a cop number in the middle of the presentation
Real Tavern intermission
So please don't shoot
You can't have a 3-hour show without an intermission that's just rude
I find it really fascinating
How many times there are people who call in
With horror stories
To Alex's show about things
Things that are just like they're just being annoying
Another story is
Nothing happened
I was bothering somebody and then I didn't receive any consequences for it Alex can you believe this world
I was being super annoying to a cop who just decided to let me go with a warning man
I am us
Call Alex about the
Because of that
I feel like so much of Alex
Scholars
With these types
YouTube stories like the unspoken parentheses is
And I'm white
You know like this type of treatment happens to non-white
I can't believe it happened to me
I think a lot of the time they're probably a little bit of that energy but in this case I think it's more just
Rosario sabado
Different world
Alex wants to know whether or not there was
Chicanery going on with the 2000 election
Guess there was a document
Romance
Fraudulent
Fragile activity what with the with the
What's going on
I only do
Buck off
Very rarely
Oklahoma City
Took over
Was the president
Okay
What's the present
Democrat
Voting machines
Car
He has an example of Republicans treating to just to be like
Aboveboard and make sure that
I cut it off
Ver Broncos like the rest of the clip Rambles on a bit but it does give an example of like
Okay are the Republicans
Yes of course
I didn't know that voter news service
Is
Behind everything
The military-industrial complex change their name to voter new service
I don't know that was a
That was a real grocery list of being wrong about stuff how
How is it possible that I've listened to thousands of hours of Alex's show
I've never heard him weaving Yarns about voter new service they change their name
They had so many names you don't even know what their name is now I don't even know if it was that they don't exist okay well there's that
They didn't exist
At the time of Alex's recording
Husqvarna
This is Addison exit polling group that was formed to various news entities didn't have to do duplicate work exit polling
Doing the same question
All have one uniform
Source
The organization did such a bad job with a 2000 election however that they were disbanded in January 2003
Well before the episode Alex is doing right now that we're going over
Okay I have no idea how voter new service could have took it over after
Kennedy was killed seeing as they were formed in 1990
Also I think that if Alex knows the people were stopping ballots
Did the voting machines that they had stored in their cars then the answer to the question of whether or not he knows of any fraud going on and that election is
Yes
The answer is not a long-winded non-answer about I only know things that I know
Do a yes or no question they are looking
For an answer that is
Is yes
Or no
And when the answer is yes
Because there were people
7 ballots are devoting
Machines that they hadn't
The cars you just say yes yeah
You were stuffing
Balance
Into voting machines
In their car
Yeah they're sitting the cargo my God has so many pellets
I'm supposed to believe that fraud
Get my call right now I am freaking out I'm still so many ballads
These people are so bad at feeling election all the sudden they're in their cars
And their fuc
Wait wait
What if this is fast 10
This is what we do they're stealing election ultimate fever
What's a ildas feel all that f****** money just to train to steal an election
And they're going
Roman and Taz realize we belong out there
They take their long rifles assassinate Elon Musk
Steelers Vulcan rocket
Going to space in order to steal the next election
Alright we can
Only steal this election if we have ballet
Machines in cars
Call Dominic Toretto
Surprise outcome of the 2024 election
Family is the president
Wow
Aaliyah Toretto Toretto ticket
Absolutely definitely related to Dominic Toretto jud.ct yes whatever
Yeah I think the voter do services not the nefarious group
Alex
Presenting I don't know what
He's trying to insinuate
Is he insinuating that they
Killed Kennedy or that they just filled the power vacuum after Kennedy
No idea
I'd love to learn more will come up in other 2003 episodes cuz
Again over the next 20 years
Boy
Confusing
So
You know the people revolutionaries
The catchphrases
They've used
Chirp
Each one teach one
Read something that said
Gets used to know
In order to grow a movement needs a friend
Then you tell somebody
The Alex is talking to somebody
Showed his
What about Alex's documentaries
At their Church
Function
Gray metallic slime view longest winded way possible
To say Each one teach one
Bring 100 we going to do this
Alright
Yeah I don't know if he realized like this was getting a little long or if he couldn't do that do that Matthew
You seem to be doing okay up till that point
Yeah it didn't even seem like it was taking him that long to come to the the x 2 and there
I mean
I just think there's an
Talking easier way to express
Concept that's been around since the beginning of humans
Trying to let you know
Congregate yeah I would assume that we would have figured out a shorter way to say it by now
This Mexico
I just think it's really funny
Because I want to talk to this guy who played this video
Documentaries for his church
And Alex
Needs to know like
How did it go how'd it go today
Standing ovation
Yeah I mean
Gas
1 and over
Not even like good people like it he went straight to
How crazy did people find it at people gas
How many how many Church ladies fainted
How many people brought out to another fans
How did they like the new movie did anybody get down on their knees
Play some good to worship me
Is that
No no zero people not even one that's you and that's unusual I'm going to call voter new service
Exit poll data address
I need one last clip here and it's one of the other big headlines that Alex
Has been hitting
And that is that
There's been a little bit of a stock market downturn and the United States has lost
North America as a whole has lost some millionaires
Oh no I would like you
Think about
The way in which Alex
Describes
Relative wealth
Okay
Millionaire
Are you getting ready
What
The
That's pretty interesting but that's
What is conception
Also also it's not the crumbs
The Klumps
Yeah
Sorry
That's like whenever there is
Ask a politician they like how much does a
Is a gallon of milk cost at $23 isn't real to me anymore
It's really strange that Alex in 2000
3:00 would have this
Kind of
Up respect
Ociaa dentist dad his family comes from oil money I wouldn't be surprised if he's not
Unfamiliar with the Finer Things and very on
Familiar with I do believe that Alex
Is
It was a boy of memes that say
But I I still think so much of his primary brand is supposed to be like
I'm like you
Yeah you know that
Sing
Sings it
Having a couple million
Is being lower-middle-class is
Inaccurate
Do you know how many people have a couple of million
That would be the top 1%
But there are a lot of millionaires
That is true I mean yeah but
The even if I'd remember the numbers correctly like
It is
90% of the country does not have anywhere near a million.
So
Yeah
Yeah the middle class
What you would say
Suggested somewhere in the median in o
There that they're nowhere near a million. Middle middle class is going to be
Do you know something in the alike
$100,000 a year
Salary I know it's going to be in that conversation
Not a couple billion dollars
Batman
Well
A couple million dollars
Christ
What it what Daisy just did I just I have no idea
They just don't know if you're rich you just
You have no idea if you're listening to Alex
2003 and you hear that and you're like
I make
30 grand
The year
You've got to be like
What am I
I'm so poor
Lower middle classes somebody with millions of dollars
She's a
Jesus Christ
It's just it's
It's very strange
I think it speaks to his brain
He's weird
He doesn't know how people live
Nope nope rich people don't
Also about as much connect
Come to reality as
Before when you talk to somebody who have been to heaven
Michelle Cohen
You know we come to the end of this year and we've had a little bit of a ride
Well we have Alex on timeout
Will be back to check in on him in the present-day are on Monday but
I need it I need a little
That's
Stay in the past
Got to break
For my own
My own well-being
Alex and his friends have been trying
Time to enlist
Sniper Coors
For long time long time people just been thinking that it's a good idea to get sniper
The Rifleman
For what's coming
Also I think it would be fun
If we ever watch another one of Alex's films
We just gas but everything
How many gases are there
We're going to count
We're going to f****** keep count there's going to be a projector screen
Try
I don't have a car but you do
I like
To get your permission to drive it
Without a license
I meant try and get myself pulled over
And I know she hears the problem there
One I don't believe in the Bible so that justification is out s***
I'm too I think the Constitution is b*******
I don't have a driver's license I can't have insurance
Another is that
Anyway we're not going to do this
Permission that says not equal license
We are fighting that go to bed
Please find a local charity or Bellefontaine area to help out people doing
Indeed
Until then
Emilio Emilio MDX car cantero rundus
The sex robot
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work