Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Indeed we are.
Jordan Jordan
Vibrate for today is actually something I've been waiting
Quite awhile to be able
To be a bright
Spot
I have sent out
All of the butt
That is coming to the email address
But be set up for the button
I have finished
Sending out
Probably I think I probably made about 4,000 but
Yeah
Various countries around the world in
All the states of the Union
Yeah it's it's a it took longer than expected
The demand was higher than I anticipated
But
Plugging on through it
So we we reach
Obvious points
I know that there are some people who have scented emails late
Messages that went to the places that aren't of the
Dedicated email address and I'm going to try and regroup
And get those last stragglers
Taking care of eventually but I'm
I'm not rushing
I have
Completed what I set out to do
I'm really proud of you I'm really proud of you
Yeah that's the type of thing
You know
You could have been like
I've done 2000 I'm not doing another 2K
And early on you were taunting me about how I bit off more than I could chew and you were saying
Did you do that again
Oh no this isn't going to work
What are the things that really motivated mean
It is
Big idea that I can sit here and
Press buttons and put them in envelopes
And eventually they were the effort that I was putting in was going
Translate to
Somebody being happy when they went to their mailbox
Stan Blake
I know maybe not everybody
Maybe not everybody didn't brighten their day figure something out.
Respect means a lot you know
Like this park isn't going to last forever we're not going to be doing this forever and
When
So you know things and
I would much rather look back
On the time
That we spent
It was put in about stuff like that all this time
Making these buttons
To send to people sell gray instead of like negotiated
Everybody was interested
Created that demand
For these buttons and allowing me to be able to
Experience that
That process of giving that gift
Fan of you folks
Yams
No I haven't gotten one don't send me a message now way to wildlands
Buttons will open up again
But there'll be something
Is a little bit I've had a
Pretty bad depressive episode for the last little bit and all came to a head Friday
But my bright spot is
My partner
Is so supportive
And so
Kind and helpful and has really helped me get through it
A lot
You know
Better than I otherwise
I've if you've
Been incredibly helpful as well so
I am a that's my b b
Perkspot with a bright hat you know it's it's like
All too often and bright
Mustache
I know people appreciate being open and honest about mental illness so it's like it's one of those things where
You know you are you do your best and then
Part of
That is
You do give people around you an opportunity
To be supportive or
Choose not to be
You know
And when somebody does choose to Abby's
Supportive it's such a good thing and it's
A good thing to give them the opportunity to do that instead of just suffer
Spring by yourself
Yeah you know
Generally most
People aren't going
To respond to
Vulnerability by hurting you
Yeah I think they will you think they will
I think
You they're not going to kill you you'll survive whatever and then you can choose not to associate
Yeah that is
Around people who are
Is that helps a lot
It's an incredibly bright spot
It really is
It smells great
And onward and upward
Infiniti
And at least somewhere around a pivoting.
We have present day episode September 2nd
I was way off
This depressive episode not feeling good
I wanted to do this because we've been in the past
For a bit and also clip
Made the rounds
Oh yeah of Alex yeah there was a clip of him taking Ivermectin on air
F****** morons do we live in the same world and he's very defensive
Well so we're going to learn a lot
I'm not going to say that
Okay
As is generally the case goes around of Alex I like to do is
Check and see if it's
Something worth talking about extremely it's not
Usually it's something that's like this doesn't
Anything to our conversation
I think this is one of those rare instances where it's like this is a clip the viral
I'd also
There's something people are
Slightly missing
In there that is definitely worth talking about
So we're going to do that today I am so much more
But before we do let's take
So first
Lauren spelled lorian
Who also loves Jordan
Cackle
CarGurus
Thank you
Next
Not mad at the crew in Colorado thank you so much with no follow-through are
It's like Sleepless in Seattle not mad at the group that would be a great if I was going to get another tattoo based on the
Michelle
That's a good weather to be on Alex's family crest
Next Tyrus I hope your recent shedding went well your heat Rockaway to you goddamn glorious Lizard King
Thank you so much and I apologize
Alex Jones is just a far-right Alan Partridge thank you so much and I was wrong
I'm a policy wonk so thank you so much
What up to Knox
Knox
Business
Heroin
Freakishly large
Cool man sounds like a British Countryside pronunciation of NOS
Like a fast guy
I feel I feel like everybody makes fun of him
For the Fort Knox thing but that dude
Can drive
Or there was that character knock
With an X
Start with a k in front of the Cadillac season of Heroes
Is played by
The guy who played Marlo on The Wire
Marlin school he was able to send
Beer around him
And the more fear that was around him the stronger he got
What
That's the worst Power I've ever heard it was such
Dangerous power that he was on the alike
The level
The lowest level
Of like security heightened
Security there
Deep underground under primatech paper
Alright
Alright seems like you could just fell apart
It seems like if you were like oh this guy feed done. You're like if I relax I'm pretty cool I think that's how
Planet with a personal situation
People don't know they're going to be afraid
It's a sneaker thing was down there with the guy who
Could do like Sonic booms
Whether it's a sonic boom guy wasn't afraid of him he could the sonic boom guy he's got no chance against
Tyler Broke everybody out
Anyway
Today
Also
Do Auntie a.m.
Mtti
Alright internet in the honor of Celine donated to protect the
Syma ringsels
Lucille's
I believe that second there's only two
400 of them left in the world
Christ everyone like in Finland
So
Donating to help keep them going as it is a very nice thing in Celina preciate that
She says meow
Thank you so much
Jordan we got this episode to go over but first years not a contacts drop
Today Show
Oops
That's it all right
Okay I just would like him to say that I just wanted to introduce into our drop catalog as I can clean drop
Oops
So we start here with this this for
Flip and Dad
Trump news
Stuff going on
Stop all right
Coming out a few days ago and saying it
Pfizer really rhymes
The FDA and the governments of the world in people on a look at Pfizer in the booster shot
So he's starting to
Towards taking on the fraud he knows he's been set up
He needs to do it
That will take Trump from
Maine
A figure pushed off to the side still getting some the Republicans elected
Power to bend the populist tea with meth
People will forgive him in a moment
Well that's
Am I lying about the vaccines
So when I first heard Alex talking about this I was listening this episode I assume that this clippy was talking about a trump was this one
From May to August
Alex's doctor
Incessantly
And it was Trump calling into the Fox Business show mornings with Maria hosted by Maria Bartiromo
He's just is bang that gone so many time
Since Trump
And Maria talk about vaccines
Interrupts speculates
The booster shot is a scam on the part of drug companies
To make more money
Great good work
He said that because he's an idiot and he doesn't care if his followers.
Correct notably absent from that clip is Trump saying that fisa runs the FDA or the governments of the world
World which is what Alex
We can always talking about here so
That's what was my first indication that maybe there's a different clip
And it does turn out to be a different color
But I wanted to play a little bit of the Bartiromo clip that Alex never plays okay
And then there's there's something
I do still think is worth talking
Nobody is talk to the FDA like I did they don't like me
We have a Backpage
Better saving Millions
YouTube lives throughout the world I think we have a Spanish
Blue situation like
19 seven
I believe that
Maybe a hundred million people
50 million 100 million people like that
So very proud of the fact I've taken the vaccine
I'm very very proud of it
Super proud of the vaccine
Cuz you said it twice he did say super police don't really match up with Alex's stupid
We conspiracies at all
According to Trump Anna part of a Fox news interview that Alex will sensor from his audience
The vaccine is great
And without it covid would have killed 100 million people
This isn't the rhetoric of someone who's been set up
These are the words of someone who's two steps
Behind his own
Gripped
In many respects I think what Alex is saying there is
Accurately
Assessing the problem but
I told you that Alex can speak frankly about what the problem is
Trump's base
Half the s*** now and galvanizing around for years advisors make money off booster shot
That's not going to get anyone excited at this point
That could possibly work in the mainstream Republican
Skin types but the move of the Trump was leaving and dragging whatever mainstream Republican types they're actually word along with it
Steve moved on to the next stage were there once
Step away from violence
The escalation is gone one step away from
They are there
True
Some of them
Yes in terms of people disrupt
Open City Council meetings and school boards in the way this Behavior has been cheered on and incentivize with attention on social media
That's where the Grist is now than the extreme fringes of it or the roving gangs you see in the Pacific
Yeah yeah yelling at school boards don't want to talk about Pfizer's profits they wanted Yellow by Bayou
Weapons in the spirit of humanity that won't accept tyrannical martial law or some s***
In order for Trumpeter gainswave the the populist movement that he was the head of and he
Fire to overthrow the
Government
He needs to meet them where they are
They're not going to meet him where he is
He'll be exactly what Alex the same
I figure pushed off to the side
Still getting some Republicans elected
The movement that follow Trump didn't
Follow him because they actually thought he organically held
Any worthwhile beliefs or had a good
Understanding of policy
They just recognized that he was willing to go where they already were and then they could push
Further
Trump games fans by pretending to be the champion of whatever dum-dum right wing
Bingo they were mad about that day and it really works from W stuff
College campus Adventures
Big Tech censorship
He was King shitpost
And now Trump has been out of office and not useful to the hard-right folk
He was a disappointment to them after January 6th and he literally did nothing to get himself
Or any of them back on Twitter
As if that wasn't enough he's now completely misread the room and he's trying to encourage people to get vaccines
Which is like if you'd gone up in front of his followers in early 2016 and said
You know when you get right down to it feminists have some pretty valid point exact
He doesn't get the Gang
I'm doing if he's actually thinking about running in 2024 like some of suggest
If he doesn't come out until the extremist line
He's not going to have an actual Bass
Just not
Did this visit doesn't work with
Him like being like
Oh you need to come to me
He has nothing to offer unless he comes to them
You know this is starting to sound exactly like when Trump tried to get into football
Call and sued the NFL for a full dollar
And then lost everything
So
That sounds right I just you know I think
That
Clip that Alex is playing
Not the right clip
This this point is really say when
That the Trump is not going to
Get his shift back
If he doesn't do what they
Doesn't cave to Grievous demands he will not be their leader find somebody who's
As charismatic as him
Probably less embarrassing right
We'll go along with it
You got it
So
When you when you make a mob
You don't wind up leaving
Become apart of
Or were you have to dance
Really fast
Yeah
Keep up with
The desires of the mob the will of the mob
It's a mess and you have to give them everything they want or they will toss you under there
And create reasons why they were right to do that
So anyway Alex has a busy bee
He wants to make sure that you know that he does a lot of work
Let me explain something to you
I stayed up till 2 in the morning last night with this
Information
It's right here
My wife went to bed about 9
Children went to bed about
Better last night
Till 2 a.m.
Before the show and I
Rue
All of this
Shower I'm going to have to drink breaks and then go back through because
It's so bombshell
Who cares right
Wow
Who cares how often are up till 2 in the morning I don't give a s***
You know I know I don't know this I don't know this for sure but I'm pretty I'm pretty confident
Did Alex Isley
What type of dad who is like wandered into his kids room at 2 a.m. and then like
You got to watch this movie
You got to watch this movie with me while he's absolutely s***-faced that's totally true stories Wonder to do kids room at 2 in the morning and then
Music Ivermectin
The bomb coming
Larry got there by paying on your bed this time
The morning
Like watching the YouTube videos like I've been up till 2 working
Very impressed I did
So impress
Alex talks about vaccine
Until there's monitoring goes on
About them
And this is really
Just the globalist
Trying to know if they've
The target sure this is such
Bulshit
Number hospitalizations are heart attacks or blood clots
Crosshairs
Rifle
Uses the Optics to see if he shot you
Gun camera
16 recording image
John Hopkins they know about the heart attack
The targeting computer
And so they're watching just like
B-17 pilot
Bomb site on their aircraft
And then there
Skip three more eggs
What did hit that Target sell
No go ahead and
We had that talk
We got that Target
Targeting
The movie Predator
It is really stupid and it comes entirely from Alex's imagination
What else is talking with reports
Score of the vaccine adverse event reporting see
We talked about bears a little bit in the past and how it's really difficult to take raw data from the system and reach any solid
Conclusions based solely on that
But
I don't think we've done a good enough job of
Discussing exactly why that is
Apparently a
Passive data collector
Consistent which is to say that the FDA and CDC who operated
In conjunction with each other they don't make any efforts to collect data
It's captured in that says
It's wholly up the individuals and Healthcare professionals to report
Adverse Events
In this way
The thing is important to understand is that the FDA and CDC.
Only use various data to monitor vaccine
Pictures of thing you hear the most
About because it
Is the easiest thing for idiots like Alex and his friends
The poll numbers from
10% out-of-context on Facebook in hopes of making
Your parents in space
B vaccine
The CDC has an active arm of it
It's program to monitor the safety of vaccines
What are the largest parts of which is the vaccine safety data
This is a collaboration between the CDC and 9
Huge Healthcare organizations
Where concerns raised by various data could be
Explored in a construct it's more meaningful
For making scientific
Connections between thyroid
The FDA has their own programs in place such as the post-licensure
Rapid immunization safety monitoring
Prism for sure
This is a modern program that has been used
Investigate possible vaccine
Interactions and side effects
Once it's already been released
The market
So you're saying that the
There's is almost more of like a
Wendy's
Anecdotal evidence if they get enough anecdotal evidence there like maybe there's something here and so then they'll be as other text
Unique Stuart Florida
Information comes out of these other more active programs it's usually press releases where they've done in-depth reviews of
Possible connections between vaccine and a condition
Impound Nolan
You'll essentially never hear someone like Alex bring these programs up however because their studies are much harder to misrepresent
Then random out of
Contact Thursday.
Is lying here from a 2015 article in the Journal of Acts
How they put it
There's is primarily a safety signal detection and hypothesis generating
Ring system
There is data interpreted allowed or out of context can lead to erroneous conclusions
About cause and effect
Or the risk of Adverse Events
What's after vaccination
That's the way to look at it right this is a hypothesis generating and safety signals
Protection right sister
No governmental organizational system is
But there are layers upon layers in place of people trying
Safe baby don't even know about
There are countless people who have made it their life's work to pour over data on things like prism or the vaccine
About to make sure their bomb hit the right target
But to be able to respond.
Quickly as possible with the public health measures life done
Result
And I just
Binded really stupid
He's not
Really looking at
Picture as it exists
Just as it exists in his imagination
Service
I would prefer if instead of staying up till 2 a.m. pretending to research thing he stayed up till 2 a.m. writing
Better similes
You saw a man like that would be nice
He was a good extemporaneous speaker so he would write all of that stuff we will fight
He's been writing that for years
I wish I were to Fayetteville 2 in the morning working on his Churchill impression
I think you should just take a right in
In class
Did you come up with
How to write
Brother
Probably not
Alex's got some news about Israel
Israel
Has the most deaths in the most illnesses of the most vaccine in the world of any large.
12 year old shot
25 year old is totally healthy
People are just
Excruciating pain
Their hearts just swell up and bust open
Kaboom
Got none of this is
Spaced on anyting
Get 44% or something hundred most populous country in a popular
This country in the world according to the New York Times
Which is just reporting from Johns Hopkins
Data share
Israel sitting at an overall vaccination rate of 61
Okay exclamation rate is higher than that but
It's not the number one in the world
Here's a possibly incomplete list of countries that have higher population than Israel and higher vaccination rates
The Netherlands
United Kingdom in Belgium Portugal
Currently the United States has the highest number of average daily cases and it's not even close
We're also way ahead on average daily.
If you only look at the statistics
Pic of average number of daily cases
Is per 100,000 persons top of that list
But it's not as much of a blowout as our various number one
Everyone's going through a little bit of a bad stretch right now with a Delta variant and their experience has shown very clearly how the vaccines are various
Effective but also not a perf
Perfect solution
In Late July they began rolling out boost
Jobs for people over 60
Bring I see a lot of folks recommending is Mass
Sam returning to
A bit more
Caution
You know and also the the thing I just I just saw that somebody had done
Indian
Didn't study of excess deaths and so
Countries with let's say
Mad dictators like the ones that Alex likes have been under-reporting there
Covid numbers for a long
Time there are some issues will take a while to sort out all those front
Yeah
Trying to make about Israel's infection rate is just in playing games
But the bigger point is at the specific claims he's making are just
Backup
So there's a bombshell
That Alex has
Alright
What's the site on
Is it using a B7
19 bombshell or is he using the Sidewinder bombshell the movie Predator
When put the headliner show
CDC documents that the CDC put out themselves
Idiots
Plainview where they admit
Heart attack
And all the rest of this
The show headline today is
Absolute Global bombshell
That's a bad show head
Pop
FDA
Scientist
Have
Now come out and admitted
Covid-19 vaccine
After the headline breaking
Mega bombshell
I thought it was the CDC
He said
CDC CDC release the headline is a bombshell about
DEA
Scientist admitting that the shot is killing people
I'm confused
Well
This is a bombshell
The cdc's bombshell
Is
Different from the fda's bombshell
Which one are we concerned about
I'm not sure
But Alex don't start talking about these FDA scientists
And
Some dramatic
Remember this is the other gigantic
2 days ago
The number one and number two scientist
His death
1035 years Ones been there 12 years
People they said hey
You can have the CDC in the white house running nose
You shouldn't give it to Under 12
DM
It's not going to work
We don't care
PA
Oxycontin
Previously an end.
For children
If I was just worse
Overrode them instead
We're going to say it's an authorized shot
If you just heard Alex's version of the story that sounds like really high drama
A couple of higher-ups in the backseat Department try to tell the truth to power and then the power-mad woman in charge wanted to give
Wouldn't hear it
Pretend everything's fine wow
That sounds
Like a
Plot of a movie there's a little Game of Thrones going on there
The woman Alex is referring to is Janet woodcock
Lock the acting head of the FDA
Who recently ruled out is Biden's nominee to be the head of the agency so she won't be in that role very long
For what it's worth the issue here is that there are very serious concerns about woodcox time as the head of the center for drug
Drug evaluation and research
The wing of the FDA in charge of approving new drugs
Many of Webbie prisms that you did not do enough to
The public from the opiate
That were approved
During her tenure
This is awful and she should be held accountable for the
The decisions that were made under her leadership and even so
It's a pretty Far Cry from what Alex
Claiming she did
According to Alex you wanted to give Oxycontin and Fentanyl to
Two children
Jameden
For one thing most brands of Oxycodone are not approved for use
Some people under 12
Most versatile prescriptions are for
Very narrow situation
Particularly breakthrough pain in cancer patients who are quote already receiving and we're tolerant to opioids
Therapy for their underlying cancer pain and it is not indicated for use in purse
Underrated
There's some very serious concerns about the fda's handling of the opiate crisis but when you cover that story by saying that his evil woman wanted
Fentanyl in Oxycontin
Children
You're making an ass of yourself and you guarantee that your audience will only have access to a bulshit version of the story
It's useless
In terms of helping
Where's all the actual underlying issues with the story present Frank maker
You're making their their ability to deal with reality input
You got it anyway
The main story Alex's.
I'm about was this head of the FDA vaccine stuff in his deputy
Right that's what the main story was
Call up inside character wanted to do SAR kids with
God dammit
Anyway this is about dr. Marion Gruber the director of the office of vaccine research and review
Dr. Philip Crouse the deputy of said office
All right well unfortunately if your last name is Gruber you are from die-hard VA
Well and also
The doctor group is a woman
Alex kept referring
Cuz it's Hans gruber's daughter
Who's come back to Heather FL Alex
Repeatedly
Referred to dr. Gruber Elsa as a man
Anyway
Secondly doctor Gruber announced that she was retiring after being with the FDA for 32 years
Across adopted to leave as well
The exact reason for their departure hasn't been announced but one unnamed Source cited in Politico article claimed they quote
Leftover differences with fda's top vaccine official
Peter marks
You see doctor Mark's is the director of the center for biologics
Evaluation research
Which is the umbrella underneath which the office of vaccine research and review exist
Alice is conveniently decided
The cut marks out of
The story because he complicates
It's things because
I was just naturally know anything about what's going on you just Kim just political article anyway
Exactly we better
Here's how you can tell what Alex is doing his ass Kim job
The headline of the article in Politico is quote
Biden's top-down booster plan
Sparks anger at FDA
And then the sub-headline is quote
Acting FDA commissioner Janet Woodcock sent a memo Tuesday evening to vexing regulators
Reiterating her support as frustration over the process spread
Within their right
If you are all had of all you had to go on was that blurb of information
Your mind might turn into a situation where these two bold scientists said the booster vaccines wooden
The work and then they were shot down by this evil doctor woodcock
Who wants kids
To get hooked on Fentanyl
You can see the first stages of the building blocks for Alex's narrative in that headline and sub-headline
But if you actually read the article you see that there's more texture to this story than his coverage is allowing
There is a very real possibility that the two doctors departures does have something to do with a disagreement
Silver the vaccine booster program
But their concerns are nothing like what Alex is pretending they are
They're very valid criticisms that we've discussed here about how booster
They're not necessarily the best allocation of resources when dealing with a community-level issue as we are right now
Alright very well maybe that it's a great strategy on an individual level but that's
It's not always
The main variable that you're concerned with
Right we're dealing with spread
I need to look at this as a community issue
Yeah that would only reinforce the two different
Maxine vaccinated unvaccinated America's yeah
Yeah and take
Internationally as well as countries that are in need
Politico article they bring up some other valid concerns which have to do with the White House aiming to take the lead
And making declarations about time frames that are not been fully endorsed by the FDA
I can definitely see that being an issue for Regulators within the FDA and I'd love jobs
For last
I don't I don't know if
Weekend
Definitively say exactly what
The situation vacations
There's there's some
Uniformity
Yeah yeah
You know that's that's interesting this is one of the few times where if I were
One of those.
Is that would be like
Who the
F***** you
President Biden
To tell us when scienceworks
You know what I'm saying like you're just a f****** president shut up
I can also see being in the position you're in and refuses
Listen to leave
During the
Beginning of the pandemic
Even if things are being mishandled and Trump is coming out and being like
Let's take this a weirdo hydroxychloroquine
You know it cuz
Leonardo dates
All hands on deck
We're not out of the woods right now but it is a little bit different
Damn if you have a different
In the steps
That are being taken moving forward
It might now be a time where you could make it
Decision where you like I have to resign
I don't I don't know I think it was probably a really complicated
Situation that these doctors
Are are engaging with death and I look forward to learning more about it
These are the best speculation
That we can make
Based on one anonymous source
That was listed
In the Politico article that Alex didn't read
The important thing to focus on here that I think is the way that the reporting Alex
Is doing
It's essentially a dramatization of what he thinks happened based on skimming a headline
That's the level of analysis
That goes on on Alex's show
I meant once that's done
He takes that
And make stuff up about
And the two top scientist
Have gone public saying
Resignation
We are mad about the authorization that's not a real authorization
About children
We said don't do this and they did in the fine print
Oh they're just mad about the booster
Schedule
Distraction
And everybody took the bait and just went with the booster issue
Is not as big as
We've been bypassed
They shouldn't have done the emergency authorization saying that's an authorization
It's attacking
So I mean he's just making up with these
Concerns and like
Almost creating a fictional resignation letter that everyone's ignoring their dad
It's not real
I remember I did check out dr. risers
Resignation email where he said he was mad about you Paul
I think
Alright whatever man
It's just not fair you just can't just eat can't create like yeah
Primary sources life
Everyone's ignoring you
It's not real
So I wanted to
Play this clip
What are the reasons they wanted to play this was because I almost didn't
And I want
Is to live as an example of like this is something
Ignore
Okay this is something that just rolls off my back right
It's crazy and it is something that I was like
I don't have time
Trials now
And it hurts
Babies are having convulsions babies are dying
Weather freakazoid
Liberal parents
This is child sacrifices
Munchausen by proxy
This is
This is a demonic spirit
Doughboy pedigo's on his show all the time and it's just like
Tears
If you really believe that liberal parents are taking
Babies to get
Vaccinate as a satanic demonic sacrifice
Yeah it but that's very extreme stuff
And it is just
The kind of thing that I end up listening to
Like ho-hum another Navy officer
While a lot of people go into work all day and they never hear about babies being murdered by all the doctors in the
Never hear about
So Prime
For like the devil to actually make me a deal cuz I'm still bored by the ideas
Give me
I heard about the
Anytime
Hey devil I'm good
What do what deal do you have
What is it
Board board by the devil will give you rich
She's beyond your madman I don't have the imagination for riches well
No deal just
I ignore stuff like that it's fun
To just take a step back sometimes and think about like well that's
Implore
Yep that's
That's normal
Play a clip of this guy who's giving
Speech about to have a son
Died because of the
You're just wondering latest videos Man son dies
Enlarged heart
They wouldn't give it a buyer's report though
100 * 40
And they're just getting started
Legitimately no idea how this person wouldn't be able to make a report to bears
Like I was poking around prepping this episode and I could have easily filed a fake Bears report online in about 2 minutes
I'm going to say they probably have a
Contact us button.
Not exist
Hypotheses they can use other data sources or experiments
The test
I don't believe it
This guy somehow couldn't report to there's no idea how any whistleblower to possibly quantify
How many reports art
Being made to occur
Completely voluntary reporting system
They can be accessed from any
Computer
It's all seems like Malik Jones bulshit man
As far as this guy and his son go I'm not going to engage with the story any further at side is saying that I don't believe that he wouldn't be able to report it
Tavares
Anecdotal stories in cases of death
The can't even be proven to
Pain caused by the vaccine that's a compelling evidence of anything
And you know
I feel bad
I'd like the guy
Son died
Presumably in like
That's awful.
Awful
That's awful
Did it to his death
After a vaccination doesn't
Prove anything about the vaccination
He was in a car accident after the vaccinations they would have been like well the vaccine was
Messing with his brain and that's why he
He died you know that it wouldn't matter
Whatever happened
He got the vaccine and then shortly after
He died so it's
Exploitable and that's all that
Alex Dam
So you got this clip of this guy talking about his son dying cuz he got the vaccine
And then here's the next clip that Alex decides to cover
Let's go
Priest talking about the devil
Is overplaying his hand I totally agree the devil Dover playing as hell
The devil
Is over playing
Alex reported that correctly
Sing that used in some weird Christian circles
There's a
Preoccupation with convincing congregations that
This time the devil is just gone too far it made everything way too obvious
This time all the people couldn't see the magical things you're seeing
Are finally going to realize that you've been right all along
Princeton Sears a dumb dumb preacher on Jim Bakker Show back in 2018
I believe that
That the devil overplayed his
Panda New York
I believe what we're going to see happen
Is that this
Overplaying of the handle
The devil it actually is
Is going to
Sure
President
Trump the ending
Dependent vote in 2000
It's a way of reassuring people that your beliefs though people look at
Get you as if
You're crazy for thinking
The devil
Is manipulating your enemies
Yeah you're actually right
And this proves at this time
Yeah you can believe in
Any of what your religion stands for and also believe that the devil can
Overplay anyhow
Again your religion States
But this is how it happened
+ 2
To imagine that the devil is going to make a mistake
The devil's going to make a whoop
The devil
Yeah I think the overplaying the Hampton is just a way of like
Appealing to people's inaugurate
The clip that Alex's playing is something that one of his employees found posted on to
Tik-Tok
It was a little video posted on account called RJ Richmond to just
Clips of someone appears to be a castle
Priest giving sermon
This is a fella named Meeks was actually a Catholic priest in Maryland but around
A bit too much and
And doing so I discovered an aspect of
Solecism but I didn't know existed
Apparently there's an entire branch of Catholicism called the
Ordinariate of the chair of saint
Peter
Which exists to cater to people in the United States and Canada who want to be Catholic but also want to hold on to some aspect
Of the Anglican Church
But they're converting from
Is Masters at math Camp which I guess is okay I just didn't know that is
The Reka half-and-half version
School that means we believe in the Bible for sure anyway
The point is that Alex is reporting on a video that someone found on Tik-Tok of a dude preaching about the devil and this is not hard hitting
Uno
No
The devil has overplayed his hand and you can hear it in that said now if you
You wanted to save the devil is overplayed his hand
I would suggest that
Convincing all of these cats
Play priests to tell people that
Don't worry about it
The devils
By not going to beat him this time that would be the devil's work
Of tricking you into a false
Sense of safety
And then that's when he comes in the devil's got a tell
He licks his lips
How you know
Is that Alexis Lipton that's how you know you is to parrot
You're fine
You got it
Thanks Jesus
AC
What's the bible verse When you guys can pull it up
The devil goes around like a wild
Beast roaring
Seeing who he may devour
Because
Or is going to take on the wall
Take on the Beast
What a Satanist I left this will grovel or fall down
On their back
This show is really good
Yeah that's good stuff
He stayed up
Till 2 a.m. for that kind of information to drop on you
Right
Why do we spend so much time
Documenting his noise
I don't know I think it's noises are that maybe they
He talked about how he was one of the world's most respected voice
Man is one of the places where he has
The most tablets true that is true except for the dragon character that's just
That's good
Optimus Prime
He would have been a great guardian of the
Star-Lord
Tell Alex Beyond
And
I guess save it
Patriots
Can be the devil but left a Satanist
Can't we just love the devils
Anyway
The Goblins have a plan
Is it a different one
Fire truck
ILearn
Things
The FDA is virtually controlled by Pfizer
Pfizer
Has control not Johnson & Johnson not moderna
But Pfizer has control over the FDA
What's the difference
You have till 2 a.m.
A policy advisor
With government
People running Pfizer
Have a great relationship
Government
Pfizer what they did
Yeah Pfizer runs the whole thing worldwide
Yeoman
Pfizer runs the whole
Babalous programme
Kewanee
Plane
Supreme
That's something that has been a part of every plan that he said the globalist have had right
I feel like it's weird that Alex is surprised by that clip of trump saying that
Pfizer basically runs the FDA considering that's what he reported at the beginning of the show
Only imp
The second clip implied that they're good with government contract
Like there's some closeness internally do well with government
Which
Sure good lobbying
Claire's close relationships with
That doesn't mean they run the FBI or the government of the world
The f*** Alex's reporting who is
A little bit like I said at the beginning
He's behind the scam
Yeah he's behind the grill
He thinks that this insinuation game is going to lower the
Extremists to him
And instead
He is only signaling to them
In a way that is going to be a
And here's what I think will happen make them angry
Vince said he was
The entire time
To these
Extreme is 12
You know
Their belief is advisor strike
Kill everyone
Right where
Did Pfizer runs the FDA and is in bed with the government and stuff
And he's not doing something about it that he's facilitating either by
Active decisions or negligence
The killing off of people with right by their bed right
No it
It only
It's the only
Conclusion UK
Could draw from those types
Clips is like
You were the
You approved the vaccine you got that going
You're in on it well even even though even that you might be able to pretend that he like always been tricked or what
But
Now
You're still
Trump and they can get rid of them now they don't
Nope
You but you could still do a whole lot other than
Gu
Manifold about like hey you know I hear that visors real good with the government
You know you could be a little bit more assertive
You could take some actions as opposed to just
Talk s***
I'm always amazed at how
Quickly our press just
Dislike
Alright well you were the president now you're not anymore so we don't need to worry about all the stuff you did
Just like
Hey you know what
Yeah sure
It's due to you and your government that all of these people are dead
But anymore so we'll just have you on
Quick interview
You think it's a tough
Box to open
Once you start holding presidential countable boy everything goes great I'm not saying we shouldn't
Obviously
But it stopped
Fans
This makes clip Jordan
Yes
Feel like
This is a death toll
Call Schwab Bill Gates
You will never reverse the bakery set
In the poverty
2 kill
Majority
How's everybody
By then
Books
The clothes
Do
You
Under
How much
You
You work under
Ohio
Weapon
Synthetic
Ohio
And you look at the left how pale they are and how greenskins they are
How zombie-like they are
Spirit over the spirit of death
Is abortion
Animal cloning
You just hating themselves and hating you
What I hear stuff like this
Switches you know fairly routine on Alex's yet
It's really hard not to think of the lessons that were learned
After the Rwandan genocide
Radio demonization
Did play a role in turning people against their neighbors you betcha
I don't think that Alex's reaches nearly
What ya need to beat down
But this is the kind of behavior that
That is in the same
Ballpark
Obviously not equivalent but it's in the same ballpark you're taking a group
Of people and you're creating
Demon zombies out of them
Who exists only to be taken over by this evil force that wants to kill you and your fam
There's no there's no end of this road that is in
Bad no I mean
If if if
If anybody
Compares the left
Two Nazis
Or the like
How
Do you get
More noxious than a law that has you
Reporting gender Traders for about
No likes
Give give me any situation where that is allowed to run rampant
For two years and it doesn't wind up with women getting murder charges
And then being exit
Like that is straight up
Real life
100%
Nazi s***
No joke
No
F***** around
Just Nazis in Texas
Run the government
That whole situation is
Almost too bizarre even for me to feel comfortable covering it
Yeah
Like
Alex and didn't bring it up on this installed
Yaks
Booty does bring up his
More evils that Pfizer is bringing
Into the world
And so now I got the article Pet Shop please
Pfizer is now developing infowars.com
It must be taken alongside vaccines
And they're saying
Your Apple show
You'll have to
Check yourself
Proven you taking it
Better not have any
Drug avoidance
So thx-1138
Here
Oh man
I hate it when
28 x 11 3/8 is here
Thx-1138
Yu-Gi-Oh
Pfizer's working on
Some clinical trials on an antiviral called
Pf07 321 332
By which
Addition to a trial date data in July
They're waiting on results or not entirely sure how effective this drug is
Where is this drug work
Works in theory is that it blocks the enzyme that the coronavirus uses to multiply
At the same time with these trials are going on work is also doing trials on a drug called Moon
Good morning
Pure Revere
Which works
Spy quote introducing errors into the RNA of the virus that eventually prevented from replicating
This isn't surprising nor is it a bombshell that pharmaceutical companies will be working on different approaches
Dissolving different aspect
Gigantic global
No problem right
They're good and they help a lot but what if you add vaccines to help out a community level and then you develop good antiviral
Medications that can be used on an end
Individual basis
Look for people you know Google
Protect people who can't
Vaccinated
WFAN better
Also this really is already a thing since Ram desertview exists and isn't approved antiviral treatment
Don't know why this
It is sometimes
You know like
Just like with that clip
The valix being like they killed baby
Freezer whatever in your life
Sometimes it is amazing to hear that they're just
You
We live in an era where they can make a pill
With the irna of a virus
What the f***
Crazy it is
Much more valuable used time to discuss like the amazing breakthrough
There's a technology
Wouldn't that be great or like when you're talkin about this like
Misrepresentations of Vera's data like
Actually understanding
The structure of
Active and passive monitoring of Public Health stuff
Because when we get bring so much more people's lives
To like
Get a dopamine Rush
Yeah out of it been the same way you do like
I know you're disincentivize for learning about those.
Let me know but sometimes I get
Drenalin restroom like whole ship
Yeah we are weird
We are weird
A picture of a world where everyone has to accept all these shots
Can't leave their home
Complete bulshit
The trials for Pfizer's drugs are being given to people with confirmed diagnosis so the goal is to see if they can develop a drug test
Effective as a treatment
Conversely The Merck drugs
Testing is aimed at seeing if they can develop a preventative
Type of medication
This trial is going to involve people who live with someone who has a lab confirm
Asymptomatic
A covalent determine if a drug has an effect on whether or not people get it at all
Albright right for that Alex is describing benefits
Summer cocktail but all that was his evil nightmares are already built up around Pfizer
So I guess he's just sort of pretending this is all the same
Well
Alex
It's merkins
I mean that dopamine Rush that you get from that beer and that
Excitement is
Diminished by actually to do that
So anyway women
What about
Still doing
Still going
Accepting tyranny
I mean if you live in Texas yeah you sure are
This
Clip is dumb
Bill is expected to be released
By the end of the year and will be required to be twice per day
I noticed
For women worldwide friends
And shouldn't be the leader of the household
The women hopping around ordering husband around
Stepin fetchit
When they can go out and how much meat
If they can have a child or cuddle
I'm bleeding out 25
And so
That's how sick this is
I like to retract what I was saying with Alex doing good voices
Yeah that was Tara
You know I
Do like
The idea of being married to a man who thinks all women are weak and dumb
That's great that sounds great
And they're being tricked into
Pretending that they're equal with
Men speaking to media is making me play there's nothing better than a relationship
One person thinks you're useless
Terrible and if you get a little bit too you know
Confident in yourself that's only going to lead to the globalist
Exactly
Yeah you cannot have confidence in yourself if you're a woman otherwise you'll be taken advantage of us you're confident
Position of being subservient
Exactly as long as you got a man telling you what to do you will be fine
Women understand that could it be all of human history
Alright I find this a little bit
Damning cdc.gov
But he's brought up
Sure
Really talked about what it is
And maybe it's at the AIDS
Something
Either way absolute Global bombshell
Based on how he presented it so far I've been very
I'm an open the phone's up in 15 after
The next hour but it's really big store that I mention
In the end
Horseshoe sandwich the next hour
Nashville CDC document
Last year
Were they last
Parts swelling
Heart attacks
Frogs
Cancer
Death
Liquification of the uterus
What their scientists were telling him what happened
Now you know why the two-headed virologist quit
Today's ago
At this point Alex doesn't actually specify what the documentary is referring to is so I was left to try and find it on my own
I was able to find an FDA PowerPoint presentation from October
2020 that was about a quote
Plans for monitoring covid-19 vaccine safety and Ethel
This is just a breakdown of the various passive strategies like there's an active strategy
She's like prism that the f
Damc DC to monitor how the vaccines are working
It explains another initiative the FDA best
System
What's a biologic
Effectiveness and safety
I guess beauty is just imply that my backronym
You guys got to work on that
The best system works by compiling data from emergency rooms as well as insurance claims covering the policies of
American
In order to track how many Adverse Events are being seen and what sorts
The really effective
Active
Monitoring strategies that they can use
Self-report Hodge through things like there's
The presentation covers have their multiple approaches because no one system really can capture a lot of the stuff on its own
And each has strengths and weakness
Particularly when one of the large objectives
Is respecting patients rights and privacy
16 of this the 65 is a draft
Working list of
Possible adverse event
You might say
Specific enough yet so this
Probably isn't the document he's talking about
Therapist
Yeah that would be really sad
Before I hope we don't end up finding out that this is the document
There's no way that that
Could possibly happen
0% of 1
Instead
Baby at 2
The biggest news in the world
The Rogue
Yes
She
Made a lot of
Because he came out and said that he had Kobe
And that he took
Ivermectin
Along with
Literally everything else
So Alex
Needs
Do you know if
The first thing that he needs you to know
Is
But he knew about Rogan before you
12 Corsica
Text all the time
And also Rogen's not supposed to
Special
Mike down
All freaked out
Joe Rogan
Cuz they don't tell anybody yet
I'm making out
Easton Maryland to Florida
What's Rochelle
Thought I was hungover
And man that I
Happy sweat
Fever and I
I talked to Matt Reed Rd been on it for a day was already feeling a lot better
Out of some people right close to me they had it again it
What's sitting on their chest
I'm at
Even closer to my parents
I know someone that had covid
But I I
Deprived
Gorillas on my chest
And I went and got tested
Mikrotik
So it doesn't say it's the same virus
I just call it cub
So I had covid 2 and I took Ivermectin I was Giratina granted I took a test and it was negative
What
I was going to say I believe he did not have covid
So somehow
He took a test
And was okay this is just convoluted
No idea with the reality of this is
I have no idea
It is certainly his behavior would suggest somebody who's at high risk
Connect ecobee
Over the course of this
So if you were to get it I would not be surprised
If you were to get it I also think
He has access to pretty good Healthcare and wouldn't have all the things that
Joe Rogan would have access to as well
I'll be the monoclonal antibodies and whatever kind of
Urgency use treatments
People will have
Are trying
Hey if you're rich and sick you'll probably be okay
I think it's possible that he
Did ecobee
And I also think it's possible that he didn't
Based on him saying that he took a test and he was negative
So that's weird
But I also think that I totally believe
But I want to be jealous of Joe Rogan's attention 100% IMDb like not only did I know about his diagnose
Closest before all you did
But I actually did the same thing that he did before he did it
And I just didn't want to tell the media but now that I see the proof-of-concept that people are enjoying Rogan
Yep yep
It is attention
I don't know what the reality is
I could see it all being true
Being vaccinated to see it all possible
All bets are off cuz he's not telling the truth to anyone
Ever
Yeah it's very confusing but I do find it
Funny
Yeah he's getting on air
Alright f*** it I had covid
I have been denying everything for so long
So I lied about it
I could see that now not only that not only did I recently but also
And I had trouble year-and-a-half ago as well
And
Oh my God it was very very mild did
This was this was Stronger this was more intense this
That's why I look blown
Oh she had to get over the year and a half ago to see vet you've got
You got it twice
Now
Isn't interesting also
It seems like
Maybe
Is a year-and-a-half ago you got sick and it was mild
And this time it was a lot more
Severe
The A-Team coincidental
Or interesting
Or maybe not coincidental that your coverage is last time it was fake and this time it's really just seem like that
Whatever your personal experience
Applied to the entire world to Maidu
Sing that sounds somewhat familiar boy it is exactly in the pattern of the way Alex Jones behave
It's it's hard to look at any of those like
List of signs of
Malignant narcissists and not be like 11 11
I think you even create new simple
Who like he's mutated
So creative with his narcissism
Enable
It is he really it does it does remind you of
Virus
To contain this out
It's narcissism
Lampeter screen
Omicron
Garbage
Data
That's right people mispronounce zaida
The data
I did not know that
So Alec Alec says enemies that make up things about
I think he's talking about us
You think so
6000k
And that's why he didn't want to tell everyone
But he had covid
Twice right
A lot of enemies that always
I never got into it with a while back
I thought explain buddy else
And you're going to get sick again unless you just overload your vitamins and minerals
Prophylactically
Oh no
Guys
We do my officers a big brown paper bag
Oh boy this is falling off the rails now brown paper bag
Is getting a not good alright
I didn't tell people year-and-a-half ago I had covid cuz I knew that dumb podcast would really s*** all over me for a long time
It all over me like that screaming guy would have screamed for a long time
Stupid I am really tough not appear that that way is up
Or even
Just take us out of it like it would have really hurt a lot of the arguments I was making back then people had known that
Covid-19
Astonishing
But the second part that I need to really really highlight here is
Did he saying that like
You told it people like you're not going to escape this if you're going to get it or whatever
By not disclosing that he has it
I'm going
Get to rallies
Is going to Auntie Mass protests
Going to the grocery store in Florida
By where is that rotten her mask
All the stuff
He is essentially making a decision
For the people around him
Expose them to it
Yeah he's making this decision that you're not going to escape it
For them
And that's f***** up that is beyond
Disgusting Behavior
I don't know if all of the people who work at Infowars were aware of his
His diagnosis
Expose them to it but if not
I think they could probably sue him totally
I think it's an unsafe work environment that Alex
Consciously created
Ryan the Hills
Denial of the risk doesn't
Actually mitigate the risk
I think this is just admitting he's a horrible person
Yeah he's a nightmarish person who is
Possibly directly responsible for the death
I am he doesn't eat
It's clear that he doesn't
Looks like respect
Other people's ability to make informed
Decision
If he's lying
About whether or not he has it or lying by omission
I don't know.
The timeline of when he had it but he obviously didn't Courant
13mm cell
Well I mean not just that but you think
S*** he had it
The same time he's telling people
To go rip off
People's masks from their faces
It's true you know like if I'm screaming at people in stores if they ask me where am I
That's f***** up yeah that's really f*****
The only other thing I can think about is like maybe he did actually
Get sick
At some point
Quarantine himself
Because
There's a lot of vacations
That is true
There have been weeks where he's gone
Yeah
So maybe one of those was at him covering
Right now I thought Alex was right about everything
Anyway he gets really cocky about how he's got Ivermectin now
Prophylactically
Totally cool
Attract guys
We do my officers a big brown paper bag and bring it to me please
The one with the Ivermectin bag
Nnn just bring it to me
So
Remember these murderers and criminals don't want you to know that
Support.com
Wow wow
I can't I mean on the other hand
I can absolutely see the doctor that's willing to take Alex Jones as a patient just being like
You want to shut down after mekton I'm not going to stop I get I get my Ivermectin from a doctor's name is dr.
Are you going to are you going to mock my Paul Reiser joke and then pull up Mister Ed out of your way back
Alright
Alright wonder what
I just think this is really silly that he's getting really defensive
About Ivermectin and then
Doing a pivot to a my pillow at
I don't know if it's a copy that he has to read but you always like to have amazing human beds
Do they also sell like dog bed
Yeah it's okay great great
Cry cry cry
Put your specified human bed is always
Always sticks out his
That's a weird
Weird way to describe
So Alex
Gets
This bag
You made you
Your human bed now lie in it
He's good at lying
Sir Alex against his paper bag
One of them has a 40 on it
The other one had to divert Mac
Want to see my Ivermectin
Oh what's what's all this
Let's just open it up for you
Tractor Supply
Does Evan like Santa Claus taking care of everybody
Hours a day
Vermont
What does that mean
Ivermectin hours a day forum
Arete shot please
This is Ivermectin for humans want to Nobel prizes antiviral
Does that taking hours a day
Does that mean he's Doctor shopping for people like
Guess no idea what that's supposed to even rain
I definitely means he's it doesn't mean that he's taking people chicken
Can soup and s*** like that though
Ivermectin won a Nobel Prize
Didn't win a Nobel Prize Dance 2015 William C Campbell Eco won the Nobel Prize in physiology
Via Madison
First contributions to the discovery of a Vermeer
From which Ivermectin was derived
It didn't win the Nobel Prize as a health supplement or as an antiviral though italics
Claiming
I was specifically about it being a really exciting anti-parasitic
Sticktherock that have been discovered
A bunch of drugs have been able to be made from this discovery include selamectin which is a topical parasite killer
For dogs and cats
Interim actin which is an oral drug
For cattle
It sounds like a really good thing for like
50 warming
Yeah yeah that's really good for
Killing bees
Take a note from Acton believing it to be a preventative or cure for covid is just really stupid and intensely dangerous
Chris just for no reason
The cdc's reported on data
Poison control centers that shows a tripling of calls related to Ivermectin in 2021
And I have to assume Alex doing this bizarre pageant are you taking pills on air isn't going to help
Flatten the curve at all no no
I don't know
I feel like he wants people to be like somehow offended or like
Triggered by this I guess I guess he wants people to be like
Oh my God look at how I can ask if he's taking pills on a hair
Instead of everybody just going like hey man if you want to kill yourself don't go for it
This is dangerous and you're being irresponsible
Pure audio
Yeah
But you've done worse
That's true
I guess your whole like last year-and-a-half where you just been sort of lying and
Pretend it didn't have covid
It's probably worse
I really am starting to think you just want a lot of people to die
Do I struggle with that myself I mean it's a little bit like
It's a little bit like that
That
Impulse
Did some religious people have
To where it's like
I will see the end time
The world will not last beyond babe
And if it's not going to happen
I'm going to make it
His behavior is really
Tough to find a coherent explanation for the Dozen
Involved
Right
The end of the world is involved in whatever he's doing it's got to be something but if you want to be lazy and just
Adopted
Conclusion that is 1 UK
I'm just
I don't know man it's so weird
It's so weird to just be like
Defensively and aggressively take
Taking pills on air
It really reminded me of that 2013 episode we listen
To where he had a hamburger
Any put all these supplements
Super male vitality
Yeah
I don't know what I'm supposed to be experiencing but this is funny I guess
This is stupid
Yeah it starts yelling about this is going to save him or something
So let me show you
Earlier
See that's falchi see this Bill Gates
I'm going to kill those prions you bastard murderers
Bio weapon you monster
You want to suppress me you want to kill me yourself
I'm going to roll over here
Button press
Is there a Cheesy this Bill Gates I'm going to kill those prions you bastard murderers
Bio weapon you monster
You want to suppress me you want to kill me you son-of-a-b**** you goddamn demon
You think I'm easy to kill
We're going to roll over to your
Crap
I got out of the radio broadcast
I just
Underwhelmed by the devil if the Devils playing
Can be counteracted with a
Anti parasite medication
Damn
We've just started playing the magic
Magic the Gathering you know what it feels like to overplay your hand
And I assume Satan is it going like oh s***
I should have tapped
That mana and instead used it
To create a defensive creature or something like that
Sure but that game
Been up this belief system entails the devil having a
Thousands of your long plan oh no I didn't consider
My evil plan to put prions and everyone is counteracted by this
Medication
Seems dumb
I definitely think they like the devil it in his
Mind is really stupid
Somebody that's been there since the birth of creation right next to God with
Probably not be surprised by Ivermectin but who knows
Sports Medicine
The devil can't even God has
I guess
I would like
To introduce this into the person
Call care point
Anyway this a won the Nobel Prize for humans
This Ivermectin
Wichita
No although my pillow in the running
Seattle
Google prize-winning
Or humans
Bergen Record
Jerome
Who is feta cheese
Stupid
Yeah he's rich
You can't be stupid stupid
That makes sense makes sense I don't think that people who were saying that Joe Rogan's taking horse medicine
We're actually thinking
He was taking the worst medicine
It's just that
His listeners will
Yes
He can afford whatever it is he wants he has access
People who can get him
Human pill form
Where is a lot of people who don't have memes can't see doctors
Don't have insurance
Any of these kind of things will be inclined to take shortcuts if they believe that there is some kind of miracle cure
And the danger of the behavior of people like Alex
Joe Rogan
Is that people who are in that
Kind of a situation In Their audience
Made
I think like a good idea imma take this horse
Yeah yeah that's the
A comic with a few times she
Had a joke about her dad
Taking
Fish penicillin
Because he was like same as regular
Penicillin it's the same thing
And you're like
That is not a man being stupid that is
The end of a healthcare
System is what you're looking at that the complete failure of a band who's like
I can't just go to the doctor
You know so I'll just take Pisces
Nicely done better joke
I did punch up for this till you got a call that you got to call this
I don't know she's a nationally touring headliner
Okay
Google
I might go with 0 to 1
Anyway Joe Rogan
He's a brat
So you smart
He's very smart
House on the river
You left this taking all the shots and Dino the dumbasses
He's the one that headlines with Dave Chappelle
You're stupid
Yep sure wish you'd wake up
But you said they're calling me stupid independent
But he's not because he's rich and he has a really bright house down by the river
Now it's like you call me stupid
A white why is the defensiveness shifted over from Rogan to
About you isn't it Alex really just about you
Blisters
Can you sit around and laugh at us medical doctors gave that to me
Is incredible
Cuz he wants to plan it for himself he wants you Dad
Optimistic
Presented without comment
Spot
What are read Lottery do you think
Mike Lindell is
Stupid
For Pizza Hut has a bad break that he is too optimistic
That doesn't sound like something Alex
Improvised or wrote
B a
So Alex is taking his Ivermectin on air
We did it
The Wynn I'm not saying
That you should immediately or anything but he does play special report for the next exit
Throw it up or something. But it's fun to imagine
Highway comes back and he's got some other news
Are some of the giant development
Wards.com zerohedge story
Europe CDC breaks with bigen Administration
Has no urgent need
Recovered Buster's
Five European countries have now suddenly said they're ending all color restrictions
Sweden
Has the lowest numbers in the world in the lowest vaccinated
Now it's other
European country
The EU CDC making the same point that we keep hitting on their boosters are not really a higher price
I already than making sure the wider population has access
To the primary dose
What's the vaccine
Statement was also the vaccines of cells are working great and they boosters are still very appropriate
For people with weakened immune
Willfully misrepresenting the position and pretending that day
You know the uet ucdc thinks
The booster shots are danger
Nonsense
I'm not sure what I was talking about with five European countries ending other covid
Restrictions but I think I might have found the article that he's a mystery
Reporting
Just a couple days before this episode the European Council announced that they were five countries which were going
To be excluded from their list of countries
The redeem safe to accept Travelers
From into the EU
They're working on quote
A gradual lifting of the temporary
Directions on non-essential
Will travel into the
The EU
But some countries are seeing transmission that makes them to risk
Whiskey for that list
Incidentally the list is Israel
Lebanon Montenegro the Republic of North Macedonia
In the United States
It's there we go
If this is the story that I was referring to that the reality is actually the
Complete opposite of what you think
This is a five countries giving up on covid restrictions
Hbe you working to gradually return to normal and it part of that process
Heavy restrictions on people from five countries or not doing
Good enough job respecting
Yeah those
Restriction he should be saying that the EU is
Putting new restrictions
That said there are news stories of periodically the popup but countries planning to ease restrictions
Princeton's Ireland recently announced that they plan to ease restrictions in October mostly due to the fact they reach 9
Movie percent vaccination rate
Among adults
Wow
What good country
How many stores are actually really interesting to look at
Prince Denmark is planning to ease most of their pandemic restore
Merchants & B
September because they feel the
The pandemic is under control
Thanks to high vaccinations
Parlor using restrictions is no longer requiring busy
Businesses to use coronavirus passports to make sure that customers have been vaccinated
Four-headed negative test
The past 72 hours
This is relevant because part of Alex's
This big argument about the pandemic is that it's an
An attempt to bring
These vaccine passports it'll become the mark of the beast or something and then they'll never go away
Because as we all know you know this
What's a government gain the power that power never goes away
But here we have a concrete example in the form of Denmark where they use this strategy
It appears to have work
Between affective
And now they're going to stop with the passports because the reason they were using them
Has gone away
The Counterpoint to a whole bunch of Alex's
Real primary
Yeah
Also I suspect him bring up Sweden is just in grasping at straws
It was all that he could come up with was this month Soul talking point that he's forgotten about the context
Completely meaningless bulshit
Exhausting
You hear about New Zealand
And you're just like God you guys are do
Like they had one case show up again
And they were like
Lockdown
Lock it down we're not
I'm doing this for another year
One is enough
You know it's
Easier in
Smaller
It is and it's easier when it's an island
Weights for sale
Definitely
Definitely there is a
Yo I can't help but think
Of tweets that I've seen of like
The government could have just paid everyone
Stay-home
Yep or whatever you know like
We would have found a way to suck that up this is America
You couldn't pay people enough
To save their own lives
Misrepresenting these stories out of the EU whatever
A story not the not the FDA story that the CDC documents
But it's the FDA story that is the people quitting
Okay the doctors quit
Rebellion
Lighthouse rushed booster plan
It's not
About the booster that was one issue
FDA doing whatever it wants
The scientist
Salazar browsing program
Sainsbury
Authorization of the Franken shots
Genetic therapy
When it was never authorized and I just reduced into the emergency authorization
Level of fraud is
The level of this attack and the transparency of it is just mind-blowing to me
Really hard to tell what Alex's even talkin about here and nickel
Because of that whether he's lying or just trying to mislead people
There's a distinct
Where do I hear this is him saying that there's a fraud going on that the covid-19 got full FDA approval when it real
Galatea just got an extension
Hobbit emergency youth authorization
This is the fraud that doctor's Gruber and Krause were so upset by that they quit
BFDIA
That's how I heard that
The only drug that people acclaimed has received FDA approval is the Pfizer shot
And this is true
It did
It got full at the approval not just in
An extension of its emergency
To use authorization
The confusion that Alex seems to be representing is that the FDA has not given the same fool approval
Farthest shot
It's going it's going to be marketed as
Call her daddy
I hate that name I don't know if I'm pronouncing it right if there are so many creative bernadee
Maybe it's so many creative
Writing majors
With no work
All you got to do is hire them to name ship for you
That name is a speedball
The FDA hasn't approved that to be used in people aged 12 to 15
Normally fully approved a third dose being used as a booster
These two uses as a booster in for people under 16 continue to be allowed under an emergency use authorization
But the vaccine itself is fully FDA-approved
If Alex is trying to tell us audience that the vaccine itself hasn't been approved
He's lying
If he's trying to tell them that these specific
Two uses for the vaccine are still under review and only allowed by emerge
To use authorization
But he's not delivering that information very
Clearly
And feels like he's trying to mislead people definitely
Whatever the reality of the situation isn't conveyed by his coverage of it
Which is his job
And so he is felt
And that I was going to go with talking to people who've been to heaven
Is this job but
Man I miss that
Osgood South oh my God
I wanted to talk somebody's been to Hell
Only ever talked to anyone who's been to Hell
Oh my God
God probably cuz religious people don't want to hear about it now I'm going to be poring over those 2003 episode looking for
Girl Craig Roberts is Becky also went to hell
Yeah you didn't do a good enough job with his second life
Glad to give him a taste of what it was going to be f***** around with this third
So now it's back to talk about the CDC document
That might be an FDA.
Sure
Oops
Accidentally reveals list
I'm coming back scene
Side effects including
Micro card
Autoimmune disease and death are we going to go to break
Whitley
Actual CDC document
Does NFPA documents taken cause problems
Well it said it might not that they would so we say it's false
What
We believe this will cause heart attacks blood clots in other phone
Happened
Heroin you might have an overdose and die
We can send you mine. I thought Alex was and I
Expert on
Causal relation
Cause and effect
It turns out he's not know it doesn't seem like
So now that he's being more specific I can say with certainty that the bombshell CDC documents he thinks he's going to spend the night
Recovering
Or just the FDA PowerPoint presentation I mentioned earlier
This is very sad
We're defensiveness bad fact-checking is
A little depressing
Like I don't
Think that Alex
Can possibly actually believe the things that he believes
He saying
The Books of John fact-checks on this on the claims of this presentation is actually evidence of foreknowledge
Side effects
Discuss the larger picture of what the PowerPoint presentation
Was about
One of them includes a nfda spokesman
Speaking to fact-check
Quotes
No specific covid-19 vaccine was the
Disgusted that meeting but rather that meeting was held to discuss in general
The criteria FDA may take into account when making a decision about emergence
Authorization
Tori covid-19
The list of Adverse Events on slide 16 is just a list
Two possible outcomes
But the FDA could
Centrally monitor for
When conducting
Safety surveillance
Once a vaccine was authorized
There's a big difference between the list as it
Existing this presentation and
A list of potential side effects
It's based on studies
Or science
Kind of hard for me to leave it outside
Understand
Distinction
It's just
It's really tough
If he doesn't understand that he has no business
Conveying information to the public
He does understand that
Extinction time he's willfully misrepresenting its people and is a liar
Yasso
Possibility of a third option
No
Nope
And it's weird
The FDA and CDC of the same thing
A red Shop please
This is from the cdc's website
At fda.gov
Website
In October I'm going to show you this
When we come back
That was a magician magician level sleight-of-hand there is this year
Car my God I feel like I'm playing card Monte with somebody who doesn't know what either card is
Is this your government agency
Very
Wild
Fairies
Bad not good not good work
Anyway Alex gets to talking
Because he needs money anyway he wants
Do you want to know that you was going
Scale back
We remember these days
But now he's going to launch somebody podcast
He's going to
Go a million hours a day
And I think maybe
It's because you super committed to the info war or
He started selling human beds for Michael indelicato
We are still on here and we have
Major plan to expand
In the face of this tyranny
Because I was quite frankly going to cut
2 years ago
My work
I was going to colleges
Remove myself in write a book a year
I've committed to
14 hours a day 7 days a week
And I'm going to start 7-Day week podcast Special Report
Different news bureaus all over the country
And so that takes a lot of money to do that and we'll be watching a lot of things the next few months but
Hemiola next we get stronger
And so I need your prayers and your support I need you to go to infowars.com
How many how much money did Mike Lindell give him
I mean he said that all he has is an affiliate relationship with Michael
Glendale my Glendale does not
Give Hillary said one of our biggest sponsors is Mike Lindell on this episode
He does have a monetary relationship with confusing one
I don't know but I would strongly man
Again Alex to the f****** Washington Bureau with Jerome corsi
Go good no I thought it ended well I think I don't know if that lawsuits still active but corsi and Larry Clem
Assuage
And you overpaid that dude real bad by repay that guy
And it's easy to have
Bureaus in other cities because
All you need is an idiot with the laptop
And just a Blog
Or whatever
Can you can get any one of those
Yeah yeah I still even that is overextending yourself at this point
As a friend Alex
Anyway congratulation
On the pillow
Now it's Sia
God no
Oh look US Food and Drug Administration
Hour 20
Watch minute
Video that is on YouTube
You can
Beer plans for monitoring covid-19 vaccine safety and effectiveness
Idiotic
Scientist lab
And said basically this isn't safe
Stop the shop
Wild
But there it is
Hour 50 minutes
Video sorry I'm
So
This is how Alex's workflow generally goes
You make some erroneous claim and then when he needs to muster up the evidence 40 points doing almost 9 hour long video and then he gestured
Pictures at it
It's all the proof you need it's all in there seems like if you've got that and you've got a staff
They can find
The clip for YouTube channel
Yeah yeah it's not the proof
But he needs this game is boring and old
I wasn't watch this very long very dry meeting of the center for biologics evaluation and research
Any couldn't point to any specific point later play any clips from it they would make his argument
Only knows that he's is that he seen memes of this PowerPoint presentation slide that includes a list of side effects
Am I posting this super long video will look more impressive people than just saying hey look at this meme I found
Now that Alex has his evidence in place this long-ass video that no one in the audience is going to watch
He can use it to give credibility to other b******* narratives that
He's pushing like that the EU is stopping vaccinations or
The FDA scientists
Cuz they were against the vaccine
Also this clip includes one of my favorite ways that Alex
Cannot allow himself to be wrong about any
He gets the runtime of this video wrong which doesn't matter at all
But he can't let that stand
Who use it as an example of a time when
Something was worse than he said
People accused of exaggerating balls of time things are worse
Liquor time when he was
Half an hour off on the runtime of a video
Supercritical
Detailed of evil think
Attack him for exaggerating about I was actually about to scream at him
Forgetting that number wrong
Because
If you're up till 2 a.m.
Just
Dork
IPad
But I think one of the themes of this episode if there is one
Based on my
Viewing of it
Is it Alex's pretty.
About people calling Ivermectin horse
Seems like that
Nobel Prize is an antiviral for humans
We shouldn't
Horses drink water
Are you getting
Weird
By the way if you talk to any farmer or
Rancho Scott horses
To the vet's office today
6:30 in the morning
Boxer
We must be doing a lot of cows or horses
Is there healthier on there better
Antiviral
The story is not true
Such enemies of humanity
Trying to suppress their real jerks a real real jerks
Overplayed his hand
Like a real jerk
What'd
Jerk
They're calling this horse Pace horsepower
Yep yep
Wow what a knot
True story
Just real made up
App that's a convenient piece of Alex's backstory that he was he worked as like a blanket up
Smalls accent
When he was younger
Expertise in all these
Animal medicines that he wants his listeners to take
Put that horse paste in DIY even put it in horses myself so that means it must be good for you
Straight
What's so good man I can't believe it but Alex is
Is being a real jerk
Real jewelry
You know that we talked about this many many many many many many times
Alex up my China
Some coverage of China that I think
Scuse kind of positive for our
And then as I said there are large
Quadrants
Critical race Theory
Male girly Behavior band China cracks down on sissy man
CIA propaganda destroy the family and their country
Which it is
Zambia City man
That's up to you but
They're doing it to undermine
The culture
I really think that a free-speech crusader like Alex
To be super again
What's the government of China Banning effeminate men for being allowed on television legislate feminist sounding
Superman
According to NPR the rules the government put in place also would quote limit anyone under 18 23 hours per week
Online games play on school days
They're also regulating who's allowed to be promoted as a celebrity
Quotes
Pastor should avoid performers who violate public order or have lost morality
Hey come on now is super transphobic and aggressively anti-lgbtq as a whole butt
The larger world you should really require him be
Super against
I mean if you think that a government never gives up power
This shouldn't be the one instance where everything
China's got it right
Did you be a drastic and super aggressive attack on freedom of expression and speech
In China
His beliefs mean nothing one violates
That is convenient to advancing good thing
So Alex has been teasing
For quite a while that he's going to go to
Call Fanny.
Not you get to call from a guy who's a retired
Pharmacy type guy
But you know this hold
Coveting made him after get back in the game
Now got to go out for one last
I will say that one thing that made me a little bit worried about him
Is he talks about his wife
Apparently
How is an IUD
He refers to as
An IED
Would you be quite different
She also had the
A regular
Michael is well
And she's being an IED for I forget how long
Beaver Avenue.
Syndrome
Anything
Man what is going on our phone system this happened yesterday on the show and it just have
Open again
Brothers important right after he got into his wife
Improvised explosive device
Hellboy
Yeah
Those that's unfortunate
Can they are they okay with it
Can can far-right people be okay with iuds
Let's just not do
Good point
That's it that's the way they treated like
Cut off
That's bad
Tusken Raider call
So in the past
They would do.
Now wearing a modern Steve's words
More like
Spy
For each stab
Chameleon
What
Hahaha
I'm at the crib
Put the order in analog phone
Billet Allendale
So yeah this is fun
Skittle wall
Fukkit Waluigi
Can't even get a
Found work yet
I've been through a lot on this episode
Some interesting things to learn about Alex
Very very defensively and angrily taking Ivermectin on air
Talking about how he's had covid multiple-time jealously trying to grab onto whatever
Joe Rogan
Baby can get
And now this
Smile Vista
Phone
Problem
When when Alex said this
There was a little bit left in the third hour and I just said
I give up I'm going home for the day
System 44
We're rebuilding the system and change the passcode to change the passcode around here anymore routine basis
The bathtub
Composed
That's all a matter delivery
Oh my God I'm punching out man I just said nothing
Nothing nothing else can happen on this episode that
Will is an anyway
Somebody hacked
My system just to occasionally cut off phone
And
Somehow
People
Not changing the password
Right
Something to
To do
With Tim
Correct
Yes
And his sexual orientation which must
Dimensions very relevant
Nope so I bid you adieu September 2nd episode
Pretty amazing
I think of the Revelation that Alex
That's God Cohen
The bunch
So did did pieczenik Iran the first time
I don't know man
With antibiotic
Text sure are we using antibiotics
Get the Steve pieczenik license but don't don't you enjoy though to that Alex pulled the
China kind of with that like
Yeah 12 closer to me than my parents yet
Ulta Beauty
I could not help but
Hear that same exact thing I was trying to do that same kind of reveal such as
I think it's
I think one of the things I find really interesting about this is like
It's kind of a big reveal in as much as like
XM Sirius
That he had
Covid-19 conceivably multiple times
But it's also like
I'm not surprised
It's not a bombshell I assumed
The way he's alright
Always lift his legs means yes
He probably got covid and I would have assumed 80 did
He didn't need to tell me
Thanks
Employee sues you
Another one of your employees Jordan we will be back
Interesting
Touchback into the present day this week
Until we return we have a website we do acknowledge right.com
We also wrote Twitter
Go to bed
Sorry that's not mine
I'm going to have to say there we go
Robot
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color