Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge b b
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Indeed we are dads
Getting a little bit of work done
This morning and
Take a little break
And I looked on YouTube and I saw that there was a new trailer for the new Matrix
Movie that just got released
Is today and I watched it
And I have some
Interesting thoughts about it
But they're the reason to Bright Spot is because
I can't wait for Alex's review
Immediately I saw this trailer on my car
Be great yeah we're going to be there
Yeah into now I feel like it's my responsibility
You would have I have to fund
Infowars
I have to keep them on the air if so we will buy them tickets to The Matrix
Resurrection I have been a show on the air at least until the end of the year
Like we can't deprive the World of Alex Jones is Mayfair
Counting down the minute when is it Wednesday so that means that we
We're going to get
Alex's
Doom review
We're going to get his
Matrix review I assume he's going to watch Calvin what about the live-action one
The brunette one movie no they don't even have a second movie deal yet
And he's just like I can only make the first half of this movie so I can only make the first fifteen patients f*** it I don't care
Don't watch it
You're not going to see how it is good f****** luck
I like that strategy
Yeah it was going to be
The banner end-of-the-year for Alex's Carly Rae reviews have been like
Dune
Is the movie
That you've always wanted to see dude made into
Batman excited
I don't know how much you can tell from
A single trailer but I will say
That I don't know if I need another Matrix movie that wrestles with whether or not the things he's experiencing or
Oh I can see the look that was established
I read a big couple time
Double back around and I like now it's actually a double secret Matrix
I'm out are you insane I just wrote that Rodger Stone
Is that the counter counter counter cool narrative that would be
Clancy
Tom Clancy
Temperature
FairPoint
I think they made
I think they wrote a spec script and it got rejected
Cuz it probably sucks
Set strip to replace Keanu Reeves character Thomas Anderson with dzx Clark
Intrepid psychologists f****** machine
Himself
That's 55
Dan is the
TV show Taskmaster
You mentioned this the other day I think I might have
So I wanted to
To do something out about wanting to do a British panel game show of Love qi
I was a huge fan of Stephen Fry for I will be rhyming the rest of the show
And get out of here
Taskmaster is another Bridge
British panel game show but the conceit behind it
Is this guy gets a bunch
New comics and it gives them this very open-ended tasks like
Open this thing
Or whatever and then they have to
Do it in an interesting and creative way
Yeah and the combination of like different personalities that they get ever
Retirement shares that
There will be Creative Solutions that are like
Out-of-left-field in also they'll be Solutions where somebody's like
Okay and in two seconds just two matches it with a f****** hammer and you're like well that is opening the jar that's fair
I'm freaking out right now because I legitimately can't remember if you brought this upon the show or in casual social
Conversation can't remember either way it out and I'm glad for the
The reminder really great it really is
Episode
To get into I think it's one of the weirder ones I've heard quite a while its September
That was pretty close that was pretty close
Yeah it's
Wild business episodes nuts
I don't know I don't know how else to put it
It's just it's just nuts
Unaccept
That's better than
Yeah it's so we'll get down to business on that before we do this hello.
Tabor like Sabre with a
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
I'm a policy
Text spooky
Stout Alex
Spooky scout out
Thank you next
Do you know how it is with our inboxes
How to Michael in Estonia happy 5 years and four countries with two puppies
Lovemark thank you so much you are now probably want
Thank you very much
I got if that's your real name
I don't think it a real name is Dirk Stryker hard name
Next half asleep and gave her pajamas thank you so much
And Selene secret National Geographic
Something about your nail polish
Also
I don't know I don't know what I
Conclude this ass like a policy wonk shout-out or a hostile threat that we're sending over
But Villa Ville I don't know
Let her DND characters
Should quote be prepared for an unconventional family reunions that definitely sounds like
A threat right no that's not a threat that's a tease that means that they're going to in the game at look as a form
Dungeon master myself
Something for the past is going to come up and there's going to be an exciting new scenario for them to play out
I disagree I think that same as characters family is dead
And there's going to be joining them
Roseola
Super clear about this threats for other people
This is not going to become a thing weird
Prison Architect dropped
From Today Show
I'm not stupid
You're not stupid
I disagree with all the way
That's over six
Strongly disagree with all of this
I was listening to this episode
The up to a lot of places and there's a lot of things
Musica covered
Being covered my thought was
Going to Stranges
Is Owen Shroyer still a political prisoner
Is he still alive
Money and now he's going to hang out about that
I went to the go give fun
Whatever this alternative GoFundMe
The 200,000 really fast
Yeah
Do they have not even if it yet that's fantastic
This is not something they're talkin about as much if you don't
Hit your goal do you not
Get the money
I think you still do I don't think it's
Kickstarter
David Gray Plumbing really f****** great if they if it that the last second there just like sorry man
248,000
If that were the case then every one of these grapefruit Style with just haven't Nicole of $1
But more importantly get the money you had maybe a lot
So we start off the show here in this is this is a trend that I've been noticing
And I don't know what to think of it
But it might be worried
Alright that Wolf Blitzer with the Nightly News
Next
Tuesday
Alex has been using send in the clowns cuz Bumper Music
More regularly
And this is how he starts the show starts to show this is what an old man plays before they die
The day before you die
Close to record
Losing my timing this late in my career like ugly it's grim
It's on the nose that leads
Yeah
Introspective when he starts off
The episode obviously I mean if you start with
Sinatra's
Version of send in the clowns
You're in a mood
Yeah it's like playing only the first 10 minutes of It's a Wonderful Life and being like that was a great movie right
Always try to be calm those are really my best broadcast
But the mainstream media
Pigeonhole.
It was Barry Goldwater
Famous maniacs
Help build that Ron Paul and Donald Trump and others stood on top oven
Myself as well with his shoulders
Is no Vice
First very important point
The shows were Alex's, are not the best ones
The ones that where you drunkenly throws hatchets at one of them cameras those of the best choice
And it's not even close
Oh yeah second this is an interesting that Barry Goldwater
Quote because Alex isn't wrong
The Goldwater did say those words
However they were written by his speech writer a big big toe
Time Lincoln scholar name
Goldwater many times falsely attributed the quote to Cicero
Sure most importantly though
Just because Barry Goldwater said something that doesn't make it
True
Oh well it's a it's a well-written sense because it was written by a speechwriter but that doesn't mean that it
Expresses of accurate
Point
It really just a pissy way of saying like
If you bomb something for a good reason and you also kind of seemed to enjoy bombing things that you shouldn't be judged
Just because you secretly enjoy bombing things you doing it for a good reason
Is it is what it is
Yeah but it's a little bit sounds better than
The Goldwater not only sadness
Folks
I'm going to do whatever the f*** I want
It's better if I say it like
Extremism in the service of good it's fine to quote Barry Goldwater do what thou wilt
Mother quotes
I'll go along with that would you like to buy antsy pants
Extremism in defense of Liberty is no Vice
This one isn't one of them
He also said
Sometimes silence
Is it golden
It's yellow
That was Alex's presenting that is Goldwater
It is it is
Is not
It's most famously attributed to Georgia Senator Zell Miller
Who was the Democrat named but was basically a Republican
You can find the trans
In front of the Congressional Record what Miller said these words
February 12th 2004 if you read them in their full context they are
Bucking absurd
This whole thing
Is about how the US isn't immoral
The client it's going to collapse
Because of it okay
The proof
The culture of the far-left America was displayed in a startling way during the Super Bowls now-infamous halftime show
Show brought to us on behalf of value Les moonves
And the Pagan Temple of Viacom Babylon
I am really bummed out
The far-right can somehow lionize in history another old man
Bitching in the
Back same way they do now about the Super Bowl halftime show
He goes on to say quote
How many of you have ever run over a skunk with your car
I know the president has somewhere over there around Frog Hollow
I have many times
I can tell you that the stink
Stays around for a long time
You can take the car through the carwash and it's still there
So the scent of this event will long linger in the nostrils of America
Legislation
We will be dealing with this brat in Congress the job you were clearly meant to have
He swore that he wasn't just talking about a titty going on to say quote
Wouldn't you expect
Bumping humping trashy routine and titled I'm going to get you naked
The end of that way
A point of order this outfit
Responsible adult ever listen to the words of crap crap
I would quote years ago and I'm already mad.
Call Dad call Dad
There's more to close
I would put you some of the the lyrics
You some of it but the sergeant-at-arms at throw me out of this chamber as well he should
Then there was that prancing dancing strutting running guy
Evidently suffering from jock itch
Because he kept yelling and grabbing his crotch
Maybe there's a culture of crotch-grabbing in this country I don't know about
What is bad as all that was
My chain the hardest was seeing
This ignoramus with his pointed head sticking up through a hole that he
The flag of United States of America screaming about having
A bottle of scotch and wanting lots of crotch
What is it about old white people
That just makes them the worst
I went back and I watch that halftime show cuz I certainly haven't watch
Sticking his head toward American flag and yellow gajewski
I didn't see it in there maybe there was a part with like Littlejohn that got edited out now why not
Why not who cares
Who cares that up either direction he's just going to whine about it and I saw it
The performance of Rhythm Nation was pretty good
Piti
2400 like
Have you heard some of these lyrics these men
Boys would say
Buchheit
Why you apologize rap crap
So this dude was on one
In the Senate chamber
You might be confused about what he was actually speaking about because he doesn't
Get to that point until later on
Quote
The desire in Wheel of this Congress
Demeaning Polly do anything about any of these so-called social issues as non-existent embarrassingly
Disgraceful
The American people are waiting and growing impatient with us
They want something done
I'm pleased to be a co-sponsor of SJ resolution 26
Siri's a real sj-r
Sjr
Guitar you us there was something there a nice try
Couldn't remember what that is
26 Constitutional Amendment defining marriage
Between
There we go
The rest of his speech literally flows around this topic from the Superbowl
Complaints to not liking rap music
What a f****** a******
Speaking alongside to do do it later be outed as a pedophile
Oh no hold on
I stay in shoulder-to-shoulder not only with my Senate co-sponsors and chief justice Roy Moore of Alabama
More importantly with our company
Great
Great. Sounds really good when you isolated
It's not hard to agree with a point that sometimes being silent is the equivalent of being cowardly sure
Pretty important
Alex's got the speaker wrong
For the quote
The quote itself
Is a ridiculous piece
Zell Miller
Very very dumb
Gay people can't get married
Good-looking five-minute serovital from Senator Jordan from the great state of Illinois
Let the record show Jordan is making the
Jerk-off motion and he is see this is a floor would like to remind
Senator from Jordan that neighbor
We want people to hear you in Maryland
Sometimes it's yellow
To be silent
Play golzar interfreight Yellow
SanDisk italics on another etymological
Ambivalent
Grounding
Competition and urinate on themselves
People pissing themselves
Is that where the term yellow-bellied come
Comes from I understand how it seems like I'm just nitpicking things Alex says that he's wrong about but I need to stress that this
As part of demonstrating a pattern
Alex doesn't know anything he's just repeating things he's heard as if they're the product of excellent
Domestication or
Some sort of knowledge on his part
I'm he's just hoping that you as a listener will be fooled into weeks
Stepping is confident words as truth
They're not
In the specific case he's just imagine that the term yellow-bellied comes from soldiers who pissed on themselves in war because
That's something he's decided cowards do and yellow-bellied is a term of a coward
Brave I do I do appreciate that I know for a
Facts like what
He just starts talking that he's making that up completely out of his ass but it does sound like he knows what he's talkin
About
Actually kind of
Would be willing to believe that he think
Except that he's actually the apology up
Fascinating
The history of this because no one
Actually knows where the term comes from
Right they can't really trace it down
Direct
Route
There's a derogatory usage of the term yellow bellies from England
And in the late 1700s to refer to people from the
The fans which is Mary around
Coastal East
Country
It's talking about like they're they're like they're real
Is that there
Weaken brother in the US
Apartment newspaper
I was referring to Mexico
Soldiers is yellow-belly
It's unclear this is
Something that's racist or about a uniform
Its history is kind of Forgotten a bit of the context of that isolated
Instance of the term could literally be their uniform what had
Yellow
Black circle possibility
Does the word I thought of
There are some people who
Suggest that the root of the term has to do with the days when doctors believe that medical issues were all traced back to
The humors
And one of the four humors is yellow bile
Is true
But there is one of the four
Yeah I believe in the humors
Why not
This is a complicated ml edible logical history that you have going on here and it's not something that has it
Definitive answer
Explanation that no one gives
Yep he just made it up as he was talking
Astonishing that he could really say that out loud
With no context or even background for it and just go with it
It's such a confidence
Manor I don't know I feel like if you go see enough improv shows you see people say things that are incorrect a lot and they just have to learn
Keep moving you know if you stop and you're likely hold onto second that doesn't make any sense at all
Not actually driving a car
The show is over
So look dude
Alex is not wanted
But he did a lot of work
I'm not mad at
Prepared
Complaining I did probably 3 hours research last night about 4 hours research earlier than
Several hours of research
Myself
Orders
I think I have a responsibility to really try to cover all this
I'm nom nom nom nom nom nom nom nom
He couldn't help himself it was like a buffet oven
Information
So what's going on is he's got so much paper on the table which is evidence of
How much
Brookies
Johnny's got so much favor
So if he realizes that in his metaphor
Ordering those 20 plates
He is insured
He cannot consume all of the food on
Can any of those Play-Doh
Thus making the matter for him not being able to consume the information
Daisy ostensibly going to regurgitate towards out almost like
He's lost his timing this late in his career
Well I mean somebody sent in the clouds
Alex introduces what like the
MacGuffin
Is that what it's called like the driving force
Yeah the things that
Would explain why he's done so much research but obviously
Is not at all true right whatever is in that
Open Suitcase
It's just the prop that he's using
End
It has to do with story from the intercept
Let me just do this before I drill into the top stories
Let me just give you some big announcements
Major journalistic organizations will get into the interception others
For your request fauci
Salon in Chapel Hill
North Carolina
USA in China
Hundreds of pages
A fallacy directing
Murder of five viruses into a
Covid SARS
Do they make a super vaccine
For something that didn't exist
The entire evolutionary system of this planet
So Alex is literally all the details wrong
About this intercept
Story
They've got a Freedom of Information Act request going against
The national
Roots of Health
Imperative
Two really long
Grant contract
Between the NIH
Ecohealth Alliance
Involving coronavirus related work
Some of which did involve
Do the virologist
Hundreds of pages but that's because one grand is 528 pages long
And the other is 380
He's our long-ass document
What are the problems that comes from using a document like
Like this at 7
Conspiracy
Is it there super granular
In terms of detail
For instance on page 7
92 of the first grade
Which cover the project was ongoing from 24
The 2019
Breakdown of expenses related to
Two doctors who are part of the support team
Like for their phone and internet
This amounts to $47 per month but it merits
The paragraph
In this grant proposal
If you can't find specifics on this document with
This many specifics
Conspiracy
Yeah it's bad
Not good
So there to Grant's here but one of them doesn't even begin until July twenty
20 so I'm not going to consider it in terms of
The conspiracy that Alex
Suspense
The other one is for this one that I mentioned from 2014 to 2019
The actual details of it are pretty fascinating
I ran over a bunch of it like you brought this to my attention
Cuz you do you stay up on The Intercept a little more than I do
Sneaky Snake episode this Wednesday partially because of Labor Day mostly because of Labor Day
Also because I was reading
These G
Yeah they were excited
Ultimately a lot of it got really technical so I called them they help of our friend who's not a health Ranger
And I got to clarify.
This project
What they were up to was to
To prompt
The first part of the research was to go out and find samples to test for Coronavirus
Either one's we previously identified or new one
This would be done by going out to wild bat populations and take
Examples from Human to have interactions with wild animal population
And from people who work in
And animals at live animal Market
These samples and sequence brna of the coronavirus as they found him
They take this are in a to make samples
In Petri dish that would go on to it
Express this virus
And these work
Exposed to other cell
That were expressing ace2 receptor
The reason to do this is because if
The animal to human transmission of any of these viruses
It would most likely happen by way of The ace2 receptors
So this was a way to
Hancock circumstances
Where they could test whether or not the wild viruses they found would be something
It could possibly be transmitted to
So it doesn't make sense to you
And two I would argue almost all of the extreme-right has
Exploiting this
That is Arthur C Clarke's
Magic
Attitude
What is willemstad like
They take the virus from space and they put it into a hole and then the whole turns more virus around
And nothing is being created
That's one of the really important
Function this is not
They're not ripping the RNA apart milk in their own genetically created sequences do then create a stir
Stronger virus and then tested on the H2 receptors in order to
Destroy the
F****** population
Part of this one gram
Write the second part of the research
Because basically the phylogenetic research
Where they were trying to place evolutionary roots of the coronavirus as the paved
Discovered
The reason for doing this research is because there are some of these viruses they find it only info
Affect bats
A song that only infect humans
And there are some that are in the middle like more likely to infect humans less likely to infect
By studying the variations in these viruses
Different about them between them on Lauren a level
These scientists might be able to make some progress in terms of isolating
The part of a virus that makes it dangerous to human right
Very important research
You can easily see the reasons of these types of Grantswood
Things they were aiming to look
Into where
Here's some of the corrections
From just the last clip that we heard
The foia request
Did not volcano function Reeser
The grants are not touchy Direct
Chimeric emerging of five viruses into one Coronavirus
To create that
The end goal of the grant was not to make a super vaccine
All that stuff is just ask
Alex is made up and he's using the Specter of this intercept article to lend credibility to his
His Notions but none of it's real
Timer backed up by the article that has reference
Alex is making up these details cuz he doesn't care about the truth about what's going on he just saw a headline that look useful to him
He's filling in the details
The pieces of his already exist
Narratives
Not while we're on the subject
I'd like to take a moment to scold the intercept
Just for this article
Together support journalistic
Dushyanth exploring unlikely or even sometimes derided possibilities
I have no problem
At all the people sending for your request
To learn more about the research
That our government phone
Totally appropriate
Great
For instance
If they were jamming five viruses together into one super coronavirus and order to make a super vaccine
I think it would be good for somebody with a little bit of credibility to dig into it and try and figure out if there's any proof of then I would like
I would like a journalistic outlet with standards to take a real look at
I take issue with the framing
Of this article.
These grants but they found in there for your requests are not having a
Should we use any kind of Justice
Application for even slightly shifting closer to
Accepting
The lab leak
Theory
Hypothesis that the virus could have escaped from a lab accident
Which is
Still way different than Alex's story
That is pasa
Current weight of evidence leans more toward the natural or
On page 38 of the grant proposal in the section where the participants give their personal state
Wondery researcher said
Quote my work on Starz coronavirus ecology in collaboration
With co-investigators dacic
Let me to the
Discovery of several sars-like coronavirus is in bats
Which appeared to be an stress ancestral to SARS Coronavirus
And most recently which
Utilize the same ace2 receptor
I sorry
Suggesting direct spillover to
The humans as possible
Part of the justification for this grant
To be worth funding is that at this point
With 2014 when they're applying for the grant that they'd already discovered previously unknown sars-like virus as they could
Statically
Directly infect humans there is a very real impetus behind this happening
When you're coming off SARS and MERS exactly they were like let's not do it
Yeah they wouldn't be good
Yeah it was
Really would
Yeah it's almost like if you let it go wild
It would go bad
I understand that Alex is insane but the Interceptor Interceptor do better
Interview have a friend that story
They're boarding on these grants being released by a foia request
Shouldn't have a headline as vague as quote
New details emerge about coronavirus research
Chinese lab that is not a good headline to accurately
Portray
What's going on in the story mediate insinuate
I would allow for this just to be bad like a click
Activate type headline
Except for the tone of this article is incredibly so
Suggestive
Sources
This is a roadmap to the high-risk research that could have led to the current pandemic said Gary Ruskin
Executive director of us right to know a group that's been investigating the origins of covid-19
That's great
But the way this is written
Suggest that us right to know is an impartial Group B
Just trying to get to the bottom of this stuff
It's the voice of clarity on the issue of the origin of covid
That's not true
U.s. right2know is largely funded by the organic consumers Association
Haitian which is a naturopathic
Kind of outlets
They don't seem to like mainstream medicine all that much
They have a post on their website about how they've been
Slandered by the media for me
Quote row vaccine safety
That's the same Dodge that literally every anti-vax
Century makes when things
You get tough
In the middle of a pandemic
Basically the way you keep your auntie expositions
Don't look too ridiculous and Pablo
Asking questions of the medical establishment
Here's a little bit
From that post on the organic consumers association website
Why should we be injecting experimental drugs into people at all when there are safe
Effective
True preventive measures
Seven parentheses healthy food and natural health supplementation
The strengthen our immune system and generic drugs are at home or outpatient treatment
To reduce the chances of hospitalization or death and there was the series pre-existing Medical
Call conditions
A slightly better written version of Alex's positions without any fun gallon
Oh also on their website they're promoting a tribunal that they held in April to
Get to the bottom of the roots of
Covid-19 also served as a way to promote
Dr. Joseph mercola's newest book
Titled
The truth about covid
19 exposing the great reset lockdowns vaccine passports on the
New Normal
Impact their blog routinely repost things
That were originally posted
Humber College website
And if you don't know Joseph
McCulloch is one of the
Biggest anti-vax figures that exist
The media
Dispute
I've checked out their site and the organic consumers Association
Hard to tell apart
For Mike Adams natural news and they are by
Far
The largest funder of us rate
To know we're being presented as impartial investigators into the roots of covid in this article
That's
Not recognizing the person they're citing as a neutral source
Is essentially an advocate for the unproven position that this article is insinuating
Is not
Good Yelp
That said probably the thing that made me most
Disappointed about this article is the last paragraph
Quote the second Grant understanding risk of zoonotic virus emergent
Emerging
Infectious disease hotspots in Southeast Asia
The Proposal written in 2019 often seems prescient
Focusing on scaling up
Open to playing resources in Asia in case of an outbreak of an
Infectious disease
In referring to Asia is quote the hottest of the Eid hotspot
Here's the deal
This article is about the conflicting hypotheses about the origin of the novel Coronavirus
The underlying documents
GameFly the foia request
Aren't really Bombshells or evidence that makes the lab Theory
Compelling as if they should be seeing that way
This grant is
Prescient
As opposed to reflecting the well-documented history that many emerging infectious diseases pop up in Asia
Yippee huge, I was going to say though the ideas like that was one word that I read and I was like this whole
Thing can be f****** tossed away if you say prescient on a thing that is
Israeli Wyoming League happened a million times in the past your f****** wrong
Incentive
To the point where it's psilostachya out of
Play Yeah Yeah Yeahs
It was a group that investigated The Roots
To covet not an advocacy group primarily funded by an anti-vaxxer I'm sorry pro-vaccine safety
Outlet of weirdos
This isn't
Good
We were in normal time
I wouldn't really care that much
This wouldn't be that huge of a screw-up
Yeah maybe a little misses from time to time sometimes you interview but somebody and you don't
Check in all the possible,
Play Aventuras course
Problem is
But the stakes are too high
Free of The Intercept to lend its credibility to this s*** is
Damaging
I'm Not Lisa
How is it that you can be a journalist
In 2021
And actually hear the name us right
To know and not immediately go wonder who that is
Obviously that's an anti-vaxxer I mean I saw the quote from US1
Clicked on the link and immediately I was like
What am I doing here
I know what this shouldn't to know is is a little bit broader in their scope
Some of that
There's a global pandemic and the connection to reality surrounding that
Extremists to radicalize people into their ranks
This is not a time to make unforced errors and play directly into the hands of the fairies actors
If I were the editor at The Intercept I might
Give it another go on this one before I sent it to print
Oh yeah
F*** Alex
Three interceptions different responses with a good ruler
Who's all bulshit the hypothesis
He does remain an outside possibility that just hasn't been shown to be likely
So
That's his big story
He doesn't spend much time on it
Irreverence is it a bit
And
I will see we spent this time on
Other than that
Noboru Jordan I over-prepared Ono Ono
I over prepare don't know I'm not able to make any points
Too much
Too much information
Consumed burp
Infobear
That is a good name for the info
I think that's better
Yeah I mean
The more I read
The sourcing for that intercept article the more I got to the opposite
The conclusion that it's less likely
Like the more I read that tomorrow I'm like
You guys should have made this
Look at how reasonable everybody is act
That's the headliners
Everybody acting reasonably in best interest
Yeah it's crazy contacts
Is absolutely missing a lot of it
Scapula
Alex talks more about two things that are true
Also scientific facts
Literature literature
Virus vaccine
Carrie
When the body
Created in response to that was also very poisonous
Indiana
Add
So interesting
Sing I'm not true
If you go to India's Ministry of Health and Family welfare website you can
Define they're offering AstraZeneca and Kovacs
Some vaccines
They also approve Russia's Sputnik
View vaccine back in April
None of these are mRNA
Talking about is almost certainly the Kovacs in
That was made by India's own
Bharat biotech
I have no idea where Alex
Just coming up with all the other stuff though
Kovacs and recently released data showing their vaccine is 65.2% effective against
Hey 93.4% effective against
Severe
Symptomatic covid
Hindi currently also has a 12% vaccination rate in his work
Not getting that number higher so I don't
Nobody's talked about with
Suspended
Campaigns whatever I'm just so you just say whatever you want just so Furious
I don't
I don't I know it's
Easy
For him
But you can't say the virus is quota quotes
So deadly
Like that's unfair
You've spent the past
How many months
Telling me that the virus either doesn't exist or isn't
Deadly as they say
That the virus is a bioweapon
But it's a fake by a weapon
And the vaccine is the real thing that
India vaccine program is in Port
To talk about what you're not taking into account is that Alex had a
Mild case of
Covid-19
Any other more serious one
I'm so it's real serious.
Just get to get away with
You don't think I saw that go around
Yeah
Madison not is penetrated as Joe Rogan or Alex is dumb
Bulshit stunts of taking covid on are there
Evil
Created the virus
It released it intentionally
It's not even
It's super debate it's not give you a rebuttal
It's not fair.
It's like what temperature water freezes at you don't debate
Temperature
Or
Why would you make that or fluoride
These are known things
Spell incredible
Fauci created this and then released in Odyssey on purpose
No
That they knew that if they created a vaccine
Common cold
70 years
All of that is
Anderlecht
The temperature that water boils is like a scientific
Exact but it also depends on
All of the things that he just describer variables that we know are only what we know
You know in relation to other circumstances
In these environments we do know that
We also know that they change
So I know we mentioned this earlier
But Alex
Stacks of paper
Yeah he does have a lot of
Do any of them say that they
The speed of light is
Actually
Money stack okay
How many you know what they probably have a definite weight
It's not debated
Facts of 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12
13 14 15 16
Pablo Escobar
22 stocks
You could do a whole show on
So do a whole show on 100 fish Ali announcing
Via covid
Including the US
Is the end of the family and the family band
Officially from the UN I'm going to show you the
Official
Government document
Listen to the rest of the show and I don't think that he ever provided evidence that the UN has decided to end family
Such a huge official announcement
That word that to be an official announcement
Next thing you should show me the secretary-general being like
Like look family suck
My family sucks
Guess what
No family
All my friends
Complain about going home for Thanksgiving
Annoying it is what
You know what my dad was a real dick when I was a child so let's just end family
Also leaving that aside here's a good rule for you
Don't measure something like the news you have to cover by volume
Haven't more paper or presumably more stories
That's not navigation.
The better or borax
Important stories to cover or
That you are stories that you understand or can even
Communicate to an audience I'm better than mainstream news I have more sex
Typically when someone's trying to sell you something in bulk
It's not a high-quality item come on Sam's Club Kirkland you know it's great stuff
I don't know man multiple meal
Often isn't as good as
More expensive materials
Now
Just saying
Anyway Alex is a little bit mobile
Yeah it's a little bit sad share
You know they're bending the class
Send
Cloud
There should be clowns
He's in that mood because he realizes like
Man
I used to have a website prisonplanet.com used to update that website
No One updates that web
Anymore
Infowars.com
And Paul Watson
Quasi doesn't work with us
Really doesn't need more so no one even update
Prisonplanet.com
On screen
You know the last time it was updated
Five bucks says you don't
Twenty-something years ago
He's going to get a bunch of callers to decide
People quit using inside forgot a month ago I directed people
We're going to resurrect
Why
So that's where we are
We don't even have the money or the crew
To be able
Even
Everything even stay up
Update
I'm not complaining
Platform
Got to run just kind of stood back
Yeah they all left
They all laughed
Oh boy
Society
This is
Also
Generally prisonplanet and Infowars we're kind of like
Duplicate website content with posted on both ends
Infowars
As the website goes back to 1999
Like if you can find stuff on the Wayback machine
Combat Barbie
Yeah so I don't I don't know what the
The pointed-toe URL the now it's a redirect on your video site for wistful reminiscence
About websites that I didn't
Care about the first
And outside you are doesn't really do anything for you anymore
Directed it's abandoned video
Yes clearly you had a staff there who did it for you
You're fine
So
We got send in the clowns
It started to become more of the rotation
I noticed another song goes like what you doing
Police running over people all over the Western world
Horses
What
Alex is clearly an eagle's guy
It's happening he constantly rants Over You Belong To The City by Glenn Frey now we have Dirty Laundry by Don Henley
Emily coming out
If we get life's been good
To me so far it's not going to be an accident but that's one comes in
I'm sick of the Eagles I don't have any solo hits
Did not also Alex playing dirty laundry is bumper music while he launches into a string of Sensational headlines about people getting run
Run over by horses
All across the Western world
And all that kind of bulshit that's honestly entering the territory of stuff they could
Possibly be set
Yeah it's 2 on the
This absolutely isn't the case but it's Alex where performance artist desperately trying to clue his audience and that he's doing a
A bit this is exactly the song he would choose
Dirty Laundry the song where Don Henley is complaining about the way the news become more sensationalized
Tabloid
Focused in the early 80s
Here's some lyrics on that song it really imagine if you were doing satire
How this would be hilarious theme music
Play on The Alex Jones Show
We can do the innuendo we can dance and sing
When it said and done we haven't told you a thing
We all know that crap is King give us dirty laundry
Exactly what you would play for Alex if it was a joke about to get a divorce
I said just be like hey listen to Rumours by Fleetwood Mac and then leave the room that's all you need to do
If somebody like it
The evidence is mounting
Of a rogue board operators
Well done the most romantic romantic
Comedy Zaika
Can think of
Is the board operator trying to send you messages
Eventually after the whole thing's over you guys reconnect 20 years
Start playing
So far
Absolutely we made a real signal
So a little bit about how population that's what's going on
And generally I would say that
But your position should be
Against
Depopulation Wars
Should be conditional
It should not be
Conditional 4 hours organized the population
You're saying we're overpopulated like gear in the city
Predator
So they're naturally going to create
Artificial
Closings for the viruses in
Conflict information that get rid of it
And you can even argue that in the survival of the fittest mode
There's a place
But you see the people running this your pedophile
And Satan the center the worst
Greediest people
The problem
Oh boy
I mean obviously our population should be controlled by natural predators
I think keep us from starving to death
I don't want pedophile Predators doing it
I don't want Satanist
Look if I was being hunted by a
You f****** tiger in the jungle
I would be furious if I found out it was a pedophile tiger
It would be like what's the f****** point
I think that whenever
You talk about like
Believing in humanity and
No like liking
Shod
I think that generally typically that doesn't include
Also the weak should die
Look
I think it's
A bad thing
Giant herons have started eating human than pulling them out of their office
There's a better adapted
I will say that
The humans who survive are going to be a lot stronger fighting those herons in about a hundred years if not
The herons have shown that they are the ones
Souderton B plan as you probably know
Kill everyone
Right I mean
Sort of well not every
Maybe it's
Call the stock market
Collapse once everybody
You got it
I don't know they're going to kill everybody clap
During everybody paid
And killed probably
Kelly Brook
Actually get us in a position
Address for under attack by we must address for in a war
Intuit
Going further I'm really excited about this I told you
That we're going to have a lot of products coming out
A lot
Process of selling my house
Even more products
Does the problem Schroeder's house shows up again
Who knows we're on year 4 of house watch also not entirely sure how selling your house resolved
Supply chain issues if I sell my house I can bribe
Truck driver gas
To bypass
From like
We're all going to die can talk
Exciting new product
Fun 4 years ago
Look we're all about to die
Look forward to my new product
It's coming up so crass inoffensive
Eso Just
Boring and
Normal brows
Yeah so
You can still come
Consume before you die capitalism will be here for you
You got to get right with God
I'm really close to God I've gotten right
Never been closer to
I'm not some goody-two-shoes up here on some high horse. No released
Fake preachers
This is good versus evil
Millions of supporters in u.s.
Research the movie had a hit movie hail Satan
Hit movie
Adopt
French Revolution 2.0
Came out said we sacrifice babies when we killed
So did the UN
Cool put that it whip
I need it
I do I didn't see it
You didn't see it
Know if you don't have any proof
How could you say something like that
I don't I don't know it
Troubling
Also hit movie
I'm Blown Away by the movie
That's just like having prestigious doctor
You can't just have a under-the-radar
Indie film
Movie
Of Satan
It's got to be f****** Billboard charts
And anything that Alex has been into the huge into
Scanner Darkly was one of the biggest box office manager
Steps are God's real
And you got a
Stand up cuz you don't want to be yellow you want to be golden or silencer Goldwater quotes
Father quote
Hero
God is real
This is a test
You better well stand up
I'll tell you what I'm going to do to you
Nothing of God God is going to push you into The Phantom Zone with the 5th
Dishonorable
People that are into betrayal and manipulation because there we
Power from indominus world
Sold out
Weather 15 minutes of power
Nothing
The Phantom Zone of course it be parallel Dimension from Superman comics where folks
Getting prison
Real fun how Alex relates to his holy concept
Next thing you know he's going to be on the show referring to Heaven is Xavier school for gifted youngsters
Honestly I really like the moment I heard that I would immediately was transported really real
Realizing like how much
Power hell had over me as a child
And if
1.8
Any point
Time the pastor just been like
Hell is the apps
Essence of God and if you don't get right with God he will send you to the Phantom Zone
All of my fears would disappear not be like
You're right hell is he
Exactly as stupid as the Phantom you're going to hang out with General Zod
Job
Ultimately this show is about
If you want to pretend he knows anything about the news topics he's covering you're making no f******
Can fool out of yourself
This is about
Talking about this
Self mythologize at work
I've been around there real Nazis
Garden-variety pops
I hate garden-variety about sickness
I've been there
When the rich people the billionaire
To watch a ticket sacrifice
Long-term
Omnipresent
What
Does have
Computer
Direct the lines in the future
Matter where I went or what I did
When I was young
I was going to end up
God
And thank God I did but let's take a moment really let that soak in
When Joe Rogan has Alex Jones
Seriously
What he's doing is a validating and tacitly condoning this person who claims on are that Satan must have been trying to recruit in his
School life
Because Satan can see the future
And he knew that eventually Alex would be important
Infer God's plans for the site it's like the battle
Now unfortunately for Satan
Not have long-term
Any presidents true
Power set deal
Rule over the Phantom
And if you managed to say his name backwards
That's my power
And my limitation is never being able to catch up Alex doesn't say stuff like that on Joe Rogan show beak
Because it would turn off the broader audio
People would laugh at him having seen him for what he really is
As a raving idiot
This kind of talk is for Alex's show because it's
We're pretty safe assumption that anyone is going to make it 45 minutes into this s***
They're already fairly accurate
Essentially is recruiting an army of idiots who will never listen to his show but who are willing to post
Snarky b******* about how like
Actually Alex Jones is more right
Did they use wrong often
Super worried about government corruption
These f****** Rubes provide Alex and Infowars the tons of Free Press and make it so the message
You know we'll get out to a wider audience
The odds of sucking in people who will resume with the idea of fighting the literal devil
Will increase and those people will get sucked into Alex's Revenue stream
Nothing really else to say but
Shame on you Joe Rogan how dare you
Yeah here you know
You have every reason to know
That the show that your friend does
That you give support to
Is this
He talks about the devil
Trying to recruit him and his entire life
Because the devil can see the future bright and he knew that Alex would be important
The gods battle planet
That's f***** up
Don't forget to treat him like he's a guy who's read documents
How dare you
Anyway Alex
Enjoyed
Enjoyed the wrong word
He's experience
Some of the energy of Satan
Right
Yeah he's experienced some of the satanic energy
I'm so
Annoyed
I mean think about think about
Listening to
Alexei
What Satan can and cannot do
Like
What are you doing with a deity at all
At all
At all if you're going to claim that you can talk
To God and God told you that Satan
Can only do certain things and you know it and that you are allowed to tell everybody
Just give up on God just just just go to the books
Float
But it can't fly
What are we doing what are we f****** doing here just give up
Just give up and read your mind but he can't implant thoughts
Who's your mom
What
What what else
Cuz he's actually felt
Power of sage
I thought it was cuz he read the dark
Phoenix storyline
He probably had this real
Enforce
And I got to have sex with it
Piss God off
And moved himself further from God
Trying to get his pond
Do bad things to
Zombie
Again I do seriously wonder what Rogan takes about having a giant world
Play making it
Acceptable an edgy
To say things like Alex's right about a lot of stuff
I thought hope he feels like
Like a big pile of s***
Hey and while we're at it I'm going to toss Tim building in there to Figueroa
Piece of s***
Yeah I don't know I don't know him personally but he certainly yeah
Also I would ask Alex what he had to do
To feel that satanic energy for like a minute
If the Satanist get this
From killing kids did he like kill a kid
Or did he get a mini rush from that time he killed his dog
Inquiring-minds-want-to-know also what does
Does Satan give you the rush
And if so why does Satan make
So short is it like is it like a Reagan and trying to get people to Dick's
I think it must be
Could be
Oh yeah
They sound similar
Done
Truth
And things that kind of rhyme
If it's a slant rhyme it's
What's my fourth at
Barry Goldwater said
So goes out to
Do things
Wherever he goes
Burnout
Holyshit
Temporary
Nope cuz I'm depressed until temporary that doesn't
I don't even know what that means
It means that there's
The temporary end
If you have temporary presents for a while
And then you also have presents at the other times right
Also temporary omnipresence does not imply or it doesn't it doesn't require
That when you're not omnipresent you are not
I mean if you are omnipresent
You can always
Infinite Space
I'm in space and time are the exact same thing
Sacrilege
FaceTime
I don't really care to tell me what the devil
I need to really nail down what the. I want a stat sheet for the devil
I would be in
YouTube mad as well
Is buff star
He's like a little bit of magic
Like a gigantosaurus
Absolutely there's no way you can talk to them
So anyway here's a story about Alex saying alright
Go to the Capitol
On a separate issue what's this it's a pro-life saying it was all these Democrat
Booties women
Abortion law pro-life
Like Bigfoot
And then all the sudden and I walk into the hallway and the women are going like this
Video
Ran into the other hot daughters whatever when I was young
They were all in control
So when you look at the British royal family
Those are devil worshippers
Who's come out
Them
Their selfishness
The Rothschilds The Rockefellers all of their selfishness
I don't want your old baby
What's going on in really horrified of course
That makes sense
You're not worried about this
Ghetto
Guillotines
About your soul
And you need
They found the clips
That was it that was a repulsive display on his part
Interesting Lee he does get to the end he says he has one of the
Eclipse
And I've only
Seeing him threaten
Play View
As one clip
Someone clearly f****** with
The protesters telling him that he's evil and then he needs to repent
An abortion of course
This is dr. Robert Santella Planning Center in San Diego
4017 santello lost his medical license
Partially due to claims that he quote
Over prescribe narcotics 26 patient sandbox
In the portion on another page
However another part of
The Judgment by the medical board of California was that he engaged in unprofessional conduct
Based on his behavior in that video
The protester who confronted
Santella claimed that he was acting hyper aggressively
And threatening him with a pair of scissors
Whatever the case
Quote in a brief phone conversation Santella told NBC 7 invest
Navigate he lost his composure that day and he regrets his behave
As it turns out it was a doctor with a couple of reprimands and his past
85 year probation stretch in the mid-80s
Her quote gross negligence
Stanton carpet
Overall it seems like he was kind of a s*******
Exactly the sort of doctor you might expect the f***
The protester by pretending to be a demon
Instead of just leaving them alone
But what he wasn't wasn't
Actual
Demon
Answer this
This is something that I have these kind of what a demon
Maybe that's
Just like how raptors go around with
The Jurassic Park
Yeah demons go around making
Idaho.
I don't know
I was I was shocked
I was talked about this all the time and he very rarely plays any specific
And this is one specific that
Do you like this is a flying.
This is a faint this is
Borderline
Quote unquote
Famous yeah
High-profile video
Of this doctor he got in trouble
I mean granted he also was overprescribing
Narcotics
But they're still consequences for his actions in that video
That's still part of what he was reprimanded
4 +
It's interesting to me that there was one side that has consequences
And there's one that does not
88 and almost seems like when there's consequences
Does her negative behavior people
Put to learn a lot
But you thought you'd think
You know what one thing there's no consequences for
Alex not getting to the news
I'm going to try to know if I can do this
Satan
Alright
Well I mean
I like that moment of Crisis that he had
Clearly very authentically
Momento
I cannot get all this no I can't do it I'm going to expose it all album everyday
Lord give me some
Talk about this intercept articles
All right I will be lost
Okay well we'll get to that eventually
To get to First
Are there is one thing that's really important
I am so busy not complaining this is true
But I have not tried
A new ad
For a week
And we were supposed to launch it last week but
5 minutes
Plug
Honoring the network brakes
Operation
And so
You can get a
Product
The same
Time so I don't have to do any work off air
Or you
Why what years ago
I was talking to a lot of the top developers out their high-end supplements
Just staggering
Staggeringly lazy
Lorde
Lord give me strength
Come back from the break
Exposes everything Lord
Leprechaun commercial on air
Because
Want to stay past 5
This is a no-man's-land some Stations don't carry this water reveal the truth it's station
Carrier
I don't want to
I want to do work
Later
Stay past 5
So he talks about this product for a bit
Unfortunately
Some stray names of things in this
The ad read that he was unprepared for
Botanical name
Is flavored 4S Mini
Support yourself looking forward
Now
Exclusive
Launch price before it's gone
Flip the switch
Supercharged
I'll just be honest but y'all have to recut this and later by 1
Read out that almost took off today I'm not complaining
I just
Alex
This is just so horrible
Do you think it's a
Optimistic
Deposit
This is just G
Seems like it seems like a sketchy
You and I wrote yeah
Trying to do an ad
He doesn't have to do it later
A fuc
What's up you can't read the copy
I would have to redo this I just wasted ever
It's just it's just unreal
Yeah
It really doesn't work if it doesn't seem like a
I mean there's no way that they brought
Cats that
And then you stop for a second
That was live
Is all there
You know what
What sucks
About being me
Is
I think that's
The funniest thick sort of thing I could
Possibly imagine
Cuz it's not trying to be funny not pay those in it
You don't feel that bad cuz he's a monster every bit of it is both in character and 100% in
Possible to believe
You couldn't believe it
I love it
Is in blank do you know the difference
Flavors of this show already just as one episode
They're all over the place
Screaming about the f****** devil and his power set
Refusing to actually cover this intercept article that proves
Custom order to bio-weapon
Him been failing to do it ad reads heater lazy-ass can go home and get drunk I just can't I mean can you imagine.
Dan Rather just all the sudden being like hey I got to cut this Lifeline commercial
And I don't have the time for it after the show my little kids playing at a baseball game
So real quick
Lifeline have you fallen down or something so I'm going to say Eliza dirty laundry
I don't think I'm ready to do this commercial right now to take the next week off
No I'm just going to go talk to my
What
He sounds like maybe he's got covid again
I'm coughing pretty heavily on my chest
Yeah I should take the
I should really
Get over this
If you will
So instead of actually covering
The Intercept story
You'll notice the way that he does this
Cuz if you look at the intercept story it's based on two documents
That they
Have posted in their entirety
Available
That they got the report
Instead of covering the
Some people might cover the intercept
And I think that would be a way to go about
Instead
Alex covers
The American Journal coverage of
The intercept
Story The Boy Like Me
Oia Freedom formation
Confirmed fauci
Funded construction of chimera
Coronavirus is that was the headline for American
Journal today
So that's the American Journal
Coverage
Study
He he he reads this and then there's a bit from The Intercept article that he
He's reading
And it's just not enough for him
It's not salacious and I have a lot of insinuation that is inappropriate I believe
At no point does it claim that the royal family has
F*** the child
So it is kind of dry
So Alex's is
It's going through like looking
Through the actual
Text of The Intercept article
Bored
Information
Intercept is making the full document
To the public
Real journalist
Right here
Oh I
A release
Fauci funded Coronavirus
A quote
Chimeric coronavirus is
Material
Aaron here we know this place
Augusta zerohedge coverage of the intercept article
Because it's a he needs the filter of some other s*** head
Coming up with the angle for him or else like he doesn't know what he's doing
He has no context for the story he hasn't read
Any of these documents he hasn't read
Probably even The Intercept article
Please read the American Journal headline and
Excited
Pretty good I mean you can
Jesus Lizard thing running surface of the water
And you can hear how slow it is
C-cold raids
So you know
So you're like
I can see you maybe
Maybe spending 3 hours trying to
To finish the intercept
SEPTA article
If that's your research level
If your ability to
Then they
Okay
The Intercept articles not that long
Maybe 1,000
Maybe maybe
Are pretty long
I would not fault
Sorry I made it through about 50 page
And I was like what am I
I didn't write this
It's Grant and I don't need a considerably more but
At the same time
I think it would be silly to demand
Someone who is not
Super literate in those
230 you didn't read all of it
Whatsoever
That's why Paul Paul Joseph Watson has been such an important
Piece of his workflow for so long
Paul comes up with these framing
For him to get the article or like annadanam Salazar at these people do do the writing for Alex
They get the story they posted on Infowars
In his voice
End in the way that he can Hughes get the Angle Inlet me embellish on top of it out but I can't
Self generate a good angle cuz I'm a moron generate an angle from
The Intercept Artica
That's not even enough for him he's so lazy
You need that be stopped in there
And zerohedge does that
American Eagle
So anyway Alex cold reads a bit of the screenshot that Cindy Zero Hedge article
From the other Grant
The one that started in June
Prescient
If you will
Destructive viruses
And
Redelivered full-length
Recombinant SARS covid V
From the Silko sequence all three stars
Movies full-length
Isolate
Viruses
In vitro that's in test tubes
E6 cells
Shells
Shiver
Ace2
Civet
246 196
Thesaurus covid reverse genetics
System 722 generator
This is
Is like
What is he saying
I don't know I don't know I did nothing out of this other than knowing that
He can't read
Yeah
Straight up not being able to read
Grant is a little bit more complicated
Grainger
Did describe this to me it again it's
It's kind of the same thing
Taking viruses that are found in the wild
From sampling
And putting them in
A laboratory setting
Where you can see if they can in fact
Sal's
With a stew
Recite
It's
It's more complicated but it's very similar
In terms of goal and scope
And do some of the language used sounds like
Okay Mary
Oh that sounds like
Still this isn't Gano function research
This is not at all but Alex
Is pretending that it is
Has nothing to do with like
Fauci being like
I'll order this one
Ridiculous
That was another thing that I learned
Raptor reading like that
The pages of the grant proposal is just reading that language is going like
Even if I read all of this
It is not my area of under
Standing
Reading all of this information is not going to help me
Be whatsoever just like calling somebody who is not a health Ranger is going to be the best way to figure out how the Grinch
Incredibly helpful
Southside
Confirmed
In my consult was
How
Not
A lot of money every time people
Liquid Alex been like all they're killing people for 60g it's like
They wouldn't beat you wouldn't be able to get
These people to like
Design
A world-destroying bio-weapon
Free
$600,000
Kind of silly telling me that they wouldn't spend at least a billion on a world ended virus
Let me know. I feel games could spend a billion tomorrow until everybody why would they do it
Cheap places the same thing as those fake antifa contract to like
There wouldn't be a grant
For this
If someone works out
Cooking up a
Spell supervisor weapon
It kind of imagined maybe they would
Wouldn't leave a paper tree
Anyway
Alberto's
Bombshell staff
Put on screen
Body
The show headline today
Just think about what a bombshell
That is
Maybe Riddler
Freedom of Information Act. Confirm
Galaxy created covid-19
Team chimera
Bio weapon
And lied to Congress
This is an emergency broadcast
It's probably going to need to
Retract that
How is it that you can call your own headline of bombshell
F******
But you'll get the headline I mailed out of the made-up information that I made
Also because it's really fun
In that first
528 pages long
How many times do you think I'll choose name is in it
Zero so close
So outside of cold reading and yelling a little bit
Alex does not cover these documents
At all
Of course not there's no wrestling with what the actual
Research they were doing was actually
I thought it hyper disappointing
Because I think mostly what do you think could be rebutted
Just by saying
Nope
Yep I fell really pissed off
But I tried
Yeah
Yeah that is that's a massive
Massive disappointment
There's just nothing to hang your hat on man there's no there's no juice
Even The Intercept was trying to be
Insinuated because probably is just so f****** boring I'm not I'm not sure if
You know you could
Reply emotive to them I have no idea what led that coverage to be what it was
It's got a thing like we got
Document
Yeah we might as well put something
Sing out about it
Could see another angle of it to being like well if we have these documents that we got through our foia lawsuit
And we don't report on them
People will think we're covering something up
I could see all kinds
Different thought processes he's going it but I just still
Take another path
Yeah
You know what's bad news though
Headliner
Will that do it would be
It's not true that
Got the bad news is that everybody's going to
Mismatch
Last year was a hoe
Last year was fear-mongering
This year from Indy up with the Delta Marriott
He's super infested there's no way to hide it no way to get away with
If you haven't already had, before you're going to get it
You better
Have your vitamins and minerals in your water in your sunshine
Early treatment
We going to the hospital
My head is security I had security guy at a really good friends was in great shape
Amanda's use a nurse
North Austin
That's a bummer
If it is life-in-death Alex
Then you are responsible for the deaths
Quite a few
Yeah and I mean this
This blase everyone
When's going to get it
Attitude
Is not something that he's had
A long. Of time
And that attitude
If he had that attitude
During some of the other stages of his coverage
That's a problem
Who's the real problem
Anyways a liar and day-to-day doesn't actually believe any
You saying so who gives a
You want some more bad news
Usher
I'm not busy
Oz is a fraud
Okay rainforest Ultra or Ultra
Alright how's this supply chain
Add device oldest house so it's fine
But the product
Might be too strong
I said I want to make something even stronger super clean
What is the best strongest formula out there
Kill people
Tell me how
They're quite
Of the product total
Twice as strong
Charles
Twice as much
And twice as strong as four times
It may be too strong for some people
The first time it's a few drops
It's got
Everything in it
Guarana seed
Oh boy
Okay
Twice as strong
And you take a
Fifth Third of it
Aren't you only taking two thirds of your regular about
Twice as strong and there's
Double the amount
So if you take a third of it
Actually
What were 3rd
4:30
Only take a little bit
Boricua
So he's like really had trouble with that
Play energy
Drinks of Cortana
Alright what's the
All right product team let's get together
I really want to
People up with this s***
What do we do
Let's double it
Yeah
If he was going
Going through this product read about house
Maybe it's too strong
To f***
I had a realization
Mike down for this cuz you may have the same realization
Hide
Don't use this product it'll turn all your clothes White
Please don't you tell you why that's so powerful
Green tea leaves you tell you about that
Antioxidant
Levels
Potassium magnesium
Content
That has been the focus of both ancient and modern fascination with science
Ashwagandha root
3000 years
4 inch mini beneficial properties
That's the line that Alex f***** up in the read that he did earlier
He's doing it again he's not saying it at this time
What a f****** a****** I love it I hate him so much
It's
It's the only way that comedy could be hiding
Next step in the game it really is trying to do the same.
5 minutes after he gets off air
Oh my God
I I think
I think he's trying
How to kill me
He's trying to see if he can make one person so angry that person
Explodes
That is all that I can
Process
Through all of this
The part of a blood pressure medication trial
He's really good at
I love you
I loved it so f****** great
Pretty obvious to your product
It's just that you might as well just say we crammed a bunch of s*** in there
We put out if we put all this crap in a blender and turned it into a pill
That's how little we care about what it is we do as somebody who listen
Do a lot of Alex's show
Relish those moments
Ashwagandha root is 548
Chaga mushroom
You're right that is fun
So look
Alex has not done his job
We're pretty clear on this
He struggled and then he swear to God that he was going to reveal it all and
Tell them every
And then he pried
Twice to record a
New commercials they didn't have to do it later
4 hour left of the show Ono
Owen Shroyer
But I definitely
Use yes right now
Emergency reporting
Michelle today
Everything breaking right now is totally insane
It came out today
Perception of God
F*** off
Where fauci is in hundreds of pages of documents we showed earlier
I want all these viruses to buy you a chimera Force for a new SARS virus
Yes sir Alex is going to need to take an hour of o in the show because he hasn't covered this news that he has
Rambled about
He doesn't know
How to cover this
So he can't do it
What no
If he cannot
It's a fascinating
Thing where he's unable to do it
But he's calling out that he hasn't done it
But he has done it as well as he ever covers any other news story witches
Say a headline from zero Edge and then yellow B
I think I think what's going on
Is the intercept
Appears to have way more credibility than all of his other
Dumb dumb s*** yes right
So he knows that he's got to talk about this because it's a big
For his b*******
It's as close to a get as he's going to be
And then
He thought well just do it like
I do my other regular
So we didn't really do any prep
Britney thought he could do
Just Spin A Yarn out of it however my
What you want
And then because it's actual
Did journalism
It's written very drily with information and he doesn't really know how to deal with that are too high
Right because
Like when
Zero Hedge or Infowars is reporting that fauci
She created a bio-weapon
Or whatever
It doesn't really
Rise any alarms when nothing happened right
Who treats them as if they're actual journalism reporting
Used to like
Oh wow another cover-up
Or whatever
The Intercept is
At least
An outlet
Get something
And they've done actual cover-ups
Stories where you been like holyshit has been
Attached to someone
Important pieces of Journalism
And the stakes are really high for Alex
Pretend
That The Intercept is reporting
Documents that prove that fauci created a bioweapon out of like
Uptown menu the cool little bit of this Coronavirus
Who were Liberty
Some mustard you know what it is it's almost like a canker sore you know like
He keeps he doesn't know how to do it
He doesn't feel like he can do it
But he can't leave it alone
Just keeps tapping it and going like maybe if maybe I've got it in this time and maybe I'll get her shot
And then every
Every time it just looks like he's spending his wheels like an
And what I mean by the states
Being too high like there's no explanation for why if that is the case nothingness have
Because
Snowden
Yeah
Cuz everybody
King insane
What if your Alex you can't really explain like
This isn't
Infowars
Guys this is real busy these people are real
These people do like what I would do but sometimes it's real
I imagine I'm doing what the intercept
Was doing
Snow
The intercept
Friday weather report
What they have
But I will say
To their credit
They wouldn't do that
So we've got a very special guest I really wanted to get on
She really helped expose hydroxychloroquine
One-hundred-percent Freeman train
Yesterday
NY Newsday
Indian
What
Stella Immanuel
MD is the successful physician with an active practice in Houston as well as the founder of
Power Ministries in Cheney
So Stella Immanuel is one of the doctors who was Oprah molding hydroxychloroquine as part of their big push last year by that
Mysterious group America
Cuz Frontline doctors
Almost immediately after she appeared in a video endorsing hydroxychloroquine people began looking into who this doctor was
Nevada gold mines
In an article in The Daily Beast will summer reported quote
She is often claimed that gynecological Pro problems like system endometriosis are inside caused by people
Will having sex in their dreams
With demons and witch
So suck
What would that be
Incubus succubus
It may well seven witches
From the article quotes
According to Immanuel people can tell if they've taken a demonic
Spirit husband or Spirit wife
If they have a sex dream about someone they know or a celebrity
Wake up aroused
Stop getting along with their real-world spouse lose money or generally experience
Any hardship
Ultimately they could be having a dream sex with a human witch instead of a demon
Deposits
She has some ideas
I mean I'm glad that you posited that as opposed to
Claimed it
That's it that I mean she is asking a good
Question article
She alleges alien DNA is currently used in medical treatment
Scientist
They're cooking up a vaccine to prevent people from being
And despite appearing in Washington DC to Lobby Congress on Monday
She is said that the government is run in part not by humans but by reptilian
Other
Aliens
Okay so here's why I
I should be in government
Because I want to ride a log that's just like the you got to go
Where it's like if you're if you're this
You know what live your life that's fine
But you got
We had a pretty good balance going for a while
Black people that go to Roswell and
Just go leave us alone after Facebook
Took down videos of her speech
Trumed Frontline doctor Rallis he replied quotes
Hello Facebook put back my profile page and videos up over York
Computers will start crashing till you do
You are not bigger than God I promise you if my page is not backup Facebook will be down in Jesus name
Wow I did not know she
You could call upon the power of Jesus to take down one of her is that her powers yet
In addition to all this nonsense she's claimed that scientist to found a gene that makes people religious
And they're trying to find a vaccine against it
She seems to think that magic eight ball toys are in the farias bottom
Make children witches
And she is super
Super anti-lgbt
Atq
She's quote
Accused gay Americans
Practicing quote homosexual terrorism
In the same sermon she praised the father's decision not to love his transgender son
After a gender
Stella Immanuel is not a serious person and has a ton of
Very seriously f***** up beliefs
A year ago she had a video that went viral so Alex is going to bend over
See if you can squeeze any of that attention
He can get out of her cool this is a sad book
Looking for both of them not good
Not good
Associate to please don't like demon
Insects and stuff like that and I mean but that's every time I've ever had Morningwood I've known that I was
Sleeping with a demon in my dream
And that's why I am such a happy person
Has she ever wreck
Recognize that
Sleeping with demons in your dreams brings happiness
Demons are freely
Their conversation is not to be believed and one of the things
The reasons today
Demodex
Episode unacceptable
There is one thing that comes up that's like well maybe this explains something
I'm putting the genomes of dead babies
Bizarre cells never Diana's isn't satanic I don't know what it is
Children
I don't know what
Is it possible that this whole time the issues that Alex's.
But satanic
Just means that some
Things bad
Do you think that
Maybe he has like
That level Lowe's
That level of just like
Childish morality
You're just leaving
Like not understanding terms
Yeah
Asking me whether he
He understands work
I think we both know the answer to that
I lack the words to describe this be
Pacific
Lack of understanding of words
Yes
I mean cuz childish doesn't describe it now could ask
The four-year-old if satanic means bad in a four-year-old would say
Why would we need the word satanic if it's just a longer version of Bad
Yeah there's other
Other characters in other other
2 satanic
Yep anyway
This interview is out of
Out there man
To something else
This is dependent
Trying to make money
It's
Genesis 6
Einstein Hospital
Humanity
I'm creating a new being might they say that humans are obsolete
What happened the days of Noah
Yes
Wow
Okay
So
Class Schwab
And all these people
Gates fauci all them together
They're having these
Who's covid pandemic
In order to
Forget the vaccines at the people with
Will turn them into a
Completely new thing not human anymore
Which is
I guess going to cause a stock market
Crash
The collapse of the dollar or something
I don't know anymore but look
This happened back when Noah was for
That was my conclusion as well
Highways are specifically thinking man
History repeats
It's out this is exactly what
When did Noah
As I was
Thinking about
The stock market collapsing
I was like man
Noah's going to need
Two of every currency with a as the world is Left Behind do we have any reports of any like
Cryptocurrency billionaires trying to build a giant
Boat
Cuz if so
Let's make him serious
I have another question
How do we reconcile viruses with the Noah story
You know what I'm saying
We don't
Farpoint story is really more about there being giant that's
Didn't you know that
Fowling
Genesis 6
But we also
Double really wanted to
By the way all the other ancient cultures have this in their in their text
And all the other ancient culture
Psychotic
So apparently were talking Nephilim here
We're talkin about
The Giants in like
Show Angels Came Down at sex
Human women that created hybrids
That's why she had a flood
Oh boy so weird
We're doing that again
Apparently
I I mean yeah you know
You know I
Fine
With people believe I don't think you are God
This is exactly like you telling me that
Zeus really had sex with people
As a swan
Yeah and it's like
No
No he didn't
Nope
I feel like
I feel like you
True
You know you might be shooting your shot a little bit too early cuz this is just the beginning of the interview
No
Nose
Strong no slapping
In the face swell
Sounds to me like you're a naysayer
I'm a super huge naysayer
You telling me that people got off of ships and interbred with humans sacrificed and that's
It's all God's plan
Stella Immanuel
But pray for you
To be quiet no
See what I'm saying
Any boys that wants to jump Island
Name of Jesus
Silence
Antifa
I need to pay that.
Amen to that.
I do I do enjoy the combination of Amen to that and Doc
So now you're going to have to be quiet
Once again degrades at rivermill annoys making the
Jerk-off motion
Yeah so we come back from break
We get an interesting Theory presented
And that seems to be that there are inhuman vampires that walk among us
But appear to be human
Come on Irene
Kathy told me that forever ago
What is going on right now Alexander we have
I'm just going to stay on somebody wake up on GFS
Which people were dealing with
Human beings
We are dealing with
Evil seat in the land
Human
Hoverboard
So we got an evil seed in the land
Another vampire
Sure it's a little bit after this
Astellas Skype goes out
Alex takes this opportunity to
Try and be ration
Who did God take her Skype out is retribution for Facebook not putting her page back
Someone probably hacked
In the back end
Taylor Swift
Mingle
Skype Roku
I think you need to hear this phone
The voice of reason
There'd even is that how you
Interpret right I know this might sound a little bit out there that there is any human vampires walking around
But let me
Credibly
And responsibly discuss this their demon
Possessed
Obviously I agree with you
Miss that disagrees with me right and they are working for the devil
About what you're saying
That might seem a little out there for some people
These people are just demon-possessed come on
You really have to recognize that what's going on is there's an interview where they conservative
Rational position The Voice
Open Center is maybe they're just demon-possessed
It's just suck we've gone so far
Rich has gone so far
Eastman's
Hour on this interview instead of covering the intercept
That's right I completely forgot
I didn't try and cut it add in the middle of neck is well
Excuse me I'm sorry doc
This is our favorite new
Formula too strong for demon
So the Skype is out Alex's trying to reframe the conversation a little bit
But Stella stays on point
She has a point
That you wants to make
And is not going to be
Or are you saying that it is a spiritual
Come out and say abortion is our ritual
Do you want to kill babies
Let me ask you this why do you think they're revealing themselves right now
Alex you don't understand
They are not human beings this is not station
So we have not human
Yep that are walking around
How to keep appealing to bib Bible verses
Is it don't seem too
Make her point
It is really funny cuz Alex can't argue again
Cancel Bible whenever people are making
You're using your own power against you you can't make up quotes from the Bible I make up quotes from the Bible
Otherwise I can't make them up anymore
This is this was a little bit
Tough to understand exactly the point
That was being
Made
No
Complicated
Xan
The grant.
Quite frankly
Do to get to the bottom of
As it turns out
Stella believes essentially
The people are being cloned
And then these clones
Being taken over by the devil or something
It's a little bit convoluted
But it'll become more clear as we go along
Tell you guys
Worried about
Who sing that
Images onto the base
You people like gif
You made them live forever
Die
Themself
Microsoft has right here
Common ground
Frontier
So now the global is still being told by the devil
Right that they're going to make this clone
That'll be immortal
Download the brain into it
Alex I was like alright
And these clothes are not human
My phones are not human vampire
I just don't
I don't like
Listening to all of that and actually
Hearing in my brain Alex go
I got a handhold here
I can jump on this weekend
A little glimmer of
F****** light at the end of the tunnel is like let's roll baby
Really pathetic
Phantom Zone
It's a demonic
Why you're so blood test
What is living in this preacher
We don't even know what else
Evil
I know that's definitely the future plan that's how I interpret Revelation as well definitely wow
That's exactly how I interpreted revelation
Yep The Book of Revelations dangerous thought process that she's
Advancing
Alex is agreeing with
Is that right
There's really no way to definitively know if let's say Bill Gates
Is a human
Or if he's a clone that's
It's been taken over by a demon
I didn't really even human and if he's not human I mean he doesn't really
Amorites
And you know what
There's really no way to tell about
Anybody
I think there is a way to tell
Advantage there
Showing signs of demons
Well
Demon real
Well I think
The only person who could possibly tell me exactly
Who is the Satan
Nesting who is a demon
Is somebody
He was so confident and who's willing to pray for me to just listen to her have somebody who has discerned
I think I think I'm any different people with
Discernment will have different conclusions
And yet somehow they'll all look like they care about
My town for this
Is it going to really piss you off
Stella discusses how she had a vision
No
All of these people have something
Very specific in common
People
Ministry
Oh yes
But really
In the Bible the Bible talks about
The problem is
Right now
Genetically modified human being
Zodiac loans
Containers
Intermountain looking fontanez
Watch a movie called The late because when they gave me this bitching
Advanced Eyecare in the movie theater
Always
It's always a movie always a movie
Exactly like iMovie
Every single
It's so consistent
These people who have these conspiratorial views
And
Bizarre theories that are
Distinct from reality ultimately they just can't tell the difference
It does seem like that is a very
Consistent
Feature
Thinking that just like a movie 18 ability to grasp
Sort of themes inability to grasp
Metaphor
Symbolism
That kind of stuff is
Is it really
Does
I'm becoming more and more convinced
Stated that kind of concrete thinking
He's kind of
It like not
Not indicative where are diagnostic of
Having
Kind of
Worldview
It's something
Is shared
Between a lot of folks
In what would appear to be separate
Branches of
Yeah
Conspiracy you know I mean we've talked a lot about like
Ways to avoid search
Certain things and
And for me I think there's a really easy balance
Between free speech
And kind of controlling
This
Angela
Propaganda
And I think it's so simple really and it's just like
You can't
Call other people not here
Like I feel like that's so simple any
Isn't it at the heart of literally every genocide
The propaganda almost always begins with dividing people into who is real
And who's not
Who counts and who doesn't
Who's that human being and who's in human form
Subhuman werbelow human and the Only Rule was you just cannot go
On the radio or on TV
And say
And claimed that these people are not
Human
Yeah water a lot of the justice
Suffocation
Massive violent campaign
Have been predicated on the idea
Of people being less than human
Various groups for whatever reason
Yeah it I mean I don't I don't know if
That's the Only Rule I would have but I certainly would have that as a rule
It just really does and it what I like I'm sure I've called somebody
Inhuman worser something along those lines behavior is that
There is a
But even then I am totally willing to change my communication style because I feel like
100% volume
Instances where you have behaved that way I'm sure you'd be willing to apologize for
Anyway
Look globalist
Think of brains are going to be redownload it
The body is
Did the trick
What you doing
If you die
Demonic spirits
Windows
Demonic spirits inside them
The new blood
If demons can possess the spirit
Possess a body that hasn't been cloned
Why would they need to clone
The body secondary question
What's that what
Consent is necessary to make a club
There's no reason why human Bill Gates would need to be involved in the plan to make
Kill Bill Gaither make a clone pod people situation because
Do you have to get their consent
And even if you're tricking do you have to go along with the
The plan wear your promise
Your brain will go into a clown later with seams
Stupid
For someone to be like
Utrecht
The smartest
And most
Entrepreneurial mind
Yeah around
Just clone them after you
After they were dead and put a demon in
Yeah
I don't understand
This is really dumb think I think what's fascinating is that all of their Devil's arak
Exactly exactly to the
T as stupid
As they are
I mean I would be insulted
If I was
God because they
I think my photo is so dumb
What's the point of even having a large enemy if he
This stupid well I mean you know
Actually you know this wedding
But the example I was going to use
Brings up a very calm
Placated
I was going to say like you know the the Harlem Globetrotters playing against the washer
Generals cuz they like to
Should be fancy
The people who are the Washington generals have to be very talented
Really dude
What's funny to me is that
The God Satan Dynamic that they have created in their minds
Is exactly like pink
Pinky and the Brain
Snowboards what's going on
Do clones need blood
Show me plush
Yeah
This idea
Fairly expensive
And that is that like
A hospital administrators
Possibly
Clone
Themselves
And that's why people are dying in the hospitals of like covid and
And stuff and that's why they won't give people hydroxychloroquine and Ivermectin
Because they want people died in the hospital because they need blood
Something we need to realize that in the hospital
Beautiful and kill them
Let me say this
What what the f***
Hey listen that sounds pretty far out it sounds like it could get some people killed, so go for it
Possibly some Hospital
Traders are clones that if somebody doesn't give you Hydrochloric win that probably be
Because the CEO of the hospitals that closed and if it's a clone who wants your blood f*** it go kill him who gives a s***
Going to kill you and steal your
Jesus
Is Christ these people have no real clue how dangerous it's outrageous
Stella has made her points and
Alex
As a
Responsible engager in
The public discourse
Yeah conversation responsibility to probably end by saying
A lot of the stuff has been really dumb
Also dangerous
I hope they
By having this conversation by audience has been exposed to these ideas and knows that you're not someone to be taken seriously
Instead
He says this
Craziest sounds weather
She's pick
Catching up on this site
Louis.
In the future
Whether it's actually happening
How crazy this is
Damn
So
Either
You know things are crazier than we know and she's right
Or the holy spirit is giving her a vision of the future
And this is what
What's coming
That's not a good way to wrap up the interview
Irresponsible
Yep yep
But we're not done
I don't
See how that's f***
Kim Possible
That lady
Is nuts
What's that straight-up lunacy
Project Camelot
It's it's
Embarrassing I mean it's a problem is if exact
Ugliest stupidest stuff that you hear from like Joe Rogan or whatever
You just get Nephilim so you're like oh well Giants are involved so I can just write it off
If Joe Rogan just said
I took Ivermectin because this guy who believes in
F****** Nephilim told me it's a good idea we could all move the f*** on it would help
It'll be easier
Let me see this one thing
They could Elevate The Comedy of this episode
It's him doing that talk
He's not going to know that that
Alex Wassabi
No he has to get creative
Get mad about a random internet comment about an interview he did the table
Get the f***
Yesterday
Dr. McCullough
It was very powerful and Luke
86ed
You're the salon
It's been nine years and I'm done with
We still keep pushing the virus narrative
Anything he is
Muddying the Waters of Truth
Is changed
What has happened to him.
Car wrecks gunshot wounds
Delta
What hospital they were empty
Totally overwhelmed
Almost died my mom almost died
I bought it really was on my chest
Mostar office
That's had this
I do of my own observation what kind of fun
F****** denial has he been in about the
The spreading of this virus that he's been actively participate
His whole office had covid
His parents had covid
He said it multiple times
I guarantee
There's someone in this chain that's dead
There we just don't know about
Totally there's somebody in this
Cluster
Let's say this Hadley
Serious complication
Braum's there their irresponsible
Handling a
Yeah and also just for fun
He interviewed Joseph
Mercola the day before
Great Robert
I mean this is
That's just
I just so f***** up
Fiance
I mean I don't know it's definitely not something
Just about
Fairly recently
All these people who is
I mean that
That's just so f***** up
That's just so f***** up it's also really funny that he's so mad about this internet
I mean thirty-five-year-old Luke
Has a lot to say
Look
Some people on the internet who have
Usernames that I've no idea who they are
Think I've changed
Dick pics and 45 won't stop
Claiming that I'm not
The same person I used to be
So I'm going to have a
Real defense
Meltdown over it while I tell people all the s*** that I did that I received the consequences for
But I refuse to learn from
So that's one way to add
An extra layer of forests into the episode
I hate you don't know if you can handle this
Doctor why don't you why don't you lead us in prayer
Definition for a couple minutes
Yes thank you
People
Gloria
You're stupid
The universe
Send it
Poster in the name of
Cancel
She prays for a while
Close things out
A prayer
Send in the clowns
I just think that a lot over
The course of this episode has been a lot.
Disgusting
End
Refocus
Guess on
How proud Joe Rogan
When should be convincing his audience
That Alex is worthwhile things to say and that he's generally right about things
You know what sometimes he's wrong and when he's wrong he apologizes
Way more than these other people in the media
A Outburst but he comes to me we talk privately and he's he's a good guy nothing that he's ever
Merced has actually been that crazy know I sound crazy out there
Later on you see it happen and you know that it
It's true. I got to get his words out like when you see
Blood-drinking demon clones wandering Hospital hallways
If people didn't know that when they go to the hospital there's a good chance that a saint evil clone
Possessed by a demonic
Spirit trying to kill them
Well they might just be going to the hospital thinking that they're going to get medical care
I don't care who's on who's show and I don't care any of that stuff
A culture blah blah blah whatever the
I don't care about any of that nonsense but I do want
To be queer
That being that effective
And treating him as anything other
Gavin
A buffoon and a liar
And a dangerous
This person
Lend credibility that is undeserved to things like
What we've listened to on this show
Yeah I mean it's
And just the level of like
Look at all these people trying to kill you as they waded through the blood of people that they have been
Office
Like the whole f****** thing
Yeah and I
Reflecting a little bit on like
What are we doing
You know sometime
Listen to this stuff and I like what are we doing
Really worried that some people who listen to our shadow might have the idea that like
We could we have
Any kind of ability to like
Get Alex off a air or
Or
Yeah he'll the damage that he's caused yeah I don't believe that at all
And I am coming around to possibly
The things that we can do
Is present something
They can hopefully
Be a rebuttal
To the point
Of people who think
Did Alex
Yeah something
That's it
That's the best I can do
He's like abbv countervailing
Enforce
Against that that flood of
Actually Alex is right
On my Galaxy
Unlock Galaxy
Two claims that world leaders listen to him
I can
Guarantee to every one of our listeners
0 World list
World leaders listen to this podcast that's true with any power gives a s***
Okay couple of people who are verified on Twitter
Close reader
And it's not going to get more power
No
Just let it go we do what we
WhatsApp
Are we controlled by the devil
No I had huge breaking news
Oh no what was that did we run out of time
I look I prepared too much we can't get to it
That one has a extra sleep
We paid that's a good stack
We could have talked about that one with his
Gummy melatonin
We're not selling them
Talked all about
3racha I will say that I've gotten back into it a little bit I haven't had it in a long time
Absence come back to Vista
Warm
It was really getting
Old
Back then
Taking time away
Exactly like a like a fresh Breeze
Anyways we're done
I got lost in
Thoughts because
I do think
It's kind of funny that Stella was kind of praying for you to shut up
If only you had prayed for that
A long time ago
No I enjoy you not shut it off
Backyard
Rihanna on Facebook and Twitter and it's better is at Dollar General but until
Amigo I'm Leo MDX
It's Clark I'm Daryl run this
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color