Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Where's the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
Hardy Dam
What's up what's my future bright
But I know it's going to be bright is a couple people have brought to my attention that look
Flavor
I am
Plumped URI it okay that the polar
Plum
Situation
Cleaver was
So good
Caught me off-guard
I am so now I'm very excited
Do I get this world
But I've not seen it in stores I don't
Interested but I've heard rumor of it
The Badlands
I will try the public
I might if it's good
I might stalk up
I do like Plum flavor
Stuff anyway what do I do with your DNA
Today is the final of the United
States Open tennis Communications and development and the fight
Final is between Novak Djokovic and Medvedev
And if Djokovic wins which he almost certainly will he will have 21 Grand Slam majors
You say you will have completed the first calendar Grand Slam
It's like 1960s
Jimmy Connors and stuff
Any will have cemented himself
As the greatest tennis player
Of all time
Oh yeah yeah yeah I know a guy might throw his racket at him man the guy
Don't have many tennis reference
You got that one what would I know about him
Harry is very hairy man Andre Agassi
Bald
Okay good
Did you know who I didn't know that that's an interesting tennis fact about Andre
Welcome back to interesting tennis facts about Andre Agassi our new spin-off podcast
Jordan today get that we have an episode to go over
We're doing today is
I felt like
Sometimes you have to go off the beat
Empath it works sometimes we just
Need
Something
Elsinore lives in Alex Jones
Too much about him
Honestly
Oh yeah
Make the same point over and over again so here's an out-of-context drop
Talk from talk about today
Civilizations
Inside the planet
Planet
Often conducted
Boris bike
Throwing
Even neutron stars
Each other
And I'm so that face
Planetarium
Planetoids
Rocks m
All of this
And this is indeed
Impark how
Atlantis was song
Fascinator
Fascinating
This is great
Put somebody through a neutron star Earth and suck Atlanta
That's what
Part of it
Just ask
I like that there was something else the other part of it
Got2b
The longest time
People have been requesting that we get back to take
Wacky Wednesday break
It can't wait till Wednesday we're both
In that kind of mood where this is very much necessary
Here's the great news
There's another YouTube clone type website
Where is Kerry Cassidy from Project Camelot
Not behind a paywall
Things have been results
That is good news is good news
I kind of
Feel like the time that we've had away
Can like make us kind of
Forget that she's a
Like maybe better
We could have fun with it again
Sorbet where it's like if I need to remember the Tri-City credible anti-semite
I'll be there I got that
Wacky Wednesdays and I've discovered from
Trying to find other sources there's
Just nobody else who does
Does it Better
Warren G and Nate Dogg
Regulate
Yo
Real anti-regulation
Before we get to today's episode which is a update
About the state of the world from September 9th
Okay Isaac Carree put out
Is there a couple days back
I think if there's one thing that's important
The Alex is stressed
To me it's that diversity of opinion
It's something that should be cherish
That's true and that's why we need to bring in other voices
Find out what's going on with the political speaker what's going on
Maybe not about neutron stars being used as what
There's plenty of other things
The color
Gmail
How heavy do drugs
What stars are
Yeah but
Do you understand the technology that the Raptors have
I literally created a sinkhole in space-time
Atlanta
Walks all that's great just don't trust the trees with big limbs they're very shady thank you so much you're now policy want
You very much
Speckled Jim thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Why thank you
Gymboree
And now won't stop buying male vitality
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much that's going to make Rob Do's wife for real
Sore or the cat's wife
Jordan
Yes not just Herman Cain tax plan
Also the day of Gary's World update
And as as all of these episode start
We must say hello
Hi everyone I'm Kerry Cassidy from Project Camelot
I want to talk about my latest articles and also the latest
Video interviews I've been doing
Because there are a lot of
Questions out there and obviously now that you know
Everything is not
Super simple so we're living in very complex times
Discuss
It is
Is definitely worth discussing how complicated the times we're living in our
I have a question
Possible in her worldview for things to get more complicated than they already are
I mean we've got international space trees going on I feel like an end this is from her perspective
Yeah Earth is low priority
Invisible
There's
Fairly complicated complicated
You make a good point
I honestly don't know
Everything's a little rude that we discovered
8 News states of matter
It's complicated complicated
To play in the world right now is it the forces that are jockeying for control of the world
Sure you got the good guys who are the Trump
Why not exactly
It turns out that they're in negotiation
Taking a look
At my web
I've got an article there which
Which is basically talking about
Negotiation
Going on between
The Deep state
And the trunk
And the trunk group can really be thought of as
Q
As well as
Members of
Military Intelligence agencies Etc
Who are what we call wife
Score trying to change the system
From within secrets
Okay and
So that's how they started
We're entering a time in which they need
To infuriate
Become much more pub
But it is taking a long time.
A really long time
Almost like it's not going to happen almost Apple you got these white hat
But the whole big DM
People in the military whoever they may be
Although Steve pieczenik
Wide-ranging
Rodger Stones North Korean Powell sure at some weirdos who carry talks to that have funny ideas
Charlie freak
I don't know probably the Tiger game
Joe exotic
Yeah they're the good guys the white hats
And they're working
Against the Deep state but they're in negotiation
We're going to learn a little bit later what these negotiations are based
I want to know more about these negotiations real bad
We will learn a little bit more of that but we need to delineate here again
The state of play who are the team
Do you have the white hats
The cube
That's the good guys the Trump
Other political ideologies are
Just from the outset let's just say
The playing field
And understand that
Yes
As
Jordan Maxwell has always said
There are two
Two Wings to
To the bird
The Democrats and
Applicants they're both
Wings on the same bird
Another words
Be there is
The
What about what we think of as the Rino Republicans and the Democrats
Working together
Part of the deep state
And then there's
The Trump team
White hats
And they're part of
The people
The reflecting the will of the people
That's therein
Intention
That's their stated in
Contention
You think they do that
That's what
They are attempting to do
And
Trump is their leader
Four worlds
Super complicated that almost sounds like an over-simplification
So there's good and bad Ryan Trump is the leader of good
That doesn't seem very
And all the people in government
Are essentially working against the good. They're all collaborating together and get can't get anything done
That
Like somehow the Rhino like there are delineations in the Republican
There's a
Plethora of opinion as we know is the Republican rhinos and Weirdos that's basically what you've got
That's the only complicated Factor otherwise it's Republicans and Democrats are the same except for Trump speech
There's a couple people like a boat or a
Marjorie Taylor Greene
Yeah he's alright
Hawthorne School to see the wheelchair
In the GOP are okay
These are the teams
I'm thinking about going
To Riot
Obsessed Chicago
Mighty Bosstones
Are playing
And I am an old-school
Mighty Mighty Bosstones.
Of course and I will not apologize for it
Nobody's asking you
Someone is out there one of these people listening is wants me to apologize
Do apologize for the Boston refuse to never
But I also was like looking at the lineup in like on that same day Saturday
Who is playing
And I'd like to see them opening for Mighty Mighty Bosstones exit
I've liked the LPS
Stick damaging like the company flow know this s*** spree run the jewels
Motherfukers
And I was like a man
I'm old school
I'm I am I'm being a hipster about
My liking LP and that's not cool that's not
No
I mean Minneapolis address rap groups
I feel like you cannot also have nostalgia
Yeah but you have to let that kind of stuff
Because I was listening to like a father Factory in
Deep Space Nine mm back in the day
That I get to act all cool
The reason I bring this up is
Who carries been down with this s*** since way before Q course she's been hanging out with
But wait longer than you choose a cute hipster
What we know of
I've asked the white hats and I've been dealing with the white hat since long before
Hugh
Became public
And Trump was involved
You know my knowledge
The white hats had
A lot to do with
The group
That we're putting out the White House
Reports
And I was working with them
And
Interviewing Paladin
Interviewing T-man
And basically they were talking about
This group
That is called the white hats
It again
Is made up of people that are in
All aspects of the military
Retired military
Government officials
You name it
Around the world not just in the United States
And that they have
Created a network
Secret Network
Under the circumstances
That is
Perhaps not so secret among the
Ball
Because they get attacked
Terrifying
Yeah
Yeah that doesn't sound good at all
I think based on what a lot of
People in these
Conspiracy communities believe about shadoweave
National Group
Secret exit military folks or working
Kick 2 Chainz
The direction of the work of the thing I have with again we go
To their limitations on
Creativity
She's tossing out like
The government the military the cabals you name it for me
The you-name-it you doing out there yet
Here's what more terrifying
Alright
20 water treatment supervised
Vien
Think about a conspiracy of water treatment supervisor
All across
This f****** country
It would drive everyone mad
You don't need to be in the government, I can't do s*** we watch it fail
Effective
Under the radar
You make an interesting point I think that if you were
Trying to write some sort of a fiction about ways that
Disruption could happen
Have you come up with way better things then International group of X-Men
Military people who are all hanging out
And working
Trump yeah I mean imagine you don't know anything about these 20 water treatment super
Nothing
And then they're gone.
Wow is this your Nextbook I hope so
Not only do they unfortunately no water treatment
Supervisors on board the entire world
Militaries and governments or whatever
Folks were
Really cool
They also have
Hyperintelligence
Jhene Aiko
It's also useful to know
That
Chewing team have
Clearly into
Vacated that
First of all we know behind the scenes they're relying on it
When an AI
Some people
Mycolic qai
Then they're also working and relying on
Sun
Su Art of War
And if you read that hasn't gotten better season
Acting to be much weaker than you are is one of its main
Principles
So that the enemy
Doesn't attack you direct
So and also
Appearing to go along when I'm back
You plan to double-cross them
Towards the end is also
One of the
Principles and
Do your own research on that
I haven't read The Art of War Sun
College
Probably put
I think there's more to it
No he is really short
I don't
I think those were the basic idea
Like that did the primary ideas when I died
Trump has brought up
And maybe have to do with the art of the deal
I'm sorry
So you got to understand that this is
What's going on these are the teams and this is one of the
The primary ways
Is the decew team is
Figuring out bruschetta
Art of War has almost certainly
Not read The Art of War
So the II cannot assimilate Concepts from the aisle
Affordable Coronavirus
There's a method to Trump's Madden
And you got understand that he's not working alone
But
He's not working with
The person you might think he's work
So
Understanding the methods in The Madness of trump and
Team
You can
Kind of figure out why it is
Trump.
Certain things or doesn't do other
And also
To really keep in mind.
So we're not talking about
Two men
You know Biden and Trump this is how people
Refer to it
But that's not really what's going on
Okay that how people refer to it I guess that there's a theory that Trump is working
Our like pulling
Biden strings behind the scenes
Guess what that's a theory that some people have put forth
That's not one that I
Run into too much so
Good to know that that's
The theory would kind of bummed me out to have a shity two-headed white man Hydra run
Running the country but you know
It could be worse
Two dudes you're disappointed with but in different ways
Exactly
This is going to be good
Oh yeah oh yeah
So we didn't this like we learned that Biden is not biting
Biden's been being played
Okay
He probably being played by three entities
This is
So fun
Biden is
Said to be played
Goodbye at least
Three individual
One down
A general
That's on
Trump side and three Jim Carrey
Who's off the game
Brodovitch
That means that in theory Biden is under control of
From however
That's not quite
Case because a lot of the decisions
Biden is May
Making are what we call Deep state
Decision
And
Those decisions are being allowed to happen
Buy the truck
By the way
Again because
What they really want is they having an ending inside
They want to wake up
People who voted
For Biden or who
Who fell for the
For the deception
Sure sure
I almost lost it
When I heard that
It's quite a surprise
Clone a general into
Good man
Clone a general in Jim Carrey
Walk into a bar
Aeroplan
Clone been a general
Jim Carrey
Why not entertain the other one with references to his old movies I'm sure would love that
Hi I think this is my last name because what you have if you have to be like okay Biden's not by
Something else
He's a clone Jim Carrey and a general
He's working with Trump in the cutie
The General Eight who's playing him is
Inwood
The truck General carries kind of controller off also
So why is it
The bidens doing things we hate
Well it must
Because
Trump wants him to do those globalist
State decision yeah wake up
The public is fun
If you
Can understand
This is coming from
Alright you can reverse-engineer the thought process behind his
Decision
Now it could be incredibly complex
Or it could just be
Very simple does this benefit me
Or no
I will do the thing that benefits
I think I think one of the ways you could look
This is like
What if
Joe Biden is just a purse
What is Jim Carrey's look
Jim Carrey you don't need an explanation for why he's making
Decisions that the Q team doesn't like that doesn't make sense because
Here's the craziest part and this is going to blow your mind
All right right
Biden is making decisions that are almost
Entirely consistent with his 50
Year career in government
So it's obvious
Obvious
That while Ace Ventura was filming
Jim Carrey was also in Congress
There's no other explanation
Right filmed in Florida
I got one I got one got away with me I don't know where Dan Marino fit into this
We should have known like on Election night
When
Biden gave his acceptance speech and it ended with
If you guys want me to be the president
I don't I couldn't work that into a contact really hard
But here's the thing though
My explanation that Biden
Is President music
Person
But fails one very important
Test
Information to Trump
Actually
Right now the problem
To fit in with Joe Biden is a purse
We do know that
Trump has been sworn in
And he is actually surprised
And even now
How Trump is set
I could be sworn in by
And I wanna 7 in my opinion everything points to the back
Play Junior
I do understand there's another guy named Michael
Protsman I think
Last name
Who is
Infatuated by numbers
And he's gone on several
Girl shows
Exedra some people think
Kids voice sounds like
Again
JFK jr.
Amy is neither here nor there
And assert
Play no proof of anything
Agreed yeah
What do you mean by he's infatuated by number
Beep I get a little bit like that you know he's just infatuated by numbers and it's eventually going to drive him mad and then he will be
Felipe's JFK jr. number 23 Jim Carrey played by ignant
Cancel
So 107
How did they get rid of
Clone Joe Biden's memory
Spotless Mind
Kate Winslet exactly Hillary Clinton
Baby cross in that movie probably
So 107 is a guy who's like one of Carrie's
Like
Now that you can't go to prison and talk to Mark Richards
Juan o Savin is like a
A big Insider
Expert guy
I think I think his name is a play on 007 107
I think there's some sort of a numerological thing parent says he's picky fancies himself
So his name is intentional
To make himself look
Lucky's JFK jr.
I've done several shows on y
JFK jr.
And 1070 the same
In person
Aside from the
That Juan equals John
So it goes Jackie O and Savin is
Savin Hill
Weather
Library is
Built and no one would use that moniker
And come out
Not to the public unless they wanted to
People to know they were actually work
JFK jr. or associated with him in some
So that
Shows intention
On the part of 107
To be known as that other
It sure does
I mean
I'm honestly honestly I'm almost impressed
Well hello do you how far did she have to go to get from 107
A very simple 007 pot
Into JFK jr.
I think that but I think she's I think she's probably right
That
You know 107
Maybe intentionally chosen
Names in order to evoke JFK Junior capitalized on the excitement in the Keuka
Community junior is alive
I think that you might be right that like you intentionally did name himself or this as a means of
Intentionally trying to evoke that
But that also
So does not prove that he is now there is a problem there
Although I have heard
That he sounds like a young G
No I mean 100 are there
Neither here nor there we know that voices don't mean s***
Carrie
Psych profile
On
Juan o Savin
And also on JFK jr.
Okay but think of it I think they match up boy
I want to give you my hands on these high-profile
Shawano seven I did a whole psychology
Profile as to why this person is
JFK Junior and I think it holds up
And I also
Have
Also had
Psychic dreams about this
Sure pad
Constant on and off
Dialogue
Text
And occasional phone calls
What's the weather
The person calling himself leidos
Or are you go
For all intents and purposes that individual is laying out
The philosophy
The plans
And and being sort of the
The laser
If you want to call and press
Liazon
For the trunk
Team
So yeah I guess you've got this guy who's so far at the sense that I'm getting is that he is he's branded himself
B of A
Hi
Hi access weirdo
And now we've decided to accept him as the
Media attention
Trump
Did involved
Jose isuper
Computing
And the Art of War
This is good I like when we cross genres and you can just see who would be a retired lieutenant colonel and who is
Super soldier and who's you know you can just
What kind of sibo
The basic archetypes
So this guy might've actually played multiple roles
We might have a little bit of History to I'm a little bit like Jim Carrey
Absolutely
So you might notice that this is something that I'm it's kind of an elephant
The room
And Carries got to
Address
The short time tonight is it a lot of her whistleblowers
To be like
Bulshit wow
Takers Flyers
Call shatara
Kahneman
Liar I think a better way to put it is they were born into Illuminati family
Have Arizona leave that
Another switch.
These individuals
Whistleblowers in fact
And all of the individuals I'm sure on the Trump team
Who have worked for the Deep state
In other words
Many being born into deep State families originally excetera
What we're talking about is
Individual
Girls who have
Change sides
And have decided
To come and work
With and for
For the people
So that's a
Chucky
Understanding.
You know these individuals regardless of their original back
And in fact
Because of their original background
They actually know what the
They're talkin about
They have seen
The reality behind the scenes
Having work for the Deep state in various capacities
Damn answer a lot of these people are like Oliver whistleblowers are from the Luminati families that
I like a lot of them are people who are using like
Deep Alias is in stuffing
Isn't is Leo zagami
Not sure not sure if
But he's one of the only people I've been able to like really break through and figure out a lot of details about his door
Does not check out no
But let this story was
Spell peed
Sick
B6
And a reputation around the room club scene for being silly
Yeah
Oh man
I just I mean
They all have to be from former Illuminati
All of them
Is the problem though with all of them being from Illuminati families
You can't trust any of them then
True
You know I mean if it's a few defectors you can tell that there's an organized block tried to keep people from
Artifact tank and you got a couple
People coming over who is like escaped and they've got really
Good stories and you can trust him in there double Asia
But if is everybody
Status II
For sure
What what I think
I think this is just a way to
Do you like have these people be allowed to have first-hand information about these evil things
And also they're not bad people were vapor and on it
Expose the darkness or whatever
It's a way to
I think I also call it now that's not right the right term but just make some unpalatable
Who's allowed to be like I was there when they killed all the babies
Rye or whatever
Swan
Isn't a tough spot
I don't know why
Yeah I'm really confused as to why it seems like he's doing great. The media liaison for secret Trump press people that involves
Is a worldwide network of ex-military people who are controlling everything
EXO
Thankfully because he's JFK Junior he's
It's a fine
So Dove Road
2 to go down
Aura
A difficult
Tightrope
Assertive
That 107 has to
Could negotiate
But
As John F Kennedy Junior he's in a unique position to do so
And he does drop hints
By the way Wendy
Does interviews
Time
As to the fact
Now there is probably
A so-called 107
Pretender behind-the-scenes who works with him call Dwayne Willis
No doubt there is a Wayne Willis
There are pictures you know online and there's
NetSpend
One video where
One was talking and then they showed up
Physical
View of
When will it be in the same room
But that's not
Surprised
In fact
Entirely possible.
When will it is not only
Comrade
Rod of
A good friend
But he's also on a sign
Assignment and he's on his Steinman
Deflect
Whatever is necessary to play a double
If you will and two
To basically
Protect him
Sorry lot
Logical that he might even be
Checks out
This is a good way to explain away how like people have found videos of someone who looks exactly like 107
Do a conspiracy drift in the same room
They been in the same room there's no doubt
That way dwell
I don't know if I have not seen the video where they're in the same room I have no idea what you're talking about but I have sound
A number of people claiming
She's a guy was doing stuff back in like 2014 my
A guy's a big a big whistleblower type of type of
You've done this game before
It's basically the
What I, wave
You know
What I Come Away with this is
Hazel
So long as you say the right
Stuff
People like Carrie will makeup
Any reason to let you
Keep going
Any possible explanation will be way better than to
Just being like Oh well he's
Line I think that's definitely true but I also think
This comes down
The same issues that a lot of the mainstream media has with
Access
Yeah you know a lot of the
Reporting on Trump let's say was
Maybe not as critical as it could have been sure
Or not as could have been
Because of organizations fearing they would lose access
To like your land rightfully so you would have probably take that long
He already
Define unfortunately it's in that case it's the presses World APUSH
The issue
Satisfying
What what I think Akira suffers from the same thing
She has access to these people who are high-profile weirdos
If she pressed the issue she would lose access to
Want you lose access to Mark Richard Wright
And somebody else would go to
Go to them and take all of hers of vacuum that would be filled yeah people are Griffin
Avedro
Facilitate their grip
That's true but I mean God damn it really freaks me out sometimes cuz I'm I'm on the edge of her knowing that she's
F****** with me and I'm on the edge of her having no clue
Like I just don't know
I know there's no like Middle Ground
She's either in or out
You know
I don't think she's f****** with you
No I know but I mean like
Shinichi went back and let's go earlier episode to like what I got it
F*** with your Daddy's Hands On handy
So we were talking earlier about the negotiation
An aspect of this
I'm going on
Hey turns at the negotiation has to do with like a verdict
Civil War kind of thing
Sanctuary
But in their plan already to like kill a bunch of people
The Deep state
Sure
But they're going to stop that
Nice because the Deep state is now in a position where they have to negotiate because of three things
All three Joe Biden
Jim Carrey's
Here's the first one
So there was a negotiation he felt
The reason they're at a place of negotiation is
Is because
Of the follow
Which is
What's gone down in Afghanistan which has two
Suh dude
The
You know the Trump Administration to expose
The poor leadership
Under
Biden and team
And the Deep state in essence there
Their dark intentions
And how they would
You know basically you're happy.
See American suffer
And so on
So far
So they feel that.
Is going to be the coup de gras
It takes down Biden in the minds of
The unenlightened letshe
7-Eleven woken up
Was going to be what happened in Afghanistan during the wake up at Joe Biden
Boy if you're really thinking that this one reflects poorly on Biden's Administration instead of the entirety
City of the past 20 years of American government
You're out of your mind dwell on it pictures
The first thing is I've gained
Sam is the second thing
I don't know about this
Then there's hurricane Ida and hurricane Ida there was a lot of conversation he said about
That
And again
No pure cane Ida would have been a deep state
Shot across the bow a weather War
Weather weapon
Which state do use hurricanes all the time to do
And earthquake
Extend all other you know
So-called
Climate
Events
And then basically hurricane Ida was
Has
Purposes
One of which was
Shutdown
Oil production
2 Gang
To Cripple the country
And
To also
Shutdown
The area
Louisiana
New Orleans area and unrelated areas
And
To basically
Threatened
Again the American people
So
Yeah I guess hurricane Ida was a weather weapon that was my till like
Lookout
Bebo
We can do this to you at any time
I didn't invite invasion
Advertise that I didn't experience
Certainly.
The weather event
Tragic
Anyways
Yeah I mean if it's a warning you have
To warn people
Going to be a warning
Yes
You can't warn somebody with magic that they have no idea you
You can do right
The reason to give a warning
Is to like change someone's Behavior
Kid is doing something you don't like you
You know I take away their allowing if they do it again here it's simple
Consequences which will lead to larger contact
Right
I don't understand what babe you're supposed to be stopped
Or else we'll get another hurricane
Even if
Like
It's like
Pranking somebody
With one of those things where they open the door and then the bucket of water falls on their head
Right but
Never Like Nobody's around
And nobody ever finds out it's you
That's not a warning
That's just a weird thing to do to somebody it's also not a prank even in that so it's just weird attack
Yeah I don't know this
Confusing to me these the reason that the Deep State swelling
Negotiate that is because of Afghanistan make inviting look bad
And then
Ida apparently being a deep State weather weapon
I know how that makes the Deep State more willing
To negotiate
Yeah I don't know
I think the thing I hate
Most about this type of
This is this group of people
Admiration for Trump
Is that
The one group of people who understands Trump
Is the one who likes him because of his psychopathic
Hatred for human life
And that allows them to
Indulging their violin
And then you've got carry who's got this whole other narrative Trump cares about people
And it's like
Somehow
You're crazier than people who are trying to murder right now cuz at least they know what Trump is for
You know that's what she's ate you're out of your mind if you've
Think he cares about one human
Who died anywhere
Yeah yeah definitely out of your mind
So those are the two things the first two things there's a third thing
Making the the New World Order deep State willing to negotiate
And then we have the auto
And this is where I think
Phil made his most important point
Basically saying that the audit
With an ass
We're not just
Maricopa
County but
Going into all the other states
And that the evidence was always already
And that
In essence what they have been doing is sitting
So that the
Trump team
Is
Sitting on
Of the
I was coming through these audits that are sort of like this
Dog and pony
Show
With Michael
DeLand
Basically
Going in slow motion to do a count a recount
Of something they already have on blockchain
They knew the election would be stolen.
Trump had one
Percentage-wise
And
That
Actually before the election
So they were
Totally forgot
In the background that's just delightful
But yeah so
Votes
Sure all that is a sting operation like Steve told us naturally
These these audits are happening
Right they're going to reveal the information.
Trump team already has
The Trump 18020
Shorten the election charges unheard-of numbers
That would be difficult that's a registered the popular vote
48 f****** States or whatever it is that he did not get a 220 that's for goddamn sure did not
No
Yes
Answer these the reasons that they
Deep States willing to negotiate they know they're in trouble
That doesn't sound like it makes any sense whatsoever
Why would the Deep State negotiate
With people who can
I mean essentially get rid of them at any point in time
You know like if you have the evidence
You can just go
Yeah it really sounds like
The bad guys are on the ropes
So there must be some kind of a reason why
This isn't happy
Yeah I know there's got to be an explanation
Trump and team now hold
The trump card
That shows that
Trump is indeed legitimate
Commander and chief
I'm president of the United States
He has been actually sworn in by the military since again March
It doesn't make sense it's something that one has said
Repeatedly
And so
Basically were talking about
An acknowledgement
This fact and a recognition of this fact
By the American public
Our bird wet there
Holding on the evidence
To prevent
Civil War
Because they
Believe that they still don't have
A critical mass of individuals who have a wake
Last time I heard one on one of the show's say
They have something like 70
Percent
They need 80
They got this
Deflect
You know Civil War
If you just come out and give this
Proof
Point of order
If Trump 18020
To find out that he won a T20
Would suggest that 80% of the population
Would be going
Hooray
80% the population we already know
So why would there be a civil war
They will get one.
Also I want to see some
Data
Is there a Pew research
That kind of access only 107
Or JFK jr.
Who knows
Who's been around for a long time lying to people who knows
Yeah I find this to be
Ifun
Underwhelming
Explanation for why the evidence isn't there
Really 10% more
Listen it 75% now it's
It's like a GoFundMe unless we reach our goal we don't get to overthrow the
Bring up
So there's that there's an election coming up
In California
Hours of the recall whenever he loses it
Fall into a nightmare
It's probably going to be stolen
By the way we're about
California election in which
They've already photograph
People stealing the
The mail-in votes and all this kind of thing
So there's no doubt
Election is working
Be stolen as well weather
To be rough
Skewed
By the White House
I don't know
Isn't that a fascinating turn afraid
Can this election be rescue sure
Sure now
Rescue Bots already imply
I think there are a lot of people who have that mentality of like
It's already implied they were going to lose
Because of cheating
So now the only way we can win
Is buy some kind of aggressive
Tactic to rescue the election
Rhombus
Presume that
We've lost a legitimate election not because our policies and ideas are batshit
Crazy and everybody hates
It is definitely because it's going to be stolen bright so what
We should do to these cheaters
Is beat them up outside of polling
Places
And then we'll never have to deal with it
That's a good way to rescue something
So we can all see the political
Intrigued
The
Is he is he not JFK jr.
Negotiations with the Tri-State situation
And now we have to learn about a woman
Greater vision
Does very important
Apparently an in
Individual called Anna Marie
On 82
Saw a vision and she saw a
Mushroom
Cloud in helping field
In what she thought was a national park
Civil War
4/10
And in color and and then
You know some some mountains and
A plume of smoke
That turned into a mushroom
She believes it may be Gettysburg
Or near Gettys
Course
Happens
The reason that's interesting is B
Because I did some research on Getty
Leesburg and found out that during the Civil War
Actually Gettys
Pittsburgh was considered
Tubi
Supposedly the Battle of Gettysburg
Bird was supposed to be the end of the
Civil War
In the minds of
I guess
Mine
Girls fighting
That were at the time
And that instead
Became
Not only
Sort of an inch
Alligator but it's
It actually
Prolong the Civil War 4
Another
2 years
She might want to read a couple more pages about the Gettysburg battle gone with a cup
The people who thought it would be the end of the war where the
Confederacy
Lee was marching
And the reason is a turning point in the war in the war ended up going longer was
Because it was a decisive Union victory
And so I guess if you're saying it should have been the end of the war
Then you think the Confederacy should have won
So congratulations on that interpretation of History that's a little bit weird
Also wire welders
Why are we
Taking the as gospel divisions of a random woman
You know I feel like here's what I feel like I think I figured out most of human history right
You know how no one is interested in your dreams but you
Well
If you want to tell somebody a dream store
Right and you know in advance
That they're going to be like I don't give a s*** about your dreams you dumb dumb
So you want to tell the story
You have to say it was a prophetic
Yeah otherwise people are going to listen to your dumb story about your dumb dream about a mushroom cloud in Gettysburg
That's a dumb dream it implies a little bit more weight
Yeah and it also implies it is
Something not to do with g
Just your own psyche like maybe the dream is saying something metaphorically about what you're going through these are
Archetypical images maybe or something that reflect
The part of your feeling
Yeah as opposed to there's actually going to be a nuke set off at Gettysburg
Yeah I mean it would not
Make a religion if Matthew was like hey
Hey dudes
Check this out I had this dream where Jesus came out of this f****** cave am I right
Everybody
Oh yeah of course
But the other possibility is that
They're going to do Gattis
If the Illuminati are looking
Looking for a site
By which two
Unleash any kind of
Weapon
Whether it be a nuclear or something else
The mushroom cloud
Not sure what other things too
Bomba
Then
Perhaps
Annamarie was seeing
Is something that
That would be
Physically
Buy them and she thought
This would happen in September
Back I think she thinks
It's on
September 11th
Which is coming up in
You confirm or deny that
Uber got nuked on September 11th
I'm going to go to the nose
The doctor
How many score and seven years ago is Gettys
I also think they
It does bear mention
Gary does bring UPS
Some other remote viewers who are some of them instead September 21st
That's good
Pastor b******* and they also said that it might be New York
So well I mean there's a lot of New York on the 11th or the 21st
Probably is also involved
If anything happens we predicted
I'll find a way to hammer that into a mushroom cloud metaphor
But it's not just this random woman Anna Maria who saw this
It's also
Something that
Like I said these remote viewers that carries heard about assure
Then what happened was
I stumbled on
Just somebody sending me a
Crypto video
Which normally I wouldn't even bother to watch
But I
Nized of the individual
On the cover
Quite remember 280 West
Hand and then I realized it was Dick
Algar the famous remote viewer
Do I have interviewed in the past
She's used to work with
With Courtney Brown
So did Dad Smith who's on this team of
Expert remote viewers and
They were going to look at events in shut
September
Very recently
And they're going to
Report about
Krypto and instead they all saw a mushroom
And they sought
You know their self
Ways and they didn't know the other one saw that and then eventually they came together and discussed it
Well
I think this
Got to put this to bed
Yeah
Leesburg lovey idea
A ragtag band of remote viewers just getting together and being like we got a
Stop this apocalypse
Books today I'm telling you right now we got the water treatment supervisors
We got the form
Ragtag remote viewers coming out of everywhere we got Jim Carrey becoming president
They're all in there I'm a little bit pissed off that Biden did such a bad job as the Riddler
He wasn't great I do think of that
That's picture that you have about a ragtag group of
Remote viewers that kind of sounds like
The Forgotten Philip K dick novel
Second Foundation by as about maybe that's what I'm thinking
Beaver Mountain View hours they also this mushroom cloud
It's September
They won't come and talk
Harry Caray
Will explain that they don't like
Talk about things separately so they don't have their stories in concert
Man sucking laissez-faire
What I know about these remote viewers is they don't want to
Talk about this
Because they don't want to be a
Placated in
Putting out false
Stata if they're wrong
And
Number two
When
Trying to you know give energy
To this idea
However
In the interest of
Deflecting
The acts of The Darkside then
Eliminating the element
Surprise
Is why I'm doing this and why I'm making a Sazon
I'm here is simply because this
Will possibly
Deflect
Them
If they sink their
There are plans are known
They may not
Carry them out
Or they may change
Their plans whatever that have
Tubi
You know these are the kinds of things you're dealing with your dealing
With a lot of variables
When you have some kind of
Dyer Act
But I would
Pass them to
Actually carry it out anyway
So what you have here is
Do you have Carrie
Setting up the exact same scenario that Alex does whenever he makes these predictions
What you doing is your creating a trap where you can never be wrong
Because you're talking about this thing and
The bad guys are going to maybe hear this and they might change their plans because their plans have been exposed but also
You should still be scared cuz I wouldn't put it past them to do it anyway
You can never be wrong
When you set up
But predictions and Analysis like this
Because you can
You have a fish
External back door built into your story already
Yeah
It's it's
Interesting to see these kind of like
Rhetorical similarities
Ride
You know cuz it is it is how you
Keep people stuck
No I mean
If you were
If you were talking to somebody and they were like I remote viewed
The future and you are like okay
So it's going to happen and they were like
Maybe not
Then you be like well then what's the f****** point of view I don't know the future and I know maybe or maybe not
So you don't need to be here at 5 so they have to add this element of like but I did something by
By my actions
I averted the future that I predicted
Okay
Never allowing you to prove me right or wrong
They can do nothing with this thank you very much
Carrie I was talking to someone named Kim gouge
I'm not sure who this person is I think it's another
Radio host
There's some sort of another YouTube show
Any related to Paul Go-Go
Probably
Distantly
There's some talk about whether or not the US went to Defcon 2
When
Recently
Why I don't know
Okay text me Kim has an explanation
A what
Explain what Kim
Has to say but
I want to be
A clear very fair
Terry's not
Actually saying that she's recording at this is what
Campsite
Can go again come back to me and said
The death come
Chew on Monday or Tuesday
Was
Current information was that
The death come to on Monday or Tuesday
Was stated to be dude
To send
Text and ballistic missiles found in Boulder Colorado
What's DHHS bomb squad was called in most likely they will pick
4 missiles
Boogeyman and go to war this was authorized enclosed
By military agencies otherwise it would never have made it
Over the Mexican border
The story is that it was attempted repeated
The chance to move
The financial system
Texas
It was supposed to
Deflect and
Sort of attention from the movement of
Financial
Systems to
To Texas
Ask her what she said okay
Her sources said
Circa a he's not necessarily saying that you're not saying
It's not true
Apaches just reporting
This isn't this something that's being chatted about
Through the Defcon two because they were missiles
That came up
From Mexico that were found in Boulder Colorado
And the DHHS
I was going to find somebody to blame on that
And start a war in order to
Deflect from
The fact that they're trying to move the financial Market to Texas
Interesting Wall Street now in Texas
DIA
VI
Dia of the DHHS calling in a bomb squad
For Missy
The funniest
Possible thing I can think of
I mean imagine
Just imagine there being missiles in the bomb squad is wearing the f****** bomb suit going to be like
Hey maybe I'll survive this f***
Basil if I blow it up get the f*** out of here
Maybe somebody whose job it is to deal with missile
Somebody will probably not like there's a million different types
The missile also North
Grumman has a station in Boulder
So like a bunch of people there
Blame it on a patsy
Thrive in the financial system
What does that mean
Victor MIT
Has been caught with a missile that he brought
Kim from Mexico
So we're going to start a war
And this is all too distracting the fact that Joe Rogan and Elon Musk move to Texas
Or something
I want it I want to see I want to see it
There's some other talk going on
That is if they're going to shut down a state
I don't know which
State security doesn't remember which state
Jimmy Choo doesn't sweat the details
State in the United States
Going to be shut down
Just shut down
Someone recently said
They're going to cut
They're going to
Completely closed down
Forget what you said it is
Whatever
You do not let people in or out and and all kinds of craziness is going to go on
Apparently they do want to try
Divorce vaxis
That's going to cause
More Civil War type issues
You don't want a civil war if
The Chinese are at your borders which they are
Find it on my website
Saying that they're actually training in Pennsylvania
So shutdown Pennsylvania Chinese military is training in Pennsylvania
Burning a land invasion
When they're already in the United States
I love the idea of the
The Chinese military
Anywhere in the United States
Sing for anything because there's zero possibility in the United States that a Yoko will not stumble upon
0 possibility that somebody will not stumble upon the Chinese military practicing
I got to get out of here
I have to I have to make a confession
I did not
Go check out her website.
Goddamn
I let this one slip
I'm going to stipulate
Whatever
If she doesn't know what state she's talking about Ryan
I'm not going to look into the Chinese land Invasion by way of Pennsylvania
You can't just say you know what happened you don't have a 11
The Chinese are working with a Pennsylvania Dutch
Yep
Oh man
I give Carrie a hard time and you know
Some of it is
Good-spirited
Some of its not
But
I think that there are really salient
Similarities
Is between the way that she disseminates information
Another way Alex
You can't learn from
Totally now as a way to punch
Alex Wright in his gut
I would like to play clip
That
I think goes along way too
To show that
Even carry
Someone who believes in space Raptors
And all this nonsense
He's still a little bit more sensible than our
So one and two are basic
Sickly one
Sandwiches
In absence the Rino
Pelicans and the demo
Then
The other group would be
In essence the
White House
People
Part of the people can easily be a person who is a demo
Republic
These labels actually have to go by the wayside eventually
Because they don't really symbolize
The truth
What's going on here in the philosophies of the people
I'm sure there are plenty of Democrats out there that think they don't want
To be in a
Can't do anything with their bodies whatsoever
Let alone
Democrats that are
What I call closet Nazis
And there
Just the opposite so
Yeah I think it's important not to so to slot somebody
Automatically into a
An enemy
If you will category of humanity
Swimming carries even sensible enough to know that like some people who are like
Like maybe
Visually or superficially on a different
Track the new
Where is Alex spends most of his time talking about how everyone who disagrees with me eventually the Democratic Party
Killing babies as a ritual
It's a
It's a bummer you know this person who believes
The JFK is her weird friend
Ed's all this stuff is going on and there's a
Caballo
Secret until the
People around the world that are working with
Trump
And they still have like in terms of where the rubber meets the road how you treat other people
Beautiful more evolves
More tolerant kind of perspective
Yeah especially when you Jeff
Deposit with 2003 Alex fan like these nut bags out there making us all look bad
They make us look like
Conspiracy theorist these people out there with their
Oh I've met aliens before
Man buddy
Even she's like
Hey what's up
Dick all the time
Everybody's
We won last clip and I was
Feeling something as I was listening to this and I was like
Where are the
Ifucking aliens
There is nothing about Raptors
There is nothing about the Mercantile dogs
Nothing about the feline
Contessa's
There is nothing about the
Wrapped up adamantas beating
There's nothing about the
Squid I think there's some
Squid involved somewhere
Disappointed
And then we get towards the end
And Kerry says this and I kind of felt like
This is lip service oh no
I guess whatever you take what you can
This situation is also influenced by the ETA
Visitors
Andy T's inhabit human bodies
The Schumann
E.t.
Hybrids that are here
Many of us are a mixture of many races of UT's
And
There is also
Said to be in a show called
By human
Group that's Adama
Are from Adam
Adam seed
But I think that that's also a
A misunderstanding
Because if you go into the work
Ashiana Dean
And her books are on the phone
Page
On the Lord
Apart of
Front page of my website
And read those
She will find out that
Life on Earth and humans did not
Bpn
When is the Anunnaki decided
You know inter
Kefir with are chinos
Tooele home
You know Garden of Eden
Story stems from that
.
And at certainly
Talking about
Where the Bible stems from and and
Prior to that time there was no Bible so
A lot of those stories also
Are slightly
If not completely misleading
Alex wouldn't
Like that
That would not be good
That would not make it easy to talk to somebody who's been to heaven
A lot of the Bible is barely Wiggly
Who would have guessed
I felt a little bit sort of
Unsatisfied by that
Does not your aliens are involved but how
Yeah
This is big stuff like we got a lot going on right now
What she's talking about
Nuke
Gettysburg
Yeah I have to be involved bulshit before
They were like oh there's a trade disagreement between China the United States so we got the Mercantile.
Austin ago she was actually aliens eating people and they had to close off an area
Whenever there was like a war it was close a portal or something
Do with like with good alien
No mantis beings anywhere
No no Beatles
A little disappointed
Betrays the entire worldview
Because it either goes
One way or the other
You know it's got to be small s*** with aliens
Otherwise we would notice
Right so that's got to be that like
We're showing up in Vietnam during the war
That thing
Aurora's got to be so big
That the only thing that matters is space
ACNL
Like if you're talkin about intergalactic
Take travel
Who gives a f*** about politics in the United States
Do you know like the only thing that implicates
Exactly or it's part of a larger war between them and it's a proxy war them everybody where the universe
Does Vietnam you know that but I'm not seeing is
How's that work
In relation to the topics
But she's covering from here
Aliens are involved
And then
A drop
I find that to be not at all
Now I need more
Weak tea
Itweak
There's something that I wanted what by coming back
But I did get some
Black-eyed nice reprieve
There was some fun
And to be found your Waters yeah
And so like I'm glad that I was able to find these not vinup a wall
Assertive ethically discuss
Get another voice
About what's going on in the world
It's important it's important
To be able to have different
Different information streams
You know I think what
Really disappoint
I think what really disappointed
Is that
It's because I would assume it's because of carries audience
But she has to go in
You know what I'm saying
Because if anybody is set up
To be in a situation
We're even during the Trump and Biden
Disagreement years
Or whatever it is we wouldn't even during the
The cold Civil War we've been fighting
Obama
It's right you know I mean it's like
You can stay above The Fray
You're talking about space
You're out there
You know and you can apply the greys
Is to whatever's going on
But that's not as important as the international trade disagreements
Between the f****** bluebirds
Yeah
I think social media algorithm gaming and
Like a lot of those
Influences
Just became such a Gold Rush people during the Trump.
That's how I feel like it maybe they were it.
But it was impossible to avoid couldn't
You couldn't
Not there might be a place in the market
Good place for you to have weird ideas
Maintain an audience and not have a strong position on Trump
Right cuz there's other people out there who
Who's got alien weirdos
But they've got a strong position on Trump and now that those two are intertwined
I think it's possible I don't know maybe someone will write a book about it one day
Jordan will be back
With another episode will get back to Alex Jones
Had to give him a break had to give ourselves a break break feel I feel much better
Yes I will be back but until then we website
It's right we're also on Twitter underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan
Until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
And now here comes
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work