Air Jordan
Nola.com
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Everybody
Where's for the owner of Selena little bit about Alex Jones
A Jordan is that my watching of Survivor
I've made it to season 31
Brawn vs Beauty season
Survivor has a couple of themes of a developed over the course of the years
One of them is very
Interesting and compelling
Lingonberries blood vs water
Okay you have
People who have
Play again
Their loved ones
Like my wife for their job
Get the child is
People are crying all over the place it's a i
It's interest
The compelling twist if you have
Keep changing this show
From what it originally was
At least that's heard of an interesting sociological
Industrious
Novel ya
That isn't just asking
Another theme is beauty verse Braun
So just like what's the most
Important thing
Three tribes one of them are like beautiful people one or smart people who want to really strong people
What a weird things
To do I find it to be really
Poorly done idea to
Because it's not like
The people who are the brain orally through the bronchi but strong.
Not like they have no mental ability seems like an order for it to truly be fair
All things must be boiled down to a single attribute has only string exactly you can only use
Drink though you can only use beauty or you can only use your brain that type of thing.
Seems to me like that would be how you would do that
Girl pretty attractive people
Beauty tribe is like love you were maybe models and stuff
Everybody says I look
Look like Obama
Very attractive man
I'm very smart and I look like
President Obama
My bright spots
How about you by bright spot.
You know
Over the years I've had
Mani pedi
Refutes for no reason other than a door suicide
Has a
Cured in my life again
For some reason on Twitter he decided you again
He said something stupid and people started
Stepping up what made it good for me though was it was like revisiting an old neighborhood you know I went back
Avondale the other day
And you see all the stuff
It's the same and you see the stuff that
It's different you like I remember this
Friedersdorf
Dealership
Never change man
Never change
Is that your word of encouragement the word of encouragement
It always feels like home do your bad take it is
Reuleaux level app
I'm happy for you on my phone
Complaining
Thank you and hello to the new wasp
First The Hobbit thank you so much
GoNoodle
I'm starting a podcast Factory you think mother about
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
You're not bald
Thank you so much you are now but
And also like to say thank you to a technocrat out there what's up Lauren Al how you doing
I'm a policy wonk
Business
Money off that heroin
Usually large
Bigalora
Before we get
To business on this episode
To do is we have to take a little
Are we going to be
Taking a trip into the past
Are you ready to take a trip with me
Okay I've been to Scotland I like Scott Happy Birthday to Ross
From Scotland on Monday but
Been so happy birthday
And also in Scotland
There's big news
Thanks to Tyler
In the Glencoe wood
Scotland
Okay there's a plot of land
But has been adopted
And now the name of saline
One of the fun things that comes along with this
Is it with this land
You get a title
So now it's Selena baroness she's a lady She's a Lady Lady Selena
Time that we're moving up
Not just in the animal world but him the Earth World we're taking over
It's very exciting
You slowly spell congratulations
The lady's Helene take you some
Watch Tyler plays very cool
Selena
That would be a
Let's get back to Chicago so you can record the episode
Text mr. Peabody
So I've had a bad week
Already
And a lot of it has to do with
People posting that goddamn song of Alex
Another
Million-and-a-half views as video a lion all over Twitter
Really it really was bumming me out
And it's going to make me need to fully turn off
Notifications and any kind of
Beetle with cuz here's the thing
We talked about that on episode 65
Team wow we dealt with that in the
Discussed how that is actually
It's fun and it's funny
Is good it is actually something that plays directly into Alex's actually
Making content like that and making it really popular
Allows him to better inoculate
For keep trapped
Yep and make him seem like somebody who's actually aboveboard
It solidifies a lot of the the
The negative
Narratives
The dangerous
I will do 30 perpetuate
I wanted to discuss that again
I may be in Greater detail but I realize we've already done it
Highbank that gong 100 time
But then when I see these tweets come in I get like notifications on my phone cuz I had to turn off the
David
It just felt like
Constantly like
Your work doesn't matter
Yeah it doesn't matter
And no one cares
It really bums me out to know that we did that five years ago that's
Too long ago
It's too long ago it specially for us to have essentially the same tape
Grown at all in five years because
The correct steak is already been laid down
I don't want I don't want to save it there's no room
A girl them sure there's Nuance we can add to it but
It's a little bit of a bummer and that really like soda mess with
With my my
Emotional state that I like to be generally
No I understand
No one's fault and like I like even we talked about
I get why people think this is funny I want to share
Did I get it
He says we need to get to a place where we recognize
The things that are useful for propagandist in the pan
Is that are not
Land
I don't know
What's important
Is that those things
Are great
But will only be great
After Alex is no longer a threat to everyone
Yeah man I think I would love to enjoy it five years from now and Alex's if I don't know in space or something
It was even kind of the point was like a perfect world this would be great
But
It doesn't work
No no
Anyway
Here's the deal
Another thing happened
And that was the on Friday
Over the weekend
Alex was on
Stream
Some like
Gamer or not gamer but like
I guess I don't know what some people told me these guys are gamergate
Type
I don't know it's like a pop-culture
Recover it
Because I was drunk showed up on this weird
And
I really will show up anywhere.
Without without saying anything too much I think he might be showing up a lot of places you might be willing to
Surprised by the pathetic places you may end up seeing
But
Let's just say Rogan is not not the
The floor
I went my watch this
It was just a depressing
Display is really boring
These guys
8 white dudes
Just sitting around letting Alex Gil things
Mmm being like your jeans
Yeah it was it was a bummer it was a little bit depressed
It was also strange to see like these people who fancy themselves
Soar like
Lisa presentation
As far as I can tell like I have no idea I don't know
I'm not watch
These people's Conte
Then up there they were doing a pop culture related show
And at least
Three of them have beards that are unacceptable for the office Place broadcasting for bed
Bedrooms like DVD collections behind them
Great and so like
Weird for me to see these people who are like
Modern
Pop culture
And then they have their minds blown by like repackage
John Birch
Society talking points
From back when bees like Alex's
Heroes were fighting against the Civil Rights
It's so weird to me to see if you like them
This is fresh
They are
It's fresh
Whenever you're not in the middle of seeing the con
Deserve that bulge
You know perhaps like I feel like
The United States has gone through a constant
Ebb and flow of like
Okay The far-right Kills everybody and then it flows back as everybody's like I know we can't allow that to go on for
A couple years everything goes fine everybody forgets
That's that it's your f***
And far-right friends are going
Kill Everybody
If they do it again and then we go another two
20 years inside
We can't let this happen and then you know a new generation
S******* show up and we'll see what happens this time
Anyway I watch this stream
Didn't think it was interesting I didn't
I think it really brought up
How many points that I felt compelled to like really cover
Andrea Lee
Kind of just
Bumping out cuz here I am
Trying to go down these roads
I would like
Check out Alex
A different contacts
This may be fun
Wasn't
And then all these people just
Bombarding me with like 12
Rivera meme
He was almost nothing
This is my Victor Von Doom backstory 8 people on that stream
Yeah it dudes Bunch theme song
Coach Steve dozen
Usually have them all on video at the same time
I just
Gross
And so anyway I decided
Episode
I don't want to punish the world
About a dare
Make Alex go viral for this stupid
Bulshit again so I am turning heel
Oh God no
Hello and welcome to the Jim Bakker Show
I knew this was coming
Beautiful Ozark Mountains is the author
Courts of Heaven. Pastor Robert Henderson
Pastor Robert Hadden
Anderson it's been a long time
We should've left you without
Can food
Step 2
Here's the thing
Jim Bakker had a stroke
A while back
And there's been a long beard time where I've been like I don't want to talk about his show
Cuz
I don't feel good about it
Stroked out old weirdo propagandist monster
Some of his stuff
And in this episode that I was watching maybe kind of realize
I don't think it's the stroke I think users old and I don't feel as bad but at the same time
Little bit restrained
Sure
I have no interest in making fun of
The points where like
You know just aging maybe coming in
Into a fact get something or whatever like
But at the same time
This episode
Was amazing this Robert Henderson guy is the one who must be spoken about
Pretty hard we're going to find out if you heard about this guy
Pastor Robert
Some self in a
Apostle
That's not good claimed that
He claimed responsibility
Possibility
Ruth Bader Ginsburg
Okay
Okay okay
Alright
Interesting
Here's what he said
We were in the meeting on Monday night in DC and I told them I said look
We need to go to the courts of heaven right now while we're on site in DC and we need to shut the mouth of a lion
Judicially
We need to ask for a judgement against the lion that is actually been devouring and it tends to devour from the Supreme Court
We need to get a judgment against this lion that Paul said God shut the mouths of
So I let us into that place
Well guess what
Ruth Bader Ginsburg has passed away
President Trump. Blache new Supreme Court
That's no accident
Okay
Alright well I mean
I guess arrest
Tim
He's claimed through prayer you put a hit on
A confession
And I think he should be arrested
If you believe that he murdered Ruth Bader Ginsburg he should be punished accordingly
He later walk that back a little bit was like look I'm just saying I was praying
I heard
This like a nerd
I'll just put on my car.
The episode is titled
Mike's
Speaking in tongues
All right right
Tower in my wheelhouse pretty excited about like
What's Jim Bakker going to talk to the
This guy about
Speaking in tongue
It does not end up being mostly about that
The content of this episode is way more interesting
Something that
Albino
Every episode of Jim Bakker
The show starts
Took a little bit of light-hearted
Discussion
With the family
His co-host
Tammy Sue Bakker sings
The theme song and blood brings people in
The radio.
They're in their own compound
Fake TV show for fake people
In a fake situation
For money for no reason
When I was watching this
I will not
Say that I didn't think it's possible this is that tire
It's so over-the-top Robert Henderson who's the guest yeah
He has to stop himself from laughing
What the f*** out know that's not fair he almost break
You can't beat Jimmy Fallon and a f****** cogman at the same time that's how it works
It's pretty wild
Beginning they talked a little bit about going to family stuff
Happy birthday is coming
Interesting point
Wow
Wow years old now she told me the other day and I just don't accept it
I don't accept it either Jim
That's cute that's cute as hell
I really like that
There's also a point where Lori says that her like their anniversary is coming up
Can you remember which one it is and he's like 20
It's going to be 23 so I have right God
Still think they're horrible people
The presentation of like soft
Miss sure
Seems like
It's caring
Queen Victoria back in her day I'd like this
Goofing around
I kill people I can't accept that my daughter is 50 years old
I don't accept
Build those little kids aren't they though aren't your babies always the babies in the ass
Handlery you're going to be old are you going to be
You know you're not supposed to ask a lady how old she is
Before retiring one more year
Wish I was turning 50
C5 so I could get my medicare
Yep over that year and go straight to 6
I'm so grateful I can't wait so I can take advantage
Program
I'm philosophically opposed to everything that the Democrats
1960s whenever they did pass Medicare Medicaid that was a pretty good called
Social Security in the 1940 that was a great idea can't live without that everything about my political ideology leads
Me to do definitely want this to go away but I also would like to skip this here so I can take a shower
Healthcare that I refuse to accept it should be allowed to pay into this but no I want to skip
Years like experience socialism a I like to vacation in socialism
Better there
I'm going to
Generally not
Hotspot
Lunchtime on gyms.
Because I really do think
Henderson guy
Not so much
I don't I got a lot of theories about him okay
He's bringing to the table
He's
Amazing
Okay
He has this new book about speaking
In tongues
But it is Introduction Jim brings up his other books
The series
He's called the courts of Heaven
Get the f*** out
But we're about to introduce our Pastor Robert Henderson
Speakers in America today leave that
Books
Going bananas
Edward yousif
Do people love the
The court of Heaven
Siri this is actual
Play series
Books on it
It's just it
People have found an answer
Two unanswered
Prayer in those books
Yeah that's that's what that's what's called them
Almost
Supernatural
Oh absolutely
That there's a supernatural
Ocean on those
It's not just letters on a page
It's like a spinner
Portation
What is Magic
Are you really going to come out
The gate with this book
Will heal you because the words are literal Matt it hasn't unction
I was intrigued
Float away by the gall of someone to be like my book
Is literally mad
Pretty I was pretty
Taken aback by the
The open it
I want to know more what is
What it what's going on I mean if you try some of his words
Silver and you get the name the true name of the person that you want to curse then you will of course have power over
That isn't in the book
Is that more to do with the
The courts of Heaven I don't spoil too much
Learning about this is going to be amazing
I'll tell you this
If rbjs in the courts of Heaven he's going to be real pissed
She didn't make it.
What are the things that we always find Most Fascinating is
The preoccupation
Among space weirdos and Alex
With like
Interstellar contract law
And that's really why this episode of special
Because when he's talking about the courts of Heaven
Literally
When I go to heaven
Is a little bit of a light-year the movie Defending Your Life
It's not just after you die
It's also while you're alive
You can take advantage of the Heavenly court system
Alright
Who do I sue
Alright okay so
I take the devil to court I get it I get a Selmon's I got a subpoena
Serves as somebody
A court representing the devil or angel
Atlanta demon shows up in a suit and tied the lawyer for the devil
Leaving
Then you argued your case
And then what
Do you get rest
What if you lose
See these are the questions that I'm glad you have
And
Only one man
Can explain
OK Google I want to do time
No I got
Excitement
This is what happens when I turn heel
He's got a book he's working on
With the court system
Interesting Dynamics at play
Deli news there's going to be another one
Oh yeah
Coming out with me and my son real quickly it's called importing
Generational blessings from the court of Heaven
A lot of times we talked about doing all that.
The Devil's Due
But there are legal things that are hanging in the spirit world that we can grab hold up and
Generational blessings and party decorations
Show
Broke out the gifts of tongues and boys it a good book
You can kind of get the idea of why this guy can't keep a secret
That is
Hilariously sit there are legal things you can
Can do in the spirit world if you want to avoid the generational death tax
In the spirit Court obviously I don't want to have to pay
Taxes on the money that I want to leave by the blessing
Absolutely
You don't you don't want God taking 16
Pics of your blessings
Here's the number one problem I have I swear to you
If I was a religious person
That wouldn't
Furiate me
So much
Just because
If you are
Getting me to live through this
To Heaven you're telling me that when I get to heaven
It's vision
You have to have
The calm down
Because again
It's not about like when you died
I understand how that judgment
In court saying it right
Seems like it's when you died
That's probably
Only part of it
It's happening now
Okay it's like everyday
Alright everyday to open 24/7 rab5 and you can go to them
Deal with the devil for all the wrongs we done
Take him to court for suing that fiddle contest
For cheating
That was a Goldendoodle
So we recently learned that Alex
Is that covid
Multiple times
And his entire staff
Got over it
It seems like
Had some troubles on that for
Front to the Holy Spirit
Quickening made
Pray
Our son Ricky
He's been through he's been
Is
Is been down a little bit
Oh yeah and I'm in bed
Physically ill
Oh yeah yeah covid I already told everybody on TV
Everything
The meaning he had it bad
Previous episode
Like you realize we're not
Doing that
We're not saying that
Pretended something else going to have to take
You to a quart
What is the notice to is that Lori is really coming into her
I don't know if
The time since
That guy you know
Stroke engine
Step up I think that she has a lot more personality
Then when I was watching
The show before
Confidence
Nice to be able to like have her own identity I can applaud that a little
There's episode you know the the old boss
Got to step aside and let the Youngblood takeover otherwise
Just going to go out of business
I still don't
G-great ansioso
Insist on referring
Jim is Jim Bakker
Call Babe
Really weird
Dahlia conversation we've had our Fair
Robert Henderson recently spoke
Status conference
It's called the appendix
Costco Fire Conference
Just about to go
Spirit
Together to Revival
AllShare the Revival
Now there's a reason
But they had him come
Open
The entire concert
Oh yeah yeah
Treveri
There's a lot of young Revival
That are rising up across
Destination
And I mean Revival services are breaking out in tremendous ways
But the whole issue
Was to
What's 2
Grab hold of Pentecostal fire so the week
Revival come
To the nation of America
What I did my part what I did was they wanted me to open the conference
Imprison us in
That we might
Step into the courts of Heaven
Everything
Done in that conference could
Speak in the courts of Heaven
And that God on the basis of that testimony
Could render a judgment that would let his glory come to the yard
Because it needed things to be on the record
In the court of Heaven
Answer like you need you need an official
Like
A barrister a lawyer
We've moved when I was growing up there was that there's that paradox
School question of like
Good God who can do everything create a mountain that he can't move
Message just like
Look
If you don't open the court
God can't hear you
Or he can choose to hear you or not
God has a lot of weird rules how so happen to be ones that maybe I created
This thought is coming too late cuz we're in the middle of recording this episode but I really should have called the opening arguments
Guys
Deals in the car
Give me the standing of the Heavenly law
In the courts of Heaven
What's the statute of limitation
If it's a dinner if it's Eternal how long do I go
Jim wants a little bit of an explainer
We all do
This
I'm going to do a lot more look
This guy because he seems like a tip of an iceberg
On the Sanders.
But the others new listeners new viewers Maybe
Chocolate
Can you explain how we
I need to be able to enter the
The courts of Heaven
Run again
We never get tired of hearing
The courts of Heaven that
We're talking about
What you do
Just keep getting I have my own show on your network
You heard
Teachers a little bitty piece of the court of Heaven
He has a show on Jim's Network
There's just all about the court of Heaven all right when you watch that show and you're going to
Can I get a law degree
Alright
Not
Not a joke
Honest-to-god pitch
Nightcore.
Love it
I would like a giant bailiff
To take care of
Baby
I think
There is a very good
I will be watching
The s*** out of this year
Is it anything like it seems like it would be
That sounds amazing
Pizza Little Bitty Pretty part of Gotham
Little bit
About
Paris
Just a lovely lovely little
Teaser for everyday what's your daily Court Of Heaven
There's a little bit of that little bit of Education about the court of Heaven
And that he talked about also testimonials things that people have written into him about
Love that s***
Of course people are amazing
Mini testimony
Out of the Court
I just got a testimony this morning
I'm someone in England
Who was in a coma or in a whatever state they were in
With covid
And while they was covid they were in the court of Heaven they knew nothing about the quarterback
Against
And they began while they were in the court of Heaven while they're in this state
Answer that
Case they got completely well
When they got back and started sharing their testimony
Someone said have you heard of Robert Henderson in the teaching on the port of Heaven they said no
And I said
Go to email everything you say is real
Wow I got deal from covid-19 the court of Evan
Telling people is real
Wow wow
Toilet bowl
Spectacular fireworks
Yeah
Did you hear a good deviled egg
You hear about Robert Half
Take care of the Courts
No implication or insinuation that you need a lawyer
You can represent yourself
Thought I would assume that God would provide a lawyer for you on the bench
God's got the judge
I mean but yeah but
It's so it got is also the lawyers in
The it got is also saying the Triune
Why is there a tory
Jordan
I regret that you lost your s*** so much of that last clip because that wasn't the one that I thought was
Going to be
It's going to get bad
It's going to get it was where I was like
Definite Mike down for this
I like a clip that turns into a club because I have to put the bike that sometimes our unexpected a little bit
But this one holyshit
Plays a trailer
Seems absolutely like it's a joke
I have
Almost no ability to believe is a serious
This is a trailer from his show so let's roll that and then we'll talk
Divine restraining order restraining order
In behalf of us
In our family
You didn't notice what this Widow said
Estes4me
So she was saying I want the
I don't want to just be free from judgement
I want the devil judge and I want
What he stole from me God did not only vindicate
Exactly like a lawyer commercial
Exactly what that sounded like sounded like some late-night have you been injured
Are you injured
Have you been injured by the devil you're not the only one doing the class action lawsuit
I've got Jesus Ophelia Loma
I cannot believe
You can get putative damages what is that count for
What is that code for
I get the joke
Before but I was Jeff who gives a s***
Let's get those old son's back
Look the court can't do anything about that
Those new kids are good enough
I like the idea that there's punitive
Images and like that that is what happened
The story of Jobe what I learned from Jobe was not
Don't question
God he'll just f*** with you for no reason who are you to say s***
You got to take the devil the devil Courtright
Because that's the only place you can get Jeff
Sky
This is this is so weird
I think it probably goes without saying but it one point in this
He does that he's not a big research guy
Feeling it out
I just kind of like a / 5
Like I've watched
Really
Ridiculous stuff
On Jim Bakker
Like I've seen some swings for the fences
Booking Mike lindell's been on Hellyeah
The Christian world
Outrage
Just we've talked about
What's her name Paula white-cain
Batshit even even
Like a lot of these Prosperity Gospel people like
Bay
Healing
Comparison
To the guy who's pitching
Heaven Court
Hey just
I'm Blown Away
I'm bi mean
That's that's just
People are so in
Interested to learn about heaven Court
Of course they are
It's not mentioned anywhere in the Bible that is not really
Disgust or anything and honestly
That sounds crazy
Well I should tell you that in this next clip Henderson does give
A scriptural basis
Okay for his believe his beliefs and then also like he explained
How it works
And if you don't quite pick up on what he saying Alex
Daniel 7:10
But anybody that's
Kind of unfamiliar
Best
What are the best
Maybe the best scripture on the cord
Where is Santa
That he seen
Daniel seen all of this activity in the Unseen realm and then it says
And of course
Was seated and the books roll
So what that means is that the books that means
That's stupid that's the place
The cases come out of Princeton
Images used in the ministry has a book in heaven
Okay
It's written because you didn't just dream this ministry up
Now I'm just Ministry originated in heaven Before Time began
16 that before time again
He was written in heaven Before Time Again
So what happens is that God
God comes and he began to reveal what this ministry is supposed to be what it's supposed to do
You take that prophetic weariness and you presented in the court
And you say God
Let
What you said about this ministry come to pass and then
Anything that there's
To touch that
Just like this Onslaught you went through to touch that
You bring that he's a god
This is not about me this is about your purpose
Yeah
Come to pass
Everything is supposed to happen with Cumberbatch and anything that there's the
Asking
From the courts of Heaven
And you're asking for a legal judgment
The purposes of God
Excuse me you took off your glasses using a counselor
I would just like to
2 point outside
Court
Has multiple definition
Oh yeah it does and
So one quart
Could simply be the king's court
Or
Another word for written
A group of people
Surround the king and provide the assistant and it even Beyond
Two biblical translation
And there's a lot of issues where words mean
Multiple things in life
The Aramaic that it comes from in the Book of Daniel
Is a little bit questionable could just mean judgement
Surprising that the King James version would include the word Court
Considering the
Consensus around Wichita
It's dubious at best
He was more of a study guy
Imagine
You could have got to the bottom of this
Get out
Helpful
Here's how it works
Open heaven.
Predetermined
Everything that's going to have
No you can't include that part
Because if you include the part where it's predetermined
Then the rest of it
Nothing everything is predestined
Send in these books
Right so everything that you're going to do that is
Is Meaningful to heaven
Congrats in these books
Sing his
TV station
And weird compound
The beginning of time
Write board
Okay
Sorry
I guess who go to prison was also part
8D
Send my book right into
Jim Bakker gets a silly idea
About what he wants to do like
Add another layer to the compound or whatever
Put in
An ice cream parlor
Forgot permission
We get these ideas is experienced
Does prophecy
We get these prophetic visions
Of what he's going to do with his compound
Predestined in the book
Friends actually getting is a glimpse
Set that book
So if anything stands in the way of him putting up that ice cream shop at Morningside right
Then you got to take it to court
I got to take that trip to court and he's got to get it
Right
Now now and I'm going to throw this out here for you
I'm just going to toss this one why it out I'm just going to break this whole case wide open
Watch yourself counselor if it's predetermined
Okay
Then it doesn't matter if someone tries to get in the way
That is also pretty tutor
All of this is predetermined if it's so predetermined
Not
Happened
Otherwise you're saying that your God has no Act
Willpower
Yeah yeah there's that there's a lot of loose threads
I wonder if you can get a sidebar
In the quarters Hadley
Cell
To the side and be like you realize this guy is
So let's say that something is like you've planned that you've decided is prosthetics
Something comes up against
Set right you've got to go take it to Heaven Court
It doesn't matter
If it's not a prophecy
You're getting hung up on that
Stop that you have to let it go because if you take these things
Escort that are getting in the way and get damages
Once you get a judgement from the Lord then you ask for rest
Duration just like Joe
Lord we want double
Back everything not only what was lost but we walked
Punitive damages
For your pain and suffering
True yes
That my God
He got he got CC everything you because jokes
Even Joe recognize that
Is h a
Scab
Like it
Though
So bizarre
And I don't know if
Jim Bakker really does have
A large enough audience
This is
Dangerous as a belief
Call boy
At least before the internet
You used to have
To sell snake oil
There had to be some oil
This is literally a guy just going like hey man
If you buy my books
And take your
Evil people to court
Then you get
Snake oil
It's really the Steve pieczenik of televangelists wings
It's a big sweater
Yeah
So Jim recently had a prosthetic
North Korea
6/2 main lower steak
Glow sticks
You thinking about putting some
Parking at
Oh boy
English show me every detail
Sidewalks
Walkways around
Things that he wanted here
Things that you wouldn't even think about
The new Studios
I'm going to go ahead and out
Around the perimeter
Of this great
Mountain
Right where the Studio's going to sit in the center
All the way on the edges show me how to
Level this thing out but
2 stories
Parking
Underneath
Out of the weather
For the people that
Live here now
We like people that
Tell
Visit here right
Get me out of the weather you know what I mean
I don't mean to go into my buildings but I saw it last night
That's where am I going to get the money
You got the money honey I got the time
Sleep machine
Dream but you said it
Right now business
A piece of my puzzle that's right
Dream is a prophetic awareness of what God
So you take that
That word into the court
And you say anything that would dare stand on the way of them
Stewart weight loss
In this
Beauty Box
Call Dominic
We could do what was your sister
Yeah that's what this dream of a parking lot God is a prosthetic limb
What's in that
At book that's in
In the courts of Heaven
So anything that would stand in the way of Jim making this parking lot
You know
Junction from the court
Heavenly board deal with zoning
Look what if somebody is like hey
This could be an indigenous burial ground
You can't just let them get away with looking for the crimes of the past
You got to go to court
In with heaven and then he'll give you twice as many people as were in the graves
That works
Possibly I think so
Is there a small claims Heaven Court
I mean this is first grade
Leadership right here
You can't you can't even just say
I think we want to park
It has to be a prophecy even just be like hey I think people could appreciate a parking lot
We don't have enough parking
Ozarks there is winter issues with parking
Inside parking would be advantageous
Record Fender this
Spell prophesied
God
Giraffes of
My yes into that is
F****** Prophecy from God
My time for this
BisMan
I don't know what kind of alike
Deal this Henderson character has good like having his show on the network
Jim selling his books and what have you
But if you ever needed to like claim that he made his money
Right here is where he burns his money
The mayor said one more thing about you
Forgivers your partners
Yes
Partner with you by giving their Finance
They become a part of your break
What I mean by that
Is there is a Kinect
Shin made in the spirit
It allows them to claim for themselves
The same blessing that comes up on Jim Bakker in PTL Network all these kind of things
Because finances make
Connections
In the spirit world
I'm so whenever we when we take our finances and we stole them
We are connected
Dean 222 something
That we literally have a legal right
The claim drawing right
Now what that thousand dollars I just want to say this rsos we have put out there for you
Walmart
Oh baby
You give him
You're bigger money
Special drawing rights on the blessings
Little little boy figure
You give a little piece
It's not trickle down economics
It's not just that
It's a legal right that you have on these blessings
What if
Your maker is doing
By giving him money
Would actually be a detriment
Pliable
I've some things that Jim Bakker in his life today
It's a pretty bad
If you don't
You tell Nate to Jim Bakker you're running a deficit
Yes
You're throwing money
Literally
Spiritual
Soaked
But it turns out as you give a thousand dollars
Haha
Fundraising Cafe topes
You get a very special gift
What that thousand-dollar just don't quit that's OS off
We have Joan Hunters which we love this America blanket we absolutely love this
So you going to Miracle by
Doing another miracle
Does the blanket that says miracles
Dope for a thousand dollars you could have like a couple of other things like a book in a CD sure but
What is a CD
Is this preacher friend of theirs
Speaking the word over very relaxed
Some music
Actually I might listen
LPS with Miracle blanket this friend of theirs so the preacher prays over all of them
A couple of pictures that they show up
Eduardo Velez like Laurie
It's no one else putting the blanket over gym
Lego clones
Christmas carols
The very stage photo
Looks awesome
I am just
You know it's almost like
It's almost
It's so brazen
I'm blue you know you're more likely to be like
There's no way they could get away with that if
If it's not true
That's insane
Equals
Have it like that's banana
Imagine
The dark moments of
Curiosity or doubt
Are really difficult
If you if you
If you don't
Imagine that they know they're f****** around
Let me know that this is
Is a scam
Sincere
I just don't understand how you would ever get out of the moment of Crisis where you're like
No way
It's so so
Silly that it
Has to be all like that
House of Cards is such
Watch that anyting
Even though
Slightest
With of doubt
Would knock the whole thing down immediate
So it has to be
Perfect
Or nothing
Anybody any rates
Thinking person
Checking out that
Trailer for the dudes
Joe
If you're trying to put
Trailer for The Sky show you
Guys this looks
Ridiculous
This is Better Call Saul
Parody of what we're doing
We need to
Let's try and give it a little bit of Gravitas
Let's give
Like an edge to it
It's it's
Awesome show I do I do appreciate that
It does seem like
The Scientology scam
Took all the lessons
It's from like the early revivalist preachers that
You know that the marjos in the like that whole thing
And then they were like
What if we made it even more Brazen and just
Just ask for money and blackmail
Tell people
Jim Baker's like well I mean scientology's got a great scam going but what if we just go even
Crazier
Don't even bother blackmailing people
Jesus freak people out and then
You don't need to pay to get these secrets
These secrets
Are so crazy we can't.
Give them to you
So
The baker family for
You're not wrong I believe
Maybe even before
Lori would like to remind us that
JustBats
Allah people falling away but
Also Harvest
Time
You know we have to always remember that this
It's harvesttime yes there's going to be a great falling away the word says
But it's
A harvest I'm with right here right now
People are getting saved because
Covid is making them know they're not immoral
Edgar realizing we're going to die
We're going to die just causing people
To look at their eternity
Dayton
That's depressing
Stats
Bananas
I shouldn't use that
No
That really I mean there's
This is really funny
That's it.
Really sad that is f*****
That's the danger though of religion
Did you know you can laugh at how stupid all of it is
But then you get a religion
I understand this is a religion
Everybody anybody who has like I don't know a relation
Kinship with a deity or like
You know like had some kind of a belief in
That is not
Something that should be
You necessarily
Like outright
Like wrong or stupid
This is stupid
No this is not what I would say that any kind
Kind of connection you have with eternity
But when you start making up dumb rules
That's when we start talking about religion that I think
Exactly like heaven
Having dislike
Prospective tour
What's covid
You know
Not for nothing
Or a spec
Infidel
Knock knock
For a second
Courts
Can help you with that
Did you know that
Wu said there's a way to receive Divine protection
From the courts of Heaven
What must we do
I believe Joe bazooka
Picture before he went through what he went through
It was a hedge
Around him
As long as it means a little lie a protective restraining order
If you well
It's not some kind of flower tea thing that the devil can't pain-free
It's a legal rendering that says you can't go past that
You can't touch him he's mine
And
That was set in place
Three things happen
No harm could come to joban his house
Accumulation of wealth
And great influence
Because the enemy had no power to devour that
Because he couldn't touch him
Because he was behind a restraining order of God
Fossa
Daughter that is
I guess what we need to do to protect yourself from covid is go to heaven
Concord
So I approve that it's predestined that you're not supposed
And then get a restraining order from
You know I would recommend that Pastor Henry
Carson read a wonderful play by Scotsman
Call Jacob
Much better explained
The point of the book of Jobe
And how to go about interpreta get from an existentialist point of view
I'm sure he's going to put that I will tell you what the point of Jobe was
That there is a
Court system that both God and the devil abide by
As though there were a higher power it would two of them
Yes
Imply that there is haze level of power
Both God and Satan voucher
Right cuz it's a legally binding document
It's just
I didn't expect this
I mean like I just wanted to hear about
Speaking in tongues
That would have been great
Brizard judicial system that exists
Today's
Robert Hutchins on today
The first day is mostly getting off track
Into the courts
I feel edified
That I've learned about it
Pixlr
Something
Play I've been like
Still learn about the
Speaking in tongues
I find that to be something that I'd love to see demonstrated
This is a great scam
One of the best
I would have loved
Spoiler they don't end up
Doing a split
But I thought it might be fun if it's gas
Started doing well you can't do it on command otherwise people will know you're fake
I think this guy can do it on
You can't do it on command because you know in the wrong audio
Someone might say
There's two things that appear to be speaking in tongues
According to this conversation
And
One of them is what we would understand
As being in tongues
Speaking
What could appear to be gibberish he Angels language and then it is given to someone else within the
The Conch
Aggregation
Spread their word
There's that and then there's also like you
I'm speaking sometimes in known languages like where
End up speaking
Does a mother foreign language
So you don't know right
ROM
That's one end of it
But there's another end of it
It's what is Henderson fella
That describes kind of like
It's like praying in tongues okay
And I actually found this
Incredibly fascinating
Because what
He's describing
Is essentially just
Having a mantra
He's just talking about
Meditation with a mantra
So he was in a little bit on this
The truth is if I didn't have the gift
The town's I wouldn't have a prayer
For me parsley
Because
If you have us
Even your artists have you ever
Try to spend any amount of time praying at all is one of the hardest
Best things you'll ever do I remember
Back when Larry Lee was so popular
I was like I started trying to pray for an hour and I thought
It's got to have been 30 minutes
But but the cars I knew because I was filled with the spirit and I could
Speak in tongues
When I did
Deprived
And then out of my prayer to Spirit
Understanding would begin to unlock and I could pray in English and I pray in the spirit some more
Origin of like the challenges of meditation
It is kind of like boring
If you're not used to it to sit
4A in quietness
Miss furlong.
But one of the things that is advantageous about having
Mantra
Is the deer words that don't necessarily mean anything
And your primary language
Is things that I like
A sentence that has a meaning to you if you think that
Then your brain will actively be thinking that
Think or
Warchant repeat something that doesn't have an intrinsic meaning to you
You have a better ability to let your mind
Settle
And let your thoughts
Supposed to
Grabbing onto the thoughts as they happen
Something that
Pretty basic meditation David Lynch
Very similar
Transcendental Meditation
Meditation
It's basically the same thing
Yeah I mean hey you put enough new age
B******* in there
Maybe they'll get a little something out of it and I'll give you some praying in tongues
Is what it is
I just put it in there
Much like meditation
Whenever Henderson needs a little bit of clarity
Yeah he goes and Appraisal
Meditation
If I'm feeling
Discouraged I'm feeling overwhelmed
I can start pregnant spirit and what happens to me
Is all of a sudden it's like
The fall
Claire's
And in a new
Destroys to come
And I move
From
Doubt and fear
Back in the face
I mean that's what happens to me when I pray in the spirit
That don't seem right because
This is what I believe I believe
Tongue
Is an entry
Point
Is the entry point
Did we go through a gate into the supernatural Realms of God
See this is all fun but like if you were if this was like a Hindu person saying this or like
The Buddhist they would be like this is
Heretical
I mean I I do as somebody who is at scratches
Is the time where I be
More active and meditating
Then
Currently
At the moment
I've experienced some of
EBenefits
Are similar
What he saying
That calms
State you can get into
Definitely feel Supernatural X
There's a book
Called
A pilgrims way or the pilgrims way if I recall correctly
And the
Idea behind it is just there's a there's a dude
He's like what does it mean in Thessalonians When God Says pray without ceasing
And then it goes on this journey and talk to a bunch of wise men about it
And ultimately he's just like
Do the prayer should be
Essentially yours
You know the way you breathe in and breathe out
Should have something
To do with
Mindfulness
You know through the the whole crew
Christianity meet those he
To the same place that
Buddhism get
It's too or that Hindu
Gets through with that meditation of
Controlling in a mindful
There's something interesting about that
That's not what they're not even a little bit
Nope nope
Sowell tractor
I was looking for examples of Robert Andrew
I'm talking about like
When he's spoken
And here's here's an example of
And I found this to be
Compelling
You can explain it to people
Experience
Tongue
Oh now I understand
I will never forget I was in a
And I was leaving the primate
We're all praying
And we got through after about an hour
He walks up to me and he says do you know French
Cuz I think
Expansion in Haiti and I said
In the spirit
You would say shoot him
Is it do you know it's just a mess
Heated is French for I love you
You were telling God in
French the French language
I love you every time you would finish whatever it is whatever else you were saying
Yeah that's so amazing you know I've heard that
Story so
Many
I've heard story or similar stories.
Backupify
Thoughts first, is not really
I think the pronunciation
The little bit off
It also is a sound that you might just make
You know like it sounds like something you might do
It also sounds like maybe if you were screaming about how his evil than somebody might hear her
Satan
Took French in high school
Like zit time is more like I like
The door is closer to I love you
I don't know I don't
A cappella
If you were just be-bopping
It's gotten a little bit
You might come up with
Yeah I mean there's no doubt if you've ever been to those like religious experience
Kind of places you know I weigh I've been into a goddamn swear I felt
The Holy Ghost
Westin Southfield
It's the same thing that happens with any large crowd as you
Start to feel the energy
Do you get the same thing at the f****** music
There's there's
Like a collective
Energy
Or whatever
There's a
There's a and experience
So
We get back to praying in tongues
Songs here and we learn
This is how
Our friend Robert came up with
I don't know where
I'm praying in tongues
I'm praying in tongues I'm not having to think about it because you just blowing out of my spirit
But it lets my mind be free
To think about that scripture
I'm praying in tongues and thinking about the and all of a sudden things
Just start unlock
And I start seeing Revelation from that
Scripture
That
Can be life-changing
And that's what happened to the court of
Many other things that the Lords allow me the privilege
To teach
But it but it
Source
My prayer language
So he was eat users basically a meditating
And came up with the idea of Heaven
Courts
And then decided it was a revelation
This is
This is what happened
This is what
When an entire generation grows up
With illegal marijuana
Because if this guy was just
Smoking weed and he had this idea be like
That was a hilarious idea guys this was really great
Let's get something to eat and we will never see
Speakable
I basically run
Don't do that
And he would have friends
Because it's
He's got weed
Emigrate
Yeah but that might be wrong because he's
I mean pretty good
Truth
He's got too comfortable scampi
With the
Right
Leave that morning with him
Myself emotionally have to live with the fact that he is hanging out with
I'm so
Another thing
It's very
Interesting
Within this
Is
The universal
Proof
That we always find
That
Any of these facts
If it movie
Sorry the movie
I said
To meet praying in the spirit
And we're all old enough to remember the old Batman series
When Commissioner Gordon
Pick up the red phone it goes straight to the Batcave
Hey go straight to God
Winona rapture
It is Little Italy is a
Hotline
A hotline
To God
Ithaca bat phone
Seems to imply that other prayers.
Just normal prayers
They go to an answering service
Pretty
Wild you know is that God doesn't always
Check is inbox
Fox first thing in the morning
Correspondences
Stop.
Gmail inbox
I find this
To be a little bit silly
It is
Is it is always funny to me that
Whatever we really get down to all of these weirdos
Is it comparing everything to movies like
If you go back
Back and look at all of the
Culture that they
Compare everything to
It was almost
80% and above made by people that they would despise
Isn't hey you know
Like all of their
Cultural Touchstone
These were made by the very
People they are trying
To destroy now
And they have
No way to figure that out same thing with like Lori wishing to 65 so she could get Medicare
I want to enjoy all the stuff
That you guys make but I don't want to
Yes sir we have one last clip year
Lori asking
If
And that is a
Are these demons
Can I understand it when you speak it
In tongues
Like if you're praying in tongues
Can the demons understand you
So is it true
That when you're praying
Spirit
Praying with your heavenly language
That's going like you were talking about Batman and it goes
R82 godso
Can
The enemy can Satan understand that prayer language
I don't think so
I don't need I don't think
I don't have
Scripture verse for that but he doesn't we speak
With the tongues of men
And of angels
Hey so I would say and if someone told me I agree with this
And when you pray in tongues
You're speaking you could be speaking in a known language
Brighton
Yeah
Or you could be speaking in an or
Language that used to be in the earth is not here anymore
We speak in the tongues of angels
And I tell people I said be very careful about
Criticizing what a tongue sounds like you might be insulting an angel
Don't f*** with the game okay
If someone is speaking in tongues
Don't say that cuz I can
And also really
If one person you remember have you ever heard that
Story about that
King wasn't wearing any clothes
You know that everybody as long as everybody was like yeah he's wearing clothes
What's that assholes like he's not wearing any clothes
He's an a******
You kids are out
Yeah I think
I mean I don't know how where's yone this was but I thought there was literally no chance
That I could resist telling you about heaven
Have a cart
Is it too good
The joy and the Mirth
It's just too good I would like to bring some of that happiness into the world 2
Negate
The negative feelings that I have
How about everybody tweeting
I goddamn stupid Alex Jones meme
Then can
Devil's understand the meme
Probably
Can I record for that meeting
Damages what you like Dan
Is there a jury award
Can I also add this was not at all
Adequately
Disgust
And that's why I need to watch more of
What if you don't
What you want
It's not predestined
Since it's not in the book so there was no prophecy
For you to take.
Is it possible that you go to court and God says
Can you lose a case in heaven
You never really addresses
Now I don't think
It's a good idea to get
Bogged down with all these little nuances
Yeah that you're a good boy
About havenscourt let's
Get in the weeds with the legalese of it
How do you create a god
Perfect
And yet still has to
To go to court
Conceptions about court order
Generally really bogged down
Specific
And technicalities those are the things that like a really
Important to the law
Like to see a little bit more of that what are the major
Precedence
Yeah
Does God respect Brown V. Board of education is there anything that's been overturned it Evans
Got still fine with segregation
Probably
Hotels on Friday
Down the road
Couple days
Until we are back
We have wept
Sunny do its knowledge right.com
But so then I mean
The sex robot
Alex