Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
The altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Jordan is
I'm continuing on with season 32 Survivor I think that there's
Straight up trying to give people
Okay like I have that actually makes me want to watch Survivor
I've been saying since the beginning like
Someone's got to die on the show
And now we get to see him there to it like
Make me a little bit uncomfortable
I don't want to give anything away in case anyone actually wants to
See it but years old
It's not like
You know
There's one episode where there's a challenge and like
People are dropping like flies
Okay
I've watched all the seasons
There's been nothing like this like a couple episodes in
I'm like someone's death
Okay
They have to call an audible
They have to call an audible roast is calling in like
All non-emergency staff to come fan people off
Alright
Not okay
Definitely
Like there's a lot of stuff on that show that appears to be like it's a little bit
But stage
I think people were legitimately freaked out
Spaghetti Pizza it was it was
Anytime there's those reality TV show freak-outs though it's almost always like the task is so mad
Meticulously planned and then it's like
Oops
It's 110° on this day
We're going to go ahead and give it a shot anyways and you're like none of the problem isn't that the thing you guys were planning on doing his
Bad it's that these people are going to die
Of heat exhaustion
They don't have enough water
Physically strenuous for an hour
Hey
That's why I like watching Naked and Afraid cuz when they find themselves in like 120° they're all like
We were just going to lay down today
What today is
You know what
What's remarkable about it is that everybody was
Shockingly chill about it
Like if I were on the show I would be
Furious approach
Sure
I bet you did this you know what I mean is that just a sort of
Blind Trust
Is there a sort of blind Trust of like oh well we're on
On TV there's no way that we
Die you know there's no way that these people would be irresponsible enough to let it
Died of heat exhaustion what I was thinking until this season
Everyone's totally safe it's on TV I understand that there's like venomous creatures at view but like
You know there's people with blow darts of antivenin.
On standby
I am no longer confident that
Someone could
Possibly not
Is there any of them
The day after that they were like that exact same you know I was really confident that we were not going to die no matter what
And now I
Yeah this is Game of Thrones now all of our favorite characters
Could die at any moment I mean like not like
Totally talked too much about this but like
There have been people who have been medically evacuated before
Yeah it's happened in previous Seasons shut light
Whatever
This isn't actually think like
This is killing me this is why I keep going back to Nick and Afraid whenever you talk about Survivor because with a negative
Afraid it's so amazing to me they'll be the will
Medically evacuate people
All the time because you're naked in the middle of a place where you're not supposed to be
Which is why you're terrified
Just injure themselves like nothing
Non-stop but these people are so f******
Crazy that they'll be like
Alright well it's day three in my ankle is 6 times the size of my forehead
I just don't want to go home you know I don't want to tap out
Yeah you see their leg like dangling with a broken f***
Tibia
You know I don't want to tap out
Survivor it's like I have I'm sure they'll take care of it and episode that I just watch
Boys like
Multiple people on the show
Have
Threatening infection
They have cuts that have gotten infected
People summer like I'm sure it's 5
Located where
Dirt is getting it to our moon
But I'm sure it's fine we're going to have to start calling this game green because this is not going well
Responsible
It's actually
I think it's elevated my enjoyment of the shower
Real
Well I mean anything that gets to 32 years old there's a good chance something
He's going to die
Keep it fresh exactly
Damn I think you know what my bright spot is so
Straight from the White Sox Angels game earlier
Sure and then I went to the Angels game last night
He was in person
Yeah
Statuesque sure built like a brick shithouse just an amazing man
He didn't have a good game yesterday
That's strikeouts today
Blah better
244 and then I was so disappointed
Because okay
Baroness / 5 is a
Vine
Friday for a picture
Sadly for the second place the home run hitter in the league over 5 is not a
The reason that you have
To go see him live
And this is something that baseball people with State pattern
Absolutely false
I got to go see.
With weather tonight
One of the things about baseball is that if you're really really good
Like really really good
Then the ball sounds
Front when you hit it like Vlad Guerrero Jr now is the league leader in home runs of 45 and when he gets ahold of
It sounds different
From every other player
Exact
And taking Out to the Ballgame I was really hoping for
2 days into game
Games to get it
But he hit a ball
So f***
Working hard
The crack
Echo throughout the
The crowd unfortunately it was a foul ball
But he hid it so f****** hard Uke
Could hear it
And it was beautiful
I don't know if I
Watched enough baseball to know the distinction in sounds but I ate the sound of a ball getting hit is very satisfying
Satisfying long enough you know you can tell the difference
Between when Barry Bonds hit a homerun and when
Point where I still remember
When I was playing baseball and I was like
Like 70
Team
We were playing in the playoffs
And this team was terrible
And we were terrible also
But this kid
This one kid
Was
Just a
A bigger kids and everybody else
And he couldn't move
Couldn't run
Couldn't do anything
But when he hit that f****** ball
The Sounds workout
My ear like he hid it so well
And he couldn't do anything else and I was like man that guy
We got a bottle of that
The f*** out of here
Steph secondary Brightside for me actually has been watching you so just be a fan
It's kind of fun
There is a reminds me of like a
A more innocent time
I like being able to excitement of going
To see this
Player live
Oh yeah
Some enjoyment out of that so
Thank you it's just hard to believe that there's only one of
There's only one and it's like
I mean
Oh okay
Better and I should talk on Babe Ruth all the time because they only played against white players who gives
The fuk what he did
Just remote
Racist a random Justin Moore statista
Physical standpoint
At Babe Ruth's time
This is people
F****** fighting
Coming off of a war
2 million people in the United States
Maybe a million white people in United States to draw a talent
Right so somebody who can hit and picture
At the same time
Out of a million people
Not
Terribly
Surprising
Scary and unusual but not terribly surprising
Shohei ohtani is 1 out of a billion
Potential people
Secret play
Yeah and no one else can do it
Yeah just
Yeah
Just what
Yeah I get it
So Jordan today we have an episode to do I forgot
Sorry present-day Alex
We are dragging
Back to the Press
September 14th
20 ft drip line
I would love that
Stutter Step
I saw my mother to Hangouts
So we're going to get down to business on this there's some real
Gyms in here slow start but then towards the end may be one of the most
Bizarre Clips I've heard in a long time
And also further evidence that I think
But maybe this is a parody
Okay again. Alex is desperately trying to tell the world I've been joking this whole time
Yeah don't hold me responsible
Get down to business on this before we do let's say hello just walks
Vitality Rob do is never grown so big thank you so much you're now about to go on
Very much Super Mario vitality
Pretty fun what fun
That is for breakfast thank you so much
Thank-yous for exercise
I'm a policy wonk
Unchaste Charisse
Thanks Theresa thank you so much you're in our policy
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
That's like big sexy
Kevin thought that was a regular ass name
Reagan
Everyone
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much they also donated
Nice good Monica donation
Hey what's up to a new member of saline
Up at 8
A b a b
I think so maybe
That's a very short-term adoption
I am not sure if this was just a single be adoption
But there will be an avatar of a
Furby in Saline family
And this is the only be that I will make these with cuz you know I have a war with Abby
I mean is it a truce
Sorathi spider on your or perhaps
It's an uneasy truce some guy
Cuz my brother raise bees and when I went to go see them
I was shocked by how little they paid attention
Come to me and I was not afraid of them at all they went about their business flying around me
Yeah
I'm fine with bees and all the joys elincia the bet
The family
Valencia
This show starts
Slow
First 20 minutes of the show are Alex
Just saying like I use a special report event disappearance
First two whole segment
Artist desk
The same system CNN
All this video coming up so see
Now it's all out in the open
It's just that
Like a little bit of a headline and then long video
Famous newscaster
Compelling hunt
But when he does get back there's something important that he does
When I get up in my head in a little bit worried that he's going to find out about
Auto Show
How do I feel
Property tax
And every now and again we got to re-up
I mean for us to do exactly the show that we're doing
Send archives the shows in Article 2 videos
I don't care
Okay
Alright we're son
That's a worry about that anymore I think we've got one from that's
From 2021
We got at least one from 29th
India pretty sure we've got
Three pattern looks like
Whatever you want to get up
Target
So we got some sad news
014 Larry Nichols okay
Bad news for your hanging out
Playing golf with the California recall
Let's get
The really sad news your butt understand
There's a
Major Ray
Sunshine or or silver lining
In This Cloud
It's going to get people up off their butt
In the midterms now
Only
Is everybody
Really push back and expose what's happening
I talked about this a thousand times again
Fornia isn't really
Blue
Connecticut's not really blue
Vermont's not really blue
Michigan's not really blue
There is such fraud
In States like Pennsylvania and Georgia where they
When we control everything else
Just play ball with us and Taylor's on fraud
So yeah the it's all
It's all cheating
Every election now California is not really blue
So the one thing that I think
Just about everybody
Could have agreed on 5 years ago
California was so thoroughly f****** blue hard never change anything
Twitter Democrat
Everyone would say California just blew and f***
Not anymore
Nevermind never has been in all of the places that are blue states that are blue states are actually not they are all
80% Trump
20%.
Probably that's why we need a fake
Re-election
Yeah it's just
I mean I can't help
But feel like there's a certain amount of like
For this
Community
Democracy has failed
Oh yeah never have an election that is perceived as anything other
Other than complete that
Later on they even talked about like Ron DeSantis winning re-election
And it's like it's not even enough that he won
He should have one more
The fact that he won
And it was closed memes that there was a fat
Okay
All right it is amazing cuz it does make you think like when people see
See that Putin won with 97% of the vote there's a
There's a
Pretty significant percentages that's like
Yeah that's about right
Cuz he's great
Is a strong leader ninety-seven percent of people shoot approval
Yahoo
How to use fake ballots
Of course naturally
Just like you know 22
The balance
Through flooding provisional balancing
Flooding mail-in ballot
That use Excuse of K
11 months ago
2020 election
Two-plus weeks
Of these balance
Course they had a bunch held back behind
Republicans
Take a percentage
40 30%
Computerized
Fill out the balance
Pennsylvania
Postal workers
Unfolded all bubbletron
With only the race
Manforce
Also
Here it is you knew it was coming
You knew it was coming early so you knew this Ark
Would you consider the Democrats have
Taken
Taken isn't
Interesting word to describe the way the Democrats have
Power in the
Send it yeah
Eat some
Compelling and I know that it's going to be exactly what Alex is after every
Single action
Ever again
So there were some things that came out of the California recall
Things that we reported that we're
Maybe slightly suspicious chair
Here's one of them
California
Miller shooting videos
When workers go sorry
Yeah she's already voted here's a provisional it'll be counted in a week that one can
I don't think that they said this is a provisional ballot that it won't be counted in a week
That makes up a weird thing to say
A couple of reports
That you can find of people who found out the pay or were listed as having already voted
When they showed up
Voting place
And they got provisional ballots and that's something that happens because
Computers
Do you have a job where Computing errors happened to happen sometimes may happen
I don't want to stay over like
Entire James
Running intellect
You're going to have
Things like this
Panda you have is actually kind of argument that things are working cuz there's a back-up plan.
Supervision
Are there for this specific reason
It does feel a lot like
These people are acting like shity patrons at a bar and the waiter is like
Constantly trying to help this like
Look I'm so sorry I'm so sorry we just made a mistake in the kitchen here I'm going to go back up
Take 2 seconds here we go go to fix it
And they throw the meal away and they like
You know
So looking at understand that there's so much evidence
Of
Like you know
I can Pennsylvania
Trump
Huge crowds
No
Huge crowd
Just but that's not annoying
Losers
Is only one postal worker that went public and goes
Another state
Disrespect something was supposed to
Supposed to do
He looks in the damn thing just what's in the box and see what it is
Call balance
Alex's
Conflating store
He's here what actually happened was that there was a postal worker named Richard
Who came forward after the election
Pennsylvania claiming that he quote
Overheard the local postmaster discussing plans to backdate ballots received after they November 3rd vote
And pass them off to election officials as a
Legitimately
Hopkins
Glam through project Veritas and it gained a lot of traction in the right-wing dum dum media is evidence of widespread voter fraud
Naturally an investigation of these claims was launched and at that point
Hopkins recanted his allegations
Because when there's an
Investigation the stakes are real whenever you might get in trouble
When you're just talking s***
James O'Keefe there's no rules or Consequences so you can just say whatever you want
In an interview with the
Navigation Hopkin
Quote revised his initial claims event
Simply stating that he had not
Heard a conversation about balance
At all
Rather he saw the postmaster and supervisor having a discussion and assumed it was about fraudulent backdated
Great
Some good stuff literally that's all that
This dude saw two people having a conversation and he decided to make up a story about what they were talking about which was then reported by James
Luke even has proof of election meddling
When sincere people try to look into the claims and it becomes clear that Hopkins going to be a big trouble if he makes
False allegations against people
Arkansas claim
But there's no retraction of the story by the right way
Dum dum media
You don't put out a report where they discussed how they were wrong and they got that information
James O'Keefe doesn't have to give back all the money he fundraise off pushing this fake story
And you can see now even in 2021 Alex is still using the basic details of this story while embellishing a ton of it
The basically claim
The California recall must have also been stolen
This is the state of work and effort that goes into the media sphere that Alex is apart of
None of these people are serious about the information they present
Because if they were
Three-quarters of their show would just be them having
The correct things
It would just be wall-to-wall correction
They don't give a fuk
Yeah I know I mean if if anything we're going to have been done about this problem
Then the three million voters
Tweet
From the 2016 election where is like 3 million illegals voted in this election
And it's just some a****** tweeting and then it turned into a national story somebody would have done something about it then
Shirley
And if it didn't happen then
Who gives a f***
Yeah
Not not all of Alex's coverage
On this side this episode
High-minded politics
Some of it is getting down into the nitty-gritty sure some of it is getting down into the culture issues that matter
The culture issues yeah the matter
Met Gala
What's happening in California
$50,000 a plate Hollywood Gala
Toptenz
Thousand
Is that how you're going to grow up that dress
On the Democrats Richard politicians
Latino
Mulatto women
What type of
Hello boy oh boy
Alicia
Yeah I mean
I guess this is probably the reaction
AOC might have expected from someone like Alex
Alex is the one that looks like an ass all here
I think so
And it's not like she's only wearing dresses with statements on them to do so legislator
They're doing a lot of that
Stop
Well just like
If she were just a figure that only existed to
To do publicity stunts
I would kind of understand the outrage
Instead
She's a legislator who is getting
Some other things done
And then also doing this to drive people like Alex crazy and make him end up saying things like
Yeah yeah I mean it doesn't
Seem like a right-wing media
Picks up all those stories where it's like a OC's office during flood goes out around
Call of individuals tries and helps them get to safety
Too much of that is to say that like obviously
She's still a politician
She still has
No blind spots and things
Things that are not ideal
About her but you know
Caricature that
Painted baby boy Galaxy
Funny
It's pretty funny
So Alex
You know what
Things that he is super against
Is like
World government
Tyranny
Things that I think is
Salient about that is
Like you know
Colonialism
To our food is bad
Because you know what is world government
Other than colonialism over every
Once it becomes a world government than nothing
Well
I know that Alex is he's not a fan
Wait. Okay
PC cases
200 Ferraris for their son
25 Jets including jumbo jet
15 Jets
Publix
Madison
When there was Europeans
Areas of Africa
Wanda they had a Christian minority of black Nonono Nonono
The build a civilization
Collapsed amazing
You can't really make it much clearer than that Alex is super into apartheid and colonialism
Also with Alex read any books at all they were put out by the John Birch Society he might have understanding of the Rwanda genocide
Poseidon the underlying dynamics that we're at play there
We've gone over this in-depth another episode but the issue is not that one group with Christian and prosperous of the UN paid the
The other animus group two killed
It is far more to do with cultural tensions going back to the roots of Belgian colonialism in the country
And how they chose
The tootsie is the ethnic group that that a trusted with
With power though the Hutu represented the vast
Majority of the population
They're all kinds of Dynamics
They grew out of that
What Alex is doing a genocide revisionism
I'm going to be every bit as offensive is when he makes up nonsense about WWII
Like legit
This dude
Believable
That is kind of like
Like even in his store UK
You can see the outline of
The truth where he's like
You know whether they didn't have anything in the white people came over they had electricity and then the white people left in there they didn't
Have anything you like
Well then maybe the story is the white people showed up and stole everything and then left
With it
What are the other things that you like I don't think a lot of people understand is that like
The John Birch
Society an anti-communist types
Like they
They were very into
South African apartheid
Is the proving
It was them it was them looking at
Like
If this work
Then we can take
Global
That's what the birchers looked at the South
Freaking apartheid
Afrikaners as it's like
If we can conquer this place and pick it up white nationalist Utopia
Then guess what we can take the
Global whether or not it was proof-of-concept or not it was
Very much
A convenient way to frame
Support for apartheid as actually opposition to communist
Ideas have trickled down to Alex's
Like his positions in the present day
Sure that is
Somebody I don't think you can understand the
No
I agree with you
So there's a war against the family
Australian with your black or white
I was thinking about this
What I do
I don't know if I do this with a
Blast
Today
I have
Pacheco soda water they're also likely
Troy
Crave alcohol
Coffee
About it
What what allows me to stop
Wow
But Evans on real
To take some supplements and Topo Chico on air
Somehow he just
Defies deflects
And avoids his alcoholism
In-N-Out
Pivot
Selling one of his b*******
Supplement this could be really big for the
Dinner with the community of Alcoholics
All they need is some Topo Chico and Alex
This is a curb your addiction is a little bit like
Senegal
I'm f****** intervention for an Avon salesman's alcoholism and then everybody leaves with Avon
The person goes
Metaphor
Complaints about stress
Obviously
Caldwell
She said tax the rich and that's a
Statement that could not be more fun again
But there's other there other celebrities that are doing the Lord's work
Work that are doing
And far more
Nicki Minaj
Oh God
These these prions that the vaccine create
So first of all Nicki Minaj's Queen had to do with our cousin's friend
Men's balls which were not trunk but allegedly became swollen
This friend allegedly lived in Trinidad and because Nicki Minaj has over 22 million followers on Twitter
Any sort two pieces of straight information can have serious ramifications on public opinion
The health minister of Trinidad and Tobago came out and said the
This was not true
Terrence Dale senior quote
One of the reasons why we cannot respond yesterday in real time to miss Minaj is that we had to check and make sure that what
What you was claiming was either true or false
Unfortunately we wasted so much time yesterday running down this false claim
This story is one of those
Few times are you like
Oh that's right
We rate
We're not human being
We're just Apes we got to stop pretending that we are any different from a Capuchin
Looking at the strongest member drive going over
It was a bit of a bummer
Kind of sad to see Alex running with this but I saw that Tucker was also running
Nicki Minaj's cousin's friend
I just
I mean it's Saturday I think the Tucker covered it
Cuz he's on TV
Alex
Like whatever
He has no standards
Tucker used to he should at least be pretending to be more seriously
Somebody should have been added the
Meeting being like week
Tucker Carlson
Talk about Nicki Minaj
Is fake friends cousin
Balls cousin's friend
Whatever we can't do this
She's going to wear this can't happen
And I no longer like super bass turns out
Fat buddy going to do
There are some side effects
From the back saying that Alex is going to talk about very responsible
Reuters don't show these folks on Twitter hard inflammation ever coming 19 shots higher-than-expected
Article from the end of
Juno was originally reported on Riders
There's a study that was done they found a higher-than-expected rate of hard inflammation among vaccinated military members
That's definitely concerned but also it's important to not let this be blown too far out of proportion
That study involved 36,000 military members and there were only twenty-three cases of hardened
Inflammation in the general population you'd expect eight cases among otherwise normally healthy
Free People
Is it in Port
Something for scientist
The track and learn more about butt
Not the sort of red flag that Alex is trying to make it out to
He also is completely making up that part about the mass deaths
They're really 23 people in the study who had this inflammation and according to the very Reuters article that Alex is using as his prime
Resource
All of the patients had recovered or were recovering from myocarditis
And inflammation of the heart
He's just a total liar
Jamaican bulshit up
Yeah that sounds like you're right on the other hand
And maybe
All of those military people are dead
And have been cloned
As we know that they can do with Joe Biden and or Jim Carrey's yeah I think it's this
Still up in the air now the real question is how they balls
I do love living in a world now where we're just
We're just talking about balls on TV
I grew up
Bruno Home Improvement times
Use eight euphemisms before they could even get to a joke about a dick while we're back on the
The ball talk
Touchback on Survivor for a second every now and again like every other season.
So are you up to stand on like a little
Block
Plate
MMA ball on it
They can roll off the balance
Like a f****** survivor's a balance
Some challenge
Jeff Probst
Goes way too far with the this person's balls are moving jokes
It's incest
He makes a meal out of it it almost like you can tell he's looking forward to that challenge so you can talk about people
Every year it's like listen I'm going to take the balls at
And I'm going to run with it on the Run
Buddy you got to get your balls and check
Goddamn
But never bad times map
Never bedtime so Gaston this episode
And
I think
If you actually are paying attention to the suffix and Alex
Augusta Ave
Alfie Oakes he's that guy who runs the mask free grocery store in Florida
What are you doing anyway he's on and turns out he's a big fan of Mike lindell's
What what they've done it's a Sal lynskey
Where are they
Made my quindell seem like he's some kind of
Tinfoil hat
Very much
Provable
But
To fly privately fly
Legislator in
The Symposium and guess what nobody would do it they said
Spanish song
It's too partisan I guess now the truth is to
Become too partisan that was them being polite
I don't think anyone's making my Glendale look nuts
He's doing that himself
Is it is fun whenever they watch Mike Lindell
In like a
Neutral situation you know they don't have somebody like Alex
Tucker talking over and being like
What's going on they just let him go
And then the conservative see him the way we do
And they're like well obviously somebody's doing this
If they have
Conspiracy
That I think he is that I'm watching right now
Alright then that means that Alex and Tucker Carlson are both
Absolutely f****** in
Well it's Saul Alinsky
Here's the deal
Alex and these Folk
I don't
Fox anchor actually watch
Sing any uninterrupted
Long chunks
Of Mike Lindell trying to
Explain
You find out he was full of s*** right
Alex's on the payroll
It's
All bets are off with him
And then other people are just getting like
Glimpses of
What is reported on like is symposium or these things in
And yeah you can
Choose to like okay if it's in the mainstream media at all must be in attack you must have actually said something real
Yeah it's going on here
Also I have decided that I'm going
To create something called the
Lynn delameter
And that is that if you
It now
Are supporting Mike Lindell
You're on the payroll or your approval
Okay that's that's
Be the sort of line I like steak the Mendoza Line
That's what separates
You're a True Believer or getting paid right
Anybody who can
Can think for themselves has left that train
If you do good
That went away a long time ago
Alfie's got a lot of
Employees
For his store
They're all on Ivermectin
But I mean like summer
Itsec
I like maybe
But maybe a lot I don't know some of them might have gotten seriously sick
Every single
Over the last year-and-a-half
We might have had 16 employees that
Enter back to work in 5 days
3202 weeks
Hospital
Almost
The murdered in the hospital right back with Alby Hobbs responsible to report on what they would have done if your dad
Did something different done this they would have killed them
Got sick
From one of these
Sick employees I mean it's not not possible
But Noel so by the way she is doing
No contact racing at all on these
Thousands of people
Who work there
Who knows how many of them may have been
Asymptomatic carrying it
You have a very good chance
This is why do someday
I don't understand how
These people
Seem to think that they're making their case
When is it like no you just
Are caring about the actual details of him
I don't talk to them I make more money than them and then I fire them whatever they bother me and some of them
Summer sick and some of them are
What do I care
The world is
Fine for me
I don't know about like a people that they may have enacted or their grandparents
His dad was sick one time but I didn't care about it
Why do I care now please
You might be asking yourself what's it all about Alfie
I mean obviously it's the globalist trying to exterminate the human race
He wanted to come on Alex's show cuz he has a very
Rhonda saint
Governor
Florida
Nightmare cycle
Ronnie
He's apparently coming to do
Promotional
Fundraising event at Alfie store he is
Or 2 or something
Alright alright
But
Alfie needs an emergency meeting with Ron DeSantis
Can't wait
Until the in-store
It's Alex has been enlisted
To try and get the audience to harass Ron DeSantis
Got a plan he needs to talk
Governor Ron DeSantis
GOG
MyFlorida
Tom
Or text USA 28
50 108
USA 280
08 31
Get the number to Santa to me
Meet with Alby
Wow I don't know another meeting why do you need to go on Alex's show and
It almost send
Also I think
I don't know a whole lot about campaign Finance
Total expert in the
This seems
Dicey
What do people do when they call these numbers or go to this website what do they do
If there's a way to put
Email cross the screen I'm begging every person that watches did you send him an email
If they have this meeting with Alfie
I'm going to make a huge cock
Contribution weather at the end of the meeting
Decides
You know to believe what we say but all I want is two hours with the experts they're going to be with me
Because he's a smart man
After 2 hours I believe that he'll realize
The amount of fraud that happened even here in Florida
And that he's boarded-up he's the one man that is bold enough
In history will be talkin about Ron DeSantis
200 years ago like like we are founding fathers
Receiving
Republic
Yikes
Let's put the clock up countdown to 12 santosuossos going to cancel that event
That's the first clock
Yeah
I mean I know that there's a bit of back scratching that goes on in the world of Chihuahua picture
Think if the register to be like
What's it called evil
No
A lobbyist
That's it
I don't think I said different things
Yeah I think you have to register to be a lobbyist which is kind of what he seems you doing
It's that thing that on also if you're if you're a foreign lobbyist
Just for like a different country you have to register it that thing that most of our Congress without registering
Speaking of that
Michael Flynn is also working with Alfie he's going to be in that meeting
If he gets with Ron DeSantis
Yeah I love it
I love it
Find this confusing
I find this very confusing because we have a situation where Alfie ostensibly is like really good friends
Doesn't
At the same time
Yvette is really important thing you need to tell him there's no other way for this to happen
Then for him to go on Infowars and have the audience
Harass
DeSantis is office
I'm going to I'm just going to go out and say it the
The way that I've always
Successfully lobbied
Going on at weird show and telling people to send s*** tons of
Emails this is the behavior of someone who
I feel dumb
Don't have much access
But I could be wrong if you have to say the quiet part loud and just be like
I'm going to give you money
Yeah talk to me
That's the idea
Wink it's not conditional on you believe in God
This money
Free money I just need to speak to you very quick
You will be the room for a few hours
Now if you sit through the whole 2 hours
You will get a free bottle of tequila and a two-day three-night stay at the timeshare
Talking thing
Yeah anyway what Alfie needs
Is Vicki
He needs
The scientists stand up
Because then we can overturn
The 2020 election or something
We can prove fraud or something sure
I mean
A lot of time with Michael and I happen to believe
Most of everything that he saying
At least let one stay
Verify okay
Nobody's everyone's running the other way because they like I said we've done the Salton Sea
Tacticon Mike Lindell to make him seem crazy
No one's done any
Tactics
That's what he's basically doing here is demanding people proven negative
So you want to stay
To prove that there was no fraud and that'll satisfy
Google what's Mike lindell's so crazy then why won't some stuff
Completely prune negative
That's a losing game
And even if some state were to somehow
Forensically prove literally every vote was
Was perfect and wonderful
Well yeah that's the one state that they had everything run smoothly and in order to serve as a distraction from the other
States with that with that
Goalpost would just move that nonsense every time it's not
Anybody should take seriously the real argument is had the moment he said I believe most of everything Mike lindell's
Elsa and you said wait most of
Why is your first instinct most parks
Yeah what is Mike Lindell saying that even you don't believe me
You said most of you were just trying to sound saying haha
So Alex
Gets back to his army vaccine study story that he is continuing to fraudulently report
I've got a Reuters study here Reuters article about the Pentagon
Over a million truths
Swelling
This is Josef Mengele
We Are The Twilight Zone here
Again that is a lie about a article from the end of June
Yeah
The great reset is here
Alright
Shut up shut the f****** shut the fuk up I see that face I see that look on
Your face that says
Non-sequitur your way out of that
That's near the Great
Gregory set the roof
Any proof
I don't know you're laughing either give me that look that I was well
I happen to have fur
Air filtration supplement
To the textiles are still plenty of
Back in February
Broken
Problem
The pool heater broke
Broke
Flooded it it's all wrong I'm trying to sell my house
Wigs and no one has
Close to it
All breaking down the great reset
Yeah see proof
Alex can't fix his pool
If you can't get
You know the countries broken down
I also guarantee you cut do you know who's the last person to say that was
F****** Mero buddy that's how you know that the truth is being
Unspoken it's Alex and Nero the only two people
When they needed pool tiles in the whole country
We will always remember when class Schwab
Fiddled while Alex's pool went unfix
F****** I mean
Look at that white people problems we've moved on from that mean but God
Damn bitching about
Pool tile is about as close as it gets to
I've found a number of places you can buy a pool tiles
You can get overnight I was going to record a phone call with a
Will a Line in the Sand what we can put up with what we can
Sure
That's that's
Normal
I suppose
Alfie
You have a Line in the Sand
Unfortunately this sand
Is the
Murdering other p
People sand
The line
You know where it's okay to start murdering other people already in the sand
It's coming still but it's there is a specific line
And it's fast approaching
If we don't stop this if it
The one in the sand
Is 20-22 if they steal if they are successful in stealing the 2022 election it's only a year
It's game over it's going time there's not going to be talking to anymore
Handshakes and Pen deals
It's going to be it's going to be
I don't want that to happen I'm not one of these guys
I want to stop at before albino outside the Constitution said everybody was $600
Fourth Amendment
It's a little bit
Off the beaten path Road
I'll be saying it
It's gun time yeah
That's that's intense
You know if you're if you're the type of person who doesn't want
To use gun
Then why does it
It seemed like
Your solution to every time you don't get what you want is gone
And it's a constant like whenever you're not getting your way at the concert if I don't get my way soon it will be gone bad
Time
Yeah it kind of
It kind of makes me feel like maybe you're not being very sincere about not wanting
It's begun time you kind of just one
Begun time
Waiting for everyone else
To give you the permission
To do what you know is morally wrong
So Alfie takes off he's got two more
Employees to put at risk
So he can't tell stay on the phone all day
News
Is this this little nugget about General milley
How is a traitor
But wow Moore's coming out turns out was A5 I one of the quote on Alliance Nations it picked
Sing
Whatever you do will call you will weigh
Launch nuclear weapons at us whatever
This is so insane
Peebles
Military over their leadership
And resulted in a
5i
Rocket of what the f
I don't know all the details of everything that was discussed
Between General million is CounterPoint
Is kind of silly
Go Dukas lysing the story
I'm not a full expert on
These kinds of issues but I can kind of see how that might be a really inappropriate thing for him to have done
You know in terms of chain-of-command I can see that being
Kind of
Could get in trouble for sure
At the same time
I was alive then and I remember how
Belligerent
Trump was being
The idea of
Engaging in a little bit of diplomacy
Maybe maybe
McDonald Longway
I mean there's
That and then there's
Is Jaime Lannister's way
So like
I've I mean I I suppose
It's better that he
Just made a phone call instead of
Stabbing the Mad King as though
Brownsburg
I think there was a better way maybe well icing
His favor is you know this was an act that was meant
Encourage stability
And to reinforce
To China that
There is stability
You know like
This rhetoric is not nothing we're not going to do nuts yet we're not going to war with you
Like a reasonable phone call you would make to a friend Elena stairway would not
Encourage stability would work against the goals that Millions have for their
So Alex keeps hitting on this Army study
He keeps missing
Reporting it
Don't let this be you talk about your sister or brother or you
Everybody
Allexa cannot
Deal with this Army study accurately
Nighteye
Can't do it
I feel like he's playing with fire there just because
The military is going to be fine
And they're not going anywhere
So it's hard to like
Maintain.
What story do you know what I mean like
I guess
It's not going to be able to continue and I have people like 2,000 for that they were all getting chipped
That's fair
The stakes are low that's fair I was just Thinkin o if you're going to say that the military is all going to die
Is your I imagine your audience has
At least some
I mean I would I would think demographically
Alex is audience would have
Fewer Degrees of Separation
In from military members
You know what I'm saying like I don't know anybody personally but I imagine that they
Closer table to example
A military person would like be like right now
Bears
Alex has a pool to fix
Fair enough
Alex's Mister police state
Police state
Hate hate
Play 2000 have graded was it apart at least eight
Rise of the Machines
He's made a lot of films
The biggest things that he would yell about is
Is the police state
Courtney know his entire career
That makes me
Think that
He's the kind of person who would be in favor of body cams on police
Because it wouldn't
Accountability for the police state in order to make sure that they don't go over
Because it seems like one of the only ways that you could make sure there was accountability is if there were ways
Is 2nd
Viewing wow
But guess what
What
Body cams
Discretion
Good folks
No they're not
The enemy uses
Okay
You mean everything
I don't even know I swear I don't think these people know what they support
Today
The day-to-day Thin Blue Line police are the most important people in the world flags
Next day
Tapas says that a right-winger did something
Is sjw cops
Murder a protester
Baby Topsy Turvy protect we need to support them if you fire this person we will riot
Cops arrest a sovereign citizen
My God
It seems it seems very
Bizarre to me like
Kind of discretion
They were talking about here
Body cams would be relevant in terms of is not like
Whether you get a ticket or not
Is never going to be the subject of a body camera view
It's killing people
Important
It's wet
I don't know I think this is really dumb. There's just the story going around on Twitter today
Showing the the like
I believe she won a like three million dollar judgment or something against the cops
Because they
Brits are out of her car
Grab their child and then did a photo op with her
Right
And somebody was just
Juxtaposing that
Story
With the immediate aftermath that the LA Times put out
Whoever it was
With that picture of them doing the photo op like
Hero cop save everybody a mediately juxtaposed with three years later
3 million-dollar judgement against
The cops being evil nobody's going
Like fuk all of these people
Because yeah
Bucked up
We do anybody
But
In Canada
There's terrible news
Covid restrictions
Control
The Walmart
Once
Sacred
Tim Hortons
Right
Now
You need a vaccine to enter
There's another one
Walmart
So that thing that Alex's reading isn't real
That was a hoax
Facebook post that was going around the claim
Do you need proof of vaccination order shop at Walmarts in Canada
They would realize that their bread-and-butter is
Peopleshare
Totally not fake
I totally totally worth reporting
Yes. I reached out to Walmart instead quote customers do not have to
To show proof of vaccinations to shop at our stores
We continue to work with governments across the country and are following
Required
Even the official verified Walmart Canada Twitter account posted that this mean that was going around was not real
The standard of evidence or something that Alex is going to report on air is proof of the mark of the beast being upon us is just something he saw in
Random hoax face
This is pathetic
The level of work he's doing it
I mean
At least at least with the court of Heaven you can laugh
Real hard at the just
It's nonsensical
Felix's just doing a
Same difference I saw it
I got a chain email let me report on
I do like the image of
My
When I was growing up that Walmart greeter
Nice little old woman 5 ft 2
Ish
Just really should just shambling around with the
The car it's not really doing
I imagine her now
Happened to stay at the Gateway Bay like
Can I have proof of vaccination before you enter and
How long would you survive that long
Because they were killed and replaced with a
Sagano know that would work
Yeah that's how we do it that would
I mean this was a hoax Facebook
Proposed that Alex was real
Was pretending was real in order for him to use it as fodder for his reporting
He doesn't do much better with his neck story
What
P52 Mustang or whatever it is you're pulling trigger
Hospital
Mongolia
Red
Covid-19 graph
Play start the shots
2 weeks later
This is from the UN from John Hopkins from a mall
Oh it's so amazing
Is reporting based on a grassy found on a random
A person's Twitter account
In the video
On the overhead camera that Alex is using you can literally see that he just has a printout of this dude's Queen
He has done no work
Past that
It's just a Twitter account to the guy's name is Seguin on Weiss
Oh well I mean I try
Rusty Edelweiss
Itself it's just
Statistical misrepresentation
Notice anywhere as those statistics would look at that chip twice and it's enough for Alex to report his bombshell info on his show
Like
I can't stress this enough he shows f***
Looking pathetic like this is the kind of thing
That he he takes as like all I got it
Get this on are the people must know about this tweet
Like he might as well just
Be doing a Roundup shows like
Stupid s*** his friends found on social media passed along to him
That Inspire ramps
Yeah but with more is the devil
Cliff Tompkins
Racist
Yeah
And I'm looking at this grass that he found on Twitter he's just blown away
Numbers
Read text
So the reason the numbers me is because the person who made this graph
Specifically designed the scale of the two lions so they would
Each space on the scale of the total vaccinations lines representative of 500,000 vaccinations where is the equivalent space
Show me total covid deaths scale represent
Actually it's not clear immediately if you look at it what eat
Space represents
Staff so they are each labeled on the vaccination side
But the scale is so disordered on the death scale that it's really difficult to assess how the graph
Is set up just from a first plant
In order to make the dataset appear to match up this dude had to make the scale
Exactly what he
We're five sections of the graph on they represent 600 deaths
Sofive
Spaces is 600 deaths
On one side
Batman each space is 500,000 vaccinations
In order to make the the lines look
Like they have similar 5 million vaccinations
Three
In terms of making it like
Yeah I see what you're saying
On the death side each segment isn't labeled because it's a graph
It's built on cherry pick
And if the date or responsibly presented it wouldn't be something Alex could Marvel over like this
Very sad
Twitter
Like
I imagine if you took
Alex
To like a Hall of Mirrors
And just showed you your face
But through the wrong shaped mirror he be like
What happened to you
Are you okay
Your face is wavy now I don't know what's going on we need again again we wrestle with
Whether or not object permanence is something he is grass
Exactly
So this next clip
Gitim Italy think
Is where
Like this
Got2b parody it has to be
McDonald's
I don't normally
Drop a ball because
11 letters
Coming off of the vaccinated we showing all the numbers
Videos
As for what
Covid-19 murdering logic contest winner announced
So he's got a covid denial video contest
That he wasn't able to judge the winner of because too many people around him including himself. Covid
God
I feel like he should
If this has to be a joke right II if the next time he does any cause-and-effect
I'm going to hit him he does like
You know like how when you throw a ball it then hits the thing I'm like you don't understand that you don't understand
How's traffic to work
B & I don't care I don't care
Unreal
I understand like
The reality of people are sick so I couldn't find a winner for this contest
Wouldn't you want to present it as like I got too busy
Or something not like
Hey everybody had covid so I couldn't I couldn't get an award out for this covid video
All of you to make the best video about how covid is fake and is all a lie
I wanted to judge that however
Everyone I know has covid
So it was very difficult to judge the
Submissions
About how covid-19 real
While I was sick with covid
Now
Why
Not the reason you think the office if they made a show at the office but Alex
To show that would be one of the plot
How do we navigate this
And that would be like a two or three-week situation like at the writers room would Bandy about ideas
Then you have somebody go rated they have to come back and everybody to edit it
Together again brutal cuz life is a farce
Absolutely some big news though
About like things are going to be happening around Infowars
Like maybe they have some new
I want all these calls I do want to
Really seriously considering
2 hour commercial free
Do it
Pray to God
Energized
More what you're sending
Going on here free of Alex considering doing a colony
Got it just never ends
Talking to you
The viewer
Is what I love the most
Which is why I'm going to take
Call Zan
20 minutes left in my broadcast I have to leave
I love it
So much
I'm going to start doing this show that I've been
Saying I'm going to do 4 years and never do
Haha
Weird
So
You can actually get a call
Well I mean
Just so you know
Look
Desert is my favorite part of a meal but sometimes I eat too much of the meal and I forget that I had to leave room for dessert
Is there I understand
I do too
Ice cream
So lucky
You got cover this big new story that he forgot to get 200 sorry
The story
Call Simon
Comes out today
Tell Paul I'm introducing
Bipartisan Bill Democrats are pushing it
National ID covid-19
Char 521
That's a sexy plus billion dollars
Improve data sharing and other aspects of immunization
Information
Population
Okay without further Ado. He's calls in
Washington welcome.
That was it
That's his coverage of this
Scott it
Nailed it
What else
What else is there to say
Not much
Maryville
One of the other piece of information that I'd like to bring
This HR 550 what about it was introduced in January okay
If this year how many months ago
They've introduced
Tomorrow's
I do like the gravitas with it
They've introduced
It's going
It started at January several several 9/8 months ago
Whenever it happens
What a dork
Alex tells this really fun story
That's very not true about Bilderberg
We would hear them speak and say once we
Collapse of system they won't have money to protest.
Massachu
Some other crew is in other areas of Europe
I did not know
This never happened
Resume.
Killer retrofit that
To be a German accent
This story never happened
Alex would go Yellen to a bullhorn occasionally emitted hang out with
Complete nut bars like Daniel estulin or anti-semites like big Jim Tucker
And they would tell him a bunch of bulshit
That's what they
Stadler coverage of Bilderberg
Kind of appreciate that strategy of being like
I'm going to do a weirdly racist Asian accent
And then
I'm just going to say that it was German
I don't even know if that was an attempt at a racist Asian accent
I don't know what it was like it was just a part of his
His accent work is just a cactus
Accidentally becoming
There was a first call / Diana
A call but
Business picks up
Okay the next caller
I like I got to tell you
Sky used to be into the devil
Alex
Trying to reach you in lunch
Truck driver
53 year old male
Man I want to give you a hug
The statements
Since I was 13
The Holy Spirit
Hit me with a rock man
He woke me up
The truth
It's always Spirits takes me a lot and I just want to say something
Warren is
Okay
It's not something
It's a weakness
I'm just letting you know
That's the way they see it
We know that these people
Destroy this world
High Spirits
That's why
I'm just going to laugh
When people protest
Which is really a shame
Hard hard
Don't feel like this is a sort of stuff that Alex would like
Necessarily be
The firming and sort of enabling
He doesn't know what the
Perspective this caller is coming
I'd say that if someone were to approach me
And tell me that
They were satanists since they were 13
And recently the Lord has been
Been talking to them too much
Probably wouldn't
Extend that conversation much
Further
I probably be like
Oribi incredibly
If it were a private conversation I might be polite
Radio show
Let's talk a little bit
You're a what you do are you a long-haul trucker and you're saying that God is speaking to you all the time
Might not be got buddy
Exhausted
To who talk to your boss
About how they do
Distribute miles
And then figure out how to
I get a schedule that doesn't require you to go
You might have a c w McCall situation where someone's on the seat
BB true
Breaker breaker
Gods coming in calling your rubber duck
God if you knew that there was another truck driver at you you just kind of just
Every now and I got you have to try and talk with
The bright side I think I would be
Low Brotherhood
Sure the other truckers get together and they like
Gigantic vaccines
F*** with butt
Mothballs
So Alex keeps talking to this guy and he has some ideas about communism
What we are seeing happened right now
We're feet happened right now
Is that okay
Exactly chest about cognizant see here's the deal
Great
Exception
The Bible talks
Okay
The great deception is the largest human sacrifice
History
Android
They're all they're all in line to call the planet
Amazing call her
So I mean like look
Whenever people are doing that Rogan thing of like Alex's actually write a lot
Take that edge East answer
He's dumbfucks having aleksandrova actually
Owning is that
That's what they're actually own
It's not
Some kind of a fun
Show where they talk about
A reporting on
F****** social media post
That he hasn't even looked into at all
I've been rambling with some unhinged collar about the
Devil wanting to bring in communism
Death by killing everybody
Nonsense
Yeah they
The devil is really dropping
On the ball
Nicely done
Everything I've heard about the
Does deviled eggs
Does not know
What's
Married to a coat rack
I mean
I haven't been able to stop thinking about joper awhile now
Present our last episode for a while
Like I thought you might I thought you might go Blue
I don't care for jokes
No
Like
That exact moment in the Bible where God
Is doing his whole thing and he's like hey
F****** shut up
I'm literally God you don't understand what I'm doing why are you why are you being a dick about this
The point is
The universe is big
Just be a humble a******
You know right
And and
To be so misunderstood that these people
Cannot process Concepts that they
Don't understand
Like they don't have the humility to be like
Maybe I just don't understand
What's going on
Why would you think that the devil the literal devil
In a battle with god for eternity over man's soul
Yes it's like
Communism
I thought we're going to do it
Right and
Not only that but
Whatever happens to be the modern
The devil has always been
Every 5 years
Even though it's different
Yeah it's that immediacy bias of like whatever your most fascinated by now is the most fascinating thing
Trump guilty of it too
Super into Survivor right now and I definitely won't be in a few months
Sure talk about Seltzer if you want
Most important thing ever I got to tell you all about the south
Alex has the same way with the devil's plans
Yeah I know it's
Just said like
When you stop and you think about how many things
In your lifetime
You have been
Told
Hysterically
Are the markets
Like can you like
UPC symbols seriously barcodes
F****** many
Tattoos
Don't stop
Non-stop since I was a boy and it's never been the mark of the beast and everything that is
Similar to the mark of the beast
They just get a phone for
Is completely
Yeah but I like what you going to do I need to use a phone
Another caller and this guy is an anti-vaxxer
Does not like vaccines
What
Competent it
Professional would like to have a job someplace but they all wanted because
Button
Instead what he wants
To do is start like a LinkedIn
For people who don't want to take vaccine
Okay
We got it at work together
Construction
Employers and employees
This new age
Bulletin board
Because I'm a hard-working father 31 on the way got a beautiful wife is my angel
That works so hard to put all this information in my head.
You can go to a doctor
I know you're single
What I'm saying
You're not supposed to take something give you having a meal you can really hurt you
So
Alex
Defraud a doctor just say I've already had it
What's a myth
Okay
Cool
I hear you saying like Okay yeah well that's what they should do I have these places you don't want to get vaccines they have this
Bulletin board for businesses
But I would say that the only way that that's acceptable
Is a vole so all of these businesses have to be very public
About our employees are not back
Your own discretion I wrote down I'm fine with that
Not because
I
It's a good idea or is that it's
Hey functional
It is at least in keeping with their like free-market ideas like the reason I say I'm fine with that is
Because I can find no hypocrisy and right right
But we believe the free market
You take care of it
Now obviously when it fails miserably they'll say it's not the free market and they should
Be able to kill all of us in order to make it work the way they want
But
In this situation
Theoretically it is the free bar
I mean I don't know if that means anything but yeah
You know what Alex might give him one
It's going to happen
I hear you brother sending your resume. I want extra money
RIT people about a week
If you want to be part in between two more people are doing a lot of stuff
Please don't touch my pool
Your help
Can you deliver pool tiles products.com
Wintersun back in stock I called you out of a D3 we have
Nailed it
Yeah he has more people but also
Plugged in the shell
Some however I might give
This guy money turns into you should give me money because then I'll have that money to give this guy
Honestly I really hope it gets back to
Pineda to work area
How many people around him have been
Passing this around I don't know if it
It's a good idea to work at Infowars
I guess even an ideal circumstances it's not a good idea to work there but
Now even more
It is it is funny how many people
Have noticed like
Conservative radio hosts
K o
Summit covid
TV
Conservative post
No covid
No coffee
How could that possibly be
What sort of income
Define the difference between tvo's
Conservative radio host at work
One is obviously but you're implying
What time the second thing is also like
I think the TV people have much more vested interest in image
And like there could be people who have gotten sick and we just don't even know
Seem like a lot of people dying
Are radio host
That doesn't to happen
No I mean obviously there's there's a far
Bigger budget and more people who like
It's bad for us don't don't say that also the barrier-to-entry is a lot lower for radio host
Many many of them probably
You know
I mean look
If you were an 80s, eventually became a 2000's radio host that's how it works
Basically all I all I got is
Alex is just
Basically
What's that song
After show for the zombies
Your parents found on social media
Yes is Ridiculousness but for
Fake social media post
It's pretty sad
I never want to lose this image in my head
Because it's soap
Alex being unable to judge the covid video contest
Does everyone have a Coke
Unreal
I can't believe should be against the 888 should be against some sort of decency law or orgy
Like just literary law should apply in real life
This is too far when it comes out of Alex's mouth on air he should be like
Oh wait
Dawning irony that would just change the world wrong
Ty.com
Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm Darryl Ruckus
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color