Damn important items swetik
I have great respect for snowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
The author of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
Jordan Jordan
My break is at long last
I have finally been able to check off
Seeing the Mighty Mighty Bosstones on my Maybach
Bucket list
I was
12 I think
When
The impression that I get came out on the radio and like
I just like I love these horns
It was so exciting and then
My brother's a little bit older than me more tuned into
The music album
He played for me another Drinking Song
I like that song it's so great you just blew my mind
I remember hearing that they were on a radio show
The interview that ended up turning out to be loved line
And I remembered I stayed up like with a radio listening in my bed
Like it listening in to hear the Bosstones on on Loveline
I love
When I went back and I found all there
Another world records
It was just great I mean I didn't know that the Lifelong Love of Loveline
How Ya Wanna Talk About It
Before we started recording and it was not.
The setlist I would have chose
And it was a little bit underwhelming
A little depressed and want to talk made me think that they might be vaccine Skeptics
Like I don't know anything about the boss Downs politics this is a good I haven't listened to any of their albums
Jackknife to a swan
But seeing them do Someday I Suppose life was really do
Great
Yeah
It felt like it it
A momentary been a long time coming in my life like that song really meant a lot to me when I was younger
And
They still sound sharp away from them
A someone who is Dicky Barrett to voice that growling like the fact that he is as old as he is now and
Can still sound pretty good
Is not
That's that's impress
It is fantastic
Is it is like a you know the dates
It's a little bit like how baseball players are tennis players you know their Prime used to be
And now you can hit all the way up till 3031 you know like Rafa and Djokovic all those guys there
The same is true I feel like for like
Like the rolly rolly voices
Technology now
Honey and P Technologies
There are three
Vicks VapoRub
I felt really weird to about the idea of going
To write
Obsessed because it's a large Gathering of people but
I talked it over with some people that I trusted their opinions on and
You have to present a vaccination
Card to get in
There's a lot of space to
Train
The pit the skank Circle
And do you know math
People are still wearing masks
It felt like a responsible risk
As far as it went.
There's still a part of my brain that couldn't get past that
You know they couldn't get past like
This long. Of time readjusting to like
What is okay
You know the thing that
Open for me was whenever cuz Lollapalooza this year
I was like looking at that going horrify
War Fox
This is going to be a nightmare
Yeah and then only like
Tiny tiny percentage actually like it was not a super spreader as hell
It's almost like they is there's the people you came with
If you if it was that number of people you know I remember I don't remember the exact
Districts on if it was the numbers were
Shockingly low interact
Any cases that were traceable to
Yeah and I think that did make me feel a little bit more comfortable they like
If you're doing these things if you can do them response
Sibley and especially if it's like
You know Mexican carjacking
Where are you I don't know if
Maybe maybe we're at a point where
Some some
By reasonable risk
Can be accepted
It is
Sure sir Cortana Cassie I got to make sure
But it was
It's not worth it
No that is it is
It is also a little bit that
Kind of
We've talked about it for months now but that two different America's you know the vaccinated and unvaccinated
You can go to a f******
Festival
You know
Like but then you go to non-vaccinated part of America and you can't f*** around
It everywhere
Bananas yeah
It is bananas
It is so what's your bright spot today Dan is as you well know I live a very
Unhealthy lifestyle from me
Pretty ecstatic well last night my partner and I
We've signed up for some like healthy
I think
They send you meals
Don't give him a shout out
But it's not one of the ones that ever ties done podcast again okay I'm so last night I ate my first
Beyond meat so it's like a it's like a meat replacement the whole thing
That's interesting
I tried it and everybody says it's like regular milk can f*** off
It's not
However
It is not
Not unlike
Regular meat
Know what I mean
Yeah that's kind of the the sense that I've got for vlogging
People
Yeah their similarities to me
It's not exactly the same but
But it's like a drastic improvement over what was there was there
Totally
Still no progress
Is being made we ate a Burger it was
Was like good yesterday
All vegetables
That was my first all-vegetable day
Ever Maybe
Buy on purpose
He's going to be gay
Coronavirus boots it's not going to last very long but I
Did it well I'm proud of myself
Applaud
I'm sure I think that
What's the best contacts for those
Meal delivery things
Elizabeth within a couple
Yeah cuz I tried it once
Stan
I was out in Alabama
Why would I do that
Yeah
It was depressing
To see the two meals
Just sitting there
This'll take a little bit of preparation tonight like I can just pull it out of the fridge and top
You know what it what's amazing about it and the thing that is the only big thing for me
Because f*** being healthier with
Begin the nonsense or whatever
I mean I do feel it I feel it took
One day of eating vegetable I feel way better
Portion
Control like last night
I8
What made me full
And then I was
Done I didn't have like another entire meal of Chinese food said like continue jamming in
And my face sure is it taste
Is great so you just
Gyros
Well I look forward to tracking your adventures see what happens
We're in the present-day of Alex Jones Show September 17th
Why you're laughing
President
Well that's like that for sure.
So
Look this episodes pretty
Why
Great
We're going we're going there
This is not necessarily break
Alex says
Shockingly awful and also there's a topic that comes up that I would like to talk about
So we'll get to that
Before we do
That's a good
The first Adam thank you so much
Sydney Clorox Clorox Clorox plant
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much I drink ipas and have a cool dogs
I'm a policy wonk very much Jason also thank you
I worry I'm subconsciously indoctrinating my son
I'm a policy wonk podcast around children
Yeah if you are pregnant or
With with a child do not listen to this podcast
You know how they say
What does Bacchus is the opposite
No
And even if even if your child becomes
Successful
An Avenue like this and you don't want
You don't want that let me tell you this child
Pipefitters jobs
So we start here Jordan on September 7th
And Alex has a big news story not so concerned with covid for most of this episode although it is apparently bio
I'm going to kill everybody
There's bigger news and that is
They're Haisha
Chen's in America
Well now in one Bridge
In Del Rio Texas
2030 major bridges are more
There have been over 10,000 Asians
Just yesterday now it's over 15,000
And a band any drones with
The technocracy with the geofence they put up
Free program
We were there with our drones
They suddenly wouldn't take off the Fox News drones with dick off
We put up a geo-fence in order to Biden you can't
Why these
Mexico side
Got one up and then we were able
Nobody else has
Last night as the sun was setting
Thousands more
Surging across
The border and walking over to dangerous spillway
In the Rio Grande men women and children
Because Biden a days ago said any actions that get here
We're in an object already not coming testim
And bring them into the United States to sign up for welfare
I use with a permanent underclass
It sounds like
Or
We were accepting refugees from nightmarish
Escape that climate change itself has caused as well as
Roar in turmoil over the weird fascination of their president by some random ass doctor in Florida
What will get to this on the 2nd but like I want it I want to just put the like
Right up front
Like I'm not entirely sure what was going on with the no-fly area over this
This bridge
Sure I presume that there may be a safety reason why that was.
In terms of like not allowing Fox news's
Drones
The flyover
I don't know but I do think that's a legitimate
That is the only thing that I think is legitimate Within
Any of this coverage is it appropriate
To save media companies cannot fly a drone
Over
This area
I'm not sure
I mean
Here's my only rebuttal to that
That is
At the end of the day if Fox News and Infowars
They're trying to put drones over a bridge where refugees are coming
They stopped being media organizations and start turning into propagandist trying to get people kill I agree
So at that point I was like the moment he said they wouldn't allow drones to take off I was like oh yeah that's what I would have
I was going to get propaganda
I don't
Don't know at what point
You were able to
You say
That rule is
You can't do this because you're going to do bad things with the pics
After the migrant Caravan
I mean we should have learned our lesson there
See but
Turning all the drugs off
Maybe Jeff so this story if you just hear from Alex is that Joe Biden is begging Haitian
Succumb to the United States where they'll be
Accept it in with no process at all
Put on welfare and used as a political weapon against people like Alex breed white people
It's essentially 100% does the newest articulation of the great replacement narrative and it's a little more than white nationalism
Pretending to be a policy
Concern
So here's the real story
There's approximately 12,000 and maybe a little more now but they're asylum-seekers mostly from Haiti who made camp
Under the Del Rio International Bridge
While they wait processing by customs
Border Protection
This is technically within the United States
And it's important
It is because you can't request
Asylum anywhere except for inside the United States
They do that if you want to request Asylum
I plead your case
Within like
You have to be
BND
Across the border
Pretending that that's not the case is
The two of the right-wing media
Rivalry
This isn't a situation where this is an invasion Point nor is it a situation that you can extrapolate
Every bridge
On the texas-mexico Border
It's a specific set of circumstances that exist for a reason
And it's a humanitarian in logistics
Call challenge
Not a crisis that requires were treating to white supremacist
Conspiracy theories
This is kind of the state of things for Alex's information
Space though
Much like there will never be election coverage anymore that isn't rooted
Assumption that the Democrats are cheating in the GOP you're secretly always the rifle winners
There's never going to be any coverage of any immigration and Refugee related stories on Alex's show
It isn't firmly entrenched in the belief that non-white people coming to the United States
Is an attack on white people in the United
Explicitly
What are the large contributing factors to the specific circumstances were seeing now
Is that there was a large influx of people from Haiti seeking Asylum
Four Seasons
Like you touched on
The president was assassinated in July and then there's a huge earthquake in mid August
The destroyed over 120,000 home
Earlier in the year immigrant rights groups have noted that Biden's administration at actually been using title 42 explosions to do
Deport immigrants back to
I hate more than Trump even did
Yeah
Title 42 for the US go that says the president
You can limit the ability of migrants to come to the United
If they come from countries where communal
Double diseases are present to a level
There's a pretend
Apple health risk
Trumpy focus on the context of covid to limit the ability of migraine
Prince to come to United States
And unlike how you might have hoped
It would go Biden has continued with
This policy
And many folks on the left have been
Intensely critical of him for this
Rightfully so yeah I do like how people are like nobody on the left criticizes Joe Biden
There are
On August 3rd the Department of Homeland Security temporarily placed people arriving from Haiti on the list of migrants are qualified for
Temporary protected status
Set to be in effect from August
Easter 2021
Do temporary 3rd 2023
Possible for individuals from Haiti who were in the country to apply for TPO
Yes status which would make them not able to be summarily deported
Before they could apply for Asylum
Side note
If you ever wondered why there
Particular countries that end up
Become a hot-button
Topics for right-wing media you know like in terms of immigration
Because these countries are on the temporary protective
Somalia sedan Syria Venezuela all on the way
Highway 80 was on the TPS list and US deportation should have been halted but it turns out that last week
Immigration and Customs
Enforcement on Wednesday expelled 86 Haitian Nationals from the unite
Red States
And flew them back to Haiti
Two fairly shocking given the priority PS announcement and migrant rights groups
As well as Democratic house members like
Ayanna Pressley had sharp criticism
There's alot going on here
The ministration appears to be really dropping
Turn the ball in terms of this issue
In response to the news of the situation at the Del Rio bridge at ice announced that they were planning to ramp up deportation
With a deportation
Complaints with him
Next week antenna week after that which is
There seems to be
Incongruent message incoming
From different parts of the government
To a knot
But small extent
Going back to the Obama Administration
Ice has often seemed like they have
Become just a complete row gauge
I don't know how to look
Get some of the information that you're able to find a belated the stories about this
Seem like
Wait why why are you doing that is exactly again
The the stated
Department of Homeland Security
Do you know it is it is
A little bit like that
So
So all too often
Part of the reason that
You know that the
The Chicago PD is
Is it complete Rogue agency
Is because
Anytime they disagree with the mayor or whatever
All of a sudden the mayor agrees with them
And it's
Partly because if you really allowed that
To go
And like fatback
Back against them
People would find out
They have just as much power if not more than the mayor
And you don't want to look like you're not as powerful as your own
So I imagine Biden doesn't want to look like he literally cannot
Control ice
That maybe there might be something to that I was very
Confuse the looking into
The details of the story
Cuz I mean
My paygrade I don't understand
I mean you know
I guess a lot of people in every government have always been like we've got a certain amount that we can do right
And f****** with Isis going to be a lot more than we can do today
Maybe you know
So we've lived through a number of
Scares
On Alex's part about immigration
I'm sure all of them look kind of embarrassing and
C-130
Employees down
The Border 22
To take care of
One of them
Music I think it is getting married and I like another one couldn't go for another reason which is
Really private
No
Capture footage
A humongous
Haitian Caravan slamming over
The Texas border last night and our crew is there now
With no sleep
Amazing job
Is there doing an amazing job on the ground
Getting even more insane footage as we speak
What is his ongoing one of our camera guys getting married this weekend
Another added on podcast Yeti last night that's fine I understand
Amazing job we need more crew we need to expand but
That's really up to you and your support.
Appreciate you all.
Infowarsstore.com is bringing you all this information
Wintersun high-quality vitamin B
D3 flower
Do you want to plug your employees podcast AJ AJ
How to do my own podcast
Anywhere from between 100 to 200 listeners who will get very unhappy if I do get it out tomorrow
Sorry I can't help you save the Border I got to record my podcast
Yeah that tells you
Just how important a big deal this is yet
I feel like this
This is an inability on Alex's party
To convince employees
Of the seriousness of the things are there
Personal reason wedding braids
Schedule a wedding 2
What are the people who does end up going
Going to the Border I don't know who else is there cuz this is the only person they bring up
Is Tim Enloe
Who's one of the guys who went with Alex the last time they went down to the Wrath
Catholic charity
Rite Aid in McAllen
And he's also former Blackwater so that's cool
He believes that you know the un's trying to replace us with h
Sure
There is no way
Something like this on such a massive scale
That's action occur in a vacuum
This is organized
These people all have cell phones we showed that to you
These people have the ability to recharge their cell phone
2 to have a cell phone to pay for the services
They have supplies fresh clothes
Everything
And this is a journey that takes months for them
So this is absolutely a un sponsor soros-funded invasion
Of the United States
And the goal is clear we know what the goal is it is absolutely
Replacement migration there is no doubt
Jesus
Pretty blunt
It is weird that a guy who more likely than not committed war crimes
In another country
That weird rated
Is now like
I think that
Compelling that the evidence of humanitarian Aid existing is Bruce
There's an invasion of our country
I don't know I find that to be an unconvincing feeding and clothing people
And then bringing him to the United States
What they should be doing is invading another country and killing them
That's how it is work
210 sucks
He's very bluntly.
I was spitting
What is essentially watered-down white National
And it gets worse like
Adamantly seems to this is the first instance on this show
Of someone at Infowars saying
Dehumanizing
Things about people from other countries
Also just dumping
Their children off and leaving them in the bushes and never coming back
Just like you said Bagram air base with the women throwing their babies over the walls
That's exactly right right
Body sculptures
Children quite honestly are viewed as dispensable
Right they serve a purpose
What about purposes eventually bury tomorrow for profit
Or you know whatever the purpose is very from culture to culture
But what they don't have
Is the very close attachment
That we are the Westfield right the responsibility
To stay with that child and even die for
If necessary
Wow
That's
If you can
Just take something that some
But he says
And then put the word
Gypsy in it
Go like that's what
That's it literally whatnot
He said
You don't get the flight drones over Refuge
That's how you're going to litigate this
Interesting way to do it
When
You are trying to Rally people
Against
Refugees asylum-seekers immigrant
Part of your argument is
They don't love their children in the same way
They don't have that attachment
Children in the West
Do
You are
F***** up
This is this is
Is not a policy
Kind of show there's no
Politics in
This is straight demonization
I mean
It doesn't surprise me though
What would you
To fix somebody who went into another country and committed war crimes
Do you know
Allegedly
More likely than not there you go
I just I find it
To be concluded
Completely unacceptable
End the conversation
Is about
A situation with Haitians fleeing from this gigantic earthquake in political and
Stability
Other issues trying to find Safety and Security of the United States
And your conversation
Involved
They don't love their children like white people
People do
F*** yourself. How about that
You don't
Get a place at the table no don't get to talk you don't
No no
I think they don't love their children
So
Alex gets a little bit
Will you gotta talk Schwab
But it's today yeah
Reset all that good stuff
Sources that he wants 2.2 about you have that are a little bit sad
If you go
To Wikipedia and Klaus Schwab Zone Wikipedia
Corporate fascist group that runs the UN
We are going to capture all the nation-states and he's been that was 6 years ago
Why you were lying on Wikipedia man
You shouldn't do
Level
Sources in Wikipedia
Cluster of didn't say whatever he said
Wikipedia
Whatever that is that may or may not be on Wikipedia
From somewhere else should I see you should say that
Thing instead
Do you have any kind of awareness of the
Like a larger that I really see why he dropped out of Community College
Play a Ted not a great source for Alex we pulling out
If you do go to it
You'll find a section about a proposal that was that was put up by the world economic Forum back in 2010
When Oswald was the head of the organization
The Proposal argue that governments were no longer the quote dominant actors on the world stage
Henry could be time for a new model of governance that reflected a stakeholder paradigm
This was a proposal
The part about capture that capturing the countries
What is a swab saying that he's going to capture the world's countries at the description of this proposal that was given by the transnational
Institute
The Wikipedia page quotes
Them which is what Alex is presenting itself
Schwab set
Also Alex would absolutely think of the transnational Institute or a bunch
The globalist
Add because they get funding from the Rockefeller Brothers fund
Well that'll do it
Back for a little difficult for Alex to try and explain his worldview so dependent on Good vs Evil
How can be possible to this Rockefeller funded group
Has a sharp criticism of a policy proposal from the world economic forum
They're all evil globalist imma try to work on the same cold
Makes no sense this is like you know this is a screenwriting situation this
This is a book adaptation where you come by in a couple of characters into one character in your movie
I need just kind of Move Along
Nonsense
Sure it's not a cure
Wikipedia Alex reporting on a
Tweet
That's a hoax Facebook meme
Strong stuff here this guy's
Up all night
Doing this research a citation
Since page for this episode
It's probably just like
You know like back
In the day you sit on a Xerox machine Iraq your ass
That's a citation MLA format for your ass
More dehumanization of immigrants coming right up
We want to abolish all borders to solve The World's problems
We're being flooded by millions
A month basically and they say
Please consider just getting rid of your borders
Edline I've got today
Please
Consider
Your borders today
Completely
And then they cut the food off the third world tens of millions starving
Military age men
Development
Zombies
Cheese
You know when you put in a mediately after the words that you are specifically using to describe black people
I don't care if you're black or white
You are one hundred percent just driving by people
See through the same thing as the code of the West
Actually believe any of the things he's saying any wasn't just trying to find ways to dehumanize migrants and make his audience think of them
Dumbest things not people
He should be staunchly in favor of government subsidized food program
For all citizens
If you think that malnutrition turns people into zombies then he should support free lunch programs and universal access to nutrition
I can't imagine he'd want his fellow citizen
Since we turned into zombies
Just because I can't afford good food
Yeah I bet he would he would super support the black panther panther brexit
This program you know I really loved it make sure that people didn't grow up to be zombies and they weren't malnourished
Obviously you must
Supported
The Black Panther Party
It seems like he would
Consistency dictate you should
Seems like it's only the story about the UN saying that everyone should get rid of bloating
Please please sir would you consider getting rid of your bored
That's just Alex lying and misrepresenting a story about a representative from the UN Human Rights Council suggests into the UK
But they should not Implement a new immigration bill into law because doing so would make
Criminals of many ref
Gigi's on the silence
Rosella Pagliacci lure said quote
I find it ironic to be honest but the very same people we felt so affected by when we saw them hanging
Complains in Kabul or those we are now discussing how they should be
Distracted
If they extracted themselves and made it here they would if that bill were Lobby liable to be potential
To potentially four years in jail and then subject to some attempt
To return them to the other countries
There's something ironic in the way they were so concerned about them while they're there but we're not ready to
Consider them
When they come to the UK
That's what I want to say
With this this new law that
Is a bill in the UK there could be
Become law
The UN Human Rights
Cancel was advising like
You shouldn't do this
Yeah people who are able to flee from countries
The Koch brothers what is wrong with you people you may end up then incarcerating a
Next clip suck
There's no way around it
Where do you want these people that give them phones
They gave him debit cards with $1,000 on them
Women you want
Play structure
Never get off welfare
This is what's going on
But to bring us down to their level
Wildwood flower on a private jet with 100,000 acres private ranches
My robot
Thank you almost lost track of that set
I'm trying to be as racist as possible and then
Robot saturno let's be racist towards them to a man that sucks
That is
That's
That's real like hey man
You're talking genocide
No more talk
Looking for you please also cite your sources on the 90% we know of the immigrants never get off welfare
Particularly considering
Like what do you mean by wealth
At such a broad category of
Another social programs that are involved
What are you talkin about first
Are you talking about it like food assistance are you talking about
Medicaid what are you talkin about
Menu at 2
Think about
Well in the United States
There are rules in place
But you can't be on
Welfare programs
45 years after arriving
And so
Okay what about that Alex
He's talking about Europe so look at Europe
Which country
What are you doing
Spaghetti
So many differences in terms of what kind of a welfare state
Exist
Between like Scandinavian countries and
And other
It's outrageous
But I don't know if this means nothing
They accepted Alex
Really wants agitate against
Immigrants
Yeah especially considering
I mean
Just the sheer volume of
Immigrant stories that are told about America
Going back
Accents
Begin like
That's one of our favorite f****** stories is people who come here from a different country
And then
Turn into a thing here that's what we love to hear about
Yeah it's our lower
Favorite story like how you act came into Ellis Island they changed my f****** name and I still didn't
Do anybody I'm still a good person
I'm pretty
So
I complained a little bit recently of that Damien that went around
Again owes Alex
Another Bon Iver song
I'm a little bit after that there was another thing that went viral
I don't know sometime in the nineties bad news on Lake Public Access TV
He was young
When is Dad bottom
It was around then
He was an attractive dude talked about this before he was an attractive man when he was younger
And it's
It's very icy this video of him a number of times I do I don't know if it was from his
Just
From his show or if he included it in one of his early documentaries
Madonna Street in Austin
Complaining about how one of the council members houses is overgrown
Like the plants in the yard
Because someone
I guess probably a right-wing weirdo head gotten
The ticket for having an overgrown yard
Or something you like well this city council member
It granted the steaks
A pissant
Go back to those steaks shirt
Whatever
He doesn't seem like
The Alex Jones that you know now
And that's obviously because of
Money
Drugs
Alcohol everything
Negative reinforcement patterns
All all sorts of things
I mean just basic
Malignant narcissism
And I
There were a few people who responded
I bet I would be super against
I don't think I am nearly as much
Because
I think that that is
A ducky
All the time and Alex's life
Sure and
Pretending that he's still the same person
Yeah that would be irresponsible
But looking back on this and recognizing that from this
Route through this
Disgusting tree
Like that's not
I am 880 to be censorious with me to be like
Hey don't
Spread that around
Feel like you isn't Alex hot
Yeah I'm a waste of time
I don't know it seems like
Worst
Waste of time where is
The Bon Iver thing
He's actually dangerous
Yeah
So I didn't actually have any kind of negative response
People sharing that I think there is a
The difference between them is that
Humanizes and
What
Kind of
Defang
To ascertain
Extant
Present Persona and the other one
I've almost as a
Contra
Tears Alex in the present
If you go back and you watch that you look at a man who are youngboy
Who is handsome
And who is
Not
F****** calling for genocide I'm not yelling about how the devil walks Among Us and all Democrats are demons
Disaster if you look at that video I'm sure part of what you see is just like
F*** what
Become right and I think that's what a lot of
The people who were commenting on it
Listening to a bony Vera clip and being like this is kind of fun and this is all look at him yay
Also the fact that you can see like
Okay this is him back in like the 90s these are the
The sort of issues that like
Really his bread-and-butter is
Silly
And
It's
It ground
You know like it's like he's not some kind of guy
There is a trajectory that went from there to
Mystical Magic
Cool things that happened it's just
Look at what
Would be exactly as famous as he wasn't at clip
If you still talking about the
City councilors installed that's basically and started doing crazy or s***
And got more famous
Anyway Alex has some thoughts
About this video going around
And I immediately was like we started talking about it I thought like
I don't know if I'm going to enjoy this coverage
Of it
I did because he's super defense
About how hot he used to be
Yeah
There's a video that popped up last night that I have millions of views on Instagram and hundreds of thousands on Twitter people
They're like my God Alex Jones
I was like 20
1 years old then
I was not
Teenager as they say in the video
So that's not the bat is
That is me
Play sigala
And my teeth are a little bit longer the front
Grinding my teeth
Coke
Alex Jones has
And quite the transformation so I see some of the
Joke police out there
Over the years I'll actually get 180 lbs in Iran
6 miles every other day and let's awaits about 2 hours a day
I can bench press
Thompson and duskwatch 600
And I was quite special
Quite the specimen
This is
That didn't sound that defense
It will be later
I'm grateful for not being that hot
When I was young
It's it's
It's the fall
It's that he was too hot and now he's to hit
You know
Like I'm
Fine I wasn't that good looking I don't get worse but it's like the fall is going to be that bad
I don't I don't really particularly care that much
What about his physical being
Critique inasmuch as like
Yes
I can see how he was
Conventionally attractive before and now
And also
Seems to be in poor health
Yeah I'm working
Concerned about lick his ideas
Honestly think that the idea that being expressed in that video from his youth
Although it is covering up
Some pretty
F*****-up believes that he just wants
Probably a public with at the time he was aperture
Had all kinds of
Anti-government ideas
Little
Extreme
Like the
D idea that's in that video is
Hey ticketing of overgrown Lawns should be equally enforced
Purifying
That's great
Find
You did it
Do pigs that are being expressed now are ugly
Bear bear
Black immigrants are people
It's far more important to how how ugly his insides and his ideas are to me
There any kind of like
Whether or not you're hot
Very defensive about people saying is not hot anymore
Yeah there is a certain element of like
He got the wrong picture of Dorian Gray you know
Picture looks
Gorgeous
Prettier
I used to get like a lot of
Hate mail bacon die
Recognized in college
I wrote for the paper
Like people who are like
Saying IQ the artifact
You piece of s***
And I would always just laugh
Listen to buy heads of state
Absolutely I was
The number one man fighting against the devil in the world
Intelligence service broken
The time is running out
Right
I might not spend time on my show talking about a video of me
Happyville saying I used to be hot but you know might leave that alone
Comes up
You got to address it
Even if it is even if it interrupts
Yeah and you know what to think that I'm not factoring in is this sometimes you want to have
And like
It's not fun
To talk about
The Border
It's fun
Talk about people making fun of Alex
I don't look like Orson Welles anymore at
I had no problems with the ladies
Back
Amazon
I would have some fun
The last thing I'm already kind of doing it
That makes me being a good mood
Just have some fun and show some please
People make fun of me cuz I like stuff
I don't want to talk about
Caldera
What the show the live show headliner cuz I wrote it
That's what I do I don't just go with the rest of media saying
Older 10,000-plus
My grandson smashed over the Border
No our cruise been there
Up and down the Rio Grande River for miles in all directions
NFL
Football game
Hey Zach I don't listen to what other people are saying I make up my own number
I estimate crazyshit on my own I don't need there
Hell-born
And
My conversation about this is going to be
Flagrantly offense
Open flagrantly offensive about that are you sure
So we're bringing that all these wonderful third world people
A lot of them are thugs
Bagram Air Base
Where the most the first flight for like 9% man
Jimmy's other cultures
It's not
Women & Children First
Women and children what
It's survival of the thuggish
And then that
Men breed their like that
And you get people that'll put your throat for nothing I don't care about you
But that's what's happening
Holyshit
Congratulations Joe Rogan
That might be a little bit
Boy
Survival of the thuggish
Don't know if we'll ever
Heard
A more black
Pot
Makeup a Black Kettle to call Black
Disgusting
I mean Lucia
I don't really have much commentary on this outside of stuff we've said a hundred times on the show it's just discussed
Yeah I am I mean
It can't cannot be said enough though
It cannot be said enough
That this
Is the rhetoric that precedes a genocide
It never
Doesn't well-endowed genocide that just like f****** shows up one day
It doesn't always lead to that
But those already happen
This is rhetoric that you find
Yeah pre-loading it
Yeah it was same way that it went Alex talks
Like a lot of his like they're going to pull false flag
The terrorist edging
Kind of
Yeah always lead to some kind of violent outburst
And it's
Whether or not it's just unacceptable
Yeah like I think that there are
Reasonable
Differences of opinion people can have
About immigration
Asian policy
I think that you
Can yeah
I think there's a line where your
Opinion
My rear end too dangerous
And I still think those conversations
You can have on those fronts
When you're talkin like this
About people from other
Countries in other cultures
That's not
Policy pay
That's not a conversation this is just
There's nothing that you can
Do to engage with this other than to say
This is
Disgusting
This deserves
Condemnation
People who would
Sincerely present ideas like this
Have no place in public discourse
Your beard both talking mess I would very much like
The conversation but
Between political parties and
Even ideology
Needs to be like
Should a progressive income tax be like
47%
Or should it be a graduated income-tax it starts at 90% for your first million and then gradually decreases from
Or should it be
Be a great conversation with different ideologies
Not
We should kill them because they want to text us slightly more than we're used to
And the rest of the world are basically cavemen kill them too
And there are cavemen that come out of every group
I had to look at Christian ideas
Neighbors
And do better society and that's what's built our world
What's the question
You don't want that
They don't want
To deal with chivalry
And private property
And women and children
Children Medical experiments and having sex with
York
Wow
He realizes
That America is not that alright
And that
All of our stuff
Just came from somewhere else
So like
Some stuff we got from
Asia some stuff we got from Africa
And some stuff we got four
From Europe I know that Jesus was big on private property
Loved it every second amendment easier to get into heaven
For a rich person then it is to heaven
F****** by a Campbell
Walking to Heaven if you're rich
Look bro if you're rich it's tough to get into heaven
You should have every right to calculate all your stuff
Hold on
I mean imagine you're going to heaven
Write in your in the waiting room and you meet your imaginary friend and he's like I got some evil s*** to tell about you
One second and you give him a hundred-dollar bill and he's like well
You had a good day see that's how you get into heaven if you're rich you bribe the fuel
It's called it's called
Ecclesiastical capture
I believe it's
Find all of this
Awful trying to make everything funny
Really want to light fires
I mean it's just
It looks kind of like a kind of interesting experience on my end because going to be head to
Two wacky episodes last weekend so covid
I keep being like
Come on anything else
Hey quit
Quit scaremongering about vac
Vaccines and then he's like okay well I guess I'll go kerbals
Immigrants are people
On an interesting
Demons or Heaven
Alex might not be in the best
He did have he was feeling in a good mood though people were talking about him on Twitter that makes me feel good
Because he got up really early this morning
I'm going to try to calm down
Wild Horses couldn't drag me away but I've been up since
Exaggerate
I've been running around the house my wife woke her up cuz I was
Yelling at people on the telephone
I'm there anybody on the other end
Watching attack over watching the UNC
The people on welfare piss him off and make him a white people
Doing that to class
Where they're saying officially in Tampa says whites are bad
Comedy classes why can't be in the gym
Total divide-and-conquer
Culture destroy our Unity
And totally rejected
Yeah
There's a war on whites and that's why I was yelling into the phone right now but morning and woke his wife up
When she's mad but he's normal
Norva this is a normal response to have when there's a war on white
Good
I think I think that Alex is like a big-time racist
And I really like dangerous antiinmigrante type
Right but I also think that this mood really does have to
To do with that video I think I think that it really does think
I used to be f******
Good looking
If you don't appreciate Dad losing it all
Right now
I'm sorry I'm not real
And so yeah
I don't look
Like I used to I could look a lot better I'm not family looks great 67 years old
All the stress I
I stayed up
Nothing to coffee
Probably two nights a week
For the first 45 years I was on air
Hours a day
I had edited all the film
Why would a head jobs on top of it
I did the sales job the radio station
I didn't care about the mission
Look like a war hardened Goblin
I do and
I'm not trying to win pretty boy contest around here to take on the plane
Myself to Bringing Down the New World Order
Because I will not spiritually
And I will not genetically
Sign on to what state is doing
All you people
Spell tyranny
Over there
Leonardo DiCaprio you just rub skin creams on your faces Alden
When you die
Your soul and your energy is going to be sunken the middle of a black hole with all the energy just like you
I don't care about this body
What does the Warren White
Let me ask you a question
For all of his
You just see how
Evil they look on TV just evil they're ugly the world
Know if you're pretty
Then you're evil
Skin cream on yourself all day
Battle-hardened God
Okay alright
I am starting to think that he might be a bit
Hypocrite
I think he's an idiot I also do love though the idea that he's like
I took out all the stress I took all the pain of the world and that's why I look like a mess
Yeah that was that was definitely him talking to him not me
Yeah it's totally fine you're a hero
You do not need to do voices
Look I'm not in great shape
And 10 one of the reasons is
Because
I don't try as hard
Sure
I'll be straight up about that I think it's probably because of
The fight
Do Auburn have to go if it's the fight
I'm busy you care more about the mission no I'm busy but I also
Shoes
Things like unhealthy food
Could exercise
Or I could watch another episode of Survivor
Sometimes I choose the Survivor
Look
I'm here
Nonsense
Absolutely not anyway
Globalist
Save a plant
They want to make their sales
Completely clear about
All this news all day but you understand that the
Big corporations the world
Believe that they're going to develop super Technologies
A Salesman word either Delaware forever
They're worth an overpopulated Planet will hurt
The planet
Hertz are nests to live forever on
And they go on in their own papers around statements
Feels like Highlander
It's okay
Is like you know like we can be killed by violent right right
Right
Right haha
Haha create their cells
To be immortal
There's too many people to their immortal
I don't want to run
Getting in the way of their
They're fun because you are because you know what you know what I think of these Immortal people who know what they would really love to do is
Spend their time
In an agrarian exist
Growing their own food
You know not having people
Society around
Weathers delegations of Labor in places
So we can all do different things out of the deal with her
Basic necessities
All the time
Set reminder this reminds me of
If there's like a couple thousand Goebbels how are they going to have a Sanitation
System
What are we going to do
Well I mean in asimov's the robots of dawn
Trilogy one forgot about the robots
I believe what happened is they went off to another planet
The immortal
Rich people
And they had giant massive Estates
Covered with nothing but robots that
Took care of everything
For them
And then never saw an another human being in real life
They always got video chatted essentially
Ian
Man came
And he was like this is terrible
And then they were like
Yeah I think you might be right yeah it's
Dystopia
This is
Yeah the point of those novels like that are generally like
Oh no this is what happens when rich people have ideas
Technology is a great thing and it could be used in a lot of good ways but laugh
Dr. go entirely in One Direction.
Any wife
I believe
That's a Alex
Has no business
Speaking on public issues
He is a
Toxic awful s*******
Navagraga list
They might have thought differently at various point
And Alex's career
This is so stupid
Talk to them at their level about
Then you don't deserve to live
You'll be able to
Bring your perspective to the table
And we will listen
But if you just
Opposed
The public is profaned or evil
And you want to join us later
You eat that say that a bit now like everyone probably just
Deserves to die
Yeah he does say that quite a bit
I want I want to say one thing
I don't
Know if
I believe
That
The devil
Was trying to enlist Alex when he was a little kid
And then throughout his entire life
Haven't simultaneously the globalist have been trying to enlist him
Like it seems like maybe that's
In his head
Either that or there's a coup
Full court press for the past
30 years
To get Alex Jones on the time before he ever had political inclination
I was like a predestination thing childhood magical ability
I will new would be a problem for in later little bit psychic
Hahaha
Possibility is is making all this up
Could be another one is
These nuts
Is
I mean the Alex's the hint
Avalanche Panda pond with
All time and history relies
Like he is
As goes Alex
Sogos hiss
It does feel like that is his Central thesis
I can't imagine a more
Person in the world is the things he saying are true
The devil tried to recruit him and then his enemies and tried to recruit him
By the way
Control all of the world's governments that all of the monetary systems
They've tried to recruit him
When they were trying to recruit him
They would have allowed his input
To go into their plans
The globalist initially wanted him to moderate
It's their globalist plans with his perspective or at least his ideas
Kind of makes me question whether or not the globalist
Plans
For a long time seemed like if they were still looking
Cantor input from a twelve-year-old Berkshire their plans were not good
Find me portable
So f****** stupid
Congratulations Rogan
Hanging out with a f****** xenophobic racist to think he's the most important person in the world congrats
Yeah yeah that's great
His show is the way it is
Because of choices that have been made
Over the course of
The last
Couple decades
He has fine-tuned to show in Waze
I like this works
For me
This isn't the way we do things
But you know what
Kind of sucks
Analysis like I wanted this she'll have to be the way it is that's a good question
Empowered
I feel inrage the Goblin
Get angry
I really want to try to start doing a show this commercial free music free
Very small crew off the weather's great crocosmia podcast
It's crazy it's the latest show
Evolve
I like it but it is
And it's frustrating
It's not really who I am
What
I was wrong about the good in the world and the beauty in the world and the good part of
Squirrels goddamn
Starry night and how it evokes
Hotel motion beyond all reason to tell you about why Humanity should not be destroyed
Dumb dick to advocate for love
I really do enjoy the way he's like
Alright the show evolve the way it did but this isn't me
This absolutely this show is definitely not an expression
Of my rapidly deteriorating mine
It's frenetic and fast
That's my way of saying I never really cover anything but that's not
All of Me
The globalist
My children upset me sometimes
Look at that.
Yeah
There are thousands of fake ideology
Thousands of fake gurus
Thousands of false tool that the system doesn't block
And the system doesn't care about
It's going to make it all okay
No
There is a scientific development
Kill everybody machines become God
The planets
Happening
What's coming after all of us
I have no desire
In fact I have a roboutian
And a repulsion of being part of it
And if you don't have a revulsion of these people
You are not in God's orbit and you got a serious problem
Got a serious problem, cuz the devil
In the form of these people who want to become robots
Yeah for a guy who wants
Schools to teach
Which that black people came to America because
Because they were looking for jobs in a free market
I don't know how much I want him telling me what
Schools are telling the truth
No
Reasonable point
The beginnings there with like
There are a lot of things that should be banned
From YouTube that are
And it is it is a little strange that there is
You know the thing
Get the attention
That are necessary for them
Take action and the things
Is that the don't you know like
Like I can see all kinds of like
Space cult
Probably being as dangerous
To somebody
When you look at some of the investigative reporting on
Facebook and how they not just
Kowtow to conservatives but actively
Like help them out
You're like
You're not wrong
Corporations are evil Dave there's these ideologies that are
Sharkbanz
I guess the answer will be even
More social media Crackdown
Cuz I I don't think the answer is just let anyone say whatever they want
Doesn't seem like he doesn't last YouTube
Decided that
Exactly what they want their
And then
I think I could leave
Cousin problems
Probably
But
I don't know the devil
He's coming he's usually, Alex knows this because he
He's connected to God
And he's also connected to the devil
Okay we've heard him say that we worked him say that he has a weird position living in between both
Both Worlds and then it goes
Real bad
And I can see
These guys
The sunglasses on
I want you to put the sunglasses on and we're not going to be fighting
The Haitians are a weapon that the globalist of controlled and dominated and enslaved as slaves
Hundreds and hundreds of year
Gold bars flavors
To us
And there's some up or terribly evil people
Just like everybody else but the point is they're coming
End of the globalist pan
To be controlled and use the political weapon
I'm all for water
I love beautiful lakes and waterfalls I love to water-ski
And I love to do all that stuff
Around the jet ski
45 minutes till I die
Dirty corrupted water
Being brought to our dirty corrupted country to bring us
Energy
Jesus
Right
So Haitians
Don't care about their children or with
Pictures are like
Thugs survival
Yep and then not just that but they are also a
Tool and a weapon
A pretty standard nationalist ideology go to
The other populations from like develop
10 countries are being used as a
Weapon by the globe
Alex says
Quite a bit
I just don't like the idea of like the Haitians are like water they're dirty
Did water
God what the f*** is wrong with you
Yeah that's
Really really
Really
These immigrants are being brought in because that'll take down America
And then once
America's gone there'll be nothing
Sing to fight the Antichrist
Yeah that's right this is where this is going
They're being brought here as a political weapon just like every other group is
Because once the country goes down they'll be no other example of America
And the whole world's going to go down
And fold Antichrist control
Why
Halftime Folk
It's only the halftime this Alien Force
Is going to win at halftime but rules in the 4th quarter
Okay
So
I don't know
Think it's a little bit funny
That like
I don't know
Skeptic
And all those
Does Certo
Communities are
Pretty into being like
Starbucks stock
Oh yeah yeah he believes that
Yeah
You know I think it's
I think it's weird
And then
And then it all in and then it made perfect sense
Because
For people who
Prophesy should all the time
Prophecy is coming true
Is aren't in Port
But because
If it's the only thing that could possibly validate your religion
Is it all of your prophecies come true
That's it
And the Book of Revelations
Is done
There's you can't make more Book of Revelation
So is the Book of Revelations doesn't happen
As it's written
But your religion is a lie
Or it requires a reinterpretation
Sure
Sure but they're basing their
He's raising his Bible on that it's the literal
Truth of God
Sure
By God's for him it's a problem so to fight against what happens in The Book of Revelation
Is to blaspheme against
God himself
And say that you have power over here I'll see I thought about that but then I think that another way to look
Look at it is that Alex has doomed
Himself to a losing
Fight
And that he has cast himself in the role of the people who played against the aunt
Antichrist
Toulouse Aptos
Sure and that's the position he's putting them
Southend
Digging some kind of
I think I think it allows him
Say these kinds of things that he says about immigrant give these positions
Be such a toxic
Awful
Danger is Persona and still
Pretend that he's a good person like somehow like there is there's a
There's Integrity to what I'm doing
Because I'm fighting against the Antichrist
Like I'm going down with the ship or whatever as opposed to like I'm just trying to get people
Look at it if you want to sleep
If you want to sleep that is a good way to recontextualizing your monstrous action
Alex said he was going to
Get back to talking about that video of him
When he was younger cuz that's
Fun
That is fine but turns out
There's no time for
Fun mr. Jones
You know I said I'd get to the fun Alex Jones thing
Casino fun
Enough fun Abilene
Dogs 2
Maybe I'll do it
Doctor coming on it was in the hospital and watch them basically killing people
Athan Runner who they wouldn't get medication to
We demanded I give him medication today
SWAT team
Hospital
For 4 hours
I didn't run out of the hospital and we said hey
Let us know what happens while they wouldn't give the guy any Aid
Hospital doing
He was a long-term medical doctor he's retired
He was telling what they
Monex
And they just said no there's no time for fun
Cuz you got to interview this guy who was in a hospital
Text to a guy
And then
SWAT team
I don't know that's pretty confusing
I would like a more concrete narrative about
The guy comes on the show but a little bit
I don't even think it's at the gas
Let's do this
This guy with the backup
The story
I think that's a little bit
Yeah but there is still some time for fun
And it says teenage
Content creator
Alex Jones
You going to say there's an underlying story here
Did he get a head injury at some point after this
Cuz I was so nice and friendly and sweet
There's a tens of thousands of tweets of women saying
Really nice guy
New about all this stuff and I was finding it
Lived it and went through 20
728 years of it
Took a toll on me
Caring about myself and my family everybody else
I can't do much that's why I'm not this
Sensible seeming
Hot young man anymore
There's no way I could change my Offspring Have It
Snowbird
That's what that's what I think is really interesting is that like there's a
Physical defensiveness that Alex has about like how
People singing used to be hot
There's also a defensiveness
You seem like a normal person
Like there's like
You have
Lost it both physically and
Emotionally and intellectually
You are a
Essentially a completely different
In the like
Madden stat level
They've all gone down Universal
It's like it's like
It's like
The difference between Madden Drew Brees in 2001
And Madden Drew Brees in 2014 there's a big difference
Category that Alex is still really high at
That's true he still got it yeah he does still got it
Better
It turns out
Is releasing films
Cuz you know it's been a long time
Confused as to how he's got
I'm better about
Well I mean
It's been like 9 years since he did it
Well that is better
Get back on the horse
Need to fight back against the new lockdown
That's why we made a new film the first of the five-part series
Full film called coven land
Robert Kennedy Jr Dr Sherri Tenpenny myself everybody else star-studded
Restart traffic.
Reverend proud of the cell
A British gentleman because I fired
Yeah
Yep I don't got I don't got any in-house production staff
Got to go somewhere else
We will keep coming up with ideas and I fire a pic Gators Gates
Signal is gone up
I may have to check in on
Covid lab documentary
So this.
Doctor comes on
Stephen Belafonte
His deal was that he was in the hospital being treated for covid and he decided he would go ahead and play doctor for the person playing
Tire Doctor
He's way up on current Medical Technology I'm sure
Javonte looked over the guys records
You got permission from the guy in the
So it's not like a total violation of pneumonia diagnosis
And they wouldn't listen to him when he brought it up
The next details are a little bit hazy because it
It's just kevantes telling of the story because obviously the hospital can't comment on the treatment
Given to a third person without their
Arkansas
Other patients ad
Advocate let the nurses
Call the doctor so excited
Like he was going to check himself out against medical advice right
At that point allegedly he was restrained for a while and then he was
Discharge from hospital against medical advice
From the story something that doesn't match up
Anyway
I don't think I'll tell you one thing that I know for
The fact is in that story and left out
That guy was an a****** to a bunch of people
Belligerence I would assume
Or I think that there is a possible liability that the hospital could take on
Totally this guy is acting as a doctor inappropriately like
You can't do that just because this guy says like I am his medical Advocate or whatever does
Mean
That there isn't still a lawsuit possible
I don't know I don't know exactly but there's something missing
I don't really care about what it is right
Because
This guy
Davonte
Comes on Alex's show
Are you talkin about this other patient there was there in the hospital with him
And this guy is dying
And now there's a funeral that's going to happen
Alex
It's really excited kind of about this story anyway that's just
And by the way did you talk to the families that how you got photos of the man would you like to say his name or they want that
Humanizing
His name is is Keith
And his funeral is
Next
Next Saturday
And there's a GoFundMe page
As far as hero
Kids are looking at our
I didn't know that so I'm glad you're back on can you dock look that up or let us know
Like to get his children on a guy's The Producers can we call
Mother daughter cancer
Antiviruses sv40 Restylane
Dad dad
Wow what a doctor telling us about that
Wow he's Alex's just decided that this woman who he knows nothing about had a cancer that must have
Have been caused by vaccines
Oh wow
What a way to turn this this
This tragedy into something
Profitable in your anti-vax
Phuc yea
If this doctor is offended by missing a pneumonia diagnosis offended by that
No cuz he is
Cuz he's a she
Absolute
And so one of the things that he did was
If you took a picture of this guy
Not in the hospital
And posted it on Facebook
Facebook
Presumably
He got permission from the guy
Keith
Time to post
This picture on Facebook
Papa guess what
The family
Is not thrilled about
Have you had a chance to talk to the family
I yes
They were not happy with me
Overstaying his
Hospital
On on Facebook
But I'm afraid
Where's my Facebook
Post that got
That got him
Antibiotics and
Noi Channel
Yes
Yeah you knew him better than his kids
Wow
I mean
I can't imagine
Like
If it
Because here's the story
That you could
Tell
I guess
Is
Either
The patients
Says
Nonono current doctors
Listen to this
80 year old man
Miami be like 70
And then
Give me what he says right
There's no way you wouldn't
Sue the hospital later and be like how f****** dare you take the advice of this crazy person right
I don't know how to do that
To him
Is
Insane
I don't understand
How
I don't understand how this guy to show this
Avanti
Can look in the mirror
And
Recognize that the family of this
Person
Like
Davonte isn't somebody who's
Relevant at all
The only reason that he is even on Alex's shows cuz he was in the hospital next to this guy
To be f*****
In an episode of Scrubs
The other guy
Is essentially what Vic Avanti is riding
To attention on
And
The family does not appreciate that
V8 just appearing on the show
And discussing this stuff
Is legitimately
You can
Safe assumption against the wishes of the family
It's an insult
Degrading
End-to-end to then have
Alex be like oh yeah
Young people don't want attention until their emotional
I mean
Now
So he keeps mentioning that they have a GoFundMe for the funeral
And
The plug it and I
Very glad actually that he doesn't
Actually knows what it is
It's not like a
Choice
These people
I'm glad
Mostly because
Seems pretty clear
The family does
Not like this guy at all
But I'm sure the family appreciates you now trying to save their father
Ya never know
Remember doctors are the Bringers of bad news
So I don't know if I'll find out
Appreciate me or not
At the funeral
No do not have much to go to his funeral
And you know
I mean
Can I say the lady wants it was choking
Great
Look if someone if you don't if you're not sure the family is going to be pissed off at you or not
Don't go to the
Funeral you pile of s***
I will tell you what I would do if I saw him show up at a funeral
Call SWAT team
Rocking chair for 4 hours
I don't understand
Get it
How can how can you live like
What a
You f****** psycho
That's just that level of like
Maybe you don't have any empathy
Like that's just it
Insane
That's just
So f****** disc
Respectful
I mean just
Exploitative and all in your own service to make
You feel like you were importing row and a hero yeah absolutely
From boring
Like okay maybe this guy had a
Misdiagnosis of the
The person
Next to him in the hospital and I don't
Care to like
Wow it's really clear even from the way you are talking
That this family is not
Thrilled with your behavior
And how your
Exploiting their loved one
And that's f***** up
That is not
It's just wrong
I mean it's gone skywok
Furious if he went on local access news
Let alone to go on
F****** info
Talking about like your loved one
Oh my God
Absolutely we want last clip and it's Alex discussing we we've heard him talk
B about
Like you know there's
People getting covid around
We haven't really talked
I heard him talk about like
Some specific
And it turns out
His parents
Especially his dad
Maybe it'll really severe case
Father
Grandmother got sick
5 weeks
I told the story
Incredible
Apparent
My mommy
Triathlete
And
That does well
But they did tell me they were sick
And I will accept this is serious I go over there
And my dad is
Not knowing who he is
And he looks blue
Call dr. Barbara he sends over medical doctors he knows the house there was no straight people
Mother french benefits being Alex Jones there's like they're like an hour
Being rich
They thought they got a small Pharmacy
I got the
Ivermectin got the
Pill steroids they said
Neymar making do this and that making breathing
I was literally not slapping but like 10 she would say
Back to sleep my mom's doing the same thing
And he lost
Like 20-something
He's not fat
Like I am and
By the next morning again they delivered a bunch of lawn chairs again
And he was there putting them together
Now his mind at a fog
2 Days Later was back at 97%
And that was the Ivermectin that was a steroid and we know
I don't believe that
Number
One of them is that Alex has always said
These things
Are like
Their miracle cures
We got to give it to him
People early
Alex's dad was
Deep into AC
Sickness absence there that is not early in
It's not like the
Even based on the conspiracies and
The b******* that Alex bread
At that point
And should not have been helped
Fulda a.m.
Second
I don't know how much of this is real
I don't know how much of this is true and how much of it is a story Alex's telling
But if there is truth to this
I don't see like
I don't see it being impossible that Alex got his dad's
Maybe gave him
Something that could be per
Yes brain fog
It wasn't there
You know if
To whatever extent it is yes absolutely put like
Just based on what Alex's report
His dad had a brain fog that has not gone away now five weeks later
This could be something that he got through
Hoosier
From Alex
Not taking the virus seriously
And could that be
The rest of his life and even if it's not
It's deeply traumatic
Toulouse
20 lb if you're 71 then
And end up not knowing your name like fevers
Fever so high you don't know where you are
This is just sick s***
I mean and also one thing
How can
Covid
Be a bio-weapon
If everybody you know f******
Got it and your
Well
Assume
Right I mean Alex didn't tell these stories about Alex
His family being sick
Him being sick multiple times right for one at the office being sick tell those stories were very long time
Friends of Friends
Or other people who are any good
The case back
Who are dead and we just don't know it
He doesn't know it or if he does he's not going to talk about it absolutely
Talked about this before
When he was
Did it different stage
Do the covid graph
Like it's just
I find this episode to be like
I mean
I declared an episode Reese
Leon accept
Right right right
It's not wrong
This is not fit for human consumption it really is
It's really really really really f***** up
I don't know how many different ways you can be
I mean
Astonishingly disgusting
He and his
Blackwater buddy dehumanize the s*** out of immigrants
In ways that are
Reminiscing
Yeah
Of deeply deeply troubling times
He gets really bad into feet
Sensitive about how to use
To be hot and not insane
He
Spins weird Yarns about how the devil in the globalist have been trying to enlist him
How many interviews a guy who's
Using the memory of
Someone he was hospitalized with two
Get attention this is
Just
All of you
This is a
This is a real Viking
Villains row
Just like nonstop shiting
Yeah times when like doing this show is really fun
You learn about stuff in
Now and then there's times where I mad that we do this
I don't think I don't think that too I like it this is my job sometimes sometimes
Interesting and sometimes it's just staring into the
Gaping maw love
The depths of
Human
Depravity in disgust
You know just like
How how can how
How can you do this
Snook no argumentation is going
Going to convince
Alex or
Ex Blackwater guy that
People from other cultures love their children
Or just people
Nothing nothing nothing no response
That we have
Can possibly
Penetrate
That kind of
If thinking
And it's just
Depressing
That
People
Wood
Either willingly or unwillingly
Give Credence and credibility to someone
Whose job it is to spread b******* like this
I mean
Where We Are
Yeah it is it is one of those things
We're like
You
You have to step back from them
Because you realize that like these people are fuc
Disgusting in it
It's too late to like change their mind or anything
What needs to be
Dresses
How many
Famous people
Public people people
Barb
Attaching themselves to this
Who are
I mean I would hope at least a little more fungible in
Let's kill all of non-white peoples
I know you even hope that their their support is based on a lack of awareness not of the things that
Actually talks about
As opposed to them
Actually being on board with this
Horrible vile bullshittin
It's either that or
It just be like a Joe Rogan isn't out now.
Bien
Hey.
Owl
Well anyway
Will be back
Hopefully
Episode
Until then we wasn't fighting
Not go to bed Jordan
Adelia Clark of Darrell rundus
The sex robots
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work