Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge by now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about Alex Emerick Joe
Jordan Jordan
Passion 47
Whatsyourprice
Today Jordan age
Still upcoming
But ever-closer
I finally found two
Finally going to be a movie
Look at mine is that I finally found veal Aqua Beach Plum flavor
I missed it a couple of stores look for it at
I finally got my hands on out okay
A pack of them
And they're Cooling in the fridge as we speak
We haven't tried them yet but it's gotten
The anticipation is building
It's bad
It's going to be an intense emotional experience
If you're going to be I'm going
To get like
Beach Plum merch
I got hat and I got a reply
Recovered heads
Either that or you're going to see the other eleven of these
Thrown out my window
In fury because
Can't possibly just be okay
And the reason is not just because it couldn't be I'm sure
Could be okay
Because it's so built up
Attention crack one way or the other is not going to just
Ben no
And I'm here to make an announcement what's that
Next episode of ours
Episode 6
I'm going to try the
The Plaza Live
I will hold out until our next episode
So everyone can have the Delight of
Experiencing okay that'll be too much for not special drug number episode
Fuel pump brand
It does I like it
Spots this week
Today or whatever so much you know
I suppose there's this I have a silver leg
My grandma passed away
Sorry to hear that a couple of days ago
And
You know it
It's it's tough but
For the past
3 years ago
It's been
A style of living that I would
Aspire to
So in the end you do it
It's not good that it's now but it
It's not
Bad that it's
You know 95 years
Think so
There is that
It could be it could be much much
So I got that
That's about as close to
A bright spot
Get this week
It's not great
Look up better maybe later it might be
A judge you for you know having these feelings
Dino
I guess I guess
You could frame it is a bright spot is that she's not in pain to nobody
Incredibly well
I didn't say it was a bright spot I would probably be more eloquent
Bratz
I'm sorry for your loss Jordan it is
I understand where you're coming
Jordan today
We have worked
Davido
I'm not really a human I don't I don't know how to talk to a human
We have work to be done
They were talking about the past we're going to June 13th 2003
A reason is decided to its
At what one of the rights that I
Retained
For myself
Is that I reserve the right
To go back
And put Alex on timeout
Whatever I feel it is appropriate
After our last episode was so white nationalist disgusting
The phobic I just felt like I don't I don't even want to
I don't even want a
Risk emotionally engaging
And that
I'm tired of vaccines
And I don't want to risk the audience having to engage with more of that with him the same week
We can be with this
Down the line but today we're going back to the greener pastures
If they weren't
They weren't really that much bergner
Our last episode had to be like
I do
Harrison Smith isn't what am I am I looking for a more boring white nationalism right now
Disgusting to me so yes
Button-up white nationalism
Because I don't want my white nationalist
Ripping shirt off
Scream at me while riding down there
Greased up like a pig
Buy I do not want that
So this is going to be an interesting
Episode we have some
Some news stories that Alex's covering
Possibly well
Possibly not well
And then I really funny thing happens when to call her calls in and W Alex
Superdude Source that'll be fun
The first Reverend shorty doo-wop thank you so much you're now policy walk
I would like to hang out with that
With that it's not a person that's a robot
Could be next squirrels thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Pretty please do more live streams
Very much
I mean have we ever done one that was hours
Watson way back
It's the way back yet you did some videos
Some games we can play Magic
We could
We could do some streaming of us could probably do it I can figure it out
If you can figure that out maybe we'll do that
Steven
Find Jay from the Mohawk Nation
MattyB on this level you turn up
Love Eric J from the Mohawk Nation
Heroin
Yub
Freakishly large
I realize that it's been a little while since we've had an out-of-context drop
Maybe it hasn't been
It feels like it has
Yes and so I'm thrilled to start today's episode
With an auto Conte
Oh
So that's why he doesn't
Mystery solved explain that
You know what I feel like he got it out of the way in 2003 he had those
So good
Sabaton
Depression
So we start off today show with Alex covering a story about a Massachusetts family
Got in trouble
Cuz I didn't want to take a standardized test
Audible articles
Are almost grown up
They are refusing
Threaten them
Purple
Were you going to wrap
I just
I don't know what
Story this is
I hear these details and I'm like
Nothing
And I noticed there was this pattern
It's kind of develop
In the past that is like
And it's like
I'm going to have to really dig
To figure out what the fuc
Well if
If there was
If his story was true
I feel like it would be
Easier to go
You know whenever you go back and look for stories for him is in the Paw
What are the easiest ways to know it's not true is that it's very hard to find
Because this story
Would be very easy to find true I'm not sure
Easily be
A bit of a domestic
Family Court
Type of issue
Isn't there anymore on the website or something
Think of this local news
Organization
Impossible
You know whatever it is Peter a non-story
Happen or the sum lie
Very difficult
The track down
Conversely
I will agree with
If you that like
This next story that I was talking about
If this happened
Ever want to know about the
Home
What
Again
Grilled
That little
I have some thoughts
So so if I understand
What he's
Televator
Correctly
SWAT teams every four or five months about three times a year a SWAT team will go into a school
Andrews
Moe everyone down
And including themselves sure
So it's just a big orgy of bullets
And we don't know about this
Yeah.
It's not making the news somehow
June 30th
Stories about this
Around
Drill
So at this point I'm kind of getting bewilder
Pretty rare that Alex talks about the
Specific incidents that I can just
I can't find any evidence of having happen
Usually there's some detail that he's getting wrong and it makes
More difficult to track down as I heard them
I was struggling
Beautiful story about the having the family having their children taken
Because they wouldn't take a task was intriguing
Short on details about school shooting in the kind of thing that
Everyone would have written an article about
They shoot a kid
What stop is something that would be drills for a while at least conversation
Maybe shooting drills are bad
According to Alex the SWAT team to come to the school in Detroit to do a drill and they shot a kid in the
Huge deal
Can't find any news stories about this happening
And that is
Did happen
But then Alex kept talking and it became clear that I think you
Well it's happened again
Ganja plant
Drill
The year
Grill
So within a couple minutes now the story seems to be that a year prior
Cop shot another cop in the head of the school drill right
I don't know what this is the same story or like what I don't know what's going on
This still isn't good but you definitely can see that this
Doesn't appear to be the same
I think it's something that's very important to
Who is involved in this is that
0 zloty
True so the upside is now actually know what some of the details of that story are
Chance of tracking down the store
The thing is
The only thing I can find that
The clothes doesn't even match the second
Conversion of Alex's story
So I believe that Alex is talking about Corporal Joseph Kush
Men based on the details of the story that he's telling
Cushman was involved in a training exercise in an area junior high school and was engaged in a demonstration with another officer when
Are there gunfire Deadshot Cushman in the head
There's some really critical details that match up with Alex's narrative
Princess this was a police officer who was shot in the head within the general time frame
Of when Alex was saying this was supposed to happen
Cushman was not named top of the
The year if that's
Nothing but
He was the police
Rookie of the Year in 1999
And you've been promoted a day before he was killed 99 mile an hour fastball
But there are these details also that don't
For one that didn't happen to Detroit happened to Darling
Texas
Second Alexandra's happened around children but that's not true the school district is on summer vacation
And there were no students on campus when they were doing the training
There were 200 students enrolled in summer school classes but those classes ended at noon and this exercise began at 3 p.m.
3rd Cushman didn't die on the spot he was taken by helicopter to John Peter Smith Hospital
It was pronounced dead at 7:30 that even
I'm fairly sure Joseph Cushman is a cop that Alex is talking about at least partially because the reference to the story as the is the
Fort Worth Star-Telegram
Which is a paper that would be much more likely to cover an accidental police shooting in
Denton Texas
Good morning.
Detroit
The story itself is horrifying and it's a good argument against many things like you know cops using real guns
The training exercises or having guns
Cops using schools to Stage training had it all
Guns at all yet
You can take the actual details of the story and use it to make the points you want but
How to basically just a dick
Adeline
He can't tell us straight version of the story even if it works
For some of his points yeah
Children being president
SWAT team
I want to see this because I feel like
I could
Be bordering on
Offensive in some
I don't know
If there was an incident where a student got shot
School end
Detroit by a cop
Dragonite
I will allow that there is a possibility that this is
Strew
I can't
Find
Vic story that Alex is talking about
But I don't want to be like that didn't happen on the off-chance that there is some real incident
And there's real there's a real tragedy that Alex's
In some way mischaracterizing
In the world
That we live in
It is
More possible
That
Something like that
Or at least possible enough that were true everybody would be like
Okay
That happen
Is part of the story but Alex
Can still be lying about it
Yeah if it even if it happened somewhere else
It's not like he remembers everything of that kind of
I can't tell what's going on in terms of what the stories are
Find
Clear case of what he's talking about the cop of the year
I can't figure out what he's talkin
Sing about
In terms of Detroit and I don't know if there's
Supposed to be the same story
I just don't want to be disrespectful on the off chance that there is a story that I met totally at night so
Yeah yeah
Cupboard
So there's another story that Alex has that makes
The point that the SWAT teams are evil
They use special weapons
More cops being killed
Throwing up
Video audio
But at least the innocent man
One of the things that I think it's really key to understand and recognizes the way that Alex uses vagueness as a weapon when he tells his
Stories any always has
He doesn't get into specifics
Even give enough
Detail for you to really know what story he's talking about because
These stories aren't here to be accurate representations of things that happen
They exist to evoke feelings that support his worldview
This case from Lubbock is about Sergeant Kevin Cox
Who was shot and killed during a July 13th 2001 standoff
Happy home of Richard Robinson
Robinson he barricaded himself in the house following a fight with his wife
Apparently also in the process of getting some small fires in his front yard
So the police
Gather information about the case and they learned that Robin
Benson head quote talk to a relative earlier in the day about suicide
Well the police were attempting to approach the house
Throw in some gas
Shooting broke out in attic
Confusion of it all that it wasn't clear how it at all gotten started
When the dust settled Cox
Sipping fatally shot and Robinson was arrested and charged with his shoe
However
Upon analysis of the 13 guns he had which Alex
Cuz weirdly reporting a 0 gun
The police determine that Robinson did not actually fired any guns during the standoff
So he couldn't
Do possibly shock cock
Yeah
A week later on July 20th Robinson was released in the charges are dropped
His lawyer told the Lubbock Avalanche-Journal quote
We're so pleased that the police
Didn't try to cover anything up and the Disco
Attorney's office did the right
Ultimately was determined that another op
Officers fired the bullet
Who killed Cox
And there was
Good reason for the shooting to a broken out in the first place
Except some kind of like
No conversations about in in
Insufficient
Training
That kind of thing
Yeah I would like taking there
Their guns away but that's fine
The big message of this story is the cops need better training and maybe in a situation like the one Robinson was in militarized police
Police aren't the best approach
Possibly better outcomes could have been reached
Social workers are mental health professionals were dispatched
Instead
Maybe we'd all be better off
Who took some of that
That's funding that goes to the police and diverted it to better approaches
Complicated situations like the one
That this man was
I be so cool if Alex at
Still hated
The police like
A lot cooler on a lot cooler term think so if he's still hated the police I think I think it would be
Easier for you to be tricked
Into believing that he wasn't
Horrible bigot or a horrible
The cops doesn't mean I'm not I'm going to forget you're a horrible big idea of it would make things a little bit smoother for me there's a whole lot of people
People who I think
Piles of s*** it have a distrust
Civilianaire
Definitely true
Taking this story and fudge some of the details to make the central narrative about the police trying to frame this guy
With the information doesn't support that narrative at all
In order for Alex
To fit the square peg into a round hole he has to lie about things like whether or not Robinson had a gun
Disagree
Fiction about
The police planting a gun on him in a good guy cop on the scene blowing the whistle
Alex is a liar
But it's important to understand that he has to be
In order to maintain the political beliefs he holds
He could not deal with stories honestly and still have the same point
Zup
Yeah I mean
Part of what we're dealing with is that
As much as he's talking to everybody else on his radio show he's also convinced
Sing himself that he's not
Monster
So
But look dude
You are worried about
SWAT teams
I heard it on the news
Increase
Funding
Police departments are they going to increase the funding of them
Planting guns on you it when they kill each other
If
If this isn't
Specific murdering / covering up
The murder at training people they will need to allocate more funds for guns to leave at the
So I suppose they will have to dhs's probably don't have to increase funding for that
Yeah to have about the problems with policing
This is childish it's his bad
This is bad
Divert you from an actual conversation into like
But I kill you I plant I got on you okay
Okay buddy alright
Which is not to say that they don't do that
About every time
So what are the things that I think is really fascinating would you go back to 2000
Jordan
As you start to see things but Alex has an awareness of it he doesn't
In the present
Maybe primary aspect of his brand
Our misunderstandings that he didn't have any
The past weird
Yeah it's very strange like
Princeton
This one caller calls in
On this side is here June 13th
Shelton
And he's mad about G Gordon Liddy
Right
Gordon lady
Is on the radio
Brightness guy calls in
I like how does it feel to be on a station that's full of censorship
And people
Better about G Gordon Liddy sure
What's the farthest they won't have Alex's show on there are proof
Alex understands that this kind of thing
Is not censorship
Mister lady
I'll just wanted him to know that time
He was on the radio station
That would not allow your program to go on the air
All you talk about me
No I
That he was on a
Station that would not allow your program on the air
I wanted to get his feelings about that
Is alive and well
Islanders country we know.
Call format
Local
Program
Lahore
Well you won't
So are saying it would be someone's right have someone on their
Bamiyan certainly heat that seemed spelled out by the comments
Thingy there censorship
He knows that it's not that
Right leg is it if you have an internet platform that
You know you own
Right and you don't want somebody on there is a real piece of s***
You're right there country
Weird
Strange weird
Alex gets it
Conveniently doesn't
It is almost like they're all making it up as they go along depending on what they think will benefit the most in the exact moment they
With no long-term plans whatsoever
So Alex gets another call and this actually charged me quite a bit
The paper
And what's Alex's house
I don't think he does a great job
But
He does do a good job of revealing a very quickly that he has no idea what the person is talking about
I'm writing a paper for my
School about the ethical arguments if there is one
Regime change in
Cake on the riots
24-hours there
Rehash
The 19th
CIA
Basically riding in the streets against
President khatami
Over there and trying to ask
The Muslim clerics better
People with incredibly brutal choirboy
Fascinating that response is so weird
He starts talking about like the present-day situation in 2003 and Alex
Cut Her Off
And start stalking
You just get the two is talking point
Like the little bullets that he remembers
His
Move there
Which she should have
Called-out immediate
You know like to talk about that why don't you explain what's going on
That it was an instant like
Dude you have no idea what's going on
Why don't you explain it for what's going on for the rest of the crowd obviously I know what you're talkin about
But you can explain it better than I could your more eloquent
Words for you not to explain it over by your calling in to ask for help with a high school paper
High School paper maybe College
You could explain it better than I can
There are people whose way of engaging is a little more
Socratic
That is something that I would believe from someone
What do you want to use explain what's going cuz then you can
Get a better sense of what their understanding of what's happening it is
Thanking figure out you know
What do play you'd like to
Take the conversation
F****** foreign for Alex
He Rambles about everything
He let her talk for
5 seconds before you started talking about the shop
So y'all are also need the citation
What I want that in
Justice
Sixteen-year-old girl just like
I am writing a paper about one of the most concert
Sequential issues of our day I am going to call into the only man who speak
Speaks the truth
Cuz you can't trust the mainstream media so I'm going to get his take on it
Could you explain why you don't know and you don't know a f****** thing
Finally this is delusion
CIA badge
Also needs a little citation was on the Galaxy's talked about and it's
This is not good going to go out
Question
I'm I'm kind of right
About the meal times and I was wondering how
Where can I go to get
Some information on how to connect them to the gillioz
Sprouts
Neocon
This is just an editorial article from the Asia times that Alex is telling a student to use as their primary source about the connection between
Leo Strauss
Neoconservatism
An a****** teaching the Next Generation to do a bad job
I think you make a compelling argument
There's some connection between Strauss
The leaders of the nyoka
Conservative movement from at least an idea logic
Legal perspective
You'll find some overlaps but
You shouldn't rely wholly on the headline of
Op-ed to do so
Like if you know anything about the sub
Pick your covering Alex should be able to
2.2
If you're a teacher and someone like
Work cited page
Does an editorial like that
That's not good
It is
It is fascinating to notice
Respect any any right-wing
S******* liberal
Wing s*******
Propagandist
Is absolutely going to
To fail any High School
Yes like
Apps any anything
Any
Hold them to the standards that you would hold a high-schooler too if you're doing
They will fail miserably Alex's head 15 years to come up with a bibliography for endgame and if I were in
High School teacher I would throw that of a
Trash
Get out of here
To get out of here
Yeah so Alex has another thing he wants a yell at this young lady about
Where he can prove that needle cons are actually communist
But you can find
Infowars.com
Walk The Halls in the White House
Thank you very much Alex
You better not really make
All around
I doubt it
I am confused yet
Just another iPad
Excuse me excuse me child
Where did you get this s*** sweet
Himself told you to do that
Who's Alex Alex Jones
Why are you taking his advice
Dear God
This is just look really awful work being mirrored B being modeled for the
Like it's just
If they learn
From this like how you're supposed to
To present your information
Your work we're doomed
The deflation I heard a tone of deflation in her voice so I would think so
I would suggest that she learned
From this experience know not what she was hoping
And she will not be the last
Call her be disappointed by Alex on this episode
I'm so Alex bees like you know that teacher of yours
When you tell him
The f******
Mainstream media has admitted a neocon the communist
Breakout
Alex has no idea anything about this teacher and he doesn't know if it's a man he doesn't know it
Did the Lefty
Medication anyone in education does not compute
Oh man oh no oh no you showed me an op-ed I've got to
But is it is really funny that foundational mess that they they have about their knowledge of like
He's going to wake up people on the left
And their examples are always somebody who's like
I've never paid attention to politics
Show me YouTube video
Never somebody is like I
Yeah I have a education
Not going to happen
Oh well
So Alex in the present-day loves Michael Savage
Don't talk about it awhile but he the last we heard he loved Michael said
Images of patriot
Brightness
Turns out 2003 hours
Hey does Michael
Programming
You find out
Yard
So what I would like
Is
Alex to wrestle with or have a discussion about what
Changed about Michael Savage
Between 2003
And what's a 2019
Or
I would like him to have a conversation about what
He misread in 2003 and how wrong you was about Michael Savage being a wolf in sheep
Clothing in it
A greasy hippie
I've never considered Michael Savage
I wrote it down a dirty oily slimy
He was
He was a beatnik kind of guy or Lyon
The 60s and 70s
I don't I don't get that into that
No he was hanging out with like Ginsburg
Wayback
Alex Azar
Like that piece of his history makes him
Dirty beatnik
But it's like a
So I wouldn't he wouldn't like to find out very well house
Beatniks especially the ones that were involved they're all kind of
Wound up being
Nut bag
Interesting
So
Alex habit paper and
I think you realize like what happened
Pretended I was going to talk
Better figure out what I'm going to do and here is a great prediction on Alex's bar about what's going to happen in a run
Now
Call
Literal monarch
And now the fool again
I'm free lunches now
That's interesting I don't think this has come to pass
At this point the relatives of the shop come back in new monarchy
Like a King Arthur
Situation I imagine
Alright then like
All other news
Media stuff you use always
Is right
It's real tough to go from
Theocracy
Back
To a monarch
You know
Theocracy the religious people don't like going back to him and I
Monarchy
No not only a few years away from coming in
I was going to deal with that
Free election
So Alex just worried about everything
So so right
I don't know how he nailed this predict
But it was just
Spectacular
And they want to put my nose and now they have
Credit card as well
Real quick you talking about driver's
Work
Yeah man
Mommy needs
I don't know how he was so ahead of his time
I love that I want more conversation
With collars like that where he's like they're going to do this whole thing with computer chips that I got to put in there
The Meltdown
To melt Those computer chips and you can put it in a microwave
Okay you can go through their butts
Just called
Also
Find this
To be stupid
Well one big reason is like at this point Alex
Is less talking about the devil
Being the big bad guy and it's the banks
Are the big bad guys
Why the f*** would the bank
Thanks destroy their own industry in order to make all state IDs credit card
Ruin the entire basis of their financial power
Realize it's about
Power turns into power but we you when you have power you don't need money
Do you do
Are interconnected in a certain sub
You might say that
Yeah just feel like this
This era of the Schofield little bit more like
Sci-fi dystopia
We thought out
Scheme
Describe this app
Sitting there laying back
And like all right if I was going to torture
Everybody how would I do
Villains acting against their self-interest
So Alex gets another collar this guy has a great
Rate
Ask
And it's hey Alex
You know all those documents you got
Why don't you put them on a floppy
Desk
Cuz that we could look
I think that's a great ass
Normal question anyone could have her Alex
Okay Alex I believe you
Now
Can I get them document
Alex can't do it though
Soriana
Probably different
2 / $50
I know I would sure be here
Is
Computer addicted run off.
To get that data
I understand
What what
Newspaper articles and all that
Here's the problem hours
Today in the morning
45-minute interview
Live TV shows
2 a.m.
Do I wasn't
Yourself
First Weber
Cuz you have the X
Where would I get
It is further
This is
Are you worried
Downloaded
Floppy disk
The Farms
Okay
That's not what I was asking
Classic
Classic moves by people
Why don't you explain it and now we've also got the like
Look I'm just too busy
Can I can I ask
Also who the f*** are all these people they're interviewing Alex
TV shows on at the same day
Actually this busy into that he would love to put all of these World shattering
Floppy disk out then sell them to this guy
Haha
He's just
Very very very sincerely argue
732 that if Alex was
Sincere about what he was doing his State admission what do you
Pretending to be
Give the moral obligation
To make this floppy disk
Because if what
Keep saying is accurate
Then everyone must
No
Do you know what I mean
And if this is the proof
Right
And the proof needs to be seen by everybody
The problem with that is once you reveal your proof
You review
What can be critiqued right
Once you lay your proof on the table if someone like Dan can come along
See this service representative
CU this is what happens when I pull myself out here
Damn shows up and makes me look like a fool had a 30-year long careers
I don't want to be a jerk
I want to be a jerk
And like honestly I be on your team if your first mention anything I really would
I wouldn't be a racist but
Okay. I hate those funeral order
Conditional love is what I get from you
Not love
You're mistaking believing and love
I don't think unconditional believe in his effort healthy
Let me know you're not for this place get out of here you're going to need to see your computer tonight
Put it in the sink I have a place in the Republic of Texas
The Republic yeah I love that
Exchange
It's like the questions or
Straight up I are like
Alright
Yeah
I see what you're saying
I know you're busy but there's got to be someone else who can put this together like you personally
Oh yeah
Hey did you know that law enforcement magazine say stop
Sir Isaac
Expecting you to take no for an answer at least
The second or third time now that you have gone to number for II
Very angry
This goes on and actually Alex has a whole nother reason why you can't do this this is amazing
Call Emma
Thank you
Be able to
Lecture there.
Really
Copyright if you're arguing
StoryBots
Dump
Realized
I do that
You could take a deposit
Haha
Did you see that one brief moment of weakness that the other guy had and he was like
I won because I brought up the Specter of copyright law
In the sky has decided to take that seriously and now this is my reason for not providing
Slow down
So dumb
Beautiful
The globalist have these evil plan
Because
Can you get sued for copyright infringement listen I would love to tell you that my boss has murdered 38 people
But I signed an NDA
I'm sorry if true Alex is a rank
Coward
Everything seriously
I would love to save millions of lives
Shoestring budget here you know I'm paycheck-to-paycheck
And that's why you need to take something like this conversation like this it has been thoroughly embarrassing
And turn it into a money-making proposition
The White Cap America weave
About who the Real Enemy combatant before I do
Your call
Wards.com
Hope you order
Myself
The solution is always something
That will benefit Alex within his Revenue
That is just
The direction that ship goes
Play out
So pretty
Effectively
With this collar he like
I don't
Like I haven't seen nothing I would agree with
Much
This color believes
But I do think
Did from everything that they're bringing to the table and everything
The way the conversation
Amtrak's
I think they're being sincere
Yeah yeah I know there's and that's why I
I hate it more than everything else is because he
He's coming with a certain level-headed monotone credibility to own a voice is like
Listen I believe you
I just want to
Get everything I want to do what's best
Tour the Infowars
I'll leave early
Sure
And I just need these tools for how my supposed to get these manuals
But you have
And it's just sad
I've got that is sad that is that is one of those ultimate like
If that guy didn't lose cops
Copyright law
If that guy didn't lose confidence with that then your urine out
Screw forever because that's
Meet Your Heroes level of like
Oh no you're a you're a massive disappointment aren't you
So Alex gets back to the story about the family in Waltham Massachusetts and we can finally get some details on that
This is almost two hours into the show now where Alex finally gives details about the story that he started the show
Show talking about
So it's going to this family guy got in trouble as they want
Sure
Seems like
On the second telling there's an additional
Bit of information there's some more details of the people's names and like you can just
Search for these sentences that he's cold reading you can find
He's talking about
Hit pretty hard to find
The actual article that Alex's reading but you can find the text
Copy and paste it on all kinds of right-wing message boards
Hopefully run mid-june 2003 right with this episode of therein
Alright if I had the gas I would say that
Probably just reporting this trade-off
15.com
The most full version of this article I can
Can find is on three republics message
Bored and I don't think that this is a real
Article
I mean I think it might be a real article but it's possibly like
I don't know how much of this is
Is it apocryphal kind of like that Meme where the soldiers in the
Professor's classroom
Professor says something Soldier
Stand up
I love America and the professor like
750 bucks
Have you ever seen those memes no it's the same thing
So what I'm talking about is this article quotes
The department of social service worker named Susan escovitch
We have legal custody of the
The children and we will do with them as we see fit
They are miners and they will do we tell him to
Okay I absolutely do not believe that's a quote but it's presented as such in this article
But if you look closely you'll see that this quote
What is actually the inner being reported in this article
Actually a second hand
No that's not a quote from eskovitz that was relayed to the reporter by the
The family but is being included in the article as if it's a quote
Presentation of the story
Do you think the family might have had like a
But I don't know maybe like a personal interest that might
Colored perhaps everyday
Quote
Yeah and it may have also it like it
The article might be a little bit one-sided
As best as I can tell this was one in a long string of incidents involving this family's approach to homeschooling
Apparently the district that they lived in the school district their policy about homeschooling requires that
The educational plans be filed
But there is a set grading system in place for the students
Two things that this family refused
Comply with
According to the art
So are also currently article Terrence lost legal custody of the children in 2001 but it doesn't say what
For exactly an overall business
And it's not just about attached I'm really I said it was about a test I was like let's see what
Happens but now I'm starting to guess
But there's more than
What maybe the colonel of the present story has to do with this test Friday
It's not about that
What's going on is a much larger situation that
You know a lot of that context the stuff that fills in the picture is stuff that Alex has conveniently
We ignore it
Because this story is Lupron
For him and actually looking at the details and Reporting out the story
As it exists
How to make a less useful prop
Yeah yeah
They don't seem like the most sympathetic Heroes that
But he's trying to pay
Yeah and
You know it mean it's just so predictable like
Alex
Read through the story of us
Decline with it
It's fine
Larry it again
We will do and Emily
AR
Close close
I like that the clothes quote was still in the DS liquor with you
That's commitment to the bed
Spell probably
Close
Cold
Make sure you quote
One of the things that's so important now we know why he did The Voice
That has been cleared up but isn't
It is nice to know now
The only part of the story that he can
Youi really latches onto inserted
Can can really bring to life is this quote
That the second hand thing
It's just
Trash this is just bad
Yeah yeah this is
This is that level of
Dispute that you find on lyca
Did Judge Judy
Episode where
They're like telling you the story about moskovitz
Cement Judge Judy ass like 3 Quest
And and I like okay well maybe she didn't say
Maybe she didn't say exact
Actually asked if you know maybe she didn't say that it word for word
I find this
Tubi
Alex's Nisha is like at this point I mean you just fines like a couple of headlines
And Rambles about them sometimes does some characters
Easy job
It's pretty sweet that's nice
All you're doing is
TV interviews and avoiding work that could help people on us
If I were him I might have stayed right in that sweet Paca
Sweetie
Like Icarus he flew too close to the Sun with all those Upland
Story it is actually the story that he was talking about earlier which is there as headlines about the shooting
It schools
By the SWAT teams
Two stories today okay
You got one
Grill on
Brandon
Fort Worth
So again
I find some of the details definitely wrong
About to pass drills that Alex
Does talking about and
Some of them
Questionable
I'm not entirely sure
And also for this drill
That in the Florida
I couldn't get a sense of if there were kids
Around at all again it's during the summer
Right so like
I think I mean if the SWAT
Teams ran in
Started blowing children away and themselves then yes there would have had to be kids there in the article about
This Florida drill there's a reference to the football coach who was having a
Kamp-rite he couldn't he didn't even hear the gunshot
So presumably there's like a summer football camp what's going on
Outside in a way and maybe there is there in some areas
The school where they're nobody nobody is at
Yeah one of their guns went off
Because they didn't
Yaki The holster empty the chamber without going into the wall
Like
Obviously awful and bad but not
Rising to the level that Alex's
It was not SWAT teams going in and blowing everyone and themselves away
Dumb way to talk about this
Alex gets another call and
On the show
Track that
International
Remember that article about a wolf
In World War I
That's still available your website you have any idea
Okay
Wow
What I like that
Go
Yeah
I think he might have had a better answer if he hadn't have dealt with this same kind of thing twice on the ticket
Dollars and eating some kind of like a what are you talkin about
Look copyright law
Honestly
I bet
He remembers the show
Three colors asking him for documents
That must have been his worst show in the history of the world pretty nuts cuz it doesn't happen that often
Specific day
Is it that has nightmares about it
People won't stop asking me for proof
I find it interesting that he's hung up on copyright law when
He without permission reposts other people's new stories on Infowars
Andre headlines them
He's paying them and exposure
Pay the global is her exposure in a lawsuit
Yeah 1998's very unconvincing
Displayed
Today hear from Alex
Not good
I'm not going to get over
That dude was like oh well copy
That was the one where he was like wow that bit that's International
These people believe in weird
Intractable laws
For some reason maritime
I would like it if Alex's was like alright
The copyright law thing didn't work and then he just yells
Tariffs
CL something
Voya request
Yeah we got to the end of this and Alex still waiting on that floppy disk baby let's
Look at that thing put together
Microsoft
That was
Pretty heavily used in
In endgame right
Physical copy of the CD because I don't work anymore
So yeah we'll be back
You know I think it has episodes a little bit shorter and I've had a little bit of stuff going on this week
I've been a little bit
Little bit busy and also Alex impressed days on timeout and I think it's hilarious that to these collars
Keep asking him for his got nothing so good
Jordan on Monday 4 episodes
$600
Plum 600
ESATA hard for me not to drink that before
Performer
Not that good drink it before and then round it up
You gotta bring it
No
I don't think I can I don't think I can do that. I can't artificially
Look there might be artificial flavors
I can't be artificial
We are there is that no judges or fight and I go to bed Jordan
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo and easyxplore come Darrell rundus
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color