Holding
Alexandra Thurston color
Everybody welcome back to knowledge
Jordan
Today we take another adventure down into the land of Alex Jones
Insanity iWatch
Infowars
And I have no fun
Conclude what he's
About and I will do my best
To explain what's going on in the world
Well
Going on in the world is it
Going on in the imaginary world
The world of Jones as it were
Yeah
I've been wrestling with a few things
Alright involved 14-hour live broadcast
But Infowars dead
Which
Everyone can agree is except
There's no way anybody watch
More than a half-hour of
Right I think a lot of people watched
The bunch of it
Raise I know that I was checking it out
Periodically it was in the thousands
Fluctuated near me and Matt Riggs
Get together and watch podcast Athan
Ricardo's charity
But Marathon show up and down
Just know people don't have time for this b*******
People drop-in drop-out
Donut
Myself I'm not super thrilled to admit I could really only make it through a couple hours of it
Retreat to the safe Waters of how are you how are you not super thrilled that you made it
Through a cup
School because the hours
Through maybe 45
If I was
Really focused on
And then David night we're like
Is the most boring
He's a smug prick
Yeah it was a girl
Leanne
Choose flying
Most of what I watched her do with interview a guy about how Russia is okay
That was a big narrative that kept spinning with a k
Way too much about Russia
Like
To establish
Because the whole look up because for so long all about
Show
Russian
Basically
Now they have to
Two established
Yeah
If I pretty
Tending that none of
Yeah actually
One of the things I was going to do is because this inauguration
14 hour broadcast is
Almost
Impossible to cover
I wanted
Maybe we could do a special episode
Send to the 911 episodes
And it's shockingly boring
Really
It's just like
That was yesterday
You do have to give him credit he did
Like in the in the Y2K up
Episode
The the
Blind squirrel in the crazy occasion
Hazelnutty totally nailed
But it's very easy to predict that
Take responsibility
Given that he'd already attacked the World Trade Center wants to do it again
Loudly
Lightsabers
You're not reading
B
Osama's going to
Yeah
I have a lot of theories
About what happened
To get back to that cuz I do but we're going to cover
RMV
Great nightmare that began
On the inauguration
The women's March just happened
This is the day after all that was fuckingawesome
Millions of people taking to the streets
3 million
Across the country
Which is a population
Like fuk
Like one person
But you have to factor in
Beverly
Even if you go just by voting
Population that's a full two and a half
That is a huge part of the elect
Largest protest in America
What's going to end up having Countrywide it's not
Because that's always the narrative
Of likes
Countrywide
Kansas
City there were thousands
Women showing a Heart of Texas
Yeah
Unoccupied around the world
One-place
Erica
All seven continents
Sarah people approach
But
We don't have feedback of what he
Was going to say about this in the narrative
Cannabis pain
But I guarantee
What's going to happen is he's going to
Conflate
With the people breaking
Starbucks Windows the night before
It's going to be this wasn't protest
I mean we'll deal with that when we get to it
I'm having a disjointed open
Because I don't know how to
Everything is overwhelming
Yep
Compared to one of the most amazing days I've ever seen
Like I've been so hope
I'm seeing all of those women
Show the f****** and
Like and that's the other thing in d.c.
No arrest
There were four
Yeah 300 women's
Walking down the street
Zerorez
Useful tops there's no narrative
Can spend other than
These are full-on protest
I want to start
I have a theory
The Alex was only on the broadcast
A couple
H and
Vague check-ins with him
Because he was on a bender
I think Alex was
Real drunk throughout most of inauguration
Yeah
Well he did go to the deplorable right
Assuming they all got
S***-faced
Same here I want to start with a clip
Of him right before the
The floorball that he was very drunk
He was out of out of
What is Gord
He was scheduled to speak at the deplorable and this is before it
Who want to take over with freedom and so here's that works
Dumbasses walk-around
So he also I should give a point of clarification there he always talks about the people and watch
Big trench coat
Spy work right there
Go to
Fedoras walking around like you own the place
You girls on
Get to the point where I am
Absolutely positive
You have to actually tell reality now
Infowars.com
Shop w
We got to go to the Powerball now
Oh my God
So, that right now
Kroger's
Major effect bulshit is over
Get ready
1776bank
Dodo somebody yelled 1776
Baby
I got to go find a
The tree depends on our I don't know
That's a drunk like
Slurring his words
That is a drunk me
Absolutely
It further make the argument that he was wasted
Trying to act
He's trying to sound like
She's not wasted
A one-point
He's not drunk
Exactly what I've been a doorman at bars
I'm not
Too much
I haven't stepped
So here's my here's my
Business that may be developed over the course of
Is a three-prong thesis
The first is that Alex was
Did through most of the weekend that's why they kept him off air and had David Knight hosting most of
Their coverage
Pretty well-established
Studio Lee Ann McAdoo also in-studio Paul Joseph Watson lives in London
So he was
He just Skype
Stuff like that
Alex
Owen Shroyer and Rob do were on
On the ground
Rob do of courses the cameraman who sometimes gets on camera
Is not great
Also
They had shots
Because there's do like cameras
On top of cameras
Best golf
And you could see better videotape
Can people video.
Yes
He has one of those
The stabilizer
Is to iPhone
They don't even have cameras
They have iPhones
You know the
The cameras are there
There's some good stuff I'm not advertising
For iPhones
Nope professional operation would have cameras as opposed to what I have
Well we've already established their money stream is very
Tenuous
This is that
Then they kept him off after a large portion
We want Alex we don't want these other people drunk on broadcast the whole time 10 hours
I've ever seen I wouldn't have turned it off
Compelling situation
My second know he would fall in and out of
Sleep at least once or twice
Artichoke
Before football
Imagine after
Amazing
Drawing of my
Do you have
Wikipedia
It at the at the Coronavirus
Dorset like Hillary a Goldman Sachs
The second prong of my thesis is Vicky wasn't really welcome
At the inauguration
The Trump didn't even really invite him
You went to this deplorable which was a secondary thing is like there
Deplorable
But there's a video and it's not really good for audio so I didn't put it on
An art collection
Thrown out of the inauguration
Does a video of taking him out of a big crowd past the barrier
Globalist
Yep afraid of me
Fusarium just somewhere on the street
Surrounded by like 10 or 20
Replace
You don't need access to get to
I have no evidence
But he's actually anywhere in Port
With my first one
Is that this is all sort of an elaborate charade about his access
But he has Zach Britton
Really sucks
Him up
Now feels like
Credit
You carry in the water
Trade like that
Every single
Weirdo
People who are a liability
The first time he's ever been
Stepped on
On the way there
Wow
Nobody's he's never had anybody to step
Because nobody likes
Or 17 and then all the sudden
He did some
Now I got a Kik
Kick you to the curb
Horrified
I don't
I hope everything
He's very
So I think that what's happening is
Trump is
Let him along
In a big way
I can't have you at the gala
Are you going to call
He's let on all of his supporters
Middle-class people need to pay more
Interest on their morgue
Apart of any platform
His supporters
For the middle class
To really take over and then the first thing he does is go
Yeah it's going to be really shocking
Like the waves of awareness
Start selling.
You YouTube
He is lying
Just like
He's lied to
Everyone
Fake news
Let's just get into it one clip that I think
Apparent
Enough
The inauguration
It's sort of a breakdown
It's sort of like a
Let's fucken take this
Apart piece-by-piece the inauguration
And I don't think he does a really great job
Here is the beginning of the clip where he introduces his
Is Pisa
Okay about what Trump's inauguration
Which was all about
First off let me just take a deep breath here
Undoubtedly
This was Trump declaring
Office Republican George Washington talked about
Little bit dog whistle
That is
Straight up
You know that every white supremacist
Super thrilled
To hear that sort of thing
To the third prong of my piece
And that is that what we're witnessing
Is
Alex Jones sort of being in charge of
A move towards fiachra
Christian theocracy
This clip
If you pair it with him being a drunk on the streets
It's pretty funny
Did you take it just
Of like
It's incredibly
So get ready to get a little bit scared
Little bit
Tweet that they're going to reimburse Oak
Spirit of America
And empower the globe
Coming in the way from the microphone
It's Pro he wants to empower
Power
I don't think he's drunk at this point but I think he's probably hungover
Or maybe not maybe all of his weirdo supplements are actually hangover cures maybe that's the secret all along
If you're hungover take super male vitality
I got to order sub
Telling thing that he
He said
Was I haven't talked to Trump about
Oh no I did not happen
Not that we
No I swear to God he said he hasn't
Talk to Trump about it no no no okay
Between
And the Providence
Ideas
He didn't talk to Trump about
Is the spirit of America Rising
Okay
Because I swear because the media is the media
What was the
Spirit of America
So he did he says that too though
We'll talk to
Trump
Telling you
He is saying is
One the media ask
They did not
He didn't talk to
To Trump but there's a mind-meld
He is trying to
He's trying to
Consider himself part of that
Very clear that Trump
Is cutting off
Like an ax through starting to move away from you and your like
No I gave him all the great ideas
Afraid
He is lost
All of that can
Then the question
Become even more non-existent
Somehow even in his own imagination he will have
To admit
The media isn't talking
Sing to me anymore because
Cuz I'm not a player
Yeah all I've got is
Weird dude
Who come on my show
Don't have a roster like a Cadre of weirdos
Those who do come on his show
Pretty regularly
Who are all just like
On exactly the same pages
One of us yeah there's one
Google Google Google
I'm ready
Come on
Skype in
From rooms
Bedrooms that look empty
I think you nailed
The pizza rolls are done shut up
Mommy I'm talking to Alex
And Trump have
Some sort of communication possibly it's waning
Altruism
The message we heard this speech
Open my message
4 over a decade
Laundromat from my music
Not quite so similar to what I say on the show don't you hear Trump say later
Okay and yes prep I was in Atlas Michelle told me but let's just move past all that
Of course
Classic
That's not a lie
I don't think it's a lie either when he was on when Trump was on Alex
Yeah and he's
He said that Alex's record has been
Spectacular make his is history of
The other things
The other thing that I think is really scary
Is I don't think
Keep that much wrong
About
Trump giving his message
Nope like
Trump is
Pulling from that
That kind of Playbook there
Which is the most frightening
As yet we have to illuminate
The things that are being said
Onvisource
Are now president actually believe
He really does this over and over
Various States
Intoxication
Will talking to friends I really sincerely think that people who haven't
At all dwelled in weird parts of the internet are about to be
Be very surprised
Why what happen
Because some of our leaders
And some of their advisors
Are beholden to
Or incredulous of
Really fatty dumb
Conspiracies
And the consequences could be sack
Well and it's also because
Of that isolation
Where they're in their own world
There's that constant
Feedback loop
Especially like with Alex Jones where he says
Infowars.com then one of his crazy colors
Also
One of those crazy colors as being
People are talking about this
People it's not literally alive but it's spiritually alive
Inauguration went off
Another
You're old
Tunks there were also a lot of very important people there may be people who are oppressed
Maybe people who are rich
Yeah
We're here this is a giant victory for Humanity it is massive looking at Michelle
Mama
Ultron
When they were singing the Star Spangled Banner
Obama with that miracles
Call Timbers putting Power by the globalist
They're absolutely evil skins for people not to have a future it's why he goes to Africa and says
Cars rare condition air it was
Because because literally there to hurt people
Across-the-board
Donald Trump right now
Phone calls
Jobs
Detroit jobs Atlanta
Sue
Well one
Fear there was we were going into a real racist
Transphobic
You showed a little bit of restraint
In your face
I actually went pulled the clip from Obama's speech that he gave that that keeps
Black people in poor people in foreign countries can't have cars please enjoy
Hurley from Obama's speech
That is being misrepresented work
I am
Africa
Work together
Define Waze
In which
Collectively
We reduced carbon
We make sure that
There's some differentiation so that
Countries that are very wealthy
Are expected to do more
And
Countries
That
Are still developing
Obviously
Mission Beach
Resign to Poverty simply because
The Western Europe in
America got there first
That wouldn't be fair but everybody's going to have to do something
Everybody's going to have to make
Some important choices here
And
Expected duration that helps leave this because
Is going to be your generation
That suffers the most
Ultimately if you think about all the youth that everybody's mentioned here in Africa
Raising living standards
Everybody's got air conditioning
Well the platter will boil over
Is a producing energy
Absolutely
Positive of Alex Jones being a
Interested in the truth
I'm being just a complete liar
Oh yeah you build a fake narrative
Voice
Obama voice so bad around
I love him
There's there's
Citizens I have about Obama
Especially regarding
Drone Warfare crazy
So many
So many prisoners of
Political memes
Not even
You know
Which is the right
There's no problem
God dammit
Trying so
F****** hard
To make
The best decision available to
They have it every time
In a minute
Of audio
He's able to lay out a problem
Show both sides of it
I'm say where the consideration
We have a problem with carbon
Consumption and it's causing
Global issues
And it's not
Your fault
Of course not
If everybody used
Carbon emissions
But if we
If we roll back
You're still the one most
Yeah
We're trying
To do more of our part B
We did more of the day
And within that clip
Even clearly says
You know
We have to find a way
Do not resign you to poverty
And not completely destroyed
The society
But we have built already
So it's
If you mean the thing that makes sense
It's f****** insanity
It's
Saying that Obama hates poor people
Or the Trump is
Trying to bring jobs back
Obama
Brought all the jobs back
With the auto bailout whenever it was so close to all of those places just being like
Well
GM is gone
Yeah like it was
Very close to that
No point in time does anybody ever give him
The credit of being the guy who
Forced that
And again
Well the end result of me not doing this
More abhorrent to my principal
Then saying like let's not bail out these businesses that made bad decisions
Which is why the
Where are you
I don't know
Another another fun clip
Is a little towards the middle starts with an O
I'd like to remind you
It's the tistic
I can
Can confirm for you that
60%
Under the age of 18
Correct
Young people
This is indicative of
Awakening that is happening on a planetary scale not just here so
This revolutionary ilysm
This revolution is globalism
Trump said that
This revolution is about you
You are watching powers that you are the future
We're going to get out of your way and let
Have your destiny
Have your dreams
As America goes the rest of world go
Washington envisioned all of this
Farewell address
All countries
V don't talk about God
Don't call the shop
Stool horrible deal the idea of Americans Providence in manifest destiny
All of the Sears and talk about the problems and crimes associated problems
But overall the greater Destiny worldwide in the future
Republic
Guitar World Government anti-human
A system so
Is an anti-human Eugenics bass technocracy system
But that's almost like a Philip K Dick's locked
What is the ballast
Human eugenics
Technically
Saying that we're going to turn tablets chimeras are real
People into computers
What's the singularity my friend
I mean that's common
Walmart hours
That's about abortion at Planned Parenthood
Text Chrissy I believe is about to have a singularity
Are growing Reliance on a surveillance state
That's that's fine
I don't know what the
I guess the anti-human part is just you
So they are satanic
Goes with the
Here's where we're going to here's where we're going to get into another
Thing right there
Is there any Christian principle he adheres
Other than
Didn't saying he's a
I mean it depends on one of the big one
That's one of the big ones
He doesn't honor his father because
He claims that he
He lies about his dad's Battlefield
Now
First like movies has to come from his dad but
Chimera
That's that's a possibility but I don't actually know too much about his mom I feel like it might be in Port A
To do research about
His family
Invoked by him I have no interest in knowing about cuz it seems like
Not fair game is son to the extent that he is an Infowars reporter
But I don't want to make fun of him cuz he's a kids
His dad
Because he is
The babies brought up a ton
Makes
Toothpaste
I don't know I don't think so
This is
Please be made I don't have a clip of it but
The Infowars
On the last episode when we found out
They're selling body armor
I predicted that they're going to start start selling guns
I am now they have started telling cantar
14 hour broadcast if they're selling AR-15s
Team lowers
Which is the central piece of an AR-15
Which is the gun that is most commonly used
In mass shooting
Shooting which is really problematic
Kind of anti-human right now I was on the traces we keep making
Technocracy is probably
Better than a
Gun based like I don't know man
The bunch of crazy
Paranoid
Religious folks
Guns YouTube
It is hard to make the argument
That human
Positive for
Yeah
There's always exceptions to rules are some grapes
Yeah I think it was rated one of the problems that I had with edit
And that is
This
Speech
Is about 12 minutes
Uninterrupted talking
Wow
For a breath for like 10 minutes
And he's just a verbal jazz
Yeah
And I don't know where
Barely a little
Consistency
Globalist
You just
Selena
You know we committed
Does he like
Not like the genocide
But did that
God
The Patriots have never done that kind of thing
From Texas
Kill all the message
Like I love the Remember the Alamo as like
To take all their stuff remember parts of the Alamo
Really what the places do
This next clip is more Bebop and Scat
Having to do with the New World Order
Voters guide
Open welsing
World
The American system is too much competition for them they admit that the white paper
The British government 200 years ago
The British are throwing off globalism
The fact that we go through these crowds
People of every race color creed or all just human
With red blood
This is the will of the
You paying around that Audience by the way and there is like
98%
We do get some interviews a little bit later in these clips
He manages to find the one black guy who's there tokenism a representative idea is
So disappointing people later
And one of them is a black preacher
And the other is
And Incredibly angry Indian
What's the weather I think he's under house arrest
Nuts
He said that is
Is actually true which is that
The
Middle class has been
Taken away
There's no
Reasoning
Poop like the people who have
Taking it away
Are the ones who are in control of the White House
And the Congress
And eventually the Supreme Court
Yeah
It's people who are in business who have done
Yeah who did it on purpose
Those people
Will drive me insane
You have a billion dollars
Wealth and influence
Billion dollars
In 22 billion dollars or 1.2
2 billion dollars quick what to do any of this other than this
Weird sociopath
Greedy
Like mental illness
I think what it is is that
People who are really rich now a lot of them are
Super jealous of old money
There's an old money and I think the people believe
This is the kind of an assumption on my part I'm not I don't have any
Facts about this up
But I know that
New money is kind of scoffed at as opposed to
Do people who are like the Rockefellers
Yeah and I think that these billionaire Folk
They're like
Enough money
Next generation will be old
Yeah there's an idea that they could become the new old money
Well and I do think there is that are is kind of some of that
Right now where I'm there are upward Mobility look down on those Silicon Valley
You still going to wear a hoodie
Get out of here
Without a mask
Ladies and gentlemen
Turn it up
White person
You can't have guns private property or future you don't have the American Birthright
You don't have a future of wealth
That's your enemy that's racist
Programming
All the globalist
Poorest country in Africa
Play the Christians off against you know the animals for the Muslims or vice versa
Divide and conquer because the elite are destroying nation-states are trying to make the 4th
That's true
Cool hundred percent true
Well we
Does a blanket term
Just going by post-reconstruction
Reconstruction Era South
How do you get
Poor people fight with each other perfect
This is one of those weird whenever Alex is talking bulshit we kind of have to stop it
Point Pleasant
Agree with your diagnosis
How to treat it or what caused
You're describing a problem but everything else around it is
Wackadoo
How did we not come up with a Capricorn
I can't even keep track of how many we done
Is it kind of
Lose a little bit of
Where
Yeah but
Here we go
America
Died basically in the last few years it was a globalist program bushes and Clinton's behind it
With criminal elements the intelligence agency
But
Resurrection
But my country can come back
From the dead in America
Come back from the dead come back to life
Phoenix
How
Powerful that Phoenix is incredible that Destiny is you talk to us
We are what breathes life into the spirit get into us and the enemy knows everything's energy
Forget all the religious books and all the all the stuff
Monster destroy our spirit
We're taking
And those devil-worshipers up they're the enemy
Obama devil worshippers well now
Okay what's my prosperian Renaissance
Play 112 cornucopia
Somebody's got a big house or good-looking wife
Provide person as long as you don't race pace car
Devil worshippers and what happened today for
Beat the chief executive invited God back in and said the doors open
Genocide of the people the doors open now to you if you want this Birthright
If you want goodness
We've all got to be good we got to come together
And we've got a
What is your black card white people white people
What we believe in all the control
Did
He definitely didn't invoke
God or Providence
Overtures towards Jesus all of the all of the
Could not listen
Intuit
Like I just couldn't do it but I did see a couple of those like
The list of words that have never been said in a in a naughty Ranch
There was no message of Hope
And yes we can there was pure like
This country is turning into a monstrous nightmare all going to die
We're all day
You know we talked about confirmation bias a bunch
On the show and I think it is one of those things
Other logical fallacy
Beholden to
And one of them is
Actually I think it's still just got
You believe whatever you want to believe
And you read into things whatever you want to read into
Hey so if you go up there and vaguely mentioned religion
He's brought God back we have to
Just a radical Islam
Victory.com
We have to say it or else we
We can't tackle it
It's such b*******
They use these precise words
So what if someone does say
Radical Islam
It becomes code for
Argument for Trump only briefly mentioning it
Is like
He can't stay directly otherwise
I think it was
The CIA
He said or no doubt it was it was one of the previous
He was like
We're going to take Dad radical Islam
You have to say it
You just have to say the words
Did Alex Jones you say
It's all energy
Oh yeah he just said it wrong
You left the Christian train
I was just like heck man guy is real of the Earth
How do you rather
You remember when the bubble is up here
It will get your Kundalini Rising
Water filtration devices
You know the fluoride in the water calcifies your pineal gland
I'm not a hundred percent sure that's bulshit
Might just be something I read on some weird hippie webcam
I'm not I'm not too worried about Krista
A little bit of a straw about Russia
Which is kind of fun
To give you some sort of a little bit of a setup
Maxine Waters was being interviewed auntie
TV on an active democratic
I'm not at otherwise.
Never going to make the right song
She gives bad interview
Is the problem
Things in ways that are really easy to attack
As you become
Like sort of
Lightning rod
For Republican
Quiet she ends up being attacked on
Dumb drama
Yeah recently she was talking about how
If
Comes out
That
The Russian
Things were Consulting with Trump about his
Campaign
And how to frame thing
Like saying that Hillary is crooked
And sayings
She's sick
Send these should be impeachable of
Is that
Calitris
I feel like anytime boys on the cob
Influences the election
Specifically in the definition
No treason
That's a good
Point the very specifically Define what it is I don't think it may actually be a committed other treason
This one is absolutely
For the way she was setting it up
It's very clear if you go watch the clip
If
We find out that this is
McKay's
Then
That isn't
What is a perfectly logical statement
Study Tagalog
Formal logic
Can college at the University of Missouri
Veterinary logic
So
The problem is
Instead of saying if we find that he was Consulting with Russia then we'd
Stacked on that
She used to Pacific examples like if the Crooked Hillary came from them
Because
We know the tricks that Alex plays
Accusing
Russia of coming up with crooked Hillary
He even has played the clip
On the show and then attacked
Have you like that's not what she said
It's insane
Yeah it's a little bit
Incredible straw man fallacy arguing
Russian spy
You can have your own ideas you can have a strong leader
Russian
The reason Trump got elected and everything come from the Russian
You like that
I think they're over Mike
Because
Would be like 75
How is marriage
What would a
I would estimated it like 75
Proud
It's maybe like three deep
I'm kind of in the round
Do you think he's doing Shakespeare in the round
Circling
Alex sharks
Like he's the nucleus of this
Weird Adam
New York Times
I don't think so
I don't know cuz I
Nexus I'm not going to be able to
I'm not be able to try in like search
Through all of their articles
The Russians and crooked Hillary but I know that I know what Maxine Waters said and he's misrepresenting that
He's also lying
Here is
Here is the
The next question there
Also God I love
Nothing
Alright that's a little bit
A little bit right on the cusp
I think it's
Clear that Russia did influence the election
In some
Fashion
To what extent
Don't know
Debatable
What legitimate effects
Certain things they did
I think it's almost undeniable at this point that
They were in contact with Trump
I think they were operatives
Multiple people who are very close
Reconnected with Trump
Are literally under investigation
Yeah
They have they say they have communicated
Vape juice
If you're if you're the CIA or the NSA
And you have the information potentially nest
Necessary to
I'd like
Undeniably impeached
Yeah
How can you not release that
I think you'd have to wait until he was actually inaugurated so we might
See some of that happened now
Well because if it happened before he was inaugurated we enter
Tucson crepe
Election do we have a new president
Select
At the end of the day you enter a bigger crisis necessarily than
Do you need
Where is afib
It is true
That they have this evidence
He's compromised
They maybe they do maybe they don't I don't know
Through the channels we already have
Here's my next Quest
Is there any
Benefit for the GOP
Leggett funeral
If you're in the GOP
You got
The absolute best
Scenario
In that you have an
Easily impeachable on
Uncontrollable
As your president
With a vice president who is
You actually want in the present
Hates women
He doesn't hate women but he wants them to never have
Control over their own bodies
Yeah I would never say that
Is like the idea of is there anything
The game by not doing it
You're you're you're sort of touching on the same thing that Trump and Alex Jones have
Alex's outlived his usefulness to Trump
And if it
Did the Jeep now the only issue with that is the drug does have a sizable
Of weirdos
Yes but if you are the GOP and you sign off on this impeachment proceeding
Elections
Everybody
Doesn't show up for you
The everything swings
Either
Weird Fringe libertarian or Democrat
Emmanuel
Completely lost
All of your blood
CorePower
That's the usefulness he has
In that like there's a
The threat to going against
But there's no upside
Other than avoiding that threat
Which end if you if you
If you can even put together like a
Based understanding of what they're going
Things to do in the next
2 years
How can you
You possibly imagine that they're going to
Attain their majority
I think it would be impossible
Worse
That could be the
Do you like
Now we're not talking about a 48
Voter turnout
Nope
Some real s***
A lot of other countries
I have the ability to vote no confidence in your leaders you have a prime minister or president
Job
People can just
Introduce measures to be like you should get out
And we don't have that that we should
Introduce that
The ability to vote no,
Because if we have that now
He be gone
That kind of separation
Power is element
Where in
If you have a congress
Like the one we have
Completely controlled by one
Imagine
Situation where is Aldi
And a republic
President
Confidence and all of a sudden
The Democrats
Control
Everything
Or one-party can
Controls
But the vote of no confidence isn't done by the people in the
The Senate is done by
Like a general election
I'm not sure that that's not how that works
I mean in the UK
Which is the other
Like Maine
I believe in
I'm not sure
Concocting something but doesn't
I hate
You know what time it is
What time is it
You know my favorite thing in the world is Alex and also
My second favorite thing is him fake crying
Okay
History happening right now is get this network brake and and David not intrude upon whenever they want here but I'm going to go get settled down
Take a shower so just get on my knees and pray to God
Oh there it is
Call we got to be ready but we know who they are
Yogurtland it's been Infowars people
You hear that
Oh yeah
And that's what
Kicked him out of his fake crying
Yeah
That's what got him to be like
Oh crab turning
That's my favorite thing in the world he is so over-the-top with his
Least wants to do is get into a room by himself
Oh yeah yeah
Ya RAB do
If he doesn't get that attention
Then he's really going to spiral into a into a depression
Fallen Brown everywhere
On suicide watch
He is finally doing some
Introspective
In a long long
I kind of imagined it being like Rob do is falling around taking the bottle of wild turkey
That's that's kind of how I picture it like
I get back on the air come on
He's on like babysitting
Patrol
Do this if it starts right after that one
The fake crying is great
Such b*******
Explain
Is part of the info
All of mouses
Look away as the blueprint battle plan
Infowars an orgasm myself and you listeners
Matt drudge all of us together are the infowar
We are the blueprint of the operating system
America 2.0 supercharged wedding
So get ready
Yuck
Yeah
Brutal he's very humble though
I will say that
Attributes my humility stands for
The most humble person
Going for a job interview
Too good
Hard worker
So now at this point in his ramble
In front of these
270 people
Who are overly Mike
Someone
Who may be from another press organization
Question
You might be
Are we going to commit to the
I don't tip my hat about who he is cuz they
Maybe a little bit of Crossmark
Russia's population
Call Jennifer strong
Hot tub by Trump
Good we have the tools
We have the history we got the pedigree we got it all everybody here is a morse
Really
Play the word Trump Tower the people and let them know you are this revolution
Yep
Breitbart
And the question was
Did Trump really lay the wood to him
That's a post
Game question to like
I just want to thank the president
Yeah his name is Trump
But I need laid it all out there on the diet serially less it left it in
You know
Girl's hands
Yeah yeah
Give me the
Yeah f****** Breitbart Christ comes up
Strategist of the White House should have a say in who
Alex Jones
Maybe drunk on the street
So he allows Breitbart couple questions that are all like really like their meatballs
Knockout a park like
When I go to church
Are we talking ice cream I don't need that anymore
Do I take
Superman ice cream ice cream
Another question about the spirituality
What's going on also from the Breitbart reporter
Very spiritual speech unlike a lot of the rallies pages that I tweeted
Going to invoke
Probably about the Covenants
I need it
Because they all understand
Got out. Let us feel empowered not let us know about America's destiny
That narrative
Globalist beautiful psychological abuse it gives us a culture unify
Killing our culture
The second phase of slavery just fell today
Progressive the future they call themselves the progressive
They're the opposite they're not the progressive
And that's what the Democrats
Were called what
Was the French Revolution party
They wanted to regress everything
What you're seeing here is a real Renaissance I know you're seeing here is the real 1776
George Washington quotes
Guard against the imposters of pretended patriotism
Interesting
10% quotes
Quote if the freedom of speech is taken away then dumb and
And silently maybe LED
Like sheep to the slaughter
In the last week or so Alex has also been up on this like I add a calendar
Today's word is Providence
Arbitrary power is most easily established on the ruins of Liberty reviews to licentiousness
Bingo
I really do but this is George
The two point out a calendar event Providence
Birthright loves Rhode Island and then also the other one is
Even talk about
The Jacobin party for like the last few days
Nope
It does he have any idea what happened next
Does he know about the terror
You know he does not he doesn't know about that stuff
But what he doesn't know is that no one else does
People listening don't know like a sort of
You know what sounds like Lutheran
The kind of it has that religious feel too as a religious feel you can talk about The Maccabees
And stuff like that you don't want knows what you're referring to
You can talk about like and that's why a lot of these pseudo-religious
People who scream talk about like
The Book of Enoch
Agnostics never read this stuff they don't actually know what these being saved
But they know that
People that talking to don't eat
And it's the same thing with the Jacobins.
The Guyver the Democrats come from
Not really no
Do you have any information about the jacket
As far as
The timeline of the French Revolution
With a good idea
And then it further ends with an autocratic dictator
A warlock
Yes
Progressive
Straight
African-American shows up
He's got a great hat on
Also
Look
No
A gentleman
Describe it
Logout of madman
Angiitis
As well cuz that's the way you are
As I recall he's got a full suit on
Oh and a nice coat
Looks great
OK Google
Yes sir
God bless
Marshalls
You know what
Today was the beginning of something new
We've been waiting for this for a long time
And in
Was that our president is putting back
America first
We've been compromising we've been putting everybody else second
Politically correct
A&R prison said America
Has nothing wrong with any other country
So we're going to
Put on focus on
Iran education today was that I present
Right in the Bible
We can't do anything without God
Today out of all the different agendas and so forth was putting God first
Everything else be added to its encourage today we're starting over today
So one of the things that I think is really fascinating is when your team says something about God
It's like this is a sign that God is coming back
But when the opposite side says
Falsely pretending to be
The word of God is a weapon
Brilliance of
The Bible is that you can kind of say whatever the f*** you want
Like it even even in the evenin what is
Is it the Old Testament where it says
The devil can quote the Bible as well
Like it's all just
Any reference of
It's really the devil
But also
Who's the thing that always drive me up a f****** wall
Is that
If you
Fiat Fiat
People who are religious
Refuse to acknowledge
That one of the big
Parts of Jesus
Is that he undid the old cover
The old Covenant in the Old Testament is no invoice
Welcome
Genuinely had that conversation where they're like
Maybe we should just get rid of the old
If there it's important as maybe a historical document is one of the
Great
Like what is like a Philip K Dick's alternate-history of what if we got rid of the Old Testament
Like the
World is a much better place
An eye for an eye is
Replaced by turn the other cheek
Yeah if you'd only use the teachings of Jesus
You are in a better State problems
Ford gospel
You're in a much better state
The Epistles are all f*****
Even taking those letters my review of
On Amazon I give a one-star cuz Timothy was a dick
If you take all those people who are really involved with building the early church
Think about who those people would be nowadays
They would be crazy
They were crazy cult members
Wanted
Power probably
And they built the system wherein they could they could get some power
Which was Within
This burgeoning church
The interesting thing about the
That is
It was the reverse of most cults
Good
And in this circumstance that is kind of like
They were taking advantage of the fact that
Jesus
Preach
Love
Which everybody is on board
Which might be why it was so
Yeah well and also why it was so Danger
Is because
He was he was like maybe this
Maybe this whole patriarchy with a
You know
There's some indications
If you go into it and look through
Historical records
There's a decent chance that they might have gotten
Their records
Yeah I'm at the Jesus who was the rabbi
Wasn't actually ever crucified
It was another guy name
And the director
Iowa
But there are a lot of experts believe that there were two Jesus
Historically and they've been can
Inflated into
Yeah well and also the the Jesus
The whole Miracle story is
The same one that mithras had
Like the whole thing is just a mish-mosh in a hodgepodge of all these other religions but if you take a lot of it
Teaching
You take the teaching
Person dead
Thomas Jefferson had a Bible
Novel
You take that out
So this interview goes on a little bit more and it gets more and more religious
I want to kill Trump
The spirit is kasasa opened up is already Rising
They're not going to stop at all the world country
Berryville
Perilous times
We can no longer
Go to hell
Stand up for what is right
Heritage
Disagreement
Agree to disagree
Positions of that particular principal are
American is taken
American countries all around the world has been waiting on us
Tradutor
Rome
American Patriots stand against
But this divisiveness is blocked
This all this stuff
Have you ever felt the spirit stronger
I want to say a couple things stronger than that
All of the spirit
Really f****** up
Really should be dependent on the president
I would think not
The couple things
Opposition
I'm self
You saying that we should agree to disagree about stuff and look for the higher principle
Just taking those words I agree that there's some value in that
Can't do that when the other side
Is
Religiously-based
You know you saw where that one
White supremacist got punched
Richard Spencer
The violence of the protesters
But there's
He wasn't literal literal
He's advocating for genocide
About it and I think they're both equally valid
Amazingly cathartic
And I can't lie I watch that clip like 15.
I also see
The
Bad off
Pics of it I see that like it's
Just because you disagree with someone you disagree with them intensely it doesn't mean you should have salt
I don't think that person did anything wrong
But I probably wouldn't have done it myself
No I would I would
I'm not a violin
Dude by nature but then again
He's a Nazi
Yep there's no defense for now
The defense for Nazi
He's being allowed to
He's not
Being put in prison for espousing
They're dumb belief
That is freedom of speech
You cannot
Taking apart by the
Government
Yeah punched in the face for being a Nazi I'm cool with
It kind of comes with
The territory
Just f******
Straight up murdered
Yeah
From the first
Clip
Right before the last one
It's time for America to
Yeah he said it's okay if
Everybody else put
Themselves
Because America's
That for them
Like single-most
We're all going to
Fight a war thing
Can possibly stay
If we all put ourselves first that I don't have you ever have international compromised
Human first
Yeah
Vineyard
You're literally going when you
Come up against
The other country to put them
In any conflict
Now there's always a zero-sum game
Always
Always even though
That's going to wind up being more damaging to both party
Well I think that the nobility of sacrifice has kind of been lost
Fun people
But like this
You know the idea of like
We can all play actually if they would just sit down and look at the
The prisoner's dilemma
I think they might actually be able to realize like Concepts
Fall Apart
See that they would have no con
What does the idea that sometimes collaboration is the best possible outcome brandano you individual
Hollywood get more by turning your back on your partner
It's it's insane to me that you aren't able to have these abstract thoughts of like we can all Do Better Together
If we work together although it doesn't
Appear that way
Some horseshit
This interview
And I visit Alaska for this interview because I
Interrupt him in
Credibly rude way
Oh no really funny
Nevermind we'll get to we'll get to why I have an issue with him interrupting this
Specific
Person in this
Because he's put a lot of restraint into that bottle of wild turkey
Yeah
To get that
But the power was strong
Power with Trump
That might even be sacrilegious
Yeah that's
Well he's already said that it doesn't matter by religion
That's true
I want to take a break from the literal chronology
Being drunk
We need a little fun right about now screaming on the street after the deplorable
Carroll Shelby
Republic
A lot of the time whenever I go for it
I don't think I've ever been
Like if this level order
Mixed with super male vitality
I hate to call it a demon
I think a big part of that
Super male vitality
Is probably
And testosterone is something bad
If you don't have control over testosterone
Yeah
I'll never be more glad that I probably have
Tableautier
Then when I watch him
Passive by nature but it's like a way worse
Well and that's why it always it always boggles my mind
Whenever that
Never
And like all of the
The things that
Glorify High
It's never come with like
By the way this is also
Thing where it's like
Your supervisor
Like I
Pictures for
Any of them
What is hot what is fighting still allowed in hockey
Because we all have to get out some kind of sublimated
Testosterone
Sports in general
Created
By the powers-that-be in order to mimic Warfare 2
To take away our male energy
I mean
For the created by a nonsense thing that's kind of what sports are for like
Also we don't have Gladiators killing each other is because we have football
Football videos
Will kill each other slowly
It also said that Hitler was responsible for
For popularizing
Which I'm not sure if that's true but
Berkeley true but the 1936 Olympics
Were the ones
Tire world
Stood at attention
But there's a big reason
For that
Reasons
He's not done yelling
1776 will commence again
I know you do now.
We haven't taken the gloves off
And if you want to keep pushing
Please everybody else
Map
All the secret weapons in the control you anymore are they
They're now in the hands of George Washington 2.0
So I know why you're taking
That is a drunk man
Shaking and fever
He also if you watch the video he looks
Wasted
It's like he's got like a
Is he wearing a
Yeah but it's
Appetizer
He's just like he's the guy at the wedding who's waiting to f*** somebody and it's
Not happening looks like he's out on Bourbon
Street to
That's really the vibe that the video has and it's like
Maybe six
People standing around and when he's just yelling at me
Like it's he's doing the wrestling promo globalist
You don't have the secret weapons anymore
Yeah what secret was there secret about
Knows about it bro because some caller told him about him
So this one is a nice
Between his two interviews
What he does on the street
Again
This whole thing is supposed to be a breakdown of
Speech
It seems to just be turning into church
Or at least a long rambling
Yeah stream-of-consciousness
Consciousness
I don't really understand based on my
Klipsch I really like I said
Office what I'm trying
This one is called got to be humble
I'm not sure I'm not entirely sure
That is his first track
Above yeah
Are there in studio
Very special time
Have to go back to 30 seconds
Cuz it's worth it
Very special time
I missed it again no no no no funny
Very special time professional outfit
I missed again to go grab a bite to eat
Take some notes got2breal hump
What are you talkin about Willis on his wall
A little bit of insight into his mind
Be humble is on his checklist
Internalize
Which which I don't necessarily I don't necessarily find
Because I don't think it is
Like a
An internal
Like a dozen
Virtues aren't really in
I think I think there's work to be done but
You
Generally do the work
It becomes second nature
So humility deficient that he has to work on it real hard everyday
Or it's new
It's a new practice for her
I would actually go with the
Yeah probably he seems like
The most humility to fishing
Person
It's it's
Like his entire radio show itself
Aggrandizing how he
He gets everything 104
True
Like that whole that whole like
How did you know
The trumps cuz we're on the same page
I'm always for Americana
Yeah of course somebody who's always correct is following my PlayBook
Self-aggrandizement
To a ridiculous
Express
Literally what he says about why he's right all the time
I understand I have the globalists Playbook I'm not predicting Things based on like
Does random predict
Centration Camp so just be randomly predict
Yeah
He's very humble and his own for a little bit
Wacky
Leanne
Told it was getting ready.
They were about to watch the full
Total take over the media WrestleMania.
Torturing
Comic book
DC movies you read history books
Photos of
My point is
Crazy stuff going on
He's employs about polonium
The end of that
Yep people were sneaking llamas in heaven
Having somebody on the news say and
I think about there's definitely better
Mechanisms to get a bomb somewhere
Funny Rebecca.
Circle wizard
From the Middle East to the United States you just flip her over sometime and I'll over
Ask you this Jordan if you were to put a bomb in a llama
Would you or would you make the Llama eat
Beat the bomb
Belong with Ethan
Nobody would be there a funny visual
With the surgery
And if you're going to make
Okay if you're going to make it easier Gogoat
The way that they are digested is they're going to explode
Right
You Babble I was well you cut open the belly of the Llama you put the bomb in
What up
Hastily
Sitting inside the flama for a long time
With proper Veterinary experience
The best
False
Flood Infowars the whole time
Clear Isaac Alex was saying that as a
The joke
Identity actually was saying there's a bomb in a llama
I think that he was pictures of llamas
Cowardice I don't know
But also
The top hat he's been poisoned with polonium
Let's f*** off
Is the top hat like
The the Mad Hatter situation where that's where is fancy dresser
Use a little bit of a puss
Salat
I wanted to try and
Figure out what the f*** was going on with the polonium
Any mainstream possible sources
In my research I learned
Rodger Stone has been banned
CNN and NBC
And the reason
It's kind of fun
Okay
He says it's because he supports
Trump and because
You know
Used to conserve
Tiffany knows the truth
What is
That over a. Of time
He
Caught calling various media personalities who work for CNN and MSNBC
A quote
An arrogant know-it-all negro
A stupid negro negro
A professional negro a mandingo
Quota
Set a big dick guy right or no
That's very not good
I also he referred to
I would assume is Rachel Maddow but I don't know it doesn't
Specifically say who he was talking about
Please call someone
The Muff Diver
So
Pretty good
Grow
People who work for those stations
There's a good chance he is almost
Freezing
Some pictures of
Rodger Stone shirtless looking like he's at
Mardi Gras in Brazil
It was a woman licking
Otherwise he is a Snappy
He is
Various sources
Perhaps it in d.c.
Professional negro
So awful
And it's like a wide
Like that
Look
Do you want to cut the budget and maybe bounce
That's okay
Do not
Racist
Yeah but also
The other thing about that
It's because you're a
Conservative
Then you are
Conflating that racism
With conserve
So if you are going to catch that
But if you
Kicked off for saying
And then say it's because you're
Dozer
You do the same thing
That is
Conservatism is racist
Yeah according to Rogers.
Wasn't Poisoned With polonium
No there's no possible way
No
F******
Possible way the only images that he's released that prove it it just looks like he has
Like it looks like there's a little bit of a pockmarked face
Claim about that
Register claim that he was poisoned
Is in the cage
UB agent bright
Putin
And they
Even more damage
For that
Is not going on Apple m
But just been going
Immediately to
And Rodger Stone
But he's debunking
King things
Is nubuck
And you're like
Sweetest little f***
Selling the book
Twist of like
He's claiming something that's so easily to bunkable
And also he's plugging his
We're going to debunk
Well it came out the other day
He's under federal investigation
Oh really
Being in touch with wikileak
Exam the Russian
Wasn't
An official Trump campaign person
Might
Be okay for now
If you are President Trump
Yeah
With the capability to
Stop
That
Manuel of the amount of
The amount of political Capital that would cost
Would be so tough out of the gate
Yeah there is no more political capital.
Control the entire government
And Trump
Is a f****** lunatic
But why wouldn't you a minority in Congress if pushed
Jafar in with millions of
People on the street
Could shut down the government a latte
Like 88
I think if he squash these investigations into his friends
I think that it might be a Tipping Point
That would be
It would be cut and dry
Legend
Then why are we having a
If you're going
Squash investigation
It that are that are
Concurrent and running and have been
For about manafort about Rodger
Carter page
You are essentially admitting that whatever their vest
Right that's the is America today yesterday with the women's March
We were like
Genuinely not felt hope like that
I'm such a long
Still backed
Picture of Rodger Stone
Cuz it's kind of fun
Yeah
I think I Alex does to now
Really test on himself over the last month
Over the month of
December
9 into January
He's like
In-Shape
Do you know it started doing all this
I just work too much at the radio I put on
Pounds
I just lost so much weight
You know I keep my supplements on a lazy Susan
On the table
That someone took away the Lazy Susan
CC has another table in his Lazy Susan with him stopping taking supplements
The test on myself the next month
Crazy he doesn't
He was like 9
9 lb of something
Who cares
Show me pictures of
Shirtless
In these ads
What is it with those big barrel chest
Crazy it looks gross
So he's out on the street
Physical appearance
This is not what we're here
Doesn't the negative
Thing
Gross though
That's a personal opinion
Charlie Ann McAdoo
Awesomeness but I will say this
He couldn't hit
Could not get it just a little bit later after
Yelling about how you got to be humble
And Rodger Stone has been poisoned with polonium
Defines an Indian gentleman with a Maga hat on
I make America great hat
And this guy is
F****** angry
Nice to be here in nice to see you and my name is
Naturalized American citizen
Island
Many parts of the world
And I know how human rights
Are being violated
It all
People of other religions are treated like dirt
This country is a great country for the past eight years we had a nightmare with Obama
Nightmares over today
Accept the other brother
You read Daniel chapter 2
God is the installer and God is a remover Upton's today God and install
Trump
Country that's right we are already but nothing to do work you all turned against the promise
Yeah
Probably don't want to use
Is in this situation there
Irresponsible like they are there because of God's will
The practice of religion
Anyone can or can't practice whatever religion they want but this is a Christian country
Kings Kings
Kings
What else you got
I do like how
Like you choosing your words carefully
Because
He was
Very clear
About his name being
Phillip Thomas
Yeah
Now
That was a chosen
Picnic somewhere else
Respect
Completely there is a certain amount of nobody is more
Fervent about the America
Can dream then
Immigrants because that's the whole reason
Cuz that's the that's the idea there
Dutch Friesen
Maybe I can figure out the last name
But Joshua be my first name
Patel Vista
Haiti
I'm sorry I interrupted you
We got the Kings there I agree with him on the human rights
Sure I absolutely do I would like him
To follow up with
More wise
He's unhappy with
Why was a nightmare
Why
The human rights
That's a really interesting thing that I would want to have a full conversation because he doesn't explain where
To Grapple with it
And if his argument is it's a human rights nightmare because of
Like the Drone killings
Conversation
About Isaac
That would be giving a lot of credits
I think it's
More brainwashing
Right
The next
Here's the thing
Gets to me about that narrative
For that that brainwash
Can you point
To any specific
That's not made up
Where Obama has
Infringed upon
Any kind of rye
Yes
Environmental
Okay
Basically
Really what they're going with recognized
These gay marriage
When it's against their religion to believe in
Gay marriage
Is that
What's cake cake
Right
Who cares
Make a cake
Or don't
Yeah don't but old is Joy of the blowback that's fine
No gays allowed
Yeah
Down to like what the free-market literally is
If you want to do that
You know the
People who are super like libertarian on free marketside
We'll make the Oregon
Yeah if someone puts up a no black sign at their restaurant
Then they're going to go out of business
Yeah sounds good in theory
But if you look at what happened with g
Chick-fil-A
It doesn't work that way bother them at all
Did Republicans rallied around it
Conservatives are like Chick-fil-A and make a big deal out of how we're going to it
Support them for hating gay people
Do they know there are enough bigots in the world that will celebrate
Kind of Wilkie
Keep them in business
But even then
It's not as though he
Anyone
To do anything
Other than
The same thing that the government is therefore
Which is
In the eyes of our law
That is the case
If you don't want to acknowledge that
The government
Cannot arrest
Unless you are working for the government
Like a judge or the clerk
The clerk that Famous Dave's
Deny those license
Is that legal
Yeah because that's a purely loss
You don't have to acknowledge that they're getting married
You're Jamaican
F****** cake
Nobody put those people
I don't think
With any understanding of God like I don't want to get off on a like God as I see him
Rent
Yeah but like
Any word that is conceivable
I can't imagine
Him being like
Order being like
Hey you live a good life
I appreciate what you did you had a great family
That's a big deal
That's hilarious God
YouTube Pastor gave that was if that was really God that's
Pretty funny f******
Yeah
This guy goes on little bit more
And no you don't
Ellison beat his ice moments
He wants to destroy United States disagree with that
An emergency break up
If you don't wake up using your Slumber and your Slumber bleed to death
Agree with that
For different reasons for 3 on Dub City
But the other two you'd disagree with what he's actually saying you just
Agree with the literal words
No evidence I can find that 2,000
Some of the radical islamist
Hi Google
0 research
That's how much research shiny
Need to do a little and
I've also done some research on this
Choose another wild accusation
Could you believe
In Europe
I've been watching is
Videos
He's a hardcore what lobbyist what's it will happen
It's one of the branches of radical is
Groups
That
Mostly
Responsible for
The terrorism that we
I didn't know that
Brennan former head of the CIA was a lobbyist
Sleeper Cell kind of thing
Is a
It's like
Therapy
We talked about this
Before which is that
Because
A lot of
People are so
If you want to
Go
And
Paint them is
Evil
You have to make s*** up
Yeah you can't engage with them on real
Reasons that they have it narrative I wanted to get to the bottom of why they think that
Brennan is at what happiest Sleeper Cell
The dates back to him refusing
To call
The terrorists radical Islamic terrorist
You want to call them
Extremist
Okay
Like taking away the fact that they
Were
Obviously
But just prioritizing with they are extremists
Terrorist
Which is really the more important Point probably
What do you call the IRA
You call that much
Call them Irish Catholic
Yeah radical Catholic
But even then
If you do call them that
What are you
You doing
What is the what is
The go there other than
Demonized
Yeah it's two tar other Catholics who are involved in their butt
You're going to go with any kind of radical
Religion there
All you're really doing is saying
These are the people
Believe
What they're saying and other people maybe don't
Also believe that that
This should be
In that it's sort of like they're doing it we should too
Mentality of being like these are the radical
Islamist
Is radically
With radical Christianity
Call whatever it is
They say we're doing is what they're due
Describe him.
We can talk a little bit about Alex Jones
I've been watching is
Is videos on YouTube
Don't don't don't
Alex Jones news
Very important and it's a shame America
They got a lot of issues on their plate
See that that dude just eliminated
I didn't see that you liked all of your paper currency is now worth
Whoa
Did you see this guy right there.
In the past talked about how India has monkey police
Yes and people think that I'm
Some sort of a xenophobic
Bigot because I
15 problems
It's such a
Huge place
Cultures and languages
Isn't everything
Like a
The North and the South are like night and day
Hey we can't even really understand that we we think of our like
Rural America and the urban Elite
His well-being
Whole thing it boggles my mind how
It's all basically the UK
Always their fault
Whatever they just drew up random lines where it's like okay everybody who identifies as pack
Pakistani now
From wherever they were living
Just drop these random border
And that could not have caused
More insane
Remnants of colonialism being
Being
Brought
The full light
Another thing he wants to stay this is direct shout out to
To the Muslims maybe another pro wrestling promo type of thing
You don't let them people that's home
Nobody says they're all good
And also that's
Simplistic view of
By the world Muslim
Fun
It is it is
They simply
View of the world
The good verses
Evil
Concept2
It makes everything
So easy
What you missing the nuances that kind of reality
12 years one more thing he wants to say and this really scares me quite a bit this is our last clip from
Alex is breakdown of trump speech
On the street
A bit scary
A military Secret Service out strong
But pumpkin science
Installed
Yes
That's true
That is true we are the greatest
Superpower in the
Scariest possible reality
Trump as the f****** president
But just that part works
He's like Trump will Triumph
Screaming at
Just like that
So hitlerian
Like that is the kind of
Speech
Would hear from people who are a super into
And I'm not here to say that Trump is Hitler
Simplistic
Has a great little
Concept
I would rather we call him Hitler
Before he becomes Hitler like
If Hitler was called out for being Hitler before
That's a good thing
That's a good thing that we're trying to
Because we have the awareness of what has happened in the past week
We should use that awareness
Yeah it was the only way for never again to actually work
The same kind of national
Isn't that gay
I mean like we're seeing these people on the street and they're all like they're wrapping up all there
Religious beliefs
Into this nationalist
Sick movement
And and whether or not Trump
Means that to happen
He's not
Strong enough
Control these
Imagine a scenario where he actually does
Just want to lower taxes
If that were all he really wanted to do
He still has these Fringe weirdos who are emboldened by him
Powered by
And they're putting whatever bulshit they have
Into his victory
And you can't control them
No one can
No
Which is the lesson that the GOP is
Currently learning
Because they couldn't
Control truck party
What day did we
It was a piggybacked on it
They could
Minimizer
If I mean you just look at how Fox News
Instead of being the
And alarm for the
The GOP
Became the
Did Geo
Yeah
Dictate
To the GOP what was going to
Instead of
Did you appear
Telling them to Heroes talking points
Exactly
I mean
If you if
Just go by like the
The stated objective
Years ago
It's in
All the sudden now
Not just
Lip service
To balancing
In the budget
But their use
Troll like
Okay
Cuts for the rich
What's the culture War
The same like
You get people to fight over.
You can trick them
Into voting a
Alex Jones's analysis
Has to do with the dumb s***
He's not giving him the props
Analysis
Just want to give him
Swing of his own language
I want to end this episode with a couple of clips
Awesome no please I don't I don't want to limit your phone down
I don't want to limit your freedom microphone but it's important to hear what's being said about my religion
So this
This is an interaction that Alex had with a protester on the street
Who are the
I had to do with
Free speech in the first amendment being
Taking away and depressed
And what have you
This woman I don't know who she is
But she is my new hero
Really
Depress
Wyndham legalising
Obama
Oh my God
Are you up
Baby
Fake news
Earlier
Yeah that's
I had a coffee
That's what you think
But you have liquor on your breath
Could you get out of the car please
No I'm not
Rhonchi
Coffee
I'm going to yell fake news at Kopp's
From now on
Mediamatters.org spaying three million people to protest
Does that lady is
Fuckingawesome
Exactly what you did at mediately
She started to throw that reality at him so you smell like booze
I need to yell at someone like you
Cuz they have another interaction
This shows
Thin-skinned cowardice
Oh yeah you gotta Listen sweetheart
Hey if I was losing an argument how do I get my salmon and I wouldn't we checked
I would bring you over here if I was losing the argument
Note or something
I'm over coffee company
What
Appreciate
Over here
Yeah
What
Dick what a total
F****** dick
Someone who agreed with us
Acted like that
We would have the same response
Yeah that's insanely shity Behavior misogynistic
Childish bully
13 year old on the playground
Who just can't engage with anybody on ideas
Yeah
Yeah that's full-on drunk
F******
For most of the time but they were
Do you think s*** like that
I can't
I can't Co-op to the offense
You know like
It is
It is not something that I'm offended by
Because I under
Stand any kind
That I've never had
A credit that lady handle that with aplomb and decency and decorum
Even anger
He would have pulled back
And then like
Taking the high road
Look at this dump feminist
Exactly little Rosa drill
Accepted what he was doing
Recognized it and then immediately minimized and narrated sort of the absurdity
The child small child what would happen to us if we ran into would make him
So many times
Cake
Smiley f***
Enough
That is f****** b******* friend Marty DeRosa the other night
A reminder he gave me a nice reminder of
We watched
Alex's coverage
Which of Julian Assange
Big announcement
During the campaign
At 3 in the morning I'm going to make a big announcement
And so Alex and his whole crew
To watch that
And brought
Cuz they thought it was going to be all about like a nail in the coffin for Hillary
It was
Was that it was Wikileaks 10th anniversary
Hahaha
And so at that point they started
Screaming
Hillary's butt plug
Look how much that's shifted
With only a couple months
Yeah only a couple months
Now they're like WikiLeaks
Is the oldest tourist true information
It's such a wild hypocrite
F***
And this is
The thing that you see on
Twitter all the
Or even on The Daily Show
Right remember whenever John used to have those clips of
Some playing some b*******
Yeah and then four years later Mitch
Richmond
Conical
Saying the exact opposite
And
The thing about
Is no one cares
Will you forget no one cares about hip-hop
Because your team
You forget that three years ago you only won the championship to the guy who beats his wife was on
Have you returned to blind items
So now you can still cheer for the team next
Ran the ball real hard I know he punched his wife
Drag her out of an elevator but man he ran the ball
Over and over
Problem IO
Please have with
Even even with
Who just
Accept everything
No
He was
Critical in a lot of
A bunch of waste
To justify it and
And I know he's met
Then I can
Possibly match
That does not
He is not still
Been a hypocrite
So many
The argument that it's wrong to hit
The team you're playing
You should absolutely
Like the Democrats right now
They should
The f****** women's March
Well it's like it's like we don't need
The
Thomas Anderson
That is
Disappointed he makes that is very fine
It's valid
But anyway the inauguration happen
Alex
Was clearly drunk for a good part of it
Which means
It's time
On the street and there was a very limited amount of time
The he did
And our next episodes will be back in studio I think we'll be able to bring
Things back towards
Backwards
Normal Alex
Screaming the whole bunch
Good deal
Now you can follow us on Twitter at knowledge underscore fights
We are on iTunes knowledge
Subscribe give us a review
Unless you're a cuck
I also you can email
Especially if
One of us
Yeah we're dumb libtard Crock-Pot cut
If you want to send it
Female knowledge fight
At gmail.com
Time in the UK I look forward to hearing all about it when you get back
Tell me if you find any of these Muslim no-go areas
Text me about what it feels like to be an American in the age of
I remember when I was abroad
And there was a lot of everyone I was
Your path
I remember when I was abroad when Bush was president
I got a lot of
Got a feeling
I can't imagine
Any better
I think I think if I do
If I do a
Set
The first words I have
Have to say are
I'm sorry
And then I can continue
I like to start
Shortly
Ladies and gentlemen
Thank you
Good luck
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work