Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
I'm Jordan we're couple dudes like to sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Which is one
Thank you
Your first words are
This might be very very fun or you might be curious
Wow you could introduce our beverage
Search for the day cuz this is your choice
Vanilla cream
How's that taste
You're based what is pretty good
Vanilla
Cake frosting but liquid
Okay now I think I know what the next
The next you know a lot about our
Alex
You don't know anything about witches
Is very exciting for me
Like like Jordan alluded to I told him
Before the show drinking a vanilla
It's weird
Before the show I told Jordan that today we're going to do something a little bit different
Here's why
Pretty violent
In the current want to talk about that
It's kind of boring
And I also don't want to
Feed into a really even dissect to the CNN
Oops
The project obviously
Manipulative the edited
He's James O'Keefe Eli
Monster High
Discredited repeatedly in the past
Been sued
Repeatedly
Somebody that somehow people are still
The narratives that other people wish were true
Right but I mean
Come on
That brothers are Mercer fund
Astro
Money gifts to make
Let's make sure billionaires
Control our world
Recent video was about to Hooker
Okay here's here's the video
I've already I've already taken you off track
Freezer one is legitimately James O'Keefe outside
Zucker's house
Microphone
And he's like
Basically
Hooker
In a car
I meant O'Keefe's like what a coward
They reveal that they've been staking out in front of his house
To get his morning routine down
Are you stalking him basically
This is something that we should adopt
Don't f******
Don't f****** go to your congressman
Get 1000 10,000 people and just sit around outside there
Studio is
I mean it would be that hard we could employ the exact same tactics and running
That's true
Give us money I'll do it
Alright
The other thing is we're currently in the middle of an Alex Jones
Distraction
Which is
Whenever
I don't know exactly what the there's no through-line exactly why he does
The things he does
Money
But every now and again something will pop up and it'll be
Look up
It's me it's the right sheet
To the charging bull
What group is about to smack Alex Jones
But he's been lying about a bunch of stuff
And he gets the red tape out and distract
Cibola
This week
At the end of last week
He had Robert David's
Honor the go
Who we've discussed in the past
When he came on
And was saying the Trump needs his own propaganda TV network
He was the guy who came on it was like
I need you to talk to for me
I have a list of suggestions he needs to read that
We talked about it
Beyond the one with the
No no it was Dennis Montgomery
Time for a little bit
Because he was
Basically saying that they need massive election
Reform
In order to like
Liberals
In a democracy is a really bad idea
He came on the show the end of last week on Thursday
You dropped this nugget
Tell me just point out that pedophilia does not stop with sodomizing children
It goes straight into terrorizing them to Adrenalize their blood
And then murdering them
It also includes murdering them so that they can have their bone marrow harvested as well
Body parts
Pedophilia is must be original
Yes yes it's an anti-aging singing
And way out but we actually believe that there is a call
Only on Mars
Populated by children who were kidnapped
Space on a 20-year Rye
I saw the once they get tomorrow if they have no alternative but to be slaves
No idea
I mean
We see a bunch of
Original guys on the air and could you do I think you should be the truth
Channel in America he can't be he doesn't know how
But
They say ridiculous s***
Then everyone is like
Look at how ridiculous
Play me a clip of me saying that well
We played the clip you had a guy who you have focal said you respect
What is opinion
About
Hey man your response
There's machine wreckage on Mars
You're reinforcing it without actually saying you believe in it
Attract
It's all a trap for the media it's all a trap
For people who don't like Alex Jones
Non him for bars
Yeah I've seen
This this one in particular on the on the Twitter
Yeah I saw that
And said no
The course that was that
Come on bro scientist walk up to a podium
Rubbers for hedges
Come on
Why do I have
And the only real function that we get out of this
I think it's always funny when official organization
Below their status
Just shut up
I always think conceptually that's pretty funny right but it's
Putting out articles about it
By people not being really accurate and just making fun of him for it
The end result is the people are exposed Alex Jones
They if they watch that full clip they get to hear him talk about how terrible pedophilia is
I'm at Mike's at office
Files
There is a decent chance that people will end up
Listening to
He was just allowing free speech on his show
Come from falling for this
This bull trick
Okay
It is always like what
Twitter the Twitter
Which is amazing how Alex
Can just keep
F****** showing up in the world every time
It seems like he's somewhere in the on the internet
Like
Are we helping
Are we
No just making it more likely for it cuz
The movie click on it
Do anything fun
Everybody thinks like I do appreciate our listeners who engage with stuff
Appropriately
Famous Mart
A lot of people and text
Some stuff about how like
Juicy this new Alex Jones meme
And I think there's a mentality people think that you can just block him out of it
Not realizing that no you can't that's not going to work
There's going to
Need to be a much
More
Deliberative
Focus
Truth Bass
Exposure of what he believes in
And who he actually is
Hiding behind those silly things
Is a bigot
In the same way
Reading
Trump's tweets
Bright all of them
Get f****** hit by a meteor
I don't f******
Supposed to
Please go f******
Making
Trying to make it so we can vote
He is destroying the healthcare
Re-election
With 97
Crazy.
So we have that to look forward to
So here's the deal I don't want to talk too much
About
Nonsense
It's not worth
Discussing most
So the stuff that Alex
What is on at the end of last week
Beginning of the week he was on vacation
I don't
I don't know what's going on
He's living a wildlife La Vida Loca
Play
Life on Mars
Dakota on that
They did not
From that album
Exact
Also
Is episode comes out will be getting surgery
I want a treatment
So
I've decided to do a complete audible on this episode
And explore
Where this idea of bases on Mars come from
Play f****** at are you kidding me yes the rest of this episode will have very little to do with Alex Jones
But it will have to do with where
And deleted from the iTunes
I promise you that this will actually be maybe more entertaining
There are a lot of people who believe
In
Space spaces
And what have you community community is very diverse
You can find tons of people who cites far more diverse than Alex Jones
Totally
I'm sure there's more than 3% African-American
But maybe not I haven't seen study
But
There are a lot of people believe
You know
Lot of rampant speculation
There's a lot of people who have been fooled
Buy fake documents about stuff
And that's all fun we could do deep dive into that or we could even do a deep dive into stuff like move
That is an organization
Keep track of
Self-reported UFO experiences
Multi
The National UFO
Network something I don't
Stanford
Milana the movie that very traumatized Mike Pence
I don't know
Anybody other than my wife
Weather
Woman
Other than my wife
Mother
What
Like a radio show his childhood has
Open Dumbo
F***** up
Yeah for the mutual UFO Network
It's a non-profit
Investigative body with Emmylou just they have a lot of
They have Maps
We're UFOs have been sighted
And stuff like that
Is apocryphal so much of it is basically just
Hey I saw this
And there's no real evidence
You know it's as good as a people
And putting them online
So I tried to find some more concrete
Version
Space Bass
Stop
And one of the organ and we're going
Straight Talk
Space command for our first
Right now we don't really have space command doesn't really come into play because that's a pedestrian
Title
The people in the know with never calls
Okay
Organization
Camelot
Hey what you doing
What's today
Apparently
She had a very large inheritance
And she started
An organization
She's has Skype interview
People
About their weird
Experience
She's had a ton of interviews with people who
Claim
But they were personally involved with a lot of really f***** up
One of the people that we have
In the past
Guy by the name of Andrew basiago he's done some interviews with Project Camelot
He is the guy who claims that you as a child was in a time travel program he went back to like the Getty
Leesburg address
He's been years
Future like
He's been far in the future
When he was a kid
Barack Obama was in the program with him
Hemet believe that
He also ran for
For president in 2016
Is Rodney
Also is Eric Hall is a big proponent of what's-his-name go
No longer does anybody say Bernie would have won
Also I would know you would lose that race
It seems like
He knows that he's going to win
2020 race
And he just had to go
Get his profile out
Clearly
You have no idea
He also believes
Stargate
He's big into that also has made reference
Affected use half dolphin
And has
Stargate
Kingdom leading class
Anthony just agreed
Standing ever
Conspiracy theory thrown out of
Getting in hospital interviews
Scott Aukerman
August blind
Guessing
But a lot of it is the same methodology
Dolphin
I'm a chimera
You fear me Alex Jones
The Camelot
We were texting the other day about how
Mysterious it is
Never brings up like Louise Mensch
She would be an obvious Target for him if
He was he's mad at anybody who's against Trump
She has created this whole cottage industry online
Of being
Superga
And having super secret information
Seems like our Jones
Making up in
Information
About her as we should be
Very beginning and I have this very short conversation
Could give her that I'm sitting there screaming
I told you so
I wasn't saying I believe
I was saying that she was in a different
Class of
Commentator
Right and his time is going on the proof of the pudding is
Eating and I don't think I stand by my comment
Broad
People who are perfect
Is one thing
Finally get he could
Tee off on the line
Everything has proven wrong
He could easily do that but he doesn't
Does a little mysterious.
I'm not sure it means anything
Control.
I have no idea
He also doesn't ever talk about these
Please Andrew basiago
Via this whole world of stuff
And there's also a reason
It's because they expose how stupid his ideas
Will know
Not directly
Pfizer word
Okay thanks
Are horseshoes
Like a Warrior
Make lunacy of Alex Jones
Fish people walking around
Is there a fish people walking around that have one of them
If you did you interview him and you guys.
Let the real world version of the fake ship that is
Garbage is almost if
Alex Jones
12 dimensional dreams
Susan lies all
Came true like people are alarmed
What Alec
Alex Jones is talk
Yeah it more or less
Carrie Callahan
Does this
Project Camelot
She puts out really long YouTube
Interviews with people
Sort of Hallmarks of her interview Style
Is she believes Buckeye
Can ever
She's like like
You know George Noory on Coast to Coast AM
Is never make people feel we
Whenever people call it was outlandish stories he's kind of
You never is like
Shut up you're stupid
Carrie is like
Even farther
Like
Play Crazy Horse
Christina
That seems more intellectually honest
Tomato
A Fox news interview where they pretend
The pushback
Phuc yea
Believe it
Any reason
Suspect that she doesn't believe
The things you say
I I kind of agree with you
She's a professional bowler
Yeah like what she's paid to do is just believe everything
Yeah
Although the thing is
Her videos often have as many views as Alex Jones videos online
No
She could be making multiplayer
Everybody had a real serious cut
YouTube address
Okay because they're switching over to that YouTube
TV format
They're shifting into like a lot of Fringe stuff and political stuff
He's getting caught in terms of their ad Revenue
But it's not
You can claim the train
To censor libertarian
Those two channels that also had massive cut
In terms of what they are making
So
Who cares
Carrie Callahan
Project Camelot
I have done
Severian
Nursing interview is over
Over the years and one of them we're going to be
I'd like to read a little bit
Perspective
From an interview she did with
Nicki Minaj
Which is a bikini magazine
This is this will give you a good scent
Is a good precursor for the interview we're going to be
Hit I'll start with v
Thought so what do you think
Aliens have such an interest in Earth
So why do you think it is
What's a good or special about us
Her answer
There are many things on earth they find quite desirable and I have a good number of whistleblowers who have given me information
To that effect
My whistleblowers are predominately ex-military
Some of whom are still working for
The secret
Also record the aliens are very interested in our gold for exam
Fargo
Yes I'm told the gold on earth is relatively easy to access
Compared to getting it off an asteroid
Which obviously would have issues when it comes to mining for gold
Rebuttal
You also mentioned aliens wanting to do business
Yes
Earth is also a very pleasurable place
To do business
There's also reason to use Earth as a jumping-off point to explore the rest of the solar system and the Galaxy
Also apparently human females are considered to be very useful for breeding
A genetic experimentation the extraterrestrials
Is also come here for food
Turn reptilian races consider us a food stores
Are those
Simply wants us with us
We're very good at building things we also
Send troops
Conflict around the universe
Now this is important
Human soldiers are being sent to Interstellar conflict
Her answer
Soldiers were alleged to be going to Iraq or Afghanistan
Places like Mars
To fight battles alongside other alien race
Those men and women will have their minds wiped when they come back
This is why we're having so many suicides with exposure
In some cases their minds have been wiped so many times
They become
As a result
When they returned they don't know where they've been
They think they've been to the Middle East
But they've actually been out
What is a good primer
Love this
I have never been in love
Quite like this
So what are your thoughts
Man
Ex-military
We're off to a great start
First sentence
Gold is easy enough to find on Earth
Which is
I mean
It seems not true
I don't know is there a lot of gold
I don't know
So
Gold
Really only manual
Turd
The center of
Rockstars so when they explode that's why I heard
Metals on Earth
Because
Fusion in
Stars exploding
So
It would seem that planets
Would probably be
Where to get gold from
I don't know I think there are trace minerals
Okay I'm going to say that once
Do you understand why they want our gold
Why do you feel like that's important
Sixer iPhones
Need the conductor
We're all good though
Interstellar travel
They still haven't figured out
Okay
Pleasurable
Disagree with entirely if you could leave
Yes that's true option of leaving the planet be nice to be
Places
Vacation
All right well now you've convinced
Secret government is still out
Okay
Jury is still in a
Not disproved
Probably better for genetic
Experiments
I would say that
I don't
Alien races
I'm not sure how much
Genetic experimentation
Would be relevant
Seeing as we're completely
Different species
Then why
Eksperimente
Also there's
So we're just going to go by curiosity
Philip
Eating people the reptilians
Maybe maybe not
I don't know
What about Komodo dragon
Coronavirus in Hawaii
Slight fear of
The Komodo
Lizards
Around
Little bit scary
What dinosaurs
Poisonous snakes eating humans
Eating our flesh it's also like
Harvesting emotion
And stuff like that
I did not know that
In these communities there is a lot of feeling
The world is so negative
Because
You have to create negative energy that these
The demonic
Being scanned
Beast off
I have not heard that
Which one
Soldiers are committing
Suicide
Is because
They've traveled the universe
And have their mind
But
You find that both offense
Insofar as completely trivializes
Destructive
Post-traumatic
Basically trying to say
There is no war in the Middle East
And all those 100,000 million
The people who have died
Ezra as a
Results of fake news fake news
People die
Call
ETF
It's so stupid
Defensive
Terrible
That's it
I want to live in that
That's the world I want to live in this world sucks
Give me the world where
Universe traveling soldiers
But that's why people gravitate towards
Because it is
Much more pleasant world
Fantastical and Wild
Okay so today
We're going to be going over
T45 with a note
446 with a
Jury still out on the
Yeah so
We're going to be looking at an interview that she did
With a gentleman by the name of Randy Cramer
To give you a little bit of a syllabus of what we're about to hear
According to himself
Maybe I'll just let it play out I don't want you to I want you to be surprised by the things he says
Super soldier or Dolph Lundgren
I don't even know where to draw the line
His story
Like I said
This is not
Sara leave the beginning
Of the idea that there are
Colonies on Mars
And stuff like that
F*** yeah they come up
Course they do
VI
This isn't the beginning of the ideas
Mars
Look into it in the
The stuff that's being spewed online
Very little in terms of people who have come out
Thought they were involved in those things
And therefore I think
Worthwhile
To take a peek at
So I will
This thing start with Carrie
Callahan
Project
Given the introduction
Give him some credit
Captain Randy Cramer is a US Marine is super soldier who served
For 17 years on Mars
Canning the Mars colony
And was assigned to the Mars
Defense Force
Covert military branch United States Marine Corp
Designed to handle all matters
I'm really glad that that's your reaction when doing a Regular Show f*** that
No it is all about Carrie Callahan
No thank you
That's hard and before the show that this could indicate a new direction that we can take the shower
You guys enjoy this episode please do let us know cuz we
More than willing
Episodes about these whistleblowers
Absolutely
You can take away from that is
He has been ready Cramer
Has been on Mars for 17 years
He is a super soldier
U.s. Marine
I'm going to
To speculate that he's
Did you look it up
I can't find any evidence that he is
When we what's his story is flashed explain why I'm not convinced he's actually a Marine
I will be honest but
His timeline and stuff like that to be very
But at the same time I don't want to take anything away from his service
And I appreciate it even if he is
A little bit naughty
Even if it was on Mars
Also 3D I think I would appreciate that because
Long drive tomorrow 17
Which means
You know that was
We probably could have gotten to Mars
What
Oh no.
You left Earth
In like 1983
Let's take a look
In 1980
83 how long do you
I think it would have taken
Infinite Thai
So he's
Rufflet
Super soldier because he
75 years old
I promise you all of you
Relativity is involved he has to be I promise you
I promise you all of these concerns will be addressed
Just poorly
Like I said I'm not
Play sure what the super soldier
Your stuff is at this point
Four serum
Well let's see
Without divulging too much richer did Elizabeth are in the 1960s pretty much became the priority technology
Developing a technology
Ability
From the ground up
Field trip report
Nothing but, based mind control technology
Really damaging to the subject
Incognito
So if you want to guarantee that you have a subject that can get a job done
For you you know us a hint at the end of a very very large
It will happen but you're not going to get it
You're self-destructive become completely mentioned in stable or something
Checks out
United States Marine Corps special section being the organization that it was again and being beholden to the
I'm getting really was doing plenty of passionate about the technology and was assessing that much of the
Trauma-based mind control is not working
MK Ultra
We think that your methodology
Jackson
We think you ought to consider why
This is a better way of doing things than what you're doing because we think the week all going with the brain training versus the
Against the grain
Create a better
Last longer
They won't go crazy if it works right and they'll actually want to do their job because you won't be
Absolutely
Upgrading Supercell
Did a great job of giving us One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest
Sometimes A Great Notion also why the Unabomber
Never
Take me to bomber out of there
Unabomber out of there
Jaded Drake
Yeah
John Holmes
Add event
MK Ultra
And it did exist
Like in the 50s
Robux that was one part of it right there were also
Weird psychological tests that we're done on people
In terms of
Abusing them
I'm seeing what would happen
Brett
Just line up in Italy
It's a horrible thing
And it has come out there is evidence
Continue past
Date as it were
Which is
Not what this
Secret government wants you to think
Exactly
Secret government
Damn you
This all started with Eisenhower apparently as Randy Cramer
He explains that
Basically
They were working
With space programs
And what have you
And that's what
Track you was actually talking about
This whole program
And I off of planetary stuff
Also Eisen
How was
The first Super
Slogan
Be like
Right ba
Going on and on
Don't really even explaining what they did
Here we go here
Specific
And by late 1969
My DNA was being concocted in the petri dish somewhere and then when I was born
Animal of 1970
Super silver fighting machine
Implanted
Came out nine months later and raised
I could figure that everything being happening
Religious background so any of the sort of the more weird metaphysical things that were
Write off
Being a
Demonic attack on the household or
You know something that was much more spiritually answer both of their religious system
So we can take from that
Parents are crazy
Which which would lead to
A higher incidence of the kid being a little
So
He was
In a test tube in a lab
Implanted back into his mother's womb
Born and raised
Is as normally as possible
Which is why we need
Stop playing
I'm sure they would have
So he goes on
Being something maybe more material
Strange bruises
They're getting older and they don't remember a lot of
Conversation
Strange things are going on today
I kind of live in their own universes while I'm somewhere ISO
They actually took it very well very well
Would you rather
I shouldn't
The smoke follows pregnant
I shouldn't have used God while
Things to like mysterious bruises and stuff like that
I know you speculated sleepwalking
It's entirely possible
There's also possibilities
Usually when there are bruises
And stuff mysteriously on children
Stigmata
From his childhood
That wasn't
Parents receive
Absolutely
Do that pause
I'm not saying that is the case but it is entirely possible and when you bring up stuff like that
Ghosts
And super soldier
I don't know how is genetic engineering
To be a super soldier would cause me
Mysterious bruises
Outsiders
Experimental program
Sparring when he's five
His body is rebuilding itself around these
Genetic
The veins
The the arteries
Tazewell pop
Growing inside
That's where Bruce
Nothing interesting.
Why the f*** not
Blow your mind
Also this is not where I'm going to plant my flag
Before
They have this MKUltra this abuse
Super soldier
But the problem
Will you come too
Is the DC super soldiers
Ucreate had no morality
Did they die real young
Sort of
Robot
They weren't a robot
Super soldier that you would need
Brandi goes on today
Explain how he is
A version of amore
Amor mortal
Super-soul
It's basically I was trained from my adolescence left my teenage years the age of 17
As a super soldier in Project
What's the different kind of program
Actually thinking feeling
Moral super soldiers that would make moral and ethical decisions
That would be for the good of the people
Historical notion
Plastic
Greco-Roman heroic model and said Luckett really want to create people like you know this
Hercules
Ajax
They're not just murder me
These are moral ethical Heroes
Who did what they did because they believe in a better purpose
Bigger stronger faster smarter
Monster they were bigger stronger faster
Smarter stronger better
Because they believed in self-sacrifice they believed in
Chicken back and being fat with a bunch of bunch of wires but you know they were out
Fighting the Dragon
People
No real dragons
Ben
This man
I don't care.
Would this dude be probably better than Charles
So
Re-examine
History
Let's first of all
A Titan he wasn't human
How do I listen
Because he was bad
But be that as it may use a use a warrior
He is wrathful primary characterization
The only reason
There's a story in The Iliad
Is because Achilles
Gets pissed off
General
Comes over in his like
Hey I'm going to take your warbound
Which was women
Yeah his woman got stolen his plunder got stolen he like f*** it I'm not fighting then
That's the whole beginning tension
Oh
Hero
It's not like he was fighting for some Noble purpose in the simile
In the Trojan War
Cheerleading the Second Amendment property in the sensitive person was his property yes absolutely
His examples are immoral
Super soldier with
Hercules weather
Hero
As a
Play
The guy but he was also a demigod
The Gorgon
The 12
The cleanup
Superhero I will admit
Clean up that shed
You're good so I think we're pretty well established
At this point
Imagine a
Much deeper into the essence of
The program that makes
Other than to say in that last
Was training
I was sparring with trees
Think you got that thing on your
Your face huh
What's cross-eyed
The surgery
Maybe it's a homing Beacon that I'm going to be cutting out of myself
Suddenly in
Mysteriously
They refer you out after
Initial diagnosis
He did
Oh no
Secret government so
Future
I'm glad we have
Explain what happened
The program
So as they took 300
The program and then when I guess
Graduated about age 17
Moonshadow essentially
Only one of many super soldier programs
Not just in America but around the world that contribute to the larger program
Then parcel soldiers out of the programs to something called project manager
Mannequin is a larger Global program
Which takes all the super soldier program from everybody else and then assigns them either back
Reprogrammed on the ground
Waiting on word to the outer program the DVD
The Briefing is off-world Adams off-planet is definitely PDF
So you either trying to get parcel back into a special unit or you get sent off
Idiot block
DDS in park without exposure to radiant Guardian into the other store stations in any of the other planet
Radiant guardian come on
The program
3DS
Fundrise
Foundation
Brett
First offense
I'm not privy to every planet
Play Parcels at them to all of those
And
Come tomorrow
Mars the Mars colony Corporation is what runs smartphones makes Contracting MDF
Which is the only private military Contracting agency
The water is not
Paperwork thing is no longer you know in charge of everybody at the nccr the India
Bureaucracy
We live in this
Go to
That makes me
Like
Bureaucracy
Call the time
Makes me think maybe he's had a shity job
Paperwork
Before but
B I like that all the people in the moon Defense Force are from the Earth Defense Force
Coronado members of the Earth Defense Force members
This is just normal
So you might be asking
Yourself
And how are you you comes in at 7
What happened
What was the actual moment
Whatever
300f
Defeating the
From Earth at age 17
Remember the 17th
1987re actually in the morning of the would have been November 18th 1987 at 2:30 a.m.
A localized Wormhole a two guys
But we didn't just go do training session it was
Talk to an underground base to a like
Hanger with an aurora trb-3 big black triangular vehicles at the
Actually manufactured by Boeing
And that other
Schoolmaster the Air Force wherever else
You're still kind of a standard
Terrestrial shuttle vehicles are not the most advanced thing at all but you know if they do the job
Advanced technology
You know people if they catch one or get one
Tjk
I want to take a moment to say his story is changed
Substantially over interview
He's a lot of his stuff did not appear in early interviews about size.
Absolutely
But you know he's remembering more and more
He does like a
Recovers blocks of his memory and stuff like that
Explains why a lot of the stories
Some changes
But it also explains why
Has gotten to
To the point where a lot of this
This is blase
A lot of
Who's like you know
Forest there's a lot of paperwork
Carryover
Localized
Were you given warning or was it just like a hole
Space is opened up into dude walked out more like
Alright
Get in. Get in here so you go stupid
And my butt
They come through this wormhole
Localized wormhole
Older Country
Absolutely you don't want to be second opening up he's crazy lungworm
Anyway that's
Again
Riverside Lodge
You're right there
You want to go with the safest route and you've already got the
Pizza Inn
You might ask
I mean is there anything.
Maybe
Where we going with reprocessing process
In front of a junior officer
We're going away for a 20-year tour
You don't know where you're going to go yet I can't tell you that we don't know it's the package classified but yet Edition.
Going to happen then we'll bring you back
Erase your memory for security reasons
Anyway
Not the lie but no
Medical exam
And there's a waiting.
I love that there's another another medical exam I think
Contract
You're not going to
Remember that
F****** stay
Secret government always lied about
Make you sign a contract
You'd like they would even acknowledge
You are genetically engineered in a lab.
Super soldier
It's not like you're going to do you need that paperwork on file
Also if you're going to
To be a super Soldier on Mars
Like you haven't
How are you
Localized
A wormhole
Everything is localized
Geo behind wormholes
R1
Across the Universe
Words coming out of
Listeners are like
Wow I thought perspective Jordan that was
That's what you're doing with the Wormhole you're taking one
Because there's no real
Between the two of them
Play the same thing so how do you even think of
Localized
Is Wormhole is any
Interstellar
And that's the magic of
Allows immediate
Theoretically
Now you might be surprised to learn
But at the same time
Randy tells us this next clip
Takes 15 minutes
To get from the Moon to Mars
No I don't even want to be a part of this
I think I cut out the
The part where you talked about this but
If we're talking about an einstein-rosen
Sure
There is
0 time
He goes to a Moon Bay
I'm guessing that's where they did
This process
And then from there they enter
8 story tall
Spaceship
Don't know why they're there waiting
Evolve
Therefore we could be living
8 stories tall is a Mastiff
To get off the ground
He gets on this ship and they go
Not even from the Moon that would be difficult
Who cares
Anyway
There's a lot more than I've ever cared about it
Save your energy
So they go in this 8-story tall ship
From the Moon
Go past the due a buzz by
Buzz flyby of Earth
From the ceiling
You can see the Earth
And you can see electrical storms
Cousin Randy is filled with his scent
The Earth is alive
It fits nice last
View of Earth
Before they shoot off
For Mars
And I hear is
I'm talking about
The trip
Tomorrow I'm assuming that eventually we'll get in
He still has
Maybe
Literally Maybe
Cal or something
Forget to check
Good memory erase box there's a clause in his contract
Secret government
So we had to let him go
Answer that question
But I have to do it later
Assuming you're not going to answer
I just want to know if there's a
Possible
I mean
There's a fence
I can't tell you that there is an answer that's good
Look we're in Alex
We're engaged
Yeah absolutely
Mr. Tire
Also I'd like them
This is about the trip to Mars and the beginning of his time there also DuckTales nicely into some
About time
Find me travel distance
Much time was passing during this time
I mean it say was the matter of minutes
Seems like I mean maybe it was a 15-20 minute you know
Ride from the moon to the back to the sort of looking at Earth and then
Once we left everything was maybe a 15-20 minute right tomorrow because then we went via Wormhole so then the vehicle
However the wormholes are manifested went through one and then we came out of Mars and then eat those unwelcome tomorrow's you grab Daryl
Location
Drive time to the ground and landed a Terri Freeman
Okay
And then this was your base for
3 years
So some kind of
Solar Warden
I'm not sure what you doing
He was radiant Guardian when I was
The part of that program but it's changed you know number of times and it's all it's been that something similar to that
About you whenever was the remainder of my 20-year tour you know however that worked out exactly what 17 years three months
14 days in
You know I guess so
In order to get more time out of it they're not going to waste time on YouTube
The actual service time unlike okay crackhead find getting extra
When you move from one place
If they want there to be if they want to see if they want to save time
You know they can do something out of time so that instead of it taking days weeks or month to take
You know 5 minutes or 15 minutes
Play with time like that I'm not a really good at Temple mechanics
The time guys really understand their businesses and certainly know how to move things around about
So you understand what he's saying they're basically is that there's time travel involved so they can
Screw you out of the
You the time that you've been you sign up for 20 years so maybe you do some of it takes like 3
MMA
Yeah
It's a living
Cursive
Well if they want
Why would they look like they are they are they joyriding are they
They f****** with you what's happening
I don't know
Stopwatch
If they want to stop loss
Right that's true it's a very bizarre understanding of time
And I don't
We hung up on 15 minutes of time
Like if you want
Travel
Here's my second theory here's my theory on that
Alright
Because of all the time traveler
That he's done
The only
Real amount of time that he can
Can measure in his brain
Like that's all you've got
Possible
You're talking to him
And you're like it's a 11
Now
Do you want to watch the Cubs
Game that's it
How long
Do you think it's
Going to be
Maybe
Siri
Time travel
True
Absolutely I've seen lost
Time travel I guess Desmond's mine just
You're wrong
Celine Dion's AR all day but
Does next
But Randy ends up on Mars
This next clip we get to little bit of talk about what
Is like when he shows up
But innocent you were based in on Mars
Explain to people that you know we're going to be relatively
On Mars
Except that point from the Earth Defense Force which route
Military private military company that is contracted to the Mars colony Corporation of the MCC to defend the Marc Cohn
One of many station to create a buffer zone around the territory with the colonies are located
Any of the local
Hostile animal life & Style of life
You know out of that territory
And I can only sort of answer for you know what was taking place in our area which Dino for sometime I certify
Northern Arctic
So you know
Everywhere else but
Crossovers and validation
Eventually they will be a lot more people talking about
They're not ready to come forward right now but you know
You were talking to people on a regular basis to
To go to their meeting
People end up in a work
Planning for a lunch happen
I want a wrong number group text
Hey
What was your experience like
Local
Hostile
And possibly also possibly
Sentient
Oh no
There is no possible about it there were aliens
Oh yeah well
Indigenous Marsh
As I believe they prefer to be
Yeah yeah
That's the correct terminology
He was there you was on Mars
Colonies
We find some overlap with Robert David
Steal from The Alex Jones Show
Talking about there being
And colonies on
On Mars
He was
Super soldier Randy was
Fight off
Dogs
Right
So now he has a really interesting
Prob
Don't look at me like that
So what is
The one problem
He goes on to say that their bases were like Underground
And within a mount
Cuz of course they
I mean
Cuz otherwise
There are a lot of people
Why they would need to
There a lot of people with a lot of telescopes
We have a Rover on Mars now
Figure out
Breitbart
The spot where we
Faces
Yeah that's true
See the entire planet
If you have underground base
Where are things
Coming at you from
How are you having a war in underground bases
That's the thing that they do
Discovered
So they go there to set up the
Is everybody doing coke pretty well-established
It started before the 8-hour shift.
Pictures of
We got the nuclear bomb and then immediately went to Mars
Distraction
That's when they did it everybody was is the Fallout of Nagasaki
We only really mean
One yeah
Butthole
McCoy
Everybody's too busy with the tragedy
Digging underground to develop our Martian colonies
But
To their surprise
There's
Right they are fighting
Against
I'm going to go with gold
Orson Scott Card
Wood-style
Morlocks
They already have bases
Is down there
If you're just occupying
Morlocks
I need Super Soldier
If there was nothing going on on Mars
You just have a bunch of people there
Marrow of
Children adrenochrome blog
And you'd like but you'd still like
Weird underground battles going on because
EBay people who were able to withstand
These Wormhole jumps
Some stuff like that
Spaghetti
As a
Forgotify
True scientist
We know that Mars
There's no aux
Oxygen are there
Could not really exist there
Randy wants you to know
You're a dumb dumb
He wants to tell you the truth about Mars
Climate
Right now
About it
It's not exactly the way not to tell the snack
Thousands that doesn't have a breathable oxygen
I love how
It's not
Exactly
Missy sarcasm
You guys are dumb
Do you believe
It's not quite like that but your clothes
Right
So good
It's a it's a real turn-on
Super breathable in mountainair for us it's really not recommended
Outside the equatorial regions to try and like survive without an environment suit
Regions can be a bit warmer in a bit more mild and temporary
So it's not the worst thing in the world apparently to just be sort of exposed in any Street clothing Thursday
Can you get any of the directions for the farther north and south and you're going to get way more extreme temperatures and Wednesday so Coruscant
You're going to need some protection
You're fighting
Never went outside without an environment without a powered environment
Everything else
Package
Did you have structures that you
Or was it all Underground
We were inside of a mountain free much everything is I understand is underground I mean there may be some facilities which
Operate on the surface of everything that you want to stay functioning it's got to be Underground
Inform
It's fair
I just looked it up it has to be
I'll tell you why
Near the poles
Temperatures can get down all the way
- 100
It's pretty cold
Even on the equator on
During a summer day
Which I don't remember the length of Mars
Around Earth
Who cares but Summers awhile
It can get all the way up to 7
Degrees Fahrenheit you could be out there it's a bit mountainair
You can still breathe
Don't run
Equator of Mars
Sad at night
Even
Get down to mine
100 wild fluctuations
That checks out I'm on his side now let's be clear
Things are colder Underground
You can control the environment a little bit better and put in like
Heaters and stuff like that
But if its -195 degrees north
He's at the North most
Point of their operations
Negative
If you go underground that's going to be
That is going to be way colder
Do you like 30 feet underground you are is not going to make a difference
He said he's in a mountain
Underground could be inside of mountaineer cylinder
Sitter mountains ground
What are the volcano
See now you don't even have to worry about From the Vault
All volcanoes
Not all men
Volcano
When people are on earth
Call gentleman
Amen
You might be asked
Asking yourself which is something I keep fighting myself
At this point you might be quizzically thinking
Hey
It's all the stuff
Is going on and there are all these
Space spaces
On the moon
Probably going on at work
You can get anywhere around the world
Are we getting any indication of like radio signal
Communication must be going off between
Now he's got it covered
Technology
Say something
Yeah
Alright
RadioShack
Cigna Cigna
Be strong enough to
Reach Earth
From Mars
And it would have to be
Selective enough
So you could have this
Signals you do want
Coming in coming in communication
Between the
Basis
Absolutely I don't know what is the technology people use
Sorry go ahead
Now that's a good point
I don't know
To know whether or not you could hide once
Successfully from
We weren't
Specially-created in test tubes and implanted into our parent
That's true you don't know all these
Soldiers
Right
That means they also must
WhatsApp created
They're the ones who were lying to us
Climate change
You don't think this is a 3-hour interview
And I don't have all that much
Kept it mostly to the Mars stuff yet he believes in climate change so
If we're getting we're getting off-planet
The Eisenhower
Totally clear
Really give
Any real reason that any of this stuff exists
Would be idea that it is
Is a potential colony to move to or anything like that really
Cuz why not
Sure
Explore-the-world
What has to go to Mars
I think the more likely thing is
This guy had a little bit of a psycho
Psychotic break
Crystal superfunctional
It could just be
Creative
A lot of fun
If I could
Sustained a 3-hour interview of made-up b******* with
Credulous
Woman in the world could
Listen to harass
Question
Completely
Oh yeah
Called it to the radio
Celestial defense
Yeah yeah
Weld
Is it goes by it's different
I have here discusses
To go up there
Get to the bottom of that
Mars
Basically encountering
From what I understand
Program who have interviews
Which day are called frogs
You know other Hive insects as you know sort of the do there
Building machines is genetically engineering another bug read another you know insects
Job and so
Call Zack
Just like here in
United States
Giraffe fighting
I think it's important to point out because I I keep telling people presume what that conflict was it
Or what we were fighting over and climb I'm feeling more and more that I need to be real
About why we were fighting and what we were fighting for
It was not for supremacy of the planet it was not for a total Global work the planet
Attacking got involved
But you know we were having when I would call
Conflict really with the native reptoids in the native insectoids messerly
It was way more polite and civilized
Stop What was a
Organic system of territorial
Boundary keeping that was not meant overrun somebody else's 5 or territory dispensary can maintain
Everyone
No one could grow over strong
So that everyone could maintain a Peaceable territory without anyone actually trying to become our whole planet
Words
Back-and-forth that was meant to maintain and stabilize the territory
It might
Look we were fighting
Soupremacy
F****** reptile
Ostensibly another
Local population
Skirmishes
Big fan
But I want them
Because if
They just genetically engineered another
Insectoids in
I don't understand
Feed the draconian
Bring an insectoid back
Here you have a create all kinds of Technology solve a lot of problems should be taken care of
Folding ancient Europe
Just want to f*** everything up
Very much so
Is a very
Included in the entire mythology of the lizard
Draconian
David Icke
A little bit here
Lithia the lizard-folk
War with Iran
But there was
It's not there was
You didn't
Fight forever no not even on Mars
Between Russia and the United States
Sooner or later going to get paid
Just like that
Conflict is right
I think they're going to be
I think what
Sort of
Expressing is
Is a little bit of an eye
Madea and maybe a fanciful idea about
Like Wars between Native American tribes
Before the white man came
Is a little bit of that to everybody saying
I don't know
I don't know enough
I don't know enough about
Native American history
But I do think that if you also don't know a lot
You might speculate that
That was how Native
Warfare when
And then the draconians would be
The Europeans
I'm coming over in
Going for
So maybe this is all an allegory
Just about arse
If that's
McKay's
But also I don't know
I don't know if that's accurate
No but I mean even the lesson
I'm not sure if
Accurate
Again I don't know enough about
Old time
American history
No they were people
It feels right to me
That lesson
But I don't I don't know what to
Beetroot
Because of all of the stuff that we
Kind of idolize about the neighbor
Living
The nature and all the buffalo
Did nothing
People they still f****** each other letters right there tribes
We're driven
Inspire others
Simulated there was slavery there is all that other stuff
Fiat currency
Seeing what have you all to make the argument
Just use bartering
Really if you look at it
That's not Tommy
Sophisticated
It's a little bit
Is not because we were so
Technologically
Superior cuz we were
Is native a
Most native
Where at
The disease before we ever even got here
But
Like archaeologist
Found that they've had
One of these
Largest
Cities
In the world
This has been fun but let's get back to crazy
So you
Heaven
Giggling
And what happened
A f****** Delight from you've been giggling everytime
He worried about the Mars colony Corporation
It is a corporation
I mean come on
Condos on Mars
It's a business Endeavor that is being protected by a black water as
Super soldiers on Mars
If you want to really look at the Longview that's what's going on
Randy talks a little bit about the actual colonies themselves
And you're not really allowed to visit the colony I've never been to them
I've never seen them I don't even know what they exactly look like I sent you
Albemarle County Corporation colony
Apparently they have five colonies Corporation
A Consortium of
Ghetto Earth base banking money people
Technological Corporation
Government
We're all participating
In order to be part of the operation and to be part of the colonies
Jackson
Yuno future civilization project
In order to preserve Humanity its efforts extra so
Correct I have never seen the colonies never even been close enough to them to tell you whether they're don't under
Around or what they look like
You don't want your
Colonist
Being in
Influence
Warlike
People
Movie Pollyanna
Like people who are born
Winterfell necessarily to know about the others who are up north where the white walkers
The wall
We have no idea of other
Filipino thing
Resume Game of Thrones coming back soon
Still will not pick up on those goddamn books
Even if my life
Dependable
List
13 + 5 or good
2 + 4
Interesting trends
Just take
Every other book off
I got no time for it I got to refill stuff
Anyway this
Next
Part of this clip cuz I've never been to the colonies I don't know what they look like they might be
I have no idea
Carrie Callahan
Comes back
With a real nice rebuttal
She does
Okay I respect
The f*** out of this answer
Still crazy
But it's great
Possible if you're fighting
I mean was there
Battle at the end that actually you know
Reassigned to
To the Moon
But prior to that
Your brain
With all due respect
That's been erased
Call memories that I extracted but I find that
Unlikely at this point since I feel that I've done a pretty solid extraction of pretty much everything like all the chunks
It would be something that would be a missing chunk that I am
Unlikely that I haven't found that
Rap
Now that makes me feel
Terry's right
All the more
If you
But his denial of that like
He was if he was making this
Here been like
No you're right
He would have attended her baby maybe that's possible even in his denial
Absolutely not
I've done all the searching
It's possible in my memory has been cleared I know everything
Absolutely not
That would be more respectable because that is an outright denial this still allows him to later be like oh s*** I do
Remember to call
If you're dealing with somebody who's in
Early stages
Ulta
See them
Them questions
Most likely
Play be like
I mean
I don't like cooked
It could be but I don't
So it's very unlikely
They feel like they're in
Control
Praise they don't they're not aware of their own passport of the early onset Alzheimer's
Could you get
You had your memory wiped
Different we don't actually know how many times
You know that
He's constantly
Trying to get as much
So you got to lose
Restore
Drive you're going to still get
Artifacts
If you are if you got it
You got to ask yourself to how is he going about recovering this
Obviously it's
Just talking to other crazy
I think
He's giving me the idea of them
Machine that
You are like
Hypnosis or some
I think maybe hypnosis maybe regressions
Stuff
Crystal therapy
Get to some of his science a little bit later
There's too much
Too much sodium
Randy was a hero
On Mars
Acer valiantly for 17 years and then was in this
Becoming a pilot on the moon for the last three years of battle
Tiberius infiltrate like a Draconian base
Or something like that
Something
That these guys
Are always the hero
There's no there's no okay I was on I was on Mars
I ran away from everything I lied
Pissed my pants
Four different times because
My friends they were going to get rid of
Like what
I'm genetically engineered
To be a super soldier
Who's the greatest
I'm too expensive for them to get rid
Some other weird
Dad and battle
Everything is so crazy
Everything is
Absolutely
Is
About
His 20-year Tour of Duty
Actually let's skip that set
Year did you
Return to Earth
Technically I finished my tour in 2007 but then was returned to 15 minutes after I left on the
Remember the morning of November 18th 1987
2445 or 3 in the morning
You were here at least in this 3D reality
Did the mission for 20 years and then they told us to Aid reversing thing which I don't think was really anything more than putting
Efficient
Think I'm still 17 with repressed memories
A bunch of times to so
Maybe hear my original body wasn't my original for a long long time cuz all the parts have been replaced please one point
Another
Question
You've got this guy
You replace one
He's still the same.
But if you reply
Place all of his body
I don't I didn't keep this clefable
Connection in your brain
The electrical impulses in your brain connection
Your soul
As long as there's a connection
Between your brain and your soul
They can just recover and take your brain and put it in the Clone body
You're like a car that's totaled
Okay so in this last
Battle videos
He was lucky enough to
Lost a lot of good men
Buttercup supercharged
I'm just saying that this has the
It was all a dream
No s*** if you're bringing it back to 50
2 minutes
15 minutes 15 minutes back
After you've already left
But you're still in your
20 year old 20 years later
So what they do is
Kill your old self
And then put
Well I guess if you left
2 in the morning
Weeks in the morning there is nobody
The old body
Right that's what it is exactly the same no one will notice exactly
Configuration
This clone would have had to been raised up to the point
17 years
If you would have had to time it is
Exactly
Ortega's cuz time travels Rio you could just go ahead of time travel the body to the right the right
Cara
Transfer the Consciousness put it back
Making you young
Right and he's like
These f******
Probably
Just put
Me into a younger
Clone your dresses
We make me younger at all this technology certainly exists
Technology
City Sign was he get a job
You're not even old enough to drink
And they've erased your memories
You've got a little bit of regret
He going all of us
Whoa
This could be like the Israeli Army
IVF is part of
PDF
How's your GF
Both Moon
And Mars
Little Mix
Totally makes sense
Is sort of a coda to
The entire experience
Carrie asked him how things going on Mars now
You wouldn't if you listen to it too.
Know what's going on there and he wasn't interested
Little bit
Do you know for example that the reptilians have been completely
Neither one of them are still ongoing
Do you know that kind of information do you have
Ongoing Intel
Or are you completely detached
This time
Well I can certainly tell you that the last time that I was on the moon within 2007 I remember the closing Sarah
Ceremonies that they had for the returning officers
Good2Go so
But they've changed about Luna Operations Command
The last time I was there
Now I do
Regular intelligence report weekly intelligence free from the Brigadier we have conversations on a regular basis
So I feel like
When I know I have to
My people are telling me the truth on and there's certain things sure I can use my own abilities and I can remote
I have to double-check but I still take them
He's psychic abilities
But there is a brigadier. We're going to learn a little bit more about him in the future
But so what
You get the weekly update
Like briefing
Which seems like it would be outside
The purview of this organization
And probably doesn't want him to be
Remember
You must have
The brigadier's the man on
The thing as
He tells it
He
Clearance
Requested that you make
This information public
The Army the secret programs that he was in
The reason that it's fine for him to be talked about
Speaker program
Is that they requested that he starts
To disseminate the information cuz he want they want to get the public ready
Okay so he is like the tip of the spear internal
He's coming over
He's coming out to the crazy
He's right now
Yeah and then they'll be
Steady
Trickle
More of these
He's coming out until we get them
The mainstream
Finally when they're in the Stream
Declassify all of
And we'll all have
Prepared
Technology
No I was oh I bet you would call him
Anybody who's been on Project Camelot
Would probably still have a
So
Hear it
Now
Hebrew
Set the 2
He lived through
The same 2000
I don't know
I'm tired
I feel like a it's very difficult and exhausting to try and wrap your head around like
Of course I mean
His play has been preparing for this
Tire life I've read
Watched
Earth makes it a
Future than the 27th
He experienced original
Influence
So that that makes
He was on
The Moon
Was there
The other him
The other clown
Now
Simultaneous
Is
And this is what I can't find evidence
He ever in the military in real life
Or is all his service
This other time streamware clone came back
15 minutes
How could you
You put him in the
Right
He was he was raised
And he is a
U.s. Marine
Send
The people who trained
Give me back when he was like 13 before you went in the portal
I guess
I don't know
Look him up
Unless they
Didn't look
Typically go out of their way
Atlanta versus real world
Yes in real world
He wouldn't be able to get into the military because
Uggs for kids
Contract set the army with the Army would be able to see
He's a clone of this traveling super soldiers
Is it only in the brain
Or we
What's going on there
Fully genetic
I mean otherwise how would he get
That's true
You have some kind
People believe that everybody
Remote viewing
Okay
Alright that's not necessarily super powers as much as it is like
Spotify
You genetically
Engineer the original
But you build the Clones
From the original
From the pre genetic
Brightright moving his
Is embryo
U-Save part of it
You genetically engineer the other one that
What you need the super-soul
You use this
So then when the super soldier comes back
Kill the Supra
Put his brain into the regular
Who's really dicey though cuz then you've got to make a sort of habit of
Killing super soldier
Receive
No but I mean it would be difficult
There super soldier
Bourne Identity
Stupid let's not expect this to go to H
You had no idea
Okay one more listen to before we
You know I'm also a military officer when I can grab it with my hands and it's very very real to me
With my hand and I can't stab it then it has
Celebrities me so
I presume
Terriers want to help the process
And I provided a lot of information to me that has been honest and truthful and helpful and the other folks as well
So he has a chain of command
What's going on on Mars now
This is
This is very
I don't like that at all
Fly
Because he's already established
Multiple times about the job
Why would you
You assumed they were telling
I don't know
Duchess
You should have a
Much healthier
Considering
To use psionics and you can remote view things
Think about the Brigadier
Yes and here is where he explained
Situation
Hey before you
Into a crazy for
Best Buy Theory
Let's see if you agree with me or him
He goes by the name of Brigadier General Julian smile I can tell you that
Names on your driver's license when he goes home at night and there's a name on his you know drivers
I think when he goes to work every day and they're not necessarily the same thing
But that doesn't mean that that's you know the name on you know his
What's a pseudonym
MCs
Us
United States Marine Corps super soldier
Probably
Because that's part of
Super soldier program
We're right but if that's in Fantasyland
In the real world timeline
If we
He just
Slept through the night of November 18th
And woke up
You know did some drugs
Maybe add some
False memories
If you go to therapy if you don't
Theoretically credible person if you are not careful about it
It's very easy to employ
False memories
Exactly
People
Jail for
Life for crimes
Did not even have
Yep
My theory would be that that is what
He has full memories
He's turned them into a very robust narrative
That is fun
Fantasyland timeline where he was a super soldier
Did not exist
He is found on the internet
Who agree with him
Brett and have their own narrative
Decided to work together and combine
And reinforce each other one of them is a brigadier general
Who has a fake name
Brigadier General Julian
Great faith
The good fake
Briefings in this at all these
Data
Dumps to him
That are just some other guy
Reinforcing his narrative
Informing him of bars
Wonderful
No the other day
That's not it's sort of where my brain
I don't know if you're different
But that's where I'm at
I like
I will say this
I would
ReDiscover
Exactly
When he got
Yeah
That's what I would like
I don't know if I'm aware of that I don't know I'm not going to
Do too much more digging on him
I will I will tell you this
Good
But I can't find evidence that he was actually
In the military
But
I did find
A GoFundMe
Started
On February 3rd
13th of this year
A GoFundMe
Looking for $70,000
Okay bye
That's a new car
Then you might be asking
What the f*** is
Is he trying to do
I'll tell you what he's trying to do
He's trying to create holographic
Regenerating Medical
Wait why do you need the
Let me read you
Overcomplicate
In Randy's heroic efforts to help research and develop Earth's first holographic regenerating
His funds are running low
To continue his awesome Endeavor he needs your help
This $70,000 gold will help bridge the gap
What's
Kramer has these fun
His mission
Sanctioned by the Brigadier General
Is to bring together large investors to employ full-time medical engineers
Computer software engineers
Security Services and other personnel
And a team of
To develop his first prototype
HR
Holographic
Regenerating
Memes that
We as the Earth's population can finally have access to a technology which
Regrow limbs
Perfect
Cure all diseases including cancer
For much longer to have fun
These funds are needed right now
Play head only
Field commander Randy Cramer
The sooner we can reach this goal the sooner we can all get access to these amazing
Elysium style holographic regenerating Med beds
According to Randy Cramer
Holographic technology
Cheaper
Traumatic
It just works better cost less money
Cures everything
Everything
Blindness
Darkness
Lindsay Korman
Organs that are damaged
I love this
Infomercial why is this
The the
The what's it called
Give me a
Restart
Regrowing limbs
It would absolutely every single thing
Even the things that are modern science can't
Not only can you fix everything
We're very excited about that
It's not even
80 contribution that was the largest capitalized
Life-forms
Now and in the future
Especially right now
And those who are dying of so-called incurable diseases
This is the way you can be up people's champion
You can be like a rock
This is the way you can live and be healthy
Super soldier spacepilot modern-day hero
This one
Small action May one day save your life
Family friends or community
We all sincerely thank you for whatever size contribution you make to this historic campaign
The future of medicine is here now knocking at our door
Thank you for your time
Much love and respect
Viva la libertad
Psychically interact with
What The Rock is
Hologram
Why do you knead challah
Also
Edit on that cop
Maybe a little
This is this was started in February
You going to create
Things that will regrow limbs
Cure cancer cure everything in the world
Is the most important
How much money
482nd down
Your family a little bit more there bro
That is good
Soda Springs
End of our exploration
Randy Cramer
Interesting because this holographic
Regenerative
Is very much the sort of stuff that Alex Jones talks about
He talks about the life expect
Technology
That the globalist they don't want us to have
I am
So is kind of
Because I was never specific
Think about the kind of life
Centra Technologies
Person is promoting on the internet
Yeah
We're about it
Can you get mods
Right
So that's one similarity and then
Alex is allowing a guy like Steel
Mr. Steele
Come on is Joanne.
I'm specifically talk about bars Bass
Well you just explained another
Figure in the world of weirdos on the internet
Who
You know issuing knowledge
But
There's been a lot of torture
This almost feels like
Jordan
Which makes me suspect this next episode that we do
It's going to be
Horrific
It's more like you made it through David
Here's that
I mean that was
My primary motivation.
Turn out that way
I'm glad you enjoyed that listeners
If you'd like
What's to do more stuff like this
Send a message
John Facebook
Twitter retinology underscore fight on Twitter
Actress knowledge fight on Facebook
Pikachu doesn't email at knowledge fight at
Gmail.com
You can leave a review of ours
Episodes
If you want to donate to the show you can on knowledge fight, there's a button to sport the show
Do more stuff like this
When you make a donation
Spend that money towards our investigation of
Secret space program
It is
It's kind of tragic
Original gin
Let me get through this
John Rappaport was on the show on Thursday
He was just saying the exact same things you said in the episode that we cover
He's just
He spent like 40 minutes talking about how the DSM 4
Doesn't have any blood
So he's
Just a hologram
The real
It's f****** dead
What's the new sign up
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color