Jordan
I have a great respect for Tenaya Lodge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about Alex
Jordans
Jordan question for you what's up
Episode
600 it up in here
I don't do anything special in rock going to
But because of that promise I have
In front of me a chilled
Ice cold beachplum LaCroix
In front of me as well
I was on a good sound effect of your can opening life
I will I will go first
Isn't that Malachi boy you could have told me
How is it
Pretty good it's pretty good
Yeah don't tell no no no do not be do not be nonplussed
It's not it's not as sharp as I expected it
Yeah you're right
I kind of got thrown off by that deliver
What flavor is pretty nice
Just stays in the front of your tongue I'm not used to it I don't know why
Ply difference
I grew up in Hawaii and so like
Well some of the time me and my parents sooner we would go down to San Souci Beach
Break out those plums
It's just an everyday kind of figured
No I know you you said it home it's like 1 in the afternoon
Saturday you're not sure what to do when you're like I need a snack so you go to the fridge you get a plum you take a bite your like this
But then
You like wait
You drive 25 MI
Do take a bite
Yeah
I don't know what the association with Beach in
Jim Plum is there maybe something I don't know about but that's not bad
No I mean it takes
We had something to eat
Thieves and of course beer
Brightspot Dan
Netflix
Doing a live-action Cowboy Bebop remake okay
Not sure about how much I'm in
Interested in the live-action Cowboy Bebop
Considering it was part
However
Cowboy Rocksteady nice
Cowboy birth of the cool jazz
Yoko kanno
V
Composer for all of Cowboy Bebop in like
So much of anime she's she's one of the most brilliant
Composers
And peanuts she's incredible
And she's back on board
For the new series I can go a long way and they just released the the open
Cowboy Bebop has maybe one of the most
Iconic open
Putting credits
Sequences
Ever
With tank
Yoko kanno greatest achievements
And they ripped they put out the live-action one
It's so amazing
It's amazing it's the same exact
What is the maze
Well this is the sounds like it may it may live up to whatever your hypest music
Will for sure
Yeah the show might suck but her music is
Incredibles music
Stuff does like it does end up adding so much like David Wise being back for the
Donkey Kong tropical
Do the
Yeah yeah like another character in that
It's like she's she's on the level of like nobuo uematsu with the Final Fantasy
Soundtracks like he's
Legendary
Composer level look like
Okay you're the you're the
Kman
Kind of level well I hope I hope I hope you enjoy it
Super 8
We were going to do something
Different but we're not we're just a 22nd 2021.
I saw that coming a mile away this time
Yeah
Surah talk about that those Wednesday
Pretty pretty on
Pretty irresistible headline for his live show and we'll get into that
Let's say hello.
The new walks
CT utepers on Clark Street
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Alexandria elderly pepper
I'm a policy wonk
Actually a sentient rainbow trout
Hello to so what is up out there did Dan ever
Ever make that lasagna Jordan have a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
What's the business
Heroin
Look here's the deal
Sentence with look
We've already discussed this a million times look implies look
,
Look at your video are both ways of me saying I did not make that much
I have the pan
Sure I got the single serving lasagna pan
I bought the ingredients of multiple times
It's tough to make a lasagna for one it's embarrassing a little bit by yourself
Might be more embarrassing than not making lasagna
I would feel accomplished
By doing it perhaps
But yeah
If it struck me as a little bit sad
I don't know if that's why I didn't do it could just be lazy
No that's entirely
But yeah
One of these days
Episode 600
By episode 700
God is my witness
Everyone knows do the 600's not really that special of a number we were looking forward to
Leviathan the whole time
We will reveal our true
Episode 666
Taking place
Perhaps
I hope so
We start Today Show
And this is big
This is real.
I mean right out of the gate
You know it
This is not f****** around
Today
This is like
The world is standing still
Mark your calendars as the day the world Stood Still
Broke yesterday afternoon
Took care of a lot of technical
Business and things around here and infrastructure keep this operation afloat
So I did not know about it until we couldn't sleep all night
Approximately 5 hours of research on this
Tell you unequivocally
This story is
10 times bigger than anything else you ever reported
10 times bigger
Quantifiably
Ten times bigger than anything else Alex has ever reported
You know
I think my favorite part of this show
My position
I love remembering that this is in the past
Yes
The Day the Earth Stood Salem like
So this was last
Next week cuz I do not remember The Day the Earth Stood Still at all
Yeah I was a little bit confused
I was jogging my memory as
Wednesday
Covid-19
I won't spit still very much
Still Irene I didn't go out much
This is not
10 times bigger than any news that Alex has ever broken in his life
Okay
Bigger than
Other Monumental pieces of History
Dropping atomic bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki
I remember those Cold War
Remember that one
This is better than World War
Oh that was easy to remember
The first one
In modern world history
And you can argue they succeed
It is the biggest thing
In history
Nice save
Nice
Oh man what if it go back to
Jesus that he didn't add that in the end I was so impressed by that
Immediately when I was listening to
What about Jesus
Look
If there's anyone who would be impressed by that safe
Jesus
Oh yeah let me do the same
You're probably curious with this news is
Well Alex doesn't wait too long
Can I get to the bombshells
I saw this yesterday
I was going to bed early I was
I'd only got 5 hours
Go to bed at 1 in the morning
6 in the morning
Rilke he went to DC to go beyond
Tim kulas podcast
What a great guy
I was energized Electric
Police documents
Release documents
Approach them
3 years ago
You want to release a chimera
Coronavirus described is covid-19
Freon
Vagina
Honestly
If that were true
That would make the Earth standstill right like there's no way other than to say that that
Is definitely a bio-weapon
That's true I mean
Sure
I don't think it's true that the world would stand still
Astro I think that would make a real standstill more than this probably here's the situation
Reporting
DARPA didn't release any document
An alleged document was released by an internet-based investigative group called brass
Which stands for decentralized autonomous search team investigating covid-19
Rename document his only been
Confirmed by an anonymous former Trump
Official
Still
Kind of
Like a little bit of cash
Confusion surrounding it
Jurassic is claimed that they got the documents from an anonymous source so it's really difficult for me to assess
All Robins but even assuming we can just assume that it's real
And what it is is it the grant proposal that said to have been made by Peter.
Through the ecohealth alliance
A project called
Project diffuse
This isn't interesting stuff and it falls into pretty much similar territory as the last documents that we discussed
But it's not a smoker
Gone in the way that Alex is reporting it
If you wanted to get a little bit out there with it you could use this to argue that the lab leak hypothesis is slightly more
More likely than it would appear to be before
Sure but what Alex is doing this misreporting
Also this is electrogram proposal that was rejected
So unless there's some kind of evidence that it was accepted by someone other than DARPA
I don't know what this illustrates
Doesn't show anything
So that means that Alex is in a type of movie you know the one where the person goes and they've got this
Proposal never do that
And then some random rich guy just walks up and he's like
You've got just the ideas we've been looking
Bright
I even looked at the article write-up on
Infowars and it is like they just quoted somebody as being like
Well let's see prove that I don't I don't know if you could just speculate these things
I think with wild about
Is somehow
These these types of things
Keep coming out and they're being used
Is to smear the people who is
It seems like
If you look at these things
Saw the world as it was like 3 years ago and we're like
You know China's regions were there a lot of baths cause a lot of viruses maybe we should keep an eye on that like
It could not be more like these people were like hey we've correctly identified a problem and then we saw what happens when we
We don't listen to them
Absolute
Repo we should be list
There are various
Parts of the world
China is such a
Huge country
That it also
It has
Has a lot of those places where there are
Russia's the same tooth they were there animal population
That aren't used to enter
Interacting with humans
As time the climate is changing
Patterns
Is of interaction
Archangel
And monitoring
What we should be worried about from those novel interactions is definitely something that is good the people are
Research
I'm not exactly sure
You know what to what
To draw from this but I don't
I think this is
Nearly
As evil as I wasn't suggesting a lot of details
She's coming up with arches
Why
I'm confused as to why they called it covid-19 in there for
Proposed in 2018 for them to do
Sketchy
To even darker like
And I like their evil right
But they thought this way
Was too evil
They brought grants to DARPA saying we want to create nanotech
That delivers viruses
Go through human skin
So we can spray it on people
Barbara said this will endanger the humans of Earth
We will not do this
Do you
This will endanger the humans over
According to Alex like DARPA has been on this like they did harp their create 5G to everybody
How do you put a no
Decent
I have a little dick
Yeah
I don't
I know how Alex keeps his villain straight and I'm like
They're out of line the villain
Everybody
He's everybody's not sure of what they're
Jobs are
The thing that got that gets me is like if you sent all of his villains down and just like
Clearly delineated response
Disabilities
SA
The devil
You could
Rush it right
You got a lot of All-Stars working for it I would
Guess that since DARPA has been on these plans
Do you know
Call the population and what have you heard all this
I have to be working with a double right
So why is this to you over that way
Sono dangers the humans of Earth
Concerned with could have not showed up so this seems weird that they would say
I know this seems like a huge situation weather like
Maybe we could do the
That looks so fun
So Alex is a nano virus
Right
Nanotech in a virus
Is there something
Do you know who else is
Talking about that
General Flynn actually he hasn't actually said that publicly but like Alex's heard secondhand from
Publicly
And I agree with his horses
He said a month ago this is a synthetic
Coronavirus
I want him out there he told him
Because
Synthetic Nano virus
Hollywood
Okay
Wait how to splint
I don't know
Was he at
Maybe this is change
Not what it was before
No
Is a completely different
Story
So I just like the idea of Alex being like you know who else is saying this plant well not publicly but somebody I know
Sure
Somebody I know right
Said that he told
Medical doctor
Very excited
It's rare that some of our media worlds
Intersect
But
Before this episode
On the majority Report with Sam Cedar
They have done a segment
About Sam Harris
Paris had a podcast
That's where he was asked
Whether or not he would talk to
Bret Weinstein about covid and Ivermectin and all this and he said
No
And he gave an explanation for it part of the explanation was
I also wouldn't I wouldn't do an interview with him
In the same way I wouldn't do an interview with a 9-11 truther like Alex Jones
So Alex Jones's name is in the title of that video
Responding
Iran
YouTube
Eclipse lighter
The fake news about resigning at the a scientist
You heard the news about them voting against the booster shot
It's just not true it's fake
And we're not going to debate those fake scientist The Joe Rogan interview
Of course they did resign that you had scientists
Okay
They sit there
How many people are being force-fed the feeds
Sam Harris
Precious Bret Weinstein with Alex Jones
Comparison
The majority report
And they just go
It's not true nobody resigned it's all lies of Alex Jones
It's weird that you say your fake news and then use your name and all Alex Jones says they was on
So it's the
That's not at all
What happened
The waters on that was sad to see the intellectual dark web
Breaking up like this
They were there was there was such a
Good friends when they were also there these dangerous ideas that
They were on the edge
Way too dangerous
So yeah like I said
Explaining
Podcast
That's a cheater and Emma vigeland are
Discussing
Oh how he's not going
To talk to
Bret Weinstein now that he has a book out
He's going to go in this book to her he's not going to interview him about this
Of the irresponsibility of engaging with
Some of these ideas
So I would explain further wet to Alex's
Representing about this a clip but I'm just going to play a little clip from
From that will be able to see very
Clearly
The reason why they're stuck in a cemetery here is that it is just impossible
To debunk
Most things in real time
And
Even if
The point being made is in fact spurious
It won't seem spurious to 99% of
An audience
Sprite soda
Person on me
Conspiracy theory side of things
Convey
What about the 14 CDC officials who resigned
Last week
And wouldn't give reasons
When asked
What do you make of that
Right now
There's probably nothing to be made of that
Right I didn't even hear about it
I just made that up
But
When delivered in the contacts
Activate quote debate
About these things
It was someone who
Whose whole angle is
There's conspiracy
Everywhere
It can seem like although you didn't know about that well
That's cool a problem you should look into that
What about the paper that just came out of Micronesia
It showed
Ivermectin
With 100% of fact
I didn't see that paper
Out of Micronesia
Oh you didn't walk a to Z's really do your homework
So these are examples that he's using out of whole cloth of things that people might throw at you
Because we are part of the collective Saint Marys
Who's talking about
It's so much easier
To just make a mess
Clean it up
And you have a disadvantage
If you're somebody who's
Trying to clean up a mess
As opposed to Dee person who's throwing things around
He's not saying
But nobody resigned
Anything like that was a story that did happen
Right but he's making up
And you can't fact check that on the on the Fly absolutely reason why
Kind of counterproductive
22in Gables
I'm not a huge Sam Harris fan but I do think
Add nauseam
Yeah yeah it's why I would never really
Want to talk to any of these
But look
I know that
When we were going back in
Gametime
Maybe in 2009
Was imploring his audience
Can't stop trap
Absolutely
Run out into traffic scream into the car next
Do you
I believe you also then went on a rant about
What kind of cars he likes
Exitos like some
American Muscle
Creams similar territory now
Alright I'm asking Emory Westerner watching this live on September 22nd on this Wednesday run
Central Time
The call your friends your family your neighbors to take the live feed
Put back on screen please
Destroy
Biggest story of the 21st Century
I've never put five exclamation points up for a live show feedback I don't think
So two months ago Alex use Forex
! alive feed headline
Warp speed warped America!!
Time is now
Has he used 5
Maybe not I don't know I will admit that I stopped my research
You can't fact check everything
Oh god I've never used five! That's how much I mean this
I'm going to tell you this right now
2X
Exclamation points
Is the maximum you can use
Anything beyond that and you're just making
King of fools a
What there was a Greek quote I can only use two exclamation points in the entire
I already over their career
Probably fine advice terrible
We know that Alex Loves movies
Fix their real
They are
It's about Terrebonne
James Bond women
Depopulate
China
United States just like every other James Bond movies dates
Which is based on real things that happen during the Cold War
Former OSS agent
Plumbing
And what is what is
They're always right
Dabke Austin depopulate
What's really going on
They tell you what's that
This is this is just what they do they tell you in the Bond movies
I mean
How do you argue with somebody who
Who's like nada
What's what your what
What you're missing
Okay
Is that
The Bond movies are what you
You should be research
Moonraker
The Man with the Golden Gun on Her Majesty's Secret Service you should
Sea From Russia with Love
I'm out
Octopussy
I know that I'm not a
Aban scholarship
I don't know I don't know what your relationship
GIF is with Bond franchise
But how many books and do you think it was before Spectre was introduced
I want to say like
14 was 9 ball
It's a long jump to get there
Also we talked a little bit about Ian Fleming
Before the password I want to rehash
She too much but
Ian Fleming is revealing everything that's real through the three Bond movies
Does that mean chitty-chitty-bang-bang is real 100%
Okay absolutely
Reverse address
That's alarming
So
We also have some other news.
It's not based on
Movies not based on
The world of creative fiction
Alex seems to be maybe
Making a slight pivot towards
Supporting China
Okay
But down for this because it is outrageous new rallying cry
Find
I'm not defending gg.com put their children
We're running the American agenda to destroy the family
The u.s. is run by poison leader quotes
We're against your new world order so they've broken with them
And we're breaking with them
Motorcycles
Because you know he was supposed to defeat
Buble
That was weird
So I guess China who is
Is the greatest
Partner of the New World Order and the devil
He's now breaking with the New World Order and Alex's
List of congratulatory things are we're having children we're arresting of a sex
Why was that Angie's List
I mean well I think if you wants to be very obvious reason
I'm not saying I want to arrest Havasu
Sexual what I'm saying is I want
The government
To walk into everyone's homes
Double-checked
To make sure they're not homosexual and if
SO2 arrest
Those who are
I got to say he's been making slips like that a lot more regularly
Is Nazi a straight-up bananas
I mean they just all lost their minds they just have no f******
Complete untethered nonsense
From any direction
China
Today I lost the New World Order
The devil built the Great Wall
Just nothing just doesn't matter
Mulatto coverage is the Gabby Petit
Keto stories yes yeah I have personally not engaged too much with this because I do
Don't know what it is a missing person and a possible
Murder
I don't know I don't really know entirely enough
Is
I don't know
Nothing
It's sad someone.
And it feels like
True Crime fans
Can't get enough of a white woman not being around any
It's strange and assumed name pop-up of it but it's not it's not
Flipping out
Do too much
You would expect
That based on Alex's
Entire career and everything about him
DB super into the story
Because of the way he's covered all sorts of
Total weight
Victims of
Nothing
Slugs
He goes the other direction entirely
Cheeto
Young white woman
The missing husband the mystery
They're spending about half the news time on fox singing in MSNBC
Not with the imploding border and tens of thousands more Haitian showing up
By not knowing what planet he's on
The clap
Avakin
Fauci told the Pentagon and Arbor they were developing
Enteroviruses or synthetic
To purposely released covid-19
In the wild
Sure
Operation lockstep of the UN
No no no no
Fortune occupation
Globalist agenda here
Whole human world
Fascism
Using communism in race war for control that's not important
Don't you care about Gabby potato
What about the tens of thousands of children
See this is a story that is
About a young white woman
Girl missing
The media is covering it incest
That's why Alex can do this game
Now if this was a story that
Wasn't getting any track
Action he would say that the media is covering it up because she's white and you can't
You can't human eyes white
Victims of things
Systems against
White people
You can have your cake and eat it too you can take whatever angle you want on the story that makes you appositional
And somehow above the
Afraid but it's just
No
And it's
It's whining it's whining at look
Who Among Us has not stopped
And looked up at
The sky and thought
I wish someone loved me the way America
Culture loves it when a white woman goes away
Who am I
I get it
But if you go on your Sony like why are people paying attention to my stories my stories
R5!
It's like okay you're a
Looks now confirmed
Sprayed with Nano viruses
If you want to stop if you want to see Jessica
They're going to continue
Kitchen
Jobs
Kenosha
Protein in your body
Sure
There
Having us produce when they injected
How to say if this is all confirmed
It's an amazing amount of restraint
But Alex is showing
Believes a word of this
Bring It On
Breeze
I mean are we adding this into Chemtrails are we going with like
I exist in the rain you know those Glade plugins
That like
God dammit
You have a room by poke at night with needles
But we all do we hire the Roomba
Speak
I just think
The only thing you could possibly be advocating for if you believe this
Stop
He believed this narrative is
We need
Jurassic Revolution total total war
Yes the people who are behind this
The violence must be used against them they're Super Bowl
I mean it doesn't get more movie villain Justified Violence then
They're spraying
Play God you
Even like
Even though the
Cillian Murphy Academy water supply
Scare people
This is worse
Yes
I'm not calling for violence I don't want violence but you're going to get a John Brown moment with these levels to did all this and I don't want
Name out of your mouth
Football you get the horns those that live by the sword die by the sword
About
Myprotein
Plexiglass cage in Times Square
The federal government will administer a couple million of his own
Super virus is over a thousand times stronger than created for us
And then he can he can die miserable Delta suffocating
How about that
Imagine passing that law
Imagine how shity that would be
Debate session
We're going to hold 72 hours to debate
Yes yes we're going to take
How about we don't kill everybody is that cool
Nonono how about we now legalize
A very limited
Scale
Public School
Torture effects
Execution
Of a duck
Yeah yeah yeah
I think that debate would be
Brought
I can't imagine Ron Paul being on board with that
States map meme I'm going to have
To go with he would love that s***
Beyond the state level this could be a federal law
Torturing people to death
Obviously
F****** comic book
Anyway Alex
Advance recalled North
He actually believes
That his yelling on the radio is responsible for this grant proposal
Being released
I'm about to go to everybody I said
If you don't release this
And you're part of it
You really believe in a breakaway group
Curiosity population plan
I said I want to see the documents
If you got on them on plan
Authorized to do it if he's a pentagon wasn't behind this
Cuz that's where all the news with moving
Yeah man
He just gets on air start to talkingshit and then people leak
Document know and I hears what it hears what he doesn't know that what's that is that I was one step ahead of a
The Pentagon in advance
And I told them
That if they don't really speak
Documents
To make Alex look like a s*** head and I will release
Real documents
That reveal that they haven't revealed
The real documents yet
It all makes sense
Everybody's
Goodnight. Covid
No weapon
This is conspiracy at this point is
Is just
You just got it
Got a Buckle in
Pretend it all makes a Miss whenever it was just George Bush 9/11 Inside Job
That was simple
Damn you did it
Yeah we got it man
Sure
Now it's got to be the devil
Sure they have a cure
And only some people are going to
This cure Perry few very few
I would call this kind of like it's not an incitement to violence definitely
But at
Enabling of it
They're only giving a very small group of people
Believe me
Because backseat phone
Might have colored again all this
You continue on.
I'm going to call my mom
Well if you have the total proof
A rest
Doesn't happen
Because it's not going to because you don't have the
The total proof
Then I guess the only answer is you have a responsibility to stop these people right
Motor that's not responsible message
To be putting out
Do
Whatever audio
Okay
Here's my pet
Here's my pitch
Dog we need to get
One of these Alex Jones hose okay
How much does Tucker Carlson
Can we buy him for like a million
I feel like he's cheaper than you might expect
I feel like he's like 100k and he'll say whatever you want
Like I feel like
But
I think I think you would respond more to
Same
Assertive trying to get a little bit of attention by proxy
Alright
But what we do is
We have him
Go on one of his shows and say
You know hold up a fake b*******.
And save now the vaccine is the cure that the elites already
You had
Right
And then the mainstream media is going to look into it they're like no it's
The same exact thing
But because the mainstream media debunk
The fake bulshit
That's going to make the
Conservative Luna
It's even more the actual cure
So we'll finally have everybody vaccinated
Yeah
I looked in a story I like what your
What you're bringing to me but in the real world
It still is like
Really being manipulative about people's informed consent
I don't disagree
I'm glad
Definitely based on what you're saying I'm glad that it's not our responsibility to
Problem because I think that
That idea
Probably backfire at some point solutions to things everybody always wants to be like oh let's do the smart thing
Let's do the weird clever thing that always
Okay
Alex's decided
But everyone's
Shark world world
Naturalistic globalist
Swim but keep going
I mean once we were given life we were in
That is true
There are about 1,000 people who will survive
They have a robot
Mycroft
One shot to stop them
They're probably going to release the bio-weapon anyways
I'm not going to sit here
Worried
We're dead already
I'm dead already but we stopped this
Start easy Star Trek Wrath of Khan analogy
Because he's dead already
I'm dead already
Your dad your you and your family are dead
You and your family are dead you're dead unless you stop
Letting them kill everybody
I care about my children lot more myself about
That's more than them
I'm all in baby
100%
That's what I'm supposed to be
This is not done out of glass
Is it adult to go into that reactor
And maybe we live
Call icing on the cake
But it doesn't matter
We got to get in there and turn this around or everybody's gone
Leave you alone
Sure maybe 1,000 people are getting a ticket out of this
Weatherall building big bunker
Already moved in private island with 50 ft walls I don't even trust their security
I can assure you it's raining here
Security compound
That's why they're going into robot guns and everything
That's why they're going into robot John's
Why does every time he tells me about the
The future it feels like a
Pitch meeting
Okay
And then and then what's your resolution
Erick Khan
It does seem like he's
Again it's just a heating moving
Trying to run on the surface of the water and then what
Like a peach thing
I totally totally you're hungover your
Pitching and you don't have
Yeah probably like not totally unfair
Hearing a reading of that is
Encouragement towards suicide bomber
No I mean it doesn't get much more
That's weird there's icing it's the icing on the cake you have to take them out
Every every every time they go back in like the Legos fighting for so they were the most fearsome but it was
Because they had the same thought of
They're already dead so they just
Through their f****** yeah yeah
And I was thinking that and then I made it even the more
Explicit
Rockhurst
Robots
Remote control robots Ki gun ports
Tear gas systems everything else but that's not
Stop people on a suicide mission
Sparkles
It's on
You know the world folks this is it
Unless we stop them
End of the world
How much we stopping
It's the end of the world
Encouraging
Robot guard sure that's fine but what about people on a suicide mission
This is this is so f***** up
Yeah and it's such a good I wonder I wonder I really do wonder if Joe Rogan would like to help enlist this suicide
Dive bomber army that Alex's
You trying to inspire
I mean he's got the numbers for it do you get the numbers high enough sooner or later I'm going to find a
Sidebar in their rights
Brogan thinks his cool Ivan Joe Rogan
Explicitly sign off
On suicide bombing
Wow as well as arresting
Slough meaning
Certainly
Tacitly supported
The person who is
Absolutely
The problem is he doesn't know you know
I mean the thing about his
Description that way such that
Perfect
Distillation of what
Elite Panic is
That like
Cuz
If you go through every major disaster
Everybody
Bands together
They're like to work together to get through this situation
It's only the elites do the rich
People is only that were always like
Well obviously it's going to be cannibalism in 10 days so I need to grab all of my s*** and get away from these
Monsters
Surrounding me
Plays out over and over and over again and it's not
It's not a mentality that actually people really
Succumb to a very small percentage of people
Yeah yeah but he's almost universally like listen the only way we're going to get through this is if we work together
Ditto
Can't
Like
Regular people for the most part can't see someone hurting and not want
Especially in an emergency
Or a disaster
I don't know
I don't have nearly as dark view of humanity is Alex seems to
And yet he seems to
Pretend that you love Humanity to a mug
Anyways the end of the world
Give me the world folks this is it
Unless we stop
Animal world
The design control collapse of planet Earth
Why
That's dumb
There's a meteor heading for earth that will destroy it and other news these prices go down
What
The demise of all of us has Eminence please do not hug your children
There are some ads for tied to come and go
The switch has been flipped to destroy life on Earth
The humans of Earth are screwed
Current news coming up other news
Is York
Thinking about you it's
It's weird
It's weird to do that
It makes me think you don't need it
I think if there's more news after the end of He-Man
You might not believe in the end of you
It's going down
The buffet
Is
Good
So I'll explain this is really this is
This really fascinated me because it's
It's just such a good clear-cut example
Alex setting up a clip
It not saying what he says it says
And then him barreling forward as if it's
Let's go in here fauci talking about his primary target
Is the young people
Viruses that cause blood clots for life
Infecting a baby or a teenager or a five-year-old
We'll just killing whole person I want to keep from getting your pension fund
Sure is the children
Here is the mass murder and criminal that launched HIV covered up the cures for it
Treatment
Here is the sickle what it mean
Grim Reaper garden gnome
Himself sing primary target your children here it is
Can you keep hearing from officials and administration yourself another said that you're confident
Stanford
Can you say with some level of confidence that you think there will be
Available
Halloween
Is that what it is
I think that the really good chance it will be before Halloween
You're pretty confident
Pretty confident I I believe it's a reasonably good chance that it will do
Primary target for children
What
Did you get that
I didn't
Is there someone asking him if these shots
Sir potentially going to be ready by Halloween
And I'm saying
Probably put
It depends on what you mean by relatively certain
Primary target is the children
Like that what you got
I told Alex got from that yet
He made it up
Oh that would make
It was more fun for him to report then Patxi's headshots may be ready by Paula.
Also if traffic is listening to this that is how I want to be brought up on stage from now on
Who created the releaser of HIV
Who's Joseph Mengele of our times
I bet that devil that ladies and gentlemen
Jordan Holmes
I love you can also see him at colleges
He's a regular
So you know
Be the moment where Alex is like this is the end of the world and will get back with other news
That's
Silly
This is all so silly and pretty much the same way
And we all stand up now if we supposed to store going to back off
Order to release the new bio-weapon but at least we won't know what hit him
So
If we stand up now they'll back down or they'll kill everyone
One of the
And then we'll really sad and then we'll really get
90% global.
Depopulation but after that I'm coming for you
Absolutely
Bizarre
So
And
He is a guy who started my free.
After I think is the name of it we can
Telemedicine
Who's basically
Believe away 2
To give people Ivermectin
Prescription
Sure sure
Okay and he's on and he believed
If the property is literally responsible for every covid death
That sounds right
Population
Truskin penetrating nanoparticles
Close quote I mean this is
Everything we
Confirm
The Pentagon Declassified with
He was approached by fauci a dancing for Bill Gates
I call him doctor death
We paid for it to be created and as you just
Have released the information today
They
Released it on purpose
Yeah I don't I don't know I don't know how much I dig this doc
Even if it
Use me for it
Yeah doctor death fauci
That's also
Not very clever
Weird clever solution
He also has something
But maybe there's a little more clever move his little more up your alley
He refuses to call it a vaccine
He calls it a lethal injection
I'm done so incessantly
About what you've seen in the last 20 months since this all started or 21 months
Where you thinking
You witnessed
I would say this
We've seen lots of
Death and misery and bad side effects
From the lethal injection
The big picture problem is there in population gold
Nice
They're entitled
On the planet right now so that means
Directions that means
So this is kind of why I think this information is coming out now they're almost
Almost complete
They're getting ready
He believes that it's a lethal injection that everybody
The next clip I'm just
I got to spoil you think that everyone who's got the vaccines going to be dead in a few years
Depopulation
Sumdog
Look here's my question
Haha
Is it a Pawn on
The gates of the cemetery I think so
Cuz I think Bill Cemetery
Yeah but
Big Bill Gates of Hell is probably
That would be waived
I think it might be
It's a little clearer could cemeteries that you know you don't really think of
Gates
Let me tell you some
If we're going to start punching up one of
This guy's pigs
It's going to be a long night
I gave up on the voucher one I don't even I don't even think that's worth saving
Or does he say death.
I don't know
I think it's false
Death.
Get to Folsom
Faucet is right there
So you turn on the faucet outcomes death
Yeah
No man that's better but it
It still sucks
But it is right there
It is
Problem is is 5 billion.
Dolese injections tomorrow
Luke
Montagne he's a Nobel Prize winner he believes that everybody who's had the lethal injection will be dead in two to three years
I agree with that position from
The many thousands of Articles I've read on the subject in the past year-and-a-half
I agree that these are Lethal Injections if your design the lethal injection
Hours days weeks months or years that be too obvious
Very well said
You're not a doctor if you just feel like they can design a thing to kill you whenever they wanted
Concerned
Months from now they got a vaccine for that scene for it
Three months
They haven't figured that one out yet one year absolutely concerned about somebody who's a doctor
Sort of like this this relation
The complexity of humor
I just put it in there
I would encourage this guy to look into some of the stories of
Execution
By lethal injection
Hundred percent of the time by the book by the book kill people at exactly
The time you want the
Yeah
He's calling this lethal injection
He kind of f**** up your so-called vaccines
Are the Lidl in Philly to injection
The things people need to be aware of
Especially
Everybody should treat people who've been
You've had the lethal injection as if they have Act
Especially head cases of
Pregnant women
Pregnant woman that was around somebody who Justin recently vaccinated lost her baby
Don't think I might be a coincidence
I'm a doctor
And if there's one thing that medical school has taught me
There are no coincidences that he's passing off as somehow proving
Vaccinated are dangerous
Proved it
Someone
Got a vaccine nearby
And then sprayed in all directions
Like an anime shooting lasers all over the place and then that woman's baby
Well can't argue with that
That sounds right
I think he's saying.
Yeah I think so too
When is the only reason that I think that is cuz
He gets into talking about how he believes
Like all of the science
What's going on with covid inside
That's false escience
School
This guy
Is not TV ready
There's one study that give them results that'll make them mine that's the study they published but they bury the nine studies dead
That won't make them money
Promoting false doctors
Yeah we got
They have in the hospitals
Where they're often the patient
Jesus
That absolutely If he if he's actually a doctor that should
You should go to any medical board anywhere play that and be like
Obviously this guy can't be a doctor right and they be like total discipline a reaction
Yeah
Alex tries to do the like while you work at the hospital so you know Hospital
All that I am working out been essentially told me I should get it
But he's just doing live streams
Prescribing the Micromax
Great is his
Is clinical approaches
This point wow
Yeah also I would say that if the
Hallmark of the faulty science is taking the one Cherry Picked
Study that you like and ignoring all the others
Looking with Alex.
Snow
Holyshit frequently will just keep using
Even after it's been
Retracted sure but that's the only retracted because they don't want you to know
That's true
Faulty
Sunnyway
What is terrible
I like your
I'd like to apologize in advance
Do the nurses and doctors of America
Who may be listening
For what
This guy's about to say
They have all your videos
Think about it is so many healthcare workers doctors that are
Speak up because they might lose her job but we're just following orders well that's what the Nazi Soldier said
Holyshit
And that's just disrespect
Wow
I guess you
I mean
Man
You if he breaks his leg
Just got to you got to suck it up
If you break your legs you have one leg from now on
No one's helping you out there to make a splint
You better go into the woods
Bark down
Foxbody actually I just read this new study produced by dr. Bret
That's shows
That you know they're putting a
Cast on a broken leg
Work sometimes
Will work more
Is ivory
And
I mean I don't know what
To say but
This is
Is becoming a pattern
Crossmember mactan with me
Very safe
Denali
And you so I'm going to go ahead and take them right now
Yeah but he takes his Ivermectin on air
Which
Just now at least the second time this has happened on out today probably more
Have you consider like I bet I bet Daddy's made Harrison
Takes a it doesn't
Where's a good say no
Swear to God we live in such a dumb
Timeline
That three or four years from now we're going to find out that
You take too much Ivermectin in a short. Of time you're going to die
I meant all of these people are going to be like I am going to kill you three or four years
And then they're dead
And I don't even get to say I told you so
I don't I don't know about any predictions like that cuz it is highly possible that there will be limited effect
But anybody actually sees but
You don't know that he's just stupid we live in a dump time
I'm not saying it's going to happen
Predicting it I'm just saying that
Everything that's happened up to this point believe that dumbness is everywhere
I am a nice somebody who's in this line of work I agree
Jordan I would say that some of this sucks
This is a stupid episode where Alex has 5X
! bombshell stories that are black
CB2
Inside people toward suicide bombings
A bit out there
Now it's time for some good clean fun
That's what this wave will provide
You are gracious enough to stay in Austin and we really appreciate you and I do you
Baker Hotel see you tonight
Favorite places in Florida
I have not been there
Network where's that at
Feel like you are
Love it
Do you realize
Earlier on in the show you said
That everyone was dead already dead
That guy just said that in three years
Five Below
5 billion people will be dead
Haha and you are going to tell me that it's fine.
Love that are in Florida
DeLeon was a true search for
Of course this is a tourist attraction in Florida
Remember Luella day McConnell
Did not believe that it's actual sound of you get the f*** out of here
Stop it don't sound like you thought it would be
To open to the early 1900s
She made up a bunch of stories about it in order to attract customers that I guess Alex has fallen
2 Louella was a doctor in Chicago before heading out having succumbed to what
Described as Gold Rush fever
You going to strike it rich but you failed to do so and then ended up settling in St Augustine Florida where she quote
Became convinced that a well outside your front door for Malia spring was the Fountain of Youth
He started promoting the well when charging people in nickel to drink out of it
Hazard profile grew she started making all kinds of outrageous claims like
She was a descend
Napoleon had his pocket watch to our hand that when Jesus returned it would be at
Fountain of Youth
Is this dude related
Alex
She died in 1927 when she drove into a ditch
Continue to operate by pretending that it wasn't just a well that someone made a bunch of bulshit stories up about
Alex is really smart
It really he's really good at sussing out details of pigs
You know it does
Seem like there's
Like there's a suite that there's that moment
Where your b******* just goes into Legend and then it becomes true somehow
Didn't like what this story like
She just stuck it out for just long enough
That people were just like yeah it's probably
Play true now that she died and someone else like took over
Kind of like now you don't have to answer any question
It is like she did all our did was trying to find
It's just amazing I cannot believe the
Little things that you find of Alex's like
The things that
The Lord that is real to him is
It's fascinating.
Any couldn't pronounce
And forgot pump
This is like somebody thinking that the world's largest Walnut
Is actually the world's largest ball not the world's largest ceramic
The largest nut
Also
That giant ball of yarn
100% yarn
It's just
Trying to get you to pull over
It is the world
Look if you drive by the world's largest Walnut without stopping its via Gates you've missed
The worlds large
I did stop at the world's largest Walnut
Second
If you didn't want to miss it
It's only it's only one if you know what it is a game is that could be a really fun thing to do
Do you want a long-term
But
Alex believe in
That's not good
It is nice that he clarified that far
Silence starts the next segment with a ad
You go straight from this ad
Into talking with the good doctor
About how
Satan B BMX
Satan's in the mix
It is back in stock
They also have
Vitamin B12
Infowarsstore.com
30% off those sales
And
On Monday
It is a human what you're saying he looks like
Under a microscope
And I know this is all very occultic a bunch of them
60 60 60
Oh boy
I didn't I didn't expect that this was the direction we were going
Well I guess I should have
Yeah well your your weight looks good
Your blood pressure is looking
Great
Unfortunately I did look at your DNA
Oh no
Let me show you this is your 20 30 know the one that's the one that says 666 on it
It's not the market
The doctors
So I'm not saying
Renee Lethal Injections a firmly Mark your DNA forever
That your god-given DNA is altered
And they're saying you haven't happened to leave your house or buy or sell it is the mark of the beast
And where are the churches on this
Well that's the scary thing about it most of the churches are all like Covino do your pardon
I'm going to need a second opinion and hold on
I can't believe how normalized it is for us
To be listening to someone who present themselves are the doctor talking
Sing about the devil
No I mean I don't trust totally unacceptable
I I do love how in
Consistent all of these people are though
Unlike
I mean I know it's Satan
He's playing because that's what I would
You know like
If I were coming up with what was thinking of it never occurs to them
That maybe
Baby
Satan's operating on a higher level.
Yeah I think that all these people are bad devils
They're really shity at it and they assumed
Subway
Involves another thing that's one of my favorite Hallmark
Of these weirdos
And that is the every single thing
Goes wrong
Possibly isn't Elizabeth political attack
Of course
For the past six months we've been working with a developer pay to many thousands of dollars at 2
To develop our own server zandona happen
He was supposed to deliver that on August 1st and he backed it up to September 15th and then lo and behold a few days
And
Just took our money and said he's not going to left us we learned
All your money
That's why we
Christian Developers
Yeah
You hired a bad developer for your website and Secret
Does Scott that's what the left
Can't it
It's just it's just a child who never grew up
Figure who never figured out the boogeyman was
How could you be having that conversation and not laugh at Alex
Like it's it's
Silly
It's just like the left to not develop your servers
I hate the lyrics
Squarespace
This doctor he's putting
Some of his energies into
Productive
I can't even take this
I thought of a hypothetical cure that we need to develop which is basically tell me about it
MRNA to alter your
Not how I want to hear that
Before they got to lethal injection we could theoretically
Come up with an mRNA
Product
Restore your god-given Jeanette Cota
The previous injection does that make sense
Exactly use the very same technology to try to reverse
Okay
Oh my God it's almost like some sort of plot
That someone would develop on f******
Star Trek
For some people this might require a time machine
Because you need a tissue sample from before
Don't worry about it no holes in this plan Satan needs my advice no holes
That's what I would do here's what I would do develop a hypothetical vaccine
And what this vaccine would do
Is exactly what I would want it to
And I will give you a nebulous way it might
Yes
Sound like magic
I think that this is a silly conversation
Like in the real world because he believes that the actual mRNA is bad
Like he thinks
They actually using that
Technology
Run somehow
Toxic or dangerous to people
Using it in the way that this guy is describing it should be
Something he is completely again
Because they are just using momentum to keep going and keep
Pitching their ideas
Yep sounds like a great idea.
Alex has the doctor holdover in
Into the 4th hour
But
You know that first little bit of the fourth hour
Doesn't go out on the radio
Gas stations that play their own little thing
Keys has what they're going to do during that
That was extremely powerful info substation don't care the first 5s for a comeback
Eye doctor
You know
Medical doctor says Nicki Minaj's cousin
Nicki Minaj
Tomorrow
Workshopping ideas for a clickbait titles for whatever
So during the five minutes I'm going
Go to try and get this doctor to say that Nicki Minaj's cousin
Balls are huge he was more than willing to say that he was game
They can inject you so your balls grow a little bit
So they grow a lot of bit
Is anything that I'm afraid of
I would like a second opinion
So Alex
4/4 hour
Interview he did
With Tim pool
Until I turned it off
I think there are some people who wanted us
Discover Alex
Cuz he was just on Tim pool show
And I
Don't really want
I worry the temple is the kind of person
Bike judging his internet Behavior
Yeah and it seems like the attention economy is really what he's running
I don't even want to be a part of it
We're probably not going to
To cover that maybe
One last clip and I just wanted very funny
Cuz before Alex
Goes to his
Simple interview today
He wants to complain a little bit more about the majority rule work
Well I noticed a video I was sent this morning
Sam Harris
Weinstein
Alex Jones comparison
The whole thing from
Majority report
MPR
Cobra snake
Voice to put you to sleep in
Talk about science and how we don't debate
8 people
They're playing
I think that if you want a Lobby that criticism it's a that's kind of fine he does
Speak with a really measured tone and
Kind of a soft voice but like Sara Lee monotone but not
Anybody who's ever watches
The majority report would never think that about Sam Cedar
Yeah it's
Now it. That's
Ridiculous
Listen I watch
I watch the whole movie
420 IG
I know Saint Peter is not a quiet
Especially when he get to going on like
Medicare Lookout
I think this is this is kind of fun
But ultimately
I just
See this episode was being indicative of likes
Some real Danger
I feel better
Danger when I hear it
Yeah I don't like
I don't like
People
Getting the idea that suicide bombing
Spine
Or it's within the conversation
Well I mean yeah
That we have this
You know misreported DARPA contract
It was rejected
That is now being used as
Complete evidence
That there's
Raying nanovirus is on people
It's just
It's just a mess
I just don't know what to do I mean
Well for one
Every year
If you are a medical doctor
You should get
A very simple questionnaire
And if one of the answers is
They can make a vaccine that kills yet any time of your life whatever they want you to their like hahaha
You're not a doctor anymore if one of the questions is would you
Consider going on Alex's show
I also think
That maybe
Maybe it did a legal for a doctor to take a medication on air is an advertisement
I think it is I think it would be if they are have a financial interest
In the medication that could but I would say that it probably isn't illegal if they don't
I would imagine that the irresponsible
6 board would be like no we don't
Think that's weird
Smile upon it at the very least
MRNA tissue sample cure for the vaccine
Just take people
Set the f****** Fountain of Youth no can't do it
Can't do it
Dan it's not actually
It doesn't keep
Keep you a lot Idaho. Stelly on found
Don't tell Alex.
Well anyway Jordan
We have
Dum604
Hard to believe
It's hard to believe yours to 601
But until then Jordan we website
Net worth of laundry or fighting that go to bed Jordan
No I'm Leo MDX
What the sex robots
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work