Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge right now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Like to sit around and talk
Little bit about Alex Jones
We are. We are 65 episodes away from episode 66
Start the counter all right let's put it on the board
65 days till tomorrow
What's up
I think I might have used this as bright Biden
I guess via George Lucas talk show is back hell yeah I enjoyed it
For a bit
Since coming back in just
Just a delight Delight
Clean fun
Ben Schwartz was on the newest why I know Andy Daly is on it as well but I have not gotten to that part of the leg
No I will watch the Andy Daly Play I Believe friend Will Miles also makes an appearance
Did some comedy with back-in-the-day here in
Chicago moved out to
Workout
He did
That was a really nice I enjoyed
No matter what form you take
Brother wearing a blue nose or not I don't feel comfortable I can understand that
My bright spot is what's it called
Speed Korean show on Netflix
And it's essentially like a battle royale and parasite put together
Bunch of people
Trapped in the miseries of capitalism fighting each other to survive and
To get money and food and all that stuff
And the way that put together is a series of games that
Murder 500 people for the
Benefit of the road
Okay.
That's pretty good
That's all and it's all like
Children's games you know like one the fridge the very first episode not to spoil anything
It's the whole hook
Book of the f****** show you go in there
Everybody's playing Red Light Green Light
And if you lose
Cypress boom-boom-boom murdering people left and right
Play we read a battle royale my friend this is a this is a fictional show
I don't I
I have to apologize
Yes. You were speaking metaphorically about the murdering people like
The opposite directions
Can understand why you can handle watching this
Pointed and it saved
The murder party
I thought it was like that
Can you fit through the whole show
Forgot to do a pose until I get smashed into a wall it's fantastic that existed
The best
Auntie
I just had a memory the other day of Who Wants to Marry a Millionaire
Yeah it wasn't he liked something
Yeah LOL
Obviously
I can't
Our culture is bad now but man we weren't great then either
We did that I think what people need to understand it it started bad
And it slowly and then quickly gotten worse
More or less who Wants to Marry a multi-millionaire
So Jordan today we are going to
The past Wednesday
Burn 2003
Peeps
Alright couple days in between there their
That's because I last
Episode in the past was on a Friday
Never on Monday
I think this is this is low-key
He one of the boar
Maybe educational or Illuminating episodes of Alex and show
But I've listened to it a long time
And also there's some amazing ironies
Knowing what we know in
In the future that will probably get me label to which god dammit
Let's say hello doesn't do want
The first Laura thank you so much and I apologize
Gary thinking about you and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
The co-hosts of the dollop
Text Jessica thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Play Jessica Jones is only two years older than Dave Rubin
You very much weird reminder of mortality
And thinking about you and I hope all is well
Brian
Jordans
We're going to start here
On 2003
Dune
This purse clip I actually miss her
The first time I was listening through the episode
Pretty excited
Because I thought Alex was
Teasing app
Guess he was going to have on his show as opposed to a subject
He was going to do
Discuss
And then I got really disappointed when I realized I was first
Going to be on the show cuz I thought it would have been
Very interest
Talking about
Charles
Under Medicaid Medicare fraud
So Charles cell was a dentist from St Louis who is charged with Medicare
A frog
Even before you got in those legal hot water heater shown signs of severe mental illness with his own doctor ordering him into hospice
Asian a
Revealed that he was concerned that
Communist
Contaminated the feeling
This lady was putting into people
He's just a regular old purchase
Hospital he was medicated to code control the symptoms
He returned to practice but ended up having more flare-ups like when quote
He told police a leopard was getting on a city bus
And I several in which he thought people in his community were out
Tequila
Is mail fraud six counts of Medicaid fraud in a count of money laundering in 1990s
On accusations of quote
Submitting false claims including false documents and x-rays to Medicaid and private insurers
For dental services
He did not provide
Immediately became an issue for the courts
About whether or not he was competent
Set the stand trial
Initially he was said to be competent but I imagine that
It probably didn't help his case that it is first bond hearing in front of a federal Magistrate
Quote doctor sell scream to the magistrate using racial epithets
When she tried to continue the hearing he shouted and spat in her face
Cool
Alright Behavior
Then in April 1998
For quote conspiring to murder and the attempted murder of a witness in the fraud case
And an FBI agent
Okay well that when you're probably not going to come back from
There was a growing concern about his mental well-being
And the danger he could possibly pose if he was left untreated and in July 1999 a court ordered him to be given an
Antipsychotic meds
Against his will
This ruling was delayed pending another here
In August 2004 court-ordered him medicated and the appeal went to the 8th circuit
Record who decided not to rehear the case
On a 5-4 vote
Ultimately in June 2003
Do US Supreme Court would weigh again and Rule 63 in the case of cell versus United States
Affirming that quote
Forcibly drugging a defendant solely for trial competent is appropriate only in limited circumstances
This would overturn the previous order for him to be medicated involuntarily
And fascinatingly guess what
The Supreme Court ruling actually happened on
June 16th
Exact day that this episode were listening to was being recorded by Alex
Were you covering the subject
No
Very weird no I refuse I refuse to believe you it's very bizarre
In 2004 he was ruled fit to stand trial and his lawyers trying like hell to get him to agree to a plea deal
All the Frog stuff was one thing but that conspiracy to murder was not something that was going to be as easily move past
According to the Post-Dispatch article from the time cell agreed to plead guilty to a fraud charge but not the murderer
Conspiracy one
Those lawyers were trying to get him ruled unfit to stand trial again
More difficult to
This dude
Reasons that it's taken less seriously like some of this conversation
The Conspiracy to murder thing
Is there a lot of snow
The courts believe
But that was a manifestation
Reasons that made him under
Unfit to Sara Lee a sincere effort to
Conspire to murder somebody
It was
It's a when the conversations about whether or not it's appropriate to forcibly medicate him
It was strictly along the conversations of the fraud charge
And that
Just fascinating
So in the end he accepted a plea deal where he pled no contest
About all the charges
And he was
2 time served and 6 months in a halfway house
And then three years bro
Story particularly ones bad to he had allegations of mistreatment while he was in prison
These are very important things and I don't need to brush
Femicide at all but
For the time being this case is a perfect example of what
I was talking about back in episode 1 of our podcast
But I thought there was an important role that someone who is Alex
Pretends to be
Play in society
This case is f****** hard
Because even assuming it's I was guilty of Medicare fraud which
He definitely was
At what
Point does his individual liberty intersect with the public need to adjudicate this
Fraud charges are non-violent crimes
So does the public interest really demand that he be medicated so we can be confident
The stand trial for that
If not what should you do
Use the product people and the public Healthcare System
So there can't be no consequences but what are you doing that
That situation
It's a mess
I've got
Very easily taken care of okay
Truman Show
Vivian
That seems prohibitive expenses you would think that but it would solve the problem
So these are the sort of hard questions that don't have clear-cut answers because they really do boiled down to where you think
The line is
Between the Liberties of individuals and when that encroaches on the responsibilities we all have to each other
Someone like Alex is obviously an extremist on the side of individual liberties
But this case has the territory we actually have an interesting case study to look at
Where you can say that the state
Has no right to demand medication
I'm going to hear you out
And you can say that the state has an obligation
The demand medication
I do hear that out too
Both sides of this ham
You know compelling places
To come from
Right right
It's honestly just a shame because even in 2000
Three you can see Alex
It's completely f****** up playing
The role of somebody who just isn't the individual liberty
You can even report the details of this case accurately because he's not confident he can make the argument for this guy
If he has to accept all the unsavory aspects
McKay's
The details of the case get in the way of him being able to even talk about it
Vueling corrupt
In the city
Bogota
It seems like he was more.
Frauding medic
Well we'll get to
Alex means by that later cuz it's quite a reveal
I'm interested but
For now
Yeah
Also because it's about you know who was they're actively trying to fight for a doctor sales rights
Why not how about the ATL
Nope the ACLU wear clothes
They filed a friend-of-the-court brief on behalf of self-seeking to urge the court to reverse
The decision to medicate him against his will
So weird that they would do that
That considering how Alex thinks they're evil
Another thing really quick
This is basically nothing to do with the legal questions that the case brings up but I have a hunch of the Charles cell also happen
Since to be a racist a******
It's easy to Tribute his use of slurs and cord is possibly like a manifestation of a mental break
That becomes harder to argue when you realize that he was also prior to this
A member of the Council of conservative
There we go
The CCC is a hyper right-wing white nationalist organization that super against what they call quotes
Mixing of the races
Make no mistake about it if you're messing around with the counselor
Conservative citizen
It's not because you're politically conservative it's because you're a straight-up racist
One look at their publication the citizens Informer
Where should clear up any concerns
You may have if you think
That I'm being unfair
If you're a member of the organization you are a piece of s***
Dylann roof did they write that in the conservative Informer I didn't
I just headed to quote that was me
Dylann roof the guy who murdered 9 black
People because they were black at the Emanuel African Methodist Episcopal
Church in Charleston
Specifically mentions the Council of conservative citizens website
Is being the thing that Ross started him down his pasty white nationalism
It is manifest
Bestowed
Play f*** this Charles cell guy is clearly a racist by a butt
Still Standing his case
These issues
Uninvolved involuntary medicating like
That conversation is a Justified and it's something that's worth
Having that conversation
And it's just a shame that Alex is such a s*** head that he can't
Be the side of that conversation that
He should be
Right
Someone who pretends to have the political beliefs
Says that he does
Someone who has it as a voice in this
It is it is kind of that question of like
And I could even I could absolutely here at the argument of somebody being like
No
This is a power that
A government
Could use
Could use well
But not out
Our government cannot use it well they can only abused it
So that's a that's a fair argument to have the other argument is that
Hey man people are doing their f****** best
This guy is out of control
Maybe we don't have to like turn it into a whole thing
Yeah
I conceived definitely
A very difficult
Conversation
To be had about like
What if you allow
Medicating
Just for the sake of him being able to stand trial
Against his will
The Medicaid
In the case of this
Like Medicare fraud case
What is the line
That it is
Appropriate where do you set the line of who can you forcibly Medicaid
What type of behavior is bmdd
Like
Deserving of
A vat as a solution
Find what the documentation required for that behavior because yeah it's incredibly
No there's so many places to abuse
Places to fuk up
At the same time I know that sometimes people
Certainly
Come up in our lives
I don't know
I don't know it's a really really interesting question
Alex should be nowhere near it
No
That's exactly what Alex pretends to be
I know but
Why this is what the
All I can do is tell you it's tough
So Alex
I thought you were going to have that guy on a Zagg
He just talks about it
Does have
A couple of gas
Okay who does a radio show on Alex's Network I guess.
Some shortwave s***
Another guess that's a little bit more legit
Organization
So I guess Alex has a bizarrely mainstream Gaston this episode in the form of a Harper's writer Jeff sharlet
I'm very confused
So Charlie was the executive producer of the 2019 Netflix series
The family
Which is actually what this 2003 article in Harper's was about
I don't know if he's read this article cuz he thinks
Just called the Brotherhood which is
It's not called in the article
Not by the fact that his confusion is because members are referred to as brothers in the first line
This is a
Messed up religious extremist group it's also not like they're super Fringe
Who does
Part of the problem
Extremely powerful put on the National Prayer Breakfast every year where
President show up and give speeches a book about the group in 2008 largely about other
This group of extreme fundamentalist Christians are deeply entrenched
Conservative politics
Which Alta probably agree with Envy all four in 2020
About how it's a evil evil illuminati people who 20 years from now
I will say should be our God
Of course
Yeah yeah yeah great white be sensing a little bit of the irony that I'm talkin about
I hate the world before Alex gets into any of the real meat of the issues today
Cookie Supply
For his websites
What are these might stick out
The website
Call Ward
Virgin
Cam
Did you know that he had prisonplanet.com
No that's not the one that's spelled out
You know
Can you talk
So apparently
In 2003 Alex was running a website promoting a town in Utah called The Verge
Which was quote
A model Community for small towns in big cities alike
The Virgin city council and citizenry have made virgin a friendly place to live
For those who support the Constitution
And Bill of Rights
He started a railroad town
Are they
Jones box
This is fascinating
In the present day like in the last few years Alex's pretty regularly been talking about how his extremist right-wing buddies need to get together
Start the road self-ruled Verdes
Wow
Wow at least I have more specifics 20 years ago
Just rediscovered that Mormon teens have fun
They just go in and then don't move like I said it is fun that they rediscovered
Common 2003 was up where they learned I thought the Virgin Utah might have been like a homesteading
Kind of like convergent lamb
This is just wild
At the time that City had a population of about
And the 2010 census put the city at 1.8% White
The entire reason that Alex is promoting this city is a place for Liberty lovers is because in 2008 pass an ordinance
That every citizen had to own a gun
On their website they discuss at this ordinance was based on a similar 14
From Kennesaw County Georgia although they did misspell Kennesaw
Unsupported claims about an 80% drop in quote
Every category of crime and the 15 years since cannasouth happy ordinance
Also I love this part
One important point for any county or city thinking about passing the sword
Kennesaw County saw population
Explosion from under 5,000 citizens over 20,000 today
That's over eight times the growth of the average Community Seas
It seems
Good news travels
Fast
Americans want safe communities where they can raise their children and the right to protect their family
This is actually true
The population growth
But it's not really possible to attribute this gun ordinance
Thanks for that growth
Austin population
Camisole with a growing Community for decades
Kids experiencing a 160 7.2 per cent growth between 1950 and 1960
And then a 135% 4 % grow
Between 1960 and 1970
The gun ordinance was passed in 1982 and population actually only grew 75.4%
Between 1980 and 1990
For picking up to a 140
32.6 per cent growth rate
In the next step
If anything you could argue that based on the growth rate the city seems to be normally experiencing it was a slump.
Uptown place where you have to own a gun
No I don't want to own a gun
What are the primary drivers of this population growth the people including the Kennesaw City government's own website
Site attributes
The growth of population
Is it they're located right next to Kennesaw State University
Wow there is
The rapid growth of population is also spurred by our favorable location with respect to transportation
Including I-75 and US Highway 41
Maybe it's his meeting with gun ordinance that I'm certain is not enforced
Yeah you know what's great about Virgin Utah as they after they passed the gun ordinance
They were like we saw an 80% drop in crime
What do we do with that last 20% right
Next day
Every year one day
All crime is legal
And all crime is legal for 24 hours
Crimes
Everyone has to own a tank
Public subsidy
Subsidized tank
Yeah I guess like you know having a college there and
Good Scituate
Situatedness between
Do large highways
I do know that
That could be
Maybe it's this dumb board
I was going to go with you
Explosion of public highways that happened just about everywhere in the 50s and 60s leading to a massive
Amount of travel and people who would be brought
To the area by the college
I guess one way you could tell is that like
I guess Virgin Utah should have a massive
Explosion of
Population 2
20 years ago
Their population is 600
Still too large
How expensive
I don't think so
I think he's forgotten
Entirely about
The Rodger new dog
Also just because it's f****** hilarious to you the exemption section of the Kennesaw gun law which was copied
For Virgin Utah
Anyone quote
Exempt from the effect of this section are those a heads of household to suffer from physical or mental disability which
Them from using such a firearm
Further exempt from this effect of the section are those heads of households who are poppers
Or who conscientiously opposed maintaining Firearms as a result of beliefs or religious Doctrine or person
Convicted of a felony
I don't want to own a gun without nothing we can do here that's a loophole that's a loophole in the law
I don't want to I prefer no
This is all just for show and to excite people like Alex that's all the time
An article in the New York Times quoted their mayor is saying that they've never prosecuted someone for not owning a gun
And the law was essentially unenforceable
If I were Paul Joseph Watson I might see something like that and think it was a very extreme and childish childish case
A virtuoso
I mean there's no way that I wouldn't
Like if you pass that law in Chicago
I would walk around City Hall just being like
F****** do it man I don't own a gun arrest me
Do it take me to trial
Please
Tell me that the Supreme Court is going to side with
You have
To buy a gun
Just now it's think that's a much more of an encroachment at Liberty
The positive responsibility
Exactly
It's a mess
Nuttzo
So what episode
I'll just come back
Studio
And maybe some rumor
Floating around about a weekend
Okay Alex Dietz
To get ahead of these rumors
Warrant
And already
Friend on their boat
This weekend
I'm not a my judgment
Schwarzenegger
Colton Underwood
Mcgillycuddy's hand on a boat
That sucks also his policy on like changing his mental state certainly has been
I won't even take
Aspirin
I feel like I policies Lucent
How do you think so
Everything about what how he behaves
I do his body is a temple
And the temple needs cup
I have two possibilities
What's that one
Is he telling the truth
Second
This is suspicious
Little bit
Exaggerated perhaps
Well I mean
Did the part about the Raiders don't understand is like what what what
Are you doing why you wasting time
Turn into a room
Who cares
No it's a rumor
That he could have
What is lost a finger
What is a rumor about it that he was it's just that he was drunk right like the rumor
Alex was so drunk he caught his own f****** finger off it's got to be something like that he's trying to get ahead
Has to be the rumor
Yeah because otherwise is it just like that happens
But someone will try and help somebody on a boat I don't know
It's either
It's either indication of Alex trying to muddy the waters on something
An indication of how like
Need York suspicious his audience
That were they put the computer chip is not the real Alex 24in Luminati
Finger on you and now you have to do what it says
5 minutes
Control on this route
This also made me a little
Suspicious more detailed
And
And other
Word for them
Oh you said the n-word
Something happen
Yeah that's bad word
Looking to be a fly on the wall
I'm curious
I had some Choice words
Some Choice words
There were rumors about
I think we know what those words are
Nobody's telling rumors about Alex Jones told me to f*** off can you believe it
Can you believe that Alex Jones would tell me to f*** off maybe that would be dangerous for his brand at this time
Possible
They know he's not he's not the same
Complete lunatic videos
Today and
Like
Somebody who can feed off any kind of positive or negative
Attention
This is still a point when like
I mean it
He comes off as like
Okay
Hurt his entire ability to
To sell himself as
Hey hey
I'm just a normal very sensible person who has question I will say this to you
I I cannot prove it and you probably have a much more reasonable explanation
But deep in my guts
I'm putting money on a racial slur
That's what I'm doing
I mean it's a bond
Only possible he could have actually just been like wasted or something
There's something that happened at that dock
That I would like to do
I would like to dedicate the rest of my life
2 documentary
Will make small models will have
This is where Alex Jones
I'm going to do a f****** season of serial
Many people are wondering
What are the rumors
Spell doubt
So what's Alex's careers over and I inevitably do my
Dino documentary about
My first question
What happened on that. That day
Tonight we get into the actual meat
Some of the topics that are
Alex has John
OneStop Miller on
And he is on
To talk primarily about
The Charles cell case
Yes
Which again is that dent
Distrito
And here is where that corrupt
Part
Two-player
Get ready for your mind to be blown
Given notice
Army at the time in the reserves
They wanted him to
To do the French
For dentures so on
Now this is
Before the
Branch Davidians
Decided
All the findings of the government
Panels at the Davidian
Actually committed suicide
Exactly
Do the front
Something happen
He claims that
He had the free
I bet you didn't see that coming
This is actually a Waco cover-up story
Factoring into this at all I was a little surprised myself
Couple quick points on this year
The Waco standoff occurred in 1993 and Charles cell was first hospitalized after insisting communistic
Contaminated his feelings in 1982
He was getting hospitalized around 1984 serious problems related to delusions long predate any alleged involved
Marriott in any
Things related to Waco
I can find no credible source that backs
The claim that sell was called in to do friends
Dentistry at Waco
Okay nor that he was called in before the standoff even occurred
These are claims you can find repeated message boards and dice
He blogs but there's nothing
That I can find the make me feel confident about it
And it seems kind of unrealistic
Sixense around that time he was
Supposed to be a dentist in St Louis I mean that he would be the person they would bring in
It seems
Strange coincidental
Should that be the case
I mean it
It's the writing on that other the writing unreality needs to be taken up a notch if that's the
Yeah it's like we've run out of characters in reality like now we can make more
This is really bizarre to me because
It seems like Alex and John are putting a hat on a hat here
They have an issue that they can make a compelling case on whether or not the state has the authority to forcibly medicate someone arrested for not
Violent crime
But instead of really just sticking to the issue where there's a chance of making a decent point
These Dum Dums have to spin out and turn everything into a grand conspiracy that works into their larger worldview
The actual relevant issue is either too boring or too difficult for these people to talk about
So instead they just Django Keyes
What if we fight
To get a banana to take
Good Meds then you finally break
Waco case wide open
We don't need to fight for him to not be forcibly medicated because that's an infringing of his rights
But I guess if he's medicated in the global still succeeded in their cover up with this is nonsense that's insane
Damn
Skyrim that is that is a little bit like
Cub reporter comes up and he's like
This guy
It's going to be it's going to be
Watershed moment
Figure this out
This is a
Alex is like
That's boring your s***
I'm going to punch it up he was at Waco
I just
I know it made me feel like I gave Alex too much credit
At the beginning of the episode when this case got brought up
Because I felt like
This is an actual place where he
You could make an argument
I couldn't gauge with
His principles and his politics
Exxon
It's just a trick
Alex got a
Belt I-88 mile-an-hour fastball
3 *
The same picture
Enfield
It's pretty unfortunate
To show how even
5 years and I still give him too much credit sometime
You are somehow a very hopeful
Ilike2learn
So anyway John stadtmiller has a little bit of a different version
Of this interaction
Charles L had with the judge
But here's the government
Goodguys how it's supposed
Thought your phone
Guilty of fraud
For Medicare and Medicaid
Would only say
He is not
For a judge
Basically
And
Of The Middle
Help people
This man is not
You'll notice the John stadtmiller leaves out
A few details about cells behavior in court like the racial slurs and spitting in the judge
His face
They also conveniently forget about the prior hospitalizations the long history of delusions and everything else
Forgive this case it's contacts
And there's very clear reason why they're doing
Really interested in this case for whether or not the state has the right to forcibly medicate people
But they want the credibility that comes with
Pretending to have that conversation
They want to just present cell as a political prisoner who's being held
Then forcibly drugged because he needs to be silent
It's about Waco
That's their angle understory did the pretense of concern about cells rights that's just window dressing
The actual people concerned with the issues Alex
Pretends to be
Concerned about
Are folks like the lawyers at the ACLU
They were dealing with reality as a place to
This nonsense
Yeah yeah
What piece of s***
Yeah kind of sucks
I really does it is
It's so like man
You had a moment where you could have done something
Good beer but you know your enemies were too busy actually working on it while you distracted your audience
Yeah for no reason
It doesn't even get you more
Attention to say that he's a way to digest as far as the conspiracy of worldview
The audience is mine
And it uses this
This doctor is a prop
Pretty gross as usual people are thing
Next
Stadtmiller
Recorded
A full segment from Dateline
Aston Villa
Check my record it on like a VHA
Recorded it on based on the 2003 technology
Is banana.
I think I understand this
Broad interpretations of fair use
But they don't interrupt it at all their play a full seven minutes section it's
I don't know that might be a little too much
My charm so yeah they play this and then I hear is a little bit of comment
Government has
Fermented already lost nearly
Years of his life and his freedom
Someone like
I know
It's My Life
John's incredible
That's not what I would have gotten
From the Dateline piece
Private is
Pretty well done
Yeah like cuz it does wrestle with those issues forcible medication
Even some of the claims of mistreatment in the when he was carcerated
There it comes at it from a number of angles like I don't obviously I don't think
I don't think any news programs perfect
Fairly decent job based on my understanding of the details
It is fun whenever the global is hide something for 10 or 11 million viewers on Prime
Yeah they hide it in plain sight
Directly into the faces and eyes and ears on 5 to 10 million people in
Very sneaky
Terrifying how they do that
So I don't think that John stadtmiller brings
A whole lot
To this conversation
Just a lot of like he's going to be in prison forever with Tik-Tok that up to the
The great prediction
Alex and his
Cuz he was released
Pretty soon after there shortly after Court ruled
If they have done this episode
The next
Dejan Alex's show
But now that we know what the government says we can do a show on it would be stale the next day
Primary roles
It's kind of like whitewashing stories that might be
Uncomfortable for
Folks in the extreme right
Regice
Admitted
They buried
Inform
Something autumn
They must have
Been guilty of something
Mindless
Yeah I do think it's a show send a bad message
Perhaps but I also don't think that it has a bearing on
This one
I don't think that you can say
Here's a real life thing
Went to build my case
Opposed
Procedural
Drama show do not like
That Alex was ahead of me on topic
I don't like it
I don't like that I was behind on figuring out that all TV gives us an
Used to think that cops
Our actual
Billy doing their job
Sure
So I think that they are also John and Alex
They're misrepresenting
Misreporting
Some details here
This case was about 3 members of the Georgia Republic militia arrested in 1996
And charged with conspiring to build pipe bombs
These guys were worried about the need to prepare for a war against the US government who they thought we're going to use un troops against
Public much like Alex does and did
An informant did alert the Bureau of Alcohol Tobacco and Firearms about some of the militias activities and recorded some of their meeting
That's not the same thing is demonstrating that the government set these people offer
Any of that nonsense
What's that mother is going on
Also if you go and read the articles about this case you get quite a picture
Associated Press
Neighbor Georgine fesperman said she's seen
A pickup truck full of men with shaved heads
Scary rifles
Camouflage
Black berets
Driving to mccraney property
Something's going on back there she said
There's always gunfire back there they've got vicious dogs back there you can hear them
The article goes on quote
Informant told agents of the Bureau of Alcohol Tobacco and Firearms on April 5th
But he'd attended a meeting with McRaney star and others
At which macaw
Granny talked about blowing up a bomb on his property
And said he had enough chemicals to make 40 bomb
According to the affidavit
McCready is
Not the government
Informant that's one of the men who was arrested
Alexandra Miller turning into a martyr
Like this is all nonsense
I'll just part of the
What I would call The Lone Wolf social contract
But Alex engages in
You know like these things happen people get caught
And we will do our best
To make sure
That
These are presented as fake
In order to make it easier for the next person not to
Exactly
I'm back
Kind of feels like the game that they're playing
Cuz it's not it's not realistic
Like unbelievable seem like
The point
Is for Alex and his ilk
And the Tucker Carlson
Sins of the world
Provide
Cover
For the militias to refine and home their method
In order to eventually succeed
Do you like that
Is that unfortunately they're providing a smoke
Screen for the dumbest most cowardly people on the planet
Who have yet to refine a single method
.
We just keep finding bombs everywhere that are poorly constructed
It's very common
We get to Alex's next gas
Stadtmiller goes
Bye bye bye
And we get
Jeff sharlet
The guy from
V
The Harper's magazine
It is
This point in time
He's notable Maybe
Yeah
Yeah you get you could get some of the harbors
And
Congressman
Well we're whatever
They believe what you do
He was making beginning of his Alex's intro there
It's a little complicated but
It's not so much that the people featured in Charlotte's article or saying that Hitler was good
It's more the youth Hitler and his relationship with the Nazi leadership as an example of what
They think is a good form of government
Hitler and his top command headache
Complete Unity of purpose and there was a steadfast devotion
The following Hitler
And this is commented on in the article as a
Powerful form of covet
Another example that uses the mafia
They're basically describing the being super into
The leader of the family Doug Coe
Hierarchy
Yeah the leader dougco explains quote
A covenant like the mafia look at the
The strength of their boss
Tea for them it's honor for us
It's Jesus
The article goes on quote
Code listed other men who had changed the world through the strength of his Covenant State Forge with their brothers
Quote look at Hitler he said Lennon hoochie been bin Laden
The family of course possessed a weapon those leaders lack
The total Jesus of a Brotherhood in Christ
Whenever Hitler comes up in the article
It's basically a talk
Bring about it in this context
Still f***** up
But it's not what Alex
It's not the way Alex is understanding it
Or we presenting it to the audience
It is
Not at all sir
Surprising to me
That these people
Love
What is essentially the same thing as multi-level marketing
But in a
Like its
The same s*** you know
It's just the same f******
Yeah and maybe like a little bit more interest
Austin power then
Then
Strictly money
Yep cool boy
Yep
This interview I was very fascinated see where would go though because knowing what we know now
Where am I
Some of the stuff that Alex is saying is fairly accurate but
I want to talk about a certain irony here
Marysville
Alex is having a hyper critical coverage
Of the family back in 2000
But the reality is
He might actually be broke right now if it wasn't for them
I have we know Alex's head-on are a bunch of his finances were looking
Shaky in the past few box
And this year he would have been
Deep in the red if it weren't for Mike Lindell and his pillow money
But what if I were to tell you that the family radicalized Michael until
You're staring
No
I know
That's what I would tell you I would tell you no to your face
Sir
I don't like witches
Jonathan Larson recently wrote a piece in Salon the trace is Mike lindell's conversion to fundamentalist Christianity and
Hard right politics to his attendance at the
The 2016 National Prayer Breakfast
My f******
That event is not just
Breakfast it's actually a four-day Affair full of small group meetings that are probably familiar to anyone who's gone to an Evangelical Church
But also mix in that mln vibes
I recommend this article but
The short version is that Linda went
They ended up in one of these small rooms of someone praying and eats
Experience the prophecy that he was going to change
The course of the country
Using this prayer room with Ben Carson who's Big member of the group and they got to talk
In politics
An excerpt from lindell's book that is featured in that Salon article
Call quote
The Dozen people in the room gathered in a circle and began talking about the critical importance of the 20s
16 election
We agreed it was going to be a real spiritual turning point for the country
One path could lead us toward National renewal
The other could lead us down a dark path from which there may be no return
A path that had begun with the removal of God for
Square
We have got to go down that.
Bike path because once they remove God I decided it was time to destroy everything else
The religious group had successfully intertwined their religious vision and their political Ambitions into Mike lindell's head
And we all know where that's gone
Lindale supported Ben Carson and then Ben Carson got him into
Trump after Carson dropped out of the race
Tangled and twisted web but the family was deeply involved in not only supporting Trump candidacy but with
Directly
And scamming the s*** out of my Glendale which had a trickle-down effect of getting
Alex Auto financial hot water
Just so here I just
That's what I'm saying it's just a f****** multi-level marketing scam everywhere you go it's f****** b*******
Alex in 2003
Talkin about this article
They're going to save me in 20 years
I'm f****** real
And he believes all the same s*** the family does not almost certainly.
Did unknowingly
At this point to
Yeah like I'm not moving out unknowingly but on Cross
I mean actually I would say
Based on what we
Learned from there they're like they appreciated Hitler's hierarchy not Hitler
Alex appreciates Hitler more than the family
Pizza stuff
Total badass
Is Christ yeah what I hear is like some of the stuff about the
The beliefs and
In
The way organization should be at sounds a lot like
Like I think
I think that he has the same sort of relation
Pacific Power
Anyway Charlotte
Gets to talkin about the founder of
The group of the the family
Amanda this dude sound like
Galax
Scale
Abraham
Maintain
And everyone else
Christian that always
Minister today
That's what Christ
To go out
There's a lot of similarities with Alex they're having read the Bible
He assumed
Jesus Christ wanted him to make the rich people happy and bust Union
Read the Bible the preacher
Was like somebody
He's got to help these rich people get more money
Opposition to Union believe that God is
Is calling him to fight communism personally probably had Visions when he was Kid
Dinner and you can even get that like
Ministering to powerful people
Obsession with pretending that world leaders listen to his show and
But there's so much of this that is just like
This is ulam
Alex
You're talking to somebody who's like
You're talking to somebody
Who is analogous to the person 40 years from then
Who's going to write an article on you
You're talking to your interviewer in the future
It's our fun house mirrors to look at
Really unfortunate
About this interview is that
Narcissism
It manifests in a lot of ways and one of them is that he has to know more than the people he's interview
He basically just takes the things that Charlotte is
Is covered in
Experienced
And research
And Alex just uses it to make his own kin
Conclusion
Isn't fair
No it's annoying
Call Hitler
It does not mean
Admire
It works
There's not much
But they do say
Brother's friend
Imagine if we could put the
That model to work
Cialis
What's keeps only going back to the point of like
Did they say Hitler is good but the point where Jeff Charlotte has to be like
I have to clarify this because
I don't think it's fair the way you're characterizing it
Now I understand
And I respect
But it's
The same time
Play Love Hitler up
Are you just cuz you can't prove they love Hitler
Play f****** love Hitler and you f****** know it I think
You can be fine saying something like that as a commentator but someone who's driving themselves as
A serious reporter who backs up everything that he says with facts and research
Yeah I think that I think that he has a greater responsibility to be clear on his point totally understand
Alex make a differentiation
Between the two and I appreciate that
The Charlotte seems
Will a consistent on like not being misrepresented
Write 2 degree what I would like to hear it let me let me throw this at
Okay let's go back in time
Let me throw this at
Alright I can only prove
Through the conversations that I have heard and I've been told about
That they appreciate Hitler's business
Now
If I were a betting man
I would say if you spend a lot of time appreciating Hitler's business model
Sooner or later going to get to
He had some other good ideas
So f*** off if you think
He's they don't love Hitler
Charlotte's conversation
Things you can take away
Is
Sagano
I8
Delineation between
From his experience and the document
It's the kid been able to get ahold of any experience that he had living among these people there wasn't a ray
Racialized a version of this or an ethnic there was a religiously-based
Elite
Kind of thing
And if you wanted to
Have that conversation about
Maybe Hitler's policies clean creeping in in terms of
You know it related to Christians and non-christians
But but in terms of Master races and stuff like that show at there is a breakdown
Queen
You would
Normally have come to your mind when you envision Hitler and
What they are interested in
And I think that there is there is a difference
But there's also
You know I also get your point you cares
Alex has failed on this point
Good Charlotte's pushing back
Until Alex has to move on to a next
Young guys and I hadn't
Discussion.
Or we could all study whether or not we agree with him
Don't think that's out of line I don't think that
Yeah that's right on
The end of a good
Boy I don't know if these these rockhold's that Alex is trying to get up the side of the cliff on or are being very help
Totally evil
That's what's up
He even does slip back into being
Like a like Hitler
To the point where it just Charlotte has to do like
Basically correct
Yeah
Emphasize
Chuckled
Semite
These guys admire
Organizing
And they don't make
I believe that
German
Yeah that's kind of Sunday
Yeah f*** off
Yeah that is the most annoying thing of like
Hey I've invited you on we're going to talk about this
I don't know much about this
I'm going to tell you about dif
Like it
This guy
Giving his
In depth
Experience
And knowledge
About this subject
On the surface
The reason you have this person on your show 100%
Learn about the things that he has study
Supposed to
Condescending
Explain to him that his researches inferior to yours
I think that's another that's another element you know and would you ever want to talk to Alex Jones or anything and it's like
Getting even bothering his horrendous disqualifying views
I just don't want to be interviewed by the shitbag
He's the worst person to talk to
Yeah he just sucks
He's very rude even at this point but it's less
Like it
It's less
Aggressive ride over.
Underhanded
Yeah
There's that there's a passive aggression that may actually be going with both directions
It's because
Whether he understands it or not
Just Charlotte ends up saying some things that Alex
We consider fighting words today
Crazy there is a Groupon
Online
Play some years
If you believe in that
Ticular kind of
Literally
Reading of Revelation
My point exactly
We don't need
Any further than that
For Christ
Off the tracks right there
Yeah
But I I can't imagine someone
You if you're one of those lunatics
Those f****** crazy folks who believe that the Book of Revelations is literally going to happen have that kind of an unsub
Fisticated understand
To take the book
Book of Revelation
Literally
If someone I can't even believe people that stupid exist
Yeah
Swinging
Might be biting his tongue or whatever just
You heard earlier the interview I'm talking about like the Arbors of Art
Prestigious
I still think that he thinks this might be a get
You know like yeah
I mean for him it seems like it would be a fairly
Good chance to try and legitimize your your shity outfit
Sherman Oaks
Then maybe makes
Some connections with other relay
A folks who
Completely ignored as
Alex Burgers could you get me
Give me the phone numbers of some of those important people in my family and see if they want to give me a lot of money
A lot of money I believe
Exactly what they believe for a price
I don't think
I don't know if it goes that direction Glendale gave them a bunch of money
Don't know when you figure out how to get powerful you don't
People give you
Something that I think is really fascinating is
Charlotte
Which is about
Hit his assessment of
The people is they might not even recognize that what they're doing is essentially calling for a dick
Dictatorship
It really
You see the same things in more recent Alex Jones
More like
In last few years
There is a sense of like whether you understand it or not what you're doing is trying to push for a dictatorship
Throughout
Number of people really
Q
Policeman
Calling all the shots
The government model
Dictatorship
It's just
It's it's bizarre to me to deceive this like
Conversation with
Weirdly
You know
Illuminating of what will happen in Alex's future
So what is one point that Charlotte makes that makes me
Videos are you loose like a maybe a baseline awareness of Alex is that he brings up that the end of these are
Your Fundamentalist
That you would normally
Think of who are as he
Provincial
These are people who have international interest
Something that is relevant to Alex
His audience
Sure the one thing I'd like to say that I think that they're your Griffin
Only thing about this.
International
Liberals
Chihuahua
Business fundamentals
As
Provincial and local
Any side
None of that they're very internationalist
A very Savvy they're Charming
Screaming at you on
Eastgroup
AR
Just like everyone else
I think if we're going to really combat
We need to
Acknowledge
What credit is due
Good things about
Breeding
Of the Bible which
No historical base
Little condescending again there
Left-wing view of where you read about the book and then they've learned about it and you know it's not literally
True that's the left
This b******* that New York
Taunton schools
Because that's what knowledge comes
Songs from I'm against the left-right paradigm
Which is
To say I am a fundamentalist Christian
You got it
It was extremely hard right politics
Yep sweet and I hate left-wing bowls
Yeah makes a lot of sense
They take some calls
This one
Call brings up a pretty prescient point
I really think
This
Hits on a little bit of what Alec
What's did in relation
Think this
I'm going to say was that
It's confusing the human
Do you want to come
In the end
The conservator
There are so
Authority
And success
Heather cream never too.
Kind of fetish for Authority in
Using that way
So I think if you got if you get rid of Alex's interjection
Kind of off track a little bit
Do you have is a caller saying that's in a lot of these right-wing
Chris
Tintypes
Can't inflate
Is there a interest in successive Authority
Well you can you can
Mix that up with an image of
Of godliness
I think that Alex did an outrageous amount of that
That guy might as well have just been like
Hey you know I bet the internet's going to come along and it's going to make celebrity go kind of out of control and
Then people are just going to wind up following celebrities and believing that they know what they're talking about even if they have no f****** clue and just got there
Ceremony for no reason whatsoever for their dad gave it to him
Those people are probably going to want him to become a f****** dictator crazy
Mighty bomber
So
Give another call this fella
The compliment Charlotte
And I Alex
Do I have any other
New York
Call Jeffrey
Great work
You opened up
Nothing that we weren't even aware of
What a dick
You
Oh my God
Why do you have to do this
August 1st Radiohead show f*** off no one cares
Why did you invite this person on if you know more than them and you hardly knew about it before they ever came along
Why have the interview then welcome to the Alex Jones
Security our winter I will be feeling weak and pathetic compared to someone who is done
His work is everything I don't like secretly Justin Lester Smokescreen
Yep yep
So stupid is awful
One more call here and this this is where Alex decides
Double calls
Real
Quick if I could
You guys have been talkin about
But they going to try to make
State of Michigan
I just came in
My whole family
Is the child support issue
Put you on hold
I just want to go to work all day today today
Cassidy
Wherever you have a child
Sport issue
Hey Michigan
Trumps
And completely eclipses
The family
I think OJ really funny about that is we've got one more
Great irony
Alex does not want to talk
About child support and cuts
Custody issues on his show
Well he does
He does not with this guy
Right eye.
He tries to hold him over into the next hour and then apparently his phone
But I think
The greater point
Is
That Alex
Is being really condescending and itself
Gas
And this caller calls in a condescending and insulting to Alex's show
It is
Russian doll time to take down the entire state of Michigan
So there is another hour of the show but it is just Alex in interviewing
The mom
From that story we talked about last time
The Waltham right Right Alright Baby I learned nothing from that
But you learned so much the last time
I've only talked about the entire thing
More information
There wasn't I didn't I didn't feel like I had a better grasp on the case I didn't think it was
Interesting at all
That's not surprising
So yeah I just
I have no clips
Convalesced
I'm fine with that
It happened
Guarantee it
I think far more interesting are these first two hours
Just because each one has something really
Bizarre in it
First hour you have Alex
Completely dropping the ball on something
Could have been an issue that he could have actually
Stood on principle with
BP ball
And instead he turned it into a
Nonsense
Waco conspiracy
And then in the second hour this
Interview with the guy from Harpers
Being a real dick to people just being a real dick to anybody who knows
But in addition to just being a rude host
I also
Completely making a mockery of himself
If you had a time machine
Yeah he's really kicking his own ass
Self to the cleaners
There's a really insulting all those people who love him
You you
Got it
I don't know it's
Wolf
We we've gotta find I think Alex Jones in the past
Would be a sharper critic of Alex Jones in the present Thanos
Maybe
I think he would be less
Restrained than you
You wouldn't piss funny or as
Happy-go-lucky are we happy to Lucky
He wouldn't be
Someone that would listen to even tomorrow
Critiquing himself but I do think he would be mad at himself and we are I really feel like this is
Only like the only thing I can think of in my head for this is some sort of Celebrity Deathmatch
Claymation thing where they get
Alex Jones
20 versus Alex Jones
Just got to be
But I mean they they just
Kill each other
Just kill each other
Yeah I bet young Alex would probably win
But then he'll be suffocated under the crushing weight of all.
What a tragedy it would be a nightmare like a positron or whatever yes
Yep so I enjoyed this trip back
Back to the past
I like I like
Like series Dynamics
Snap
Butts
On Friday and another episode
Until then Jordan we have website
Yep we also are on today
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight not go to bed
But until then I'm dlm Leo I'm dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work