Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Need money
Bestbuy.com
Fix it around where they all through and talk a little bit about Alex
Why I was kind of like
Lost for a second summer
How's it going
What is
Your brakes but my brakes but they Jordan with a resounding capital letter is 100 cards
I got some
Capital letters her bright spots
Yes Magic
Car card capitals all across the board
The gate with trying out the magic Arena online it was fun
I like the art style of a lot of these cards I like the gameplay I enjoy that
But it wasn't really
Exactly what I was looking for until I got on eBay and just got a big
Box
Of random cards and that was what I was looking for
It's there's a tactile sensation to pee
Looking at Henderson before we start recording
There's almost like an implied story
That's just it's gripping and an atmospheric and
Calming
I really really really enjoy it and I wish that I've been able to
Mess around with these things when I was 13 yeah I understand
That's that same feeling that like you would never go to a bookstore bookstore that just filled with ebooks
You know like you go to a used book store with
Stacks of books that are unorganized
And you can smell the paper and you can
Touch it with your fingers and it's completely different vinyls
Where old we are old but so I was considering checking
Some of these cards out push me over the edge
Make me like you. Definitely for sure
Was that Jason sent us something at to the mailbox yeah and that was
Individually crafted Magic Car insane based on Alex Jones
Put up a picture of them
But 11 is a sudden plug and the other is not over prepare
Awesome their amazing
These are just a one-of-a-kind things in Issaquah
Why not build a collection around B
So I'm I'm starting down that road I'm going to not go too crazy
Put Jason in his notes that he sent along with it also
He requested that we give a shout out to his uncle
And I say f*** that no
To both of you
Bob homeboy Jason
Shot at a car lot of aggressive energy coming from all directions to he's telling me I have
Have to do something you're telling me that I have to do something different to I'm just going to say you can sit out of this one I'm giving both
Call Michelle.
Evolutionary RV there's no way around it
Also piggybacking on some of this stuff to I want to give a special shout-out to Dillon k
Who got in touch with me
And I was way too delayed in sending an email back about that and idea for a card game the sort of along these lines
And Lucas H thank you so much
That's a battle-hardened goblin card on Twitter that started a little bit of thread
Personalities of magic cards
Don degrandpre
Osso good really bright
The spirit indeed
In the Before Time
Alright for covid-19
Okay
My partner and I
We're going to see a magic show
Oh that place down on Clark
We were going to see that magic and a week
Before everything shut down
So
This Friday
Finally
We will be going to that very same magic show by Fred 98 it happening it's coming full circle we're get
Not a pandemic this is a symbol
This is a meaningful thing to do. Nightmare it's never going to make it
There is a magic club they don't have like a sign saying magic it's like it there like okay there's a door
The secretly find
And you're like that doesn't match apart
But you're never going to make it in the door to find that place I really really
I love that idea of this poorly advertised Magic Theater
It's a Vibe and I really mean of course
Love that book
Places always called to me I'm excited
You will sow also Jordan before we get into
Too much business here I want to give a shout out to Bodie
Who adopted a Raptor
A great horned owl
Family of Selena
Sick World Jurassic World
What was it called dinosaur not the mama
Today we have an interesting situation on our hands we have
Alex's just lost some soup and exhausted at now at this point
Sandy Hook a related lawsuit yeah Texas Courts
And today we have a little bit of his response to go over happily but before we do that Jordan let's say
Hello
Mr. pickles the Dapper Dachshund thank you so much you're now about to walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much
Persephone
My cure.
We're here
Heroin
Why you poop so good
Freakishly large
Who started the State against his net worth
Yes sir so look
I mean we all know what went down we were there
We would we saw it all happen
Alex is all the newly Vindicated everybody has changed their Tunes everybody realizes
Schnauzer
Horrible mistakes they've made in they've treated him types of bad news
Alex gotta be lost
With prejudice news came out at the end of last week
Miles in Texas court with judge in the case giving the parents
A default
Ulta judgment
These two cases initially were brought by Leonard Posner and veronique
And the one that was brought by Scarlett Lewis
I took a little bit longer for the news to break on it but there's also a third case that Alex lost that day which was robbed by Neil heslin
I wanted to get deeply into the Weeds on this development but you know how I am with these technical issues
Sometimes drop the ball so just kind of embarrassed myself sometimes I get
Emails for people who are like
You don't you don't know this term I believe in our first two deposition episode I called the guy a prosecutor
Embarrassed myself sometimes
Do you know what I think would be great
What if
What if what if we could get
The Sandy Hook parents lead counsel Mark Bankston
To come on our show and help explain it
Well yeah but I mean there's no chance
After that maneuver
Hey everybody welcome to this segment
We're going to do something a little bit very out of
Out of the norm yeah yeah
To be joined by
Lead counsel for the the Sandy Hook
Families posing Alex Jones
In court
That you're telling the truth
That's the weird part see when you when you announce something like that on this show we're supposed to be
Being ridiculous friend doing a character exactly
Mark Bankston welcome thank you for joining us
Thank you so much for having me I'm glad to
I appreciate you taking the time I know that I imagine there's some press request
This point boring
They're absolutely boring it wants to talk to you no answers
Cooper that's not
He's CIA
If you did go on Anderson Cooper and talk to him you could talk about his nose disappearing
And that would be
That is my partner call Farah was on and
Friday night
I'm talking about the disappearing nose and knothole
Insane
Proposition
For those who aren't regular followers
Mr. Jones contends that one of my clients berni Delarosa
Performed
Fake interview on a blue screen in a CNN soundstage
It's rather than actually being at Sandy Hook
Disappeared
Breakers you know just a little middle little noses.
I would love it if your fellow lawyer who is on Anderson Cooper
Where did the I got your nose trick that would have been awesome
Straight the place I'd like to start with this I guess
It is that we're doing is
What hap
What week can you explain the ruling that happens
Sure
I'm not a legal scholar
Sew-in in before I say it
There's some ground rules that we're going to be
Expected to follow today
DD
The ethical rules regarding pre-trial publicity make me not be able to say a couple things
Why can't I can't talk to you about things like
The credibility of certain Witnesses or my belief
On the guilt or innocence
Certain people Aldi
Two things chirp but they're also becomes a sort of loophole
When you're opposed
Party
Completely abuses
Pretrial publicity in says the most insane things publicly to freeze you up to
And so that's part of why I'm here today is that
It's a little bit further than I would normally be because my opponent
Has made an Absol
Mockery
This is the pot Kettle statute recall
The Paw Kettle situation
But let me just say in relation to that if there's any point where anything feels uncomfortable or like
Past what you
Can't talk about just let me know
I'll respect that entirely
Then all watching injection
Jordans
Bobby Barnes it up in here and just double-checking
Hey Google is Barnes good work B
Happened
It is never happen
It has never happened to anybody I know
Outside of
The most insane
Situation
Alright well then I can cross one of my questions off the list which was
Have you ever had a case like this before the answer is never got you
Advocates like this
Is for the past 3 years
We have been in a situation where Jones's had
Discovery Auto
Let me see the court will enter order saying yes
How to produce certain documents
Daft Punk albums
You're right
An absolute mess
So not only is he not producing the documents
Not answering the
Let me know when were talking about question where did their stuff like
Name all the employees who worked on these videos and
Name the videos themselves never met any of them questions
Simple facts are not answering
And then you have the
The documents they won't produce and then you have the documents date
Do produce when when they
End up giving us a bunch of documents
Turn over them in electronic
Format
Oh one of the Consultants up
Connecticut found that they had given us
Child pronography
Yeah that was a mess of a
Affair
Bounty on
I was
It's against
Go to those situations where it just
Nobody has ever
So we know we had a we had and I think
A credit to our judges
You just recently retired
We are Judge Scott drink
He's a mold
Charlie judge
Does things right by the book
And he was giving Infowars and Jones every chance they had
To get
Compliance
Correctly
I mean a lot of other parties they would've been done well
You don't want to give Jones the ability to say I'm being Railroad
Closest railroad jobs
What's that's not what you want to do
Enso
We gave him every chance that he had but after 3 years now we show up into our last hearing and they basically
Pretend like we have no idea where
His lawyers are brand-new he's on lawyer number 7
What is law
I don't know how love works is a legitimate thing for a lawyer that works for Alex to say
Defense is just a little while ago saying he was going to get into stand-up on
Alexa show
You know you noticed that there has been a Cavalcade of lawyers
You have
Finn Jones as an opera
Opportunity
Themselves
Admit card out
In the right wing
I probably would
Do I mean I think that's a real irrational thing to do
Bobby Barnes got it turned into a show on Infowars
For a while not the career-changing opportunity that he was open for but
Just not right maybe it was exactly
You was hoping for when you're representing these cases
You never think you're going to get so lucky
As to have your opposing counsel be an actual Infowars comment
You don't get that one
Something up for us we've noted so long we've known it for years but then you eat
You say it in person a real lawyer
Meaning it's in the real world and not just ourselves
It just completely ridiculous
An amazing perspective on this or like
Sense of humor about it
You know watching the depositions that we did it seems like it would be infuriating
Like you just be banging your head against the wall
I think most people would probably look at that and be like
I'm miserable you seem to find some amusement in it which I think is probably healthy probably how you feel
Oh yeah yeah what you got
People when I first got on the
I had to watch about 150 hours
And
As you guys know that message
Enso
After a while do you do kind of half
To take a speck
At the barn at that you you embrace the absurdity of it all
In Ennis I'll tell you this it's
You know it's particularly easy to find a good sense of humor about it all
When at the same time these things are happening you are also
Is beating them up and down
In this case
When I'm sitting in that Jones deposition in in
He is saying the most absurd stuff
Yum some level 2
Infuriating to watch him not take the
That process serious
On the other hand it's intensely rewarding when he says stuff like
Oh we ourselves we never even Envy
Was was really good
Because I haven't really answered your question is
Been there done that
Sending it over
For all
The judge has said
These people have disobeyed the rules with such intensity
With such consistency
That there's no way that my my judicial rulings are ever going to have any impact
Damn so what she's done
Just declared
Which basically says I'm going to
Instruct the jury
That what he did was
Illegal unlawful and
Can cause damage to these
And their only job
Figure out how much money that's worth
Yeah but that's the next step right that's the that's where the case goes from here then to figuring out
What's the price tag
Exactly
Another one of those where
Nobody has any idea
Because nobody has ever seen anything like
Yeah
One of the things that I know from Alex's response to the the news of these
These are default judgement
Was that he said he
Produced all of his bank records
From like his entire life
Is that true
Bu-but to the Connecticut court
In Texas and there's also a lawsuit
And he did have to produce
Some financial information
Internet
I I have
Personally viewed it
But I know what was
Requested what was had
Okay
Actually produce
It was not a
Abroad Spanish
Financial in Korean.
Mainly because what you have to understand and
You know differ
Different lawyers have
Different ways they approach
Aaron Connecticut one of the big things that they're talking about
It's an interesting idea
Is that
Part of why Jones
Did this so often
Sending so much
Cuz you'll definitely
Is that if you can look at the Wrecker
Urgency
That sales
Or brain force and male Vitality rehire on the days that Sandy Hook was
Disgust
Control modem
That he had to do
Personally I also believe you can look at
That
His motive is
Genuinely that he started
Adidas
These parents be
Came
Genuine Financial threats
Because if they got strikes
YouTube everytime you put up app
A picture of their kids saying that they were fake
Then pretty soon
Likelihood
An inference that that really was his motive is that
Alex Jones that
New
It was
He talking about Sandy
Swaney just couldn't help
Yeah that's about right that's it that's an interesting perspective I think I think there may be something to that and there may just be
Be like he's never really had any meaningful consequences ever in the past
Why why would he change his behavior if there is
Keep the Dukes of Hazzard in himself out of trouble
Exactly I mean I've never been interested
Situation where
The answers
Questions that people are asking him have any Khan
That he would be held to account
And for him being in a Depo
Position music
Completely nude
Did not like it
I came I came up in
You know my friend made me a done
Corporate negligence product liability civil rights these got a big
Cases
And
You know we have done big work
In the past of going
3M for metal
Google devices
Keypad for tread separation
Civil rights
Pretty egregious
Nobody
Ever in history
Has done
Podcast analyzing my
Ben Dunham listening
To Yelp
Talk about
What is an interesting thing as a lawyer to go to
I could imagine what are the reasons that I'm on this show right at this moment is I want y'all to go back at some point listen to those episodes in
A yo-yo go back in
I want you to know that every single time
Guys
Say all right what's going on here let's let's
You offer our guests
As to what this means or what is going on here what the
100%.
Everyhome
Laugh
The Dead on
I look particularly
I'm talking about the Paul Joseph
Watson.
That one was that one was the one that was kind of
The least
Funny but very interesting
Because
Because like you pointed out
Watson
Is very aware of how
How bad this is
He doesn't want to be
It's strange you would have never thought Paul Joseph Watson
Stop being the good guy
You know I mean
That was interesting was he really worried about it
Because he was worried about the morality or cuz you
He was worried about the money
I feel like he came off like Stringer Bell you know like you would think he was above this Fray and
And he saw his friend going to jail for you know 8 years and he's like
I have nothing to do with this I'm just over here on the other side
You mentioned Stringer Bell do it
You got to remember the other
There's that email from Watson worried
Says
Jones the Sandy Hook stop killing us these people are bad
She crazy
And that kind of reminds me of stringer Bells warning of like
You are writing
Down of criminal conspiracy
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it is wild
It almost feels like
I'm sorry Jordan had said in that podcast
When you're done with
You're sort of tempted to just go lightning around with him
And just you know climate change
Let's talk about
List of every story of Paul Watson
But I wanted to talk
But you get to that planet
Realized
Really interesting thing that
Show me the people inside him
Public record shows
They don't know
What's going on they don't
Paul Watson
Yeah
Supposed to Rob doing Alex
What's remarkable is that those emails that the toll had showed that he knew that then
He tried to make others aware of it
At the time
I am so they have every reason to know
Hidden kisses
Something that could be quiet
Warm water
Exactly
And then what
Contrast that is
From what we saw
From Rob do
My favorite thing
Rum dude has a lot
A lot on his shoulders in terms of why we're at where we are at
Is the corporate representative I'm supposed to know what that was
3 oz beer to have it more times than what happened Rob use deposition
Robbed you unlike the other Witnesses
Wasn't there testifying as himself
He was there too
Define as
Free Speech systems which is Jones
Subsidiary company that runs all this
Stop USB corporate assigned corporate Representatives
You're giving homework you're giving a list of
Topix
And you have the deed
The corporation has a reasonable Duty
Repair YouTube
Testify about those topics
And speak with the corporation
Voice give the answer
Rob you have no idea he was supposed to do that
And the funny thing about that is your remember that's the first deposition
He has no idea what he's supposed to do he has no idea
Jesus I don't know to everything
November 11th you kept having to ask back like do you not know or just free speech systems
My favorite my favorite
So I have to give a shout out
That was my other partner Bill Ogden
Did that deposition
That one
Was in the midst of it
One of the most defensive
And
Humana disre
Respect me and Sean for the process was
Infuriating
But the moment you get the transcript and listen to it becomes the most
Hilarious things
Because you don't you simply are uncapable
Did Rob didn't know
Like I think if you watch that tape of the deposition
It's kind of coming over him how unprepared he is as it's going along
I think he thought he could come in and Stonewall
Or whatever and
Comes across in your podcast about it
Because you did extra lot answer
In order to
Spirit of it
You have to win
Conclude about 20 to 30 minutes
Total silence
It was Brianna
Realtor. Are you ask a question and you're staring at a solid 2 minutes and he hasn't opened his mouth
No
The know that
What was the first time
Did Rob do you got understand that
6 months later
They got called to Discovery again
And they designated him again.
Say jail in Acworth that last time let's try it again
Throw Them Bones
Talk about these sourcing and research buying these episodes
You dummy
Didn't even know what have to do that
And so good
It was it was so offensive that.
The judge
Scratching their heads
Like I wrote an order saying that this was
Was really really bad and
Did it again
And at that point even at that point
Where we have gone through three cases
With no discovery
Child pronography and Binford
Deposition
Totally ignored it
Nothing is going on
We still got another chance
Appeal
Get this big.
21 the case and dismissed all of these cases
Still want an illegal argue
They didn't
Another appeal
Comeback
And then get another chance
Discovered it was only after they didn't do
Do that
But they were they were defaulted so when I see Jones
Person getting on his Show recently after
This happened
And an insane about how unfairly he's been treated
What a travesty it is
I've got to impress upon
This does not happen in judge
I just don't want to do it
And it took
3 years
You have been given literally
Every available benefit of the doubt to the point now where the judgment
Used to be 100 pages long and this is just one page of an ASCII middle finger
Just saying you owe money
Yeah I mean like I think anybody who lives on Star show probably is aware of how like
Very clear from an outsider's perspective it is that his strategy has been kicked the can down the road
Basically to make sure this doesn't go to trial
Or like
Partially in someone of his legal strategies we've seen in the past it's been
If we protract this case
Examples cost
The other people too much money and they want to settle
Happened a bit I think he was banking on that happening here
It's tough to know what he
Yeah
Because I think there was at that time and maybe he's still convinced of it that
No matter what happens
She's going to be at Larry Flynt hero Jugos
Look to the US Supreme Court in everybody you know it's all going to be saved and they're going to make a movie about what Heroes
Genuinely
When someone will have
The problem now though
Is that
In order to appeal to the US Supreme Court and vindicate yourself on the First Amendment rights
You have actually had to have made the first amendment argument and
And how to hello suit
Trial that actually happened here
You had
No you screwed around discover you're done
So you don't you don't get to a
People saying that you're right
We never had an exhibition of your right
I don't even know what the hell they are right now
So
Right now all we have is
You have
Massively
Disobeyed a quarter
And that is the only thing you'll ever be able to appeal
Angela Lenny Bruce Matt
He's going to do it
This is what happens when you have seven
Albuquerque Journal
Never had a
Was it was always
It was always about
It's not
Some point you have to
Two-faced it
And that's what we're looking at now we're set now for March
For us to go
Pull some jurors
I mean basically put on
Psychological evidence of what happened or plaintiff put on evidence of how far this
Brad you know we're going to have to go with me 112 people
Unlike us
Don't have a real firm understanding of what
Infowars cultural
Don't understand it
Exactly how big
This was
Talk to a jury about that but in terms of them being able to say
What we did we were just
Justified in doing it absolutely not
Dude that's going
Yeah that that chapter this is over
Yeah this is such a Owens f****** community service all over again it's like all you had to do was
30 hours
That is not a lot
All you needed to do was show up
With the documents you didn't you and then you could have pushed probably another year down the road
That implies though do you know that there's a reason he wouldn't want to do that
To be considered rational actor
And they're doing what they do for a reason
We can speculate about it but it
Yeah yeah yeah
It really is because I mean that's the whole problem
So many times you want to try to
Predict what's about to happen or
Bye-bye using a rational Act
And it never works
What you think is going to happen is not whatever happens
And so we basically
The easiest way to
Some predictive control on the over the
This case is too at any juncture
Alright if I'm Jones
Did I miss attorneys
What would I do rashes
And then you can go ahead and cross at least that one off
Admit
Now you're throwing darts at
Your chaos board figuring out which
What is that this is really how it's been
There's no
There's no controller Reimer
So
To the point where you
You go stir crazy like me
Yeah well I think that at least partially that responses the right way
Thoughts have to be a little laugh there is somewhere there is a part of me
If there's a Time
To take a break
And reflect and look at this
And go wow hasn't
It's right now
Next few months
Gearing up to do
The very seriously
The jury of very
Siri story about
People who's lied
Lucy there's where the anger comes from a little bit
Is that in the middle of this
Circus
Absurdity
Jones needs to be put down
That Institution
Trapped in some way
From the real
Gravity
And so when it comes time to put this on
This is obviously you
You know they're going to be
Media's going to be recording this trial
Talking about it
This trial is going to be done
I've been
Distracted for way too long
Yeah
Fantastic
That this trial
Is not going to be about Alex Jones
What Alex Jones did and what he's about as already decided
What does Charles is going to be about is about
Yeah that could be no better
MattyB moment
He thought was going to be his Circle
Could use for himself he don't even go
That is very kind of gratifying it now is something I do think that there is
Too much
Rickets
It's lost in you know Alex will blame but gun-grabbers and stuff for coming at him and
It's just the way it kind of I feel of deflecting from exactly what you're talkin about the the reality that at the core of this
This is these people
I've gone through something unimaginable
Yeah and I think you have to do that if you're
Someone in his position cuz how do you
How do you look in the mirror if you do
How do you deal with
There
Real grief and your part
Very challenge
That the thing he wants most is attention and that is the thing that is going to be denied him is
Delightful
It really is
We'll find a way of course he'll find a way but he's not on YouTube or Facebook as long as as long as none of the major
Your media Outlets go to Infowars
We're going to put you on TV
Then we'll be fine
Until then we always knew to it would be
It would be a suspect
Nicole without any
Of course it was going to be some
I was just
Cuz it brings me back at you something to Dan you said
About the steps
Positions in wider kind of soup
Is that if Infowars is what it is
And it is what they claim to be
I need the position should have been the most exciting
Because it was their chance to put up
What they had
They're saying they're right it's
Put up or shut up.
The time you really get
Throwdown
With you know some commie attorney like me
You get to like tell him in his place
Yeah you're
Braun look at all the stuff
And instead Jones
And do even were like not remember any down.
I did no preparation for this it gives me a headache I don't even want to do this this
I've never heard of globalism
Who the hell is Rob do
Became a
Experts such that it is
Hopes mythology
Anybody who believes this
Wolfgang halbig
And I was actually
Looking forward
Going toe-to-toe with somebody who's
And it didn't
Instead what we got from Jones was
You know
Jones-eez you said this before then you know I never said that hears video clip with you
You saying that. Saturday
Mortal Kombat X
Mute Media Matters edit
Like you can't get anywhere like
There was this idea
I think that was really observant of you both that
There's some things you can compost basically
Are there some admissions
Can get very quick
But that's done
There's not a lot of
Legal significance
It happens very quick
Culturally I think there is
And I think
You're going to see that
So where will get
I don't want to say
The show is over
You know what I mean like they're 30
For Jones that's going to happen
And it's in it's going to be
Personal
It's not just to be totally Folk
So there's still some more.
Wow
That's that's
Interested I don't know I don't know how to respond to that
Anything cuz it's such a testament to the families that they've been able to
Have the wherewithal to
Continue in the face
Like the
The difficulty of
Of living through
Play me the last three years of this case
Steven
I could not
I wouldn't fault somebody for saying this is enough I'm out
Yeah totally and it's
Is really
On some level for the for people who can't
Stand up to a bully
You know it's it's pretty
Pretty heartening that they have
Yeah well you know I'll tell you the right there are
Definitely family.
Who were The Waltons
Who don't want anything
You know who aren't
Of course
Completely respect that
Because why would you want to get into any of this
But it's really interesting that that my clients done in Texas
You know where you have
Minion veronique AniLinkz
Scarlet those are those are two families who were
Really heavily
I like they put up
Depositors address
Address to where they go pick up their mail I said they were
Starting up anti first
Terrorist organization that was coming after Infowars viewers day
They sending you a son with lying about holding his son
With a bullet holder hat
Oh crap
These clients are really stood up with their
Because they were these personal Target
To be able to make this fight on the
It's really been
A brave struggle
Minions Banana
Yeah
Weeks of this
The shooting he wrote
NSAID
Knock assault why are you doing this
This is Lenny
Is upfront about the
Like that
You know probably driving
What you drop Noah off that morning
We're driving away might have been listening in for
He was actually kind of into that
Sometimes don't realize is that
We're talking about
Years
Harassment
Followed by
3 years of the making a mockery of the Lost
Yeah
And the thing that I was always plays games with his that idea of like five years of harassment is like I didn't say all that stuff
For five years on Airtech well
It's that everyday you were saying the stuff on air it's the
They have been subjected to this harassment that was facilitated
45-year
I think you do some people who are
Really up to speed like we are on Joe
I understand that you said things were
Sandy Hook would probably think it was
It was a handful of occasions over a couple years.
Question
I have to address
You'll notice that if you watch the statement about
In reaction to the default judgment when things you said
And we don't
Because of
Not realize but
But because of
We bringing the suit
And then there shortly thereafter
YouTube and Facebook deleting all their profile
Infowars has a lost
Irreparably
A lot of it
Incontinent
So we kind of had
Play Sherlock Holmes using the public record try to figure out what videos were
Right now
Best estimate is that they made of
Episodes about
Sandy Hook
Nothing
We know that they made about 350
Pages of Infowars articles
About sand
And so
This is what we're averaging about two shows a month
Over the entire span of others sometimes when you get
2015 and 2017
Amor
But generally
5 years
Harassment
The people just don't know unless you're a real
Everybody seen the medium out of
Got when you really dig in there
Watch an hour and a half
Unscrew
Conversation
Jones and Wolfgang halbig
Will Frye
Rebel restore
You're one of the most prestigious policeman who's ever lived
All the time school safety experts
Call Mom
What is things like I mentioned the Justice Jones was
Was telling me about how
Credible
How big was Noah's like
So you've done Skype calls with how big
You seen how big
Home you seen how he lives
You know who this man is
At one point I even use I mean
I would never normally say in a deposition look you got 4,000 emails from them and reading them
You would agree with me this manager
But I normally wouldn't use that
Wolfgang halbig
You know book I don't
I don't think that I think that that state
In the matter of my
My opinion is not a state
The facts
But if Wolfgang how big is
Upset about that please please do me Wolfgang
Yeah
The number one question I get
These cases
Does Jones believe
And all I can do is put you to the
That's all I can do is point you to the public record
Into the deposition
And I think it becomes very clear
He never for a sec
You know Jones talks a lot about
Where's the observations you made it was very
Very observant
The idea of the media jumping on with both
Of this idea that you said it was a psycho
Clown
It's not really what he
He was making a metaphor
Anna was stupid
Crazy and it was
The dumb thing to say
But there are people out
There are people out there who
It popular
Tuitions
And an M the powers-that-be and then
Is the shity deal you get in life in America
Has made them distrust basically all fish
There's no question that that's a real
What happened to Alex Jones off of that
Understands that phenomenon in which to inflamed and Annex
Voided
Any good points
Justification
He is not
One of those people
He does not have that
No but I can
Everybody
I think I think that
He could still be a slight
Victim of that like that mentality
Inasmuch as he was getting caught up in it as he was
Producing that contact
And it was becoming more successful
Like
If he would just wasn't aware of what was going on and he wasn't aware he's not in touch with himself
Yeah yeah yeah
Find yourself snowballing a little bit
I do think there were radicalizing yourself at that point
He detaches from reality and just order free spins and in that way he made
Totally grounded
Like when he'll talk about an interdimensional shadow
I'm in there other times where I think he has somewhat convinced himself of
Amazon vs
You know some very Bass
World of Beer
Syrian chemical attack
Vince McMahon
But wouldn't
Sandy Hook
Not an opera
I don't believe Joe.
Ever believe
Or that there were
Stuart kids who are recruited to
Play the parts of
Different dead children and they were chatting
The scarier thought that I have is I don't think I ever cared about
The truth or falsity of it
Like the experience in the usefulness of
This claim is more important than whether or not it's true
Yeah that's really in
The level of
Conspiracy theory is is such that I have no doubt that
He was just on autopilot
You know like he wasn't even paying attention to the fake city was saying because
It's the same stuff he said
The last time
Rxpertise really hard
Is that
You can look at every
Single match
It follows
You can't really
One position I asking can you name me a mess cuz we've been eating
Didn't say was a false flag
I think maybe more the recent ones like the El Paso shooting and then on the podcast
We heard him do it over and over again
Use it as
When you have a person who's engaging in a course of conduct
That shows that
Consistent form of
Behavior to advance their business
You can assume that they made the same
The same justification
For this latest
Play music
With everything else they've ever done
The fact that he is within hours
Is going to call one of these events amass tragic
Dishes you didn't say Reckless
Disregard for the truth
Yeah anyting
Circle back to something we touched on a minute ago
It's not question
Things
Like there's such a distinction that he abuses
When he says like I was just questioning events you coming to conclusion
Advancing a conclusion
In the guise of pretending your question
Exactly
When you say
There were men arrested in
SWAT gear
If I didn't happen
It's not just you have a bad app
Radar
Or the another one that he'll try to do a trick on you is he
He will put it in a quest
But it will be a barrow b a y
You still beat your wife Quest
Yeah
Why were there why were there no paramedics allowed in the school
I'm just questioning
Yeah but your question is based upon a y that there were no Paramount
Creditzo
It's never a matter of
State Farm
A That's a classic clip of him saying that he had didn't believe it was fake at first
But then he looked into it deeply and it was all fake
All actors
And that's not question
No no
No it is not
I'm in Dexter somewhere
It's so unbelievably unequivocal
At first I thought they killed real kids
But now I know it's completely stage nysdol
Fully synthetic in bacon
Things but I never
Question didn't do tality of saying whether it
And you can play the clip right afterwards
Contacts
It's unbelievable that he can do it and invert for me I think what it came down to
24 Jones
Is
Okay so this is scary
Scariest
Is Mac
Ashley large
A lot of supplements
Could make him strong and
But
The thing that really scares me about him
Is it
Deduce
Perhaps correctly
That there are things
North Pole
More powerful more useful
In our current
Political dialogue
Then truth
Or verified
That there are
Magical narratives
That can represent what we
1 + 1
Hope to achieve in our Boudicca legenda
Better weigh more
So when the infowar how they're sick Supreme Court Justices who would say it's all about fairness and
Earning your way
I'm sure that it's about truth and honesty I guarantee
The scary part is that
I you know
Buckeye
You can probably imagine
You get involved
Attorney couple years ago
Start to get really enthusiastic
Changes that could
Not only am I going to do something
Maybe there is a a
Cultural change in how we
Talk about
And then over the past
3 years
What if I seen
In haseena a man who is
Been able to
To use
His own
Frivolous disrespect
To delay this process
There's no accountability
Over that same course
The time
All of his
More
Industry established
Contemporary
Begin copy
Are you done about Mitch McConnell
You know the one that Springs to mind
Only Timmy is Tucker Carlson
More like Infowars now
Then he did three years
He looks more like Infowars than Glenn Beck did in 2009
Stuff truth right at least at least back had this sort of pseudo
Stage production of his writing on chalkboards
Kind of silly
Terrifying
That's the same
But basically
Resume
Overlap that Alex will just play long segments of Tucker show on his show
It's right at home there
Somebody used to tell me there was one of my one of my colleagues Genevieve Zimmerman was involved with
Adidas
Lawsuits against Jim
In Michigan where
Mini Posner was able to
Willie defamation shooting
Jim Fetzer
Interesting.
Bike results
Refused
Staples
Toronto sort of birds of a feather flock together
Virginia
When she was
Helping out with closing arguments
Wine for Jake Zimmerman to use
Which was Colleen what Jones did in
Right opium
And I know I was really
Resonated with
That phrase
But then over the past
3 years
I told her that phrase no longer
Works B
Because it's not alright
Opium anymore
It's right opium
There's no
That what Jones did and what his
Flavor for how to manipulate facts and stuff
Is now just
Lingua Franca for the entire conservative
It does feel like that and I also think like just from my sense of things just from my looking at everything
I don't think that
He may even be aware of that
Like Vicky
Have discovered something more powerful than truth
Right now discovered it necessarily but he knows what he's doing
Ultimately we have a problem
That's you had
In the depositions which is this
They know
You know they're lying
You know they know they're lying
So all there is the only question is are you going to tell me that you were lying or not
So Alex is going to not say that he's lying and he'll accept
Any default judgment anything
Because then he doesn't have to say what everyone knows and why he's in the courtroom I'm lying
Sing to you that's right
You know it's y'all didn't a discussion of perjury in civil vs. criminal cases
That was dead on point that if I was a criminal lawyer
I could I could
Rosti Speedwagon album against the wall and no time
But here in Cibolo it's different
You're the best thing that I
I can do
Is to hopefully make sure the jury understands
Zuerlein
Because the reaction is DM
I bet you could probably fully demonstrate quite a bit of that vary based on those depositions
Absolutely
No it's it's going to be really
Have you seen them react
Yeah
How's the one thing we touch down the we haven't gotten to yet I was really hoping to get your perspective on was
How you felt
The coverage of the case
Was
Do you feel like
The the
The media at Large
I focused on the right points do you feel like
I think
One of the things that's definitely become very interesting to me
Over the course of the time that we've done this podcast
Is seeing how people cover Alex
Bright and seeing the ways in which
Sometimes unforced errors and then sometimes people
You know are like this is
They they got the right point there
To the first part
Do I think the media has
Typically gotten this right
No I do not
And that's that's a shame
I wanted to meet you at
Boat rentals Jonesboro
Clickbait media editors know that if they have a story but I was shown in the Sandy Hook lawsuit
Clicks psychosis
Same deal and end
Big prompt remind look I'm not
A lot of people would say alright well if you're getting my cupboard wrong or usually
Almost always
Getting it wrong in a way that's critical to Alex Jones maybe that'd be good
No no
The problem is is that Jones
Nose very itchy
But his ability to identify
Mistake
It's made by the mainstream media
Is is one of his best
Overshoot the Target on Jones uses as a way tomorrow
There was
In fact that so I was just talking about the Jim Fetzer verdict up in
Michigan
A lot of newspapers ran a story that that was Alex Jones
You got that
And Jones got on the show and made
Mainstream you look stupid
He said he was going to sue the Associated Press
There's even a lot of threats of lawsuits
All over the place
Place that never materialized but
Always gives him a good sounding boy
To say
Being accurate when these people aren't being accurate about me
Good point
Who was Jones never understood about me person
Is that I'm not
Those media that's not I'm not
Allied with them you give me a CNN Story defaming one of my clients I'm still in seeing it in a heartbeat
Insurance policy
Lawyers who don't mess around or going to pay
Help with Discover it
Boston bombing when the to Egypt
Young men were identified on the front page
New York
Has a great
Reputation in terms of things like that and
Reliability
But they've got a big insurance policy they've got lawyers they got a lot somewhere
They took care of those young men without him
The exact same situation in this case I'm not sure if you are aware of the other suit that I'm handling right
I know
The first one
Was Marcel Fontaine as a young man in Boston who was falsely identified as being the park
REI
Same deal as
I mean worse than what happened Egyptian kids because they were just like their pre people Adventure
They might
Marcel and said here's the guy
WhatsApp
Communist team t-shirt
Exactly yeah they took a a post off of porch and reported it
With no cooperation
Wish app
They do that a bit
Weave weave weave sabudana number of instances of
That kind of
Journalistic integrity
Yeah
And it's it's it's day or even
Eunos even one point Jones was trying to Define what a source wasn't deposition
Source can be you know
Hey I have a dream
That's basically 4K
The bathroom wall unit
Journalism should be protected to the extent that if I see Jane
Copper a good time call Jane Smith on a bathroom wall I can go in the paper and Report Jane Smith
This is in the public interest
You're just asking questions about what's going on with James question
The people were talking about
Right2know
Someone
And I want passionate enough to write on a bathroom wall
We've got one of the most important whistleblowers in the world their information is so powerful they couldn't put
Anywhere but a bathroom stall
So is it's funny that in Neil heslin
They were relying off
Relied
Excited
A blog post
From a Blog called zerohedge
Run libertarian Financial freak out
I beg your pardon all of the articles are written by Tyler Durden
Right on
How to blog post saying that new husband didn't help hold his kid and they end in that
Blog post itself
Cited Jim Fetzer so it's just garbage in garbage
Arbitrate
But that was the Broncos and then
Owen Shroyer gets on put that on air and says hey I'm just
Portland 10
20 at Broncos
You can see the page
You have three shares
At that moment
Red Lake
Nobody in the world
Obviously
Zerohedge
Say that you're
District
Reporting on what other
People are saying so I'm just going to
Bring on Old doctor
Steve p
Just let him go
And you know what
You're doing you knew we'd we have the emails that are in the
This case has been filed with the court
Before they put.
Christian they know exactly what he's going to stay in encourage
Say it
And you got you got to get him in a deposition. I want it so bad
We would do a whole series of episode forgotten everything
So you can't get to a Johnny Bravo would be a
A wonderful guy to have Maya
You know this whole thing but yeah.
BP is a great character
If
If you could ever get Alex back under oath I'd like you to ask him if he believes he's fighting the literal devil
I don't like I think it might be unprofessional for you to do but it's something I'm very curious how you would answer umbrella
Mine don't you mean
He's let me to believe through listening to the show that he definitely believes he's fighting the literal Christian devil
Yeah the literal one yeah exactly
From his standpoint
Do I smell like sulfur
Can you sing
You're you're assuming
That we don't seem massive
The court in the next couple weeks
Your wish will be granted
He's currently set to
Me to post again
I can't wait
I hope I hope that video ends up on YouTube as well
But here's the other thing you have to remember is that
When I suppose
Call Joseph Austin you saw that I had
Proceedings they have not yet
I was
Blind
Completely blind
News based on my own research
Nowhere the varied
Yeah we have
So you know a lot of them the song and dance that a lot of
People saw
Was was Jones
Hemming and hawing about who dhanbad Auntie was and whether.
Whether you sent the cracker
Harassed
The people in my life
Flirty hired him and she calls him to crack out about
Nevermind it was my frustration with
Without Jones talks about
He's publicly and how
It comes out the depositions and all of this when you don't have the
It still say
Yeah we got rid of them and only we didn't like what
He was doing up there Newtown
We have to get rid of them
Six weeks later we get the emails and it shows
No they were still paying them through 20
They fired
Embarrass
Demeter Trump rally
He was dumb
Making some inappropriate comments to a female
Conservative journalist
Trump rally
Media Outlets
We got to make sure
We can still get into trouble
Didn't care
Denver Donnie chase the bunch people around Newtown
I didn't care
Wolfgang halbig
Where you got how big
Showing up in a white unmarked van
Video of children of the
Now put
He was a Madman after the Boston bombing press conference
After he disrupted that and got so much traffic to Infowars
What you realize
Owen Shroyer tried to make the same work
He basically tried to do the same thing
Yeah with the the impeachment
Exactly right now and that's why
Indeed a water things that we brought up at our last
Is we were granted in 2018
We were granted an order
Saying that we were supposed to have Owen step
Along with several other
We never got
They they refused to
And now I'm in a position of
Who are really want own Shores deposition and I'm not sure I'm going to get it
Cuz there's a very good chance
If you could be in federal custody
Angus right now
He's in a situation where he's
Facing
Is charged
Leesburg for breach of
Normally be that serious except
He did it at year ago and didn't show up
Community service
We told the judge to look we're concerned not only about that deposition but that's why we want this
Position of Jones
October
Is because we're a little worried
If you looking Shroyer's arrest affidavit
With all the pictures of Owen Shroyer being places
Not supposed to be
Jones standing right now
Yeah
We're speaking in a recipe
I wouldn't I wouldn't expect anything from Alex
Because the reason that I went got in trouble was because he had a restraining order
That's because he didn't do the community service
He was barred from being like in all of those places
You're being there with him
I don't think it matters as much because he didn't have that like sort of
Yeah yeah so that's who wasn't trespassing
That's the theory anyway
Save-A-Lot
Whatever they could get Jones off off of those
Pictures is such a minor crimes did not eat
Even be worth the trouble
So you can tell more than anyone else it would be
But I think
I think we've all seen enough mafia movies to know what why the federal authorities
Might go arrest somebody
Owen Shroyer
I think we know what Thursday
About what Owen Shroyer
A could lead to see
Yeah yeah
You follow the crazy
We want that I patched
Oathkeeper is where we start
Bring me to Donuts
I didn't think about it as it is
It's a distraction to my case
Right. Great job just
Criminal stuff going on
Alongside of
Exit is a destroy
Then I want this
Because it is pretty families they're ready
Boy are they ready just now
You know this isn't a couple years ago we got him to admit under oath
Those are like a big step
That's one step
Yeah
Find me maybe
I don't I don't know
I was getting real pessimistic imma be honest
Procedures to the end of the Earth and grind diamond
I've never questions
But
Was it actually going to make it
Different stadia buddy anyway
Whitley I mean first
Could I make a difference from my own clients
Could we even collect from him all those
But then I started seeing
Joshua start seeing Coronavirus
Started senior
50 absolute insanity
Of the
The false facts being put out there
When I saw January 6th go down the big lie around the election
Are we too far gone
Did the diesel suits need to be brought
Several years ago or
Or is this too late what's going on
Ability the last couple weeks
I'm feeling a little more up
Taken notice of this
I bet there's a real-life feeling of exhaling you know like that
At least on some level I feels like you're on the way up
At least instead of on the way down to even lower wherever it can go because you're at the mercy of some
Somebody who's dragging their heels as long as they're allowed to drag their heels
Exactly
And once
The you know
The judge orders know he'll dragon
Bath
Then everything starts moving a lot quicker
One of these things to the accursed me about it is like 3 years later and
It's funny they are
I feel I feel pretty good about
How I've handled this case
I feel like I've done some really good work in it
But
The truth of the matter is they are
I think anybody
I think anybody who spends bit of time
Listening to Infowars or knows it
Semi-critical Leawood
Never expect anything other
You know like I do feel like
They would always be the
Root of there
Yeah I think
That's true when Jones was really mad after our death
And talked about me for
For couple hours
What are things you were saying is you know
They're all calling his lawyer the new Perry Mason
School
Honestly more most credit goes to you man like
I wish I could take
More depressed than I am
But it really is
A man who is so
Self-destructing
And almost a
Epic Greek tragedy sort of way
Yeah
I'm just here as a
The conductor on the train like I'm just a driving up to
Sensation
At this point there's not a note terms to be made
The track going to one place
Going down
When we go back to the 2003 episodes there is a certain feel of like
You're looking at the man who is inexorably going to wind up where we are right now you know like
His behavior then
Will eventually lead to where we are now
What's going to happen
I saw that you're looking at
Some of those earlier episodes
Then I haven't I mean it takes me back to my college days you know
In ut
99-2000
That's what Joe said become kind of huge
From
Public Access
What's the weather yesterday
And I really wanted now go back to listen
The some of those episodes
Stussy
Embryonic chaosity
Study Island
One of the reasons we went over he interviewed a guy who had gone to heaven
And it was
Is fantastic
I think there's a waiting room in heaven
Your best friend is here imaginary friend and he's also the guy who's snitching on you to God is your guardian angel
Is your childhood imaginary buddy
Becomes obvious to me when I'm watching
Videos you watch a video on 2013 versa
2015 vs 2017
The Setzer differ
You see the evolution of the show through its set
And now it's this
Big
Gotti Cinema can set
It's funny to me how
There are so many things that I know from what I think of Jones from what I came up with them in the
Is not who he is
Today cuz to me
Jones is the guy who's
About to be in tears over the alien fish hybrids
Humanize
It's so silly it's so in people
For so many years people made viral video clips and stuff that we're just making fun of these silly things out
Sex and then somewhere along the line
And it happened
Almost
I mean
Jonas face tan on Sandy Hook looking both directions
From Sandy Hook
Completely
He's starting to Edge into a completely
He's not just so he's not a lizard person silly
Jeffron Style
Absurdity
Notice something more Sinister beak
Portrayed as hardener
I'd like
Movie showing my jury a lot of videos from eminent
2000 talking about
Gay frogs
Fish hybrids
Crap
Because what they need to see is that ever since then in the last 4 years
He's trying to sound softball
What is legit news
How many times a day in four sets you're getting the real truth he ran Infowars the
Tomorrow's news today
Oh wow yeah yeah
News of the future from 6 months ago
Tomorrow's new soften blog post
6 months ago
Orwellian about
Tomorrow's news today right like
This idea that that
He's creating himself
Oh man
I had one question that I definitely needed to ask you
I want to jam this in
And is that
What's your favorite Sunday
That was it
And Alex's defense after these default judgments came out
He said that in this case
The opposing counsel was demanding that he produce something he referred to as
Sandy Hook marketing material
What can you talk a little bit about what he could have been referring to
He's mostly talking about the Laffer
Medication kinetic
You must've talked about that
Did something happen
Not even with what just happened
In other words
Discovery request that were at issue in
Is that made him default the case
None of this has any
Connecticut
They had asked him
It wasn't really sandy
Marketing
Basically what it was
Is they wanted
Any
For any episode that Sandy Hook
Discussed about
They wanted Infowars internal animals
They wanted to know
What did they get off of Google ads what did they get how many hits
And then
Infowars also uses things like a
Internal Google analytics program
It has some other message
Is there any wanted to request
What's that makes sense
Pretty fair
View
It's right because
If you want to establish how these p
People were damaged
You have to know how many
Great Lakes open Total audience
Infowars is important
Did they ask for also I think if they had
If there were any
Emails that referred to special marketing initiative
And by that I mean
Special promotional page or we're going to
Can you make sure on this video can
Can you promote some Sandy Hook videos
They've been really popular
Obviously
Rasher
You have to remember that
Infowars
Revenue and
Set
Ultimately
Quartz not a very
Yeah we're not like Haiti
Can you produce a supermarket
Getting director that you don't have
Yeah and the way he'd be robbed
Being robbed
Rob do in a silly hat
Demanding that I bring like
Then like these flyers that we printed up with
Sandy Hook sale going on
No I mean there is
There's obviously a lot of when you're up
A digital web business
Publishes on the web you're going to have some
Statistics about
What happened
Shenandoah things
But what's what's mind-blowing about it
Is that is that in my case we aren't even there yet
Like we have
We have just recently got
Sarda broke some of those is
But in my case it's like
Okay it would be a simple request
But they're not answer
Identify every video in which
Infowars discuss the
That. Has never been answer
He's our very very soon
Simple thing
And and that was what I think was most shocking door judge
You have these
Request that were supposed to be answered in 2018 like at the very beginning of the case
You can even start
Feeling your way around in the dark
Red Lake like this is so basic
Burton Lake
He has been unjustly
Had his right to a jury taken away
This is
Yeah
I agree I was just be kept here is that one of the sticking point so that's the marketing material
But there's something out there they just want to give us
Really is focused on the post-sandy hook marketing
And why you so hung up on
It might just be that he doesn't understand what he's being at
You ever run at Sandy Hooks
50% off sale
It's probably question he doesn't know the answer to and Emily doesn't want to find out the other two
Would have done that so I just don't want to find out
I do I do love I do love the judge
Being surprised when you ask that question
Give me all the videos where you have said something about Sandy Hook and the judges surprised they didn't do it
Immediately my thought was just like
Oh they said that sounds really hard
And just didn't do it
How could you guys be surprised by that I know these people they said that's hard
I won't do it and then maybe you'll go away
It's hard
It's half of
We've been so insanely negligee
Persons being sued that we have
Cause massive amounts of Evan
El favor
Do really fully just be up
Mr.
Yeah yeah
You know that's going to be as for those
People who I know your audience is
Go to watch the
The challenge going forward is
If there's any more shenanigans
How exactly do you punish
Right like there's not much more you
Do it
Yeah that was a that was a question I had in my head to like you know
Because you still have the process that you have to go through in terms of
Getting to the jury deciding
Stop.
Damages
Absolutely
He does have the some ability to drag his heels on that still
Absolutely.
Eleanor would cause other crazy problem
You got to remember Mike Mike plaintiffs are going to be
Some of the things are going to be
Testifying about
Confidential Private health
Information
And they've already made a mockery of that stuff up in kinetic
You know they
How detached from reality to
The strategy has become
Is they were in the middle of
Deposing a plaintiff
Sandy Hook
Brighten the deposition itself as designated
Confidential
Attorneys izone
I started the Depo
Is it doesn't get released
In the middle of that deposition Norm Pastor lawyer
Streaming
Basically
Was he started writing down the things
The plaintiff was saying
The continental testing
Inserted that into a motion
And then filed that motion
Publicly with the
The court on the court docket where everybody can
And okay so not a part of
This is going to make you just your jaw dropping
This is not only is that insane
The motion
But he was filing
With a motion to request that
The court compel the deposition of Hillary
Yes because apparently according to Jones
These lawsuits the only reason they happened
Because Hillary Clinton wasn't mad
For some reason my cat
About two years after she lost the election
She decided to go recruit
Attorneys
In Sandy Hook families 2
Pursue a vendetta against Alex Jones not apparently I'm under Clinton payroll and all this
What does not sound like something a malignant narcissist would invent Africa crazy
I think I think he thinks that
Hillary said he had a black heart
Or something and then that was the sign that
She's coming after Amber but
In Jones's own
Fever
Construction of all of the
Hillary Clinton is a big reason
Why he said some of the things he said about
Particularly after
Used him as a prop
To attack Trump
And to say Trump's Associated this guy in this guy's a mess right and this guy said
Everything she said about a 100
True
But she was using him very clearly as a
But
But once he did that that in raged
That was it
Because
Jones at that point was on this
Decorative beaker
Barry
Mainstream
He adhered got Trump on his show
He was being credited at that time with Trump victory
And so that's why
Just after the election
In November right after you
He did a broadcast
Cold
Alex Jones
Final
Basically couldn't stop talking about it cuz Hillary talked about him so he had to respond back
So his
Genius idea
What you get on there and go will look here's all the reasons I thought it was fake
And
Honestly if it hadn't been for that
Like some of this case would never
If it is the parents they were of the
Position that
If Jones is stopped
After 2016
They probably wouldn't have pursued this
Right but it was this Vendetta that kept up
Is that not only did he do it then
But then just a couple months later in the new year
Video call Sandy Hook vampires
Yep that's the one that
Use my clients of Faking It
2017 and he just can't stop
Disparities Socastee
Also rough name
I would out fire River name these videos
Sandy Hook vampires exposed
Doesn't look good just as a title
You know they're like I mean I can understand him being mad at Hillary
Been his villain for
Jordan years
Also she lost and ruined everybody's life
I'm sure he's mad at her about that
Well I I don't know if there's any other points you want to get to but I feel like
Media is not
Said at all that you want to that you feel like there's some information that nobody has really touched on
Really surprised that nobody in the media reported
Tetanus
Is is November 27th on Starz November 29th
18 deposition
The second episode
That he ended that deposition
By saying
Anatomies
Is like you you have made this
You understand what a mockery you've made of this that you're willing to do that at the end of that deposition
Promotional
During that deposition
He was so eager to talk
Talk about a really really wanted
During the deposition no don't work
I believe there's a player like I promise we'll get back to you
Robin
There were several points in there where his eyes glaze over
Cuz he doesn't know what's happening
God I'm agreeing with the boss
This thing this guy saying right now I don't know what to do
I'm sitting there telling him like I think you and I agree that most of the
The people who run the
This world who are the ruling class
Tree in the world
Are mainly psychic
Criminal
I do
Because of course
Ask me if something
Bribed
Really really interested
I'm a democratic
We were talking a little bit about his motion to depose Hillary Clinton and his sort of
Obsession
With this idea that these lawsuits were entirely motivated by Hillary Clinton's Vendetta against
Yeah persecution complex
It's weird because it's like do you think there's really that
Shortage of
Many people who would love to do these lawsuits
Call me Hillary only Hillary could hate me there's no one else in the world who could want to be
Bring me down right
Funny because okay so just come inside me
This is that as a plaintiff's lawyer
What I do is
Is is when people come to me for help
They don't pay me anymore
Write like I'm sort of
Need like a pirate right like
Somebody comes to a pirate and says the Spaniards took all my gold and I want you to go get it back and I like okay all outfit of fast
Pokemon guns I'll try to go get
Gold
I'm keeping a third of it
And all front any expenses and if I don't get the gold you don't owe me anything
You're working on spec
Is they say immediate in the industry
Your privateers lawyer say it is you know you talked
These lawyers who bill by H me
You say that's not me I'm a claims lawyer
Eat what I kill
That's basically how I
So for most of my case
If I'm involved in a medical device case or if I've got a product case I've got to pay experts
You know my firm were putting in 200,000 to 50 into a case before we see a diamond
And try to make that up
How's it cost
And an honest issues differin
And Jones is convinced
We funded by biliary Clinton
We've been really upfront about it since the beginning my for a handball is
It's funded every expense on this we're happy to do it we're excited to do it
There's not many law firms
To do what I do who wouldn't
Love
Do this
Have you forever you produce the Hillary Clinton marketing materials
Request for production of oh my George Soros
They never figured out
Looking yellow out
Interesting look at the
The law firm up there in Connecticut
The cost cough
The nerve area button
Barry
Normal kind of Law Firm very
You know Hauser
Advertise on really nice
I'm the guy on up
Profane podcast about our children
Slightly different approaches
I'm a little bit
The different lawyer I don't think they realize
I came into their lives
Representing a young Communists out of Masa
And not send your cousin a came to me because I brought a suit on behalf
And
I am not
Hillary Clinton
That's there's no way shape
Reformed but they never get this
The entire Infowars organization is
Is convinced
All about aquatic
Vendetta
When when
Really they just open themselves up
Yeah
It's a terrifying combination of just like narcissism and black and white
You know Alexis absolute sand
Everyone is against me because I'm the greatest
Global politics all the time thinking that he's a big-time show but really he only knows like 10
So
Okay so who's bringing this lawsuit I don't know any of these people so it's got to be
One of the 10 people I know
Yeah when you have that simple of a world
View it just you cram everything into
Run out of character
It's just really small place in his head it's like a sitcom with a low budget
Locations not a lot of characters Style
My other kind of final thoughts and this is address to the State Bar of Texas when they finally review this
And listen to me talk on this
Listen guys
I know we've we've been a little
Loosen wild today in little profane here
I know that I did my
My invitations H Jones I know it did a couple of those
Just wanted for the record he imitated me first
So I think it's fair
He compared me to Golem
Gremlin
And I just that hasn't happened yet cuz I'm
I am number one who's going to buy 10 yeah
He started it
Okay so I just don't want that to be fair for the State Bar he started it
End
It has been a situation where is
His public statements have been absurd
For somebody
Look
I have the up
Opportunity to be on National Television whenever I want
If someone was talked to said he'll call you it's going to
Fairly infra
You know I vibe
When we first started I went on the Today Show the very first time
I've done PBS Frontline appearance
About this issue to talk about it
Belmont like we don't
That's not where we're fight
And Anna went to come talk about it with y'all's audience
Your audience is never going to be on the jury
If there's anybody want to know which fight they're getting taken off the jury
Very strong feelings and will not be
Not worried about influencing the jury for anything
Then I'm going to come talk about it with y'all because I feel like
The suit has been really interesting
The Wider culture
And not enough
Really hard analysis
Being done on it not enough
A real bat
Patriots
And I know y'all guys come out like that
Have fun with it
But y'all are doing a really
A lot of
People have learned a lot more about
From now on
Don't know man
Overwhelmed to hear that and thank you that we read a lot
Place here I was talking to a friend last night about how we were going to do this interview and I was like
Man I hope he doesn't compliment us
That's the thing I'm most anxious about this today
I'm going to go on a show
There are
Adore
You can count on one hand
The number of
People in the world who know more about
Alex Jones tonight
And I'm currently talking to
I don't know I think you could use some callbacks
I bet I bet you know more about Alex Jones at most but you're probably not in the top 5
Somewhere in my head I don't have action I don't have like the ability to call it whenever I want.
Narcissistic
I'll take it
Well thank you so much for joining us Mark I hope it's some point we can reconnect and maybe check in and
Another time
Well I'm sure look up if if else comes on and some more crazy
Stuff between now and trial I love to come back and
Talk to you about that we
Taco bout it
But otherwise
Let's try to plan on me having a verdict
Sometime near the end of April
And we'll come back and talk about what that mean
Awesome maybe right in time for my birthday
Thank you again it's been an absolute Delight to talk to you and wish you and everyone
On your side of the case all the best
We're going to keep doing what we can do
Awesome thank you
Thanks
Wow
That was hallucinating
What are the odds that was a lot of fun thank you so much to mark for for joining us and having that little
Spectacular
Spectacular job
Congratulations to I think I'm not sure if we articulated that it
Enough in our conversation but like
It's gotta just feel great
Do you Snapchat. Come to a close
And just she ran and just
Talking to him you know like
He pulled it off
Like he hadn't spent the last four years in hell
You know
Like you pulled it off like this wasn't a crushing miserable thing to do on a date
Daily basis filled with abuse
Bulshit
And it looking like it might never end you know any f***
Can get it
Hell yeah maybe a little bit of that humor armor can help a little
But Jordan we are not just here
To have an interview
I would mark
Bankston we are also here
Do discus Alex's immediate response
But he put out the night that these
Now these yes I do summary judgment
Default judgment came around
Answer you put out he put out a little piece
And it's not good
It's it's not not very compelling
Piece of business
Turn on that one I was on Norm isn't there
Watching Alex just drunkenly spiral
Here is where we're at
If the last
The left in this country
Has completely
Weaponize the legal system
And the Judiciary
There's so many examples of
But
Just last few days
Decorated
Lieutenant colonel
Who came out in
Criticize the hasty
Horribly organized
Withdrawal Afghanistan
Is sitting in a military Stockade in a Brig in a prison
Without
Even being
Charged with
And he's already been there
Five Guys
This is about Lieutenant Colonel Stuart scheller criticized the administration's handling of the withdrawal from Afghanistan
A video that you posted on Facebook
He was relieved of command and put in the brig at Camp Lejeune North Carolina
Awaiting trial
He's pretty messed up and I can see how this would worry
Anybody but has nothing to do with the last
Or the Judiciary
This has to do with how they're different rules of
Conduct when you agreed to enlist in the armed services
Their military rules
Reply to you and
Not to not enlisted persons when you break them
Different sort of trouble
Peter Marshall lost yeah yeah
You can't even really say no to him
Because he violated a gag order after being relieved of command by posting the video she put on Facebook salaries accused
Quote showing contempt towards officials willfully disobeying a superior officer
Failing to obey lawful orders and committing conduct Unbecoming of an officer
I can agree that it might be a productive conversation to discuss how weird it is that the military has b-zone rule that it has for its my
Members to be subjected to
But in terms of Alex's response to
He's getting on air to talk about losing these multiple Sandy Hook cases
Nothing to do with anything
I was about to say if I was directing this I would have been like Alex
Quick cut
Alright
We're going to start over
Okay we're going to take this again it's just real quick
We're talking about your Sandy Hook lost
Track a little already left
Okay if this is the way he's deciding to start discussing list
I don't have a lot of faith that this is going to keep going
Or reach anywhere
I know you everybody's read the news they are not talking about is that it is still fat bear
And the week
Spells that bear should be held sacred
I could be clear about this I think Alex is you'll be more productive and less dangerous if he did discover fatbearweek have everybody
And have a much better time
This this is not good
Okay I thought I thought like well we're not going to get a whole lot here
But we do get right off the bat is
A little bit of a confused timeline of events
Now you go back almost 10 years ago
We saw the tragic shootings at Sandy
It was hard for Americans to believe that someone would go into execute
A bunch of Elementary
The internet quickly had questions and talked about anomaly
It was something that I
Only a few times on here
But what
Years later
Evidence came out with some of those anomalies were not accurate and I said Sally Sandy Hook actually happen
It was the minute
That I said I thought it happened that the
The mainstream media center
You said it didn't happen for attention
What a truth
Almost had employees quit over it
I want people to scream with me including some of my family
And it was not
A popular fuel my show
I can speak as someone who listen back to the entire period after the shooting and with absolute confidence I can say that that's
Bulshit
It's a good spin for Alex because most people won't actually go back and check idiots like Joe Rogan
Didn't fall for this kind of line but
That is definitely false
But even leaving that aside that clip makes no sense
I was just trying to make to claim simultaneously and it's really hard for both of them to be true
The first is that he barely ever talked about Sandy Hook maybe just a few times
The news just covering what the internet was saying
And the second thing is trying to claim
Is it the coverage of Sandy Hook was so unpopular that some of Alex's family disagreed with him
And staff almost quit because of
That's in convoluted I don't know how both of those can actually be
He's accurate are retelling of events
Over it that he never talked about it again until several years later whenever he finally said that
Believe that happened then everybody was like
Haha now it's time to take you to
What what are those years in between
I mean he mentioned it maybe
200 * I mean yeah but I mean
But other than that
Have a very few times you're the one being obtuse here
Get off my damn high horse I should probably stop thinking like
Hey
I was just questioning things man
Toledo
Forward right
So the idea that I
Question Sandy Hooks
Because it was some
Master plan of mine to get famous
I questioned wmds in Iraq
I was right about that
Why should babies in incubators Banks robbed by Saddam that wasn't true either
I questioned Jessie Smollett and that was a fraud I question
Bubba Wallace I question
Hundreds of other events
Out there
The Gulf of Tonkin
9064 that got us into Vietnam
First of all no one's claiming that Alex had a grand design to get rich and famous by way of lying about Sandy Hook or at least that's not a matter
For the courts
Immediately
Plant that idea in his audiences head because it's more defensible strawman than dealing with reality
Alex's list of things he's questioned is a little bizarre though
For one I don't think he was the one who questioned the Gulf of Tonkin incident if only because it happened 10 years before he was born
Yeah but he was the first person to really look into it
Second the cases of Jesse Smollett Bubba Wallace are the only two recent examples he comes up within those are both time
Times that he just had a knee-jerk denial but allegations of racially motivated crimes
If you listen to our show you'll find way more examples of times when Alex was very wrong
But denying racist violence
Bring those times I thought know you're always batting a thousand so long as you pretended all the times that you struck out didn't happen
And that's what his audience allows him to do it
What a
What a cheat
100%
100 well now he does get things wrong he's either 97% or Alex is playing
Propaganda with a Game Genie
Now we roll
That one was definitely that one's definitely world the one large issue his comment
There's another one that is that Alex is not questioning things
Succumbs to
Conclusion
Who be one thing if Alex's coverage was what he imagines it was
Who still be dumb and dangerous but if he was drily reporting that online conspiracy communities had questions about Ali
Alleged irregularities in the Sandy Hook case
That could be argued to just be questioning
What else was doing was persuading which is different than questioning
Questioning seeks truth
Through asking sometimes unpopular questions
Persuade
Conclusion that the audience is supposed to be drawn to
And often times you can ask a loaded question
As a tool that you can use and the path of your persuasion
And that's what I
Jack West music
Yeah that's why in court you can't do that is called the leading question
You're not allowed to do it
The way if if Alex wasn't guilty of stuff
Then he would be able to do the same stuff he does
In the courtroom
The fact that he can't do any of the things he does
The moment he steps into a place where it means something to tell you all you need to know that seems to happen over a note
Over and over again with all these people yeah
Dialysis career snowbigdeal
Look Maya please
No big deal
Sandy Hook is
A blip on the radar screen
In the different
Story for tens of thousands I've cover
But it's not a blip
On the radar screen
The Lobby's that are anti-gun the big
Corporate institutions that seek
The disarming America
The families of those
Oh you didn't
You did not.
Remington into bankruptcy
And the demonize the idea of shelter
The fence itself
I did try to basically destroying Steel
The birthright of self-defense
All Americans that's just so f****** callous in the ass insults that's insane
His act like it because he's saying that his actions are just like a blip in his career
But it wasn't a blip to the evil gun-grabbers that it did he's against
They're round every Court like your response is exactly the same thing that I was experienced and I was looking for that
Yeah you know who else it wasn't a blip for people who lost their loved ones you a******
This is
Crazy
But what he's literally doing in that sentence
Is denying that there were victims at Sandy Hook
He's at least ignoring it
And then another thing he's doing is he's taking away their agents
The gun grabbers are trying to play
There are literally real yes but their intentions are fake
Against their concerns are being weaponized by the gun grabbers
Anyways that
Would lead one to believe if you believe Alex that their concerns aren't real early on that is f****** discuss
If you if you meant
Any of what you said about
Any of what you're saying right now
UTA
I'm sorry to the victim
Yes
Also this is like a supervillain
Talk
Like this is like
It was just a blip in my career
You'll never forget nothing to me
Unreal unreal
F****** yeah that was where I was like well we're off the rails
That's going in the money hearing play that s*** right there
Even after a f****** lost he's pretending
Yeah
I can't
See any possible way that's true but I will give him a shout
Even their top legal expert says
He's definitely sanction
Basically a myth
Because you're guaranteed
To be able to try the
Facts of the case
So this is a legal Theory they're trying to get through
To get rid of due process
Using
The strawman of the demonized villain
Alex Jones
Listen dangerous everybody
Making process
Everybody's Free Speech
Wow
The bacon have the Alex
Jones law they call it
To get rid
Of people free speech selectively
While protecting the corporate media is Free Speech
I thought I'd history Works everybody
It's going to get burned by this this is nonsense
Alex has been given excessive due process and given every opportunity
And he showed himself to be unwilling at every turn
Symbicort depriving Alex of his right to Tim's shooting himself in the foot
In the court order for default judgment they specifically say that they have gotten no response and Discovery request 10th July set
Second which was months ago
Unicourt failing it's Alex's sabotage
It's pretty funny to like the order makes it clear that this is not a lawyer problem
It's Alec
Quote
It is clear to the court that Discovery misconduct is properly attributable to the client and not the attorney especially since defended
Has been represented by attorneys over the course of the suit
Regardless of the attorney defendants Discovery abuse remained
Also The Huffington Post article that Alex was talking about with wasn't quoting their top legal expert
They were quoting Bill Ogden
Who's the lawyer at Ferrari in Belle which is the law firm that Mark Bankston works at
The guy who he referenced was doing the Rob deposition
Even right next to each other on the law firm's website
This isn't a lawyer saying that to this is just a legal Theory
You saying that it's taught that way at law school because it almost never happens
Quote
It's extremely rare that a party in the parentheses Alex Jones Infowars
He's ordered by the court.
To comply with discovery
Obey with multiple orders
And then continues to blatantly disregard the court Authority bike
Continuing
To refuse to comply
Yeah it's
It's like if
Let's say okay
How about this okay so I murdered somebody
And then I took the knife home with me
And they arrest
Stickman they were like okay
You just got to bring that knife
And then we'll get this all done with
No and everytime I didn't bring the knife and I was like nah I'm just not going to go
I never liked okay football
We have to do something so I guess there's a fine or maybe
Just bring the f****** night
And then I was like nah nah how about instead I go stand outside your courthouse and wagon my dick in your face
And then holding the knife above my head and then throwing it around and then spinning
And then
Whenever you grab me
And arrest me and put me in jail
What were the top of due process this talk Rob due process
There's my one punch.
Tell Alex Watkins at the records
Straight he's giving everybody everything
He's getting he's been the king of discovery
A judge issued default judgments a rarity in the legal World against Jones and Infowars
Has failed to produce Discovery Records
Ladies and gentlemen first let me set the record straight
My lawyer told me in Connecticut
They said you shouldn't even
Produce with the rat
No one's ever done
I release all of my company bank records going back to Sandy Hook It Up Until Now
No one has ever done that
So it sounds like Trump at the end there no one's ever done anything like this is the best lawsuit anyone's ever
So we talked to t'mark a little bit about this and this cares has nothing to do with the cases he lost that's in the Connecticut
This is just sort of like
Again
Rowing
Confetti if it is a shotgun blast of b*******
A10e wallet
It might stick
So Alex thinks that there is a case is really about trying to prove that he's paid by the NRA
Are the Mercers or somebody
Is just another side deflection
They have this weird crazy theory that I'm secretly being paid off by
The NRA or something to do this
Let them see all
Let them see there's no money from the Mercers are the NRA
Are the Republicans or anybody
And so
We did that because the judge in Connecticut demanded
Right here in Texas is all coordinated
They asked for less but was still substantive
Tens of
Email thousands of record
But they kept demanding the Sandy Hook
Marketing
I don't do marketing around Newsweek cover
I products and sponsors that I
Promote and market for
And we gave them in Connecticut and taxes.
Basic information
I had to bring it up with Mark because I
I didn't know what the f*** you could possibly be referring
Baby thinks that like
It is about the source of the funding as opposed to tracking
Whether or not your Analytics
Show that you
Know that you benefit from okay so the day after we did the first Sandy Hook story we had a huge increase in trap
Traffic and then the more we did Sandy Hook Stories the more we saw an increase in traffic versus when we weren't doing
It's a very queer way to establish a pattern of malicious behavior for money
It doesn't even take it sunny
Kind of tough to imagine
Dino the image we have of Alex
That he would spend any time poring over that date of
He has employed somebody that's yes
Somebody did otherwise how're we here is any of this real if nobody is handled his traffic
F****** I quit it's just
Coincidence
What man
Part of the problem
Is the discharge
Texas
Right
The judge won't let Alex have his lawyer that he wants
They tearing I've covered up they say I haven't given any information
Discharge
And the judge previously one of her tired and Travis County will never let me have the lawyers I want their well-known famous
Personal lawyers
What is so
We have a local lawyers most of which are real brand-new will take the case and they go in and they get yelled at and
They roll over and say
I'm sorry
Will be better will give you more
When the judge in the opposing sides say we know you got the information
This is like asking somebody for a confession
That doesn't
Exist
And that's what completely
Crazy about this whole thing
Wow that's an interesting spin
That's that's a question that I guess they just didn't answer and they didn't ask him the depositions just like
Legitimately
You and me
Man to man
Tell me why you're here
Very interesting
Just keep going if your perception of what's happening what is happening
I want to know before we go anywhere what do you think is going on right now and are there is there like spinny light
It's around me yeah I remember learning in some philosophy class in in college was that like
The beginning of any kind of discussion that you can have with someone is like
Agreeing on the definition of interference
And like if you eat you do really kind of have to establish like
First principles about reality Galaxy
This is a chair weakened from their next words were going to go through the dictionary
Yeah always lawyers were just
Like little worms
They're afraid of it's so funny
So funny
They're brand new lawyers because that's all we could get to take this case a good lawyer would be like no will never do this
So then they're like maybe we can figure something like a lawyer takes on the case
Get involved realizes Alex
Maybe get them disbarred
They skedaddle and someone else coming I'm representing Alex Jones can I stop
Reasonable thing to do one of the other problems besides Alex's lawyers he didn't get to choose the lawyer
Everybody wants because there
Maybe
Not
Isn't he dead
Court Of Heaven
Some people are not qualified to practice
In Texas right we're not allowed to have
Pass the bar
In Texas or whatever
And that's a problem
But the other problem I think is probably even more serious and it's if Alex has to be believed
This job
Does not know the law
The judge also
Who is known as
A bomb thrower
By the Democrats not talk to as well as just
Unbelievably
Ill-informed about the law
They even quoted here in The Huffington Post of all places
Who's attacking me
But it's on her.
Lawyer Bill Ogden with
Fart ball
11th and post that
Gamble's default that's the judgment
Riverlink is a bit of a myth
In the legal world but not if they can make it real with me
Rita judge decides
Bad sign that Alex didn't recognize the name of the law firm Farrar and Bell
That's not good that was weird you alive
I recognize that name
And I'm not being sued for not being sued by them what could be a ridiculous number of money
Yeah and for a long time like if you were here
If you're in a protracted case
And the law firm you know the name of the law firm against you to a certain point they have been in this case so long you halfway
Expect them to a developing almost collegial relationship like
We'll go out and eat lunch together we just spent everyday together for 4 years or whatever
Nope still does another name doesn't seem to
For defamation
I didn't do
Did you know that in the you don't want you to have a jury trial
I'm being sued by people
And they say in the
I've never said their names
Texas law
Says you can't sue somebody
If you didn't say their name for defamation
But Tricare
People hear me so this is sort of true but Alex is still lying
So the cases that were brought by Neil heslin and Posner and Della Rosa those are defamation cases because
In four words
And Alex did say their name specifically on air
Conversely the case
Being brought by Charlotte Lewis isn't for defamation because her name was never said
But her child was invoked
Industrial Q's Alex of intentional infliction of emotional distress
Right does a different charge
Because the defamation statute probably would not apply
I was just playing fast and loose with these details knowing his audience will never look into it or try to figure out the difference
Or why is it I never said
Yeah yeah
In the end in any situation like this
If you would
If you're a listener of Alex
Just based on all we've had to do till like
Narrow down what
Actually happen
And how many different
Complicated things are happening simultaneously
Alex is giving you a very simple answer never heard of
Judge
Is a bomb thrower still informed on laws
Explanation I'd rather keep it simple stupid
I think I think he probably self-select for an audience that is really into easy answer
Insisting that he's never going to get a fair trial always me
So they're not going to give us a fair trial
Just like they're not going to give America for a trial because
I taking this country Oliver
Especially in blue cities almost died
Republicans have their own problems war-mongering
Surveillance police take stuff
But with the left all of that and more fused together
With their righteousness
That that that they're in control of society that they rule the world
Alex's at every opportunity to have a fair trial this is nonsense
Also it seems really weird that I like seems to be brushing aside the problems he has with Republicans when those problems are quote
War-mongering surveillance police state stuff
To take over the world
Watches at all times and control our Behavior documentaries if you made called police state
Sure there's some problem
Who's there
Because there's sanctimonious
All of us
They want a police state and their snooty no one's going to starve in the streets
No one was there was a f****** point of living in America ridiculous
How do you find this defense to be laughable
Why did I really bismal display
But it
A little bit
Satyr
And again it's been years since I've even talked about this
So I'm venting a little bit
But in a way it's a good idea
It's so insane it's almost comical for the plan
Clip of the courts to radiography
At the end that's how I stay sane
But first let me read you a statement from Warren Patton
I actually got my hands on this statement for Norm pattis
Knock knock
Who's there no seriously knock knock who's there orange
Orange who orange you glad you bought woke insurance
Good joke
Okay so you got one you got a knock knock joke what else what else
Under the guise of it being written by norpoth
It's been over this a good day for you I got called back to work Insurance in the next to this is fantastic
Yes
You get five point
I'm so we have one last clip here and it's the end of Norm quote
Okay I which is not the knock-knock joke from Alex's lawyer.
Batman
Man it feels like I was about to go to an ad that then
He doesn't really but kind of soft doesn't add
It is not an overstatement to say
The first amendment was crucified
Today
Captain George
And today we fight judicial tyranny there still some good judges are still some good at BIR still some good just fart
Running to fight these people violence or with muskets likely saw
240 something years ago
The truth
And Justice and educating the public
And taking our country back
Through election
At the rather legal in Waffle
I appreciate the last 40-plus on air
I haven't made a big deal about this last few years we've been
Incredibly persecuted by these people
High bar table top lawyers
The country that never seen anything like
It's in their lives
SOI just trust in God
And I trusted you to support us and I appreciate you all so it does kind of like us at methasoft ad
Idiocracy clip and just yelling about I was going to fight the New World Order
I don't know man I found this this is this response to be I would be underwhelmed by this if I was
Yeah I would find this to be
You would need two more directly rebut the allegations against
I would I would feel like this was a little little week
Yeah
I don't know it's not even really theatrical he's not is not
Full of bombast
I just kind of
The whet noodle
Who's just like
I mean the moment he said my lawyers have never seen anything like this I was like every single law
Lawyer on the
Planet
Had never seen anything like you Alex
I want to see anything like you
You have ruined the legal system for lawyer
You and they love that it's just a perfect storm of narcissism enabling now
The political situation where it crashed
Like he has he has
We have some
Ability whether it's in a loathsome
Area of expertise Allen
Yeah I don't know
Eyes f*****
I'm just saying that over and over again thinking
Looks like there's no there's no thought that so many times in the past
God I can't even say it
If I say there's no way then I can't do it we don't we live in a world where that you can't say there
There's no way this happened about this kind of kind of
Inasmuch as he didn't have to reveal a lot of
Information that I bet you would not want to be public
The inner workings of
How they made their news let's say
Could be a lot more damaging to him than any Financial
Penalty
So I do feel like there is that angle of his butt
At the same time
That might
Be me being too pessimistic
Because
He still has the Connecticut case right still going right
Further
As you get into the figuring out the damages and then through trials in in Texas
If he does not cooperate
They may Levy a penalty that is
Batman Beyond anybody's capability of thing
There is a decent chance you could
End up seeing is bankrupt in
Yeah I don't know that that's the case but
He has a financial incentive to cooperate
In this phase of the trial because it he doesn't he's leaving it up to chance kind of what they believe
How is a fitting punishment
And I think that he kind of gives off the air of somebody who's pretty f****** rich
Seems like it yeah no I mean the first thing I thought was as like
Throw out 250 million
Just say it
F****** do it
Because
That's what that means
I use 100 million dollar man out so sorry
Yeah I think that's probably going to be one of the more interesting things to follow is
Is does his tune change in terms of cooperation when it comes down to like
Now this is going to hit your bottom line a little bit
You ever have an interest in this
Not just office skating because eventually
A decision is going to be made with or without you
Right right
I mean it just seems like that's it
Too much
It's too much happening all at the same time for them not to come back with something
That is
Massively punitive
Because we're dealing with somebody who's
Everybody is saying that this is never f****** happened this is this is something taught in schools because it doesn't actor
Really happened
So you got that already so your summary to here we are
Default default judgment money should be like up to double just for that just for the extra
3 years it took
Or whatever you know
On top of that you've got this guy who is essentially
Created the blueprint by Which democracy is
Jamal I thought you can't punish him for that in this case you have to
Keep it
What you can do
Is make an example out of somebody who behaves the way he does
I mean I don't want Vengeance to come into it but I do think I do think that I mean straight up
This should be a simple like hey
F*** around and you're going to look at a 250 million dollar judgment
So either I think it's actually kind of loam
Yeah well I just
I don't know
I'm fascinated to see where this all goes into like his actual show
From after the. But
Because we had this conversation with Mark Bankston I didn't want to overburden the episode make it too long
Tell Dad so far next episode we will get into
Some of the actual show response but for now
I'm I'm I'm just like
I could see a number of directions this could go I know that he'll obviously try and use it to raise money
I probably have another money bomb
Mike Lindell
I don't know
There could be all about the way Michael Mendel was just on a telephone
On Jim Bakker Show
He was just a guest on Jim Baker's Telethon
What is it what is it about as very close are all of the same very close to covering that same s*** they're all the same
It doesn't matter where you go the far-right
Is the same idea
Will it back Jordan but until next time we website
We aren't underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan yes thank you so much Mark Bankston
For joining us
Wheeler
Yeah but next time Neo and Leon dzx Clark on Daryl Run 2
What the sex robot