Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Looks around at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex June
Jordan
My break but I mean look
It's going to be counted in sort of a negative
Right
Monday's episode
Load of people
Saying such positive things about the
And like that is really nice although it is
Very hard for me to deal with
Not having the brain that I have
It's as if I'm being
Given
Terrible feedback if I were a normal person
But it's kind of immersion therapy
Lots of compliments and positive
Stop it I appreciate that I appreciate that
Well I mean you're built like a balloon
You can handle a certain amount
Papa
But go too far and that sucker is going to pop
That was a flood of positive stuff could only handle a tiny bit
You're very small balloon I did I was trying to be really nice
I'm a balloon that functions Vasquez about
Empty
Remaining Luftballons
Something
Been trying to to get better at
Like accepting posit
Dolphin
I definitely
Definitely appreciate it I was happy with the episode
Yeah that's okay
Is fantastic
Edwards
What about you
I feel like whatever I say after that is going to be real late.
But it's my partner's birthday coming up soon happy birthday and I have decided at this point
I used to go out like four or five nights a week
For a decade
Get out of doing, and then in the past 3 years it's just doing the down to almost nothing like I just stay
So we're going to start doing just weird random stuff
And so for her birthday this year
We have decided to go to a casino
Neither of us Gamble
Nearest like to gamble going to be overwhelmed
It's basically a spin the wheel and we'll just
Go you guys are going to be so overwhelmed
I think you understand the
Type of
The cross-section you get when they're go to the casino people just sitting there at the slots just endlessly bully
I've been to Vegas twice
And it was the worst
Both times this one I think is going to be in either Indiana or Michigan or Wisconsin
Gostica fair but I can't wait to put it on the list man
Well that sounds depressing but one fun thing that a friend and his wife
They would go and they would choose a random.
I don't usually go on
And just get off
And spend the day around that L stop to fantastic idea
Has like some kind of
Excitement Randomness culture
City that you f****** love so much somehow I we just do not see it
Beyond your normal beaten path Lane
Missouri
There is a riverboat casino that was a good like half hour drive maybe 45 minute drive from
Columbia
And so me and my buddy Nikki gift
Savannah Burger
I think some other people like to go to but those are the two buddies that I remember who like
He would go to the Sea do
Go to the casino
And we we spent some time down there wasted
And
I don't know how this happened
Okay that's a good start
But I think Nick
1 Lakers
Free
Buffet at the
The casino if your
We went on Valentine's Day
That's the saddest place in the world
Hahaha
Nothing
Mother finest bone
I do remember being pretty fun
That sounds good
Suspend
A few hours
Is a Dodger
Nice couple of good buddies of poorly cooked steak
Getting mad at Nick cuz he keeps winning on the three card poker
Games of
$10 blackjack
That is all gone
Today we have some episode to get into where you be talking about
October 3rd and 4th
So I wanted to check in on Alex's respond
Two-course loser
All these cases
By default
Being a huge lizard
Blues easiest loser ever
White
A Big Lou's man what a big loser
So October 3rd is a Sunday's episode
And Monday is
The 4th
Ansel
The first Joy thank you so much as you want
I'm a policy wonk
Operators union for 2021
And then my Edition
Thank you very much thank you so much and hello to Morrow tark's
Thank you so much
How's your 401k
What's the business
Heroin
Large
Play tomorrow parts
Brandy
W indeed I wanted to know if we had
We should a happy birthday to
Emailed us a long time ago
We are not restarting not happening
During the time. Worried we had an obligation my birthday eyes
Reasonable expectation
It's Jus wanted to know when we have done it what did I say we might
Have I'm almost positive we did
I can't remember no clue
Just in case
Just in case from Brandi would like to wish you a happy birthday Gray
Giving someone life is giving someone dead
You can say that
Life is death
Happy birthday happy birthday
We jump in here on
Sunday Sunday Sunday
And ever since it has a base that he's in
Obviously not good
But he he knows that there's a difference but
Emotional reaction
And thought-out
Calm decision-making
Somebody's got to.
We really should all just sit back
For a moment
Take a deep breath
Cogitate
Or meditate
Georgia stats
Very
Tom Leander
So stop meditate
Cerebral level
And then we have to make
Decisions that a cerebro Bible and then emotionally
Amway
Use the emotions the good lord gave us
Very aggressively power
Against the globalist
Youcan intellectually decided
Something
Unscrew despot
Head
10 degrees
Takes the horse
Psychologically
That neck
Quickly and easily
Historical
Okay yes what a variable
Historical metaphor that is
Historically
As as we all know you must calmly decide to do something and then let your emotions take over
Whereas you killed
That was a that was an adventure
Does adventure of like Haley's cogitate
Thankless that word
Cogitate all over the meditate on it
I want to tear a despot head off right
So I need to emotionally prepare
Heritage Square
Take the emotion part out of it okay
If you just
Let's go on emotions right you will be able to achieve your goal or whatever
No problem.
Hey I'm going to tear your head off
Focus Laika is it is in state
And get your resolve ready and know that your goal is to
Twist-off desperate head paint myself like the wall of a bank and then when a despot walks
Biology
Just appear in
Marillion
Cena that's that's how you think things through
Yubin
Cogitate
So visit no-man's-land about them
Cuz a little bit into the show we get a guest
I'll give you one clue about who he is
Either Health right
If my got them
Great job reporting a story that broke
Thursday evening
Angle 2 and angle of a ipower
DOD data analysis program
Project solace
Chatters official vaccine narrative
Accelerating in the fully
Lady is the big one
Saw this and didn't follow the links
I have a whole stack of Articles here
First
This is from mainstream news
Almost 5.6 million Medicare beneficiaries
55 years and older this is a particular
September 28th
Discovered by a lawyer
So first of all it's important to note that this is Project Salas not project Solus
Project Solus is a 2d platformer you can buy on Steam
This is an AI initiative that's run by the department
That's fair enough
The jaico projects
That's something else entirely
The jic or the joint Artificial Intelligence Center launch project salad
In March
2020s quote
A predictive tool to help identify where critical supply chain shortages were occurring
During the pandemic
Essentially it compiled a ton of data together and use it to make
Predictions about where resources should be allocated
This document that Alex's.
Think about that Mike Adams
Apparently reported on is a PowerPoint presentation that was
Put together by
Humetrix
Say medical app
Developer
Who was seeking to answer some questions like
Consulting data from Project Salas
Eccentric
They were concerned with had to do with vaccine effective
And whether or not it waned over
They were further interested in reduced Effectiveness with
Delta variant and among people in subpopulations
Within the data
Information that it would be hard to just compiled and analyzed on your own yes
Essentially they found that there may be some concern about waning effectiveness of
MRNA vaccines but there's some huge caveat to have to get window
Discussing this PowerPoint presentation
The first thing is that the data that they're using
Only covers people six
55 and older
It's not necessarily something you can
Extrapolate
The entire population
Also is very important point is that this is a
PowerPoint presentation
If you're looking at the slide you can
Computer basically the visual aids
Did someone is put together to help them in giving a lecture
You're missing the essential context
Of the person's actual presentation
Which isn't being captured in the PowerPoint
Mason point to slide number 9
They were looking at vaccine vaccine effectiveness
Endive
Three to four months
Post vaccination. And 5 to 6 month
Supposed
This slide shows that their age distribution is heavily skewed
With people 85 and older making up
43% of the folks at the five
26-month group
But only 14% at least three to four
Okay conversely people aged
65 to 74
51% of the 324 month group
And only 24% of these five
The six-month
The fact that the 52 six-month groups use much older is more complicated
And as such the slide included
Discussion question on the sidebar
Could higher proportion of 85 years and older members in the first vaccinated group
Explain reduced vaccine effective
If you only have the PowerPoint to go off of you have this discussion question but you don't have the discussion
Also none of the stuff that Alex is saying about this having to do with it
Lady Is Real at all
It's just made up explanations for data that they do
Care to try to
The bunch of bulshit they're going up a PowerPoint presentation
I am creating
The fun conspiracy
Yeah could
A large number of people who six months
After anything might be
Askew
This isn't even about this is about breakthrough
Breakthrough infection
I mean obviously
There's no way that that can't have some effect
What's the date of it being presented
Ed in this PowerPoint presentation
Presentation
If everything
King is
Aboveboard and everything is accurate
It does introduce some interesting questions for people to look into it
Does not introduce conclusion
It's 88
They're being unfair
I don't know if my cat is gets his hand on a PowerPoint presentation that's all I need to hear
What I needed to know
Mike the dramatic Ranger is
Is over
Freaky
Website
It was still live on there I don't know if it's there now
But this is DOD
This is their jic
So
Some secret Source somewhere this is open-source until
What it shows a couple
Very
One is that
The
Negative side
Text
The vaccine
Get worse over time with each pass
And so the
Hospitalizations and ice
I see you
As well as deaths
It's very bad
At 3 to 4 months
Roughly doubles in about
6 months
So this presentation is nothing to do with negative side effects of the vaccine
Is he trying to say that when you get the vaccine you have negative side effects that only continue to get worse apparently
This document is entirely about the efficacy overtime of the vaccine factoring in age group as a very
Well that was totally made-up it's fair to say that this live show does seem to indicate that there is an increase in breakthrough cases at the
Does a decrease in vaccine efficacy between e324 month
N52 6-month group
Mike is ignoring all the
The context and the suggestions of possible explanations for the data presented because
He has his own explanation that he was once
Jamdown the audience
Throat
Also
On flight 68 literally says that the rate of hospitalization drop by a third comparing breakthrough cases to
People in the same age group
Who just got covid
Before the vaccines World out in March
December twenty
Reported
Not only that
In breakthrough infections there was a 2.1% death rate
Among people aged 65 and up
Compared to a 12% death rate in that same.
Between March and December
For 2020
Mike is entirely misrepresenting his PowerPoint presentation in order to make a
The fraudulent argument against vaccination
I said it before and I'll say it again every time he's on this is surprisingly weak stuff
From the health Ranger I'm underwhelmed
You know I
Since I was grown
I always sell Rangers
As like
Ballon like no
Erica
You know what I'm saying something about Strider
Is exiled used to be a king or whatever solving problem
And this man
Is no Aragorn
Answer
No Aragorn that's all
I would love for you to slap Mike Adams Piccolo's
Not only is michaelmas
Representing and misusing The Zeta he just decides that he can do whatever he wants with it
There's no rules
Looks like a flatline projection so if we continue to project this
To let's say 9 months
My switch is coming up in
Immediate future
Looks like this is going to
And it looks
We're going to see probably
This is my estimation this another
Estimation we're going to see Millions
Of Americans
Suffering severe hospitalizations and deaths
Vaccines
So that's where we are
So like making all that up
What are you saying is that he looked
At this graph any decided to draw what do you want
What's after the pain to stop
I was going to say
That look I mean that's all he's doing
Norbert
On the 1st
Sinbad Shawarma was waiting off and he hit a homerun
This would be exactly like my cat was like well obviously he's going to hit 162 this year
Game that's one everyday not only that but every at-bat
A homerun
Just based on the information in this PowerPoint presentation are very strong indication
Is that Mike will be totally wrong with his predict
For one thing he seems to be ignoring that this data is just a group of people 65 and older
Secondly because the age distribution in the 3-2 four-month group and the 52 6-month group is so different
There's not necessarily going to be this straight-line phenomenon like is
Predicting
As time goes on the average age of people getting vaccinated
Depends to go down
Because the elderly were top priority and initially for
The proportion of the people aged 85 and older goes way down in the 324 month group and also the vaccine efficacy number
Numbers go up
It's entirely possible that there's some relation
Between age and mRNA vaccine efficacy that we are yet to discover
The point is that there's a lot of possible explanations for the data
In this PowerPoint slide it like
Is it making s*** up
So you can act like a dramatic little baby talk about Millions dead
On Alex cuz that's how they have fun
And make money
It's real sad
Like I mean
To take something that so obviously shows
Massive improvement over not getting a vaccine and then being like
See I bet after
Three months it's four times as bad as it was after today but
You know but you know what like if
The numbers
Do
Show that there's like a four times higher after 9 months
That will just
Be those people
That all that will be is an indication that it's even lower numbers
For the people in the earlier
Bellator cohort
Exactly
Exhaust insane
So there is one piece of
Information that is in this
This PowerPoint presentation
That Mike
The other major finding of this route
The number one most
Reduced serious combat
Quotations over time
Was to have a
Play previous covid-19
This
Natural immunity is the number one best
Active effects
Following vaccination
Cuz I know it sounds odd
A lot of people are taking the vaccines even though they've already
Had
The oldest and been sick
Finding as people that naturally already had it
Even though this injection is compromised them
4 deaths
Body is so smart at able to figure it out
It's already been in contact with it
Because it's the vaccine itself cream in the body is that right
Is that right
Is that part of it
So it makes sense that having had covid previously would give you a leg up
Open terms of immune
Why do scientist been totally clear on the
Exact extent to which people become immune and approval covid after they get it but there is some effect
And I will know more later
Again though I need to stress that this data said is entirely comprised of individuals aged
65 and older and it's not sensible
Will The Big Biscuit be applied to the general population
I was confused himself there because the narrative on Infowars up to this point is that the MRNA vaccines train your body to attack
Itself
And Alex has been very clear that he believes that if you get the vaccine after having covid your is
Good as dead
Going to f******
Kill you
This larger the mic is covering shows some indications to the contrary to dance around that in a tunnel
Words spoken that the audience doesn't realize this is the exact opposite of what he's been
Been saying for months I mean it's just a f******
Word salad he threw out there to avoid a very obvious
I mean it's all God has its Direct
Lee County directory
God that's so
You're so stupid
That here's where things get a little bit dicey
Just here
A lot of places but this one
B b in the road
When my comes on there's usually something that's like
Oh boy at 121 be today
Get vaccinated
According to these
The number one thing that you can do
Who survived the vaccine
You take the vaccine
That's in the date
Could I have lower
Outcomes
Just people who never had any
Adapt
I go into the 80
I appreciate the restraint but I mean like the implication that he's giving is like if you're going to get the vaccine go get your
Yes
Yeah this is like
This is getting dangerously close to him saying like you should infect yourself on purpose
The number one thing you can do
The vax to survive a bullet wound is to have it not hit you in the head or the
Okay
So the number one way to survive the vaccine is to not be
Be killed by covid-19 way or the other
Yes
Yeah I mean I think
This is dangerous advice or number
A lot of read
Do you put people around you at greater risk
You could have severe complications
You could die
Yeah this is this is supposed to be the health Ranger
Yeah I think well I mean he did try and give everybody a bowl of that one time I was in the name of
For somebody who doesn't believe in vaccines
Bigelow Paula
But you put some vodka
I don't have a good time
Just want to make sure it's disinfected
I mean
The thing that I sing that weirdly got me there
Is this
Only way
That they can get
People to justify getting the vaccine
Because I'm sure most of his audience is already had covid
They haven't been being safe whatsoever
Oh man angle that they're doing of like
Listen
They're making you get the vaccine now we got all these vaccine mandates but
Guess what
If you've already had covid
You're actually going to be fine with this vaccine I know I've been telling you that the vaccine is going to murder
Family and your children and everyone you've ever met it might be a way to backdoor like a narrative
Later for like a vaccine not killing everybody exactly
Nike be like well you actually had covid before you been up to
I think that's probably
Productive for that
I think that would be that would be a way around this but functionally
As it stands
He's also
Basically saying you should go
Which sucks
Absolutely it's like hey going but you know how kids
Go to one of those
And I mean one out of every what
10 years old
No big deal
So anyway
Michael misuses some more of this data in order to claim that this is a snake biome
Also notice the last slide of the slides
The ethnic groups
Most effect
By this
Native Americans have the highest rate
Increase
Negative
American
Higher-risk
Text compared to
If you're Hispanic
1.3 to 1
4 times greater odds
It's something more like
1.25 ruffian
This
People out there
Biological weapon
This is not a responsible reading of this graph at all
There is a higher risk of hospitalization in break
Cases among people of Native American population
But this light alone is not enough to demonstrate that there is a
A causal relation
Kinship
Throughout the pandemic if you care to listen
Some people were talking about about this
Proportionately High rates of infection and death
Among native community
This is part of a long-standing conversation and there are number of hypotheses given for the numbers
Including a higher rate of Sheridan intergenerational housing
Decreased access to healthcare and higher prevalence of covid-19 comorbidities
Like heart disease diabetes and smoking
This is something relevant
For sure and it's something that researchers are
Keeping an eye on and
Discussing
Play the bikes talking about this stuff is
Just not
It's not connected to reality does sound like he's literally saying that once again smallpox
Blankets are
Roaming across this land tearing everybody to pieces
I mean
Not terribly
Wrong
In this next clip
When I think of
Is
Just
Spectacular
Is that everything that Alex says
Is made of
Everything
AI program
And they just put out a report
What it does
And they're honest about it
But no political statements are in it
And it says
That you're way more likely to die if you had the shot
Erasing your regular immune system in it
The way up though if it comes into contact
With a similar virus
I'm not just covid but any other coronavirus I mean
None of this isn't the primary sourcing that there
They're providing what is the pentagon's main
AI
You know what I'm saying like which is the main one
How
Are they still using how I guess
I don't know I would hope for a way pass out
I have
By now
Albert
Halliburton holyshit
Crack the code
Okay alright
Mike believes
Without any kind of
Proof
That they're spraying cities with covid
And then Alex hasn't it
Rejoinder
Do air supplies releases of these toxic
Nanoparticles
This coming winter
Could they release this
United States
Personally this is my opinion
And I think they're planning to do so again and I think
We are going to continue
Genocide
Against
How to drive people to the vaccines
Crashing
Restitution
As we said 20 months ago here on air
Blame the unvaccinated for the vaccine
Others and almost killed him
So apparently Alex's dad got spray
It is easier to say that your dad got sprayed then to take responsibility for almost
Healing your dad Alex you almost killed your dad that you personally
Killed your dad maybe not personally but his behavior was such
They put his dad at
But it's better if his dad was sprayed
Other than saying that
As a direct result of everything Alex believes dad almost
Just came up with like a little flower on his lapel
Alter bottle Seltzer bottles good if you are if you are putting it in a pie I think you've gone too far
Yes
A crew that I it's just a lot
Subordinate
Yes good boy you can transmit covid via pie to the face
Well I'm getting your nose there is a meringue-based
But is boss
I mean it is October obviously there's going to
Maybe some pumpkin covid
Play pumpkin spice
So
2 years ago or so little bit less like Adams appeared on the show and declared that it was over
Humanity that would only be Lone Survivor
And he was right
Yes
So now here's his new dramatic pretty
My prediction is people going to see troops on the streets
Christmas and they're going to Cebu
In certain areas
Of course with a fall
This is the winter die off
This is the
Sort of soft
Military replacement
Of the infrastructure of
Medical workers
And even
You may have even at some point
Troops
In certain areas
Grocery stores checking your vaccine
How to come in and Shop
For food so by Christmas
Like in two months two and a half months
We're going to have military on the street Garden grocery stores bodies piling up everywhere
Okay
That seems
So I'm likely
That's
An upgrade still over it's over for Humanity there will only be Lone Survivor
He's not going to compete with that
Okay you can't get more apocalyptic
Premium Dave over there against
No one
Right
They shot their shot too early
I mean
It's over for Humanity DeLonghi lone survivors of the way too early I'm going to eat my neighbors thing
Totally that's like
That's where you
You should do that
When you've got the lights what someone is giving you the light
That's your neighbors
You don't have another place to go after that they got stir crazy because they assumed that the
The cover thing wouldn't last as long so they thought it would be fun
To say to scare like a comic who got overexcited and did their closer 3 minute
It's into their sack
Too bad
Oh no I did
Not have 20
Enter the rest of the site is going to just end up being ranting about how you need to get right With God all over and over again
Everybody knows it's the end everybody understands this
Hey they say you lost your lawsuit
You don't get a jury trial doing that's unconstitutional 7th Amendment
Holden told the country
Everybody in the system is served it is going down as well
Dying in math
From the injections
This is
God
Going down
Are we God
That's not going
To happen though
It's just a lot of buffering
Killing time with you
Assertive
Meaningless platitudes I was really kind of hoping for her maybe a Barnes
I was kind of thinking that a Barnes would show up to let us know that it's actually
He actually won the lawsuit somehow and there's a secret double powerful
Amendment that we're going to
Have I feel like if your barn
Sore no more
And you're smart
You stay awake
You're out of the country
E-girl
Time in Brazil
That's what I'm doing
Respond to little bit more to the Sandy Hooks up on Monday because this is
This is mostly about Mike Adams is
Seems to have paid for some time on the propane
Aaron Paul
Alex loves
You walked Abate you refuse to debate me
Still
He is
He's acting like
It's normal.
Normal now but it's not
No it's not
The Democrats are going to be dead
Right
What can the average person do to lessen the blow what can Congress do
Fauci he's
Talking about illegal spying and
But they're still operating from there
Coon
Like everything's okay but it's not okay
Everything's falling apart
And in the hospital they're not full of the vaccinated
You are seriously ill
I'm not sure they realize how close we are to the end of the American Empire
.
Once you see
Is bribing all of the
Craft breww City carryout more voter fraud
Is there
Covid stimulus
Play ever been in power
Catastrophic for the nation
Man
Do the Democrats in power
I just think that these
Villains
With these dudes have
They're spreading themselves too thin
Yeah I like those too many plans it just makes no sense
Why do I have to do all these things
Tori Kelly
Alright
The most successful plans are simple they strike the enemy's weak point
And then they are done it is a quick
Effective and immediate solution
All other plans are Rube Goldberg machines that make us look like we're idiots
I like say
I don't know starting a war in Iraq or something
Dumb short small quick
When you're the devil you don't want to have different teams working on goals
Those that are completely at
Sabbatical to each other and have nothing to do with the
Larger objective
They seem that seems to be how the organizational chart
Works here's what I'm thinking
Alex
If I'm the Dead
I have all these people that are working
Looking for me but I'm like
I'm the f****** devil
I don't care about who pay them in Devil ducks
The only way you can afford it is my money printed right
Stimulus
BB goes to hell then it's all tied up in the courts of Heaven
Pork I'm just saying
I would want to torture the people who love
Me
Bayou
Having them work against
Me
See I'm working at cross-purposes
To them so they are fuc
Picking up my plan but actually
My plan is to
To torture them
By making them fail forever
No I'm thinking like the devil's there
Yeah yeah I guess that makes sense
I guess that makes sense
5 that's as good as it's going to get on anything else that's the point at which I have to give up
Oh wait so you're fighting the devil who's playing is to have his followers fight against himself
In order to torture them eternally because
The plan donut
Right I got to go by
I have other things I need to do
You need to stay in here this cuz it makes
So there's a lot of plan disasters Coronavirus
But you won't give a time frame for it although it
Listening
Pretty gave a bit of a Time
Baa
Situation
The energy resulting in at least Regional power options
They're going to cause an economic
Catastrophe
Maybe
Holidays
It may eventually be
The actual class of a dollar
Prediction for this
We know that inevitable
It's going to happen
You don't need all this s***
You don't need all those things
Also
I mean
All of those things have already happened in my life
And we
We've still not collapse the dollar like we had the financial collapse in 2008
We had this f****** the endemic we've had
So many power outages in the past year that it did people are shiting in the streets
We're fine the reason
That Mike does stuff like this
Scattershot
There's so many different things
Just make no sense
Why someone would have all of these plans operating
Is because like let's say that there is a famine that he can be like I called that totally hidden let's say that all the other stuff
Come to pass but
There you go
I called this I know what I'm talking about
Or there is some kind of a financial downturn
This is what I was talking about
As long as you make a hundred predictions people ignore
That you got 98 wrong if to happened
Beef close
To what ends up happening
And the weirdest part is
Is 2 mi
The weirdest part of all of them
Is that
Those things
Or all the inevitable
Hendersonville
Of all of the p
People that he's ever supported getting power
Like all of those things just happen because of the people that you want in power
That's how it work
There's an irony to that so
Wouldn't you be better predicting it
You're making it happen essentially
You don't want to be too obvious about it
So
Do you know Alex lost these the Sandy Hook cases and
If it turns out there's a reason
For that
I made some people would say that the reason is
Because he
Flagrantly abused
Is the Discovery process and was being a total baby
Thanks salt like thinks there was a moor
Sinister reason they lost
These cases
So bad
The reason to come after Infowars with the the judgement
Is going to be
AA secession of nullification
We're going to have the Republic of Texas
Infowars is going to be the news
Texas which is why you need to survive
Remove one judge for the new one in and she said I'm
First hearing
First
Document
It's stunning
Oh man starting
Also I've bad news for Mike about to Alex's relationship with the Republic of Texas
Yeah that's great
Not great
Are not a friend
Self
They all declare themselves president
You know what I say this is actually a great idea let's do the number though
Biggest experiment of its kind
Alright
We give
Conservatives the Republic of Texas and Alex is their main news source
Everybody else just watches
Let's see what happens
Will have definitive proof
On what
Could country would be
This is Alex's Madness is a dangerous experiment
The dangerous experiment Mexico
No
Alone
End of the world
Continuing as it is what you think is going to happen to the average life.
Be murdered by the devil or the vaccine or we're going to
To kill all the Republicans
This is the average
Divers left
What are all the letters February about
They're going to try
Drugs and food that they want
But they have both of them will be killed themselves
Are you going to die
Muslim
Going to die
As the only
People who have gone on air and said I will murder people hit the Apocalypse
Immediately Murder My Neighbors in the apocalypse obviously the first thing the average leftist
This is going to do
Is the thing that I have said that I will do
And I'm judging them for it
They're so immoral
I know that I have some friends who would probably classify themselves as leftist
And I do
Constantly find myself
Sitting around with them and they just
Bucking won't stop talking about how much they love not being prepared
Just like a constant Obsession for people on the left
I do I don't go anywhere I'm not prepared for
What if what if the door is locked
Not prepared
I even know some people who like if they accidentally find themselves in a position where they are prepared well
Wearing shoes for this race that I'm about to run
Better light about fire they're opposed to
Cooking because that's a preparation of food if you want to eat food you eat the seed
You just eat dirt
So I thought this was a
Dumb
Dumb dumb dumb dumb show
I know we could do about it
Flower into the second this is where Alex is at
What an incredible time to be alive ladies and gentlemen I have a very important special of Fortran
Start of the next segment
In
Sunday live
Good morning
America Journal
You should come in Spanish at the last second
Its father knows he's got
Tomorrow morning 8 a.m.
I'll be back 11 a.m. and Owen Shroyer
I'll be back tomorrow
Alex leaves half an hour early
Yep just like f*** it I'm out of here talk to Mike Adams
F****** Let Let The Little Door
Glenn boring white supremacy take take over before it gets out of the studio. He's got to try to pay them bills
Doesn't buy Patriots
Supply plug
Family
I just thought this was hilarious
This is not how you do it
Highest quality turtle food
You pay Freeport
Good nutritious and quality
Really good
What
Can you pay more and get better stuff that's how everything works
Biskup
It's pretty good it's not a great
It's not pretty okay
I don't like some of it it's pretty much
Mr. Schiff
There's going to be armed guards at my grocery store by this f****** food
Otherwise you're going to show vaccine passport another 3 minutes that's where he would have got
Defensive
6 Cal
You're going to need it
Put it in your body
Wow if I if I were
My Patriot Supply
Call Rebecca
You're not get the
Some f****** food
So this this Infowars
Thing right
B cells
Maybe bad food
It's like the rebel base in Star Wars
We need to be on
When they take everything
And a Batman the enemy
If that means radio and
Satellite relays that means their own power supplies of that mean
Microwave relays I mean you you name it we got
Looks like the rebel base
Are you taking all this
I know it's going down
Who knows it could be your last chance any day
Delta 12
Sleep support
Infowars t-shirt
I mean
Might be your last chance
Get a t-shirt
So I don't know if down-and-out is the best name for your sleeping
A depressing name
He's he's really not feeling that great
Give him some down-and-out and we'll deal with them later we get a new sleep aid called f****** depressed
Can't get out of bed
We've got a new product it's just called despair
Sleep buddy
You can't get out of bed with a mood stabilizer called all week
Esprit de corps
The highs and lows
Mildly annoyed empty on the inside
Staring for between glass I'd given another pass on that name I think that might
Tige just does these plugs
Until Harrison comes there but he has a couple of new stories that he didn't have time to cover
Where the heck Congressional
Individual over the spending package says
Weekend quotes
He actually said we can spend
Unlimited amount
Yeah
It's imagine
Get the money first one has value
And we all get handed the debt
Inflation
Turn the hell I
Problem
Global screwing assault
Haley Wilde
It's accelerating your in World War 3
What happened
We know what we're talkin about
That was a very fake
Dramatic
Acceptable
That one was very clearly like he was like oh no I've still got 3 seconds I better try I got to stretch
I got a I got to stretch
He is basically the
Assertive radio equivalent to somebody who has an awesome booster
You know like you can hit that switch
Set final it's a final quarter second but
I mean he is too soon a lot of the time too early
So what are you talkin about there about the budget thing there's about representative John yarmuth who gave a speech back in June at a rotary
Free club and we don't actually have to pay off the national
Then I guess people are mad
About this
Now even though he was
Was back in June
He's playing pretty well but Alex didn't have time to get it today before he left work early so
I guess I'll wait till he covers this given to him about it
What a dick
Oh man
It is
It is funny you just
Watching this whole Dead Sea like they just being like
This is all made up
Imaginary what are you people doing why am I reading about it why are you
You doing this this is all pretend
Please don't make
We pretend to care about 4:10
What are we doing
So we get to the
And this will always be remembered as the day that face
Yes and we will deal with that in the middle of this episode
However
Alex is back from
Sunday
I don't know what the f*** is going on on Sunday cuz he just seemed to
Talk to Mike Adams for about an hour and a half and then
I don't know what's going on
But there's an actual audience
Maybe
For his Monday showed like the weekday show
So we get to talkin about a little bit of
The Sandy Hook Bay
And look
When Alex is in trouble
South America
Has always been the canary in the coal mine
When you know Infowars in trouble you know the country
Is on its knees
Willfully sticking its head into the chopping block
Thank you so much for joining us
Well
We been at the top
Twitter all weekend since last Thursday
Alex Jones
Jury finds Jones guilty of defamation must
Name the man that they say kill those children
Sandy Hook Beach
Beyond
Drug addict
Don't know his name
My name now
Is the corporate media
Constantly attaches me to a shooting at half
Almost 10 years ago
You're so much.
Stage
A couple of kickball
I want people do remember Adam Lanza
I would say that Alex has more name recognition than Adam Lanza cuz he has a
F****** talk show
And is there somebody who constantly
Trolling for attention
And then also if you listen carefully that clip it kind of sounds like Alex
Might still think Lanza didn't do it I am pretty sure he is
Describing this in a way that suggests he is still denying Sandy Hook
Are we still doing this
Is this possible
Are you help himself
Yeah why even bother with a default judgement he's just admitted all of this s*** yet again please apply
At least implied that his mind is still there
Well there's a
Jammed up
I mean again I watch
And it's all him
It's all him
Democrat judge
Him
Doing himself a pineapple
Petard of his own bill
Temperature
But yeah
Here
They don't tell you that I judge says
Block the
Just retired
The second hearing
And you didn't give them anything and you and mr. Jones
You said there's a kangaroo trial on your show she said the ruling a month ago
Exactly what was you says the show trial I said when she said a month ago
The second hearing
Yes it did
Yeah and and also the day before you were saying it was
The first hearing and now it's the second.
Stories a little janky
See I don't know by any of this
This is pretty soft
So she said
She said that I said that what I actually said was this thing and she said something different
And I know you read what she said and she said this but what she actually said is what I say she said
This is a very productive way to describe
Definitely
The depositions and everything like
Very believable
Straight like Alex has a lot of credibility on the subject
You comported himself with
Total glass
All I'm saying is that when that
Batman defines reality
You know reality has been defiant Define corporate representative
So yeah I mean really one of the only things
To fall back on his
Every attack on me is an attack on you
You have to re-up
To personalize an app
Experience this as an attack on yourself
Because I need
You to give me
You don't have Jerry's anymore and then
Is Rachel Maddow get thrown out when she says things way more
You know I do
Don't
What things has Rachel Maddow said those gorgeous amatory and things
He doesn't give any specifics
I don't love Rachel Maddow but like
I don't think
But you said more defamatory
I am I'm going to go way out of the way
Because I don't know if I can back this up but I'm going to say Alex is probably within the top 10 all times
Famers
Of every any
I think he probably is
Have you considered that
Like the reach of his program
The
Factories been on air daily 427
You got William Randolph Hearst I assume
Was William Randolph Hearst doing
Kim cell
He was very clear about directing public opinion through lies
But then like
Ghetto is News Corp
You can't consider like
Entities
Speaking Direct
Man I don't know it's going to be tough to be
Alex is up there but apparently Rachel Maddow
Anyway look he lost in court so that means it's time to buy truck
I don't
I do
How much
I discovered you getting something that's nothing to do with what this case is
His face
Tell you that we need your financial support
I tell you then
Lot of folks out there to make sure they're serious
Money
To fight this war
Sterilizer
But I need your financial support someone tell you right now
Your last chance today to get it in Fort Worth
Take a lot of money for me to
Pay my vehicle
Ridiculous
I am so transparent
Just
Just the Staggering amount of it's already over
We're all dead
The Empire is collapse
Right
Good soldiers in front of grocery stores
Bought
Please buy a T-shirt If You by itself Infowars can protect the 7th Amendment or something
Do you buy a t-shirt
We can stay on Aaron defeat the globalist that look we're all going to be dead
I've got to go to a waterpark
Alex wants to be able to pay
Show me you failed all over and that everything that you've done up to this point is meeting I haven't checked
I get on Owens crowdfunding think will you please people for like a quarter billion dollars on that b*******
Alex is probably just trying to do the same thing
The audience to pay for his bad behaviors that he's now facing the consequences
I mean
It's an alright business model of your s*** head I am asking you
The people
To once again protect
Direct me from feeling any negative effects right for all the Behavior I've done because if things look bad
For me it's over for Humanity even though it's already
7th Amendment says quote in suits at common law
Is the right of trial by jury shall be preserved
And no fact Tried by a jury shall be otherwise re-examined in any Court of the United States
According to the rules
Of the common law
This would be relevant
Except this only applies to federal courts
And very specifically not
Civil case is being heard in state
The Supreme Court
Is Thrice a firm that
State courts have no obligations
To provide trials for civil cases but many do anyway malady
Violated all he does not know what's 7 / 2
I do love I do love sometimes you really you know like I know that
Do you know the stuff is in
But then you go back and you actually
Hear it
And you read it again and again and you're like wait a second
We're still listening to a con
Constitution
That has a 7th amendment that includes a dollar amount in it
Like a 1776
Dollar amount
You know what
$20 being like
Holyshit this is worth $1000000 in today's money I don't know for certain
I would bet that has been
But it is like water we do
Rewrite the fuc
Live in the future
$20
Party.
How bad is it for 1950
So
The point is that Alex has been
Smeared
I want to show you some of these news articles
I want to show TV viewers radio station.
The Associated Press
The most respected publication in the world
Years ago in 2019
Father of Sandy Hook
Conspiracy driven Infowars website
That's the fam
He did not write that
Not in the book
Call The Wall Street Journal also publishes
And then about a month later they took away my perfect
What's the suit
And you said to charge us more
Credit card
That's probably not true but we've covered this
Before anyone's forgotten
Alex has a good
It's not against the Associated Press
The headline that I was reading is from MarketWatch
Watch someone who works there definitely f*****-up and attributed the writing of that book.
The MarketWatch page is just an article that the reposted from the Associated Press
Who were the new headline that MarketWatch Road
Which does not appear in the original AP story
How many AP website the headline is quote Newtown parents Corwin and growing fight against
Hoaxers
And it's never claimed that Alex wrote feathers book
That's for the Wall Street Journal I can't find that article posted on their site but this is an important to understand
Alex can threaten to sue the apple-1
They didn't do anything
His beef is with MarketWatch
And I've never heard him
Complain about them
I think that this is intentional
I'm sure that Alex knows that if he just contacted MarketWatch
Complained about the
Is very demonstrable enochtrue claim
They would immediately retract
And probably even issue an apology which
Doesn't work for Al
No that's no good blaming the wrong
Tone up to something they didn't
It's just a stupid game but he's my buddy
So smeared what you do is you point to this
This headline
And you use it to imply that all the headlines about you now or not true
Several other thousand are probably
Lost
Sandy Hook
Loses case over Hoekstra Marshall
Two more
Iraq
The reason there are multiple cases isn't because lawyers are filing Wild
Plaintiffs who have different
Complaints about the
Things you said about their kids whenever you sue somebody
You get a lawfirm
Write all of those lawyers each bring their own individual suits rat makes
Pics and specs Howard law
Alex just have to find a way to make this about a fight between him and lawyers as opposed to
Wayback
The people behind it who the real victim
Except that because he's the real victim according to him
Really sad
Yeah I mean I'm waiting for you might as well have a you can't handle the truth moment where he's like
It look I'm obviously the real victim because nobody died there and then everybody's like Steve we f****** told you
This is what it was
Yeah
That's Jesus yeah
Every headline about himself
You got time to fill
Yeah
Alex Jones fumes a judge rules
She lies
Witches Caroline
Giving him nothing
And then she goes and he says
This is a show trial
81000 pages
Two depositions with myself and my whole crew
Because we don't have what you claim we have
Battle plan to say Sandy Hook was a hoax famous years ago
Do they say give me the smoking
Don't have you don't get a drink
Okay
I guess
Give me the smoking
Wow
Nothing we can do that I guess we'll have to guess we have to get a default
You didn't give us the Smoking Gun so also like
Really really heavily implies an accusation of collaboration
Between
The plaintiff's and
In order for Alex's argument to make any sense that has to be a United
Conspiracy
I didn't become like a nice fun joke
Amongst
People that they could get their Soros check
Sure you know there's protesters
Everybody loves it again are Soros checks
I regret to inform you
That Soros is actually involved
With this plot
Against Alex
Ergo
Lawyer
She is known as a
Absolute
Soros
Offended her
You doing this to me
That is just like
I mean it's parody
Yeah so Rose is doing this to me and he's going to do it
I mean this guy is really you kind of have to think he's playing with house money right now
Because he's about to be like
And I think we should put a million dollars out for anybody who takes care of this judge for me like you so close
Well I think he learned his lesson
About that when you do stuff like that you end up paying $100,000 in
Judge Campbell actually on
Unopposed
For this
59th
Courts
Weekend 2018
There's probably a dump
How to money in there to make sure she beat the lack of a
Proponent she was up against
Well I mean the lack of opponent has so much more name recognition right out of the gate
You know everybody knows no one
True
So all Alex really has to go on
Is just pointing to this MarketWatch headline over and over again
Sort of imply
There any stories about him now or not
Call AP up
I was walking on the building I just told somebody that
How did you know could it be because you are told
Repeatedly
Constant war is your behavior was going to precipitate
Dreams to figure this one out no
It also that
MarketWatch headline at nothing to do with creating the illusion of Alex's guilty doll
His actions
Took this case
Obviously
Alex needs money
He doesn't want you to think
But this is the biggest
Is this you
Mike down for this don't got this Clippers
Is f***** up
My mom wants to people I know
I mean Fox
So
This stuff is nothing
The globalist
Who killed some of Alex
His family members
I'd like some specifics on this
Is method of death
Until 4 and why you're not.
Totally
You could only if like some kind of
Giant Mafia cartel Syndicate or whatever
Write somebody as a warning to somebody else
When they don't back down at that point
They could kill
Cuz the warning the warning is before you kill
Warning is a murder
And then the follow-through is more murder
But your pot committed once you've already committed the murder
You're not going back. Why would you
Exactly
Boy
They are bad at what they do
I don't believe any of this
Oaks
Folks
It just made me think of Tommy Mac
Comedian fluffy
Since that day
Alex
Violated
Unwillingly
This is from the 7th Amendment
Common law
You have
Black total violation
According to the rules of common law
Total violation of that violates the six of them as well
Your rights being stolen that's your Birthright being stolen
How to setup the amendment rights don't apply the state court so this argument sucks but his claim that his sixth amendment right
It's been violated or even sillier
So the first four words in the sixth amendment are quote in all criminal prosecution
Already
This just doesn't apply to
Okay okay
Now I get it
Those two amendments that don't apply
Tell me where the Magna Carta does not protect
Because under the Magna Carta which is I remember it 12:15
Maintain
It's Addison
Forever law right
I'm not sure that Alex really has a really good grasp on this Constitution and Bill of Rights
But you love so much because it prevents bites at this apple
And both are errata
No as I've stated 10 million times the people who have a pocket cost
Institution understand it not at all
Right
As a prop
100%
Anyway of you as being taken over
Ian Holm
Globalist again
Is in the process of being looted and absorbed
We'll be right back with the design collaboration
I said it earlier
I just I kept having this feeling
Global stuff too many f****** plan
Why do they need all of these plans
Like no evil organization would do this to themselves cuz so much of it just
Doesn't matter
Like what
What is the US economy collapsing matter if 90% of the population is killed off by a vaccine bioweapon
That will happen on its own
None of this makes sense because Alex is just making it up as he goes along you don't need a race war
To cover up the collapsing economy or whatever let's just get this real
They do not need to
To cover up any
Because we just saw the Pandora papers come and go
Sofa
Right we know
We saw it all we got it all written down and we still do
I think
People were more interested in how much
Twitch streamers made a hundred percent correct
Yeah it's doing is basically
Bigoted narcissistic paranoid
Jazz
But he has the skeleton of these ideas in place and he just kind of rips out about whatever he's feeling on these established themes
That's why you'll get like the global Staffing 100 different plan
Odds with each other
Completely contradictory or
Seem to be working toward
Different goals it's because I was just making it up
Based on his feeling
Yeah I'm really amazed that you can even try the cover it though
Need to cover up what they're doing
No
No it's covering it up it's all very obvious WeChat you look at this
Okay this Saturday received $100,000 from this company and now they vote differently
Yeah no s*** they're not covering it up at all it's obvious
You pay for loss
We all get
Not find its Superbad
But it said we live
So
Supply chains are broken down my friend
Yeah that's true
And basically what this amounts to is that Alex needs money
Country in the world is in cardiac arrest
And then we're sitting here running out of our supply chain
Running on a product even find ourselves
Everybody to go to infowars.com
He's never needed your support now that we needed here to tonight
Expand
Dot-com
Donation donation
Long-term donation
The funds to fight that he lost a bunch of cases and now he's
Mysteriously at a point where he desperately need he the van Spotlight the globalist
He needs
Needs to expand home and there can't possibly be a one-to-one parallel here
Now that I am on the hook
Look for a almost about to be astronomical amount of money
Knowing about
They could be a disaster
Time for me to expand my operation and I need your money together and I also not going to
Tell you the things that I'm going to do
That would give them too much right it's going to be paying off my legal fee and also did you
Read the Pandora papers it is very easy to Offshore your money and they won't get it the globalist hated if I could pay my
Help me
It'll come as a shock to them I'm not even going to tell them what my plans were this money of yours is
And when I pay off my lawyer
They will be blown away
Global
So Alex
He's very afraid of
Any lies about it a little bit ago
I'm looking for the book out here it is
The great reset
Ashwaubenon advertising is book
About here right now but
Stoke Les Schwab's book The Great reset was released in July 2020 which is a little bit more than a month after the cove
The crisis start
Alex is lying about the book's release date
Because if it came out a month after covid showed up
That makes it slightly more believable that he wrote it prior to
The pandemic
And Alex get you closer to that idea he's tricked you into getting closer to accepting the conclusion that the entire pandemic
This is progress
Towards
You using things that seem
Like trivial facts
Accept them will bring you closer to accepting his
Completely nonsensical conclusion
Totally
It's a it's a manipulation
Strategy
And also it's just kind of
It's very fun big
Can just be like
See
There's no way anyone could write a book
A month that's not possible
I've never heard of Isaac Asimov
F*** all of you
I have no idea
You could write a book in a month first of all second of all
It.
It's not even about
Facts about making the
Ultimate conclusion slightly mobile
Trapping you in
Acceptable
Rat distortion
ShopRite
There's a Polish journalist
Who was not allowed
Going to the United
The kingdom analysis mad about that okay
The social credit scores here
Homeless journalist denied entry the UK over his
Opinions
Criticizing
You can come here
News about a man named roof Falls in Kauai
If you're wondering he wasn't bar for my
Turn UK because of Youth
Views on globalism or the lockdowns
Turns out he's one of the very Fortune
Folks to be on the home office's list of people who are such s*** heads
That they can't answer the
This illustrious list includes Americans like Fred Phelps
Of the Westboro Baptist Church
And Alex is Buddy Michael Savage
Typically these are people who are big
And they have a history of agitating
And I guess the UK government is smart enough to just say we don't want that kind of bulshit over here
You cannot come
There is
There is something nice about being a Sovereign Nation that can just say
You're a
Dick
Come your values are antithetical
That what we believe in and
You have a
Proven track record of educated people and causing
A public nuisance
But it's the UK
I mean you know they got Nigel farage they've got all those people that got enough but it's like you're at
Yeah we can kick Nigel farage out cannot let you in
Exactly
No Bart
Plural as for this guy Rafal he's a bigot mostly the anti-semitic islamophobic and homophobic
Variety
The reality is that he's someone who's called the Holocaust a myth
And Alex is trying to whitewash away these details and only presenting as a Polish journalist debate
That's what he does
If you have
People telling you that you
You shouldn't
Say the n word
It's a slippery slope
I'm going to go
Way pass
You shouldn't even need to
Right
I agree with you but
I think it's Eddie Galaxy thinks it's a slippery slope
What I say
Mother father
I'm sorry do that okay
Don't use the word manhole
Infowars.com
And says that white people are inherently bad
Parasites in our evil mutants
Article
Infowars.com
Where We Are
So first of all none of the words Alex's singer band are actually band at all
You can say the n-word if you want there just might be
For doing so
You can say mother and father all you want they were just conversations about making turns used on official documents
Gender-neutral
So as not to stigmatize seems
Sex parents
Houses rambling about nothing in a Canada
Just feels like he wants to say the n word
Just what it feels like to be that way
Time for that thing about white people being mutant
This is one of Alex's big headlines for the day
The left didn't say that it was just one person named Frances Cress welsing
Wilson was an Afrocentric activist and I think it might be fair to describe her beliefs as being
Black Supremacy
Haha I'm not sure what site people are referring to but you can find a number a message
Bored posts by people who are very mad
Today quote
Black History Month website quoted her
I have no idea what's going on and I can't find a link to the site in question and
Even if you assume it's all true Alex's
Presentation
Nevada still bulge
Yeah
I didn't I didn't even cut this clip out but it one point in the in the
The episode Alex is like
Yeah you know what
We are all mutants
Okay okay
Great then you retract your complaints
Because you're fine
So look too late for them wo
The new new new new new world order
Kevin Nash
Rygaard Hall
Hulk Hogan
Hollywood Hulk Hogan
To say the n word
True
And destroyed journalism
It's too late for that
Because Alex
Is to Credible
You're being concert I'm in Concord
National globalist Force
Ally
They don't want it
That was up on it
You're not going well
Stalling
And
Too late everybody knows I'm right now
Play New World Order
Battle
Scott McKay better-known is Patriot Street Fighter the high-octane Full Throttle truth
I don't really care to respond to Alex's claims that he's too credible to be allowed on are just to let that sit there
Yeah that commercial sounded weird though
That was a
It's too late
Hi everybody we're going to have a good time
The Patriot Street Fighter the truth Hammer what is this local market ass commercial doing it
Alex's big-time important
If you could Putin cares about the Streetfighter Patriot nonsense
So I decided to learn a little bit more about who this guy is and I found his Twitter
This guy named Scott
McKay and this is his bio
Quote former competitive bodybuilder Wellness industry entrepreneur
Former political a
Consultant
Campaign manager radio talk show host
Q Patriot Street Fighter
Call
Patriot street fight
Immediately drop that part off for the commercial
Seems like you say it seems like anyone
He doesn't give a
F*** man you called
Q&A globalist deep State set up and here he is taking add money to promote the cube
Korean Street Fighter speaking tour Hey by the enemy of my enemy is my friend when it comes to me needing money
Lita fight these f****** lawsuit I guess so
I scroll down a little bit on his Twitter page and I saw a picture of him and I immediately realized
He's a dude that I've seen as a guest on
Camelot
And we might have actually talked about him on the podcast
So also like atoms with a guest on his show back in August so I guess this dude is another Direct
Connection between Infowars and Project Camelot World on real fun
Just everywhere
Here's a couple of bad signs about his tour
The first is that tonight when this episode comes out he's speaking at the farm boy garage
Which is a car restoration shop
Wow this is being billed as a pre-show for the Trump rally with no suribeats
Spectacular
Small
Probably more troubling
Is that he has dates listed on his website from October 16th to December 4th
With specific cities on
On specific dates
But the venue for all of them is DVD
The page says quote
Site has not been determined
And if you know of potential location on Texas page
Communication
It's not how you plan a tour
This is not going to go well
Just want to let everybody know we'll be doing the knowledge fight theater tour across the United States are going to be doing
20 days
Next year
If you know any theaters and can feel them for a Jiffy Lube Jiffy Lube
About a follow-up
Whoa
Oh boy I think this is this is maybe putting the cart before the horse a little bit
But it's good that he'd instead of finding
Venues
In advance to promote
Buying an ad on Super Bowl
First
And then you get the infrastructure
Right that's how it's always worked that's how it always will work I've been in the entertainment business for a long time
I love that Alex is willing to promote it
Legit not happy
Ohio State's might not happen or they might happen
Interpark
I promoted my first appear and I remember this
I remember promoting
The first time I was going to be on cysk
And it was about
8 month
Listen to when I started doing stand-up
And then about six years later I did it
I promoted the s*** out of it and then
6 years later in half
Storyworks
I know that sometimes
Dunno
This happened
Independent
Touring get out like
Maybe you have nine out of 10 Dates
You have a venue and you like well
Will be between these two cities
We can fit in another date there we'd like to hit this other City
That happens sometimes
But this is two months of no venue say if you got if you got 10 Dates
And then all the sudden one of your venues drops out
They double-booked second do something anything along those something else came up that's not the
CBD
This is
I'm going to your city and I'm going to start talking
In some way somehow
Somewhere Bakery
Don't care
Next
Starbucks
Globalist
Truth ever
So damn good
Distracted by a weird commercial on Alex's show portion
Facebook is down
Okay obviously this started happening about an hour ago Facebook
WhatsApp Messenger
Oculus VR
Eonline
Offline
Probably going on there I figure that out real quick
That was fast
Almost like you too
Made it up.
Maybe you just heard and then made it up
Great I promise to say about that
This one I've been waiting for
Alex
Completely whips on this one minute acular fashion
What's going on is biting it made some comments
About protesters
Following Cinema
And
Alex is trying to
Sort of Defense
Cinema and also attack biting
In this all boy
This is just
Incoherent
A little baby
It's more in bear
Biden
Pissed off
And that's something that's up in the line but it's
Civil disobedience
I need the people in the back so
Buildings as mostly peaceful
I didn't go into the u.s.
Capital
Owen Shroyer
Also I hear Shelbina
4th democratic
I've been over the weekend by a mannequin head people on high actually
Into a restroom
I don't think they're appropriate axis pain happens to everybody
Happen to people
Who have Secret Service standing around
What part of the process process to have one of your supporters go shoot a bunch of people are trying to
Michigan independent
That's just embarrassing
One thing you cover this
Times did not say that the school shooting was a good thing or defended it
This is something completely fabricated in his
Portable shed
Also it's really fun how that dude who did the shooting was a Bernie Sanders supporter literally every time it's
Come up
But now I guess he was in Dubai
Fools like Alex is making s*** up as he goes along.
So what happened here is the Alex thought he had a point
He was going to be able to score on by
The idea was that Biden was endorsing the protesters following Cinema into a bathroom which I guess proves Alex
Suspiria that there's different treatment for left and right leading protests
Did the capitol get arrested
GolfNow
So
Clip Alex
Plays
It doesn't say what Alex
Said he was in a real unfortunate that it doesn't say that explicitly says that he didn't think that those are appropriate Act
Alex set up his cloak
Completely wrong and
Painfully obvious as it's playing
2 in the morning
But you have to find a way to ship
Detention is soon as the
The clip is over
The magically the guy who shot scalise is Valerie Biden supporter
This is a rhetorical version of Alex waving a red flag at a bull
And I suppose in this metaphor the
The bull is the consequences of his lack of preparation
Maybe I'm not sure I've lost track of the metaphor but
Yeah that one might have
What is it to distract
Compactor Galaxy's engaging ideas no relation
A reality
And also what weird thing
Leave that one alone
That's such a weird one to even try and bring up
I think it shouldn't he be fine with it I think that enough people were talking about it and he figured it was away could score a point on bike
Probably hadn't walked
Watch the clip and just had a sense of it maybe a few things
Here's how I minute dunk on
This in order to weave it into all of my narratives about right-wing aggrievement
Yeah like we repress today
I'd like these
These liberal protesters can get away with anything they changed the bathrooms
Bam
And it just doesn't work
It it's not
Yeah it doesn't play
Yeah
I mean
I would have been just like
I would have assumed he would have gone like a vet that's all they're doing and they're all complaining about it that's
That's the angle
I also think if you're listening to that clip of Biden you see a bit of self-effacing this
Only time they don't do that is very secret service around here
I'm not subjected to this kind of thing
The implication is when I was a senator
Not that this is okay it's
It's not a good time
Toxic
But it is something that people deal with
Edwin more fun if he was like no of course I don't support
That what should happen is every time she wears
Clean clothes
Somebody throws up
The fake blood on Earth
And then the moment she changes her clothes
Another one
So the globalist
So they're spreading new viruses around
And this is big news for Alec
But there might be something big
This is the real globalist attacks they intend to hide claiming a new virus has been released which they're already claiming new variants
Because you're releasing
Sales of our history
Today
We need fines
Keep this operation on here
But to stay on air and
Continue on in the future
And we need funding now to do this okay almost like you had some
Expenses pop up
Some things that you didn't maybe budget for for this quarter
Dumbass we need money completely unrelated to those lawsuits that I lost which are totally unconscious
Do so I'm sure I'll be able to challenge entire court
Lot of money
Very quick so much
Sale
I am getting rid of everything
Because when they lay that judgment down they're going to liquidate it anyways and I've worn out anybody giving a
S*** about you saying that there's a money boss that again
Flashlight
Thomas wren
Who's a lawyer apparently and got and
Yeah this guy's this guy's a weirdo
Give some information about covid
That's not good
And that information showed and it's incontrovertible straight from the CMS servers
That there
Thousands and thousands dying with this vaccine
48,000 dad within 14 days
If you're within 14 days
Perfectly healthy you go get the shot
Three days later your dad you're not a vaccine.
I'm not sure this guy knows what Within Me
Within 14 days includes
Three days off
No
Yes that's up
In the set of whole numbers
Between 1 and 14
Right Within
No
This is a Thomas Ren's first made these claims in a speech he gave it a Colorado Springs stop on The Reawakening
America Tour
TBD that venue
Out of idiots on the panel with the headliner being General Flynn
He also had Stella Immanuel talked about on the show Patcher
Woodburn is also come up on the show
Alex's favorite grocer alfio
Skater speed
And what's this ovacue Patriots
Street Fighter Scott
Of course he was
Reduce the data he's playing this comes from it's all very suspicious
The most likely explanation for what's going on is that he's just trying to repack
Get to the old conspiracies about vaccine deaths that people took
Coronavirus data
Going back to July rent was serving as the lawyer for America
Does Frontline doctors
The wacko group of doctors who love hydroxychloroquine
Lawsuit on their behalf against the Secretary of Defense
Department of Health and Human Services
And in that filing he included a section about some alleged whistleblower
Testimony
Getting expert Jane Doe who is a computer programmer who had access to Medicare and Medicaid data
From the lawsuit
Quote in her expert opinion varies under-reported deaths
Caused by the vaccines by a conservative factor of at least five
As of July 9th 2021 various reported 9048 deaths associated with the vaccine
Dana from CMS medical claims
And has determined that the number of deaths occurred within 3 days of injection with a vaccine
Exceeds those reported by a by a factor of at least five
Indicating
That the true number of deaths caused by the vaccines at least
At this point
There was this 45,000
Configure which is based on Anonymous expert witness who is guessing that you can multiply the Thursday to buy 5
To get the true vaccine death
This is absolute garbage
Anna means nothing
She didn't get to this conclusion by way of data or death records she was just gassing and multiplying and then rinse put that into his wall
I'm not impressed by any of this and it's
Clearly him trying to just sort of redo the same hostel
This is
Until that he's bringing about is based on whistleblower information involving Medicare and Medicaid date
Yeah this is this is all just
3pac
Get depressed
Rims of the 44-year old dude who quote
Pass the Ohio bar exam in November 2019 on his
Fifth attempt
And his limited litigation experience according to a Washington Post examination of a
His career
You just found a Grifton
He's going with it he's running with it.
Yeah I mean you know
You can't say you can't say that the headliner that bill is doing anything different than that I mean it's basically the same s***
Some random person send them some random b******* and they drift off of it until they can you pass the bar
Couple months ago and you're like hey holyshit here's a career I'll make my career by being this guy
Yep and it worked there will never be any negative consequences in the
Future
You've got some other whistleblower document
That show that if you get vaccinated
More like
That doesn't make sense
That's Observatory
This is a direct quote
This is an exact quote
Document
Is it right
Exercise
An additional analysis appears to indicate
Incidence of covid-19
Increased
In each group of study participants
With increasing time Posto's to
Well
So does that mean that
Are you ask
Sing me it's supposed to be your information
I found this presentation on his website he has the slides up and it's really fun
The first slide is so f****** cock
Quote
Fact-checkers please post all apologies for misleading the American public on Facebook and Twitter
They will be censured shortly thereafter you could join the rest of us in social media jail
At no point in time
Look
If there's anything that we should Hammer into first graders this is
Before we get to arithmetic
The definition of
And ways to avoid
Hubris
That is all we need to start with that's a fundamental education
Avoid hubris
The story of Icarus is relevant
So I scroll down the to the page that ranz is talking about apparently and FDA briefing document from the vaccine
Seems unrelated biological product
Advisory committee meeting
From September 17th
This page on his presentation includes the heading of it and then a random
Paragraph from
The document
This is an easily accessible document you can find the whole thing you did not need a whistleblower to get to it
I'm packed I found it and what's going on is that the line that he read theirs being taken
Completely out of con
It does say that quote
An additional analysis appears to indicate that incidence of covid-19 generally increased
In each group of study participants
Fence with increasing time post dos2
At the start of the analysis
Suspiria
That is
Gotcha
Because rent is PowerPoint presentation just drop this paragraph out of the text
You wouldn't know what this is referring to or even what's being analyzed
Seems like that would be important
Information that is
This is a study that Pfizer carried out and it was meant to quote
Compare rates of covid-19 among
Participants
Completed the two-dose primary series early in the
The study
I either those were originally randomized into the experimental group
Versus those who were who
Completed the two-dose primary series
Later in the study
I either those were originally randomized to placebo
And then crossed over to the experimental group
There is not an unvaccinated group that these people are being compared to these specific
Appointed to study
Was just a test to see if there's a waning efficacy of the vaccine and if so was it something that should be addressed by boo
In the paragraph that rents uses they do say that people who got the shot earlier had 70 points
Three cases
/ 1000
Person years
Compare to 51.6 cases
For the group that was vaccinated more recently
In the same
Person years
That would tend to support Rent-A-Center
Or at least implied that vaccine efficacy could
Drop off a bit
Sure
However
Wren's very clearly intentionally ignored v-neck
Paragraph
Quote
In contrast during the Blind and placebo
Controlled follow-up. Of the study
The data cutoff March 13th 2021
Prior to the Delta Varian
Answer the internet
It's of covid-19 in a month
Recipients in the valuable
Valuable efficacy population
Nearly 60% of whom had four months or more of blinded follow-up
Post dos2
Was 12.6 cases per 1000 person
This observation
Suggest that while waiting immunity is 1 / 2
Cancel factor that may have contributed to the higher incidence breakthrough cases
During the Delta variance search
It's possible that other factors
EG
Dynamics of the Delta variant transmission and potential differences
In vaccine effectiveness
Cancel Delta variant versus strain circulated during the
Sibo control portion
How's the trial
May also have
Contributed
This isn't saying that the vaccine will make you more likely to get
Covid
The part that rents his using is saying that one dataset showed some indications of people who got vaccinated more recent
May have better protection than those people were vaccinated longer ago
But there's also dated
It seems to indicate that conclusion
Might not be so certain
Other factors
Could be involved
Adidas ignore that
Anyway Thomas Renzo just cherry-picking bullshittin pretending credible whistleblowers are involved needs
Rightly
Figure it out all this stuff
Only thing that he's figured out is that there's a lot of money to be made in being a lawyer for these right-wing s*******
Just keep doing the dude
Yeah I mean in this situation this is one of those like
Do you not know how to read
Do you not know how to read and comprehend or are you reading comprehending in line
Beatbox
I don't like if you pass the bar even on your 5th try
You can read and comprehend
Yeah you can sing or you memorize the answers to
It does tend to em all the surrounding context would lead somebody to a reasonable
Conclusion that he's intentionally ignoring
The other part and the context that makes this line make sense that does sound scary out of contacts
Much like the Seventh Amendment does sound like Alex got screwed out of context
But you need to know the context or else you just have
The alignment
It does seem like their entire job
Is turning something
Android
God
Look at this this is so unreasonable a reasonable person would never allow this to happen
And then not going
Well there is a reason
In for it
Also the
This guy apparently was the guy who found the
Not that Mike Adams he's reporting on
What is eBay
Roof doing a lot of work has got it all there's something going on
Institutions are under attack
Yeah meanwhile you look across our nation and all the other institutions
Raucous
Chords to default judgments on me when I gave them
Everything
Assigned a new judge in the second hearing I just said default
Cuz I've lost and
Every
The Bedrock is
Yeah it really is and I'm going to tell you Alex
We want to be peaceful
Freedom you've lost it
Air Bud
Just say you want to kill people Jesus Christ
Hey
We want to do this peacefully
But if we don't say I'm now then we won't be able to stay in later so the obvious
Distinction that I'm making is
We should be
Violet now
I listen to this and I checked in on some of these documents I found some
Suspicious
Presentation issues
Next up is really funny
I also have a bunch more information that I'm going to be breaking here coming up as soon as I can get it all analyzed
We always double-check our work before we say anything
Because you know we can't afford to lose our credibility
That's going to be tough
Wow
Just wow
I can't afford to lose my credibility so I'm going to go talk to
Alex Jones
This is the thing
This is why I can never be in charge because this type of s***
This is cartoonish and it requires cartoon based Solutions like this is when
If somebody does that
In my government
We drop an anvil on your head
Play this is a cartoon there's no reason to treat you like you're a real person or rang based solution
This is
How dare you
Clown so anyway these documents then
Document citrins has
However some of the documents that Alex has
And these are the reasons
He is under attack
And that's why you need to give him
Walking money
What you see on the news
All that
Online
Asian gentleman
If you support us and spread the word about the articles
Videos of rally behind
How to post on Twitter to Facebook
So much
I got to say
I know it's probably
Obvious
But his bike
Financial stuff is
Acute
Are not in this episode
It's it's
I fix that
He's he's
Very
Worry very much
For the third hour on Monday he has Wayne Allyn root
On the show who's a trumpy talk show host guy
I also made a name for himself originally in like
Sports gambling
Cool yeah
You suck
But he is on because he has
Apparently written an article
And maybe even a full book
About the necessity
Civil disobedience
I think he wants to bring himself something of a Gandhi for the Trump era describe
I mean look
Violet resist
Going to get you to the top
In today's conservative climate
No at the same time a lot of this is just him
Kind of
Discovering
Elementary ideas about organization
I like
A Grassroots activist
Conservatives kind of hint from him all these years
In the book
The whole book is about one way of a tie
Which is the way Jesse Jackson and Al Sharpton
The last four decades
They intimidate Corporate America
I'm a Believer Alex that nothing happens
On the politicians
A bunch of nobodies right
The money is what allows them
To be important to make policy
Giroud our country
Politicians in my opinion
The most important ones are owned by China
Either owned or blackmailed
Even if we are the majority
And we've been the silence
Majority
My book The Great Patriot protest a boycott book
Is all about making us
The loud majority
We got to be loud
We got to tell Corporate America all the checks
And actually politician
Not with $10
Or a hundred dollars $4,000
P.y.t. million-dollar
So the politicians listen to them
And we got to bring to their knees and starved
Elementary level putting Financial pressure on businesses
This is
Ineffective
Organizing
Strategy
But unfortunately one of the things that he's going to quickly learn is that a lot of these same people that he would like to
The pressure also fund all of the information space
And the politician
That he supports there is that problem
Yeah it's kind of going to end up being shooting yourself in the
The foot now what
He doesn't understand
Because he can't take
Get that next step further
Is that this is an
Endemic to the entire cyst
And any idea of him being on the right side is quite left
Yeah but
Discovering
Something that everyone is already aware of
For a long time
But it's cute
Pisa do you know what
The management is
Has really taken
Taking advantage of the workers
And I just don't think we're being paid well
And there's just no way to negotiate them with by myself because they can just fire me and I know I don't have any protection
Law doesn't protect
Text me this is a free market
Consists of the only ways the only way is if we all come together
And do something like with
Hold something from these corporate power Brokers
It's all how could we do that
Probably probably not all the way no way there's just no way I found a way
This is so sad
I hired a team of telemarketers
Dialed 116
Most liberal
Companies in America
Marseilles
We conservatives Christians and Patriots
Are the ones buying their products
But they're spitting in our face
Identified what I think of that
Coca-Cola AT&T
Ben & Jerry's
Victoria's Secret
And we can bring them to their knees
Do I have the telemarketers find out what
102 phone calls
Pushing pushing pushing
What's the phone number to CL
What's the email for the co
What's this social media account
What's the website
What is the physical mailing address
I got the board of directors names
And the CEOs names
So now you just open the book
And you dial
Discipline implies that it's not his grassroot is who is he wants to sort of imagining me I had to hire a team of telemarketers to harass
Quite literally
They are paid protesters
Fun stupid
What's the recent like story about how AT&T
Company you know that company that is essentially built a trust
Is unwilling to budge on coverage or anything like that big
Think of Lila Kedrova
Telemarketer
So woke
Eddie paid them
Define theory
Contact information
A CEO's
Stop this book so you can harass them
You know what
I'm fine with that
Because one
I think it's hilarious
It's fine if that's how you get to Corporation
By picking the most woke ones
Fine you win
I got the most woke corporations you're not going to like the outcome
Exactly
Are not served by these corporations
When you say whatever Powers right now or liberal
But whatever it is you need to hate those Corporation
I'm fine with it
God bless
Yeah I think I think that if
Some kind of
The quote on quote
FIFA groupware
Finding CEOs of
Right-leaning
Companies like Hobby Lobby
Or whatever it posted their contact information
No also I think is an antifa group
The most right leading Corporation
It would be
The Identical f****** list but this a****** I bet there would be over
So
I look Wayne
Good good on you I guess
I only like if you're posting like
Ways to get in contact with
Decision maker
4 carburetor
I don't know if that's bad
But if you're putting like home addresses or phone numbers are dachshund people
I think that's still maybe like
I don't know if I add at school I'm not sure what
It might just be a corporate email address that's in his book
There's a tale of
Victory that Wayne has got his
Saddest f****** thing I've ever heard
And what just one person upon my book one
On the first day came out
Set me an email and said Wayne
I sent an email to the head of Nordstrom's
Costco
Roketsan why are you boycotting
Don't do this. What can I do to make you happy
I was one can you imagine if we got 100,000
4 million Patriots
I do this every day
Five minutes adjacent 3 out tomorrow
A new three the next
So you hit this guy got like
Customer service emails
We're going to take this country back
Huh
No way they'll figure out how to organize their inbox
Here I Am the CEO of Costco I got 100,000
Emails
Saying if people were going to boycott us but
Our numbers are unaffected
I'll ignore these emails
2%
Maybe whenever these emails come in
Formal response so no I'm so sorry oh my God
An email campaign
Huh boy
You know I was just thinking about that woman's marching of the 22 million
Walking through the streets and how effective that was Buttman
That did everything I can't believe what would have happened if they had run an email camp
I can't count the number of times where like you know I've had something that didn't get delivered or something they like
I ordered a A-Frame
From Wayfair
Didn't,
You know like a little kid
Email about how like you this sucks
I got a response
I'm so sorry
Yeah everyday
To pay their workers more
That one they they did a little while
Quiet
So we're unlikely.
Is not good
And I'll tell you I'm not the most religious person in the entire
But I do believe this is the devil
Rules for Radicals is there Bible the left
Dedicated to Lucifer
And it's not a coincidence that the other day said
Well we haven't passed my agenda yet
Play 3.5 trillion dollar bill
Why did he say it that way
Cheer chants
York weather sending out
Dammit sending out devil codes
There's nothing I can do for you sir
Sir
I'm going to have to ask you to leave
Six week six months
That's the devil is obviously the devil
Boy
I got this. Ever
Response and you know obviously Alex is in
And not good mood
Now about
The the the the cases could use some money
He's desperately trying to fundraise
Yeah I am
Let me know
Updates
It's hilariously transparent
On these episodes he hasn't reached a point yet where it would be like
Losing his s***
Right you know I still think that maybe on the horizon
Yeah
Yeah I mean I'm listening to this
Even for an Infowars listener
I am observing some of this news
And I'm just going
This ship
Is Sanka
Everytime he says he needs money to fight the globalists all I hear is another bucket of water going on
That ship if you're a fan even like how do you not hear this and be like oh he's saying you really really needs money
He just
Ended up being on the hook for a lot of
Money
In those lawsuits
I think it's connected I don't know if he's trying to expand
Search my memory real quick
His last
Expansion
Was coursing in d.c.
Well no cuz he also did that likes out Firepower out show that got cancelled
Not a good track record
What about that show that was all colors that he's going to start
On the back burner for
Anytime now
Oh I got hair done Smith he's going to do all calls I remember that
I want Wildfire David Knight
Where's Steve
I know I was kind of hoping
Perceive
Piercy about the lawsuits
Wheel well
Attract
Some other days after this on Mondays episode
But
So you know just be too much bite off
All at once
Will be back
For that until then
We're website.com
We also are on
We are we are is that knowledge underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan
And you just launched an insta
Instagram for the show
We got to promote a little bit just decided that we should put our
Cat pictures somewhere
Boat is a very generous we gotta get with it
You everybody wants to see the saline bit 8 years from now we're going to get on
Tik-Tok ever going to happen for us
Knocked out anyway we'll be back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo MDX Clark I'm Daryl rundus
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color