Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Fix-It around the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex G
Nordam
Damn
What's up what's your rights
My bright spot today is I was able to partake in
Over the weekend cuz I was invited over to Friend of the show Friends of the show
Shockey's house I got an invite to go over and watch the gcw
Game Changer wrestling pay-per-view
Gabe's vs. Jon Moxley in a deathmatch
Which is definitely not
My thing
You don't like that matches are they like real bloody
To believe they're good
But this whole thing is like
Understand this fully until kind of like watching this matching
The pieces together it's basically like with deathmatches it's like alright
There's some glass over here
I'm going to throw you through that
Running there's a sharp thing over here you're going to throw me through that right
It's at that over and over again
It's very it's very weird I don't enjoy it
Competitive
Running while innocent bystanders are carrying pain class
Everywhere you go
Yeah it needs it was not it's not my thing I don't enjoy it in terms of
I'm not even the biggest fan of pro wrestling but when I am it's not that stuff
Yeah there's a bit of blood
The hope that the rest of the pay-per-view is kind of like
Like I expected there to be more deathmatches that was like
Rose almost no blood or anything throughout the the whole proceedings were they good
Like the matches were good it was very in quality some of those all right
The audience was kind of weird I don't know they're a little bit
The low energy
Deathmatch itself here's my review
Disappoint is underwhelming
Only one man should have left
It was disgusting like I would like they're bleeding around and it's like
Why would you do that
Hey I wasn't shocked
There was nothing like
Really exciting about it so the wrestler 20 years ago is great
But when you're doing these things
I know that you don't know who they are necessarily looking like Nick Gage ER
Huge
Names in
This sort of Arena two of them competing for the championship belt
Fixer High
Like they need to deliver something that's like
Wow someone died
See that I was very
I was very bored
Engrossed
What are things that Nick gave does he cuts people with a pizza cutter
Circular pizza cutter that cuts their forehead
So Jon Moxley got a pizza cutter early in the match
And was cutting
Nick Gates Right
Right
Don't
Don't say those words and act like I'm supposed to act like that's fine
It was not a grown adult man we got a pizza cutter
Cinemax
All in good fun
For competition
Nick games did not bleed all that much
From the cuts right then later on in the match
Got the pizza cutter and was cutting Boxley and I noticed
But his technique was different and that he used his thumb
Noticing that during a death
That's how bored I have that's that's too much awareness
So anyway it's not for me but it was a fun time and it was really nice to see Marty and Sarah
I hope someday they invite me somewhere to
Anyway
I know that predisposed that evening
Indisposed
But that's what makes
More fun whenever you complain about not getting an invite that you couldn't go to anyways everybody knows we're having a great time
I meant I'm an a****** in is
My partner and I
Celebrate her birthday at the casino
As we talked about earlier
Mom it was
Very fun sure lights
Casino parts
Terrible don't like them
There's a lot of slot machines and I don't understand them whatsoever so many of them
People just sitting there smoking
Bananas I'm walking over there and the Fate my favorite part that was there was a
There was a no smoking
Which
It coming from Chicago I was like oh how quaint
Yeah there's a no-smoking area that's very small
And you go over there and you see
Those are the saddest
Worst slot machines they have they're all from 1960
B5 they look like the cash registers from 1940s you know like that kind of thing
And it was so clear that they're just like
We can still do the
This here there's nowhere else we can do this right some man with a bone to pick
Do you know what I mean
We can sit in
Smoke and drink really bad free cocktails
Everywhere else we go
Everywhere else we go people who don't smoke or like you can smoke
Here though you go in the corner
That's such a bummer
The whole vibe of a casino's Obama
I was after you mentioned this on our life episode my buddy Burger who I used to go to the island
Free casino website
Message me and it reminded me of
Some things that we were talking it's like at the casinos really depressing but what's worse is
The dog track
We can't go to a do know you can't go to Nikki gibsontown I went along with him to the dog track
I remember
Sad remember
I remember how bad the dog track is and I don't remember s*** birthday go to the.
If you really want to plumb the depths of just human desperation
I want to go further down the rabbit hole
See how much our psyches can take
Going to make us stronger
Yeah I think I was texting you incessantly because
I couldn't leave
Yeah so far away from Tampa
You couldn't go anywhere huh
Episode to go over we're going to be talking about October 5th 2020
I jumped the gun on that one
Photo finish
We need the we need to see
See who exactly
This one's going to be a review I do like eventually we ever get big enough there will be people
Combing through the audio files looking at exactly like
Damn long life is a brooder film is going back
Text Bruce frame-by-frame Hazard audio
There's going to be sabermetrics
Hey what what can we say
Moneyball
So this episode is fun
Alex's Beach
Smoking Gun of smoke
Looking guns
Is that the Smoking Gun that shot another Smoking Gun
Killed it
I mean
Yeah it don't make sense
The Gate of Gatesville Electric
Overhyping nonsense
It's actually kind of fun and I enjoyed looking into it so I am look forward to sharing some of this with you
Let's say hello does new walk
The first Jordan Deuce Bungalow Yale Juggalo thank you so much you are now apology
Thank you very much
Lyrics to thankful and fascinated disappointment to conspiracy theory
I'm a policy wonk
Comedies cats AKA
Paralegals thank you so much during our policy walk
Thank you
Speaking with Newsroom Dixie cup thank you so much you are now policy walk
We're really not going it out of the park
Wicked fellow in smudge the cat leave a small donation of kibble at the altar of Celine thank you so much or how tall is he
I got back to dungeon master Mike's thinking about you and I hope all is well
Master Mike thank you
And finally Spencer Williams loves non-structural cheese thank you so much
Your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Are you a bot
Thank you all
Jordan
To make up for
Sometimes we don't have
Contact drops
To make up for it
I have two for you today and you can decide which one of these you enjoy more
Designed to be in danger
Amazon to work 18 hours a day
Children and
Amazing Sunset Center
Animals in chess
The first one
I feel like that's plagiarism that's it that's the like we want to be free to do what we want to do speech
It was a little bit longer than most of our contacts drops but I felt like
It didn't belong in any Glyph of the episode 1 of make love
Capitalize design
Play the second one
So
His wife could eat no lean because the
Lick the platter clean
Yep
Accountability
Oh well hey you gotta move on
You just keep plowing through
Yep
Sprouts
Oh s*** I forgot the rest of it so I don't know I don't know if you want to make a choice or people listeners can tell us
Which is the better out of context drop
That's Tuff
I mean the first one
Grocer
Yeah
Light rail
They're both appealing in different ways there in a certain death match of their own right
Disappoint
Yeah that's
Restart on October 5th
Wow thank you so much for joining us on this live
Tuesday October 5th
Petoskey advisor executive
On video admitting that they know that the vaccine is destroying people's immune system
And that it's a higher rate of people that are sick they're taking the vaccine
And it's causing a d e
Dependent enhancement
It's a
And normally that would be a top story
But it's not
Is it because finally people are kind of gotten the idea that these guys are full of s*** all the time no cuz I was a bigger
Your Story by real quick on this project if you hear that name and you don't immediately like
Boo-boo either an idiot or convexo
So the video that they put out is largely about the idea that natural immunity is better than the immunity one would get
From vaccinations
This of course is a false Choice that's being presented where what option is getting vaccinated and the other is survival
Covid
This conveniently ignores a whole lot of variables like the possibility of dying or having
Severe complications from getting covid
These things aren't factored in
Because the video is arguing a stupid
Fake point
There's no evidence of this video that drives our knows the vaccines are causing adee nor that they're wiping out immune system
There's one secretly recorded interview with a guy who's credited as a quote senior associate scientist
Who says that the rise in cases were seeing with a Delta variant is
Is possibly attributable to addict
Priests efficacy of the vaccine overtime
Or the immunity waning
This is being misrepresented by Alex to be this guy saying that over time the vaccine destroys your immune system when in reality
It's just him explaining that the
Protection you may have went from 95% to 70% affect
Is a person having a loose conversation not someone who's citing hard information
So I don't know how much I would Bank on even
In the specifics of
It sounds like they finally got them
Nailed to the wall
Allow the rest of the video is talking about Pfizer profiting from the vaccine and if that's a conversation to Veritas
I welcome that conversation
Let's go ahead and nationalize production and distribution of the necessary medical breakthroughs that happened
Suspicion about profit motives
It just goes away I mean considering the fact that these are financed with federal funds I eat our money
How is it that then Vega to make money off of
The things that were paid for them to pick her up
Welcome Veritas championing that position but because they're not actually concerned if eyes are profiting off exit
Didn't want to use that fact that they do make a profit as a prop
2 attack actual vaccine
All in all this video is lousy with fake argue
Project Veritas 11 with itself
Essentially meaningless
Regret that I watch
Such a waste of time I can't believe you did
I'm proud of you
We got a knothead
I know that I say every time that a project Veritas thing happens like where this is the last time I'm looking
Daddy. It's for you
Nobody else believes them anymore except for people who already believe this s*** that there's
Just justifying for them or the only person who goes in there
Curious
Wanting to fight
And every now and again I think they really do impress by lying in a new way that's
The creative new way
That's not the top story
Rick is here
Is the motherfuking top story
But that's our second biggest story
Ladies and gentlemen
You saw you heard
Broadcast
Emergency Tuesday broadcast fauci talks about staging
Healthcare
With new virus
In 2019 video
Amazing crew ended up staying up here until
Last night
To bring you an emergency Monday transmission and then believe me I didn't just come up here for fun if this is an emergency
How is today's broadcast
This confirms a premeditated
Halcyon the video
With the head of
Health and Human Services
Virus out of China
The scary wanted to accepting the new mRNA technology
This is just a
Pathetic attempt on Alex's part to grasp at straws to build up and reinforce his covid
Conspiracy
Even before I get into any of the details on this just take a moment to grasp
How stupid Alex is in what nonsense he expects this audience
Except
Here he is saying about tree and other immune immune ology experts got together and discuss how they needed a new stars covid
The bird flu
In order to get people to accept vaccine
Does Alex know that coronavirus isn't influenza viruses are
Completely different he absolutely does not know that what you saying is gobbledygook
Did Samantha it's magic
What's going on
In October 2019 he was part of a panel hosted by the Milton Inn
Which was broadcast on C-Span
This was a discussion about the breakthroughs in science and technology that it made it conceivably possible
Who created vaccine
That actually work
Universally against all strains of influenza
Most of the discussion is about the frustrating reality that there's a lack of funding and that that's a lack of motivation
Call the part of the industry to pursue this sort of thing
Which makes sense and socks
There's literally no discussion of staging a pandemic this is
Sweetly made-up
I was just make sure we get
To playing this clip any of it I mean it would save
He gets to playing
Eclipse haha 50 minutes into the episode I was like where is the
Furious that's banana
I'm going to play for you the clip of the panel that he calls the smoke
Okay
This is heavily edited and a lot of things that sound suspicious make perfect sense
In the context of the talk
The only way for these
The dudes who have created this clip that we're about to listen to
Is to actively watch the panel and edited
Contacts there's no other explanation for this
9:52
I had to stay up late with my team editing this down into something we can lie about right
Everyone can actually take quite a
While talking about
That's not cuz I think there is a valuable illustration that we can make
By going
To the source material
God comparing it
To the way that Alex present sounds great but here is the
Combined clips
Of the panel
Why don't we blow the system up
I mean obviously we can't just turn off the spigot
On the system we have
And then say hey everyone in the world should get this new vaccine we've been given to anyone yet
But there must be some way that
We grow back seems mostly in eggs the way we did in 1947
Transition
From getting out of the
True
Results
Canby
Beneficial
Just something has to be much better
And then you got to go through all of the
Clinical trials phase one's face-to-face tree and then show
This particular product
It's going to be good over a. Of years
If it works perfectly
Is going to take a decade
There might be a need
Or even an urgent call for
An entity
Beholden to bureaucratic strings and an in Prophecy
Foreseeing influenza is going to be very difficult
Change that
Unless you
I'm okay with your perception is
Wheaton Woods arrest the problem in a disruptive
Because she do need both
But it is not
Too crazy to think that an outbreak of an novelabia virus could occur in in China
Somewhere
Beeman to a number of regional centers if not local if not even in your home at 10
OnPoint
And France those vaccines on a pageant self-administer
So that's the entirety of the clips that he has got together from
Right
How long has it been
45 minutes early maybe about 15 minutes
Well they should have added it down to just that
Hell yeah memes like they didn't have anything else important to say no certainly not
We're going to go through this each clip by each
Which clip that Alex put into this compilation
Discuss the context
Where they come from and what they're talkin about
So here's the first flipping out
Why don't we blow the system up
I mean obviously we can't just turn off the spigot
On the system we have
And then say hey everyone in the world should get this new vaccine we've been given to anyone yet
But there must be some way that
We grow back seems mostly in eggs the way we did in 1947
So this is the moderator of the discussion Michael Specter of the New Yorker
His question was very clearly about technological innovations in the Spear of vaccines
It was a prop that had to do with how this is not a space that is kept
Pace
With other field
Here is that clip in it
So it's part of my life
Do people use the
Word
Children Dollywood
I mostly
But I'm going to use it now just ruption
Why don't we blow the system up
I mean obviously we can't
Spigot on the
The system we have
And then say hey everyone in the world should get this new vaccine we've been given to anyone yet
But there must
Be somewhere
Grow back
Axiom's mostly in
In eggs the way we did in 90
I mean we live in a world where I can download whatever
Song I want
Onto my phone
Command
And we Grove.
Maxine's the way we did
70 years ago
What is going on with
That
It's conversation is about disrupt
In the field of Technology
Isolated portion of it that Alex played together and sounds like what they're really looking
4 is a catalyst to make everybody exactly
Play so if there's not going to be one that
It's just going to happen naturally we'll make one
In order to blow up assist
Shot it
So here's the second clip with Alex plays that first one of Michael Specter was from 8 minutes in
Yeah now the next clip is fauci from 22 minutes in
Pain order to make the transition
From getting out of the
True
Results
Canby
Beneficial
Does something have to be much better
And then you got to go through all of the
Clinical trials Phase 1 phase two space three and then show
This particular product
It's going to be good over a. Of years
If it works perfectly
Is going to take a decade
This is actually kind of fair like it's I don't think it's
Really all that Miss representative
Talk to you was talking about how there were break Thursday
The scientists were making in terms of universal flu vaccine
But it would be something that would still take a long time
He's not talking about the time tables that would take to make
An mRNA coronavirus vaccine
It's a different conversation but like
Sure
You saying it's something would take a long time
Look up work Sprite and it's not like
I don't know if this is this is this
Close to like okay at least it's not like maliciously out of context
Wheatley like separate conversation
I mean the obvious thing about that though it's like
What they're also describing is not just a decade of like researching
In developmental all of that I wouldn't be
To surprise
As if they had something that they building around right now that is like
30% effective against most flu and it's like okay they can refine that and then
Eventually it's going to have
How to get down to
Let's test it if we're going to give it to everybody where you have to test it on after
And this what yeah and that's a really good point
He also felt she is also discussing how this is on the shoulders of
This is research that's already in
In the process there's there's more to it
It's close
It's not nearly as bad as the rest of the
Here is the
Third clip
Which are Alex's cut-in
This is from
32 minutes
So 10 minutes after that last
There might be a need
Or even an urgent call for
An entity
Beholden to bureaucratic strings and an in processing so that clip out of context makes no sense
You don't know what is he talking about
I mean I guess what he's trying to say is that the government is acting to slow our I guess what Alex is trying to make you think
He sang is that because the government can tax
The way that we want it
To right now then there needs to be an outside entity that is not
Beholding to all of those laws
The evil government that keeps them from doing stuff we need
Satanism
Oh okay well here's the full contact
I'm I I think I'll
Also
That is just a
I mean it probably hasn't been
For quite some time
Tell me when I was in grad school everyone
Hib vaccine
Ettore Harriet Robinson
Where can I find nav
For Hy-Vee in
I came to the lab and
Everyone's working
You can do whatever one else is doing I got a little bit of left
Blue money
Lou Grant over there
And no one's in
What to do on that challenge
To make it sex
I think we have
To I like the
Disrupting
Field
If we are just
Continually thinking we're going to
Working on that
Another iteration or a
Think we need to continue or doing but
Another eight
Fashion or another ass
SAR another step
I don't know if that's enough
Recite those
Really creative thinkers
So in addition
Into doing what we're doing worse
So good at
I think in parallel
There might be a need
Or even
An urgent call for
An entity
Out there that's completely
Disruptive
That's not
Beholden to
The bureaucratic
Strings in
And processing
Well
Galvanized
Put a lot of
And I think that
Easiest way to get
Grad student really excited
It's too early to put it down on it
A lot of money
Yes you will know
There has been moved
Certain members
Congress Ed Markey
Put a billion
Increasing
Influenza for univer
Where is the flu vaccine by a billion dollars
5 years
Family Dollars
Over it
Year for five years
When you put that
Investment you will get
People excited
Not to do the
You'll get new people
Come in with new ideas that artist
Disruptive
And looking at it
So when you haven't
Resources
That's how
With HIV
So predominantly what they're talkin about and it becomes pretty clear when you listen to the full answer
And they talked about it a bit more throughout to is there needs to be
Some kind of dedicated flu
Entity
That has funding
For this new research
Because it when you have the money you attract
Creative thinkers who can attack the problem from other
Angles things you wouldn't think of the innovate
It's disruptive to the status quo of how
Treatment has been bottled up till this point
Nextdoor
It's obvious I mean he's
Did that that
We need a changes
It when he's talking about his grad school
And all of those people doing one thing and it's like
Oh
That makes perfect
Obviously
It is not this guy trying to steal the powers
The government
Create a super virus that will wipe out Humanity
No
So it's not
It's not that okay
So here's the fourth Cliff this is fauci and this is from
42 minute
I can do that so we're jumping around 10 minutes
So we really do have a problem with how the world perceives
Influenza is going to be very difficult
The change that
Unless you
Okay with your perception is
We can address the problem in a disruptive way
Because you do need both
So
What is out-of-context obviously
You know people don't take the flu seriously enough so we're going to make them take it seriously
We're going to teach them a real life
That's not what he was saying at all
It's the Diversey
City of what influence
To the community
For some people they get
The flute the real
Not like
But the real flu
They get better
So this August
Perception
If it's so serious
People get flu a
And it isn't it
Catastrophe
When you dealing with the disease like HIV
To get HIV
Serious
Whether you're young
Whether you're middle-aged will
You're old
Cancel
That bad
Whether you're young weather
Intermediate
Where is width
Wednesday
For some people they go throughout life
Active
There isn't anybody that's afraid of
You going to focus
Open you say are you afraid of getting HIV if you weren't with of
You afraid of getting cancer absolutely
Are you afraid of
I mean
The reality
The flu
Isaiah Isaiah
We're responsible
Variety
Diseases
Macon County
Is malaria
Tuberculosis
Zika Ebola
The middle of Ebola right now
So you go
The DRC
See where I was
Went to a week and a half
And you getting somebody
You worried about influenza
When you talk
Influenza
They don't
Influenza because I have enough problems
With malaria
Tuberculosis
Bowling
So what is it
Perception
Which is a myth
That it is not a serious
Disease
What is Casey
Hundreds of thousands
People diabetes
Millions and millions
So we really do have a problem with how the world
Influenza
And it's going to be very difficult
Change that
Unless you
Within
I'm okay with your perception
Wicked Witch
The problem is
Disruptive
Both so
Essentially
If you take the entire context of the clip in
Into consideration
What do you saying is that there's not going to be public pressure
Ever really to deal with this for the flu
Influenza vaccine
Possibly be something that could be created isn't going to come from people who are like I'm terrified of getting the flu
No one's calling their representative being like if you guys don't
Fund flu research right now
I'm so essentially we what he is is advocating is we need to do this from within
The people who are the researchers
Yeah I need to
Treat the problem as it is not as people perceive its right
Right now makes total sense.
It's very obvious
That's not even it that's not even hard you could have just
Hey
Do people take the flu seriously
No is that bad
Probably
DND
Yeah I got it
What Alex is doing is taking selfies words and do the Magic Tree
Basically
So here's the fifth clip which is the one that I strongly suspect is what made Alex cover this clip to begin
But it is not
Too crazy to think that an outbreak of an novelabia virus could occur in in China
Somewhere
FEMA to a number of regional centers if not local if not even in your home at 10
OnPoint
And Prince those vaccines on a pageant self-administer
That's a fascinating
Lady about technology
That would be so cool but he mentioned China and vaccine vaccines and there you go
Anyway here's the full clip
Adventure who
He thinks we are having
Plane from
In Orange
Clinton New York
Deliverable
How
How far are we
Far away but I don't
Two crazy eyes
Remove Tori
Maxine
Remove the
Dependency
We can move into
That Niger
Those sequins
Shared
Around the world
The small fry
Kevin made
In a shoebox
Is translatable
2A 3D
Napa
Those
Analogies are
But it is
Novelabia
We could get
Get the rnase
Vmat2
Number of
Local if
Your home at 10
Where Waze
Adapted
That doesn't mean it doesn't prove s***
It's it's just the weakest bombshell I've seen him try to pass off
Like you hear that and it's like though they're discussing
Hypothetical
I need to make this very fully clear
Very specifically in the context
Text of
Universal flute
The entirety of it is nothing to do
With a coronavirus the way that Alex's
Nothing nothing
And am nothing matches like the idea that they were planning something
Outbreak
To pick this new technology
They're discussing
New technology
I I swear to you
I cannot believe
That you can't sell
People on
This
Okay
Take
10 billion dollars away from the military
They won't even f****** notice
They don't have an accounting process
Apparently.
Towards
Making Universal flu vaccine printers
That you can have in your house
Incredible
Yeah I would have a problem with that
Everybody everybody
But more importantly the only people who have a problem with it now or
Big corporations who can't
That sell that probably
What does insulin think is really fascinating is that I watch
This whole
Presentation this whole panel
And it's the stuff that was very intentionally ignored
There's one comment that sink
Ratably bizarre that they left out considering they cut out clips from before and after this
In the panel.
Discussion I wonder why they didn't include this
Anywhere in this room were probably vaccinologist were probably immunologist
Preferably working on some vaccine made some back pain at some point in our life it
We're not the chemical Engineers are the other Engineers are they Anthropologist or others
To bring
Critical insight
And how you disrupt and deconstruct
A nasal problem and we've had these vaccines for 70 years
So this is an age-old
Contract
That requires those creative shaft that come out the
Kitchen deconstruct the carrot cake
I can make it look like
Play something different
The best care
Take your battery in your entire life
We need that for the influenza
Vaccine
And we also need to not forget
That poor influenza
Vaccines are the only part
Solution
I mean it's so easy to get caught up if you want to get sexy influenza
You do stay in the back seat space
But if you go into the diagnostic space for the therapeutic station non-pharmaceutical interventions
Those are the early steps
That will make a huge impact on Benny that epidemic her proceed no and a pandemic outbreak
That's why you have to have that
Single
Focus and today
Focus on stopping influenza
Not only on
Making us
That's weird
So you're saying that they don't necessarily want to only make a vac
Maxine
They want to use multi
Triple treatment
It's almost like they're Public Health
Professionals and experts who are discussing ways of treating a problem dealing with the problem as opposed to what
Alex is presented as
Which is they want to just put dabs in everybody
It is ironic that he is describing
The antithesis to Ali
You know that like
The the creative Chef who can come in and turn an amazing carrot cake into something that you don't think of the carrot cake
And you can eat deliciously without being like scared
Alex
Is the person who takes an amazing carrot cake
That won't get you f******
Killed by a virus and then goes
It's going to
Kill you
Truth it's the same job
Yeah
So I I want I watch this I saw the eclipse that Alex
Just just
Weakest attempt
I've seen to make a bombshell out of something
Does not get a degrade no I don't think that this to stay till 8
To get this kind of work done cuz this sucks
Yeah
I think that the I also enjoyed watching
Show presentation
So I appreciate Alex bringing that to my attention nice
But this is
Where are The Smoking Gun
Call Smokin gun absorb for me yes
Is the Smoking Gun of all smoking guns
Smoking guns Hoboken gods and when you add it to
Wuhan lab and fauci Indian
Function for viruses
Which is the covid-19 virus it is Joya
Unbelievable
Open and shut
Let me know if it's a smoking got a Smokin Guns of Smoking Gun what am I
The editor too hard
And then there's also a question
Do you need all of these other
Narrative
Combine all of it together for to be even
Marginally persuasive invisible Smoking Gun is smoking guns
Stupid it does seem though that if that is the Smoking Gun it Smoking Gun
And then we can at least be sure he's only going
Going to talk about that narrative from here on out because that's the one I mean it's got to be the most important be the only important
Yeah you probably take most of the you know the Restless episodes
Of the segment
Well I mean you just talked about it for a little while actually completely agree with
If this is the smoking guy need to be talked about it all day it's the only important
You should hear the 3-hour so he could play the entire thing
I still have 2 hours left
Obey Smoking Gun
Is that you no longer need evidence past
The gunman smoke it's cuz it's smoked
It's smoking did you shot something
Someone
There's a there's a there's nobody was like okay but now let's go find out where is shoes came from
Yeah we got it
We've got the Smoking Gun open-and-shut case
Look we make money on clothes for the cops
God so Alex Alex believes that not only did talk to do this
There was a specific
Okay and Alex know it's the countries that Alex thinks are white
Primary targets
Australia New Zealand Canada Europe
UK the US
We have a background of free-market and right to self-defense
Christianity
Bears against the system
Abortion and Satanism
Multiculturalism
Bio-weapon no one else is taking
That's just not true
You just make a slippery slope argument that the first look
If you force people
To recognize that race is a f****** social contract and has nothing to do and we're all just the same people all the time
What's next
Bioweapons
Probably
So the message that Alex is trying to send is that the MRNA vaccines are a weapon and they're being deployed against the country that he sees as Christian and
That's what's up
Text hear it
It's very cool
This is all just a zonolite persecution complex talking though since countries all over the world of authorized views of both the Pfizer
When you get right down to it it's really just about money
Very few countries have the ability to actually manufacture mRNA vaccines and companies that do aren't sharing that she
Because it would cut into their profits
The lower-income countries can't afford to buy large amounts of these vaccines for their population
Mako with less effective but more affordable alternative
Or maybe just not able to vaccinate the vast majority of the public have
Anyway this is a load of bulshit the only real message Alex is trying to spread here is that white people are under attack because that's
The theme of the show
Yeah it's a lot faster than I was
Expecting I didn't I didn't I didn't go faster than I expected
That that I understand I meant more in the contacts
The sentencing
We're talking about bioweapons
It's all about bio-weapons their child
Multiculturalism wait what
It's now it's race
Stated about
So
Talk to use on this
Packing tape
Smoking Gun bragging
Dab
I didn't hear that
That's
Do you know why he did that
That's what villains in movies
Why do villains in movies do it
Because they're based off of people like fauci
Jared Anthony Criminal
Hiding in plain view
Remember
Movies with villains or sci-fi films are dystopic known
Does the villain brag about what they do
They love to monologue
What they're planning very thinly veiled
In front of you
Before they do it
Just like the Riddler or the Joker will
Breaking on TV or radio
Tell you he's sending you a tree
Come knocking in the night
In the form of
So that it makes it more fun like the Zodiac Killer bragging in movies is done as an easy way
Need to fill in gaps in the plot with big
Exposition
That's what it is that's typically the narrative
A function of its the movie telling you what the movie did
Yeah it's also really convenient
Because it gives the right away to create a situation where the hero is dead to rights on the villain is all but one
But because of hubris the heroes able to wiggle out of the situation at
Classic U-verse is croosh
The Riddler sent out riddles because I was his whole character
Obsessed with puzzles inside of the Batman was the best person to test his abilities again
There's not a good choice
The Riddler actually worked for Bruce Wayne until Bruce Wayne neglected him or he had an accident or something and then riddles
Everywhere I look there's a lot of different versions of characters
But he's
He gives out riddles cuz he's the riddle
That's where the Joker he's criminally insane there was that
There was that
But Alex thinks he's living in a spy movie so it's
To come as no surprise that he imagines his pretend filling
Are taunting him like a bondability yeah
It's just really sad to see the likes he has to go to create the impression that they're actually doing that though
This bombshell today is a
Particularly weak example of that
Lucy's people taunting him at all corners
Yeah it does feel like it you do it
Movies are realer than the reality you see
You know like him
Cuz it exactly in real life
You don't monologue
Because that would
Waste time
I mean they f******
You know like that they didn't f****** monologue you know be an interesting is if you are a villain
And you're about to commit your crime monologue and then you're like
Didn't feel as good as I thought it would do that one again
You know what I thought
That would really be exciting Piazza monologue my crime out cuz normally I don't do it that only hope
Really step into those shoes hold
And you know what I just
Left me cold I don't feel I don't feel real bummer
It's a real bummer it's like meeting your Heroes you know who perform a monologue in a
On my lock situation
Or maybe that's a sign that you need to like checking in on if you're depressed
It doesn't feel good maybe you don't know the things that you would imagine that
Play commercials or whatever
These days
Yeah
I do think it's really silly
Nathan Alex beliefs
But that is bananas
Yep Alex believes that are actually much more f***** up
Open dangerous though
8:15
The Battle of Waterloo
Wellington defeated
Is British
Polian Bonaparte
Carrier pigeons the coast
I'm fast
Corvette ships across to announce that morning
For Wellington and lost a war
The British stock market plunge by 99%
Rothschild of course again
Then they came in with the news oh my God
Wellington has lost British Army destroyed
British Empire collapse Napoleon rules the Earth
Hahaha
Hundred
Plus years later
System rule the entire
Planet
Russia and a few other countries
Wow
So we talked about this in depth
In the end game coverage
Brief refreshers that story that Alex is telling about Nathan Rothschild is not
True
It has its roots in a pamphlet that was distributed by a giant anti-semite whose pen name was Satan
But I was actually named George.
Write the pamphlet released in France was titled the edifying and curious history of Rothschild the first king of the
Jews
From that point forward the story became a piece of anti-Semitic Allure passed down through generations of people who swear they don't actually a Jewish B
The story would be dramatized in the 1940 Nazi propaganda film the Rothschilds shares in Waterloo
To put it bluntly Alex either thinks this fake story is true or he knows it's a lie that's been historically used to incite public hatred of
Jewish people
Passing it along to his audience as the truth anyway
I would say whatever is true Alex is a horrible source of
Information
I'd really like to know what to orokin thinks about this
With
,
King of the Jews and it's not about Solomon
You have already let me know that you're an anti-semite
It's it's a it's troubling that Alex in the year 2021
Is still peddling this story
Literally Devon
There's every reason
For him to know that this is an anti-semitic falsehood has lingered over the years
Perpetuates
It's a it's a large part of his worldview and congratulations
Do people like Joe Rogan helping spread that message far and wide
So Jordan
Yeah
What does Alex mean money
Well
I mean in a certain sense
He needs a lesson
Because all of it's going to go away so he should start spending all of it now
Let me ask you this what
Has he sold his house.
I actually
Can't tell you whether or not he's all this house okay although some other stuff might be going up on the Block okay
Thanks for your support.
Lands End project in motion
Circumnavigate
And during key junctures
Able to pop up
Into the future time we're going
Do I need major wartime capital
That's why
You're going to see me on air soon because they're will side issues there they're important
Selling the armored truck
It's been great
Cupboard with a lot of attention
Causes butt
Director
50 cal stuff like that
Everything is going to go in
Pitiful energy
I need them to sell my house which is being sold right now
Finally
Of course I want to put
Anan
Future of humanity in my children
Looking for
Yikes
That's not good no that's man
Who's about to lose all of his money
Maybe a guy who is having buyer's remorse on that tank
I believe it took this long
Interesting
To hear him say like Goonies talking about the tank
Baby I got we got a lot of attention on the golo
Well well well done
Yeah this is this is silly
That's bad he's basically going to have a yard sale
I want a 50 cal guns you know
Stuff you want I would I would maybe by another bullhorn if he has like a tyranny Crusher
Yeah I would I would buy that
I don't know if we can find that one yeah but I'd put an offer on the tiny bullhorn I'll put an offer on the tiny Boulevard
We'll be we'll go we'll go to an auction like in Hudson Hawk and you and I
I will beat against each other for the title by
Bullard counterproductive so he's doing this plug basically where he's talking about he's going to sell it
Was 50,000
I think is grouped into what I would describe his sacrilegious territory
Be part of that ritual in front of God
The resistance
Don't just get better
Fun this war
And make sure
Arena
My shield and my sword
Helmet on
We're all together on this because you're that gladiator on the field as well
And that we are prepared
And well-fed
Focused and not distracted
To make sure we go in there in the Tom Brady Zone
This is allegory
What
With absolute precision
And so
Maximum push Zone I was born for this
We are going to see the whole nine yards now on full world government
Infowarsstore.com before it sells out today Ultra discounted
To take part in the Holy ritual in front of Gohan
Man that's intense
As dumb
Celebrities going around trying to get people to buy war bonds and stuff like
That was
We do like patriotism in like we got it at 8 they're not please and all that stuff if they were going around being like
Listen you want to defeat the Nazis
You got to buy brain for
People would have been turned off it's a ritual is that
Afterlife involved
To buy my down-and-out sleep aid
Got to get it now kinsella
So
Yes Bombshells bombshells
Smoking Gun
Talk about this all day
Well personal issues
Ted Nugent is added again
Would you speak to the people who believe it is a worthwhile
From the federal government
The people that went ahead and got
He always starts
Because
Good bit
So Ted Nugent
Well first thing I want to say Dan is thank you so much for giving us the opportunity to listen
No Ginger a lot of different things
And thank you for
No problem
Alex for getting rid of smoke and smoking guns to talk to Ted Nugent
I mean when the when the new jizz around noted suspected
Uber creep ya-ya noted suspected
Confirmed stop writing songs about how he wants to f*** miners
Silver Creek
Album the one where I detail my crimes
The narrative in the story for everyone was
Rakovic that long tail light for a long time
No the sort of fever is broken and everyone can
Just be like everyone I know had it
Nugent's no--except
Most
My buddies and my
My friend and my Hunting Buddies
Musicians
My wife and I got it
We went to the
Crap
Frontline doctors
Cross the board hydroxychlor conniver
Steroids
October of
2019 laborious taking CD B12 and I'm always eating
Take the care of myself clean and sober I get a lot exercise ID
Wild swamp
Breathe
100%
Dave
Anybody else that I know
Took the Frontline doctors
Recommended
No good
Yeah so everyone he knows got covid
And they all took over my
Better
I would wonder if those were like
PCR
Confirm test
Yeah cares about their dumb story
I bet it's it's now the
It's shifting to everybody saying everybody got it
I bet so weird
Yeah everybody just moves on
So weird that they couldn't tell deny that it even exists
For a year
And all of those people will believe them and then they can just suddenly say well that year
I had covid in that year and everybody's like
Who didn't have covid
Nobody is just going like so you were lying to us the whole time yeah and actively spreading
At your
No mask rallies are stuff
You boil my God I hate
These people so much the other they're pretty bad
So one friend of Ted Nugent
Unfortunately
Apparently didn't believe Ted about the magic of ivermectin Ono
How many died
He's dead good friend one of the greatest Americans that
Column of America
Jim Brown from Indiana
Just a great
Man Alex
And he died
Two days ago and we're still morning we are shattered
The loss of our loved ones and our dear friends
And the reason is because the United States
Is the enemy of America
Communist Chinese
Pebbles
Weaponizing virus
Mankind
United States and the Communist Chinese devils
Killed my friend Jim
.
Alright Ted feel like now that they've admitted everybody had covid
Can't we
Then just
Hey busy this can be settled with a simple bow
Bright
What's up I bet you take the vaccine and you're fine
You bet
That I take the vaccine and I die
Okay
I don't think that they would go for that
No cuz then they would have to admit that it
That they knew that it was
Spot me a problem
I hear this and I can't think of anything other than inside
Out of what that new did say
But my friend I destroy the American government if you have somebody who
You know he loved one who passed away from
I'm covid
Killed them too they murdered your family member or friend
Answer they're the enemy of America we need to take out the government
It's real bad
Real bad thing
Wild
Absolutely wild that you can live
Yeah but you know why Ted Nugent has these thoughts
While he has his position
Cuz he's a lunatic
Swamp air that could be
A lot of ducks have problems
Disturbing reality as well
I would say
That if you listen to
He would tell you
Because he practice
Critical thinking
Now I'm thinking
Critically about this next clip that I'm about to
Play Aha
It goes off the rails
Pretty fast talking about the great replacement Shore
Critical thinking is the
DNA
Freedom demanding
We the People
States of America
Fathers critical thought again
Against
Arbitrary
Monica
Rules
Forced upon its subjects so they wrote down
He knew instantly to be free to be right
Just called the Constitution the Bill of Rights
Right now
If you're a critical thinker
If you critical
Entrepreneur
Michigan ostracized
This government right now more than ever
Critical thinker
Go to school
Turn down
Emotion
History of the world
Travel that you can't live without it
People from around the world
Lifestyle
Are you using critical thinking now
Orchestration oven
Mission of America
Government of the United States of America
Make that perfectly
Berkeley Square
Gangnam
Democrat
Marxist
Government
Orchestrating
Station of America
Our Southern border
Because those people will blindly obey the
Holyshit
Wow that took Sumter
By rambling about critical thinking is what the founding fathers used as a weapon
Within 2 minutes where on replacement
Democrats want to replace the Americans
With foreigners that they can control wish we could get rid of the American Legend so much
I wish we could get rid of the American Legend because the American Revolution was dumb
Like here's what happened
The king stole Land from the Native Americans
And then the quote founding fathers
Stole it from the King
Nobody's a good guy
Yeah there's a little more nuanced than that but
That is more
To the point version of the story
So look
These founding fathers
Baby super into Alex
According to Ted Nugent
Who also says that Alex has a T-Rex balls
Run by the big AI system and found that the majority of deaths and hospitalizations
And creating a syndrome called a DE
Overtime kills about 80% of people that develop it
Dad
Project solace
Spell number one
Weed the people salute you Alex yours cuz you got a T-Rex ballsack switching from coast
And and eat your ear what the founding
Fathers wanted all Americans to be
Spirited but you look into it
Before the government
Binding
You expose the finding
Everything's you and I believe in and talk about
Call Missy
Because they guaranteed
Information on planet Earth
Comes from the United States of America
Government
So you talked about that project salads on the last episode I was just lying about that
Here's the point I want to make
It's all good and well to be suspicious but that's not what Alex and Ted are
This isn't suspicion this is coming to a predetermined conclusion and then being
Combative about anything that doesn't align with that can
Conclusion
It just so happens that the collusion conclusion that they've arrived as if the government is evil
Dotyville paint anyone who doesn't agree with them as blind cheap
But that's just a trick
That's just a sleight-of-hand trick
When someone has a suspicion the appropriate next step is to search for corroborating or disqualifying information
So you can evaluate that suspicious
That's what I heard Alex covering that C-SPAN clip
Apache
I had a suspicion that he wasn't telling the truth about
So the only way to deal with that productively with
Define the raw video
And assess it for myself
I feel like what you should have done is none of that and hung the American government May forgiving him
Ultimately it turned out that my suspicions was Meredith
Alex is lying his ass off
It would have been probably fine for me to just hear him talking about this clip
Open say I'm sure he's lying but without learning more
I would be being lazy about reaching that conclusion and it wouldn't be based on anything
This show would be really stupid if we just played clips of Alex and said nope
Without getting into the details of the story
It's good to have a healthy distrust in a level of skepticism about things that you're being told
That's
Like knocking argue with
The problem is that what tennis calling suspicion is actually just him being the lazy
But rationalizing his knee jerk anti-government position
And then he's like ouu go out there and you find the sources at prove what we knew all along was right no
Alex finds things and lies about them in such a way to make them reinforced rightly conclusions that you came to a
That's the game that's being played
Believe the Ted doesn't know that
But maybe not
I think Ted is more than capable yeah he did write Wango Tango
You've got a real gift for not knowing what it is he stalking
Thing about buddy has
Adjectives
You bring adjectives you don't need no
Annoying ask Aiden
Hatem
Smoking Gun is Smoking Gun Smoking Gun
Now we have to talk about it we had to talk to Ted
Gyros
Wango Tango he's going to get the information out
Right right so now it's time to really get down to business okay I know it's not we have another guy
It's the middle of your busy schedule
Alex thank you your listeners are getting facts they're getting science
Hashtag
Science Matters
And what you're giving people is useful information instead of
Propaganda talking point
B o
I want to thank you for your diligence for your
Tenacity for not giving up when people have
Tried to destroy you over and over again you can't keep a good man down
Alex Jones is a good man
So dr. Bartlett is the person who Alex keeps mentioning as the guy who wrote in the
Prescriptions for things like Ivermectin
He's made a bunch of Waves by claiming that the inhalable steroid
Budesonide is a quote Silver Bullet against covid
Which is not true
Little boy there may be some positive effects that a patient could get from the steroid but in terms of being a cure
Which is claimed there isn't evidence
What's the sport that
There's a lot to say about this dude he's just using the same kind of game that everyone and Alex's world does
Patients that get better with his steroids are remembered and the ones that don't conveniently get
Forgotten so the claim of a miracle cure
And keep being made
And everyone's trying to cover up the budesonide and whatever
You know what all you need to do is claim a miracle cure
Because sometimes that's how we get Kellogg's cereal
Sure
You haven't thought about that maybe Kellogg cereal is our
Original
Down and out
Could be I think about
Here's some for you too
Think about right
Dr. Richard Bartlett is our guess we just had Ted Nugent on and
A ventilator put on you you're probably going to die
Percent of people in New York Capital One
I have a suspicion about
Play decided to look into it
So this is just a whisper from a study those put out in April 2020
So it really only captured the
Beginning of the pandemic response
They found it in their data set of patients 1151 of them needed to be put on mechanical ventilator
The only knew the medical outcomes of 320 of these patients
Of these 88% had.
That number does sound really high but there's a couple of Porton points that you need to remember
The first is that if you're needing to go on a mechanical ventilator you're going to tend to be in the category of more severe cases of Coke
And you may have a higher likelihood of dying regardless of ventilation
The second thing to remember is that Approximately 80% of patients who get put on ventilators die
Regardless of the Panthers
That's how it works as a relevant jump but
It's not like a jump from 40 to 88%
This is because my mechanical ventilators are required for talkin
But seriously
The third thing to consider is that 72% of the total patients were put on ventilators are not captured in this statistic
Since they don't have a final outcome yet which is to say they haven't died or been discharged from the hospital
These 831 people we're still in the hospital and depending how their cases
What's the number could be a lot different
If they'd included these people in the calculation then at that point only
Approximately 25% of the people put on ventilators with covid
Had died which is a big
Other data sets from around this time
Places like Vanderbilt and Emory University show death rates
Did it right in that ballpark of
25 to 30
The point here is that Alex should get into some critical thinking
It might help him
Yeah that could do that could go a long way and repeating
Statistics that he's not putting into a proper context
Why would
Oh it's bad idea
Surrounded by experts like this dr. Bartlett
Who's playing fast and loose the f****** detailed the most prestigious doctors in the world
You need to use your brain your training your experience
And this is going to send a shiver down their spines right now but if you go to the NIH
Guidelines for covid 3
Budesonide is
And I don't know that cuz they don't read these things they don't educate themselves
So this is true actually budesonide is mentioned in the nih's covid treatment guidelines
In the section titled quote
Immunomodulators under evaluation for the treatment of covid-19
It's something that they think Merit evaluation
Which is a little different than Bartlett Silver Bullet claim
Budesonide is mentioned 39 times in the entire 365 page.
Like in this passage
Central page 217
Quote there is insufficient evidence
Thanks for the panel to recommend either for or against the use of inhaled budesonide for the treatment of covid-19
Most of the other times it comes up is in the context of
Get the guidelines discussing
Studies that looked at budesonide
Effectiveness
In treating covid
Studies were inconclusive and further research
Require
The fact that the drug is mentioned in the guidelines means nothing
But it's the sort of thing that a con man might say if you wanted to make the audience
Think that even the NIH admit
The pieces of silver bullet
Which is the game that's being played
By dr. Bartlett here on Alex's show
Big something that they never can
Consider
About
The way they view sign
Sprite is if science actually work
The way that they think it does
We would get
A new miracle cure for everything
Every human
Every scientist would
Constantly be like
I saw a cleat I thought fix one patient we got the miracle cure
Every single
We have we have a couple anecdotal stories
Oh yeah this one kills everybody this one doesn't kill anybody we've
Q words this this is all and then 2 weeks later they be like
We didn't but nobody paid attention
We're onto another thing already
Insane D idea of if they're if science works like the way they think it does we would live a Non-Stop chaos life
Soliloquy of The Smoking Gun Smoking Gun is smoking gods
We have to talk.
Cuz he's a celebrity that has a big-time right
Right right
Right
We have to talk.
Cuz he's an important doctor
In the world of ivermectin and budesonide and should I like
This is
We have to deal with both the origins of the pandemic
And the treatment
So now that that's out of the way we can get to talk about the smoking god of the smoking God Of The Smoking Gun
Wow actually I'm sorry
Hi, can a biopsy mon louder with Crowder Derek Richards has been banned
Hey, teacher
That because well the online
Control freaks the left said that you he said some things they didn't like
Probably
Oh man
That's something you didn't like
Another comedian is going to have to make a half hour special about how they aren't allowed to say anything I would never get to talk
You can't turn this off I can't talk
So here's the situation
There was a tour of military bases put on by the Department of Defense and the American forces entertainment
Apparently Derek Richards was at 2
Perform on this tour but then a naval officer found some of his old tweets
And sent them to the dod and Afi
Roman article in the daily.
In 1 Richard
Posted a Photoshop meme of Michael and Dell holding a pillow next to President Joe Biden in the hospital bed
The meanest Captain to make America great again
Former Donald Trump
President Donald Trump's 2016
Campaign slogan
This is just sad
Well I would be opposed to the dod and afd saying that Richard
Cannot delete these things
Infringement of free speech kind of thing
The comedian if he joked online but killing the president
A pretty clear case of behavior that'll get you kicked off a USO tour it is really funny I bet it never occur
Heard to him
That the dod would be
Uncomfortable with that because in his mind
Trump is the president and they still work for Trump
Right maybe the idea of him going on a USO tour
Doesn't make any sense to me because
They all work for the guy that you want
Do you realize that
Changed
Like the dod would be mad about you Tweeting out of
If a binding supporter
The comic and I was booked to do a USO tour
3 years ago and I was tweeting out all the things that I was tweeting out
3 years ago
The dod would have understandably been like
This is not a good idea
Usher
And let's be totally clear there is a bit of a difference in messaging between like
I don't like Joe Biden
And
This meme implying that make Lyndell
Would make a better country by killing
Yeah Joe Biden with a pillow
Yeah there is a difference between those things I don't know
I don't think that it's
Like
Advocating killing the president to post that Meme but I also don't think that it's
All that
Happy Griffin have a header to get to that we're about to we're about to do the whole
Blankets as
Outrageous
To imagine that the Uso would cancel his appearance on this door because of this and other tweets
That they found
It's not a free speech issue
It's not but whatever they're not saying he can't
Sweet now
I will say the Derek Richards
Is
At least
He doesn't seem as mad as Alex wants him to be
I Harbor no ill feelings towards Armed Forces
Or the Department of Defense
Are there Corporation
Esterline bullies
I mean show what if you were serious Christian or right-wing Christian
The Avenger telling comedy should be what your comedy is
And the whole point is
Now you got the lgbtq groups attacking people that are straight
What
Are not inclusive
Republican
This is mind control
This is all part of the leftist Takeover in Purge
Inside the military
You're just a collateral damage
Hey Derek can you be a little matter could you turn this into the biggest most important issue cuz I do not like
Like conciliatory tone
What do you think you maybe going to get booked on something again so you don't want to say hey
F*** the dod a bad idea
That doesn't play
Now we we we shopping anger here that's that's our currency
Yeah let's let's
Let's be important
Mr. Richards
Your career and its future
Meeting with me
Right now
Important
So I want you to burn it all down
And then maybe I can kind of force you to act like a drug dealer in force you to work at Infowars career is kindling
Exactly I've never heard of you before my turn told me you were on louder with Crowder
And I will never think of you again ever
Yep
The guy who smashed stuff
Where's the guy
Great memes Alex
Wanted a job
The last name Richards are not having a good year
Mark Richards this dude
I don't know we might as well go back
The captain mark
The same guy that I said
Ono Mike rich
The Jeopardy host
Yeah that's who I was thinking okay
Alex is like
They they
Hey
On the left
They insist
You got to be punished for telling jokes
What about Obama
He told jokes at the
The Correspondents Dinner
He told jokes
What about Trump
Play the clip of Obama being funny at the correspondents
All kidding aside
New York
Experience
For example
No seriously just recently in an episode of Celebrity Apprentice
At the steakhouse
The men's cooking
Did not impress the judges from Omaha Steaks
And there was a lot of blame to go around
You mr. Trump recognize that the real problem was a lack of leadership
And so ultimately you didn't
Blame
Long John
Meatloaf
You fired Gary busiek
Decisions that will keep me up at night
Yeah there you go so Derek Richardson he couldn't even some of the evil
Hollywood folks
4000 Twitter followers are so
Such a weird choice to play that.
It's actually very funny
Ed well-delivered we were laughing before and I was
It's still very good because it is
Nuance
Know that the order he did even did rule of Threes whoever wrote that joke was really good
I think it's a strange decision for Alex to do that but whatever
Especially since
Here's the difference
That was Obama making fun of a man
Four things he did
And the reason that even come up is because he was trying to say that Obama
I had a fake birth certificate
And he did this whole racist attack against
Now if I were Trump
Yeah and I had led this whole charge on the fake birth
Certificate Obama shouldn't be president there
I would simply not show up
To the dinnerware
Obama speaking
The wildest
Ourselves in a position where
Really offensive to him
For a while
I just not go
But Trump recited I'll go and then he got mad and then
I do not like being made fun
Open new easy to make fun of me which is why I surround myself with people who refused
So
And a frame this is like these liberal Hollywood Elites
Are behind what happened
Do this guy
This Derek
It's fair to say that people like Debra Messing they Amplified the calling out of Eric's tweet
Didn't search it out and like try and find it just to destroy this guy
A naval officer named Travis Acres
Found the because he stationed in the Middle East
He'd heard about the upcoming
Already decided see the performers coming over where
Because he loved stand-up
You found Eric
Twitter and as he told the daily.
The further I reviewed is filled his feed the more
Concerning it became that he would be booked on a Department of Defense sponsored tour
Since Armed Forces entertainment isn't official. Office
It's fun to pretend
This is just like all fake Hollywood liberal Elites being on the warpath but
The reason doesn't even being discussed is because this enlisted person was offended by what he saw on Derek's Twitter
Any tag the dod in a tweet about
In order for Alex's outrage
Machine to run properly though
That has to be ignored in
Tirerack.com
Definitely can't also be somebody who was a fan of
Cups and up
Because you've also got that added
He's not funny enough for me to ignore these tweets
Insult
That is
Definitely
What's up text I would I would imagine that he would have been like oh Dave Chappelle's coming
No need to look into that I guess
Patrice has said some horrible things
Oh my God
So you were bringing up Kathy Griffin and this is where she enters the four
Proceeding
But not before Derek tries to pretend
But hey man they misinterpreted my meme
And this is what this is where we see his comedic
Chops
There was one
I was advocating murdering the president
Meme
Mike Lindell
From my pillow holding a my pillow
Standing neck
Stu
President Biden who was lying in a bed
And so
Yeah that particular one of the upper right-hand rule
And it says make America great again
Now
Anybody can take that anyway they what is obviously a joke
I see is Mike Lindell clearly saying that
President Biden had an uncomfortable pillow and he was offering one of his good my pillows for the president to lay upon.
Here's the deal
It didn't cross the line
Yours didn't go 1/10 as far as that is obviously good-nature
Good nature
I'm going to leave aside anything about that
A fun game the Derek's playing about the tweet
It's supposed to because I don't really care about him tweeting this can do that all day dumb not funny joke
It does make sense that you get kicked off of USO tour for making that kind of joke though
You're entitled to your Free Speech but you're not entitled to be paid to go on USO tour
Also Kathy Griffin is probably the last example Alex should be bringing up because
She lost
So many jobs after that picture came out
She was fired from CNN where she'd been one of the host of the New Year's Eve show
You got dropped from gigs
Nancy claims that you wasn't even allowed to fly for two months
And then everybody on the left said everything is okay
The picture also apparently got Kathy Griffin on the Killer
List of Cesar sayoc
The Amar Kabal
I wonder why you would put a Target on someone is relatively obscure in
No just released it admittedly possibly distasteful picture
I don't know if they said anything to do with
But allow me to take you back Jordan In My Time Machine May 31st
2017 kind thoughts
Hey Mike cernovich is thought
About Kathy
Here we go
Why did ISIS sympathizer
Wichita
Do the ball drop she's routinely on.cnn she does comedy Pharmacy her on there all the time
Walker casino employee
And defendants were going to sell it t-shirt
You also get $1,000 2500
If you're seen wearing the T-shirt
National TV C-SPAN your local news
Or goes viral I will choose 1000
2500 until it hits 2
Hundred-thousand-dollar
Alex and Mike cernovich was so up in arms about the Kathy Griffin picture that they started a campaign to get people to buy shirts
It said CNN is Isis
How many people to yell at on live TV
The argument according to these idiot
It was like Griffin was signaling to Isis
Haydocy on that didn't fire her that means they also support Isis
It's very very stupid
And I remember it very clearly
I was
I was looking back to this was like
It was Mike cernovich yet
Where's Ali Alexander and Alexa
Message Alex wants
To give us about free speech is that when a comedian does something that's politically distasteful
It's a travesty when that person is fired if they're on the right way
However if their left-wing
You mean to offer $200,000 to wage a public pressure campaign to label them as an Isis sympathizer
To get their employees
Employer to fire them
Let's baby labeled Isis supporters as well
This is a coherent ideology and totally not Alex
Just pretending to have principles
Cuz he's a dumb piece of s***
Yeah I can also
Oscar sayoc he tried to bomb this year in at headquarters
At in Atlanta to so
That was strange
Scenic
Very weird
I am not
Giving a f*** about any right-wing
Cancel culture
Bulshit
Mainly because I was alive when the dicks
Dixie Chicks at Warriors
And then everyone
On
Every side
What she said was Natalie Maines said that she was ashamed that the president was he
That was it's not war is bad
Slightly different but I get what you're saying
Sorry it's even less innocuous
More innocuous
Yep yep
Canceled
Cashtag
Dixie Chicks burning party in real unreal
Yep
So Alex
Look you got smoke a gun or smoking, smoking gun
But you needed to talk to Ted Nugent Elizabeth
Need to talk to dr. Bartlett because he's a guy who's got medical solution
And then you needed to talk to this completely because he got canceled
Or something
This guy I've never heard of
He's on a tour that I would have never known happened
Wouldn't have cared either way nope
Now
It's time to get down to the Smoking Gun is smoking, smoking. Okay
They said the game
Very serious
And it makes me angry that the system try to suppress us
Cherry-picked contest
Try to silence us
I'm sorry what
We're fighting this corrupt murderous system
Call our futures Collective
That was just say this right now
I salute and I command and I thank all of our affiliates
Break up with me both
Russian Coronavirus
Infowars
Especially these days
God course
Most importantly for a hedge of protection if you have God deems that
Ask her what has happened
How thankful I've been knowing you
The first time you two did a month ago returned in 5 years ago
Or 27 years ago I appreciate all of you
This has been one hell of a fight
Would be what
This really sounds like
One saying goodbye remember like a year ago he recorded his fake last show
I'm looking forward to going back and visiting. What yeah
So he he's pretending he's saying goodbye cuz it's really dramatic haha I know this is a plug
I know this is a plug
I was listening to that and I was like
Just get to the f****** place already has listening to your thank-yous and going deaf
A f****** plug
It's over here I'm going to try fast-forward about it right now that's okay
They did this on purpose you understand Falcon cooked it up in Saltsburg
A couple million views of see that and go oh my God this guy's reaching out he's busted through the
Blockade
Can I stop what I'm doing I'm orally
Weather
I can't pull off
Because
You're going to get everybody if we don't stay in this position and just keep
This is a little of the disappear back like
Opera
This is information Warfare
This is the truth and if I went away tomorrow
And that's off they would
About me and use me as a tool of evil
I can't do that
The only way I'm able to get our articles
I'm banned on all the platform
You can take Clips you can share them
You can get them out
Understand
Holding up
Together
Do I need you to support the show I need you to pray for the show I need you to buy products that are already great for you and your family's own just say this
We got the big sale going on
Percent off across-the-board the emergency I'm going to have to pay out these lawsuits
Sao
It's so
Shocking to me that like
He wouldn't recognize how transparent his tone is
Wanted to like I need to really overdramatize what is going to end up in a place
It's I think it's
It takes minutes for the Preamble of the plug
Unfair
Unfair I mean I was thinking
Just like
God if I was there I would have some sort of like
Playoffs
You know that's cuz I was just immediately he's going on too long as
Oh yeah you can taste it
And then it gradually gets louder
Yeah I just
I think
There are
X
When you can get
Smoothly done at pitch
I could be sitting there be like
This guy's got the goods
You know this is not
I mean I remember back in the day I was
Sometimes
Julian
Pressed by his
Throws
To add some of it is just like being worn down over time
Brought me to see it over and over again but this is worse
Yeah I know that one's too obvious he Rambles a bit more and this is what this is
There's a lot going on you got my commitment
To burn the Midnight Oil
Short as well
I'm not risking my life and put it on the line to lose this thing
Illusion means losing I'm not worried about me
Seriously
V for Vendetta when he's ready to die
It's only the calls out that cost you and the
Phone is a 600 plus dollar value on the best phones they've got
The satellite
This is outrageous
This satellite phones
To Good Morgan have to put a clock on this one
Hi
Just I mean it
Okay let's smoke smoking, smoking got spot we needed to talk to Ted Nugent diseases Darby need to talk to dr. Bartlett cuz he's a.
And then we needed to do some ads
Because we I'm losing his lawsuit
Who's in the lawsuit now
Finally
With a couple minutes left in the show
Oh God
There's so many cases
And even just shooting people randomly all urine and Evac parades will just shoot you cuz your wife
Weirdo white devil works for meth heads nine times out of 10 they're doing
Absolutely disgusting little rodents usually their professors are assistant professors
Shooting people
Beard
Last Friday
Let's hear from her.
The audio in Hershey is
I have hair
In my armpit
Insert
Your response to them
My response to this is
I hope you find happiness but
The chances of that are very
Very very low and I pity you
I do
Your regular strength
Because she is as disgusting as she can be
Wow holy s*** man shaved except for like
Kangaskhan
Giant disgusting sideburns
What the f*** are we doing man
I mean I thought that we had the bombshell I thought we had the Smoking Gun he decides to take up the end of the show
Complaining about a woman that
I guess he's decided his on a track
I
I don't know this is so stupid
Shuffle is
The worst sonreal
They couldn't.
Have been
Like
They couldn't
They couldn't resist
Her last name is literally how you react to it tells me everything I need to know about you and you guys told her every
Thing you need to know about her
Amazing how you couldn't it was like she cheated up through time itself
For them to pay it off
Yeah yeah basically
Yep
And I would imagine that
Stop it
Hair is capable of finding
Whatever happiness and retains her armpits
Series E
A lot of people and I'm going to throw this to you
And Alex
And whoever that guy was with the comic I have no idea I think it was in the clip that Alex was playing
Look it from somebody else's, sorry about this woman f******
Oh my God so yeah I mean
We just can't not
Shame her for not conforming to your appearance
Yes
I don't even know how you can live like that
It's
It seems exhaust
Somebody has hairy armpits
Probably more emotionally exhausting than the time that it took me to assess the claim that he was making about that C-SPAN
And video
You know would have been
Easier for Alex Maybe
I actually wouldn't but infinitely harder for him because
Kirby actual stuff you are supposed to cover
That would have been good let's do two bets
Yeah right
First you take the vaccine you die I take vaccine I live
Second bed
Try doing your job one day
See how it goes
By Ivan will be a disaster
I just I don't know I'd love to see him try to be serious and actually cover something but
Look
A lot
No
No we didn't
Proudly
Nugent sucks
He sucks so bad
Put away Jordan that's all Reposado. We will be back
So until then we website.com Twitter
What is correct we will be back but
Until then I'm the only
20 CX Clark I'm Daryl
Robot
Alexandra Thurston color