Damn important swetik
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guys
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Technology
We're couple dudes like sit around where's for the altar
Tween and talk a little bit about Alex
Jordan Jordan
Quick question what's up
Today my bright spot
To the real Bass
The real made it real
Super simple
No but it is a food
Okay iced oatmeal cookies
Years ya-ya greens and I saw in the
Impulse buy section of course
Warsaw dollar for a bag of
Iced oatmeal cookies
Are they the kind with the animals
No
The point is delicious oatmeal Ginger kind of
I feel like I've aired so strongly on the side of like chocolate chip
And what have you are you sure that iced oatmeal
Gets left in the by the wayside and
It's not fair
You know I haven't had an iced cookie in a long time and
They are fantastic
This gets done Dirty by razor
You know what we've been eating
We've been trying to eat healthier last night we ate Brown bean cookies
Yeah
Yeah man
Not in the I still feel cookie
I furrowed my brow with you I have no idea what that even means. Cool
Yeah that's not your brakes
What are you got my Brightspot Dion is I just I don't
I think I've talked about it on the show
But a few weeks back I did an interview with Mike Wiley friend of the show close friend of mine
Mine for his podcast or whatever reviews
Bastard
Cast
I was a lot of fun I
Forgot to talk about it and then I took a look at it last night to see if
I couldn't remember all the b******* that I said you know whatever I've known since I was throwing up
And most of it was about my favorite PSI from the 90s which was an advertisement
Against
Aftermath
But
Unfortunately had a very
Catchy song about
Isn't that math
I think
My buddy Hogan would sing that a lot
Here.
Stuck with me since the 90s and it's I will take any opportunity to talk about
Does drug PSAs from the 90s wear
Counterproductive
Misread not great
Not great
Opposite of fact it's like all you're doing is sitting at a couch should have a good time with you like
Is that bad
This is your brain on drugs
20K
Michael
Jordan today we have a sneaky snake episode going over
17th
Wow
My mouth
Krypton
All of that seemed like you were trying to get to Blackjack
Then you remember that it wasn't coming now you know it was iced oatmeal cookies
But that'll happen slow in my jaw down do it before we get to this 2003 episode
Chronicling
The past
And what we can learn from it about the present short time to say hello to
So first Alex's neck thank you so much are now policy walk
Will that be included in the auction later
Next Coraline and her three weed smoking girlfriends thank you so much you're now apology
Could you very much
Weebles wobble but they don't fall for this information thank you so much. How about you
Very much
Jesus
I'm a policy wonk
That you very much Crystal reader thank you so much
Very much to say hello to so I would like to say hello
Well I'm not comfortable saying this out loud until I'm sure it's not some new cake with an Alex Jones mask
Anyway you know who you are your knowledge
Technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Yub
Chick-fil-A large
Thank you so much
You know a lot of them are funny some of them are puns some of them are just names that when I think of the
The first one that I've really curious
I think we should set a character limit
Bridgewater to
140 not doing this 280 here's what we're going to do
Only one depends
Santa Claus
And also for some reason no split infinitive
Sure
So Jordan wearing start off the show that's going to be a little bit of a shorter episode cuz there's
Not not a ton that happens with some stuff that is definitely worth
Discussing sound very interesting
But you know like a good
Good section of the episode is Alex talking to Larry Pratt from gun owners for America
Legit it's just
Why I love God nothing interesting going on it's just like
Wow bush is going to renew the assault weapons ban
Something that doesn't end up happening
It's kind of pointless
Alex does have some things
To say that are kind of relevant
To the situation
We find ourselves in
He is very worried
About an article that he read
That has to do with the scientist
Declaring that the end of the world of the Apocalypse
Is a 50-50 chance
What's a good article
He believed
Either happens or it doesn't 50/50
Alex believes that the most likely scenario for the end of the world is
The release
Ava superbio weather
Interesting
Okay I'm some of the support for why he thinks
This is a little dodgy
Porton down
Ground
3 rings
4 years ago
Uncorked
Wheat
Prepare
Important
Open bar
None of that is true
Anker
This issue in a previous 2003 episodes
That stuff here
But there's one detail in that telling of the story that I have not heard Alex included
The narrative in the past
In previous times I've heard him talk about this
I've not heard alekseev at Porton down
Claimed that an animal rights activist broke in and stole the
Mouth
Which then got released
Yeah Bruce Willis claims if that happen
That is a interesting wrinkle also detailed
Absurd that he doesn't usually included
Porton down
Hold these farms and told them get ready for an outbreak
I bet yeah that one was
That's nonsense with the reality of that is on a previous episode
Music the ministry of
Agriculture
They do that every
They call and say like hey are you prepared for possible
Sick animals
So there's a real
Problem with
The chain of events
Alex is the express
It's immediately apparent
Which is that an animal rights activist supposedly went on a bizarre almost certainly impossible mission
Stealing this virus just so they could release it kill animals
In the name of
Protecting animals
It doesn't make sense
From the standpoint of an animal rights activist
They'll never said that an animal rights activist
Had released
Foot in mouth
This is what the guardian refers to as a quote rural myth
And here's the basic story
There's an animal sanctuary called the hillside which is home to over 800 rescued animals from
Farms
Some representatives from the hillside visited a farm called Burnside
Farm which happened to be one of the main Farms
Where animals came down
Mouth
They were not the only ones to visit though there was an inspection by the Ministry of Agriculture haven't received
Multiple complaints about the
The conditions that animals were kept on
On the farm
After the foot-in-mouth outbreak be
Began the folks at Burnside level
Accusations at Hillside Sanctuary workers
I've haven't been the source of the outbreak
But that's pretty much impossible
The hillside folks came to the farm in December 2000
The outbreak occurred in February 2001
In January 2001 the Ministry of Agriculture
So did their inspection and said quote
There were positively no traces of foot-in-mouth
Send the pigs in the fall
For their part
A spokesman important
Actually said
Quote we have never worked on foot and mouth
That was their response
It's not that animal rights activists
From them as compared to what Alex said that their response was definitely
Movie and the other one was like we don't do with that
Alex is creating a fake way to present this world rumor as if it were the actual response of the people at Porton down
Any critical thinkers listening to his show should be asking themselves why he would do that
Certainly one possibility is that Alex just doesn't know anything and he's mixing up
Rural rumors with official statements from Bordentown
He could be that stupid and if so I would say he's probably not someone who should be taken serious
On the other hand
Another possibility is that Alex nosek
Exactly what he
Important down it claimed that an animal rights activist stole the virus that solidifies multiple things about his narrative
He can solidify any other way
The first is that foot-and-mouth originated at Porton down
Without this fake admission Alex can't demonstrate this
At all
The second thing
Is that if this is really truly the response
Bordentown head
There's still a bad guy
The story still has a villain that you can point to and scapegoat
And that second thing is super important
Because as
It often is the case
Yeah in 2007 the UK government released a final report on the foot-and-mouth outbreak and
While they were unable to come to a
Definitive
Conclusion about where it started
They have a pretty good idea
There were two Labs that were right next to each other
IAH
And Muriel which word
They actually were doing work on foot and mouth
And so it's theorized that the foot-in-mouth found its way into the ground soil through deficient drainage
Support quotes
Very been concerned for several years that the effluent pipes
We're old and needed replacing
But after much discussion
Money had not been made available
Alex's narrative conveniently side steps
The actual aunt
Answer to this problem
Which is regulation that people actually follow regular inspections and government spending
By turning it into a story where evil animal rights activist told the virus Oz not to worry about about accidentally penetrating
His world
Cuz he doesn't have a good argument against it
I would love to no longer it like
We've done this for too many of the entirety of the human races
Is existence where it's like
Okay
We're studying
I'm sorry we just don't have the budget for it right now it's just going to not going to work
2 year later
If we had put just a little bit of money into that thing
From before we wouldn't be dealing with a foot-and-mouth disease outbreak
You know a good bit of
The research is necessary in terms of dealing with
Illnesses that are detriment
To Public Health is definitely true
Simultaneously true
We need
Make it safe
Do that is make sure that these drainage pipes
How is it that we can let
Drainage pipes go bad
Yeah so what
Leafy rise did there's a number of people who are you know going
Going in and out
Through like a
Construction worker again
And somehow this transfer to the farm
They were able to trace a possible
For the marathon that
It makes sense saying he's just completely making this up as a way of like
Building his fantasy of
These
Super things escaping from labs
You know it's a preoccupation that he's had for a long time and now he's
Play get out
Present we just can't do this any more often than say
If you recognize something Alex says from being in a movie
He is referencing the movie it is not realized
Being imitated by art or whatever that is true Alex was drinking
Elsa and
It came on and he was going
I'm so actually Alex has another reason why
The government did the
They released foot mouth for a reason
Somersworth
Yeah
That's right
The farmers were going to overturn the EU
Another rule
If there is a really accurate ontarget group who is just now getting political power
Does not exist
Probably not it's a little too convenient this
What was the motive
I don't know I think this is bulshit
Alex has a a bit of
Official sources
About race specific bioweapon got to have them
Then I don't think
This is good
World leader
Military technology
Rapist
So James is a magazine that uses publicly available information to discuss weapons and Military
I wasn't able to find anything suggesting
This or mansion with Alex's saying in James archives but I was able to find
The similar discussion
From an article published in the American free press
Hit you forgot America
Country prices that publication founded by Willis carto noted whites
Supremacist Tinashe
Anyway this article uses Anonymous sources
There's a lab at Porton down working Andres
Pacific bio
I find myself
Let's buy this sorcerer
Yeah if it were me I would also say that it was James and Knotts the white nationalist rag that I almost certainly got it
Prom
Yeah edited by my good buddy Tucker
To hide that you got it from the white nationalist magazine that you totally don't read cuz you're definitely above that
Call thing has no problem admitting
That's not a problem
But it is still appears to be laundered information unless unless there's something from James that like was in the heart
Hard copy of the magazine that I can't find I don't know
That's a lot of benefit of the doubt to give Alex
He may be red or hard copy
I try to be overly careful
There's a lot of talk about pork
Down
If it gets off track a little bit
Bought
I think he is where we have to start
Using specific language
Porton down isn't the last
It's actually a 7000
Baker science
A park with a bunch of laps.
The lab analysis talking about is on the ground
Actually called the defense Science and Technology laboratory or distal
The lab is owned and funded by the UK government primarily the ministry of Defense
Their other
Find identities also that are housed in the Science Park like
Plowshare Innovations and public health England
The area also includes tetricus
Science Park which is within
The portent
New sarum
Enterprises
I guess it's possible that there's some lab that's within the area the Science Park
It's owned by a company that
The subsidiary of Carlyle Group
But that's not what Alex's suggest
Open here
The name Porton down to him means a specific lab
And that lab is the event scientist
Technology Laboratory
Which is definitely not owned by the Carlyle Group this is
Nonsense
Yeah I mean maybe it wanted they sell the land
No
Did they did they really like okay
You going to be 7000
I'm
It certainly wasn't Carlyle Group owns the UK government
So Oz is pretty concerned about North Korea on this episode
Still
But he
He has
An interesting take
Number of stories that are coming out
Around this time
About
The family
But it is going up due to natural disaster
Some crops right
Alex
Why this s***
International
People Eater Goodrow
Brexit
I'm sorry I won't do that anymore
So we got a lot
Break down here I'm going to need a real lot more information on this year
Apologies yeah actually that is true but Alex's
Very wrong about it
There have been
Confirm stories that pop up periodically about people eating other people in North Korea that is true
But what's more difficult is trying
And figure out how prevalent it is and how accurate these stories are
It's really hard to assess the situation
Because you know
Refugees have told stories of people being driven to starvation at
And eating other people
But because of how shut off the world from the world North Korea
We don't know
Watch past those addict
Internal propaganda
Is eating just fine
So I have to go by there
There's three times in the last 20 years or so when cannibalism in North Korea stories made the rounds in our press
These were in the late nineties in 2003 and in 2013
And each of these times marks
The aftermath of a large and devastating famine
Involving almost certainly combination
The Pacific
And crops being destroyed by natural disaster
I don't know exactly what's going on in North Korea or how widespread any cannibalism may have been but I can
Can say that Alex saying that this
You know what
Appointed to a severe famine this
The liberal spin
That's really dumb
Also able to do anything to be able to vote for Donald Trump jr. right now and he would welcome that hereditary dictator
Leadership questions at 100%
Also
Just real quick
I'm not saying goodbye.
Phone number
Talk about it okay
Kim Jong-il
Kill the movie stars that he kidnap
Alex is making up
This have to do with shinsei cork
And joy
Moonhee
Who were formerly a married couple
Was a movie director and joy was an actor
They were kidnapped in 1978 and taken to North Korea where they were forced to make movies with the objective of heightening North
Korea's profile in the field of Arts about this story
2060 and I think called the was at the youth the lovers and the despot
Escape while on a trip to Vienna
Cuz that they were able to evade their handlers and they made it to the US
Shannon Joy would get remarried and live in the United States for about 10 years before going back to South Korea
Jim passed away in 2006 just died
In 2018 at the age of 91
Alex is mixing up this story with Kim Jong-il apologizing to
Japan for abducting 12 Japanese Nationals
During the 70s and 80s
Eight of whom were dead as of 2002
According to the guardian
These were just random Japanese citizens who were kidnapped in Japan by North Korean Special Forces
Then take
Going to live in North Korea
Kim Jong-il said quote
The special forces were Carried Away by a reckless quest for Glory
It was regretful at I want a frankly apologize
I've taken steps to ensure that it will not happen
Then again excuse me if I'm to understand what can't juggle is apologizing for it he's saying
That there were these Rogue North Korean Special Forces
Trying to get
Glory by kidnapping random Japanese people from making them live in North Korea
It is debatable
I'm feeling
So he explained that they were abducted so they could teach spies Japanese
And so that their identities could be used to enter South Korea
Almost certainly of Kim Jong-il is admitting to adopt abducting 12 Japanese people that number might be a little bit higher
Suspicions that the eight people who were abducted and who died were killed
How to cover up the abductions but that's not something that's been definitively proven
Obviously possible but
Steidl I'm not sure
Anyway this story is really f***** up and I'm not going to bat for him Johnny O
It's important to recognize that Alex has
No idea what
He's talking about
He just randomly mixing together details were various stories to
Kind of composite image that he wants his audience
If the goal is
Just to say that Kim Jong you Liz
Bad then I guess it doesn't matter if you get the details right
You know
Spice mix all this stuff up
Alex's pretending to be a show that traffic send information
Which he's short on
Eddie's mixing up
Entirely
But you have no idea about what was going on
If you took
Place value
100% despite the fact that everybody on the left is evil and this liberal viewpoint
The liberal Viewpoint is that salmon is causing
A contributing
People possibly be
Campbell is whereas Alex's
Do you want it which is
The correct
You conservative view is that
Kim Jong-il is bad
And that's it
I mean it for somebody who understands cause and effect
The food is dead
People are not able to eat
Seems very simple
So it turns out
If you die
In a North Korean camp
Yes you're sold for me
The police
Number one
ATS
Interesting
So this is a good example of what Alex does instead of covering the actual stories that he's pretend
I think the cover
This is grab a headline and roof on it going with whatever spark some kind of anger in his mind
Quickpoint about this opium thing
The committee meeting was held on the crook illicit activity funding the regime in North Korea
One of the witnesses called was Peter a prahar the director office of Asia Africa and Europe program
Bureau of the international narcotics
Can law enforcement affairs
Which is a part of the US Department of State
Senator Coburn
And ask quote is there enough information to put North Korea under the drug majors
Category
Prahar replied quote
No sir
That is another item that we consider on a regular basis within the
The Department of State
As you know what country could be put on the majors list for basically to read
First of all it is producing 1,000 hectares or cultivating 1,000 hectares
Of more I or more of Poppy
Opium poppy or cocoa
We have been unable to
To confirm reports that we have received overtime but there is significant opium poppy cultivation in North Korea
So we've been unable to
We considered North Korea for play some
Put on the majors list
Involvement
As a major cultivator or drug producer
It's not inconceivable that the North Korean government make some money through illegal drug sales but that's a little different than
Acting like the Opium and heroin here in the United States
Came from North Korea
The odds of that are almost
0 yeah if you are probably like you don't get but not necessarily you need to be like inside
North Korea to see you them putting out 1,000 hectares of
Poppyseeds notice it coming out
In some way or another
To report put out this year by the United Nations office on drugs and crime
83% of the world's opium
Is produce an afghan
Very little of that actually makes
Exit to u.s. Market
It's however it most of the opium
Metier originates in Mexico Colombia Guatemala
Alex is recording this
Afghanistan and Myanmar would be
Far and Away the largest suppliers of opium poppy in the world
Wow
Nothing
North Korea is not even on the radar
This is just how Alex puts
Some player into his news cover
He ignores reality and throw something jarring in his audiences in order to shock them
I'd like saying that North Korea sending opium to the United States to turn your children
Into heroin-addicted sex worker
That's just his feelings though that's it's not based on anything real
I'd be a weird thing for North Korea to do as well
So Alex
Calls
Almost this here broadcast
And he gets one call
From
How to dispose of a caller
This is a gas
Okay
Felt like a caller
Person
It wasn't an expert in anything
It's a woman
Their son
Is
Special education program
He felt that he didn't need to be in it
And she was
Upside about
I don't understand tomorrow's news today I don't
Really
Wants to talk too much about it cuz I don't know what the situation is with her kid and it doesn't
Winfield appropriate
However
Blow her mind
Talking about her son at 8
Ridiculous
Two different colored eyes
Oh no
Wardenburg
This is absolutely not true but if you're
Just making things up and kind of feels like it should be true
Well got to be from a twin
One eyes from one the other eyes turn the other that's
Call Alex Jones
To believe in a heartbeat
Somebody said that and he was like well duh one-eye's from the other twin
It's
I get it I get why you would think this but it's dumb
I like that even she was like
No no
Waardenburg syndrome is a condition that's
It's quite rare as a lot more presentations then just dick
Different colored eyes
Some other details that this person gives the diagnosis actually seems
Plausible center-child also has hearing loss which is
Just another symptom of wardenburg
The icing however just on its own is a phenomenon called heterochromia iridum
Generally speaking it's not a problem and it doesn't require treatment
It has nothing
You can even develop it later in life
Do you get
Superpowers
Your eye color is determined by a series of jeans that are incredibly complicated but more or less it boils down to
Eumelanin tots
Concentration in the tissues of your iris
Reasons you can have this at Birth generally come down to a genetic trait passed on from one
Your parents
It might be as simple as having hyperpigmentation in one eye or it could be indicative of
Yeah there's a couple serious conditions that it could be an indication of his child was born as one of those serious
More serious conditions I don't think the eye color would be the most pressing thing
Bring up now
I also offered up his bit of trivia hope
When do I guess
Blow the colors mine
He didn't have to say anything
But he couldn't resist trying to look like the guy who knows everything
He's just make
But you just making s*** up or passing along bad information that he heard somewhere
And didn't look into the moment he was like do you know what that is
She's like
Yeah it's called something it's something called waardenburg syndrome he's got it he's like no no no no no
This is my turn to tell you something what's going on with your child
That it was waardenburg is actually the liberal perspective
Genius
And I can honestly here Alex
Be wrong all day
And I
Would enjoy
I would enjoy him blowing hard about like
These things that he knows nothing about
Just trivia like I you know why you know why your hair color changing you grew up
You like that kind of thing
Evil evil
Evil I would be fine with that kind of a dumb show
Problem is it
Alex is also
Perpetuating really dangerous ideas with him
Conversation with this lady
All these things
My mind
Okay
Uniform
This is
Block B
Probably best take
Okay so here's here's what I'm here
A concerned parent going like
They put my child into the special education class I don't believe that he's supposed to be in there and be having a negative effect on
Development
And Alex response to that was
Well obviously they're going to murder you
They're going to take him so if you are going to murder your child and you then you have to leave course
Her point I guess as best I can tell from the
From the conversations they have is that the special education classes are
Specific enough
Yeah I know like they're people who have different learning challenges
Group together in a way that it's not
Like you can't
All of them the same
Except that that's true
Yeah just probably FairPoint in there
However
The solution to that
Would possibly be
More
Classes more special ed classes as opposed to
Dissolution that Alex has witches get rid of
Yes
Yeah
Yeah that's trouble conversation but I just I feel like Alex's take is just so irresponsible
It's so disrespectful to
You know people who are special at Educators and
Totino who take
A lot of time and care
I-22
The dragon help kids
I mean I remember growing up I was we were at we had like enrichment
G or whatever
And that was a essentially wasn't like a gift
Did class or anything they just gave you more work
Guess what you're finally in Richmond
Do all of this extra s*** as well
There were parents who took their kids out of that program like this isn't helping them develop
And that's
Totally fine
There were kids who are not being helped in there
You don't like hearing loss is a different problem than his dad developmental disability
You know that kind of big
All of that is fine apparent should recognize what's going on there
If the company tells you that they're going to murder your child they're not doing good for you
I don't think that there
Looking at the problem as it exists
They're looking at the problem as you do want
Headed to be my son is getting extra work from
His school and I I don't think it's
Helping Hands
They're trying to make
Then they're going to take him away from you
Going to say that the government are not going to believe you believe you make sense
Call Matt actually going to call
Andy gets a call from a guy who works at Taco Bell and this guy is pretty
Concerned
About technological advance
Kitchen
Alexa
Weeks ago
History Channel
Restaurants nearby
Talking about
The drive-thru window
And I caught my eye
Because they were
We're talkin about
Maybe Annette
McDonald's
And they would ask you if you take it off
The card while they're out there
Seymour
This is freaking me out
Because
I mean
You're trying to say well
Speed up the speed
Problem
Don't worry
Camera
That's kind of an exaggerated fear to have about
Credit cards
It's just that there's just no way there's no.
Technology visit like you remember when they introduced self-checkout at a grocery store people
They're f****** mind it's not about having tobacco background groceries
I think that there is a fine conversation to have surrounding like you know the jobs that are taken by
The jobs that are
Probably going to be eliminated within the fast-food space
In the coming years 100%
But it's kind of different than this one
This is stupid
Exact
IFixit Alex
I don't know if you understand that this guy's talking about credit cards being taken at the drive-thru
Cuz he's
I don't I don't know what
He's getting that
Is it does Alex think that they've got like
Taco Bell cards
Is that like the Taco Bell is giving them Taco Bell cards
A license or something
Yeah I don't know
I think it's dumb
I'm not worried about credit cards at the drive-thru
Another call and this fella
I believe it's from the Oklahoma City area
And he heard something on the radio that he wants to run by Al
You heard about the Oklahoma City
Steering reservoir
Turn On the Radio Star radio
RadioShack
This is amazing
And that clip Alex was basically trying
Like to take credit for some of Lights resolution being disgusted the Oklahoma City Council
But he didn't even know existed
Before this call
Also shouldn't
He know about these kinds of things
Like half of the show is just yelling about the Patriot Act so you would think that he would keep himself up to date on what would be major news on that front
I mean if
City of Oklahoma City just decided to overturn the Patriot Act pretty big news
It seems like something like what what else is he paying attention to in the news if not like
Kind of thing
I'll just wait until someone calls in
I also have
No idea what this resolution was I can't fly
What are we talkin
This is almost certainly the same thing as like we're reaffirming the 8th Amendment you know like
Have fun
So this next eclipse from a call
Is
What am I one of my favorites
That I found in a long time
And possibly
Part of the rationalization for doing
Doing an episode even though it's going to be shorter chill as there's not a whole lot
I needed to bring you this blessed
These people have been around
China Wok
How wonderful it was
Dismantle
No no
Alex's just free associating
No no no. He hears the name Dewey and he knows that there's a thing called the Dewey Decimal System
Asserts that they're related
I'll talk a little bit about that but first I wanted
Explain why Alex does this
Alex has no idea who John Dewey is but
You can't make that obvious to the audience
If this caller is mentioning Dewey in relation to the early globalist
Back in the 1920s
How should be an
Expert on this guy
By Justin interjecting Dewey Decimal System
Alex is trying to feign expertise because it
It's meant to look like him saying of course I know about John Dewey
I know about this guy
Yeah it's
It's remarkable and it's kind of the same thing that he's doing with
The eye color thing
It's the same sort of
Fake Authority
Betty's presenting it's just amazing
Perfect example of that
So first of all they're talking about this. In the 1920
Can you send the Dewey Decimal System
It was created in 1876
Also it was invented by a guy named Melvil Dewey
Not John Dewey
Little weird but Alex doesn't know this
But seeing as he should be the president of the Melvil Dewey Fan Club
I don't know if you know this Jordan
Melvil Dewey was a pile of s***
I did not know that he just also happened to create a very important system for standardizing Book classic
Application fit Library
Kicked out of the American Library Association which
You found it
Because he wouldn't stop sexually harassing women
Including his daughter-in-law Jesus Christ
Just nuts to think that this guy was so out of line that he would get in trouble for making unwelcome advances to women in the early 19th
Hundreds of time of that sort of thing was pretty,
Yeah
Hey people turned the other way on it a lot
It was in the newspaper
They just wrote
Horrible sexually harassing such a problem but you got kicked out of the
So Melvin would go on to found the Lake Placid Club
Which is something of a health resort
He forbade Jews black people and any other minorities from joining the club
And he specifically band Booker T Washington
I'm coming up
He was such a bigot that
According to an article in the American libraries magazine quote
Dewey bought up the adjoining land for fear it would otherwise be sold to Jews
Cheese's
Christ
Dude is a real piece of s***
Yeah
Why couldn't we have just gone with alphabetical I didn't know that Melville alphabet was a piece of s***
Yeah it's unfortunate that he should create something it revolutionized libraries
But he saw
So conversely John Dewey was a psychologist in an educator who spent some time in China in the 1920s
You have nothing to do with libraries in library science I was just making up whatever information makes it look Smart in the
Cuz he's comfortable in the knowledge that a podcast pointing this stuff out and laughing at it wouldn't exist for another 18 years
Yeah he got he got away with it for a long time
Not anymore baby
Dewey Decimal System go f*** yourself
Dewey Destin
I was waiting for and even be like I was expect
Effingham to go with Dewey defeats Truman as his reference for that
Do that he went even dumber than doing it if he's true people might actually remember
Details about the Dewey defeats Truman
Where is Dewey Decimal System is just obscure enough that most people don't know the history behind it
It exists remember the Melvil Dewey was bios can't believe that
Why don't I get to learn about
Half of the s*** that we learn about is made by piece
Pieces of s***
And we should also get that con
Erase service person from history but
Why do we always get that contact every time I hear about DNA or even while we're talking about the MRNA vaccine
Also just a reminder the guys who did that piece of s***
It's it's unfortunate
Kind of but it is just
Depart of
Living in reality there are some things
That are important breakthroughs that have happened
In our history
I've been done by people who suck are a literature major like
Myself
You're eventually going to have to wrestle with the fact that just about everybody who wrote a good book as a giant
So
Alex
Is that you still covering that monkey paw
Quite a bit
Monkeypox scare
This it says it's just
Quickly
But that I'm able to clearly see that the government has
Most probably
Dumps is monkeypox on us
Because right away before they
You know even hardly even name of his dick
That's not good ever
I would say that the they did know the names of people who are they just didn't
Publicized
Sound like
Hey David
Protecting people's privacy
Which is
Fine
My neighbor able to
Define
What commonalities there were and they go they all went
Work in contact with
Prairie dogs at
Specific
I wonder if there's a connection here
Like
The the
Almost
Non-Stop
Reality of
A large group of people
Cool react react to anyone knowing something with well if you know something you proper
Yeah you're probably in on it just like see they knew something so they obviously did it
You could have learned
Yeah
There are the other thing too is that Alex is trying to present this like
Fear of a release of a bio-weapon by
Talking about the Monk
Epoxide which is nonsense
And then
Talking about Porton down releasing
Foot-and-mouth Yelp
That's like please
Aren't good examples they're not
They're not based on anything come onto things happened a thousand miles away they're the same thing
Obviously it's
So we check in here on Alex's views
Events that are going on in Iraq
We have an inch of
Open update
Saddam banknotes is because the public ID quote
Confidence in the only other banknote in wide circulation
By October 2003 a new DNR had been introduced with anti-fraud measures in place
Provide a unified currency without saddam's face on
This was just the least bad solution to the problem
As an article in the BBC put that quote
U.s. in British
Officials have said it's better to lose face by printing 250 DNR notes with
With Saddam on them
For a short.
Then risk further inflaming public anger
The bath party is not in power at this point and in fact just 14 days before this episode was recorded
Beactive elements of D pacification had entered into
Divorce in Iraq
Now coalition
Two forces were responsible for tracking
Determine who was a member of the bath party
So they could be banned from holding any job in the pub
Looks weird
It's really f***** up like this super destructive process is going on
And the way Alex is covering it
Could not be more detached
Cast from reality
Is the game
What's actually going on
It's bananas especially
Considering the fact that
Would you go back
Can you read through all of these books
It's like
You guys are so stupid
Why are you getting rid of everyone who knew how to do any
And immediately the whole place fell apart and they're like I don't understand
It's almost like we just hired a bunch of new people who have never done anything like
This before
Yeah
There weren't there is there were some critical mistakes that were made especially in the implementation
Of
That
Initiative
Yeah
Foolish such a brutal brutal
It's so weird that we're here in the middle of June and Alex is still on the giving the country
The baathist
I don't know when that's
Going to change
But it's one of the only things really about
Coverage of the Iraq war that I signed
At all
Because it's
Yeah it's it's so
Divorce
Like how can you read anything
And come to the conclusion that they put a bath
Austin power
I need to put his
Content through debaffle occasion
Alright sorry
Click
The cliff
Upon
Lyrics of fun until Matrix cast off
There is this sort of weird mirror of the present-day in terms of this
You know discussion of releasing bio-weapon
From
From Labs but if you look at the stuff you was talking about it
At this point
It's b*******
Nonsense
And then
That's a battery decimal thing really made me laugh
Yeah so I believe this is the story of Melvil Dewey is not to his wife
Maybe I should be we have an influence
Let's see if we can get that story out there
People will know from here on out did they change it they don't use the Dewey Decimal System anymore in libraries right through the middle librarian
I don't know how I don't think they do
They may I don't think so
I think they got rid of
Librarian somebody said that Melvil Dewey was a real piece of s***
#cancel
So yeah Jordan will be back
But until then we have website we do it's knowledge
That knowledge underscore
Will be back but until then I need om Leo mdzs Corte Madera
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work