Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge b b
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Yessir Georgetown
For yourself
Jordan is I'm going to be taking this weekend
Do you know sort of rare
Itrip
Kind of thing
I mean this is Breitbart cuz I like
I'm excited about that
Also I bring this up because
Because of this
What episodes are going to be out on Wednesday and Friday next week
I cannot even
Enjoy without couching it within an apology
I apologize brain is a mess
Open to anyone
Anything for me I'm still putting up two episodes
I have a problem
Remember problems
What's your birthday
I got a rare double bright spot
But it's also the same rights but we can't plug your stand-up show it's already happened
That's the point I did not put it on purpose
On the show
Months ago you posted
Today 12 you're still promoting
I know there's that but also the most important rights
Is on Friday
Play I found out last night
That Maria Bamford is in town
The dead and so my favor
Everett, Co
12 years who I have never been able to see life like I remember
Her first Comedy Central half hour
Like I can still do the the cult leader B
The first half-hour
Finally I get to see your life
Need somebody I know there's nobody else I know I know you got good comics
In case you're wondering
I hope you have a great time
Today we have an episode to do and because we're not going to be having an episode on Monday
I was really hoping
Present-day episode to do
Ketchup see what Alex is doing in the real world in the present
On Wednesday we had a 2003 episode
But unfortunately Alex's Studio has been hosting
I can't think of any reason why Alex would need to be out of
Studio other than probably
Furious 8 hours a day meetings with lawyers I'm not entirely sure what it is either maybe he's selling his house
House for a fourth time
Go over for say so we were in a bind
Anirban Monday
We can't not have an episode on Friday because Alex is a long week out of town
Might do I have to get a ticket head of work
Go to work
Figure out like Jim Bakker nothing good there
What the Project Camelot land
Didn't find anything
Worthwhile.
So I decided we're going to stick in 2003
Keep going through June 2003
When we talked about the 18th and the 19th
Today alright
Terrible
Unlistenable may be a long weekend bag
Bored just
Trap
And then it heated up
Okay
To tell you that this is one of the most
Revelatory episodes
We will ever do
We found
In the mire of just unlistenable garbage so we'll take care of that
Everyone stop York
Cars in traffic right now
I was really hoping to avoid that kind of language
First Emory who's Celine Works been cats made them click this button thank you so much you are now policy walk
When is naming his cat next patenaude
Thank you so much
Next
Erica from Louisville thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk spell definitely that wasn't me
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Big Louie's Sparky Donaldson thank you so much and I apologize
Text of being a feminist makes me a witch and witches are the brides of Satan I might technically the bride or cyber Satan
Thank you so much you are now by Lizzie walk
Very much and finally
Coming out of my cage and I've been doing just fine
I'm a policy wonk
Midas voice I'm Mister bright spot
That's fun
Okay that is fun
So Jordan today
Yes we're going to the zoo staying in 2003
Just like soda standard out of context drops
The other is one that I think will be very helpful in the in the future
Here's the normal line
Okay
I read that I've not heard a good argument yeah
Terms of Alex's advice
Have to be pretty bad to get there
Spot will come in very handy in the future
Ohio
Danny Riley are I was listening to that and I was like
Illinois
Alright so here we go we're going to start on
The 18th
If this is a slog
Lulu's like a really bad if you get maybe the first two hours of
Show
Real trouble seems kind of like being out of context
Non-stop we're getting
To almost every time we go back there
But also being
Inexplicably boring for long stretches of time
This sometimes walking
Through like knee-deep mud for sure
Sometimes
What is the things that I was struck by a
So much Adventure
The so much more of a radio show back then
You know he's like hitting the headlines and going
Two calls in
Hello guest
It's all it's jumping around now that you know who keeps your attention
Mostly
Yeah
I was reflecting on how would we go
The 2,000 stuffies just like singing along to Country have that right now
No it's it's kind of like
He doesn't have as much Freedom rajawat Aviv yesterday
That comes later and he starts singing country and then his life completely falls apart
This is still like I'm trying to be a professional comfortable enough to be like I'm letting it all hang out
This is on the upswing in The Highwayman
Totally
Miss that freedom I do like I do like that week
Contrack ups and downs throughout his his time and we can just
Go to like I'm feeling real bad mood let's go to 2086
Play some Highwaymen
So I would say that the beginning of this show and most of it on the 18th
Could be summed up as like
Alex is a cab
Reaper
It's just constantly talking about how evil the cops are that's bananas
I hate it so much
This is a specific live about like detectives but like he's he's going off on Cops
Joseph
Sometimes I feel like they're the right
Entire moral philosophy is just like whatever the late left likes
Today I must kill like if we could because the right has the purity of focus
Chris that comes along with
Having no distractions but hating little f
Right if we could just get
Smart enough to make them happy
I hate the right
Things
By us doing the wrong thing
Then we win
Who's a bad strategy
You run the risk of them being like Oh I like that there is Joy again
Yeah it is a Hail Mary
Like I'm saying this is pretty boring
Mostly a lot of like shiitake
Can the cops
Some interesting thing
Things like Alex get to call here
What's an interesting Theory
About the SWAT team
Okay goodnight in the United States
Barney and Maryland
Are are you doing
A reason that's a brutal
So cold
SWAT team
Where is ski mask
Is it cuz they are criminals
And if they are used over and over again
And I it's all part of the New Freedom
I don't want you to
Recognizing over and over again all around
Backcountry
Roar
Man army
As long as a
People
Handsome man army
Are you understand what's going on here outside of the suicide squad
Is amazing there's if there's one SWAT team for the whole country
Snooker
Only like 15 guys Criminal
It's the best of the best
Put should be artist
Sure
Hey that's what we do it's the suicide squad
Nonsense I like that though I enjoy these
Out-of-left-field. But sometimes will come up
No reason 2003 episode we talked about the case of dr. Charles cell
Who was that dentist
It brought up all the issues of the involuntary medicating
Because he was
Not fit to stand trial like
Refuse to take medication
And as we discussed on that episode
In June
The Supreme Court rules
That he couldn't be
Involuntary
Supreme Court ruling
Did they
Actually the opposite of the truth
Yeah this Supreme Court ruling in cell versus not establish proper Justice
Station to involuntarily Medicaid doctor cell
How much is reporting the opposite of the truth
Or what I call Ally
Alex is also making up at the Supreme Court ruled that people can be drugged as long as it's not too risky in terms of side effects
The consideration of side effect is definitely part of the equation but it's Alex it taken even
Couple minutes to read the Court's decision
He would know that the version of this he's pitching his frogs
The court has a very narrow window of cases that could lend themselves to involuntary medication
Involuntarily medicating
From the top
Quote
First a court must find that important governmental interest rates
The government's interest in bringing to trial in individual accused of a serious crime is Emporia
However courts must consider each cases fact in evaluating disinterest because
Special circumstances May lessen its importance
Eg a defendant's refusal to take drugs made me in length
Deconfinement
Which would diminish the risks of breathing without punishment one who has committed a serious crime
In addition to its substantial interest in timely prosecution
The government has a comp committed
Pinterest
In ensuring a defendant a fair trial
Second the court must conclude that forced medication would
Significantly further those concomitant State entry
It must find that medication is substantially likely to render the defendant
And substantially unlikely to have side effect that will interfere
Significantly
With the defendant ability to assist counsel
In conducting at the
Third
The court must conclude that involuntary medication is necessary
For those interested
And find the alternative less intrusive treatments are unlikely to achieve
Substantially the same result
Fourth
The court must conclude that administering the drugs
Is medically appropriate
So there are a number of considerations that are
I am in the in this ruling
Write the fact
That they have
And in the in the decision they found that the lower courts
You had ordered
Him to be medicated did not
Achieve any of these think the standard so they overturned
The lower Court's decision
But he was
Has a lazy f****** liar it's
Seems like he was like I don't really care what the
I'd say
I think the point is
I'm going to say
I think the argument would be that
Okay yeah
Alright
Hear me out
So
The decision says
But they're overturning the decision
Involuntarily Medicaid
Doctor Cell
Right
They're also saying that
That there are narrow Circle
Stances that
You can Medicaid somebody in
So like
That means they're going to do it anyway
Now I respect that however you also said that they are going to do it to Doctor Cell
Because
Those narrow Circle
They're going to make it
Digger that's just up saying they're going to do it anyway
I know it's frustrating it's very dumb
Alex
Let's be clear
These are not like the higher-ups at the FBI this isn't call me
This is
Gmail
I all dry brand new Cadillac conversation
Sick of these FBI agents that he knows in Austin
So
Tired
Of the stereotype
Of the obscenely wealthy FBI agent huh
Generously rich
Not stop
Blowing money f
FBI agent everyone knows from TV
Yeah
Choose another bit of news that Alex is going on about
Other than just rambling about how bad cops
Enjoin
Wow
So Jane Roe in the Roe v Wade case was a woman named Norma mccourtney
Norma mccorvey
Her identity is the woman in the case was a
The secret by 2003 and already undergone a public conversion to Christianity
As a person whose name is on the case that legalized abortion she was
Exactly the sort of person
The anti-abortion movement was
Desperate to court
Call Amanda
For them
It wasn't really all that clear-cut
From a piece about her Legacy in the Washington Post
In the 1990s when
Mccorvey was on their team she would tell Evangelical leaders that she supported a woman's right to terminate her pregnancy within the first
Trimester
The procedure that account
That's where the majority of all the Porsche
Quotes
We manage that by saying she's a brand new Converse
She needs time to mature and her face and her inner understanding of the pro-life
Thanks
Quote we thought just give her a little time and she'll
Amateur
Eventually they got her to stop saying it publicly but they didn't know whether she'd actually chew
Flash Forward to 2020 and a documentary gets released called AKA Jane Roe
Where director Nick Sweeney interviewed mccorvey
And since she died before the film was finished
Her statement could appropriately be called a deathbed confession
And he also said quote this is my deathbed
Confession
Why would she say
What to do about Megadeth
That seems like they only reason you would
In the documentary she admitted that she wasn't actually ever anti-abortion
I took their money and they put me out in front of the camera and told me what to say and that's what I'd say
Did this weenie replied asking quote it was all an act
I had a response
Quote
In that Washington Post peace Rob Schenck
An anti-abortion activist
In the 90s who is
The guy who had that quote
From Passenger read earlier
And his position on abortion
He said that
Confession was shocking
Quote not because of what it revealed about her but would have revealed about me and the movement
She forced me to be honest
With myself
Do you have to be honest about the fact that they used her as a
The prop and that's what I was doing right now
And honestly Jane Rose opinion on abortion rights shouldn't really be held up as any more important than anyone else's
No I mean she is proud
Probably the smartest one involved in all of this she was playing both sides for everything they got man she is smart as hell
I think that that is
Some of the sense you get beat up a little bit
I mean like
You granted her name is on the pseudonym is on
The actual K sure it's not like
Cursing aha I've changed my mind
It's at that doesn't change
Principles
That the decision is based on
That's why
She was like
F*** yeah I've already got it done. Million billion dollars
It's a PR thing
PR victory for the anti-abortion folk
It's not
It doesn't mean anything
In terms of
Weather
You your
Pro-life or pro-choice involved knows it except for the people there
Yeah
Alex get some news about Zechariah
What's he up to
He's in he's in jail
He wants to talk
The Congress
About how we did
Didn't do it
Leaving that aside
This is one of the more shocking things I've heard on the show
Appearance
Oh boy
What
Alright
So
So we've got both move salary being like
It was the government who did it
That isn't even how much the government did it
You're not even real there's nobody who's on the play
Okay I thought that was an interesting
Something to hear like and I was very disappointed expound on this
There was nobody on the plane
I would talk about this now but it comes back up later and
Do you know how they got into the air
Giant slingshot
Autopilot has remote control
LOL
Slingshot
It's valid
Brothers episode Alex's teasing
About like some
Announcement
He's going to make sure and I actually didn't think
That it meant anything the first time I heard it but he kept doing it
So I went back and here's the first time
I want exposed
Jerk
Weather control
They have control of the ones under their control
Alex's got this warning
Yeah excited
Whenever there's a warning
I would like to be warm
You got enough yeah
It's Big Steaks
We don't know he's teasing that there's a warning
To a ways into the show
Here he's teasing it again
What
Particularly
Warning
Morning again but instead of getting to it he has a gold sales
Guess what
I'm going to Prime you to buy gold
He's going to tell you how great gold is especially it's a
It's something negative were to happen to the rest of the world I have a very vague non-specific
And also gold is on sale
Hey
Then I've got a lot to tell you some
Some things are coming that you're going to want to be like really aware of
First though I'm going to tell you about how great guns are
I don't want to warn you about what I need to warn you about this yeah I mean that would be no
Yeah that's true that's owned by a gun sales
Gold's company
Being on Vitus resources
F****** smooth
Love it
Sounds good so Alex along with being a cab he's very much
Not getting the grasp
Of supreme
In Court decisions
Totally wrong about
I'd be interested
Score from the gym
And there wouldn't be any kind of Reaper
Have your arm cut off
And if the person
Delirious
Roar
It sounds like the listener or the caller is saying like I don't believe this I cannot believe that
We've come to this point
Yeah
Just cuz this is
Very much not true
Alex's talked about the Supreme Court ruling that he's referencing here a number of times throughout the show but he's never brought up the
The name of it is never brought up
Specifics
So the case in question is Chavez vs Martinez
And it was decided on May 27th 2003
How to present the situation is one where the cop withheld treatment to a person who'd been shot only allowing them to receive medal
Okay once they agreed to answer their quests
This is a complete misrepresentation of even with a basic questions were in
McKay's and what the Supreme Court rules
Here's the basic details of the underlying
A man named oliverio Martinez was stopped on his bicycle by narcotics off
To attempt to put them in cups
They were not a Narcotics invest
A cab
Struggle broke out and in the process Martinez was shot five times
Martinez did admit that in the struggle he tried to steal an officer's gun
But for reasons we'll discuss later this admission might not be all that.
Yeah
After Martinez had been shot
In the case of rice
Officer Ben Chavez Road along with the a in the ambulance with marks
Trip to the hospital and in the hospital room he questioned Martinez
Which was potentially a violation of his right
In the process of this questioning Martinez admitted that he had used heroin and that he tried to steal that officer
So the primary question of the case was whether or not that confession could be used in court
Or if it was a violation of Martinez's right
Oh yeah that's a way more interesting question than just vacant
Stand over you and watch you
Bleed out right
The essential question but that's not even totally accurate because for reasons we'll discuss later
It doesn't even
Become relevant
Because he never got charged with a crime
So it never was used against him
Still potentially a violation of a really interesting question to have solved
Portrayal of it
Because since he was never charged with a crime
Then his confession was never used against him
It now becomes a question of whether or not
The officer Ben Chavez
Qualifies for qualified immunity is able to not be sued for his action
Which is your day
Theoretically the Supreme Court was deciding
So Martinez claim to violation
The first was a fifth amendment claimed that he'd been
Compelled to be a witness against
Himself
The second was the 14th Amendment claim with guarantees due process and the right to be free of coercive question
What made the case extra complicated like I said is that Martinez never got charged with a crime in the confessions were never used
In court so
You know these
Confessions were never used in court were Martinez's rights violated by the office
Questioning everybody was in the ambulance in India
Because if so
Chavez can be sued
And this is why we need
Need to discuss this right
The ninth Circuit Court had ruled that Martinez's Fifth and Fourteenth Amendment rights had been in fridge
Based on the persistent nature of Chavez
Just questioning
And that quote
The 5th amendments purpose is to prevent coercive interrogation practices that are
Destructive to human dignity
This was that appeal to the
Supreme Court decided in May 2003 the Chavez actions did not actually constitute a violation of Martinez's
Constitutional rights
The rationale is a bit complicated but a lot of it does boil down to the fact that Martinez was never actually charged with
The crime
Since he was never under oath
The court decided that his 5th Amendment rights weren't applicable
He's questioning
As for the 14th Amendment question they found that the questioning Chavez engaged in wasn't quote egregious or quote
Conscience shocking
As it was claimed to be in Prior cases
Supreme Court
If the ruling includes
It's not conscience
Specifics of the language
F****** thing I've ever read
Pacific conducting engaged in and found that it was not consist
That was a violation of the 14th
On the consideration that the court had
Decided that Chavez has not violated Martinez's right
He was out
Algebra for qualified immunity and subsequent
Can be sued
For the actions that he took as His official capacity as a police off
If you listen to Alex's show you would know literally none of these details
You would just think that a guy got shot in the stomach and then a cop
Refuse to let medical responders treat him until he agreed to be questioned
About the Supreme Court said hey that's
Cool
The first version of its focus is entirely on the wrong question
Because
Based on a made-up version of detail of
The court wasn't determining whether or not it was appropriate to withhold medical care until someone agrees
Questioning because that didn't happen
Hear from
Supreme Court ruling
Here there's no evidence
Since the job has acted with a purpose to harm Martinez by intentionally interfering with his medical tree
Medical personnel were able to treat Martinez throughout the interview at Chavez cease this questioning to allowed test and other procedures to be
Be performed
Nor is there evidence
The job as a contact exacerbated Martinez entries or prolonged
To stay in the hospital
Moreover the need to investigate whether there have been police misconduct constituted a justifiable government interest
Given the risks
The key evidence would have been lost
Is Martinez had died without the authorities ever hearing his side
Story
That is a very
That is a good
This case is really interesting and there's something to be learned from discussing
From here you see
You see interesting things you can learn from both angles pro and con
Do what happen
It's not interesting in the way that Alex
No traffic it is interesting because I think the ultimate
Hinge point
Really comes down to
Do you believe that the physical presence
The officer there
Is it by implication
Exactly while you are being treated you are at about the weakest possible you can be
So are you mirror the mirror like act
Give him being there because of course
At any point you are aware he could just
Push somebody aside
You know that kind of
So the question is do you think that
Real or not
And I think that that that
Consideration that lives in the ruling
You know if there is evidence
That the police had acted inappropriately in the shooting
He has that evidence
And no one else
Would be able to provide it right
The Nae
Might die
It's in everyone's best interest
To be sure we know that
Mangle on this but I hadn't even considered until I right
There's alot going on here
The fake version of these stories in order to get mad about the
And then he accuses enemies of doing something they didn't do so he can get even more mad and make the audience
More mad
It's just silly
And most important of all though
He doesn't have to learn
Anyting
That's the most important lesson we can take from Infowars
Here's the other thing the other added benefit
He doesn't have to wrestle with ambiguity
Oh no absolute because you know even as I hear the details of this case
I don't know exact
Actually
What I think is the right thing to do
I don't know
How comfortable I am with the idea of police interviewing people in a hostel
Absolutely be very much abuse
At the same time that argument
Needing to
Possibly get evidence
Couldn't get any other way
Against the police sure
Theoretically theoretically
Involuntarily medicated somebody I think is not good
At the same time
If somebody is unable to
To stand trial
They're doing a disservice to their own defense right by not being able to stand trial
Inability to defend themself in court
You shouldn't try and defend yourself in
Court
On a full moon
If you're aware wolf
Wait until the the day you're feeling normal
It's not it's not black and white there's grazin in
In some of this when you're discussing it outside of let's say of courtroom
Right
I just think Alex isn't
Trip to do that and I don't think that he
Really has a
Way to make money off
The ambiguity
Definite
Concrete decisions it's far more important for him
Because ambiguity suggests that there there's the possibility you are both wrong and don't
No sure you may just not
No
And he cannot do that
No he just can't
It's it's to humbling
To be in a position where
You might be like
It's not the biggest sex
It does feel lucky
He's afraid of that terrible it's almost like yeah you just hear the word do you go for it
We heard earlier that Alex
Believe there was no one on board
The planes on 9/11
And I thought that maybe he was just
Were there any planes at all I thought he was maybe just saying it
I just tried it out yet
A caller
Closet
You talking about
Hey buddy just not call after that
Delaware
The aircraft
Oh he's even got that voice to that's great
Call cases
Chambord
We don't know
Wow
Wow walk back or not
We don't know if anybody was Alda played
Is the exact same thing to take note
Doubling down just a little bit.
Evidence of it
Really got it
Neither is this
So yeah that's already a contradiction of his
Maybe what are you saying is that there's a 20% occupied
Density of each of them because it was artificial
It would actual people on earth
Still further
Yeah and it's not true I was just lying about the people on board the airlines
So United 93 actually did have
20% of its
Seat belt with 37 passengers out of a total capacity of 182
This is noted to be significantly lower than the average load for this flight on Tuesdays in the previous three months
Which was 52%
Irrelevant
Drop
American Airlines flight 77 had 58 out of a possible 17
96 passengers on board
This was 33% which is right in line with that played three months average on Tuesdays which was 32.8%
United flight
It's 175 had 56 passengers with a capacity of 1 C
This is a 33% capacity which is
A bit lower than their average on that flight
49%
Find fault
On the other hand
American Airlines flight 1181 passengers
What's the capacity of 158
Which represented 51%
The three-month average for flight flight 11 on Tuesdays was actually 39%
This is a bit more crowded than usual
Just making up statistics to make things seem suspicious but it's all completely disconnected from reality
You the malicious liar because if you followed his logic through to its natural conclusion he must think that everyone who had a loved one
On one of those planes must be lying
Or I guess the recipe for more complicated conspiracy where the passengers got taken off boarding
Killed in a
Hanger somewhere whatever I mean
It's not
It's impossible not to look at this and see if Sandy Hook
Written all over there not there
Yeah it's like a Proto it's like he's trying easy
Beginning the thing that will overthrow his career right now
This trend of behavior
Even Sanders nine years prior not real
It's just awful
It's it's really sad
When you go back to this.
That Alex is going to be trying to sell more grounded 911
Conspiracy theories
Like you know I don't buy to buy a whole lot of it but I think if you just be talking about building 7 and the speed of sound
Doesn't make sense to go back in
Can see that like
He's actually
Trying to argue that no one was on the play
Playing space lasers
Now
They are space lasers
Bitchute Plaines
From space
It's all the government
Now if you think that Alex arguing
They're being nobody on the plane is a mess
That's about this gets worse
Break in the middle of this phone call Alex holds him over until the next segment
And then we get another teas
New World Order
Program
Another eight
And cool
Who knows what's going to happen
Maybe you should buy some maybe maybe
I told you where you could literally
So Steve this caller has a great
Okay and that is based on the things that Alex has been saying
There seems to be a suggestion that there is nobody who was on board which is very much the argument that Alex has been making
So Steve was like what about all the people who are the
The funeral let's not talk about
Now
You'll notice that Alex starts to
Pretend they're having a different conversation than they're actually having
And all the people that went to
We're here
That is abuse
That is gas-lighting arguing that there were nobody on board
Sodium boy that play Man
He literally said that I'm going to go back
Appearance
Alex is trying to
He's done his he's f***** up
Yeah he's talk
What's a bunch of s***
And he's realized oh no there's someone confronting me about a fact I can't backup at all 0 backup
Do is hostility pretend that we're having a different argument
And that argument is about all I said
Was that they were remote-controlled planes are you saying that they were paid
You're the one bringing in Crazy information here that I've never heard my never said there's nobody on the plane flight
I think that all I said is there remote control Siri you're not listening to me if you say you're not listening to be with your
I want to punch you in the face yeah it really do it's real rough
Violets
This Alex continues to pretend to be having a conversation but no one on board
Their funeral service
I'd like to know like I said you know how did they buy off all of
Focus buddy
So the pilots
If I knew that
Call the firefighters
Grout
So Alex isn't getting
Anywhere really
Because this guy isn't letting go of the fact that they were having a conversation about something else
Alex gets mad and starts yelling about Authority almost have to kind of agree with you let me
Tell you some
I talked to firefighter
I got what I f******
Index Alex just receipts to get more math
Masshole
Control
Tell the passengers using
You have a confession
Directions to Northwood
What is it that it's Northwoods is that confession
Is very weak
Yeah I mean like
Can't tell you enough how like
Weird it was to listen to
Because this guy is very much
Responding to something that Alex
No one was on board the planes on
Alex's used weird evidence
To try and argue this point
And haven't realized he can't
Pretending they were talking about whether or not the
The plan was remote can
Control I never
You said I said I never see
I never said what I said were people on board who died doing the all I said was the planes remote control
You say that I say things when I know what I said
And there's no way for anybody to follow up on this later
So now here's where it gets really
Clear that he's doing this on purpose
As soon as this dude gets off the
The phone
Alex starts
Kind of suggesting that no one was onboard again
Bottom line
Get the payoff
Oh and by the way then
Weather
Here's the thing
If you're suggesting that the families are being paid off
And that they are making sure no one can see the interviews with them right
Whether or not
The planes were a remote
Control the families wouldn't know that they weren't on the plane write the passengers on the planes wouldn't necessarily know that
I mean I assumed there would be a movie moment where somebody is like
I don't know what's going on and they knock on the door of the cockpit and they don't have nothing they like
I bet that wouldn't happen that would be a fun moment
The only thing he could be suggesting by way of these insinuations is that the families of the people who
Airplanes are lying about their family member beating those plans guy they're getting paid off to do it you got it
Correct
There was no one on that play
This is so intentional
What you did on this call is
So intentional it's so clear
He realized he couldn't
To find this thing
Next to a guy who actually wanted to talk about that thing that wasn't offensives
Suggestion
And I realized I got it I got to save face by pretending we're having a separate argument
It's cowardly
The disgust I have her a person who says something
Beck's off of it
Wines
And then he's like
Now that I'm away from that guy go back to saying whatever I want
Not did not 5 Seconds
What a what an a****** cuz if he had said those things
While Steve was still on the line
Paw Patrol
Because he couldn't get away with it while critical voice was
This is the type of behavior that cause
Capital punishment in schools to be acceptable for a liberal punishment
20 kids a day
No I'll be just like that kind of childish like I didn't say that I didn't say that makes you want to slap so
It should you can't not
I understand where you're coming from
I just get off
Or not get off I like
I'm bored validated by
Demonstrated that I can show you
This Behavior
And it's been consistent for the last 18 years
Exactly
What a dick
So Alex is another color and this person is talking about stories about
What's the Supreme Court decision
About Charles cell
The medication
Issue
And here is why
His audience is just
Screwed
In terms of their information
You can park
Whoever you want
Turbo
Medication for
Right now
The whole article reads as if
They're not going to do it I didn't even catch it until you said if I went back and got the article
It sure is
Thank you do you just trapped
Because the decision also discussed the narrow Circle
Santa's wherein
Involuntarily Medicaid
Somebody could be acceptable
They have decided that that invalidates
The other part of the ruling that over
Overturned the previous Court's decision
Listen to involuntarily Medicaid doctor cell
It's it's
Give me your trapped
It's a trap
5 minutes
Stetsom rubber York
Forever
I'm never going to admit to anything
Just going to bounce off
Alex gets
Another call
And this guy says that like we do we need to do we need to get you and John stadtmiller togethers another
Right-wing talk show host
And we need to do like a devil
Ministration in DC we need to protest
And Alex gets off on like
About how
Anytime the Patriots want to protest
The government will infiltrate and make it
Look bad
Arguments for why you
You can't have a protester with a pyrite
So now I
Everytime we start protesting there's an OKC bombing and everybody thinks that it does
Understand
Be his big warning
But I'm not sure
It's also very clearly woven in as a response
Let's do this color I wanted to march in DC
Local
Building Supply
Cereal
Maybe his warning is there are feds around
They're coming
Right there coming for you well I think the warning if the entire episode
And now we're the end of the third hour there is no fourth hour at this point
This Is the End
You saying that
People who want to do violent
Are feds trying to set you up
Fine that's a fine warning I guess because the ultimate
Conclusion is don't trust people who want to
Commit acts of violence probably a healthy perspective
I don't
No
Why did you build it up so much this is at Wright-Patt mean it today don't
Start viola
And also this morning this is
Is coming right after a phone call where the guy was
Suggesting violence
No he was suggesting a protest
Stay off drugs
Good
Kids in schools
Sleep through it all
I don't know
You know what I've always found Sodus
It's the way that he says
You know this happens to everybody
It's it happens to black people that happens to what he always starts with black people
And the reason he does that
Is because he uses this false a
He's functionally
Like
He's he's
Vocally using black people as a shield for his wife
Soupremacy it is so f******
Such a small thing but every single time he does it
It's disrespectful into
Disgusting
Play tape makes my skin crawl I hate it
That's pretty bad
So that could have been his warning
This also could have been his Warren
I'm not sure he doesn't clarify enough
Corruption
About how
You understand
Maybe this is the announcement that he's been teasing I'm not sure
I want to say also to that
Alex's defense
He does clarify that like
What I'm saying this about like
Stay away from my show with this b*******
He wasn't talking
Sing about the caller who was just suggesting
Daily sketch
Himself and realized this could be
Seeing as me saying any protestors
Right wrong
Ryan and Misty.
I don't I don't understand
The point is of this big warning to declare his independence
Depend
I mean
One might say that it's a Reclamation of Independence is opposed to a declaration of
Smite
I suppose that also work
I think you could also call it
What's the word
I'm going to
Listen
And I'm going to call my Senator right now I want them to reaffirm the Declaration
Independent OB Gray
Yes
If they don't
A Satan so unfortunately Alex's run out of time
To get to the sad news stories
Cam
That
Gold coins
Cool
Gotham
About that's even sadder than $10 Olympic
Infomercial at 2 a.m. the guy who is on for Midas resources
We can't ever find these
We can get the $5 one so we can never get the $10 ones
These are just for Alex Jones listen
I got my hands on guaranteed
250 lease
Trying to sell 250
But hey
How about we try and sell 5000
How do I get 100
The classic
You have all of them
Snake oil use
Car sales at bullshitters
So maybe Alex's big announcement at warning is that
They're going mainstream and you know where I could be hanging out with militias in the woods
All the feds
Disappointing
To get to the end of this and not really know what is an ounce
Warning
The show's over
Like I said
In that Meijer
You find
Alex getting schooled
By this guy
The claim that Alex made earlier the show
And I think there's something really valuable
About understanding what happened
In that Exchange
Between the two of them because it's essential to understanding
How you deals with the idea of anybody
Having an exchange of ideas or a debate with him
These are the sort of tact
I fixed it will get
Most people off track
Pretty easily just pretended you were having a different conversation
Now that we've seen that his
The ultimate weakness is just staying on target
Like the moment that you don't fall for his we'll have you heard or
This is the
You know
If I ever were to talk to him
I would just
Say laser-focused
On
Operation lockstep
Just anytime there was something that was slightly off track at they will talk about that later or staying on this
And it would just deteriorated
Start begin to vibrate and then I assume go Super Saiyan
Most likely
Unsatisfying for me as well
And be miserable
So we go to the 19th now
Again
This is a
F****** slog at the beginning
It is so rough
It is mostly
The first 25 minutes is largely Alec
Complaining about how some Christian organization has been bootlegging his movie
Those bastard yes
Bootlegging movies to be met you want you want you to make copies of them and spread them out to people
Does not want you selling them
I guess
And I think that he would he's really mad about it is they ran it
Something
You selling his DVD
I agree with that
It also is a little bit of a gray area based on the way that he
Sort of
Gives up one car garage as many copies of these as you can and do whatever you want with the right and don't
So don't like charge for them but what about the expenses of making copies of tapes
Exactly where is the line now at wholesale cost
I also think there's another thing that he's a little bit mad about that I actually find far more reasonable
And that is that the copies that they're making are like fifth-generation copies EXO's there bad copies that there
They're selling
And people will call him and complain about things that he didn't sell
Pretending to be a distributor of your thing
And you have no quality
Controllability
Yeah I mean it would make me mad to be in the black market for Alex Jones tapes bugs
So this is about the first
Half of the first hour is
Sure and he finally talked himself into suing
Dealer public dealer
Some people
Angry about
New World Order
What he says I'm not going to talk about these people he means by now
Can I guess that's like it that's fine
Don't give a
Whatever
This is just a sister almost
Present-day Ash
Yeah terms of pointlessness
Probably just send him a quick cease-and-desist letters
How long time on your show about it
It seems like a waste of time for a very important talk show
These people lived
So Alex talk
Facts about UNESCO
Because there's talk that bush
She's going to re-enter UNESCO
And
This is something that is very bad
Because according to
Alex globalist
Airplane is to destroy the family
He read the paragraph twice and one thing that I would really weird as if you go and actually find this Newsmax article
At the end it says judeo-christians
Civilization
Props off of judeo
I don't know if he's reading like a different version of it or if that's intentional
Why I've no idea
Yeah maybe he just doesn't
Could be
He's been trampling about this plan that UNESCO has to
To destroy the family to destroy civilization
I guess he's deciding to
Discovery by reading an op-ed in Newsmax
I think that's a good way
But honestly read like a f****** parody
Take this ridiculous run-on sentence France
Catch My Breath
Most of my quote
Most Americans are blissfully ignorant of the Insidious nature of this
Crowd of oneworld paganistic pseudo communist and real ones who are bound and determined to create a new world order
Establish new world religion
Capri worshippers that supplanted score
Christianity and Judaism
Promote abortion worldwide's capture control of the schools and school children
And is in the process of transforming National and privately owned property in the United States and elsewhere and do his greedy hands
I didn't want to hear Ted f****** Nugent on this show anymore break in that sentence
VRBO Zazzle
Tree worshipers freeware
And the basis for this according to this op is a publication called toward World understand
Switch to go put out in 1949
Actually
It's not referring to that publication
He's referring to an op-ed in The New American
Talked about that publication
These people are so easy
So here's the quote that Newsmax article attributes
The publication
Government schools must Stamp Out the love of country in the family and the family must be viewed as the enemy
As long as the child breathes The Poisoned arrows nationalism
Education in world mindedness
Can produce only rather precarious result
As we pointed out it is frequently the family that
Text the child.
Extreme nationalism
The school should therefore use the memes described earlier to combat family attitudes that favor jingoism
The sentence quote
But government schools must Stamp Out love of country and the family would be viewed as an enemy
Is it from the UNESCO text
That's really surprising yeah that really a surprise that's the interpretation of the guy who wrote the original article
In the new American which is being quoted in this Newsmax article
Call Alex
Constantly says that UNESCO admits that
The family is their enemy
When that ambition is really just an accusation from a right-wing rag
This is not a single publication form ionesco it's actually part of a 10-part series which
Shark textbook
Looks like many blogs
That incorrectly claimed
Alex incorrectly claimed their founding
Cheese and ridiculous
I found it for years prior
But these are reports of meetings where various perspectives were given by various speakers on issues related
Education
You can find the full text of this volume the other two comes from this is volume
M5 Come Away with a slightly different
Incentive what it's about
Just broadly speaking the point of the text is that
Essential part of healthy development
For children and adults
Is feeling like you belong
As you progress through life the size of the group you belong to grows along with you
Initially it's your family than Maybe
Some friends in the neighborhood then it's your class
It's cool then maybe your city your state and Nation
And eventually ideally the world
This document is about public education so it's basically a discussion of how to promote this healthy process of seeing the world as something you
You're a part of
Along with everyone else
The issue is that a lot of this is an emotional process and it relies on experiences
So for students being exposed to
The sensitivity humanizing representations of people from other cultures
Is critical
Also they recommend having an exchange with a family who has a kid
If the same age in another country still a bond can be formed with people from another culture which Williams
Still Into You
The knowledge
The stereotypes and Prejudice is someone they have
About foreigners
Aren't real
The educators are employed to focus on
Some deep meaningful ways that we are the same as opposed to
The more external a trivial ways that weird if
That said I will admit that this document is very much a
National is
And I can't imagine why someone who did not have a great impression of nationalism in 1949
I mean
Impossible to imagine
So you have a couple world wars
Driven almost in
Tireli by jingoistic propagandist nationalist
And all the sudden you think nationalism is bad
If you not saying the Pledge of Allegiance in class
So weird
Read the thing they spell out what they're talking about
Education for World mindedness of President Carter's obstacles outside the school
The principal one certainly is National
A feeling of belonging to the human Community Development normally buy an extension of the feeling of belonging
Navigate to the National community
It cannot possibly develop from
Caricature of patriotism
Which is extremely National
Nationalism in the sense of caring about your country and seeing yourself as a part of it that's an essential step towards seeing yourself as part
Art of the world community
To the writer this report is in no way suggesting that Nation should be destroyed
Conversely the real point being made is that
Extreme nationalism is a perversion of patriotism
Where everything that involves heater is good
And everything involving other countries is suspicious at that
Also this is just a report of a seminar any introduction literally says quote
The views expressed are of course not the views of the official views of UNESCO
Nor are they necessarily acceptable to all members of the group
It is hoped however that they will arouse interest and stimulate discussion among teachers
In many con
So
The little bit on
Unfair this interpretation that they're admitting that they want to destroy your family
One of those guys
To like a baseball game in 2021 and watch the planes
Flyover the evil jet planes in
Just be like hey buddy
You did it
So here's what happened with this UNESCO doctor
This report on a seminar was published in 1949 and no one really cared
Except people deep in the weeds in terms of Education
Then in October 1950 William Henry McFarland wrote about it in a newsletter from his group
The Nationalist Action League
I'm at the Outreach.
Dr. Graves
Previous to this
Actually I kind of miss Pokey
The name was changed from the National Action nationalist Action League
Something else
Before this public
Previously the Nationalist Action League now
It ends up being the America
Can flag committee
We got real close to Nazi there so now we're American flag not suggest previous
To this publication
I had to do with the UNESCO thing
Self-published series of newsletters called National progress
Antboy it's bad
I was reading over the first issue from September 1945 and it's about what you'd expect
For the first bit of it
It's laying out an aggressively anti-communist position for the newsletter and it's all pretty standard
Until you get to plank
Four of their suggestions of how to
Fix the country
Bring Hitler back to life
A real and Lasting solution of the whole racial problem in America
Stephon justice4all
Concern it must be understood the two races each possessing a
Print set of morals and ethics or a different culture not going to cannot be forced to exist
Together as equals
Sister travel we believe that the Jewish race can never become part of the Christian culture
We know that a Christian America will never accept Judaism
Those who fail to see the choice which must be made are active-active to complicate matters
For sure
Peddler
Look hello this is an illusion that they suggest is quoted the immediate deportation of all aliens
And I'm guessing that is
Definition of determine
Pretty bra I would probably
So this National progress was put out by the Nationalist
Created this new organization the American flag
Committee which was based on an outrage over an incident that in Philadelphia where un flag was raised during a
He began Distributing American flag seals which was most likely just a good PR
An informant told the FBI that the American flag committee with quote
It was just quote a sub body of the Nationalist Action League
And the goal was to gain national attention with the American flag seals
In essence McFarland was doing
What a lot of the current a fascist they're doing with the antimatter
Is the exploitation of a wedge issue that you can use to drive people unknowingly closer to extremist
Members of the American flag committee received a monthly newsletter just titled
The newsletter
In Issue 13 of the newsletter McFarland to did a misleading article about the
Does UNESCO document
And from that point it's spread around Tavares extreme nationalist community
It's the circle of the rides 1951 Republican Congress
My birth name John T wood
Who read that not the actual UNESCO document
But the coverage of it from the American
Can flight committee
Into the Congressional Record
Right
That's right that's really the spread the word a bit further about this conspiracy and the rest as you say is it just a game of
Telephone
People don't respond to actual things in the UNESCO report most likely because they've never actually seen the report
We've only heard about it through the sources that have filtered down for this anti-semitic f*** wad William Henry McFarland
Alex hasn't Reddit he's justina's Newsmax article
The Newsmax article doesn't cite the actual document it cites a different right-wing publication
Speak on it
The very same player between used to drum up
Beard extreme nationalist
Since the days of McFarland
The same person who I should remind you
Who wants to deport all night
People from the inside
I bet MacArthur I cannot so idea who these guys
I bet Joseph McCarthy was like
These guys are so crazy though I never would ever know I will see if there's a pretty positive
References to McCarthy
I will I think that it's
Fortunate in some ways that the FBI was keeping an eye on this guy's committees
Because
Now the newsletters are on the FBI's website
This is this is one of the other reasons that all the
Who's letters are there
Not because the FBI sought them out
Because McFarland sent a copy of all of them to the FBI
I will serve as a way of being like
Taunting Mike I want you to be aware of what
I'm going to leave little Clues
Also he was in his mid-twenties
At this point
So he has a a bit of a
Quintessa Levi
You know the problem with fascist
Very on creative
But enterprising when young
Yeah I mean like if you think about it in the like mid
40s
Putting out in
Like a newsletter did you distribute
Calling it newsletter there is a lot of competition
A lot of undertaking that needs to be done a lot of work
To commit to that is
You know I mean obviously I think what he did is s***
And I think it's nap
It's obviously you can see the Ripple even
Breed of this deer baiting about UNESCO
A.m.
TripAdvisor
At the same time if you just look at how much you have to do it
It's kind of impressive
Just from like
You know ethically neutral standpoint
Do you know he really put his stamp on the destruction
End of democracy
You got to give somebody credit whenever they really leave their name in the history books as destroying democ
Is completely forgotten their influences just Insidious
And the other thing is really fun
Just because I read a lot of it
It's a why not share some details
He accepted payment
The
The publication
Descriptions of South
Yeah it only through money orders
But
If you are going to buy a single-issue you could pay with stamps
Now he didn't accept the money because I guess we'll get lost
In the mail or something
Accept personal checks
Sure because
And this is spelled out in a very long story and it seems like
I believe he's not short-winded on this front
He did not have an account
At the bank
That allowed him to cash these checks
Because there's a cop size was too small
Like a backwood
Like in case
The check wasn't a good check they were willing to front him that money until the check cleared
Ain't so he ended up having to
To find a friend with a better Bank
Account like cash the check for him
The process has I will agree with him on that front
Okay
Who is the original Bitcoin bro is what you're saying
So I guess God blockchain man I was really interested diving in and seeing where this
Conspiracy came from
It's not always as
Kind of the roots are always
As to the traceable
Source material is perverted initially Friday
Goes ganoe
Add b2c to be eventually all the way down the line
The new new American
Has been covered by Newsmax which has been covered by Ali
It's just a name they just know that
The game
You know they're just really good at
The game haha they're not good at
Helping
Or doing anything but
The game that's f*****
It's earlier in the episode here's another little
Clip of Alex talking about this UNESCO
Not saying just because
He's got everything wrong
Organization
So that's that's his angle on it it's it
Their founding documents
Destroying the part about the family being the enemy and needed to be
Is from The New American article
Sort of
Manipulative Lee quoted in the Newsmax article and Alec
I guess I mean if he's not curious about it
And just takes that Newsmax article as gospel
Must think that that comes from the UNESCO documents
Actually doesn't use boxes f****** Breaking Bad
Car wash
Just just like we are we got all these lies I don't know what to do with them
Launder
So now we get to Dan in Illinois
I got an interesting Theory
What are you doing what you doing
There's only two SWAT
You think that
North Korea
Is a decoy
Like there's not going to be a war there any people in Northridge resources to exploit
To Alex
Kind of goes off
Ben price to stay on point but Alex isn't allowing
North Korea
That leader whatever his name is is
Alarm
Or what about
They don't have any resource
They don't have anything
Take a note
Concrete over whatever he's not going to
In the meantime
North Korea
What
The resource
World
That's not true
Again is trying to respond to a different point than what the color is bringing up
And this one I think is a little moron
Clear to me
Because I do think that it
Possible that Alex misunderstood him
It is responding to what
He thinks this guy is saying
As opposed to being caught in a
Ridiculous situation
Like in the previous
Dave show
Do you know one was on the
This could just be Alex not paying attention really
Yeah I can see this one just being like North Korea's probably got enough money to kill us all
I am Alex's turn today
Story about North Korea being one of the largest
Opium
Acro results
Just something that he can say
Just toss it out there
It's not a good rebuttal to this guy
It is
Anyway I'll tell the gas
Here's a couple guest on this episode
One of them is this singer-songwriter named Michelle shocked
Okay I'm not going to any of her interview because
Pointless
Cienega
I don't know
You didn't you didn't
Volume up on her.
Her singing career no Dan I expect you to do research dude I did look into who she was
And
Yeah I don't I don't know it's me a bad vibe
I mean I think a singer-songwriter on Infowars does have a very poor tracker
Crackers
Some controversies that popped up about her
Sing
Something
Like jokes about all the singer-songwriters who are nominated in a particular category Saturday
We could have called this the lesbian vocal are it is
Or something and then later on
She like got really mad
Cuz you was asked
About her take on homosexuality I got like a
I think was a Christian concert
And she's like I don't know why everyone asked me this. You're looking at the biggest homophobe in the world
But I don't know why
That's fair I don't know if that was just
Curbing
Fed up with people asking her that kind of quest
Hey
Throwing up
I didn't care
I I think that you probably just sucks
You're on Alex's show you not great another Gaston
Who's not gray
And that is
The lawyer who is representing Jane Roe
And now the woman known as Roe
Has
Because he was playing
And wants to reverse
Joining us
Like me
And weave
With the organization not here in Texas
Ring
So it's very clear from this interview if you live
Listen to it that this person is
A lawyer
The point
Abortion
But they're mainly Nancy porush
Represent
And work with
Primarily anti-abortion causes
Promoting
Somebody's got to do it
So this is really funny
The lawyer is trying to give some background on the case okay and Mike down for this
Because you will be tempted to talk about this
Learned of the ruling at the
Supreme Court
Morning News
Alex
Okay
Just got up and got away from the mic
I am going to let her cook for a little bit I'm going to get out of here
Take a little nap
Consistent
His career respect for his guests
They would be in
Studio
Run away from the belt
Yeah so Alex
Has a
Real lot of horrible things he says about divorce
Business interview
And the section
I will
Say that it's suspicious
Bad
He's
Not talkin about his own experience
He's paid for it this time
That does not seem something like something that he is willing to discuss publicly at this time
Feels like that's an important
Background
This kind of interview
He does seem to talk about
A lot of
Feelings he has about people who do
Oh yeah
He feels like they deserve
Thing about his
Right now I don't deserve
Course because
I'm better now
Right now obviously if we were to reply retroactive
Then yes I would be in trouble in the same way but since we are going to say I'm Scott free
Also he seems to have a position that
Abortions are never okay in the case of
Protecting a woman's life
Because
If you do it
Every but you go in and kill
Disgusting
Yeah
That's that's always been such a b******* like okay fine give me an exact list of when doctors are allowed
And not allowed
By God
Okay just give me
Give me a Hardline okay if you if you
You're going to get an abortion
God will do it for you
Alright God takes care of all of that
What if say you've got a broken leg
Is God going to heal your broken leg or is it okay for a doctor to heal your broken leg.
List
Of what God can and cannot do all medicine must be suspect I guess I'm recording to this kind of thing
F*** off
Yeah and then also just the idea that it's creating a bunch of broken people
This is just a
Defensive yeah I mean I'm sure that it's not been something that people have done for
The entirety
Well I mean I can't imagine
What the emotional toll would be of being forced
By the state
To carry a pregnancy to
Alex happy
But it
But I mean the person would probably
Have a lot of emotional impact
Of the person is not important
God is important
And how Alex Alex's thoughts
It's about God
Not even God for say
So this is this is one of the only things I found
Really interesting about this interview with the lawyer
All because I mean
Case didn't go anywhere and it's
Stupid
But she does have a website that you
He's promoting
Alex in a real pickle
Makeup app
Supreme Court
Is as
Case that we
President Bush
In his campaign
Hayward
Promote
Call Trav life
There is a project
Project
If you go to
Eww
F2a
2A
Project ROSE.
Sending roses
A present
For $10
President Bush with an F
Hoarding his decision
America culture of life
Justices
LaRosa's
Allison Morales
So now Alex is in an unenviable position of having to support the guy who did 9/11
Because he might appoint Supreme Court Justices that end abortion
Okay so he did 9/11
It might end abortion
That's good
I'm in a real
Call here
And I have to send roses that might be the deciding factor I don't
F*** you discomfort Alex having someone saying positive things about bush
And I
I can hear the discomfort he has with somebody giving money to somebody not him truth
So they take calls
Valerian Alex
Get this
What
We can shut the book on the devil question
Oh okay good it's literally spelled out in this town
I don't think men in and of themselves
Orchestrate
Made
Himself is the one that's actually
The genius behind
Find it all
Yep so Alec
Does believe that there is a literal devil in the devil is actually even
Definitely saying
The devil is behind the global genius behind the global level plans are too evil for people
What's there to evil and so it must be Beelzebub
Obviously the greatest trick the devil ever pulled was
Convincing people he wasn't real now we have moral relativism
Sympathy how quickly it happened
Dangerous when did he do that
7018 like when I would like to know the day
October
Gregorian calendar
For a long time listening to these 2000's believe 18 years ago that he was
Fighting the literal devil
He does
But he doesn't talk about it nearly as much
It's very clear the present-day but E's a little bit more careful about it
Turn to talk about the devil as much
Now that you're on the Downey
I think that's probably also the case with him talking about his
Experienced personally with a abortion
Twice or whatever until after I was already politically expedient for him to do some yeah this point his career
Take a major blow if he was to say I
Paid for 10 of borscht
Do this Alex guys all anti-abortion but he just said that he paid for 10 Fortune
You didn't have the position in
I like his
Fearnow community
To be able to
Have that adjustify
You would have he would have been
Looked looked at a certain way
And an Evangelical communities there's absolutely
It's not a hard
Time limit
A year after you pay for an abortion
You have not
Repented enough
Ten Years After you paid for plenty of them it's like hey
Yeah he's a changed man it's
Completely different
It's totally fine
What also the repentance
At this point in his career would probably require some humility
It would probably require him to
Like except
That
That you know he's not the Arbiter of all these
Ferrara
But now he's a star
And so is his
Does not really required
Frame to be humble literally star they let you do whatever you
Aw this case to go real
It's going to take awhile to get pretty mad about that or at least frustrated
And then this weaves nicely into a little bit of transphobia
Millions more
We have to wait
Federal District Court
Megan
Sometimes these things just move very very swiftly and other times they get bogged down
Well
Good to see that Alex's pretty early on that train
Great job
Do we have one last
Like I said
Bizarre
Alex
Is not
Talking about his own
Involvement
In abortion
Because it's hyper relevant to the conversation that's being hat
You think
That
Someone
Having abortions
Paying for an abortion
There's not anything to be ashamed of
I don't think there's anything wrong with it
But Alex does
In that community
Alex does
Something wrong with the ultimate Evil of murdering children
Right
But you can also be
You forgiven
Corsican this clip
Really feels like Alec
Talking to himself
Because we know what we know from things that he talks about later but is not talking about
At this point
You try to rationalize
Women keep it legal
The murder of other children
So he's saying this like you can be
He's talking about himself himself
That he can be forgiven
And I think that this
Is
An unfair way for him to discuss this
When he's holding back that
Information everyone else who does this now is evil
Forever
And they're working for the devil
And should be punished
Obviously
From prior to this moment when I did it
If you were still able to be forgiven for it is grandfathered in
To the whole
Let's punish everybody for the crime of murdering babies
I think if there's such a such a weird
Circle line with this
A lot of it comes down to I don't think the people
Should be required
To disclose
Things that are person
You know like if
Someone did have an abortion or something
I don't think that it's anybody's business that that they don't want it to be there busy
It's it's personal
That said Alex is engaging in a conversation
That
Applies to himself
Deeply
About a political issue that he's trying to do
Prive
People of being able to access abortion
Oh it does
In this case it does
Feel like
He has an obligation
To denote
In the same way when he talks
It's about like
Is Big Berkey water filters
And stuff he has a responsibilities at their response
You know like
I was thinking the same thing I was just going like this
It reminds me so much of
Despondent
You know like there's such a huge conflict of interest are emotional conflict of interest for him
I mean such that it is
It's just
F***** up
Women chest really f*****
You listen that last clip
And it does really feel like you talk
Talking to himself
M2d
Like this
This conversation
Is actually a psychodrama of his own
Trying to deal with his own past Route that's being projected as political
Principal or advice to the audience
That is unfair
That is a conflict of
And I think
I think that it's
Unethical
But then again it does come up against the principles
Should be forced to
Disclose
Biggest I don't know if you know it's a mess but I do know that as a radio show this is
To it to the extent that you are influencing
You got it you got to disclose that s***
You got it
Because
If your if this is who you are then that's the context
With which I'm going to understand what you're saying
And maybe if this personal experience that you have is really a major portion of what
What's driving
Your position
And this emotional plea that you're making to the audience
Service of trying to change law
Yeah it does feel like it
It's super relevant
I understand
The reasoning behind.
Talking about it
Couldn't get away with it back.
I mean it's just the thing that follows obviously is
You know
He's leaving out that if you're getting one
Now you can be forgiven
It's very conveniently in the past if you got it abortion you can be forgiven right no point in time is he saying that
In in the contactor
In the context of discussing abortion in the presence of evil
Violet
Right
Government
In the U position of the past
You can be forgiven there's no worries there's nothing
In the present you should be
Be killed for getting an abortion
So I end this on a pretty good
Obviously disgusted but also
Conflicted position
About this whole
I do think it's very interesting the way that Alex
Refuses to talk about his own experience when he does later
I think that's
Bedrooms of this episode
I really think that the most important takeaway
Is that
Nobody was on the 9/11 plane
Right I think that what happened in that occur
Exchange
Is so relevant
The understanding
The way Alex
Deals with
People who disagree with him
Or our threat
Coming to his ideas
And also it's such a good
Demonstration of why talking to him is a waste of time
For pretty much any
Yeah I mean and it's it's another Power Dynamic to that occur
Exact same
Scituate you know when you talk about the way that
Bill Ayers talk to him up just like
The same kind of functional
Just stay on topic just stay on top
Buddy just stay on topic but
Because billares is a name
Then Alex has to engage with that to some extent he can't just
Scream over you
Gaslight you directly while while
Scolding you
Daring to ask
Ask him those questions
In this power imbalance
He just gets to yell at you and say you're stupid you're talking about something else soon as you're gone he can go back to
Listening to me you're not listening to me you or not leaking no I didn't say that there were no but there's nobody on board
Until we hang up and then I'm
Suggest it again
I think that's no just awful and
But he does all the time
Anyway Jordan we will be back on Wednesday indeed but until then we have website
Yes we are also on
Twitter we are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fighting that go to bed
But until then
Amelia Hundley alarm dzx clark I'm Daryl run diss
I'm Dan Illinois
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work