I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Acknowledge little bit about Alex Jones
God.
Dot-dot-dot
Nodded my head but I refuse to clap you were following the beat
Cannot follow the beat bad
I have a question
What's up Jordan do we have the meats
Exactly are you asked me about my bright spot
Performing something about a meat
So I was taking a trip
Do this at this last weekend
Visiting a friend in DC we decided
To get
Some Burmese food for dinner
Okay and I was looking at the menu where your order it
And there's something there was a beef
I stood with Chili's all day
No no okay that was stew
Okay
And so I decided to
Get that and
My friend was ordering it
And I could hear on the other end of the
The phone to the guy taking the order
Going
It was a ridiculous tell me laugh like he's
That's our joke menu item I got your billy ated
And I thought everything was going to be fine but hey man
Man
Hot
Yeah I deserve to get laughed at but I'm up on the wall of a tire
Hi restaurant you know
I've had to I've had some adventures in spice
Yeah you got
I think I think
Maybe I'm getting old
I think it happen
Maybe I can't handle it but it also felt like
Get them that Harper
No not really but I got like overwhelmed
I got like
Sweat
It was a it was a full body experience
We are the trip was nice
I got back
And here we are that's awesome it was great
Goodtime all-in-all no bright spot but also that glass that
Over the phone
That's too good
I cherish cherish that moment took my life
He was right that is okay
Also pretty fun it is nice whenever people are confidently mocking you and then they win
The Thai place that I go to that will give you the are you sure
And usually it's okay I can handle it
But not the
Actually honestly kind of think that if it was chicken
I could have been okay
Because that they keep profile was very strong
But there was something about it being a beef and have to chew it a little bit more it's a little bit more
Gaming
I don't know you were real
Guy anyway
I'm generally not I don't need all that I'll do more of a poultry purse
Yeah
Bright spot then is
Laugh your ass off
That would be great if everytime I hear a laugh it just
It's funnel through light-years asgore by
There's only one lap
My bright spot dead is azure if you recall
Back in the day
When I went to see Shelly Otani
They stole my bag
Cuz it wasn't either
So then I got a backpack
Cuz I am a messenger bag guy all the way yeah yeah yeah
Awful
Sitting right my partner
Found me the ultimate messenger bag
It's got a
Bartholin s*** for the the thing it's amazing it fits all kinds of stuff
It's ladies night you know I love a good hidden Pocket
Only thing better than a hidden Pocket on a bag is a hidden pocket in your coat
Love those those
Interior pockets
Something dramatic Lee there
Proof
I'm going to whip it out
Why do I have this manila envelope
You know why
Hahaha
The bag is absolutely fantastic
She thought about a gift for me
I'm notoriously terrible to buy gif
Sure cuz I'm not really I don't really eat that stuff
You know when you're in a position where you're struggling
With his backpack it lends itself to a gift and it was it was a maze
I'm happy for you cuz I was getting to be calling you back back
We're back
Back from the little break
Something a little bit different
Off the beaten path made out of thing that's becoming something we may do a little bit more of Anything Goes On
It has it has its
It's not always
The easiest thing to get people
Who would want
To talk
Ownership
Are not something we do very often but we get in touch with Mike Rothschild
Is that somebody's been following qanon industry for a long time
He has a book out called the storm is upon us right about the roots of qanon
Conversation with him about
Some of the bookend
Some of the intersections with the Alex Jones World speaking of which it's very funny that even if
The book world that we live in
He has to put in parentheses
Every time you put
Is named Mike Rothschild
No relation not every time but it is
With him it now is going to sound like we're hyper-focused on there
Tacit
So we'll get to that interview here in a moment
But before we do Jordan
Let's say hello to some new walk worshipper of Celine thank you so much
The boys that raped my creepy ceiling., thank you so much you're now a policy
I worry what I just gave a shout-out please
If that becomes the new Facebook we're in real trouble that will destroy democracy
Next cam journal policy
I'm a policy wonk next to James
Wally the goodest boy thank you so much
I'm a policy to say hello to
2021 Alex Jones with the super fake 2003 radio voice is unbelievably worse
Thank you so much you are now attacking
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
See ya without further Ado I say we jump into this interview
Last time we had an interview at that fun like
Little bit that's true
That's true that's true this is less of a
Let's take you to a fantasy world where we're interfering
Exactly it is more like welcome to us interviewing a
Yeah
So here we are here we go
I enjoying will see you on Friday
Well hello joining us today very very excited we're we're drifting into interviews Jordan
This is weird we're doing two very short we've done how many episodes well over 600
We have two full interviews now yeah but opportunities of pop-up and lend themselves
Do productive conversations that are not that are interesting to the the world that we look at
Nobody ever wanted to talk to us
That is true that was a long stretch of time where
Who are they
I we got a lot of wine
Model y
What a personal trends
Joining us today very excited to have Mike Rothschild on the show there's a new book
Videos out called the storm is upon us
That was a long
Subtitle
Storm storm
Subscribe to The Alex Jones School of just reading headlines
Thank you thank you for joining us
Call thanks Robin
I'm really excited
To be here I think the elephant in the room of course is that you were very
Insisting
In the book
Okay that you're not related to the Rothschild
I am not related to the Rothschild
I drive a 2004 Toyota Corolla
Microwave
Platinum
No no there are
People with the same last name not related
Do each other at shock I know but nobody
NFL running back priest Holmes look
Just like you
You get accusations about that a lot
The like I noticed in the book there was at least a time there's parenthetically no relation to the author
I just have to assume with the world that you cover with you and I
Conspiracy
Stop people with
Make that connection and probably be mad
Yeah people
People think that I'm acting as some sort of like
Hype man for the family
You know
They're like
Chuck D
And I'm like Flavor Flav and I've got my clock
Yelling like
Like we do
Defensive like map
Yeah it's like it's like a
Braces PR hype man
Kerbals was a hype man you know I like yeah yeah
Very flashy
Swastika-shaped made it hard to tell time
But this is the thing that you find with a lot of
Old-money families is that they don't address this stuff at all
Like they don't
They don't talk
Like there's no
Members of the Rothschild family
Going on the record and talking about this something they don't talk about
They
He doesn't exist
For that day today
They just live their lives because they know that anything that they throw in
The fire is just going to be used as proof that it's all true
You can't prove that you're not some
Don't talk about it
You know you got that a lot with these
Older money
Family
He's going to pass down a lot of wealth
The subjective rumors
There's nothing to say
Yeah there's no winning in coming out and being like
Not true
It's like the you know proving you're not a witch by
Brown rice
That's exactly
I would say they could come out and say
Peasants we give no fux about you that would also count
So you wrote This Book
About qanon
And I was curious about like
How much of this was it was
Like the result of like a passion
Or did you set out
As a project
Who's this was this something you were interested in
Before
You were getting in the book were you following it
Like
Organically as it was happening
I've been writing about
Conspiracy theories for
Most of it just
No money
I mean obviously
But I've been
Interested in the subject
I really got into the whole idea
Conspiracy
Storytelling
Through coasttocoastam
I used to listen to it to Art Bell a lot and I never believed any of
So
Outside of my own
Middle class
Suburban existence
It's talking about UFOs in the Illuminati
Error code
Well yeah
But you just can't talk about
That's true
So this was
I was really into this as
Is a form of Storytelling
And so a I could have drifted into it more and more professionally
And so I
I wrote I had an opportunity right my first book with
Which came out
But long before that I'd started to
Look at qanon
The first
My first inkling of
Sing something
There was beginning of 28
First drops came out
And I started seeing tweets about
John McCain and Hillary Clinton
Wearing orthopedic
Walking boots
Not because things like hurt their feet like
The rest of us peasants
But because they were wearing ankle brace
Because they've been arrested
In a purge of the storm
All this is awesome I I got it I got to dive into this and see where it where the
What do you think this is true what else is true
This
They're not like slacker
You can't wait to hollow out a walking
A better monitor bracelet and its
Leopard print I've always liked that the most
Filmed people on Earth need ankle bracelets
Well that's
But I started to get a little more concerned about it when I started to see the parallels
Qanon
Today's previous
The araki
Donarski had them before that in the sorrow
Before that the Omega Trust scam and use some of these things
I've been running since the early 90s
And have
Built a lot of people out of a lot of money
Using the same kind of stutter
This sort of
All-knowing Guru who has access to secret Intel
They will Dole out to a select
You people
Who are the special chosen ones will know what to do when the
Kuwait change event happens
And it's always about to happen and there's always some dark force that
Gets in the way Justice
Everything's about
How to change
It's Suites
You not such a coincidence that happens
I don't talk to Everyday every time it's always like just about to happen
And with the
Dinar scam I mean the level of minutiae.
When injured
Synonymous gurus
Eyewitness
Wolfie mad
Scam artist
Kansas City
Also have like
Egret
Access to the
Inner workings of the araki
Foreign Ministry
Read the read the dinar revalue has already been announced in the mosque
Standby to get her to get your secret 1-800 number to
Call Inwood
You'll be told where to
Code words
Rest stop
Adidas
Tell anybody where you
Going in Spring your Dinars in a
Battle
Quesadilla in a faraday cage music
Conspiracy theories
Do you guys know that
The more
Arcade
Detail
Load onto something
The more believable at the
Getting more big something is the less real
Yeah cuz I think people have just sort of the way of
Being tricked by specificity
Do you know you don't think
Bit someone
Would make up all of these
Yeah and I think another element to is like when you have all those details and all of these weird
Steps that you need to take
It's if you get
Trick by one you really don't want to admit you got trick
Buy that one
Go for the 2nd of 3rd
4th step it becomes much easier to rationalize
Done
You're not done being blackmail there's always going to be more that you're supposed to do you know
Right there's always another step is always another
Bit of manusina one of my favorite details with the Omega
Precursor going to sorrow which was this
Griffis longtime grifter
Promise that he had access to
Prime European
Banknotes
Said only five people in the world knew about
This dude
Plumber in Mattoon Illinois
I mean really
Mattoon Illinois and that is where they keep those Secret banknotes
Batshit
Bite my favorite detail that was that the
The cash that you
You sent in
To buy your Omega units
How to be wrapped in
Tin foil
Sure I know why
But those Rays getting an inline currency
But it's 82
Details that make something
You seem real
Yeah because otherwise why would you do that
Admire the
These people
Yeah that's why they call them, there's a reason just such I don't know how
I mean like I don't even know how I would
Be able to tell you that I know secret European note
Let alone your ear sore
Circle.of
Church Coronavirus
Making phone calls
To get more people to invest in
Now I got to do that as the story of America though like it was literally founded upon Colton Khan
Tire country has been built out of people
Bullshiting other people for money
Memphis intertwining
The Puritans were very capital
And the the aspirational model I think it's something that
It'll really works with those kinds of ponds and works all the way going up the trunk
I mean so much
Jobs
Appeal
Was
I'm going to make you dislike me we've got the bigger boats we've got the nicer
I mean you're talking to coal miners
In like
Rural Pennsylvania
Like we're talking about boats
Penthouse apartment overlooking Central Park
Again really
Depressing thought I never really put it there put it that way in my head of like dropping like I will make you like me
Let me know when you look at the social Mobility numbers through class system
And you you realize that nobody from the lower classes even moving up
To the middle class
There's no greater, than the American dream talking build whatever you want and become rich
I really liked your your rebuttal in the book
For the Dinar revaluation thing where it was just
This is not how this works
This would never happen
Fundamentally mistaken this would destroy all money in the world
And you and that's a really
It's a really useful way to look at
It's something that seems really complex like the dinar like you and I
To break it down into the simple idea of
That's not how this works this
This is not
How things happen
Money does not
Simply
You're like that
You can't just
Become
A billionaire
Overnight
With the stroke of a pen
And I've all your friends be billionaires and have money have any value
Yeah yeah then you have the dollar is the new dinner
Here's end up circular
I think that that is helpful unless you already believe all this
I think it's still not penetrated
Yeah
No it's not it's it's been
And you start to fall back on what that's what they want you
Think that you do
They don't know what we know we have
Secret knowledge
They don't know they're asleep it's that feeling of specialness
But you got
When you are consuming conspiracy media
And it's being reflected back to you up
I know
I-know-something-you-don't-know
Ultimately if your respond with like when you boil down that DNR scam
Your response
Like at the most Elemental level is just
No
You know you want to be like a hen with a newspaper
Are you can't
What are the things that I think is is really interesting about framing qanon that way or looking at it from that perspective
Tutus like
It doesn't appear to be similar necessarily in the same way as those
Those are like
Very
Clearly I want money
Kind of skiing Torres I think
Externally
You view qanon as like wow this is
Ideas or
It doesn't seem as much of like a money machine
Right and that was what was really trouble
Something like
Nosara the dinar
There's the financial
Most people kind of Savvy enough
To know that
You can't buy a million Dinars and somebody signed a piece of paper in your Milly
Like most people know that that's
But what
You was selling wasn't
That you're going to get rich
It was
You're going to feel awesome
When did Hillary Clinton and John podesta
Get the short
Drop from the Rope at Guantanamo Bay
Good feeling better was selling
The idea that
These people that they've hated for
Decades
Finally going
Get what's coming
So it is it is absolutely no surprise
Host by
Like you was
Hillary Clinton
Is on the Run
She's going to be extradited
There's going to be riots
The National Guard's going to come out into the streets
Everything that you wanted is going to have
Yeah I think I think it'll be good so it's
I don't know if people
Recognized
In those communities
Conspiracy and right-wing communities in particular like
Hillary Clinton's like catnip
It like
If you want to pitch something kind of silly attaching her to it is
Over and over again through two years & years on Alex's show
Like Larry Nichols was able to create a cottage industry for himself
Coming up with nonsense but thing I
Hillary
Yeah I mean the movie Hitch the moment they successfully got everybody to tithe
The Foster murder to the clintons no matter what
Like
It doesn't matter if you believe it or not believe it you know
But they are
Associated with the Vince Foster murder
Then you can just make up any
Yeah that I was actually I was listening to an old Art Bell open lines Show from
I think like Miller Lite 90-95
One of the things that he was talking about was that having a handwriting analyst
Take a look at the Vince Foster suicide
Was
Going to be a little bit more skeptical that a lot of
The modern computer
Blaming stuff on the clintons I mean this is a mid-90s and it's still
Happening
Yeah
You brought up but you brought a blackened Coast
Costa Coast am quite a bit you just
Brought back up our belts and I have to ask
Do you not like a George Noory as much as I don't like it I do not like George Noory at all
Guy sucks
It's a different kind of show and it's not his
Spawn
Yeah it's not as like
We're going to figure this out
Together and
That was skeptical I mean that's one of the things about his shows that have something called in and had some
Cockamamie story like
He wasn't all that totally happened I believe that completely
He would actually sort of
Talk about this
I try to tease out
Is this pause
The guy was also a prank
He was in the least
Sort of a selective crank
If that's a thing
Kiki easy but have less of like an agenda then like George Noory is definitely like he has
Ideas
Tarbell was like
He was the one who had Courtney
Brown on
But they were talking about the
Spaceship behind Hale-Bopp
You f***** up
A bit
Yam
George Noory way worse
We can all agree on that and I'm glad
What other radio hosts do you hate go ahead and get me a list
All of the all of the feeling hosts on Coast to Coast
Sucks
Very granular
Actually that's it that's enough that's an interesting connection to
George Noory on his show
I'll actually his head Steve pieczenik
As a guest
Number of times and I know that this is something that we've sort of
Messaged a little bit about about
Assassinated to understand
What kind of an interaction
You someone who studies qanon would think
Of him
Of doctor Steve
Pieczenik
Supersonic is one of those guys
Do quasi-military connected Plaza intelligence connected
And it turns that
A Persona where they know everything
And they have all the secrets
And they can see through everything
And they're like the most
Dangerous people in the world
They're the only ones were willing to tell the
Meanwhile
Nothing if you can trust me I've murdered Aldo Moro
Like I I do about the
The slave colonies on Mars it's the most deadly secret in the world
And yet I continue to not be
But you get a lot of those people in that world
Is tenuously Eve military-connected or tenuously
Turn that into a
Persona where they are the Oreck
And there that they're the most dangerous people around me the Bill Cooper
What's the same way
These guys somehow
Have all of the Seeker
Never actually
Put in any kind of danger
A some kind of an accident they ended up
Stumbling onto like
The P I guess that's more just like Bill's mythology but yeah
They can't ever prove but they know for sure and I can't be killed over it because if they get killed then you'll know it
Right
That's why they can't assassinate you
It's a good that's a good explanation
I am
I think that it's
You comparing are you bringing up like Robert David Steele and Steve pieczenik
I can sort of the same
Area is is is
Is relevant
Except
I don't know it would
Do you know if Robert David Steele actually was in the FBI or anything like
He makes a lot of claims where Steve pieczenik was in the states
Apartment Morrow
Yeah it's it's always it's always
It's hard with these guys
Is there such
Bullshitters Eli so much
All the time
That you you kind never
Quite know where you are so you just have to
Their claims
As they, rather than serve do that
Deep dive into the
Shorts because so much of it is just so
Murky
Thoughts around their own mythology
So it's
Never quite as satisfying to try to dig in and
These people really are
In terms of the the
Qanon
Post in the lake
Not coming directly from the Cadre of
Potential
Accused
Are people just made you feel if you get the vibe that people are just making stuff up whole cloth
Or are they stealing it from somewhere
It's both
To drop
Curly story
Is told by the
What the storm was originally supposed
You know this Mass arrests
Missed my trunk through Twitter
Marines National Guard called up
That very much seems like something you would read in a Robert Ludlum novel
Co-creator of the op-center
Evening ride
Caucus
You got this order
Tom Clancy ask story being told it does seem
Barrier Ridge
At some point
What story
And then
You just kind of
Kicking the can down the road which is the traditional
And one of the things that you
That really happened
Was that there was a need for more
This became really popular
Soak you needed to just
Put more stuff
So there was a lot of
You got a lot of
Repurpose meme
Grab.
There's a
A fairly early on
Thank you
4 drop
List of rust
Child Central
Again
Not a sting that's not
Thing works
But but it's
Apple Bank in the Federal Reserve
List of Rothschild Central Bank
Floating around
From some Anonymous blog
Somebody else grabbed
All Scrabble
I didn't you grab that I'm somebody else will grab it
You do the same thing happened with the results you drop where q insinuates that
Angela Merkel is the daughter of Adolf Hitler
Sure
They're both in Germany
Purple associated with Germany
Yeah
That came from
The hoax like what
Does it meet
What does it mean
That was mean hold on hold on I got to work. Just continue say wonderful
For the rest of my life
Cuz I know from other reputable sources the Gorge
W bush is also the spawn of Hitler
That would make him and Angela Merkel like cousins second cousins a little weird
You have to
To think that like
Der fuhrer I saved
His semen
And somebody just like
For 10 years
How did that work
I don't know if you could
Bring it out every Christmas is like Silas past was firm around this is Hitler come on everybody
I've seen enough weird stuff on the History Channel that that doesn't strike me as soon as possible
You can't prove it didn't happen
Yeah I have
I have like
Assertive
Fiery
And I don't know whoever like sort of bear out here actually
If there's any Credence to it at all but
We when we were going back and looking at some of the lead-up to the 2016 election
Steve
The track was on Alex's show talking about there being a secret coup
Military people on the inside
I don't I didn't follow Catholic
Fix it already happened
You don't need to worry about already in jail
I never followed qanon closely enough to know how well that matched up but it felt
Very similar
I just felt like there were at least the Matic
Parallels
Distinguish
You isn't it
It's very different from a lot of
Conspiracy theories
People out of power
Where you get those like
The secret counter-coup when does deep State and stuff like that
With you it was we have the power and we're going to use
So that's where that aspirational model comes
We got the power to do this
We just have to wait until all of
All the pieces are in
Everything is perfect
But there can't be any questions like it has to look
Wiggle it has to be completely legit
Either we're going to Roundup
So with
It wasn't like
Because it was already
People who are in power
The question
Two people never asked
Themselves
Are we still on
Yeah
No we're just listening really really intently
That's the first time I've done this in a long time
When we do not interrupt seem like they're frozen
Impatient
Septic by now
DD question that the
The Q people never ask himself is
Why don't we just do it
The president you just do this
He doesn't have to worry about
How it works
He's the president she's lived here he's the God ever cares what the Optics are just grab them
Everyday everyday that you wait
More children are trafficked
More more adrenochrome is drained
Rothschild
Money is moved around
Do it now why you why are you waiting
I think never going to ask
Awesome songs.
Australian summer 2019
Youtube.com
It's the same thing as a chair
Nobody
Wait a minute
Is the military intelligence operations
Saving the world
Did they just take the summer off
Like where the children being trafficked engaged in matter
Using a simple question
These people never ever ask
Why it's as somebody who believes in workers rights
I would say that they should take it with this
Summer somewhere
Probably somewhere cold
What a nice change-of-pace listen
Yeah that is that is one of the interesting disconnect
Text that is the lake well
If this really where would it says to be represented self as
Vape seems incredibly in Coppell
Like what has
What has a sort of happen
And how the messages have gotten out the website
Being
What they are
It's me
Full of child pronography and Mass
Shooter Manifesto is a there's that great moment in the
You Into the Storm
Where are Liz crokin
Is being called
Calling hobak
Yeah there's there's
Child born on a chair
And she's like what
It was fighting fighting the child pornographers liquid child pronography
What kind of face
Like somebody kicked her dog or so
Computing with her house
This place
Yeah I think some of that has to do with like
The
You know the audience of this being a little bit older and maybe people who aren't it's
Familiar with the
The realities of these Message Board sites like some of them
And the character that they have and what goes on there
Yeah and there's there's a reason that BQE Kota
System really revolved around
Is Dee's website
Aggregator
I would post
The drops
After they went up on a generator
Where you didn't have to
Go to the place
Nobody should be
Should probably go there and be like I don't know about this whole thing
You want
People to be involved with
You just don't want them to know
I would actually
Very simple to use aggregator
And that's where you get
That's where you you find your
Decoding Fred
You're like
List of
Resignations and mysterious deaths
So whatever
Yeah you're not going to the store
Everything is getting
That's that's the thing that I was really struck by is like
It wasn't it was almost
Distilling
Less than it was laundering it was like
They took out the
Craziest
Parts that were on H and they put them one step below
And then one step below until the the thing that was
Valuable
Suddenly shows up on Fox News
And then people go from Fox News to the neck
Step back up
To the next step back up until they get more and more extreme
So it was kind of a weird almost
Fluctuation of
Trickle-down bulshit being pushed back
Backup
Yeah
Yeah it's definitely am up here amid where the start of the war stuff is
A chad
Really sloppy Reddit stuff
Awkward using more legitimate right-wing blogs
Social media and it winds up on Infowars that it winds up on like
Gateway pundit
Fox News and Trump tweets
Right back.
It really was a welder
Develop system I don't know that anybody Buy
It's just that says how information blows with
Nothing nothing
And there are no there's no light that your sister
It is all
Suffocating darkness and paranoia and anger.
The great sentence
And I think it's also like it information space were like
It's
Like
Truthfulness neutral
Or whatever it's
Things are things are expedient are useful they're not really
It does not really it's not a hindrance
If something is not
True order
Patently not true
Right and you say Well it's
It's true for me
And that's how the wellness world
Osaka
That's always been a world look like
Well it's if my
Experiences my Jeremiah
It's wrong is true to me
Reality is for
Right exactly
That sucks
A dirigible Corrections darkness that is that is nice distillation of
What a bummer was wondering cuz I was reading through this book and the the
Beginning of
Qanon happens so similarly to
At digest-all call
You know that just like progression of step-by-step process
And I was I was seeing it happen
And now that
Interesting so replicable
Do you know what I mean like there's so many possible nuclear anons if you go
Do any of these different faces people are trying to create that
Phenomenon again do you think that
Possible
You know every one of these things is a little bit
Difference but they're also really similar
You know what one of the
The gulls are really hard with right
In the book was to strip back
Be
The social media she not even on the reveal what the
And the component parts are all
Is all stuffy
It's been floating around
Decade
Centrum
The blood libel
12:00 or whatever it was
There's very little in
You are not at work
Poor people
Can you repurpose
Conspiracy theory
New persona
We saw that
Wishing
Coast
January 6th
Qanon
He can
And taking in a completely different
Directions you.
People like ghosts
Catalpa tree
Score taking the mythology of
Fun
Rebuilding it into something that works for
For them and they can get
Viral Fame and money
Yo everybody
Everybody takes it in their own Direction
And some of it doesn't work in some of it.
And that will
On and on and on
Forever
His people will always be
Be susceptible to being told
What to believe
Being validated and what they think is true
And in being part of a spy
Special secret community
Qanon.pub
The New World Order
Everything else
Alex Jones
That's
That is going to be with us
Now that sucks
This is the part in in like TV or normal radio interviews are where they're like
Oh okay well you told us a lot about this
What do you think our next steps are to stop it
And the previous answer is just
This is here forever
It's because like these are kind of the feelings and thoughts that I have when I when I
You know look at this stuff tonight
And I wrestle with Alex
Primarily
And you know it is
Hard to fight those feelings like well
This is just something with humanity is always going to have to
The deal with it's not it's not something that
I can
Ever be like well we've we've fixed
And it sucks
To the ghetto
Somebody else who researches a lot of his stuff
This is a geometric proof being followed up with I but you know yeah
But I do appreciate in the book also that that you did
Very clearly delineate that blood libel part
Like I'm such an important
Piece of
Like
What makes some of this like the archaic anti-semitic trope
Cooked into a lot of
These conspiracy theories
It's something that I think a lot of people
Me miss or may not want to address I think
Super bored
Yeah there's a real sense of
With you and like we're still
Doing this like we're still dredging up these stereotypes
You're based on
Things like the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Debunk
NetSpend that are knocked out
Over and over and over again
But it doesn't matter
People who walk
These things to be true
And everything that they do is
Validated by the idea that yeah there are
Wealthy string pullers who are
Making their lives miserable and the rising tide of
Progressivism
Canceling their way of life is
It's making it
You're wrong for them to do all the jokes that you
Spell worship the way they used to
Against a certain words
They they can't
Eat 25 Burgers of a week anymore that they have
E23 Burgers now
Did this Doctor Seuss book that they never heard of
Instantly not being printed anymore and it's like that's worth.
Get back how Hitler came to power book that I've never heard of
I just want somebody to come out and be like look
We've got thousands of years of unbroken hatred towards
The Jews and we're just not going to stop now well it's is always going to whoop you all this time
Really whoever made those posts really understood that
That
That you understood the way
These tropes
Work why they work
Understood
All they are communicated
It effectively unplaceable
4chan
And was able to exploit
Me whoever
These drops
Really did
Know what they were doing a really understood American Evangelical hucksters
Exploited
That's a really interesting perspective that I don't think I've heard a lot cuz I think a lot of people look at
You know it's qanon and think I got this is all stupid
And like you know hearing you say whoever did this
Was like they knew what they were doing
It is fascinating to me
Yeah and
The idea that they knew what they were doing doesn't that's
Sincerely me that there was some
Brad spiracy behind it that it
Sounds like military Glade
Grade cycling
Warfare
But you just have to know how
Hateful
Conspiratorial people
And if you spend enough
Time in places like 4chan
You can do that
It's not that difficult
Things on porch and things on Reddit
Go mainstream viral we've seen it with rickrolling we see him as Slenderman I mean
We know where the stuff
Mystery
People just
Believe it because I want to
Good story and validates things that they already believe
It almost seems like something that somebody who had like a really good grasp of like
Marketing
Could have
I could have swore
Yeah
You don't like wild to me
Do you watch Ted lasso
I don't I don't
Don't worry about it
It's a fight
But there was one episode where they straight up Rick Rolled me
And my partner had no idea what I was talking about
And that was the first time in a long time I've really felt like
I've been on the internet way too long this is not good
That's great perspective like my my wife doesn't know anything about this stuff
Stalin cheetahs
Social media really at all like
This is my world Alex albums like bring up some really common meme
Everybody knows what that isn't she like
What is that
It's a reminder that
That wall stings
Online are really important
Dismissed it stopped as like
I just internet people
Not everybody is as extremely online as
People Like Us
People who are
Mainlining
Infowars there is a there's a world
Exist
Not on
Twitter
Doesn't
Stop nnsy wrote the book is a very simple guide to
I didn't want to assume that anybody knew anything alive
You all talk about you and I'm people ask me still in there
What's an image
WhatsApp
And it said it's not
It's like this is not their world
Yeah so we have to do this very stupid
You guys are great
Breaking this stuff down
Into
Why does it matter
What about it matters
What can be discarded
How does it a
And that's
Wheatley really important things
As much as we really liked
Get into the weeds in the details
That's not where most
People that most people live
They don't have time for this they want to know the very basics
Doesn't matter to them how does it
Eliza
You guys are great
Well thank you
Yeah the thing I definitely agree to I get a lot of criticism by thing
That sometimes we're shows like well why are you
Take it like
Speaking
Like we don't know anything
May not Sicily can entry-level
I mean what you what you just said right there you know a lot of these people aren't online this isn't a full thing and then as
As you're going through the book you're reading like
Oh okay so these are people who are in a
Experience with the internet for finding this stuff
Do they have no concept of what the online people have which is like
F*** this noisy people are all out of their minds you know if you're online all the time you're
Best friend you like speak people are out of their f****** mine
That kind of feeling so if you don't have it
Experience you'd also don't know how to discern like a wing
Exactly how all these people were just dodo birds walking up to liars and just getting smashed on the head
Add another overthrowing the country hits
The degree to which
Big stories were shared
By the older Americans who got into qanon as enormous
People passing around this stuff
Because you just don't
Have the discernment
To tell real from fake and you think
These people wouldn't lie to me
They're they're my friends I've got to know them
Stories and their struggles like
It would never not
Tell me the truth
The basics that's
The basis of our Affinity fraud
Somebody
Inter-Community
A trusted member of a small insular group
Ruthlessly exploited the rest of the people in that group
Yeah yeah the Affinity itself is necessary to be
Went to a funeral my grandma's funeral was held at a megachurch and I
I like walked in there and I was ready to start fires like I just couldn't handle it
Yeah I'm out is brutal
One thing I definitely wanted to ask about is
The biggest intersection I think between Alex Jones
McEwen on directly
Is the affair of Jerome corsi
Yes and
IWatch
That happened but I don't think that we did a good job of covering that
Was that an Oscar Wilde book The Affair of 04
Lyrics
What I understand
He tried to get involved
Basically
Like he tried to become a q person
Yeah
For awhile I keep.
Really
Enjoy the night and the timing with this stuff
Is always really
Really into it like he was tweeting
Relentlessly
About
About you
Decoding the drops
You're trying to figure out what was going on tying it into his own personal stuff
I believe you are even writing a book
Yeah yeah he had them on all the time
Alex Wassabi about a holiday
White House
Swatted corsi covering 8chan I mean
Just bizarre.
And then of course like so much
Of the Alex Jones world
Johnson
And that it was disinfo and
She talked about
Talk to somebody
Who played golf
5 people who were running
She would all that was for
Taking over by Masada mean
But you know how
Is it like this is the most important thing in the world
And now suddenly we have to destroy
Yeah if I can't take it over then it must be defeated
He has talked about how he tried to
The Coop that
When it was sort of growing and it was even unable to
I I smile
Personal opinion I don't really have anything to back
Knowing the people
Ball
Is that
She was trying to co-opt it and it was getting
Bigger
That was a threat
Sanctity of the Infowars
Empire
Because it was
It was a little bit more
Participatory
It was a puzzle
That I mean nevermind there was a solution to the
But I think she started to see it as a
As more of a
Brett and Leslie something
Integrate into his own mythology and I think that's why
Yeah I would definitely read them I don't know if I have anything solid to back that up that's my sense too late
Do you have these this period of decades wear
Gary's essentially been the authority on a lot of this
I kind of conspiracy both yet you have something like you it threatens that Authority cuz there's
The decentralized ya Levi's you put a gurus
Batman stuff
He's no longer necessary as a gatekeeper
I work for this stuff and that vibe that I got four
Chew is really is really good at allowing people to rise up and create their own version of this
You have these
Promoters
These people talk about in the book
People like in The Matrix
Joab
Jordan sather
On and on and on East River Regional
Qanon promoters you're making
The videos in
Podcast
The lifestreams in the merchandise
And that if they do need our
It's just a thought Alex Jones was a sell-out
The Patriot
Was control.
Yeah they're they're doing this without any training there's building this from the ground up
And I can see it
These people are threatened
They could
They could take over my audience
Yeah I need to own this or I need to be against
Yeah
So some of those early guys
I'm falling off right I mean like a lot of them aren't really
Q folk anymore they likes
Shifted their grip
It's a little really divorce
The big promoters all kind of have their own niche
Flights
Jordan sather is really into like
The wellness stop in the secret space program
Drinking bleach
If I recall
Bmms the Miracle Medical
Do not ever
Some of them it really disappear Joanne was one of the really big
In the book who
Dot-dot-dot Charter School
Fundraiser
They're canceled
AR sharing this interpretation of a
James Comey Twitter
False flag attack
Because I was hearing some of the other
People just going
What why did they what what what has happened
That what why do we do this and let you know I covered that way
People who are organizing and then of course they had to
Cancel it the next year
And I think they canceled again and I don't
We're going to have another one
And it's just it's enraging
Think about
These Anonymous gurus
Roll this into their Grifton at age
Booba
He's really disappeared he kind of
Went to ground after the
Twitter Banner
Maybe for a little while but
He's really taken himself out of it
Cement mixer now he's a really nice guy working a job
But then you do a lot of them have gotten
Conserve
Jellicle isn't
I'm done
Stop with it
The stolen election
Completely mixed up with it and this is what I talk about with you
You is
It's now just average
She went on
As a as a brand really doesn't exist
These conspiracy theories are just
Mainstream conservatives
People who used to be nice completely
Different worlds
Yelp
Pharmaca
Conspiracy theories
Barack Obama's birth certificate
This is not what I was saying
They all believe
Poison master-slave muzzles
Donald Trump is still the real president
The Deep state
Controls everything
You know I run for school board and everything is now every
Difficult to pin down
Do you want some of these things because
Is all
Interconnected it all bolsters
Everything else so these new generation of
Dorchester Circle
Pumping out
Everything is related to
Everything else
It's a very
Lucrative personent
Do you think that they're more fractured now and then I would I would assume
That would mean more likely to compete with each other as they kind of
But
Spaces do you know what I mean
Yeah you gay
There's been a lot of
Infighting in the
Influencer Arena lately you know some people who are more so
Directions
People who are more
Anti-vax there are some people
Who sang Donna
Willie is the president some people think
Biden is
Is technically the president
Can I come back in there sir
Insulting each other and then they
Maybe she'll do for money and over
Real
Hey. You got like
Marjorie Taylor Greene
Feuding with Linwood and shooting with
Utah speeding feuding with
Qanon Jonathan
Possible
I mean
What kind of my my
View on this is this is the type of movement that is inevitably going to destroy itself
The question is just are they how quickly can they take us with
That's it like it's just going to they're going to eat each other alive they're going to cannibalize each other
You got this
What's going on with these health
Freedom stolen election conferences
They're happening like
Every weekend
Yeah used to be there
It was a big deal
Now you got the
Massive
The conference is going on
Truth or just a weekend
You got coming up
The Patriot double down in Vegas and there's another one
One that has a
Chicken
I actually I over the weekend I was looking at Twitter and I saw like some video
What a recent episode we were making
In front of the Patriots Street Fighter
Because I went and looked at his tour dates
He was advertising his Tour on Alex
There's a commercial for it
And the tour dates and everything past like
Four days in advance with all location tbg
This is never going to happen and I saw a video and it was like
Full
Yahoo like a
Conference room
And a great to be look like a bunch of
You know pretty much the
Just all old white people but
It still was like that's a lot more people than I would have
Expected to be
Hanging out with the Patriots Streetfighter
Yeah I know they they they would have
September 11th
Last year
Weather was like
120 people at the Washington Monument that was a big deal
I know that there are so many of these
Bear poaching
From each other
Mike Flynn was supposed to
Speak at the Patriot Double Down
You got a better offer from some other
It's
I mean it really is if
I went to think of this is like pro wrestling and it's almost like
Eating
Wingstop
Yeah
Stay the same thing
God knows why they haven't
Join forces other than like money
This is gotten so big
Can soda
Just use the these coffee
Thereabouts
They're about
Covid is a hoax
Second Amendment
The Border
Media censorship
The Deep state
Biden is a fake president on a set in Tyler Perry's house
Ivermectin
You know
BBC Tyler Perry's House crispy
Because you made that show The Oval right
God knows where this stuff comes from
It is
It just emerges out of the ground like worms after the
Yeah what you're describing it it almost
Like I have a real-life sort of ominous feeling of their almost
It almost feels like
Ten in Serbian
Informed you know Lake
Baker canonization
Is like a belief system
He's like in progress and we're sort of seeing it happen
Through these
Conferences in these online fight
There's going to be
The Bill of Rights Theses nailed to the wall of the Capitol building the next time they throw it up
We're really starting to get into that like
People's front of Judea vs. Judean People's from
Aspect
They're just fighting over who has the biggest audience in who has the most money
And I think that's where
Begin
Amman
Your people asked me are there going to be more to drop
And
I don't think there will be because they're not
Yeah
You Persona was taken as far as it was going to go
Angela
Need new
Nobody goes
New books of the Bible
Got the Bible
They don't need anything else
The god that you drop
Dick that uses a q
You you have more than you know
What they have
The drops are there they're taking them off into a million different Direct
Yeah
Is very it is on the very informative but very depressing
Yeah I mean it who says who says that it's done you know we we had the Bible then we got the Book of Mormon I'm sure they
There's an enterprising liar out there is going to run out again
That's fine
That you never know Jay nobody in
Yeah that around the crucifixion could have anticipated
Joseph Smith
You are way wrong sir
Several thousand years ago
Yeah it's
It's so weird because I have a lot of similar feelings about like a lot of the Alex stuff
It's it never feels
Quite like
Like it has the
Ability to
To formalize
It's like out on does or like to have to turn into something else
I think both of them are primarily
Scam oriented Uno like Alex is
Pill scam
You know qanon the various promoters are
You know basically
Attention economy scamming and
What have you put
The danger of
Of Cuban on turning into something different
It is it's so
Another thing then then
Texas purerite winking
Conspiracy stuff
I have a quick question
For you I'm working on a theory
About
Alex actually providing a weird sort of bulwark
Against
Something along the lines of
Qanon
By having a more control over that
Space
You know he creates almost a bottleneck there
And I think what we're seeing is that what happens when you
Let all the steam out is
A massive diffuse
Organization that
Nobody can have any control.
You know she can funnel all of it to his pill business and they're not overthrow
Capital
What is that
Aspect
Shoe that is not
Quite
Like a traditional called
There's no charismatic leader there's no
Figurehead at the very top with
Word is bond
With q
Thank you do your own research
You are your own leader
And that allows these promoters to step in and take
Control
And take
Their version of the movements
Spinning off in any number of direct
That's why
Becoming much more mainstream
While the actual life
Iconography
Physics you swag
Quite as much
The charm she went on they now think that that's
Something to be mainstream Media made up
To make them look crazy
Makes sense
There's no escape from these people
It never mind if they were using that term
That the most
Popular bro
Chewbacchus literally called
You want
An invitation to the Great Awakening
Right
But then they then they decided that
They're also trying to not
Love those big
Maps anymore would like to eat
1000 things on it that are all connected
The Deep State mapping project and all that stuff
Because it makes you look insane
It makes you look like
The red strings in the corkboard and
You know
Whereas
Somehow insinuating Donald Trump is
Still the president
Because you sign something executive order
12 years ago and his time-traveling uncle used Tesla
Technology
That doesn't make sense
I think one of the weirdest
Things that qanon has actually revealed
Is that
These people don't know how anything works
They don't know how Civics Works they don't know how I can omits works
So you can kind of just tell them like
So if you sign an executive the president signs
Executive order well then it must be
Law forever right right right by tomorrow could sign an executive order that we are now all part of Panama
Then we would be part of
Brighton it's it's
You know they don't know how
Banking works I don't have money Works they don't know how the media work
It's a misunderstanding of the basics
The world
Golden see the way that they want
Things to be the way that they
And are not
And they they
Cling to that and they cling to the reality that they have
Created for themselves
And that reality is a lot more entertaining and has done a lot more successful
Add has the bad people
Eventually being punished
And has somebody in control
And that's
Really what we all want
Is somebody in control
Yeah right
Not be an endless series of random events that we really don't have any
Stay over
I think to like you're just a minute
Essentially what
So much as I can
Conspiratorial thinking boils down to say
A little bit of magic
Am I like an easy solution
Someone in charge
It's
It-it's
It's remarkable how Outlet
It really is
Is helado in a lot of ways a lot of it is very simple
And a lot of it
Impossible to deal with complex
Incredibly
Basic psychology and the most incomprehensible
Garbage
But you will ever stumble upon
And somehow these people are able to kind of
One foot in each
Adam B
Make it work for themselves then rationalize away
The failures of the cognitive dissonance
Obvious fraud
Just this is the world I want to live in and
Nobody's getting them out of
I was thinking of
I remember this cult
I can't remember the name but it was in the late
And this woman had predicted the end of the world was going to happen at the stroke of midnight
On badabababa
Right
And
If the stroke of midnight happened
Not the end of the world didn't happen
They talked about it the next day
It was supposed to be next
Something along those lines you know who's that kind of thing
Who
Whenever he he believes
But the world is going to end so he went
To his own house
Stood up on top of his roof
And at the stroke of midnight
Just fell off
The more I thought about that the more I was like I'll man that guy is so stupid you could have
Survive and then now looking at all these qanon people
That guy is easily the happiest person ever to live in that cult
Right like that was the perfect time to die when everything you believed was true
You can't have to live through the deflation and the rationalization
The cult leader being messed up and you like you were supposed to know everything
Yeah and it's and it be
Call Memes
Impossible to go back
You have that is used the example
Cortez in the New World
You burned yourself
New York
Family doesn't want anything to do with you
Your friends don't want to hear you with you
You have
The money your your emotional well
Being into this
Conspiracy theory being true into this
Great event
Happening
The event doesn't happen and you have the option
I was wrong I got
Schooled
I'm sorry
Orson Welles
Ikea
I can't go back I have to just
Forwarded
Happen eventually
And then I'm going to be right
And then everybody's going to be sorry
I'll go deeper and then eventually I'll be right
Well I hate to keep saying this
But that sucks
That is the dynamic that I think a lot of people find
Themselves in
And that's why I think it's really important
To try and retain some empathy for people who are
You know caught in these
I believe traps or scams are going to its
It can be hard because a lot of the beliefs
Themselves
Destructive and there
Causing damage
H2
Polite Society right
A lot of people are victim
And what are the things that I I see so often about
All the narratives around qanon is look at how bad these people on 8th
I'll look it up
Bad all of these people are
But no one is at all dealing with the fact that the reason it is easy to believe in qanon
Is because all of the systems have failed these
Like AIDS
It's not like they were doing great
You you go into these hoping that Hillary Clinton is murdered by the government
Because the 90s weren't great
You know like that
Dramatic
What are the big things that I wish the systems would look at qanon and think is
Who maybe we f***** up
You know I get asked a lot about the the demography
Yes primarily White
It's snow
Split down the middle Madden
Upper-middle-class
But the biggest
The demographic
For believing you and I was already being if you
Is there a
You people I mean
I've been just like
MSNBC watching New York Times reading Ido Centrist
Democrats
One day
Just happened to go to
X22report Owasso
You know
Fall of the cabal and then suddenly got radicalized into thinking that there's a pedophile
That's not how
I would going to vote for medicare-for-all but I think I want Hillary Clinton to die in
You you were already on 911
You are already a
Barack Obama birthday
You already somebody who
Are there
Start of knowledge
Base rewire by Trump win
And exposing all of the corruption
Thought
You thought about but you never
Could put into words
That was that was already your world you're already listening to Infowars you're already
Reading
Gateway pundit
Or whatever
She was just the neck
Wrong on the ladder
Things
But it's
Anti-vax
Big Pharma
Conspiracy theory
G.i. Bill Gates anti globalism
Super super hardcore Bernie Sanders Hillary screwed him out of the nominations
Whatever it is
There is a conspiracy theory for you
Paraplegic
Yeah like if you're eight steps
Down the road
No matter what road it is it's easy to take those two steps
To get to the
The final point
Like
Step one or you're not even down that road
You're not going to
It's not attractive enough of a
Conspiracy to get you to be like 50 to 60
All roads lead to Rome unless you live in South America
Unless you just don't also get on the road
Eschew roads
A person who understands how things work
Denby
Conspiracy theories don't have a lot of
Like the stolen election idea
Doesn't really appeal to you because you know that that
. how about you
But you can't like there isn't one guy in a
In an office
Dominion voting
Systems
Abiding Wendy Lashley you know that that's not true
Counterpoint
There is a guy at the minion to just message
Yeah yeah I think I think they're one of the things that we always talked about 9
This is like when
What if yours if you
Deal with the complexity of
A lot of issues an event
That's that happened in the world
I love you
Conspiracies don't really make
Make sense
But if you don't want to deal with that and you want to look at
Things kind of in a
Sort of overly simplistic black-and-white way
Parowan
I don't mean you ready
You look at this s*** right now and you see mansion and Cinema are like
Well you know everybody wants this stuff but I guess we're paid enough to say f*** off
It does make sense for you to think f*** it I want Trump
To just stroke a pin and do this
Because these people are f******
Incorrupt you know it's like that's what it is
It's the unfortunate reality that there is a basis for the
The feelings that underpin a lot of conspiracy
Believer
Suffer reason like
Big business is not your friend
The government
Is Kuru
You know
Jeffrey Epstein
Did horrible things
This is all true
This is a time I was just thinking like a radio interview is like what do we do next
Execute not in my first class
Texting dead or alive
Who's not
Run down the list
I had I had one question that I definitely wanted to get to you so I'm going to slip it in here
And that is what what
I hate if it's putting me on the spot at all but
You're somebody who focuses on with this stuff a lot
I imagine that you see coverage
Of qanon
That kind of
It may be frustrating
I was wondering if there's one thing that you think is important that people know about it that
Datejust
Gets messed
Krakow lot of
The time
Wow that's a great question
Ice ice
The thing that gets missed a lot
Is that
You can believe in something like
He went on and not be crazy not be violent
Not be stupid
You are just
Looking for something
In the wrong
Think what
Missed a lot is dead
These theories are
Grab people for a reason they always
No people look at something like you would on his like
We've never dealt with anything like this
This before like
There's never been a
Brainwashing like
Turn and look to your left and I'll Mormons are wearing the same underwear
The number of people who think that there is a conspiracy to
Kill JFK
Basically the same now
As it was
Weeks after the attack
People believe this stuff
This is Meaningful and compelling and explanatory
People I think
Just writing these people off as either idiot
Or on the flip side is like
Mind control zombies with no agency
I think you're missing
The realtor
Explain
So many things to be
Yeah they drift feels the needs that maybe people
I don't want to recognize are there
One of the things that I think is is really
I think it's close to what you're getting at is that like
I think that is so
Relevant
To make fun of the thing but not the people
I think people kind of are they make the mistake of
Making fun of
The people who believe this stuff as opposed to
Mocking the idea
Candy idea
Undead mocking the promoter
Like I will
I will unsparingly Savage
People like Ron White
Ghost Ezra people like in the maitre
I will knock those people up and down left
I have
I bet you're still going to vote for Ron but
Ivy league Arizona
Lcer
Beamed
We did his way
To being an expert on Election fraud and getting retweeted by the President's Day
Impressive
Completely stupid
And do that
Yeah
People
We do all the
But the actual like rank-and-file believe
People are really stuck in this
I do have it
I think
They're caught up in something that is way worse than
It is
And at some point the rock is going to get pulled out from under them
And then
What do you have left
Who is left in your wife
That wants
Display wants to help you
After you said and done
Possibly reprehensible or illegal thing
Tonight
I have a lot of
For the people
I am taking over this day baby class
Sick thing of life
You know when you when you
Go down the road
Towards this
You don't take the first step knowing that it's going to lead to something represent
You know it's there's there's a rational
Maybe pseudo rational reason why you know you
You go down the road and then before you know it you're far down
Into
Muck
Territory gross
Nobody nobody clicked on a link on Facebook
Going like
What time to get rid of my family click
Nobody joins a cult
You join a group of people who believe the same thing
You do the same thing you do or whatever but
You have any idea about that
You didn't choose to be born
But
Something is addition
For a lot of people
I mean that
That's the thing you go back to with us
They told a story
The people wanted to be sure it wasn't one of these like FBI and honor
Inside
Early like I have all the sea
Secrets I'm going to reveal everything
That's that
Interesting
Speaking that you have
Inside knowledge is Hillary Clinton is on the run is going to be arrested on November 3rd
Wo I want that to happen
Yeah
And I mean it is compelling I think that you and I are both
Clear examples that it's compelling even if you don't believe
These things are
Intellectually and sort of academically interesting and compelling
Yep
Jim
How
Deflated interviews under our belt we've got one that was happy
Alex is going to get his comeuppance the most unimaginably Bleak thing
I still think there's a little bit of Hope in there
And if if there was no hope I wouldn't do
Because it would
Would be
If you're just telling people that everything is awful all the time
Eventually people
Some people
Like that but
I think most people will
I think the thing that
Keeps me going is
People do get out of
People do
Find
The weakness of the dangling threads
Interpol
Thing falls apart
People are
Capable of walking away from this
And people are capable of understanding
And I'll be working out for
Are the signs that somebody they care about is getting radicalized
Insecure
You were Jason conspiracy theory
And then they they maybe have
And they kind of know what the
And then they could maybe stop it
Before it goes a little bit
Yeah make it they can approach it with
Like a like a little bit of
Care instead of judgmental
As more people can
Take that perspective maybe it'll
Lead to more people leaving
Then more of those stories will
Will become Amplified in
You're the conversation
Can completely change
Little bit
Stop that's my hope is that as we go
Forward into this more
You people will will come out
Answer
Talk openly and on-the-record about their experience
Something like Scientology where there is a a very large
Rhubarb
Apostate
Who are fearlessly speaking out about
That's without
Fear of the repercussions
He was just too new to have that
You just
Did the people
Have left it
Date the reintegrating into the world they've been
Right there still
Grappling
Right I'm a good news is when they do there aren't those repercussion
Since of Scientology
Alright I have one Quick Quack
Emporia
What are the chances that in about 10 to 15 years you go full green Walden start your own kiwi
Well I would know how to do it
What you kind of do
Buttons to push
Who is the audience
Second be riled up with this kind of
Culture War Ready
It I can imagine it becomes
Attempting to cash it
And you're tired
Fighting force tubes in your tired of like
Butting your head against
It's the government and end the big media
And then you go I'm going to I'm going to cash it
Like I'm going to go
Bull culture War
And then of course you start to believe it
Right because you can't just say this.
And have it be
Persona
You you believe it
To ascertain
Next time I get that a lot with a lot of them
Broadcast
Maybe not all of it
And they know how to monetize it but
This is their world they believe this.
You have to convince yourself
You will be an obvious
Sprott
And at the same time you have to keep some of yourself back knowing like
Like Alex like
I know covid real but I keep it to myself
To make sure that nobody f****** takes that next step you know
That temptation of like
You know you know the buttons
Pushin inside
Early on during the podcast
We did talk a whole lot more about like to be so easy just to go
Turn right-wing commentators
Be the best
Make so much money
We should probably wrap this up we
This has been a delightful conversation I really appreciate
The book is called into the store
Like the storm is upon us
Stormy
The storm is upon us how qanon became a movement
Colt
Conspiracy Theory of Everything
Everywhere
You can get it as a hardcover on eBook
Audiobook
However you like information delivered to you and whoever
You like delivering it to you
Let me ask you this did you read the audiobook
I did not read the audiobook we we we got a guy
Who is Donna
Play 500 audiobooks of Maurice lamarche
Has Orson Welles
Joe
Do parodies
Gme once in awhile
How do I pronounce
That's why was it was nice that he was like committed enough to it's like understand
How important is to get the minutiae of this right
Sure that's great
How do I pronounce
Three x's in in the maitre
Tricks
Think it's just
That guy
Jeffrey Peterson
This is David
She has heard that
Angela Griffin
That is like breast
Have you turned that into an industry
Well I mean is if you do got the new Matrix movie coming out I'm sure he's going to
Make some moves online
Yeah I mean the worst thing is that so many psychopaths are so goddamn enterprising
Episode
Anything else you on the Verizon people should be looking out for anything else hopefully something's
I definitely do not want to be
If it's you guy forever
Sure
Are you are you knocking The Alex Jones guys forever is that what
Everything should have flows through him so it feels like if your understanding Alex Jones
You're understanding all of this in the thing with you and autism
That I can now graffiti is starting
Disappear so you know it's it's
Like being there
The best betamax
Text repairman
You know at some point
Do something
Assertive anti-communist tradition act like
Lot of stuff
It sort of rich
Veins
Probably has a bit of that too but it's
Stolen it's like hijacked from
Well thank you again Mike has been a lot of fun
I hope
Everything goes well for
Goodnight