Damn important sweat it
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Hey everybody you welcome back to fight knowledge of Jordan
Alex Jones
Whatsyourprice
We're great at dozen on the gun
I don't know how you have that restraint generally telling you
People are like Jordan do you get all your restraint Back In The Cut and you come in right
The right time to ask about the break
Over 50
Hear about your brakes just wait until I say 2021
I don't know if you know this
But tomorrow
We're recording this on the 21st tomorrow is October 22nd
Right and that is the day that Dune is released
Is that right
Do you want to go see it
Should we go look like
Maybe we can probably go tonight
I do hope you go tonight we can go tomorrow
I guess so. I'll dress up as Duncan Idaho
It looks like it's great
Stewart's
Interpretation
Stewart was Gurney halleck in David Lynch's very
Correct myself on that one
Goodnight Show week
We could go to
Okay well think rides go tomorrow
Go to bed now
My bright spot to Jordan
Ranger or our friend was in town very nice salon
Always nice to see some
Coming out
This is a bright spot upon a bright spot day for you.
Yes you got it right
Thank you you also could have said
I'd rather take a spice you could have said
Address business and were no actually that is sacrilegious
Oh
I can't mess with shai-hulud my lamp
I always blow it 9:00
I'm excited
See this movie
Felt this way this like sordid
Excited about a movie since
Mortal Kombat
In that like you didn't watch it
Yes I did
But it's not like real excitement
Fake excited
Sure sure
Humped
Super Mortal Kombat I was disappointed
Going to be disappointed by doing but I'm
I doubt it everything I've heard is that this is the Dune movie that you dance Pacifica
I've been waiting for a while
But we're not going to talk about doing today
As everybody is probably figured out by now this is a Jordan Apple
Episode
Number five or six I think it's number 6 total and 5
So
Today it's going to be a little bit of a shorter episode but that is
Is because
We are talking about
This is been something that we've probably needed to talk about for a long time
I've heard some Rumblings
Probably the world needs
To talk about for a long time but
While researching this
I realized very quickly why
Nobody Does this and that is because it is
Is awful
Tik-Tok is the worst
Chasing the world
But I totally get why it's very very popular and we are going
To explore
I think I'm too old
I've had the same sort of feeling about it that I had with like
Snapchat
That is like
Kamehameha
No I was looking through the the person we're talking about today
Has well over three and a half million follow
Right
And I'm going through this
With my old ass
Just like looking at these videos just going like
You know
This isn't how you're
You're supposed to do it
You're supposed to have a 20-minute Apple
You would have been the guy who likes all the early YouTube video
The Blogger who's mad at Twitter
Microblogging nonsense
At least 1,000 words to explain everything
I'm my only exposure to take that really is my my friend. Angela
Buried
Jason Smith
From time to time
Ifun animal thing
Robust
Community of animals
Videos
Asbury
From what I can see
On Tik-Tok
There is a robust
Community
For everything everywhere
And no one has any idea about the
The other ones on
I think it's I think it's probably one of the more insular
Weird faces I've ever seen
Like a lot of
Sort of isolated bubble
Yeah
You
Isolated bubble
It would be like if
You know at the height of Carson
You know with 100 million people viewing a night or whatever you know something
Ridiculous number if you just met
AAA you know people who are
Just now started to watch David Letterman it never heard of cars
Oh well
Never heard of it like
Who are you talkin
Sing about there's only
What are you talkin about animal videos
Cancer is nonsense. There's no way that they would be bulshit on here
Well I mean I guess it's probably would Vine would have become if
State around
Anyways
Before we talk about
Tik-Tok
I think it's time for us to say to hello some
To us some new walk that's a great idea you came in at the right time there
Holding back
An action lion with a commercial driver's license or no
I'm a policy wonk
Lee
Justly
Ewok
Likely
Next we have Joe Fox you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Allender is turd Anderson
That's probably a real name
I'm a policy wonk Anderson
Technocrat who has assumed
Related
It is pooping sinbon pooping
Heroin
Freakishly large
Little bit more scatological Wonka names today than normal I'm not I'm not thrilled with that
Pacifically
We're going to get it out of the way we can get that I wish that I had like a scientists told you
Hillbilly good
Well here's the episodes have to say
I am I have a little bit like
Norm Macdonald saying Turd Ferguson there sure
There is that
Today Dan
We are going to talk about little little ticktocker name to act
Ty the crazy
The guy Jack
But not an it's not all
Ty the crazy guy in the crazy guy
Wow menus
Put the right out there
No
Is that there's a huge caveat here
Which is that I do feel like this is important to talk
But like most people on
Tik-Tok we are going to be talking about a child
So it is a very thin needle to thread there without just being like
All kids are stupid
Okay well I mean technically
Majority is a safe
In his first video can join the Army
Vegan
The first video of this dude put out on
Tik-Tok I think you was like 16 years old
And it's essentially all what
Most toxic
Tik-Tok videos are it's very short thing
And it's got him kind of like dancing and mugging
Into the camera
There's music over it
And then you just point
And words appear on the
Twitter I've seen people repost
Those
The caption
Simple
Direct that's what everybody get
Sure
And in his
It's basically like him saying like
I want to be
Tik-Tok famous
Can we make that
And then overtime
It appears without changing anything
Or doing anything
Any different or having any discernible like
Sing that word
Make him stand out
You know he just started getting more and more popular
People just kind of event
Okay
This is what we call the the secret
Yeah yeah he manifested Twitter arto today
No he was like Hey I want to be Tik-Tok famous and apparently everybody on Tik-Tok was like
I guess
Let's just make this guy favorites
So he goes on for a year or so putting out these very very
Simple similar videos
He's doing he's doing pretty well
Every now and again he'll go real viral
And he'll get like
200,000 views on water
You know
Something something
Open crazy and it's
It again
These are all just him like dancing and then pointing to words as they appear
I'd say it's your basic
Internet meme Joe
Very simple him being like
When I'm in class I feel like and then he makes a face and then
When you get it
Yaya
I have no idea who this
This person is
You're saying there's millions of followers
Roseanne
It's so bizarre that
We don't have that centralized like
Engine economy
Bananas right now
And again
Because we're talking about a kid I don't mean I'm not shiting on his
Is creative output or whatever you know that it's not like
I'm expecting him to be a have already instantly distance himself from his
F****** peers or whatever you know I'm not trying to be an a****** he hasn't changed the form
But he really doesn't have any like
Pallet
He's just very
There and watchable
And I get it
I get what's going on
All of this is going along normally and then he
He puts out his
Is first conspiracy
Video
Instead of conspiracy
Conspiracy
So he's drinking
Auntie
Spilling some of it probably you got it
First
Conspiracy theory conspiracy I refuse to figures
Comes out
Insta
Instantly
Right up over like 200,000
Now it's up over like a million two million or whatever it
And here is what
Bought this kid into popular
The Kardashians are cursed by witches
We need to talk about this
In 1809 the Kardashians
For all future generations of the Kardashians to have faint
Power and wealth
The keeper
The past which is
Kardashian
Cheap airfare
Which explains the many many many exorcisms
Before you met Carnage was a happy successful businessman
Parasite
Rehab
The Kardashians sacrifice their own Brothers
That's okay that's quite
That's quite a bit of tea
So he's got the pole he's got the PJ Peter BP Watson
Humpin around
The fast-paced
Kind of necessary on
Tik-Tok
Yeah
Oh really really cut
Nice and quiet
You know what I hear when I when I was
Some of that is like a melding of
Celebrity Obsession and
Like
Fairy Tail
That is exactly what it is
I will tell you where this conspiracy comes from
A fairytale
Well in 2012
I believe February 2012
Someone named
Studio writer
Wrote this for Studio no
And it's why are the Kardashians
Famous own his whole conspiracy thing was OJ's lawyer
Hahaha okay
The biggest
Suitcase
Televised
Do you think that Tik-Tok early two-year-old tiktokers like
Well they became famous because of OJ
Just doing Twitter
Exactly
This was this whole story
It's called why are the Kardashians
Famous
A dark history exposed Sono now
I'm going to read you some of
And you tell me
Do you think it's based in reality or not just
This is how it starts
So they the Kardashian
Stare at their great-grandmother
Went to a gingerbread house
Wait
In 1809
A dark-haired woman Strode through the deep forest d'Ivoire mean
The rain lasts down through the trees
The water making her robe
Heavy and thick
But she was
Determined
This
Is a ostensibly the very real accounting something that happened in 1809
I feel like this
Sourcing on this is probably
Aboveboard
Go on it goes on for quite some time
After a some very breathless description of her traveling habits
She's experiencing
The first and
Gnarled trees rose up from the earth like a tortured head
Beyond the rough
Clearing Beyond
The dark Earth
The mouth of a cave Gates like that
The throat of a bee
Beast Within faint traces of
Flame cast shadows in the death
Ghostly treasure
I'd like to move
Alright so this is
100% Bass
I got caught up in the visuals are
Like a fairytale almost exactly like a fairytale
Here's how it is
Switchmate
Convince you that you might be right
So
The Twist on this
Is that Keiko
Goes to the Four Witches
And one of them is named Rumpelstiltskin
Close
Very close she asks for
And and this is working
I want nothing more
Then Fame Fortune
Shannon Beauty
Brighton
So
They give her Fame Fortune
Beauty
Nothing more than
So they don't have talents or brands
The whole thing is one giant
Dick
Just an a****** thing to say about why the Kardashians are famous
Cuz they're not flat they're not good
Cuz I made a deal with the witches in the 1800
It's this and the end because of that sexist
Rihanna
Is really awful
And this just has no idea that would include Robert Kardashian
Ludacris
You wasn't that hot
I don't know if that was the real takeaway here
Yeah that's
That's wild so someone just wrote this
Bizarre
Fanfiction that was basically two
Back in 2012 and now this person up Tik Tok
Is a bring it out as a
Spilling the tea you better conspiracy about these
These famous
You got it
Lamb is that nuts
I guess yeah yeah
It's sad
It's really sad
And here's a
Because a million people have watched it then
A couple of them at least we're like wow that's it
Stick right
Right
An end it
And here's the other thing you know when we talked about
Talking about some of these people who you don't know if
If they're trying to be funny or not
Yeah
I can see them conceivably
Being hidden behind that wall of well I'm Joe
This kid
Exist
With a red light where there is no
Distance between
There's never any distance between a joke and reality
There's no distance between fantasy and reality
All the same
He doesn't believe this
But at the same time he does believe it
But at the same time he doesn't believe
I kind of believe that you know
Swings-N-Things
No I don't believe it
Yeah that's the whole of what if
Exact
It is not a
Problem
For me like whenever I go through these things
The problem isn't so much
What information of what
Conspiracy theories
Disseminate
Sure
It is that
He is removed
The line
Queen fantasy and reality
It's almost like
The content is what it is
But the presentation of it is
Really damaged
Because because
If you accept that
Kind of
Way to take in information
What else are you going
Susceptible to
Because it's so short
You watch it
And it disappears and you don't even think about it again but he's up there so
No
The whole time I was thinking of
If you recall the we had a interaction one-time wear
I told you that I didn't want to drink the beer be
The temperature
And that was a thing that I'd always been told
That was real and you very correctly pointed out that that is an incredibly insane thing to think that's stupid
Beers are are stored at
At room temperature
You know but it's one of those unexamined little things that was
Popped into my head
It's some point and I never thought about
Until it just pops out
We all have those things and you're never really able to
Confront them until you're aware of the exact
So these things
Just pop in and out like and then ears
The Conspirator
Another glass
Oh yeah
The Titanic
We need to talk about this
On the Titanic
One of which was the Olympic
Ticket just come back from a journey and had a lot of damage on it
So much that I really wasn't ever safe for it to go out again
The company switched
Titanic
Purposely crash
Insurance money
It sounds crazy but look at the proof
First off the Olympic has 16 portholes in the Titanic at 4
Picture of the alleged
Titanic
Which is literally a part of Olympics
The few survivors
The Titanic
Say anything
I don't like the we need to talk about
He says it every single time I got that I got was a catchphrase you find that annoying
This is why I told you this is the worst
How many of those and I heard him say that again and again and again
Yeah yeah this one is less like
Fairytale this is something you do here in
Conspiracy Circle zygote
This is something that
I know that we even talked
By virtue of
I think was a Bill Cooper episode
And I know that Alex believes that the Titanic was
Conspiracy
Yeah that is
That's it
This is where that to that connect
That's that's
The thing you start
To see him
Because the first
Conspiracy video
Get so many f****** life
He is incentivised
To keep going
All the sudden
Very short time he goes from like
Oh isn't it funny the Kardashians are which
To like
Now I'm getting into those
Fringe
Conspiracy theories
And not the
I read on a message board
Even have the class
Pronounce acquiesce
Bright bright
Yeah I know I was a little disappointed by that
But I mean obviously this one's
Very easy
Debacle
Alright
The insurance
Wouldn't have covered the cost of the Titanic
So
DNC
Jake Kent blatant
Wrote a book on all the
The Titanic conspiracy theory
And his
His quote
The whole switch conspiracy founders
Quite literally
On its Financial merits alone
Which is a nice little that's a good little pun
He's got a nice little
The issue
Is like the conspiracy based on like what
Intentionally
For the insurance
Okay people still died on
And everything
Well they switch the boat
Right
Because the Titanic
Couldn't have asked
Haha
No it's it couldn't sail because it was too is already bust
Sure didn't want the Titanic because it's the
About stunts
Sinkable ship ever
To go out and say
So they switched it
With another
In order to
Reclaim face in order to recoup the insurance losses on the
Titanic
Okay
And none of it
None of it makes any sense
And it wouldn't cover it
Bright light just from a business standpoint
Insurance quotes are very
Not interested in paying out when they don't have to
Especially
I'm not just that but I get the money wouldn't if they would have lost money switching these things
What is it what
That's like somebody is in
Hey I bet I bet
For about a hundred grand I could make a Titanic
Disappear like there's no other there's no other explanation for that
Nuts and it's and but
But the thing about that is that with this Tik-Tok video
It's 30 sec
Edit you can go look
Intuit in 30 seconds and it'll all be gone
What that's not hurt it
Smile Tik Tok doesn't work where you watch a video and then you open a new tab
And look into it
I see about this just keeps playing
Just keep playing it more and more goes and more and more buildup so this was nothing
I heard it
Google
Did they switch the time
Titanic was immediately like
No idiot
That was what Google
And then
Here we go
Another one
The birds in the sky
Actually surveillance cameras from the CIA
We need to talk about this
So in 1953
The surveillance by a lot
Replace them with fake fur
Watching her every damn move
Between 1951 and 1979
Billion Berg
Silver 2 years the CIA
Christian airplane
50 gallons of bird poison
Sportsman's
Apple X years almost all the birds were dead
See what he heard
220 million so far in the best
The robot / 34 Lisa done such a good job that no one
Suspect
Wow
Yeah shocking if true
Yeah this is just basic
The T-shirt sales
This was just this is just a viral marketing thing
It's real bad
And somehow also
He
He's getting
Details of
The Conspiracy Theory wrong
We've got real
About the story the story actually goes
In the ER the most
Common 1in
Are birds real
Conspiracy world
Was rooted in
Just like
Like a like a like a
Was it today
Bumper sticker poster t-shirt scam
Darius
Allen Dulles
You know a guy who needs fake
Conspiracy theories about it
Boy is evil real ones kind of Mickey
He's in he's like we got to we got to watch everybody
And the story is because
Hughes
Place to be
B-52 bombers
And taking them from having all these bombs
To having 400
50 Ford
Gallon
They were like I don't know why that
And then some fix
Scientist from fake Area 51 we're like
Oh we know why that happened
Sure and then d
Theoretical quote
Theoretical quotes right
From
Jefferson actually right
The first head of the CIA
D it was
Theoretically Alvin beat
Cleaver the internal communication
Director
His phone was too
This article
Was far more measured
Cleaver is believed to have said
Quote
Which is killed about 1.1 billion so far
And the best thing is
The robot Birds we've released in their place have done such a good job
That nobody even
Suspects a thing
Doesn't that just seem so real
I'm very
Marysville
I think there's some
Technological hurdles
That don't make sense
Especially considering
This would have been in the 60s
Assertive
Robot technology that we would have had at that point
Probably not that great
One of the things that people don't take him to
Consideration Lotto time
With the robotics
Not so good outside when it rains that's a problem the birds are real high
Just got her way up there
They could fall out at any moment in time
Live outside
To be a bad place for a robot to live
Now here's the thing about this kid
That I do find
Truly.
Like this is something that is and it's really indicative on this clips
Alright in the act
Toolkit
Conspiracy theory
You know all the birds died
Right and I said
They wiped out bird
Gave them a disease
And then they would die in 24 hours
In the real
Conspiracy theory
Their bones melted within 24
Their bones dissolve
Now when you have that as part of the story you're like so you're telling me that in 1950
T3 Allen Dulles had bone melting technology to be fairy
Only worked on
Cuz they have
British Airways
They have weak bones
Yeah
So if you leave that part out
And you just have
Do they all die
Then you can make up any number of reason
Sure
A disease that got a thing they've got a thing
In the actual story is it
It's cold
Their bones melt
Sure I think that the other thing that's a disservice
It's kind of dangerous about
This
Sort of information
Dissemination
Scheme
Is that this case in particular like Allen Dulles is somebody who like
There's real things to look at he's truly one of the most evil dude you could look at
Things that are real are not as fun as he
Kill the bird
Kids to watch
Do you know what you're not as fun as that and I think
You know how Jack
Getting the attention
In that direction does a disservice to like real-world issues
Is 100
Yeah only
Gets people to look more at the
Why wants to be
Tik-Tok
You know it's such a weird thing for him to have completely succeeded at
And then here we go this is this is what I want to this is almost like a rap
Spitfire
Situation here so
This next one is so
Incredibly
Stupid okay
Just just
This is how you can tell if the FBI has tapped
Come to your phone and is watching you
Where's your phone app
Your phone
Normal
Everyday
Is the conspiracy
Actually sounds
Dangerous
Like
Kind of
No and there's no explanation just being like hey
Texas into your phone right now to see if the FBI's happened you confirm whether or not you're in danger
Battery. Might as well have been him being like there's hot singles in your area it's the same f****** thing
And if you watch him
Why not do it
Couldn't hurt
You think
Totally
They're not going to open up a tech magazine howtogeek and be like
Oh okay that's
Just the interrogation code
That says if your forward call forwarding is on
That's that's what the number is Solvang
It's benign
Atleast it's not something where
Like you could have somebody
Collecting your phone number or
Luckily it's benign
But this is
This is out of
Control there's almost
I can't I don't know what would be stopping somebody from not having
That number just
It's not been
Something
That's malicious
And it doesn't matter
If you if it's
Obvious or not or if
If you are somebody who's smart enough not to if there's a million-and-a-half use on his Tik-Tok
With him saying
Put this into your phone right now yeah a lot of
People are going to do it
Or even
It could be someone's
Remember it could be a
Tulip targeted harassment
There's that there's so many ways to be abused yeah
You know there's a lot of things
And we need to talk about
Sorry
Then we go into this
This is like
I kinda want to play these really really close to each other so we're going to talk a little bit in between each other
Yeah the next three okay
Controlling
Okay so today
The 1940s from the government
Countries
People's teeth whiter
The government never responded around 75 per-cent of
Restart
Is basically proving that impact
Basic musically
Intelligence
I'm through the tap water
Something
Amazing baby that's just
Literally an Alex Jones
Yep and it's just there
30 seconds from the guy who you were like
I'll just put
Number into my f****** phone and then I'll just do what this guy
F****** says
We've need that neutrality 4tiktok the opposing voice
Bird
30 seconds must be given to the alternate
3.0 tons of his videos that have like the
Covid misinformation thing I pay back
Yeah
And it's and it's
It's not malicious
Kid isn't in a meme kitten isn't like a far-right
He's a he's a
Young he's got tons of
This dude is just a
Livius yeah he doesn't know what he
He's doing it's pretty easy to see how
A lot of the ideas
Accepted by the audience
Would lead someone
Closer and closer
Do right wing
Territory
Play the next
Okay
You got
Thank you this is the truth of how Halloween started
We need to talk about this
Over 2000 years ago
Samhain Festival
The Pope Gregory the 4th
October 31st for unknown reasons
Robert Parish
Retail on Halloween
Reset to the Overworld
People's houses
Didn't get free food
The trick-or-treating now with kids
Keep himself safe
People are people from the Overworld so they wouldn't be targeted by the actual people looking for Souls
Costumes for Halloween
Came from conspiracy
What's the Overworld
Life I guess
Mortal Kombat the outer world
No end
This one
Conspiracy
Not a dark history
Turtle Back Zoo
To Fairy Tail
Territory even then it's just kind of like
And at it
More like a mainstream
Siri of where of our
Modern Halloween
Celtic salmon
And the pope kind of co-opted it
All of this kind of crap
Kind of
If you look into it
Then you would look into it and you be like
He got a more-or-less kind of what people would say is better
Can call that number
Exactly
Exactly episode is not
Is not dark
It's not it it's just
It's just a thing
You know he's just telling you a fact
Oreo released like a factual hypothesis
I am just
And he just mixes that in there with the rest
The b*******
There's no difference between them
Nope
Keeps
F****** going and this is the thing about
It is
Not
Done
It is accelerating
Sure and it's going through
Well
Listen to this crazy Illuminati game from the 90s Maita predicted the future
We need to talk about the Illuminati
New World Order
Predict the future
Now corsaut the time now
Does from the Illuminati button
Specific order but the specific chain of nine cards
Is so accurate
It's crazy the first one is rewriting history the second is
Terrorist nuke in the third is pentagon
To clean now we have population reduction Center for Disease Control an epidemic
Quarantine in it
When is the last three is what's going to happen in the near future
Combined disasters
Kill for peace and tape
It seems like there's going to be a rebellion against the police system which is already starting and I don't even know what this last one
Today's conspiracy
Fun fun fact right behind you
Is a bunch of the Illuminati card game on my wall
Putting this in their beehive everyday Illuminati cards are
Behind
Behind your head Thursday the frog god
There's also big
Bigfoot and
Vampire you know they talked to the Center for Disease Control
Epicenter for weird studies the hammer of Thor
Conveniently ignored when people talk about the
I mean he did bring up the fiendish Florida Gators already that's definitely there
The Clone arrangers
Red Birch Society dinosaur
Yeah exactly
Very
Very nice way to get around copyright Godzilla
I can't run can't read Atomic monster that right yeah right next to next to Dinosaur Park
Yeah yeah fun
Yep so
That's the thing about this
The thing that I kept thinking about whenever we're going through this clip is like
He is
Kind of almost systematically scouring the internet
Newark
Conspiracy theories
But they're all the same old
So it's almost like he's he's
Creating this like
Scrunched up
Version of the past
30 years of conspiracies
All in this easily digestible 32nd format
People who are unsuspecting to listen
It's Illuminati card game
Yeah I know you kind of have to assume that
Like if the workflow is Bass
Physically he's got to find
These incentivized to find new things to Spill the tea
He about as it were
Eventually you're going to end up in Holocaust denial
Eventually you're going to run out of things that are that are
Like interesting
Quotes to your audio
And right now you're going
Going to find
Way more
F***** up conspiracy look at the Illuminati card game to the Illuminati drink children's blood
Bright right
I do love those in that there's something really hilarious
But like
The Illuminati put out this card game
And no one believed it because
Whatever like
The Illuminati is like they have a press release like
Shut up aluminum
Again with the Illuminati
Yeah they're notoriously unreliable as a source
That's great
Yeah I mean
It's it's bananas
You know he he's also kind of Iowa I'm going to skip the
Okay let's play the next
Okay I'll play that one real
Aliens on Earth
Okay
Huge metal in the middle of Utah
Species from another planet on Earth
Call Monical's in Utah
Pentagon released footage
Possible UFO sightings
We talked about it
It's because the information was getting released from the inside
Is today's conspiracy
I can't wait for him to find out that they use real dinosaurs in
Dinosaur park
This one and the other was interesting to me because I
Do remember the monitor the monitor
They did discover a monolith
In Utah
And it was the talk of the internet for the day
Sure it was one of those
Reddit user Tim slang
Pinpointed the
Coordinates so the the
SparkPeople
Didn't tell Everett anybody where it was
Rightly thinking
Crazy people just show up
Right up and then f*** over
Native indigenous population sure
Protected land
So what day of course forgot was that the internet was going to find
It's just going to have
Well because they've got the robot
They can just happened everything
And you know
The other thing that I used that you didn't use
Robot
Switchers entry
He used Google Earth
Turns out you don't need robot
But you know how we developed Google Earth
So he uses historical Imaging from Google Earth
Triangulates where it is
And then they figure out
When it was
Placed in there
Somewhere between August 2015
October 26th
Alright
Not entirely sure when it happened
Probably part of the trunk
Campaign well roughly around that time
The Epic sci-fi drama Westworld was filming in a nearby
So the best at the moment is that someone on the crew either didn't pack up properly
Or maybe even use the metal slab
To play a long-term
Kubrick expire
Wow
That's from CNET
It's been used the location that they're specifically.
The filming location for
The longest
4 tons of sci-fi
Classic westerns going all the way back so yeah
It is not a super huge
Terrifying conspiracy
Certainly not
Nope and those government videos of the UFOs are pretty much
Everybody kind of figured that one out quick
The same thing that we see in Alex so often of the
Melding of faint
Tennessee in reality like movies movie
Movies being treated as if
If they were real
That's so fascinating that that's just such a
Cutest thing yeah the blending that the inability to tell the difference
It is
Is really kind of
F***** up
But the ability to mix
Them together
Is terrified
You know
The ability to remove
From others
How to differentiate
Essentially the unwillingness to three things as they are
Absolutely
How to draw the line
Now the other thing that he does
Is almost you know he's done
A ton of videos on the Mandela effect
That whole thing that one's funny yeah I mean it's it's very annoying but this one I did find it
Okay
Different dimension in 2021
People not just because
2021 we're all transported back to our original dimension
Okay number one was talked about the New Year's Eve ball drop so if you're watching
Dimension to the other nms of the time
Wow yeah
Yeah
Here's why this isn't
That
What is one of the ones that
Felt more clear these f******
Blankets
That that
To me is like okay you're taking this seriously
He's not even
Exactly
Zumiez
The bummer
Here's the other
He is taking it
In a very
Weird hat
Serious way he's mocking VI
Idea that we are in a and alternative
What he is
Actually like serious about that
Is
Mandela
Tri-City said he was obsessed with
Yeah so the Fruit Loops stuff
It is something that he believes
But the alternate
Stuff is something that he's obvious
Joking about
Yeah somehow they're both in the same 30
F****** sex
You can
You have a limited amount of time
And you have to deal with
Stuff
Exactly the same that you care about Evan is a joke
That's disoriented really f***** my head up all of
And the thing that interested in this is I was like
There's definitely an explanation for this fruit loop ship
Losing their minds aren't generally is 4
Mandela effect
Text
I mean I've looked into it and
Fruit Loops was originally called
Froot Loops
Spelled like fruit
Alright 1959
Now
Before they
Continue with that
There was a lawsuit
From
Who is like hey
There's no f****** fruit
You can't call it Fruit Loops
You will
You make people think there's fruit in it
So they had to change
Did the 20
That's it
It's always been that way since 1959
Or
We live in a
Alternative
For you and now we're back
To the normal one
I mean well you know
You thought covid was what bit but he was it a
Mature
Yep I was interested to find out
We're Fruit Loops
Yeah yeah I think
I think that if you take the time
Almost everyone
Of those
Weird
Mandela effect
Is very
Explainable
Although it does it does
Exploit
Something that is
Really Universal is like
Wait a second
I thought it right thought this happen
Powerful feeling
That you can
You can manipulate people with
Especially if you put it in the same videos
This other stuff that
Bulshit
You are a giving people this feeling of like
You're right that's not what I thought it was
Wait I thought it was
Berenstein Bears so now I'm in the state of life
Now I don't know what things
Used to be
Sure and you end up entering a space where you distrust your own perception
Oh that's
That's dangerous
Oh yeah
Yep yep
I would
The last clip is we don't need we don't need to do that one again essentially the clip is just him saying like
Is Mars getting less red
And then conspiracy theories for why we don't
See it it's it's not as red as it is
Picture and the obvious answer to that is
It's not red
It never was
Ocean verret
OSHA
And then he goes on to say did you know
Right
That humans used to live on Mars
And then they took all the resources
And moved to Earth
And then
Alright what they're going to do is they're going to take all of the resources from Earth
I move back tomorrow
Totally makes sense
That is
Essentially the plot of Mission to Mars
Starring Gary
It is again that movies
Confused with real real
Like over and over and over again
Yep
Now the thing that
It's me about
This kid and again it's a it's a it's a it's a child
I'm not going to to be like
But with these videos
So often
This is just a theory
Please no one come out
You know I am in no way claiming this is real just a theory I don't want anyone coming after
This level of like
I'm going to say my b*******
And I'm going to give myself this
Distance of like
I I don't have to
I don't have to
Account for any of this don't come after me you know I'm just taking other people's ideas repackaging them for you
You and you're somehow calling me a member of this problem
I'm take
These ideas that are patently ludicrous and doing no due diligence in terms of
Disseminating with the
Caveat that like this isn't true
But right here is the reality
Instead
Instead I'm just going to funnel it to you it with a wing
And like maybe it's real
Responsible for the same time I'm going to put stuff that is just regular old
Mainstream information out there you know the regular stuff
And I'm just going to mix those all together and I'm not going to take responsibility for a single thing about it
This is the thing
The
Andrea Marks Road
Goats Rolling Stone article
About
Tik-Tok and how it's you know
Going insane
So they talk to she talk to
And he said
I've always from a young age been really obsessed
With the what-ifs and things that don't seem like reality
Different sample the holy unsubstantiated theory that Wayfair traffic
Children
One that was circulated widely in qanon
Right
It's something that I read about
This is Andrea
Tiret about that and it
Genuinely trouble
Quote
From TY I came across an article about it that made me concerned until I thought
Posting it with
Spread that
Adding that he had not realized the theory is popular among qanon who believe a satanic pedophile
Call teze
And then he just says I didn't even know it's like a very white ring
Right-wing theory if I'm being honest
And that
Is such
Most chilling s***
To hear from a person with
10 million views on a
Conspiracy video
Yeah yeah because
You do like
It seems like
A point that a thing
It should be made it like it's less about
Him
And it's more about
This
This information dissemination
Technique and strategy
Is being used
Quite effectively luntik
Like
You do end up like
Oops
I accidentally did a blood libel
I wasn't even that I wasn't trying to and I believe that he probably wasn't
I'm trying to
I'll but the effect that it can have
Is equivalent to
We did
M2
Yeah I was I was
Was trying to come up with like a
Conclusion like a summary of
What it what what does
What is this mean and what is it
It should be what should we take away from it
I mean he's an eighteen-year-old kid
He started this when he was 16 all he wants to do is be famous on Tik-Tok and he did it
Yeah good for him
She found
The wave that destroys the world to become famous on Tik-Tok
Just bread
Bulshit conspiracy theories and get famous for it
And
Again it's not like his fault he's not maliciously doing anyting he's not writing or faking or making
Not b******* right right
Yeah
It's it's
. like a negative thing
He's doing it
The absence of the positive element that he needs to
Exact
It's a it's a
The crime of omission
And the more I kept going the more is like maybe there's there's something about the interview no like
Maybe we should
I have a life
It's like we do for Car-X
And the more I thought about it the more I've just come to the kind of
Conclusion that
I don't think Humanity can engage with the internet response
As a whole
Yeah I don't think it's just I don't think it's possible
I wonder about that myself like I think early on what are you doing this
This bike has like my
Prescription for everything
Was just like education
And I think that is still definitely something that's very important but
But I don't know if that's
Necessarily the
The full deficiency
Our brains
Do you know we've had
Thousands of years of
Development
The the introduction
Turn of the internet
And the way that information
And can be spread
It's Sonu
And so his ass
Right and we may not have caught up
Not maybe
Able to maybe we will be better
Eventually but
No see that's
That's why if I
Felt like it was really important to go to Tik-Tok
And see what
The kids are
To a certain extent
Old names what are the kids doing
He didn't start
When he was 25
Right right you started on
Somewhere you started in what it would be the accessible medium of the
The time which was local Access TV
You know that there's the
What would you do what you can
And back then
You get
A platform
The internet didn't exist The Gatekeepers
Do a broadcast television wouldn't allow you on so you got to go to local access
Now you have
Tik-Tok you have so many
Internet
Platforms
Where you can build your own thing
Yeah yeah
Yeah yeah I know I just I just feel like
What I'm watching
When I see this this kid is
The ultimate
Reality that
The internet
In the real world cannot
Coexist
Because he's trying to make them
He's trying to exist both
Fantasy and reality
Taneous Lake
And have it not be harmful to anyone you know and you just can't
You just can't
You know like I don't
I think
Should
Do this I don't think you should
Stopped I don't know if I have I shouldn't you know if somebody should not allow him to do this but I don't
I think he I think if he was
Thoughtful person
He could really get
Get through cuz he's not an insane
You know
Far-right
Nut Job
Kind of guy
Something like if he was like really just educated himself
She would himself come to the
Conclusion what I'm doing
Yeah
Yeah it's
I don't understand
You can't even conceive of
How you would set up
System where people are not allowed
To get off track
Pretty quickly
I think we need to
Do a better job of
Make it helping people recognize
The actually what they're doing
You know you're making a choice to do something and you think the choice you're making
To do this
You you might think that this is neutral
Right
Actually bad
You don't realize
It's not your fault that you're 18 years old what do you know about f****** Fury
You know like how would you be like oh well HL Mencken said you know like what are you talking
Do you educate
But it's really weird
We have gone to the land of Tik-Tok
And it is
Except for the parts with a cute animal
That part is
I'm not Faking It episode about somebody posted
The cute little horse in the cat that get along come on
It's so fun
Yeah I appreciate you bringing this to the to the our attention you know like
Definitely a space that
I ignore
But it's not irrelevant to everybody
I think it's
Hugely relevant and I think it's
It's very impenetrable
The rest of
Society
Like I'm you know you
You don't see people writing too much about
Tik-Tok
Just because you don't I don't even know how
Like I didn't even know how to put this episode together cuz it's like oh well what are we going to talk about 30 seconds
It's very difficult to kind of get a handle on
Yeah yeah
So here we are
Well thank you thank you Dan for letting me you do this
I appreciate you stepping in
And taking a swing
But I'll be back on Monday
Until then I'm
Pretty sure we have
That's I've heard Taylor
Dot-com
Deal with it which website
We are also on Twitter
We are at
Birds
Are robots robots
And at Dollar General Store fighting I go to bed rest until then
I am neither Leo
Neo
Dzx Clark
I'm just now
And now here comes
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
I love you