Damn important
Pray I have a great respect for this knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
Jordan
What's up
My brakes are officially mentioned this on the show but I have finished
Survivor
A lot of thoughts on it but I might be another medium somewhere else at a future date
But
There's a survivorship hole in my life
To be honest
As much as years from now Dan sub stack is all survivor
I'm sorry baby
Think that I was annoyed of kind of bored by the show
At various points
Good show
It has a good
Matches like
A good environment to see the
Any of the people interacting and there's fun games or
And there's tension
I know there other shows like it but like
I tried to watch The Amazing Race and it didn't do it for me
Life is really struggling
Finally found something that kind of works that I'm a
Enjoying
Hey it's called
The world's toughest race
The Eco challenge in Fiji
I think I saw that one
Yeah it's a Bear Grylls hosted
Like a ridiculously hard
Race Across Fiji
And just
I find myself compelled by the
I find them charming and I find the locale
And what they're forced to do to be
Interesting enough
Capture my attention
So
The Survivor
The bug has been
Hitched
Trapstorno you wanted to start the Amazing Race from the beginning as what I did
Problem is you got to start with the first season that they have the Globetrotter
On there and then you're like I'm in
As long as these Globetrotters are teaching me lessons growing as friends
Expressing
Hyper-real love goose
Delaware I was thinking taco
Meadowlark
I don't remember any idea other classic drive like
I went I went when I was a kid
And Boston Globetrotters I'm over being a lot of fun
Even though I was a kid and I was like this is again
That's the rule
I don't know if you're allowed to grow
Confetti out of a bucket if someone did remember thinking like this is not
What time what's it what's your birthday
Yeah that would be my bright spot Dan is
Begun
Basic obedience training with my dog Jake
That's great he's not a bad dog
He's a sweetheart he's scared of everything that we're we're learning we're growing together
The dog trainer is
The dog trainer makes you feel like you're getting your money's worth she's got that kind of like
No Nonsense
I trained dogs and now I'm training you know like that kind of vibe
You are a dog I went in there and I was immediately like a yes or no roll over until you
My belly I don't give a s***
I got to learn
What date I look forward to some Adventures for you and Jake
It's because it's not a training of likes
Something it's like a really bad dangerous Behavior like biting or anyting
It's just sort of like
Let's make
Comfortable dog
Doing that that's
The big deal
It is great
Bingo great Jordan
Episode to go over and it is wild
Yes this is one of the my God it is a roller coaster
Episodes of Alex
The show that I listen to in a very long time
Scissors October 20th 2020
That was a tile perfect
Zayas Wednesday last week
Holyshit
This thing is full of nonsense
Outrageous we've had so much we've had a bunch of different types of episode I've done an episode we got interviews I feel
So excited to get back
This type
You been up to
Let's get back into it
And here we go
So I feel like wouldn't without further Ado let's get down to our first order
A business which is
Saying hello and thank you to some new ones that's great idea
Xbox
Roblox thank you so much
Very much
Highsky we got a raptor princess in the mix hello to I signed away my soul in intergalactic
Ndaa with cyber Satan and all I got was a technocrat to say my name is podcast
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Aprilia
Barbecue your ass
It's over for Humanity
You're Beautiful song
You're coming for your balls
It's all over your God
Where is new people
Babies
Make it a
The practice of Kalinka
People pieces of garbage when they are
Hey Jude
But I always listen to that one and I think
It's so scatological where was your mind at when you work
Not together I think it was just a couple of those clips in a row at a contacts drops from recent episode
Maybe when I was going through them they were closed
Together and I just found them like a cloud
Athena's evolving
Contact drops
What's today's going to be a situation where the audience
Statues
Which one
Is the winner
Alright I'm here is Choice a
Is sexual
God
OK Google
I forgot I said it out loud again
God
Is sexual
Option b
Teenager my dad said if you turn evil I'm going to kill you and I know he was serious about it
Almost interni
Okay
Good
Alright so In that clip
He's kind of saying that honor killing is a little bit okay
But there is a time and a place for it
Is it
That's my that's my pick
They're both bewildered
Truly
We start the show off in Alex's in a place where he has battle adrenaline going through his veins
You got a big news story to cover
I can't help it have just adrenaline and
Endorphins flooding through my arteries right now
What
Thrilled
Well actually starting in
The swords clashing in the spears flying
Plunging
And 130
Two countries in the last week
Income tax but
Tracking everything you do in lifetime
Then
Tax and control what you do and punish you would level social credit score
And
It's all been prepared but it's now
Being announced
So it it surprise you to learn that that's not true
Absolutely not
Yeah 132 countries didn't sign on to this Global income tax agreement upgrade a One World Government
What happened is that there have been some negotiations going on between countries and the organization for economic cooperation
Chrisman development Angel agreeing to a minimum corporate tax rate of 15%
Four countries that agreed to be a part of clear up front to
This only applies to companies with quote
Global turnover over
20 billion euros in profit
Credibility above 10%
This is really narrowly focused on companies
Yeah so you can't just take
Your money all the way to Steven pieces of
Because
When they were countries that don't have any or at very low corporate taxation
Big International businesses have
Big huge incentive
Either actually or symbolically base their business there
In order to avoid paying massive amounts of tax to their actual base
Country Outlaw tennis players live in Monaco most of the time
What happens then is that these companies move to low-tax countries are tax shelters and all the revenue that would be being paid
Into the countries they're from
Support the infrastructure and
Development of their home countries
It instead just kept by the exact
In addition to this the plan also Delta
Digital service tax
Countries are able to impose these taxes on companies that are base
Elsewhere but provide services are Goods that are consumed
Their country
Part of the proposed plan had to do with shifting away from digital service taxes and water called a unilateral measures
United States threatened tariffs against Austria Britain France Italy and Spain
As they were part of this agreement but we're opposed to drop in their digital service
Stacks
Which would have led to Verdun
Taxation
The latest news is that these five countries agreed to keep their digital service taxes in place
Until the new tax agreement the
And then they will drop them at that
Sounds good
Obviously implement
Is it going to be a challenge
It'll be difficult to make sure these giant companies don't just
Find other loopholes
Or just move to some of the countries that didn't agree to be a part of the arrangement now there's only 132 total countries
But overall this is definitely something Alex should be in favor of
If his position is one that he's against these gigantic multinational corporations having free rein
You know the deal isn't
Perfect it's moving in the direction he should
Totally
But instead we see the complete misrepresentation of what the story is even about from Alice
And Ally designed to make his audience scared of this corporate tax agreement
He's trying to trick his listeners into opposing something that would help them
Hurt big businesses
For somebody who's
Complained about how the North American Fair Trade Agreement has moved all of our jobs offshore and all this stuff you should also be
We like and we should have the money in here as well
Right it's really strange cuz
It's kind of counter to his
Larger beliefs
The way he's reporting on this story
And honestly surprised
Didn't know
Because
You leave
The show with this
Barely comes up he doesn't understand anything that's going on there
Here we go baby
Actually one of the big problems is that Alex was out late with Rogan's last night
I can be a big problem
Is a survival-of-the-fittest
Issue I mean
I don't want
But you you don't protect yourself are you really do deserve to die
But but but
The children
They don't deserve this and that's why it's the Rubicon
Alyssa after you have died
It's set up a day like I was out with the Rogan the other guys Michael malice
The children
Children die
The premise here essentially is
That the vaccines
If children are vaccinated that's the Rubicon being cross
Sure I guess
It's time to kill people
Hey are you I'm just going to throw this out there if you're hanging out with a Nazi all the time but you're not
If you're if you're Joe Rogan I mean you're willing to
It'll put up
So this b*******
That tends to mean that you believe it
At least you're not willing to separate yourself from it
I would question him about a lot of the content they were going to end up listening to on this show
Like this this is what your damn is huh challenge
You know I would choose actually pretty right about stuff
This is a
Prime episode
For them to look at and be like I dare you to defend
Let's go for
Are you
Alex
We're out in the Heat and all of his friends
All these guys were hanging out the real smart
Right I'm a mole
These are incredibly stupid
Well they're all really smart
Anyway
They believe that a giant war is coming
But probably in a giant
The consensus that this is going to end
Gigantic massive
I don't know that consensus between those
Closest Publix
Telling Tales out of school
Hey dick
Don't put my business on the street like that you know what guess what I was hanging out with Joe Rogan Michael malice
Anyways World Boogaloo boys I don't know if anybody noticed that real quick but
Civil War
Hey they don't talk about this extremism that they believe in
Some other things to learn some really interesting things
But I got couches
I'm not ready to talk about that
Charlotte from Joe
Runs with
You can probably imagine
Wiethop
Public roster
I am.
Elon Musk
Weekly tell Joanne that's not a secret it is they got to like
Madeon
What does not like we're going and he wants humans to have a future in the future
Say what you want
Weird energy
IAH
That obscenely wealthy people believe this
The poor will just eat each other alive haha it's so crazy that
Extremely wealthy people look down on the poor and think well obviously their animals who will kill each other
At the moment
Noticed
You're assuming that any of this actually comes from
People like Elon Musk over made up
Probably thinks we're all going to kill each other
He does also have a
Pastor
There we go
So I I think that
What I find more interest
Medieval
Is that Alex is having to thread a very bizarre needle here
Which is the cyborgs Roka
If they have free will
Well of course
That seems to be counter to a lot of things that he said
If you still have free will
Oh oh they turn something on eventually in there that you didn't know was in that your free will is gone
Sooner or later you just got to accept that if you get a robot arm
You're going to be controlled by the globalist what is long as you got some free will you chosen
Hitman
At work
I just think this is really dumb anyway for the Alex to try and be like
Alright maybe I can hang out with you on musk in the future I got to get in with cyborgs
How am I going to make that okay
Cyborg
Yeah he's going to want
The super speed I would assume
It's
The man loves
Speed
Dumb
He's already drawn a line elsewhere
What I'm feeling
Doesn't match up
I think you'll find a lot of people that
What would appear to be harsh boundaries are often very fungible
Through
Ounces is in a state of frustration
Episode
He has he has a
Particular thing
I think it's actually a pretty good
Criticism of people like
But then he has
To really really shity metaphors
Good Lord
Last night and this morning
That the reason I've been so frustrated and very very very very clearly
My frustration
Is that
The opposition to the new world or does it all
Piecemeal
They opposed
And that piece and this other piece
Accu
And you decided
You decide to
Focus
Hair on my foot
What
Are you talking about
Your god-like I guess
Little tiny airplane
Microsoft
What
Coming at you
That's not pull your head off
Pull your arms and legs
And a piss on you
And yeah you're looking at it coming at you and you're trying to sweet-talk and he's going to rip your head off
No URL
Breathing
And Sass
But you don't know that so you're going to get
This show is not on track
This is a Debbie
Sir can I
I understand the metaphor that he's trying already trying to illustrate is the people within the anti newworldorder Community seemed
To be missing the forest for the
Yes
Great way of shortening up a 97 trillion gorilla metaphor
Specific detail instead of looking at the bigger
Pixar yes fine
Neither of those things were great
I was blown away by everything is like what why are these the specifics
I really am surprised
Is it in a
Comb
Measured way of saying like
You know
I am going to
Kill you and you're going to try and hurt my hair
Somehow we got off track
Blew me away cuz our God like any creative tiny aircraft
At what point do you think
Well
Obviously the best way to explain my point is to give you the power to
It's a Conger tiny airplanes Kentucky
Bombay hair
And that will get the point across there is a time when you're making a metaphor they just got a quick
Airplane with missiles you know what maybe this one
I got away from the bride
Let me suggest that if I can do that right
Whatever Powers could be
I could shrink myself down and pilot that little tiny aircraft and good luck hitting me with a hatchet then
All these powers that I love like all you have her Hatchet
Can conjure airplane to make your habits tiny I'm going to run away from your house
Airplanes and then they'll become a flying carpet
And I'll get away
Oh my God
Yeah
Anyway
That's a real good kind of example of
The place is at
Nothing's making a lot of sense you know he's missing the forest for the tiny airplane
For sure
I was talked a little bit about his enemies
They have honed
Aggressive
Traits isn't what he says
Which kind of
Struck me as a little bit of a red flag
Kind of implies like
It's genetic
Their evilness I was going to say that's racist
Certainly in the neighborhood
Why would a fire ants do that's a little baby deer a little pig let her little baby bird while they climb up trees
They like the devil worshippers
Wonder why they're attacking you
Extremely honed aggressive traits of hyper dominance and an insight
Sociopathic Behavior
And they enjoy killing people
Children
Comprende
I almost turned the dark side
What are Cabrillo
She thought when they started it
Send your bag
I enjoyed strangling people
Android
I enjoyed
Enjoy it enjoy doing it to children
I think you do enjoy it
I mean the way that you described it at the very least sounds whisper
The good old days Soho and aggressive
Traits
I don't know how like
I just did doesn't sound
Didn't he described himself
As enjoying the things that would
Be the natural result of
Quote unquote
Honed aggressive
The traits I guess
I guess
You could look at that and say like
The Hound aggressive traits that he's talking about
Could be learned behavior
Literally
I heard that and I thought like well honed over generation it's not quite clear
It makes me uncomfortable
No I don't like it
I think the thing that weird
We're missing here is that Amanda said
I like strangling people
Right well I was too busy turning into a little spaceships in attacking
And they didn't bother you
Yeah I got you
Unlike the rest of you
I love strangling people
I like removing other human beings teeth against their will
You know I'm like all of you folks we get it totally normal thing for people to think and believe
So Alex is talking about how like it's all up to you know
Is that everything
Sinbad now
It's no good
Trouble
And you know what
You got to wake up
Globalstar
More worried he's going to enjoy strangling me to death
Do you like to be spanked
Because you're part of the laugh
You're going to be at
Then this is going to be cold comfort
For Alex on The Patriot
Unless they're going to be in camps as well
Or they'll be killed first
I don't know this is just one of his standard blood ramps
And so you're going to wake up to that fact and you're going to understand that or you are going
Knife and your children are going to die
With you because what you saw in Nazi Germany and what you saw on Soviet Russia and North Korea
All that he'll is going to look like
Hey choir meeting look like Sunday School look like Grandma knitting you a pair of mittens
There's something
I mean the left tries to harass me and lie about me and exactly what they say or what they do
Is there a chance of beating
Homeless
In a long protracted collapse and then being put in an emergency center camp
How this works
Is it
Mid levels
You're the smart one
2 days
The wolves
This is just
Business shows a mass
Yeah I mean
This looks like if you could see inside his mind he's just got a refrigerator with a bunch of magnets in kind of half
Half words and he's just mixing them all together and whatever comes out
Comes out
The left are going to be in camps and get where is going to be him and his buddies out in the woods
Doing better than us
And then once all of the left
Tour in the camps
Died cuz of the soft kill weapons are Global is still come to the survivors
Who are the top four rugged individualist
And be like we were just trying to separate the week from
You this was really for you
Alex
We wanted to give you the world are just so many better ways of doing
Right
You know and I mean just
Set the very least
More efficient
Write this is stupid
Yep
The kids and buy that Alex beans
They're eventually going to be vaccines for the
Covid
Center children really feels like so far all of these clips
If we got rid of the words and just had him repeating
Honestly
Except that
What you just did was to Folk
On message
They're coming for the children they've announced
The injection
A 5-11 Italy newborn with a deadly shot that Embraces her immune system
And they're going to force it
Pause
Violence and they're going to say then the people.
How do I put it on the books
The regulations that the main mission the FBI
Military the CIA
People that don't accept lockdown
I am that they are going to come and they're going to arrest everybody and start killing people
Yeah man
Yeah this is this is
Suppa's are red
In here
They're going to vaccinate children and
Then people who are against
Vaccines will
Do some
Do some stuff
I mean I guess if the FBI goes the Civil War is not all bad
Well I think that the occupation occupation with that is
I wonder where that come from I don't know
I think it's because people like Comey
And Mueller were like
Big forget to the trumpets the FBI's kind of something
Preoccupied
That might be why you feel
Looks like it's more accessible than
Then some other branches I do appreciate the idea of like
The battalions all marching and then there's
Just one for the FBI they're all where they're FBI jackets everybody else's in
Full armor and they're like
Alright we're going to get to the bottom of this real quick
Fantastic
Alex's things like you know I don't want
This massive Civil War in all this
What makes it really hard to believe is that he keeps calling the idea of vaccinating children
The shot heard round the world
Kind of sound it seems like he's building this up into being a point at which you are Justified to kill people
Scotland
And the first child has a heart attack
Throw sand
Cancel
Mine just came out last night instead
We are going to start inoculating
Halloween
All the bills called 666
2.66 shots them in the oven
Oh my God
Billion 660 million
Leave the Asus page Cardwell
Their calling card is 666
Oh boy
I promise I didn't splice up a bunch of different things to make that sound convoluted in my testicle
That was a actual string of thought
What's that Alex I had on air
Wow does it doesn't happen to the 70's after the 666 not make it invalidated
The mark of the beast
It's just like him
Being dumb and knowing that his audience will like hang onto things lighter Halloween 666
Accessible symbols
Queen and you were expected be awhile well obviously it switches
Bill Gates
Boo
A couple quick things though in this do Merit rebuttal
The first thing is actually the evidence of a connection between the covid vaccine and myocarditis is actually it's becoming weaker than
More information that we gather
What are the main studies that was used as
Support for that claim was from the University of Ottawa heart in
Institute headline that claim
It one-on-one thousand people vaccinated develop
Myocarditis
This was from a preprint study and in the process of peer review is discovered that they used the wrong number
For the total number of vaccines administered
Switching wildly throughout their results
BP store number on 30
82 myocarditis incidence
In 30 2379 vaccinations
When the number was actually 845 thousand
930 vaccination
That's a little bit
Little office
Retracted by the authors who apologize for the error but people like Alex in the Gateway pundit who screamed about it if never acknowledged
Retraction
There's not a cover-up of people having heart attacks
It's something that was seen as a possible
Full side effect that
Examined
Substantiate
But there is a significant increase.
Dinosaur pericarditis
Can people who
Been vaccinated
Although as more information comes along the understanding of these things will
Will develop
Right I have no idea who Alex is talking about when he says that other people covering up vaccine-related resignation
But if you wants to get more specific I'll look at it at that point
I'm pretty sure he's just to talk about that story from a while back where two people at the FDA resigns and I analysis
Decided to exaggerate
Always announces their evil plans on Halloweens though
That's that's pretty exciting
Today announced on Halloween new ghost costumes
Also according to the White House the actual timetable of vaccinations for children ages 5 to 11
Quote will depend on the independent FDA and CDC process
Timeline
What are planning efforts
Me and it will be ready to begin
Shots in arms in the days following the final CDC recommendation
In the same press release they mention that the cdc's committee meeting to discuss this
He's scheduled for November
3rd 2nd and 3rd
So I'm going to guess
They're going to miss these spooky deadline of Halloween Evil plan
It really would have been fun to hear those like
Oh there's a razor blade in this and the candy at this house instead it's like
Those people
F****** vaccinate you
Do you walk up there they're like here's some Eminem's in them
Immune to disease there's a Pfizer vaccine in my Apple
Terrified
So Alex is another headline about
Forced vax
It's a little off
Here it is covid
Teams cannot vaccinate pupils against parents wishes schools toll
Australia
In Latin American countries as well
You just you're going to do it
What that sounds like
That causes convulsions and death and heart attacks and and and
Blood clots and strokes
Dad comes up to the school and when you know what that does to you
What does that oh my God
Oh my God
The anti-vax terrorist
We all want that by the way
What
Whoa
Terrorist
Oh boy
Exercising is
Very dark
Yeah that's a headline that Alex is basing this
The Killing school nurse is on its from the guardian
Article from September
I just has to do with how vaccinations would be carried out in
Schools in England
As it stands quote
In cases where parents withhold consent but the child w
What's a go-ahead the guidelines say the vaccination teams will determine if a child is able
How to make an informed decision
Known as
Gillick competent
And make every effort to contact a parent in check
Before they proceed
He's only relates to students
Between the ages of
12 and 15 and it's a pretty narrow window of application
If a parent doesn't want their child to get vaccinated and the child also doesn't want to be vaccinated there is no vaccine
If a child apparent disagreed the first effort will be to
To determine if a child is gillick competent
How to make your own battle
Decisions
If they are not being competent
Then they will not be vaccinated
In the parents words
If they are deemed competent then they will be vaccinated
But before that every effort goes into trying to reach agreement
Between the child and their parents
This article has absolutely nothing to do
But student than any other country it has nothing to do with anyone being forced to be vaccinated
Reporting this story is almost tailor-made to Insight someone toward the very violence
He's pretending to not be in favor of absolutely
Cockroach Jesus
Also that's
That's such a silly
We live in 2021 the kids are going to be like
Are you sure you can choose this we're going to have to call your parents in like
Dude they believe in q
What the f*** are you going to say to them but going to convince them to fax
Fascinate me I can read the internet I'm going to go give me the f****** back day
Yeah and very litigious age we are in
Going to be a situation where people are like
Let me poke you
Just come over
School is gone out of existence can donate blood and I'll give you a vaccine
I want under attack do Jordan
What time in School nurses are about to be alive
Call Leonard
You're not in Kansas anymore
The collapse is already here
Everywhere total Psychopathic murderer
I'm going to want to follow up
Next week
And the week after that
I would like to know who he knows who got the vaccine and whether or not they are still alive
How are you saved
Just have covid
Maybe
I also would like a follow-up in a week when he's in a little better mood and everyone
It's not going to die
What happened to others that he's not crabby
Oh yeah it does seem to be that he's kind of just taking stuff out on us
Feel like this is abusive
Yeah kind of feels like maybe he's pissed off about the safety hook lawsuit
That not going
To a trial for him to have fun with
And then also maybe you didn't get enough sleep cuz he was out with a rogue in the night before
Everyone's going to die
Yeah and it just comes out as like
Complete nonsense
Gibberish
All the scientists that were even on the payroll
Basically
Believed in the poison vaccine to the training vaccines and the human cloning all that I thought it was really
Develop
Hypertension for themselves and others
We're really just going to kill everybody
You know we're not going to get away with this where they're going to kill us
You say
Roll a die 200 yeah you're all going to die
Who is figure this out
That out yet
You just said we did boy
Wild what a wild thing to do disorienting and some of that like
I am
I don't even know how to
Lego appropriately set up a lot of these clips
To make that make sense
I get with you
He's talking about
Just from Context Clues
But if you were to listen to this cold it would be
Very bewildering
Yeah yeah yeah
Talking about a claim
That is not true at all of the scientists who were in favor of the
Shots at the FDA and the CDC in
All these places have turned on the vaccine
And are now coming out with it and
Part of the reason that they're coming out against them
Is it they realize that the plan isn't
Kill 90% of the population
They're also not going to survive
But they didn't do any of that
Not even
You know here's what I would
Like if I was growing up
Say I was 11 or 12
And my dad was pretty unstable
But everytime he had a hangover and it at the
Disable before I went to school he would say
You're going to die if you go to school today
You would think that's an abusive man
Yeah right
Point that out when I was listening to
Complete nonsense gibberish
I don't even know how to categorize it if you were somebody who didn't listen to Alex
It would be disorienting you probably turn it off
I listen to him I understand right
Just makes me more sad
I would almost call this weaponized nonsense
I think you nailed is a little bit just like
It's the mood
The feeling
I could use a snack
Here's where we take our first loop-the-loop
In the roller coaster that is in the show
Okay Alex starts talking about
And it's about time I was worried that after the 666 we weren't going to get anything after that might be
A couple of Clips here
Need to be Mike.
Here's the first
You know I'm not one that
Afraid of things
Agenda confront them
I need Jesus to
Take control of me and in not
Let me just
Everybody else is joining with it out fear
Almost everybody's joining it out of your nuts there's not a lot of people seething with the power of Lucifer in their hand
That's the people
And if you don't
The powerless proceeding in your hands
Nazi
Lucifer
I got the power
I don't want it
And I
Rejected
But I'm telling you he's a gentleman
This year's the Takeover
This is the one ring
Oh boy
So Alex apparently can see Satan because he has the power of Satan right through his hands what you were Jack
Xprite
Wooboi
I mean a Rogan what do you think of this
Going on right now huh needs to intervene for his
Health and safety
I mean I said that
A year ago but I mean at just like
If you are if you heard this
And you're on the radio you should be like
Well we got to stop with all this political stuff I'm an Infowars fan
I need to make sure Alex is going to be okay I feel like it 100 like serves him right in there we need to
I feel like if a hundred of his longtime listeners got together they should be able to 5150 up
Absolutely
Competition out there in absolutely happen
Yeah he can he can see the devil
Cuz the devil
He's running through his hands which is something
That is only allowed in a power that is the people who are above Bill Gates
Which implies that that is the level that Alec
Text belongs on
But he is a reject
Did it to help you Jordan
To help you see the lights
So he can tell you who the demons are understand the impulse to follow someone who's very
Openly says
I can at any point in time
Act as strongly and is evilly as the devil all I have to do is pick up this evil
Bright right and you better you better by my Turbo Force or else I might be
I would very much appreciate
If I'm going to go pick up the devil
Willpower
It takes like 30 seconds
So hard for me to pick up the devil's hour
Very bad
To think
Power of the devil is
Accessible to somebody who is
So moody
I think about all of that s*** where we will like all women shouldn't be president
Conover so we have some powers of the devil
God
It it's
A little a little rich
Man mentioned being charged
Anything
I don't know I don't know why he does this but
Abusers
Oh this is what I wanted to say
I honestly don't care if he believes this or not
Like somebody it might say like
Will you take it you actually believe that he thinks he has the devil's power running through him or whatever
And my response to that is he either does Believe it or he is a sane person rationally deciding to
Pretend that on are on a show like his
And neither is
F****** awful doesn't require
It's a belief
To work backwards from what he just said and say
Oldest person
If you are if you are choosing to say those things without believing that clearly an insane person
Maybe more Danger
Probably play
It's the one ring
And that's why Lord of the Rings it's so powerful by j.r.r. Tolkien until the top professors
I got to stop even right there for
This real quick
Website Rate My Professor
Off-the-charts on Netflix
Beyond minion psychology
Because
When they can't even thinks about taking the reins even
Even observing the ring
Look at what they're doing
Into the mind of
That's very
Literally starting
Man
That's why sometimes I have to go up there because
Just I reject the devil
I completely rejected
So I
I don't know
I wish
Did I could go back in time
And have a recording of me hearing that for the first time
Because the blurt laugh that I made I don't know if I can ever recreate it
It would such a huge laugh
What a f******
Stowaway
Yeah but I forgot I have to go off air when the power of the
The devil becomes too tempting to make
Ever
I don't think you understand it don't try to understand it
And to just
Just I mean it listen
I just
Looking into the f****** palantir right now the eye of Sauron is upon me
And I can't do the show
I'm sorry I put my hand on it now I'm controlled by Sauron it's over for me
And that's all because
Of what
One of the top present professors in history
You told me right
Sprite
I do I think I had some pretty good professors in college I wonder how they drank at school
I mean
I don't think I would Rate My Professor
You have a great idea for a couple semesters of formal logic
Took a game theory class from him that I wasn't even interested in because he was an intern
Compressor
Probably not as good as Tolkien
I mean my high school English teacher
Professor
He was actually a first-class playwright
In New York
4 likes
15 years
And then he was just so sick of it that it was like fine I'll teach high school English in the middle of nowhere
Browser
So what you got understand
Is that the devil has a lot of schemes
And I wants to seduce you with things
Phone who does
You know your phone
Yeah
Mark of the beast no
It's an alien brain
You know what these really are these so-called
Phones
Are super high tech
Computer
Platform
Are the brains of robots
Come when I call a
Android phone Android it is
The brain of an Android know
And
This is to take control of your life and just run everything
Seductive
I'm coming out I've seen it
I have them
And the iPhone nuts
13 or 11 is coming out about a month or whatever
I had a chance to look at one and it's just
Fallen technology
Old
What are we doing
The devil has improved the camera
Is it just no no I reject that when they call it an Android that's
F*** off when they call it an apple that's because it's made of Apple
That's dumb get out of here go away
Old Scratch Out Here
Old Scratch Out Here making your camera better
Tell me what this is still going to be like Old Scratch over there
How did like he's pretty interested in this new phone is it better than anything you could imagine
Wow
Very dumb
You goes to break and he comes back and like lives
Just doing dramatic voice-over type s*** about the end of the world
Foretold of old
Old Testament prophets Thousand Years
The alien attack on Earth takes human form
Anyone that exception
Destroy
That's basically what he wants to do all the time
It's clear that that's like his passion
Kind of
The Empire and the rebels have
$6
You want to do last time on
Yes what times
Yeah absolutely
Hoof
In the Book of Revelations
Right
We were going to end up
Situation where the globalist
They're going to cut off all food
And then eventually they have another plan and that is Truth and Reconciliation committee
Which actually
The globalist
If you if you believe this
They tried to get Alec
Text to do what
And then they're just going to cut the food off next
If you want food
You're going to have
And you were wrong and that you were a fraud
Reconciliation communist thing they do that's already begun here
I know that got me to 300 meetings.
My Little Falls
Highest levels directly obviously reach out to us
And
You said you just need to come do a true reconciliation
Call Jeter and we'll make it bigger never bad
The only protection
In this dangerous world
No thank you
If you do I tell you that it's real right
No
If I have to filter through my like what
He could be
We possibly talking about I'm going to guess that it's some point he had an offer from a network like Fox News
Who's that recognize that
He had a lot of talent
And he was somebody who maybe they could find a place for on the network sure and what would need to happen but
Before they could have him on
Is
Never contracted some kind of a public cleaning up of his image
Maybe there's some sort of an apology they make for something
I could give you a job that would be really high paying
On this News Network
It's not the communist
Trying to get a Truth and Reconciliation committee go
If this is even based on anything that actually happened that's the version of it that I kind of believe could be
Here's what I'm starting to
Okay
People have been saying that Alex
Who is Bella
CNL
And that's very
Clearly not
Trail right we've been watching a 20-year 25-year long-form improv schedule
Alex is actually delclos that's what it is he does seem a bit
See that's what how do you spell The Herald
Cowboy
I don't know I think the delclos might be a better actor than this
Because Alex starts talking about how he got this offer with the truth and Drake
Conciliation
He starts talking about how he's
Is he was at least boardrooms
I meant it turns into him talking about how he lived that scene in network
Out of here
I meant Alex does a lion reading
You know like in the Big Board rooms
In d.c.
Boardrooms in New York
Boardrooms in Los Angeles
Montreal all those cities
Pool
Howard Beale speech
Network is that speech
Think you just
A business deal with the bill
It's not a business deal
Church
Exhaust system
You are a unit
Of this church
And I'm miserable in the final equation we're going to destroy your soul
I got your attention thermocouple
12 inch screen
Countries and borders and Nations and people
There are no Nations there are no
There's only
Corporations and Company
Each of us is just a little piece of that
Larger
And Missy you're obsolete mr. bill
Your non-essential mrmeola and we're going to kill you mr. meal
We're going to give you the same speech that you've given throughout history
I'm going to clean this time it's for a good cause and we're of the favors the world
But the truth is Mister Beale we don't like you cuz you're smarter and better-looking Minaj. Can I get the God and we want to
Hurt you in a ritual
Mommy
Are we still in the movie I don't remember this fight
Where do the copies of your children
So
Are you going to join us mr. bill
Get you a little off track from Network
You know mr. Jones I feel like that was I think that was great I think we've seen all we need to see
We will be getting in contact with your agent of Michael Savage's phone number
Appomattox review
Michael Richards
Yeah I think I think that some of the beach
Beats of the networks
Buffalo
Added a few Mr Smith Goes to
So I just keeps going
Stupid Beyond satire
Also you're not going to join us
But you're going to fail and you know you're going to fail we're going to beat you or going to be Humanity
Course we are
If you won't join us
So now you'll notice has turned into a dialogue instead of a monologue of this character giving the speech
Now Alex exist within the
The seeing
And he's talking back to the person which is a
Fascinating gramatik
Turn
What it looks like
Nelson
I really need to do that
Infowars.com tomorrow's news today it's a demon
Somebody there was like we got to get him off of this we're going to throw on I'm 96 lb beam
I bet he's going to have no choice but to switch into
People will be right back
Yeah just can't not do it free soft mellow music
People fix everybody
My God that's
Beyond satire that is just as you can't do that you can't do that
Somebody working there has to
To be like
That has to be a choice
That's on purpose happens enough
That they're like it
Stop the music is so disjointed from what
Two glaring that music
Release not frequently
That's like them we're going to be back at Applejack we're having technical difficulties f****** theme music
Let's all go to the lobby there might as a yes that's exactly what that was
So you may be noticing
This point that we have not
Covered a lot of content
There's been a lot of Alex having a weird mood
There hasn't been really a ton of actual meat
You know I was thinking I haven't heard you read from a lot of note
What's so far has been listening to a man screaming incoherently
Yeah
Any plays another one
Okay let's play a report
And then
I may be able to control myself and actually cover all this
Doubt it
This little piece of paper
Right here is the death warrant of our children literally
Add
So he's going to cover but he's not
Got to go to another grease report
Vine
Kick the Can down the road will see you see if we get to it when we get to it
You know I'm going to I'm just going to say it
You know
You've got the death warrant literally
In your hands
Them admitting it is really kind of
True
Exactly
So I heard
This was just me desperate for
Anything to
To talk about
Oh just stay inside for 15 days and it'll all be over in the course it wasn't
Are you so you would have a 15-day
Don't leave your house
Areas of Africa and Latin America under imf-world May control
Still locked in their houses
1 hour day
Excuse me
Some areas of Latin America you get
2 hours a week
According to your
Social security number
What numbers
All of that is coming here
So the first obvious thing that jumps out as a sign that Alex is making this story up is he saying the people in Africa and Latin American countries
I'll get time outside based on their social security number
Yeah that one
I don't know when the Social Security Administration expanded operations
Include the entire world but unless that happened and I didn't hear about it
Social Security numbers are just something that people in the United
Well I mean f
CR Truman followed that up by expanding Social Security
Route to the
To the world
For someone who's so concerned about immigration related issues Alex should really know this
Super Bass
Sick thing that intersects with
Student visas and
Ford workers
All these things that he yells about all the time but that
People being groped by social
Security numbers is kind of a big part of his long-standing
FEMA camp narrative or should I think it might be something that he's pulling from there
At the draft
That kind of thing
Actually referring to although
I have to admit that I may be making
So the financial times has a tracker on their website that updates
It's on covid lockdown policies
On a country-by-country basis
They have this hope
Big paper where a number of political scientist
From Oxford develop what they call a stringency index
All the precise details over there too complicated for us to get into here but suffice it to say that they took indicators like
School closings restrict
Gathering
And stay at home requirements
Did the consideration
And they created a means of quantifying lockdown wrist
Naturally this is a figure the changes for any given
And Country over time but the lockdown tracker is regularly updated
The only two countries in Africa over a 75 out of 100 are Uganda and Namibia
And in Latin America
There are just too also it's Venezuela and Argentina
All those countries only Namibia and Venezuela are over in 85
Looking over the qualifications and rankings if you had a country making people stay inside for all but two hours in a week
It would have to be over 85 on the scale just on how highly they would score and all the other categories
Would be a domino effect
Good website for the US Embassy in Namibia their latest update was from October
20th 2021
If you look at that updated restrictions Daryl loud
To go to public Gatherings up to
The 200 people
Fitness centers pools beauty parlor schools
Open grocery stores are all open
You can't buy booze on Sunday or on holidays unless you're staying at a hotel or a casino
Hotels
Casinos are open
Desert camping Namibia that Alex is talking about sound like
What about Venezuela
It's got to be Venezuela
Reporting I've seen Venezuela's actually
Closer to what Alex is saying but he's still wrong
The government in Venezuela had been trying and at
Speed implemented what was the 7 by 7 plan where they would alternate weeks of strict lockdown rules
And lacks locked
Down rules
During the last week's most businesses and public spaces could operate normally but during strict weeks
Only essential businesses were open
And
I can't find any evidence building
To stay inside their homes or anything
The government also has been operating a fuel.
Distribution schedule since the end of last year
Where Vehicles could
I'll be fueled on specific days based on the last number of their license
So it's the last number of your social
Keeping up with the Social Security
I'm not entirely sure
But also according to the outlet
Venezuela analysis quote
Maduro announced
Also announced that the country would
Suspended 7 by 7 model
It's all a week of strict lockdown followed by a week of more relaxed
Text measures
Instead barring any outbreaks the country would abide by looser measures from the
The start of November until the end of the year
As part of an attempt to boost economic activity
So very recently this
This whole plan was going to go by the wayside by the present
I don't know what else is reporting on but
Nonsense for a bunch of this episode and I kind of wanted to learn something
Another we talked about
Some details of the real world
Here is back to our regularly scheduled um program
We're dead already
I think you just need to get used to that and understand it's about your spirit not the body
Hellboy
Gypsy now I'm just
Hearing that 90s music in my head all day
You're not a bother you need to stop being attached to your body
You're a soul
You're dead already
Murphy's
Demon face
It's not going to leave me for a long time though
Ethel Davis bespoke
I just feel like it
It's something that
I could go into a song
Somehow
It's
Goofy
I'm waiting for lin-manuel Miranda to follow-up Hamilton with the
Infowars
Music Hall
Called
Infowars
Colon
It's a wild things that I really love to is it so clear that like he just run out of things to say
And like had the couple seconds out of hell
Totally it was just a little came out of
I love it if there no no intention behind it and didn't mean to happen
Just out there
I know that
A lot of people in Alex's communities on his friend
And stop
They want to kill FBI
But
Even if you do kill all of them
It really wouldn't matter
You shouldn't do it it really wouldn't help
Which is somewhat confident
They're going to try to trick you
Into becoming like them
And running around murdering each other did it almost no one even understands this
You can tell a country
That makes sense
Nothing's going to happen
Because
That doesn't mean we let him take us to FEMA camps and kill us this is the discussion
We got a case of
Germany on Russia
On PCP
We are we are
Control
They want to crush
Humiliate Americans
Your guns that are going to take your food medicine away
We've been hit by a biological attack
We're in the middle of a biological War
With mega-corporations
World government
And the chairman of the board
Is a fallen off-world entity
Yeah I just
This is
If you believed any of this wasn't bulshit you'd be
F****** firing out your window
I would have
Disregard just like every everything yeah if you believe
Any of this was real if you believe any of this was real
Being on the radio would be too much of a risk you need to be dug in Wasilla
Sandbags and wire around
You need to
Somehow burn all your identifying documents live underground
You know like the developer full-on Breakaway Society underneath the Getty like you were always meant to
The implications of
The things that he's pretending
To believe
Are so staggering
That it's
Dumb to think
That he'll be doing what he's doing absolutely
That's nonsense the idea of if there was a bioweapon released
That is a
Beyond Reason
You know like I've asked you can't
You can't
Unjustify everything if there was a biological weapon released upon the People by its own government right
Rules are out the window
Why are people reporting on the Supreme Court total government is released
Do you need to like
I could get your neighborhood together and like
Do something
I don't even know what you do but you do so yeah yeah it has to be a complete break away a collective
Radio show about those for you kind of skim headlines and then a ram
Campbell
Spell dumb pills should I do
Do the change thing
I know
Make people buy
Pills I did
Kind of gift
The feeling
More so than normal that he's killing time
Like it really felt to me while I was listening to this that this is just like wow
I'm going to run out the clock
Here comes the
Horseman
And the writer on it was named as
Brave brave brave brave
Wow
Yeah
The spirit of antichrist is surging on the planet right now
And
Change disciples
Very excited
Because they are rolling headlong over the edge of a cliff and when you're falling off a cliff
Piles Jagged broken
Putting
Iron Spike sticking up
It's exhilarating isn't it
Did the class
This is killing time
Yeah
That's that's one of those things where it's at
You didn't do the homework
When do the homework
And you're just tapping on the desert wow can't believe somebody would like to a Horseman Called Death
Somebody was just like hey
You didn't do the f****** work keep it up
Hell I got God how dare you accuse me of not doing nothing over-prepared that's why I'm doing this
Apotheke La Petite clock
Oh man
I asked you this from time to time
That's the bees that are being written by
The Horseman of famine that terrifies me
I asked you this from time to time
And it's never fair
I don't never get it right
But what is the global
Hosta plant
I feel like we've already established that they're going to
Withhold food from us to get us
To do their bidding
Will be some food involved
Yeah trying to kill 90% of us
Wow
Ono Ono
Okay here's our plan
100% survey
No
One's a little bit racist
Demons
God's Amazing Creation
But I like
I don't have that in mind
Uno
It is just a launching point for us into the third dimension and Beyond that's a normal thing I said
Josh and dominion over it by
The Establishment has decided
Going to be
And so to create a self-fulfilling prophecy they have Grease the skids for the collapse of Humana
Show that those of us that have not collapsed Wheels
Be tempted in the end to join with
The Darkside
To save ourselves and help exterminate the Giant
I don't control several populations that
Will be
Traveling across
Cross the Earth
Army of
Locust
Chewing everything down to bone
You look like
They'll have a new blood
Paw Patrol games
I won't be Undead
Anime mouth psychology
Psycho
Sprint
So now apparently the globalist yeah
I'm struggling to understand this plant so could you give me the full rundown I think
Just sorta
Glanced over a couple of the first step
I like the covid lockdown destroy the food supply or whatever
So you know developing countries everybody please from them
And that's their plan is the globalist
Plan is to try and make a Civil War by bringing
Immigrants in
Then Alex will have to have a civil war Exterminating
Them
See now I feel like I'm going to throw this out that Alex doesn't want to do that I'm going to throw this out there
What if
Now here's a whatever
And this is going to blow Alex's mind all right what if we
Work
The globalist plan
Buy instead of starting a civil war over immigrant
We accept
And then we all get together
And fight against the globalist together
No
Oh well
Can see that I have not yet convinced you
Continuously
Okay will do this is becoming an intractable situation is it not
Yeah well you can't really fight the tide over the globalist plan
Civil War in the immigrants are the way to do it then
Birthday plants by just enjoying and then I'd liking the buddy you don't seem to understand
Immigrants
I just need a large-scale justification for my actions
Very wrong
But I need to be able to sleep at night so it's got to be part of the globalists plan that is forced to exterminate
People who don't look like
Yeah it does feel like a lot of this show
Today
Is just
Him trying to
Express
That he is
Filled with nothing but
Violin
Rage
And the impotence
His inability to express it in anything resembling a healthy manner
Is just what we're seeing through work
He's just hoping that somebody else will carry it out for him
Yeah I just hoping that somebody that listens to a show will cause some kind of a disaster that he can call a false flag
And then he can
Get that cycle going
Yep but you can't do anything on his own without
It just seems boring whole of actor in
Violence I mean you see what he's doing
And it is app
Absolutely the case that
Like when we bet his first description of the night before is like
Oh you guys are all
Boogaloo boys
That's what it is
You're just saying that the two Awards, acceleration is 9:50
That's what it's looking like
Thankfully
At long last
Alex gets grounded
You know this is the best
Start
Libby call about this
Let me first show you exhibit a
FDA
Policy
And it's got the stamp on it
Talked about so much
August 23rd
2021 this is what
This is what binds talking about
This is the
Testing
On babies and children
And I knew that well we didn't
Call Troy
It's okay we'll just do
We'll test it on babies and
Migraines
Only two strokes
Very exciting new way to mispronounce myocarditis
Wow
Surgical asked me to figure out what Alex is talking about something super vague
Eventually he does give the document number that he's looking at
But it's presented in such a way that it's useless
Also I guess that big news that he's lawyer friends are planning to break has been broken he just broke
Last breath.
Yeah
I mean maybe he's really confident that no one's actually listen
Probably
So what what's going on is Alex's mind has been blown
And he's acting like a violent little baby on his episode because he found a letter from the FDA to Pfizer and by
Text that they're biologics license application had been
Approved
Letter from
Back in August
I need a new drug that needs to need to apply for one of these to be allowed
To engage in interstate commerce and this is just that approval letter
It's not Nifty a policy whatever Alex thinks that means I don't know what that mean
But this is exhibit a of his
Excited for Matlock to make a case. Cuz so far this is thin
The rest of the exhibits better be stepping it up to kind of account for this
Can I make a spoiler WhatsApp
This is not going to go to it is not going to be in our favor
Alex tries to read a little bit from this letter and
That's why I thought I was reading from page 5 of this.
Stn bl125 742
4 / 0
At the annual report
Ingles gas report on
Post-marketing studies requirement
Commitments
And it talks about
Pediatric studies c459 1001
Evaluate
Vaccine in children 12 years
15 years
And it's commentary in children
12 years through 15 years of age
Describe how it's a
There their they're saying it's a
But it's actually prove in the future
When they think they're going to
See how that works
What a man to be a woman and then
It's not true
Great
So your sample
I definitely heard Alex try to claim that the Pfizer vaccine hadn't actually been
Approved yet
I never knew what his evidence was because it's absolutely not true
But I guess this is at
This letter
This is still from that
FDA letter
This is a paragraph where they're requiring Pfizer at Buy wintech
To submit a yearly Report with the title
Quote annual status report of pose
Post-marketing study requirements
In the latter they're setting out guidelines and requirements
That's for what the company will have to do to maintain its license
And one of those things is postmarked
Getting studies
The letter says quote
We are deferring submission of your Pediatric
Studies for ages younger than 16 years for this application
Because this product is ready for approval for use an individual's
16 years of age and older
And the Pediatric studies for younger ages have not yet
Completed
The section that Alex's reading is referencing the one of the studies on children
Aged
12 to 15 that has its results panda
And the final report on that is to be submitted by October 31st
Probably where Alex got Halloween from
There's a full study on children aged 6 months to 12 years that has a final report Due on May 31st 2020
4 + 1
Under 6 months that
It's supposed to be done
By October 31st
That doesn't mean that
Will definitely take until then but that's be proposed timetable
But Alex's
Those dates are set in stone is wet
When these things will be noted that when they'll be approved
Incidentally
This letter was from
And since then Pfizer has released the results
Of a phase 2/3 study that reflective
Very positive response
In children Age 5 through 11
In participants at 5 to 11 years of age the vaccine was safe
Well tolerated and showed a robust neutralizing antibody
Just this week the FDA looked at the data Pfizer collected in their study and NPR reported that they said
The quote kids size doses of Pfizer's covid-19 vaccine
You're highly effective
At preventing symptomatic
Confections in elementary school children
And cause no unexpected safety issue
Kids size
Jacuzzi lower the do now here's where they made him
Mistake it should be called Fun Size
And Halloween
PS
Right that's what you do
Hire me
Branding I'm there
Anyway Alex says this letter that has a
Some dates on it and I guess he's just
Misinterpreted
Decided it's
Conspiracy
Fall back on his transphobia
Like he's got to take this swing at Rachel Levine
For no reason
I think he's mad because he's decided that
They're saying
She's the first woman four-star Admiral but that's not true people are saying that
Right
Such a raw butt
Michelle Howard
Was promoted to four-star Admiral on July 1st
14 really unsurprising that he
He doesn't know that there was another woman
Right
I just
I find his bigotry boring
And it's awful
Karachi has to fall back on because
This is so weak
As being the evidence of his
Conspiracy theories dates but he's taken out of context
Witness approval letter
For the biologics license
For Pfizer
You're do interstate commerce with their vaccine
It's
Yeah I mean it's really it's really despicable
How
Easy it is for them to just
Throw out
Trans
Laika in the end without thinking it's like
I mean banana
I feel like there might be some more coming up
What is really horrific
Did not even
Stop for one second and think
Maybe this is not just a bad metaphor
Horrific
Sickly big
Yeah
Alex get back to talking about the dates in the letter a little more he doesn't really understand what's going on
Doesn't know what he's talking about
Bizarre long fantasy
Great study completion May 31st
October 31st 20
Approve it
What
Gaslighting
You want to build cars there's no cars in car lot that sell them
Chicken
Dimitri
And yes
Spell shopping
There's a jaguar
F-150 it's blue you don't see it
Gaslighting
What's going on here
Anythink
And then
The UN world leader arrives
For just a couple years
What
Yeah a lot of people died previously we got a billionaire so dying
The leader just gets a little bit
Terrorist start blowing things up you know who they are
Christians
Everybody
You're the same terrorist you always mRNA Factory
They're the ones that did it
Gr they cherished gr they the ones that just won't accept
Sis
They just won't do what they're told
Religious leaders
Saying that we all need to go to prison or BJ
You see the popo
Beautiful prophet
Don't tell us that they aren't humans
People are nasty
Christian
If I'm not mistaken Alex spends most of his show saying that his enemies are demons and other
The devil
He spent most of his this show saying that
Well explains why his dump a&m-cc imagine
The pope would act the same way
So
Like
The primary thing that Alex is doing throughout the step
Episode like with this fantasies of blowing up
MRNA factories right and then talking about like what
He goes and runs over the school nurse
Cheese's Keys preemptively creating a wave
Four people in his community
To see the inevitable result
Of his rhetoric
The worldview that babe
Profit off of actually being the actions of their anime
And it's
You know we see this over and over and over again
With Alex
The smug
Condescension
Towards me for not
Instantly believing
That he's telling the truth about a plan
That he is going to change tomorrow
It's so f****** infuriated he is smugly make it
Here's what they're going to do next
You idiot
You stupid fool you don't believe me this is what this is what they're going to do next
3 years from now that tomorrow is going to say something funny
F****** hate that that's so annoying
So going back to the beginning of this when Alex
Who's talking about the FDA letter
This clip you just playing games with the dates
And information
These dates are asked
Estimates on deadlines for when specific randomize triple blind studies need to be done
It doesn't mean that that's when they will be done or is it reflective of one preliminary information will be available from these trials
Princeton
That exact
Preferred Pediatrics study that Alex is referring
2 c459 1007
Was the one that was meant to look at
The vaccines effective
Children aged 6 months
12 years
According to this letter that data shouldn't be available
Until May 31st
However the vaccines and related biological
Do product advisory committee at Pfizer just released a brief
Document for their meeting
That's going to be held on October 26th
And you can find all the preliminary data from that study in their briefing
Document
This is the date of that was talked about earlier that Pfizer relisted released an initial press release for a back in
It has since been reviewed by the FDA for the
Kid sized
Doses
What else is doing is taking a month old lighter that has some dates in it that he doesn't understand
What is waving his arms around yelling about how they haven't released the data that he's too lazy to go in
This is just sloppy meaningless work
It's meant to create the impression
Of something and
Did they build all meaningless
And don't forget
He's insulting us Wylie
Right
Really fun
Elaborate fantasy of his own coming oppression
BR something goes on
The big mega churches will be where they have the guillotine chopping their heads off
Okay
Lot of time lining lying about
God's right
This is all going to come to pass and your local megachurch will be at your local execution Center
That's actually in the news here I'm I'm going to
Megachurches Sports Stadium
Okay so I may I think he's just going off of some reports
That
Community centers are two schools may have vaccination Nation by interstate Ave
So you go on about this though it's not just megachurches brochure
Football game
Cover story
You're going to be hung up by your feet
They're going to be taking over
Where are the keys to our world
They like to do that
Cuz you see
I think Alex watched squid game
Okay so
If they're going to hang me at a stadium
Could it be at least on one of the days when show his pitching
You know so you guys you're hanging there to be my last day I would like to at least see some
Good game I feel like that's a request
Could be put submitted in paper format will see
I just think that Alex watched
And that's exactly what he's doing
Because anything that's in pop culture and is a movie at the time he's speaking
Something he will be
Describing to you
Alex moves on from this topic and then he starts to get a little bit
Bummed out
Right
Cuz here's what I mean there's a lot to be bummed out if this is what
What is the problem
Is that
The FDA hasn't approved
The covid vaccine was Alex's pretending
Where is that
But that's not true
Now
Simultaneously people constantly make fun of Alex
Is the supplements that he sells aren't FDA approved
But neither is the Pfizer vaccine excited
Right
But anyway his supplements are FDA-approved
In for it
And I love the leftist media
John Oliver Oliver
Jones sells unapproved supplements
The church down the street is unapproved it's not run by the state-run religion
No it's not found
When they tried to take
Over
Supplement industry in the mid-90s
But they have no jurisdiction over
That's true
Only when you try to stay
Your supplement is a drug or competes with a drug that you're down there
In South Central LA and maybe the
MS-13 Latin Kings dramatic
True supplements
Milk
BFDIA largely doesn't care about
Supplements unless something is actually dangerous
Get in trouble with the FTC because they end up
Making unproven and almost always not true claims
How about their product
In the marketing
Materials which is what's covered by the Federal Trade
What's Alex's question the FAA has a lot to say about milk
Guidelines of a company's approved to ship milk rules about
The factories
Produce milk milk and be very dangerous even have a 447 paid guidon wedding
Exactly grade a milk is
As for oranges gas the FDA has thought there too
Their rules
Orange juice
Like pasteurized from concentrate
What can be called Orange
Joogsquad
There's a rule that artificially colored oranges must be labeled as such
Plainview
On its bulk labeling
Counter card sign or other appropriate device bearing prominently and
Inconspicuously
The fact that the oranges are artificially colored
There's a 1973 declaration that made it official what was marmalade
Because there's a controversy
About using citrus fruits and marmalade cuz you have to add more sweetener
And maybe that's not Barbra late anymore
That one starts that 1973 declaration starts
Under the federal Food Drug and cosmetic Act
Techno standard of identity has been established for marmalade
This is a
Problem
Iiiii appreciate the way he framed
22 is like when the Government tried to take over the supplement industry in the 90s they found out they had no jurisdiction
Not
A massive unregulated business with a s*** ton of money paid off a ton of politicians to make sure that they never regulated
They didn't have jurisdiction the American government's like
Wait a second
We can't
Regulate.
That is a good clarification I don't think
Food or a drug
But the EPA definitely has some thoughts about what is
Clean air and what is not
Lake Butler
The point that nothing should be regulated ever
I guess if you think things are regulated that's cuz you're stupid
Like
Yeah dude does the FDA
Have thoughts about milk
Or oranges
Yes absolutely
About the things
You put inside
Stupid
But Alex is struggling man he's having a tough day
It's just
Retard
Earpiece popped out
It's really hard to
Just sit here with this one.
Get out 11 things.
Is it possible
I try I couldn't even
Cuz you can't
Get this Justice
This is just evil
And just make a lie
A saying that
Two women had a baby in a California prison
Wow
Four Star General
It's all just
Cuckoo Land
Put a f****** loser
So here's what Alex
Does FDA letter giving a license to buy wintech
And Pfizer to Market their vaccine is just a
Impossible for him to cover and do justice to
He found some dates in the letter in decided
Conclusion that the Pfizer vaccine
Show me FDA approved
The media is lying to you saying that is because they plan to approve the 2024 when the Testaments
Did the letter r.
This lying that the media is doing
Alex compared to a prisoner
Situation and Rachel Levine
Would you give us two stories that do nothing but highlights
End up
Push Alex's transphobia
The story about the transwoman impregnating a fellow inmate at a California prison
Isn't a real story
Unsurprising
Yeah it was based on a meme
PolitiFact describe the situation like this
An image of what looks like a
Pregnant inmate in orange jumpsuit is being shared on social media
California inmate pregnant after being forced to share prison cell with transgender woman
PolitiFact they reached out to Terry Thornton the deputy press secretary for the California
Department of Corrections
Who confirmed that there were pregnant women in custody but
They were pregnant when they were admitted to State Prison
This is just a transfer pic backlash to California passing Lee transgender respect agency Integrity Act
Allows incarcerated transgender non-binary and intersex people to request
Steube house
In a Men's prison or women
Prism that is consistent with
With their gender identity
It's most likely saw this meme or was made aware of it be
Because Steven Crowder did the segment on it which
Tim kicked off YouTube
Yeah because the story wasn't real and it was essentially just anti-trans propaganda designed only to spread hate
Baby turns out view the story
And even possibly the meme originated
From a story spread by a member of the women
Liberation Front
Do the group that NBC's described as quote
A self-described radical feminist organization best known for its opposition to transgender rights
So they literally called themselves to her
In 2019 representatives from the women's Liberation Front were part of a panel hosted by the heritage
Foundation
Where members said such gems as calling accepting
Trans people quote
A social Contagion
Play this is the information flow that Alex uses to get some of his
Reporting
S***
It's just it's just meant to
Yeah
Spread
End justifies the
The spreading of bigotry
Yeah
You know it's
Think about it
But if you if you're reading and sharing that meme
You want
You know you'd like to believe it because it can form
To what you're
Vacations are of people
That you have a pret
Exactly like the idea of wanting of a being like Oh that's
Comforting to know that
Trans people are evil in my in my
I'm glad I have another
Piece of evidence to prove
Right but my hatred is Justified
And it's
Stop think for one second
You're just a
F****** a******
Do we have this
Snowball rolling downhill
And getting to app
Point where you know Ali
Alexis just
Competing theories Giselle f*****
Please
Not true stories as true as justification for
Why it's so hard for him to do his job because
Do this
FDA lighter
Alex you didn't do the homework
You're going to have
Have to go home when about this and then do your report tomorrow
And I want no transphobia
Then
I don't know who could
Fill in for him if you wanted to display at I didn't do the report I should take the day off
Do you have nobody
So again Alex Drive
Now cover this after you a letter
Study gets distracted
This is a pretty big deal
You just type in US Food Drug Administration
Dla approval Pfizer's comes right up
Apartment website
But you won't hear Riders talking about it cuz the Reuters Tio is on the board of Pfizer
Short video
Instagram
Put in 30 minutes left at Narita
Dinner
Got a million views that's that's exciting that
Right now to talk about exciting
Play yesterday the
Videos
Eclipse
Sporting event
Tell you the propaganda
Effective
It's paid for by Pfizer what's a little bit of revise though
Brought you by Pfizer
A little bit silly
It's just a collect
Program sitting
Includes disclosure
But they have some sponsorship
TripAdvisor
Especially if you can
Can find the same networks like CNN or ABC or CBS
Running stories that are negative
About Pfizer like all of them did
When they were fine
2.3 billion dollars in the Bexar
Scandal back in 2008
Yeah
The person who's on the Pfizer board that Alex is referring to his James C Smith
Actually stepped down as CEO
A company that owns Reuters the tops
Incorporation
In February 2020
Well he was CEO they ramp
Plenty of
Critical stories about Pfizer just not ones that are based on things that Alex
Is making up right and wants everybody to
The focus on
To that
Alex you're brought To Us by my pillow so
Years and years where you did not disclose or disclosed it regularly they were brought to us by
I wonder I wonder about the ethics of that
Compared to the ethics of the
Clear disclosure
Pfizer sponsoring program
Alex thinks he's doing a good job
I'm getting disappointed
Getting discipline now
It's very good news.
Jesus Christ
Cleveland flea
I got some
Good news for pugs I told the
Laboratory
My girl name cuz though
We had a long time.
Cortelyou
Do we have
Captain jumps relatives when they done
Call my guy
Amazing
Organic concentrated ingredients
Get those ingredients so I've told them just as fast as you can make it
I said
I don't care 500 come in if you have the ingredients
Costs more to set up a run Apache with a smaller batch
I don't care
Yes a big news Alex's covered a lot of news
The shot heard around the world now so we got Brian Force
Now
And I need
To get rid of it I will
Spend more money
Less money I need money
And also let's do a little sick
We like to do
Cuz I've already got so much energy with what's going on in the world dead
Supply
Using this too much
I'm getting lonely
A third of the way down
My desk
Here I'll take some right now
About
Nnnnn and some of the guys are like
I'm just saying
A lot of people
Cell grows long time to show Infowars
The last thing he needs
Is another
Wow
So f***** up and away lip licked his lips
Iced I heard that and I was like well
Can't wait to see what happens now
Super weird and now he's taking brainforce Ultra
Be too strong for me to come on now it's rainforest Ultra what could go wrong
So Alex Goes break
Any comes back
And
Who's Gregory she has not been here like 4 years now we hired and cuz he entered into a contest
We had a job memory serves but
Hawaii
Prada close today
Until we Harding
All of his employees come from contest I mean with every single person
Look
Hey who
Who is the best at running a chocolate factory
Who is the person who is that how do you choose who to follow you
You have a contest
That makes
The most
Alex shows up at professor and spy
Alright
Has written about how you run a business
Alex shows up
Welcome to the contest a of the song and a top hat
What the f***
Business model with a big neck
And then slowly is a good dog
Come with me and you'll be
There's demons everywhere
Hey come on guys
With the demon fist in the air
Reese's report cigarettes put out
Dead on
No way to wiggle out of it
And their answer is to say a man is a woman is a 4-star
Wow
Star Trek
And there's worse support
You're twice as likely to die twice as likely to get covid
20 plus times more likely to develop cancers
This is just unbelievable
This is actually really fascinating decided to check in
Because Alex
Don't have the clip of it but he says it's his best work
I got to find out
To explain to you what Gregory's did
Referring to as this bass
Just work we're not going to listen to all
Of Gregory says report
Cuz his voice
Really f*****
Annoying
So he put together a video that is just
Full of Unser
Instantiated shity claims like
This one
Destroying people's commune systems
Overtime especially between 40 and 70 years old
They have already lost
40% of their immune system
Capability
Sure or how about this claim
At this rate by Christmas
We will have 0% immune system capability
Over 40
And by March everyone over
Will have lost their immune systems as well
No it means us
And it does seem like Alex's just like I don't understand the world so I'll hate
Trans people
Alphabet is
A lot of his model
So I decided to check out this video and see the evidence for myself
Through this boringly voice video
Tell you
The level of information abuse
What's going on here actually impressed
Like
I listen to Infowars I watch this stuff
And I can see you like this is what happened
This
Fingerprints of effort
On it which is
Very rare
Birthday zombie
Congratulate
First of all the part about the
The 20 times increase in cancer in vaccinated people don't come from any data and or is it
The front of UK report
This one's just from a life site blog entry cited
Doctor from Idaho
This doctor is pushed false stories about covid in the past and unless there's a
Verifiable information here it's dumb
I'm just take his word for it
Idaho Idaho
Responses
Doctor Potato Head
The other claimed one of my people losing various percentages of their immune system
It is much more
This was actually really fun
For me to try and sort out immediately thought of the story that they f***** up where it's like because they're
The dropping antibody total
There
Bullshiting Us in being like your retirement system is going away.
Part of the defense of this point of probably but it's not the source that they're pointing to
Alright
So this story is based on a blog post on a website called the
Expose which I guess is some kind of an upstart in for cyber anti-mainstream media media Outlet
From the UK
They have an article that Greg Reese uses as a source of his video with the headline quote
New UK Health Security Agency report proves without a shadow of a doubt that covid-19 vaccines do not work
And have negative Effectiveness as low as minus 66
Percent
That's a big one so I figured I'd go and find this blog and see what they were working with
Embrace video
He shows up
Particularly jarring spreadsheet
From the blog post
Which claims to be from
Auk helps
Security Agency report showing negative rates
A vaccine effect
Assure
I go to the blog and the first thing that actually shocked me was that this post is actually arguing that getting vaccinated makes you
More likely
To get covid
The negative
Effectiveness is what
That's how they are
Describing it
Is a
Big swing
Very cuz it is hard not to go outside and say
Well obviously that's not
Rife
This argument is based on a spreadsheet
Which is labeled table 2
From this a Chase
Ihsa report
The rightmost column of this spreadsheet is labeled
Vaccine effective
And it has numbers like - 85.71%
For the group
2 people between
40 and 49 years old
Would seem to really weird that does seem weird
I found the actual HSA report that this came from
I guess what
This blog
The vaccine
Fitness column
That's a
Is made up and they photoshop to do this thing
That they're presenting as a reference to this
Official
Okay that's what
That's already fraud
They're already deceiving by way of manipulating the information because they want you to think
Think that this vaccine Effectiveness to test
It's something that
Hhsa track
It's something that they thought was relevant
Headache comes from official source
Consumer something
Then right
Have you done
I noticed something else there was a
Quite right
From top to bottom the version in the official report had eight rows of data
But the version of must blog
Only had sex
Snow
Deleted two rows of data
Do this to me the information that was in those rows would have made it harder for them to lie
Here's what's going
There are two primary columns that are relevant to this exit
Explanation
These are the rates per one of the covid rates
It's per 100,000 people who are vaccinated versus those who are not
What does block is done
Mom is taking numbers of these columns and create their own staff
You're taking me covid
Case rate per 100,000 of vaccinated people and dividing it by the rate of people who are unvaccinated
And then presenting that as a meeting.
For some reason
-85.71
Percent Effectiveness rate
4 people between
40 + 49
That was because they took the rate of 1281.8 per 100,000 which is the figure four
Vaccinated people that age range
Any / 690 point to just be rate of unpack
Vaccinated people
The result is one
1.8
Which is how they got to their figure and it's completely meaningless as of today
I mean no I remember it because when I was growing up Pythagoras
I gave his famous
Theory which is a squared plus b squared equals
Gout
However
If you look at this meeting to statistics
This helps explain why they deleted those two rows of data from the
The spreadsheet before they post
Is it on their blog
These worthy rates for the groups
The people under 18 and those between 18 and 29
People between 18 and 29 showed a significantly lower rate of cases among vaccinated people but
The under-18 group was through the
Kingroot
People under 18 had a rate
Of 278.8 / 100,000
Among the vaccinated
2320 5.7
100000 among the unvaxxed
You might have trouble dividing that into a way you can bulshit immediately you see how these datapoints would be
Bia flight problem
For the argument that this blog
I was trying to make based on their weird calculation they did and presented Asana
This would not be something they could
Lion so they delete it and they pass the information along
No need for the readers to see those datapoints it would
Just make them question they would be confusing
Confuse my readers they've come to me for Clarence B might have work for more information about what these numbers actually
Captor then they'll find out that I created an entire column
And deleted Road
F****** b******* yeah that's really f***** up at super f*****
Stop yep
Cut out one other thing and that was a note that the
Directly under the spreadsheet in the original post
An HSA report which has closed
Interpretation of the case rates in vaccinated and unvaccinated population is particularly susceptible
Do changes in denominator and should be interpreted with
Precaution
This block did the exact
Gregory's found
Didn't look further into the data at all
Episode
Next year
And that
According to Alex
Is the best work that he's ever done
This is a team of
Walking losers
We are so bad at this
You know it's not usual for the health Ministry to put out a study and then write you no like
And we think these results should be interpreted with Reckless abandon
In fact
If you just
Makeup bulshit whole-cloth out of these
That's what we want you to do because the health Ministry do not have a great time
Hey
Happy hours on us
I hope that that was
Clear
It's hard to describe a spreadsheet in a audio medium
Yeah but I have screenshots of both of their version on the blog and
Panther version
From the HSA report
And those will be up
What are citations
So Alex
After playing is Gregory's report
To recap the story
All right ladies and gentlemen we are back into our number three and I'm just going to hammer through all the news.
Eating around the edges of in the last 2 hours for you right now
First off let's go back to where we began
Official FDA letter that tells you that
B5 Rashad is approved
I says that in the year 2026 they met
I showed you that
Here is the document
Letterman Alex exciting is that letter they sent her to approve their license
To sell biological product over
Thirsty Lion
In addition to that included tentative time frames for when various studies about other questions
Supposed Market effect
Decide to be completed
It is not in any way saying that the Pfizer vaccine will not be approved
This is a fabrication of Alex not being able
Understand things that he reads
It's really simple back in August the FDA approved Pfizer vaccine for using people
16 and older
Generally just as a whole
Additionally they extended the emergency use authorization
For people between the ages
12 + 15
And that is pending a
Full
Authorization
Right now we're starting
Get the beta on this probably forthcoming
He just doesn't understand how
Things he does understand he's lying
Auntie's particularly motivated to not understand us
So he gets distracted from recapping all the Newsies covered because
Kind of a recap of what's Happening
We should all be walking around in sackcloth
Can we
Computer working
Answers all of this
Really simple
Corsola
And then go out and warn everybody
Not comply with the system but also point out that they're going to Stage false flag
Start a physical Civil War
Used to kill them so that some die
A little girl and then that's it
Really
Emailed into these stories that he's been nibbling around the edges of or we've gotten distracted rambling about 4
False flag making references to movie
Right and very
Poorly couched
8 remember
It's not going to be us committing all those terrorists tonight
That is why they're going after the children
To make us
Commit terrorist
It's not our fault
It's definitely okay for us to come in Arizona
Weather
Did the terrorist act and if we are committed
Don't like
Question whether this whole world
Open Spaces
Is toxic and leads to things like
I don't know blowing up an MRA
Things it's the Gullah bus Volkswagen
Is take stimulants
Vickerman
Because they clearly are super effective it help
What a job he's doing you seen anyone do work
This could not since Greg Reese
Rambling about how they're going to be false flags and then made a reference
2 V for Vendetta which distracted
Further
And he has to play a clip from V for Vendetta brainforce Ultra shouldn't be more focused than ever
You think
Sbux
That's my job and I'm honored to do it but I'm just telling you
Jesus
Come out and they announce
That
The children are going to take
Back in 2026
Shot heard round the world
So as the recap continues Alex claims that he's shown the biking has a plan to forcibly vaccinate children
Really trying hard to Brand as the shot heard round the world
Do you know the shot
Hot shot and then your reference don't even think he
Not really
Highlighting
Disappointing process for people under 16 is moving forward in the United
Midstate sanitizer release their preliminary data
Chilling at the vaccine is effect
Even younger people
Alex also found an article from the UK about Houston
Vaccinated but whose parent
That's don't want them to camp
Vaccinated
The article is very explicit that no one is being forced to do anything so in this recap Alex's 042
So now apparently there's going to be
Troops
That are going to be at the
The schools vaccinating children
Yeah at this point Ozark man you don't know the troops were resigning free cuz they're not taking the vaccine
I think Alex has kind of lost the fur
They are going to
Come into the schools with military run clinics
Martial law
They are going to
But they're saying it's those people
If you twist somebody's arm into something that's coerce that's
I mean it is there a law in the mafia says we'll burn down your grocery store if you don't pay a diction money
They're going to burn it down
Mafia
Classic type
The South
South again
Founded by Scotts
Always killing each other and killing everybody else
Turn acoustic
UMass Lowell
What are you talkin about
Scott
Braves versus working man
You can't work if you fight back obviously the mafia's never survived after a
Fight now
Also there's a big wing of the mafia in the New Orleans area and the trafficante crime family down in Tampa
Actually connected to the larger Italian mafia there was also the Dixie Mafia in the south
There's a lot of organized crime pretty much all over the
The place of the United
And the way his mind is working at this point the episode seems scary
It doesn't have to be this organized crime but doesn't have to be the mafia
I've organized crime well I mean the mafia is a hold
F*** off but there were famous but there were plenty of
Trampolines that had connections to the East Coast
Crime families in the south
Stop
Because Alex is not f****** praying for. Make it home
Made up
Nonsense left and right
If you're mad
I want to reassure you some
Alex is not going
Wilcox
The South again was
By Scott
Who
Look for an excuse
UMass Lowell
What
Play gentleman of the real American history
Show
That's where all this is going
Ladies and gentlemen
And
It's on
I want to get this one trillion percent clear
Cops I'm not going to kill you cuz I'm going to kill the military or bureaucrats
Portal swab or any of them
Ugly will be sorted out by God
They are going to Stage false Flags everything is set the stage is set at all prepared
Because they're coming in our children with violence with death needle
And they need to turn the issue around
Say it's the
Patriots that are terrorists that's why you the official policy of the US government
Hijacked
Protesting vaccine for lockdown terrorism
Trenton
Review the headlines of the day
Yeah
Pretty far afield
Also
I think he's wrong
About
No I mean in his own world you I think he's wrong
Yeah if what he's saying is true
Then he should absolutely go
Who killed the president
I don't understand how that doesn't make sense
Listen
If the government released a bio-weapon well then
Just stop saying I'm not going to go kill anybody if the government released to buy a weapon and murdered millions of people
Let me let me
Perspective
The puppet president killing them would not do any
It wouldn't actually resolved
It's it's morally okay in your own definition in his own definition yes but
He can always Kick the Can down the road by saying like
Know that person's just
The figurehead
Until you get to the devil
And he would have carte blanche to kill the devil started the devil you know I mean do you know if you're tired
The mafia you start low and then you try and get people to flip
Kidnap Bill Gates see if he'll flip on the devil
Plus Alex has the devil's power in his hands so he should be able to
See everybody who is a demon
Frankly there's only one true fight and that's between the two guys with the devil power and that's clearly Alex and the devil
What can we all just get out of the way
Classic archetypical battle between Alex Jones
Beelzebub
Wrestling with evil Alex has a bit of a. Here
In the show where he's struggling with the effect
Check the Trump sucks
That's what I just keep trying to get to
Is where the Congress where is Ron Paul
We're Grandpa
Eros
Trump I have the video I didn't play or stay at all if I was present still I can get the public to take the shots
He means well
He's proud of himself he thinks you did a good thing he said the damn shot
Picture of crap
Y'all want from Republican select
Japanese a foursome good overall
Diluting myself dead
I mean
Is so optimistic
Believes in
The guy that
The idea of the secret
Before
Oprah Winfrey all them base what is happening
Evie just be just
But he got that off
Let's move on from that huge story
Sure
I'm going to say this right now
And this is
I'm a maybe
Maybe not 100%
Treasure
But 99% of the time
If you proceed a statement with I'm not deluding myself
And then follow that statement
With repeating I'm not deluding myself you are
Deluding yourself
Also
I think that this is drift
Bring into cyborgs
The three-wheel territory
Worried like Alex desperately trying to come up with ways for Trump not to be evil
Yeah he's complicit
Because of his
Pride and ego in something that will kill all of our children
But he's a good guy
Guy describe
Is a man committing
All of this in
That I personally hate
And then me justifying it
Because I liked him
But if anybody else that I've already
You don't like does it
They must be killed
So there's a little bit of a stretch ear with things slow down
A tiny bit
It gets really boring
And then Alex brings up
More stuff about the military coming and shooting your kid show
Information
Message from the CDC
Nosa Lawson regulation its considerations for planning School
Located vaccine clinics coming into schools with the National Guard
And you got to go read this thing I'm just reading this on here
Incredible
Especially the UN style come and take over the village make you take the shots
And
Talked about
You need to get
Talks about
Reactions
But people enforced
Aniki is
Develop
Plan for use of electronic
Registration Anwar consent system
Rolling the children
I don't know if it's fully coming across in this clip but altitude
There was like 100 22 pretty fast
Seems like he's crashing isn't so bad advertisement
Is definitely a change in vibe
Is pauses are becoming scary
That NM
Even his
If he's not doing a good job
Skating he's literally saying well the thing that the document I'm saying says
It doesn't say that in the doctor but it's a
And the thing that the document does say
They're not doing
Well don't report
On the document if you're trying to report a
If you're trying to report about the military in National Guard coming into
Don't report on the something that doesn't say that
Cuz this is just a CBC webpage that's about consideration
Is that you should have
Like if you
You're going to set up a clinic
Like a day of vaccinations
Italy
It legitimately just has like advice on how to
Restore vaccine
Get this
It suggests
But the day after you have a vaccination day haha
Would consider sending thank you notes to volunteers
Various ship man
You should buy everyone pizza right
James
Same rules for helping somebody move you by a beef and beer afterwards
Every race has been around for centuries that's how it works I got to say but not only my worry
About Alex's energy at this point
I'm worried
Like this is just this is no good
Thank you.
Recommend
Calligraphers
Some of the Alex
I would say in the past
And his relationship with
Students people who are under the age of eight
18 weather there
Victims of
School shootings
David Hogg
For targeting children
It doesn't go well remember
That's what he's fighting to
The children
And so he's he's found another high-schooler that he's going
Target
What is the Judas goat will show you one
Judas goat
Does a train go
Used at a slaughterhouse and in general an animal hurting
But you discovered a train to associate with sheep or cattle
Leading them to a specific destination
In Stockyards a Judas goat will leave sheep to slaughter
Well it's only the sprayer Judas goats are also used to lead other animals
Just Pacific pens
And or onto trash
Judas
Greta thunberg's
I want to come back
About Kelly
Daniel poor woman come back with a Judas goat leading your children to go get the shots without telling you
Will put a put a Target on a high-school sweetheart I really can't believe that
It was
What's something that I found
Almost in defense
0 people on a staff we're like hey
Of all the things that you should not do
And I'm not even talking
Sing about like
Just in the larger sense
I'm just talkin about you
Let's consider his
Particular legal troubles that are going on right now
Seems like this would be something that would
Indicate a pattern of behavior
Commence his audience to
I don't know targeted Lee harass High School senior
That's dat mean
Irresponsibility bordering on an axe
To physical violence
From his staff
He himself is far beyond
Like that's that's just f***** up targeting that's f***** up but like
It's it's negligence on the part of people around him
That's f***** up
So he doesn't get to talkin about this
The high schooler for a while because he has to come back from break
We can talk about how I can't you know you and me
I wake up and I think I want to strangle you don't like the rest
Get it
Like you know we got
Get it get it
So now because we get it
Outlook
It's going to be bad
Just like you
What's wrong
That's that's what we are
I'm asking myself what am I going to do
Really you just be talking about
Mitigating
And saving ourselves
Ourselves we can take care of others
But has to be in that measure
I guess I should go ahead and go through scenarios of what
That is going to transpire
There's only a few different paths We're Goin Down
Absolute nightmarish horrible to just in the world
He doesn't actually go through
Through specific scenarios
Getting kind of excited for a possible scenarios scenarios and
One of them might be a really bad one if there was hitech
Technology anti-fascism in one might be a low technology looks
Four scenarios exactly I think that would be really interesting
It would be fun if one of them was just
Vampires
One of them Dragon one of them dragons
One of them is Godzilla real
Got to go with the dragon
Vampires
That should also include all Undead
So zombies and vampires scenario
Worldwide squid game 1 squid game to end them all
Yes
That's probably scenario 3304 is a worldwide
Agreement is put in
Good place for a minimum
From corporate tax I was going to go with
Murder Hornets take over the land
Breaking news
Information set
Fauci
Project
Project Developers
That's all come out
My dad knew that the mid-eighties Smurfs around the table talking about it
You know all the people you know them all
But don't work for the
Deputy see eye-to-eye
And
I told him all that stuff
Alex HIV
I'm talking about this
The Alex is known the factory was evil except for
When Steve pieczenik said that.
Ouchi was a
Great
And Alex
First started talking about you and said
He done the research on him and he was a hero he was one of the best
Because he thought
That he was siding with Trump on
Some stuff and then
Dot-dot-dot drop really fast
Alex had known since childhood
I would think
But that would have been something
The moment that his name Papa yeah I mean certainly went Steve is like I went to college with him
Galaxy be like
What
Yeah yeah I know that
Maybe your dad's a liar.
This is just a tangential nonsense
I was just kind of
Concerned that Rand Paul isn't stepping up
And he needs to risk his life over this s*** I'm excited to know that everyone is pretty
Pretty certain that none of our Senators are f****** stepping up and especially Rand Paul is
The coward
See how they win
See how they do that cuz you're in trouble we're going to win
I already thought that through
Unless senator Paul Rand Senator Hawley all of them
Come out and say Klaus Schwab Bill Gates only be arrested
Paul them won't go all the way closed
Sapori to Biggby
Police
You know Paul was the main target
Baseball game
I'll kill him in a debate
You don't think that guy just broke
But he's just going to have to stop and get ready to die
He's our best shot
And that's why they're all
And that's why they now.
Judges saying you don't even get a trial you don't even get a jury we're just going to rule this until you know shut your business down I mean
Thinking of the business
And
You just targeted a high-schooler
Yeah
Why are you this this is such a rambling defense
As for why he lost
Yeah
Yeah and how dare you say rampaul is going to die
Before he debates me sure
Sure he has plot armor
Is the main character in
This is a man everything is just jumping around here but
Two pretty violent
Sort of ideation that he has this fantasy about like well
Some people are going to have to die rampaul you got to get ready to die
Like
It does sometimes feel like
Like it's just a man screaming like I don't belong here
I don't know where I belong
I mean 88 feels like he's just like
Everything isn't the way I wanted and that's and that's his only only
I belong in a
That he has complete control over
Everybody is
Fervently extremist
Fundamentalist Christian
Oh man
So look
People have to die
In order to
Mom anything alright
Don't do it
We also have some good
Wait till you hear with a good news
The men are going to have to be willing to die stopped
The Federal Building
Don't do that appointment don't worry
You got to be willing to pick
Speak out and it would go to state houses and
The best news I've heard in a long time and it is what's really going to say
Be careful how I tell this because it's
It's incontinence and nnn so I'll just leave it like
Confirm that ABC News in CNN and other places
Dad
People's wives mainly are
Believing your husband
Family members are
Brothers going you know show up like 50 year old men beat their run around cuz you know they're on TV
Families are taking this very very serious
I'm trouble
People who work at the media
Didn't didn't demand murder his family
Because of the vet
Because he thought
That they were
Yeah
That's what Alex is good news
No I don't think
I hope
That's not what he's talkin
Yeah but it sounds almost suspiciously similar like
And beat the s*** out of his brother that's way you know what
Different from murdering I honestly forgot about that story I just thought like I don't know somebody
Somebody who works for stelter got divorced or something in this is Alex's like
That's f***** up
Yeah I think you might as well have it yet that's it if that's his good news it's just a matter of degree differ
Could have just been like
It's good news I heard that a man murdered his family because he didn't want them to be controlled by the vaccine or whatever
Honestly I'm a little on my heels here because I haven't forgotten about that
Clip-on way more chilling
Chilling clips
That I've heard on his show in a while
Brothers going no show up like that year old men beat their brother up cuz you know they're on TV
Families are taking this very very serious
I leave that at the family's what you do with your family
Teenager my dad said if you turn evil I'm going to kill you and I know he was serious about it
Almost
Number
This is a family affair
You know who you live with you know what they've done
I'm just simply saying that in in in this type of War
That's the type of wheelhouse rendering
I was
Pretty much speechless after I heard
What are the things that I think is really interesting
Is
I played
Piece of that at the beginning of this as a novel context dropped
Kind of funny
Yeah but then you listen to it in context
I don't know how you could
Could hear that any other way than Alex Surah saying it might be okay for you to kill your family
We're at the situation of like
Not this man is is
Bad this is
This means to be stopped
This needs to be
That's f****** insane
I don't think you can hear that is anything other than a
Insertive
A tenuous Justice
Application
Or is it hey
I don't judge what you do within your family if that thing is murder
F****** dare
How dare you
F****** say that there
They're going to start a civil war
And then tell people that it's okay to murder members of their
In the same time f****** real on the same
Cast be preoccupied with the machinations of the literal devil
Brand
Giving vaccines to Children the shot heard around the world
Yeah it's
It's all just
TaylorMade
Tubi
Dangerous and create the situation that he's pretending to be against
I have
Come to pass
I mean yeah not function with
Alex
It just
I have faith
Okay
I may be naive
But I believe in your help as well but look if there were people like Alex we wouldn't have
Have Clips like this
Deliciously stupid
Some dogs are stupid some dogs are smart
This is a phenomenon has been seen and now before
It actually happened some in Nazi Germany
German Shepherd
Children
German Shepherds again neither male have a maternal instinct
Why would you kill
Why would you hurt small person
What is a person doing
Dog thinks it's a human
Takes the dishes in a pack
Dog sauce might steal some food from you or
But if you're just beating people up for no reason the dog doesn't see Justice in that
Attack
Kylie
I know that you're taking Jake to dog training
Does this dog trainer have a big idea to put on have specifically
Point out that
Jake
Was a Buddhist
Has been
Spending too much time trying to do
Detached from the rest of us
Enough said his
Is dog scent
Suggested out of whack
Sure and hear you got to you got to worry about like
If your dog
I don't know how it would
Articulate this but it might believe in like the categorical imperative might be more of a utilitarian
IBEW don't like you don't know what
What standards of ethics
Your dog is going to jeans and let's go even a step further
How does my dog feel about civil forfeiture that's what I need to know
The Justice in that will my dog attack somebody for
I know that
Police dogs having to Town police for trying to take me to class at the last for
That sounds right
The only logic I can come to you
Looks so dumb
I think just said
Hey look
That fux with a dog sense of justice
If you go beat somebody up your dog's not going to like it
The dog sees that person steal your food beforehand
It'll know that it's cool to be that person up
What happens when you build your love
Bread of knowledge around lore
You're just over yeah well I mean obviously if you take them out and you put them under the Wonder after a full moon he becomes
The same person who believes
This kind of stuff is not the person
Listen to about whether or not it's okay to kill your fam
My God
My f****** god
We're getting towards the end of this this is another thing that is
Pleasanton
Upsetting really bad job
This high schooler of not trying to put a tarp
How
Do
We stopped
From attacking us but not get Violet back
So they can destroy civilization
Destroyed anyway so so
Then what's going on
So I let me tell you about
Said no to their kids
She created a resource where people who wanted to get vaccinated and they had Parents
Two or maybe into qanon or
Some kind of an antiviral
Text believe fry could
Find the resources to find a shot if they wanted to
And we're responsible enough and we're doomed
An okapi
Didn't have to make her own decisions in whatever
State or city
They happened to be an ad now Alex is talking
In about
You know
Hey look how do we do this without getting violent
Also they're going to destroy civilization anyway
Wallpaper
That's like
What it what did you find her daughter's looking at the website like but hate my dad
That's f****** Alex Jones
Clearly I have the ability to make
Decision for myself
But he cannot
Yeah so I would say
The alot of this show has been
Crash
Nothing has happened
No very little actual
Bits of meat on the bone hopefully rambling Alex having a little freak outs him being on a
Energy roller coaster
You know real weird
Taking his turboforce herb rainforests and getting like real
Everything slows down
He did not do a good job
This is why I
One stack we've covered the last.
Before watching takes over
In the next 45 minutes.
Wow
What are professional
Be busy beaver I probably going to be on for room some to it is much that I need to get to this is breaking right now
Shepherd
Formula that has the level of any brand that we know that existed
Strongest
I still good for information so that your body is back in stock 40% off ship No Time didn't get to the news
And he did not get
Get to a whole stack
You got to maybe he's giving a couple headlines getting mad about the devil
Putting a Target on a high schooler
Telling people maybe it's okay to kill your family's
Floating Gregory's for doing
Terrible work
It's not if you do it
Look if you're an Infowars listener you believe in
All kinds of bull
Get that
I would feel personally insulted
But Alex isn't taking this seriously
Tune in to your job I would feel as an Infowars listener not like
How dare you say all of these awful things I would feel like man
You're literally not stepping up you just told f****** Rand Paul is it
To die for you and you can't even
Prepare
You just get drunk the night before and then ramble about how I should murder people for 3 hours
And you expect me to follow you
Yeah there's a part of me that
Momentarily I'll feel that way you know like you don't even take this seriously and I
Covering your s***
I think that the
Deserve a psychodrama that he's
Clearly going through on this episode is
Is interesting
There is something
Compelling about it
Content-wise
I understand
I was meeting.
Twomad really offended
By the even the six
Just Jim
Of killing your family
I am
Boggled
That you could
Just to hear somebody say that and not go like well obviously he died
Guys are the worst human being in the world
Yeah
Yeah II
I often speak a little bit like
This is one of the craziest things I've heard or whatever but like
I mean it about that that clip is one of the most chilling things
But I think I've heard him
Suggest
Maybe the entire time I've done this podcast
What's let's get rid of any and all critical thought
From the star
Okay here's here's my first
Step for you whatever information out that you are going to alright
There are people who will tell you to kill your family
And there are people who will tell you not to kill your family yeah
And there are people who are
Agnostic
The people in the middle only trust people who tell you not to
Kill your family
You can start looking into
Family
This isn't the Spectrum problem
It's somewhere in the middle is the line
How in favor of killing your family should be
Do a lot of people are like Jordan sometimes you take things into a black-and-white
So black-and-white sometimes things are just black and white
This qualifies as dude
We do have a website
Please don't kill your family. Com
Sandollar stripe.com
And like I said I'll have those screenshots up
Dan Illinois
What the sex robot
Alex
Birthstone colors