Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color
We're couple dudes like sit around drink novelty beverages
I'm sorry I was running
Late
I was at I was at a top.
Schedule
Turn off work right now I immediately
There's a lot going on in your life
Speaking of miniscule
Think that's true
Treat our listeners with
The same disdain that
Cute retard novelty
God if only I could treat our listeners and I will be beverages
All of that with the same the same treat myself with will all be miserable
Little surgery
Everything is good I got cool
Thank you to the movie The replace
Yep but they'll never know cuz my beard will grow back yet
It was a it was a very weird time
At the doctor's office
That's irrelevant irrelevant
Isaac
Dorothy rella
I know the theme of the podcast
Is that I know a lot about Alex Jones
Go to Havasu
The doctor
Just I'm here
But now he's probably all too aware
The s*** is real cool
I feel very comfortable
Yeah it's real
And it's crazy to like I have painkillers but I don't need them
You're not very strong don't ask me for
Drivers
Leftover painkillers is like I had wisdom
Wisdom teeth taken out
Root canals and now I've had
Invasive surgery on my jaw
Speak up
Pacific
Mutant power
I could be
Faith
Head will later
I'm okay with that I'll take it
I'm okay with it I'll take
Is our new donator
Do the fold what's up Ryan
For joining
Thank you for joining the team
If you would like to become a policy wonk you met by going to our website
Whatever you'd like
You support the show
I also where you can just Google patreon and hope for the best
But we do have an image
My feelings about our last episode where we took a trip into space
Yeah
So you can
Command far behind
Still further into the wild blue yonder
Space
Explored it all and I will do some more of those
Project
Camelot
French
Fallen in love with Carrie Callahan
I don't think you'd be happy with me
I just mean I don't think you two are compatible
Understand
Trepidation
Let me tell you something
Who believed that everything is
I would assume I would assume with that
In terms of utility for me but like
Character traits
Start off the show today with an out-of-context drop from Alex Jones
I do not want to be in Maine
I do not want to be in these comedy mean do not put me in Maine
Whatever
Yep all right
Alright I love I love the I just
I love that I love that
Is great this time to break
Even his sarcasm he got wrong
He's a master he's a master of communication and I appreciate it very much
I do hear a little bit of sad
Totally
The past that he is the number one meme machine he's the meme machine
This involves no no
As we all know
Contest
Still going on we're going to get an update on it
Little bit
2017 episode
Maybe there'd be a lot of stuff about the 4th of July
Maybe I'm telling a story about a barbecue
Maybe he got the bottle rockets
You do any of those things you might think here's what I thought
No s*** about the founder
Weird alternative versions of true
I mean obviously
Would you like to know how he starts the show
Do I have a choice
Nope
Let me just start with this piece of news we had Leo zagami on Vatican expert
Monday
Talking about
Cocaine orgies
At the inquisition's headquarters
Broke that last weekend was on
Monday I was checking because
Police break up
At home of Secretary of the Pope Francis
What's agami said great this is a narrative
Great
Is the Inquisition still very anti
Pope
They believe that it lives on
Brother name
Alright still wings of the Inquisition going on in the Vatican
Well I mean
The Spanish Inquisition
It doesn't exist
I can feel two more question
About that quick
How to make a good I liked
Choose Wisely
Okay
USB 3
Think about it
Three questions in a riddle
Definitely not do that
Why
Daily Mail
Daily Mail my friend where they broken somewhere
What this story is this
By the authorities
Vatican cocaine orgy broken up
Chat
Total bummer
Play buzzkill a******
This story does appear in the Daily Mail and a Walmart
Is ruining everything over here
Play celebrity gossip and tips.
Empire
Historically his
So a bunch of other right-wing organizations
Well and all of it traces back
To an Italian tabloid called
Sedano
Regardless of what happens
From here on out
The fat quote
I don't know
I don't know but I do know that this is a salacious tabloid magazine that is not a legitimate source
Even with any concrete reporting
Basically hearsay and rumor because it's in Italian
I don't know what's going to read it
Use it as a source
And all the sudden
Hey this is legitimate yeah Steven from
So it's basically the Magazine's you walked by and Shop
Murdering children
And then beyond that I know what's going to happen already
Because there's nothing here
Because you already listened
Into the episode in the future from now
This
Alex
Is reporting
Steelheart
Nor that it goes nowhere
He's going to use it as a waypoint
Use it as an example of something because there's
Nothing there
Says something
Sing that he disagrees with him
Going to be like look at this guy having cocaine field
I mean let's not be remiss
I have done a lot of really f***** up stuff
Enroll in
Covering up pedophilia B
For a good long while
So we have no business
Defending
The Vatican
The Catholic organized Church
From time to time
AutoZone's hours
To be without you
Without getting a good orgy
So rich
Somebody's going to
Leo zagami is a new name
Never heard that one before
You things you need to know about Leo zagami
Infowars on Monday
About this very story
Italian gossip
Magazine
He has been a guest on Project Camelot
Excellent
But you know why
Has nothing to do with space
No he claims
To be a former member of the actual Illuminati
Phuc yea
Alex really undersold his credit
To get a literal member of the
Illuminati
Leo zagami member of the Masonic
Executive committee of Mont
DiCarlo
A high-level member of the Italian Illuminati
He's at 33rd degree Freemason and a senior member of the in
He was Prince
Illuminati King
Lee Co jail
He was born of a
Scottish Sicilian Illuminati aristocratic bloodline and so has been involved in the Illuminati Order since
Disgusted by Satanic rituals
Those who regard themselves as the elite controllers at the planet
The real story
To those who seek the truth
Without
I love whenever an organ
That is
Musically
You f****** anything about course
Heard of The Illuminati
When you're not on the inside
The same magic that Alex Boles with
What about the Illuminati one-eyed Jack
Is that still Wild
He's gone Rogue he's still in play
This narrative takes up a bit of the show and its
Audible
Alex
And another
Disreputable
Alex is in the middle of
Narrative
I'm going on for like the last week or so
About one of
The higher-ups
SSundee Ark
Australian Catholic
Church just got popped
For like molesting
Children
Is awful
And I'm sure he's done it before
Just moved in the f*** around because
Cuz there
Get down to it
To play this game
It's all about
Systematic organized pedophilia
This guy was just a procure
So this ship pops up
And he's just using it to
Kindling
The fire of antibiotic
Sentiment
It's great but it's bulshit this is bulshit
The talking about an actual pedophile
Witches real
Pedophile
And not
Did he really get into
A little bit
Just
I find it somewhat boring
Expressing it
In this way
His conclusions about the idea of it everything
Systemic pedophilia in blackmail related
It diminishes from the reality of
The situation
Moana playlist
For the fact
No talking about
I agree with that much
I was present
I wish it was more of a
Even after all of the
Great reporting and
And all of the
It's not like anybody's taking down the castle
No that's
Infiltrated with 33rd
Verdigris Scottish
Italian
Judo Mason
Well he's at 33rd degree Illuminati
That's where I
Is totally where my mind
God
So that's not the only narrative
Alex's
What's
Her being 30
Surgery
Jesus
Supplied.
Illuminati
Think I might have gotten
Thanks Obamacare
They didn't charge me
Anyway
Go to just get to this next clip this is Alex complaining about how Tom Brokaw
Talk s*** about him the other day
TV
This is Alex
Complaining about it
And also
Comply
The his grievance
Has something to do with
Stampy intellectualism
Classism
Really
To go on MSNBC NBCSN
The stand against the great evil
A fake news in Alex Jones
Twilight Zone
Poison cherry
Laugh
Rap
Fake
Condescending judgemental
Spaced out
He said I'm a complete and total
Racist fancy $10 word
And the reason
The reason
On the trail with editorials interview
Please
Continue
You call me out you delusional
War-mongering race-baiting globalist
Disrespectful.
I don't know how to say
I don't know how that work
Is this about me that I never said
Newsflash
They don't show you a quote
You know the person doing that is a race-baiter
It's even worse
Where's the notes bunch of bull
Gold as you called funny racist 11:30 40 years ago what do something
No it wouldn't
Water balloons
Paw Patrol
Yeah but the problem is but it doesn't do anything because of all those years of it not doing anything
Not having any effect on the world
The most
The use of the word unalloyed
He complains about it all the time
I don't disagree
Intellectualism
It's really bothering
Well I don't
Right well I would always go back to
Saying that the only reason that you use it
If you need to be
Fairies
Sure
Play supposed to that one big
I don't disagree with you in principle but he was live on-air Eddie said on the Lloyd and we got a deal
I don't think it's
Worth him
Complaining for like 2 weeks about
That's true
Now the other thing that I want to bring up is
Alex
You are a racist
And we have proof
Go to guy
We need some of that pill money
We started
Compiling
We're good we have to
So that's that's
If you are a media Outlet
Feel free to use us as a source for calling out
Are we sure
I just hate this
Diverse mentality of like
Racism is just a word that people use to try and gain power over you
Weird one I don't understand that
Because it's
Just
I mean it
The last Bastion of a racist
Hiding behind like oh you just calling me that
Take power away from my words
But I was his version of it is always like your
Calling me this without proof
The flip side of it is
Yuko people demons
Without proof
You call people witches
Almost every woman he's ever talked about is called
Pedophile
Pedophile lesbians are exactly
If you wanted
If you really want to play that game
You need more
Give me more proof baby
Yeah but
The problem the problem with that
His
Claims are
So outlandish
As to invite
You know indifference as opposed to
Somebody saying like
Oh show me proof that I'm a witch
If you even ask
If you ask Alex Jones Show you proof that you're a witch
You look like the crazy
The two large
That's what's protected him
Oprah being sued
What are we doing
I know that's why we're at the point where at
I hope he Slanders off at some point
Call Takata pro bono guy
Get one of these,
We got a couple comic lawyers
Will be the aggrieved party
Are we are we would be
That like
Taking power away from
By calling them eraser
Seems like an insane jump of logic
Why because I can't imagine
Kitchenware
It would
Actually take power away
Call me racist after I say something
I've never really seen white people being racist
People on the other hand are very right
My free speech
Well I mean I'm coming call rumors
Bright
I don't have the energy
I love the energy to keep it up
I mean
I think that's what Alex
But I suppose
Seems to follow
That you would then be a racist
Now I think
The connotation that
Like you're effective
Only races
In that you are
You know you're part of the
Problem that continues
Adjusting
I think
To all he thinks he has to do
Anyway
These make allegations of racism
Y'all better being with no no
There's no consequence
All of Christendom
Okay
The failure of Christendom
It was Christianity and it was Western Europe
That banned slavery worldwide
Pepper in Islamic countries in Africa
It was Christianity that first
Look at what we're doing is wrong
Used
The globalist the leftist social engineers
They be used are incense
Doesn't matter
Tribal lines where the tribes are genetically identical areas of Africa
Christian
They're super prosperous
Have industry medicine
You'll have Muslims right across the river
Oh no worshippers plant worshippers
Christianity
Fault
Christian
Create civilization
Yikes
Boats
Maybe that's a I like his modifiers New Testament
Considering the fact that
It was the Old Testament that was used to justify slavery much of Alex Jones from
Exactly
Do the Old Testament Christianity is
A helpful thing I would also add that not a lot of those letters
Very very small
Or at it cuz that's wild
That's awesome that's a good show
John of Patmos
Fever dreams
Wholeheartedly
New Testament Christianity is the
Font of civilization
But it's
This Prejudice comes from a very race
Because
Kristen
Aur
Who fuc
Kings spread
Christendom
Subjugated people
Using
Christened
Probably probably
People love free market
Position with about
You all are
Is missing a very important piece of it too
These two tribes
And one of them
Is Christian
And one of them is a
Animist let's say
Christian will have had
An oppressive
Violent
Interaction with white people
Who has forced them to become Christian
And maybe that informed
They're building of
Civilization
That mirrors the way
Generally speaking possibly
Therabox
Animes that are
Tree worshipers is Alex might say
Then have beautiful civilization
But you're just not willing to recognize a civilization
Because you're caught up in your
Prosperity of the West
Can Shinto and Buddhism
Those areas seem to do all right for themselves without the whole Jesus
Civilization
Oh I did
I didn't realize that note are we just talk about Jesus
Just a wonder why
I guess that's not fair
I want to be totally I want to be totally fair to us cuz he is saying
That's the New Testament Christianity is what
Civilization
But in
Perfect fairness to the literal words he said
He didn't say that there's no other way
He was just saying
That Muslim
Ain't doing it maybe
You never said that
Word for Muslims we would have
Buck off
Malik
Would have not much of a shell
Feels a lot of his money to Muslim bathing suit
Yeah so he's thrilled
Grateful grateful
Because
F****** these got no story
So here is Alex
Also expressing
Some beliefs
Feelings that make me
Pretty comfortable
I've been real serious problems with
Christians
End of slavery questions
End of segregation
Have the quote
E-girl
Wildside
That's all it is nearing
You settings
Now
Racism is ever
Exactly
Well I mean himself he said that he was a victim
Black on white
Does a child's of that even flies contrary to his
Things like that before
That is
The old-timey is white a thing
Because I was surrounded by
Right
How can you
Possibly say that
Racism
Wasn't around in the
That's the most insane
Utterly nonsense
But
You know
I think of it
Possible
That
From the age that he was sort of formative
He was able to really experience the world
He's had a lot of bulshit
Maybe some of these I mean
He read that none dare call it
Conspiracy when he was fouled
If you think that
The global is narrative has been in
Has had since 12
He might have
Thought you didn't experience racism
Just Justified it as once
He does as an adult
Possible but that doesn't mean that you didn't
Experience
Just mean
He didn't particularly care and it was
Another story that he wants to get into on this
July 5th episode
No no Christian
No
Christians do not get to take credit for ending
F****** any
Christians get to take
Credit for starting
The s*** not necessarily starting slavery like
Yeah
I can think of no exam
Now racism is ever
I'll tell you that right now
Back in the good old
308 there was no racism
And then Christians you know after the Council of Trent racism is everywhere
Everywhere
Empowering
To the people who are fighting against segregation
To say that Christians
It might be incidental that some people were Christians but it was largely oppressed classes
He's super socially let's not talk about that
A little bit about the Olympics
Cuz they're coming up
Here's what
In every sport
What shooting
Every sport
But shooting
Men are faster stronger
The Olympic men out there
99999999
Superman
Children
Is it 10 guys are superhuman
Normal people
That's one of the most
Confusing
Rambles that I've ever heard on the show
Okay so you think you can parse that
Coming from there
Athletes especially women who have
It's like
That I can't really
Because there are a lot of like
The committee has
Horse genetic testing
Genetic testing
For some reason they don't need to do it
But there are female athletes who have had a lot of testosterone in this
In their system
Because of that
Additional chromosome
Female Vitality as Alex Jones
But
That is its own form of prejudice
Dear of an equal playing field
Is
Ridiculous
It was an impulse
As women and women can
Friend stuff
Female-to-male transgender
And compete as male
And now they've made it so the other way
I don't really care either
He's making the same argument that recently made about Serena Williams
Are you sad
She would be 700
On the mend
Bulshit
Well
No she would destroy pretty much all them
I don't know
I mean I don't know
Pretty sure
I have no idea
Think it matters not right
I don't care particularly but I
Think she would be
I think she's
Agassi I mean like then then you get into just average
Powerline
How hard do you hit the ball
Gives a s***
At all
She is
The best female tennis player
In the history of the game
Yeah ever
So who the f*** cares
Like look like what do you want
What do you want her to play against Federer
Maybe she would
Who wouldn't
I don't know I don't know enough about
All the time
Which is great I love female World Cup soccer team
Another one
Curling
My friend
It just doesn't make any
Modern pentathlon
I guess the only reason that it's important
Ski backflip in there and the reason
Cut it out was
Like
He's all about exclusion
It is really just that's what motivates
Keep these people out
Sounds like he's
He's like I could never compete with anybody
That you get from people who who say like
Because they have more
Fast-twitch
Which fiber whatever
They were bred to be stronger
Yeah
You
Yeah let's get out of this
Alex wants to talk about
North Korea
You know you got that I'm assuming that he's going to go directly for there
Burgeoning nuclear power
Facebook
North Korea's well episode
You think that you're 60 years old you get it
It's been almost 60 years since the ceasefire in Korea
All the experts agree
Kim jong-un's Outta control
Meijer mPerks
Believe it.
Inside guy
This is the number
75000 on the list of reasons the globalists are mad about Trump
It's so many f****** reasons I didn't know that it was because radiation beam weapon technology doesn't want the
Publix
Would you have radiation
Amwell board for
Also for me to just be unhappy about Trump being president let alone
We have sci-fi weapons
I mean
These are probably stick to the you trying to bring back Prosperity globalists don't want that Baseline
Not super magic Neutron beam weapon
Fun stuff
Ever get back to any real talk about North Korea
We'll just kind of fun
I'm saying I will get to it
Because North Korea is now a nuclear power but
Joe Scarborough's going we got to get to the good like 20 minutes talking about how Joe Scarborough's a creep
Amica's an a******
And Joe Scarborough is probably
Migos rap snacks
Has it from
Real good source
Oh no
Is that he wanted to run for
I meant Trump started to pick up keep me like I can't do this I can't get in the game
So then he was like
I'd be a perfect VP for trump snubbed it so now he's super mad he wants to take down Trump
She's making up all this stuff about The Enquirer why I was like
Guys just let Let It Go no one really liked just come from
Mockingbird
Who's going to Bedford here's why you go to bed for Joe's Crab
The president is blackmailing TV
Yeah I'm pretty
Very very bad.
Everybody involved
Guys that Trump is
Far worse than everybody else involved victims were like
Dick I wouldn't want to hang out with Railroad and Barnett
Hollywood house is rubbing off on me
Dadeville they do that
And Alex doesn't get back to
Cuz he has bigger fish
Stir fry
Looks like a huge Bass
What is North Korea nuclear war
This is the main
Saying that Alex
Talking about today
Surprise
Is elotes
Creator
Financing
Violence
I'm guessing the lady I probably
Deal
Based on
A fake fight with Vince McMahon
And Donald Trump years ago
Wii Sports
He told him
Apologize
Would destroy you
Remove it
Bridgewater speak
What
You can say
The last 2 days
Garbage Island
CL South Korea and Japan
Alaska
How he was evil
Sounds like your show
We won't
Give you remove your free speech pure bullying in the federal state law
Cool cool
MP40 told CNN's apologize
I would never support any kind of violence
He was so then why is this account
Don't do follow up on that
He apologizes
Who knows if that's even a real account or a real person
Google
Biggest problem with the CNN
Is that
Trump was actually in that
Yeah that is an actual WWE
Recording president
Weather
Believers at Wrestlemania
Whoever
Feather shave their head
Right
I'm guessing Trump's head didn't get shaved
I don't believe so
That was contingent upon his being part of it
Literally don't touch my
Literally zero problem with Trump WWE
Nope
I have a huge problem with him then becoming president
If it weren't
The exact person of Donald Trump
I totally disagree
I think it's
Totally fine
It's Showmanship
It's nonsense
I don't think
I don't think it has anything to do with who you are as a person
Like Jon Stewart
Is gone and done a couple things
No oh no
The Daily Show Jon Stewart hit John Cena with a chair
He's great with a lot of fun
John McCain
Hillary Clinton
They all appeared on the
Titantron
To give a speech
Do the wrong Nation
3 WWE
Great presentable
I would have been better than others
Well we know we know who is the time you got there appeared on WWE
I don't really think I understand there's a difference between having a head-shaving match
Kyle Drive Vince McMahon
Nobody has five years earlier 10 years earlier
When he wasn't involved in politics
Like that
I don't think I really care that much
I would
Your Square
Be that as it may be a racist to take the power away from
Han a****** solo which is
A terrible pun
Any number one
Was a guy who posted this meme
And the president
And the situation goes
People started to look at
And they found a bunch of really big
You created the one that got the heaviest circulation was a picture of
Cons of CNN employees with
Star of David that's right he made sure everybody knew
Jewish right
And then what is the coincidence
Notebook
Just wanted to make sure everybody knew
Give me of something I'm not ShopRite
Yeah
Just keep an eye on it
You was one of them
So this guy you post this
And that's what people are talking
Trump meme being a
Is very easy to find on Reddit
Cuz it's f****** Reddit
So people started to dig into that.
Neo-Nazi tender
What the f*** is going on here
So
One thing that people need to be keenly aware of
Your internet history of its public
Gives a lot of clues about who you are
I could probably go through it
Hunter people
Breaded pasta
Confine their post
With a reasonable certainty figure out who they are
And that's what
They have a whole department that does stuff like that researchers
Cancel.
Infowars with you I don't I don't believe that that
Set a process exists
They figure out based on Clues
Who this guy is based on his history
To a Facebook page
That is all that
Yeah and they tried to get in touch with him
Run success
First of all
After they reached out to dry
Of his own accord
He made that apology post
He had already made his apology
They didn't believe him
He did that of his own accord
And
They were gracious
NBA
We will keep your privacy intact
Is a good
Faith kindness
In the story that they wrote about his apology
Do you have reached out to
They said
We reserve the right
To reveal his identity
If he
Doesn't stop doing this
And everyone takes that is black
They went above and beyond by not revealing it
It's a story
They have every right
To give away cuz I done
But he made
Amines that essentially got a lot of
People who reported on it
There was a guy with a long thread on Twitter reposted bunch of
Screencap
I hope you die
I'm going to come find your children type stuff
Yep Ana Navarro posted
Screenshot
These are things when there are crazy people out there
Create a violent tone towards them as our world has
In the last 6 months
Body slamming them
What have you
You're creating a in trouble
Were it not for the
Contacts that we live in
Now
Instilling me
Yeah maybe
Yeah I think that would be if if he
Key if Trump did not
Constantly
Threatened
The Free Press the enemy of the people
If the Free Press were not
Constantly under death row
Constantly under attack
At this point from
Then
That would be fun like
Look at it it's stupid
Perfect metaphor for the world that we live in
Posting a meme like that the guy did anything illegal certainly is well within
Is right
It is a nice reminder that there are legitimate
Hot a****** solo
I don't know I don't know I haven't looked at that I don't care I don't want to know who he is and I don't want to feed into
People posting
Screenshots
You know various message boards
Complete dachshund
CNN employees wives names
Phone numbers office addresses
And stuff like that
Let me know retaliatory stuff online
I mean just because we don't hear about every piece of it it's way worse than
Where where
But
Directions
You know
Blewett
With the president retweeting
You're missing the forest for the trees there
Dismissing in terms of Forestry action
Is that
His apology has a very important piece
Alex of talk about
I'm not sure if you CNN coverage really covered it that well
But one of them
Pieces of it was he was talking about how
He got sort of addicted
To making these memes
I trying to shock
And
And what have you
As best I can tell from the apology that he wrote
It was a moment where he realized the reality
It doesn't exist just inside
This bubble
Abusers real-world consequence
And
You realize I
Had a bit I have a bit of a problem with that
That is a message that
Needs to be
Fred far and wide
Ice cream
Brent friendships
Over
Meme addiction
Well what's so his his argument for what he's done
Is that what he was doing is just
Doing it for the light
For the low
That's what he was doing it because they were reinforcing it
And if you if you
Keep finding ways to give those people what they want the only career
The only problem there is
No
You are a racist
Well if you maybe not maybe maybe not unalloyed of every f******
Jewish employee that you
You can find it
CNN
And put a star of David next to them
F*** you you're apology means f*** all them
Apology is done
You claim I would never do that
No you are
Erase
My position on it and this is not a firm
Because I'm not sure about
I don't really know
If meme addiction woodwork
The same as
Other addiction
But
You know if someone's using their like a cokehead or
They're going to do things
Vetter outside of their morale
Things that are outside of who they are as a person
And what's that get help
Grow through the recovery process
And maybe there's a possibility that that
Same thing is true of this
Version of Internet
It might be possible
Puke
Say the same thing is true of once he goes through therapy
Configure s*** out
Then maybe he will do
Discover that he is grown as a person
And doesn't exhibit those
Racist Behavior
But you can't
Apologize
Is it
Baby
Big picture but where I'm going to draw a line is
I don't think you hear a lot of apologies that are that
Introspective
I think that
I mean he might have been pushing to Bruno's
But if you can make a meme
Obviously you can write a coach
Apology
If you take it at face value as the
Sincere and Anna
Which I might as well I've no idea who haunt assholes
I got no idea about tonight
If you are against
People doxxing
People on your side
You also have to be against
Beam.
Text if they're on the other
All of it
Gametime
I don't know when we live in this world of such interconnect
It is like
If you even give somebody's name
Everything about that
I know where he lives I know his
I know all of this s*** just
Just putting a guy
Facebook profile out there
You've been.
You can gather a ton of information
Our names are
Public so we're doxxing ourselves
Just by existing
Picture with every CNN
What have you
I am not
Alright I'm not going to give up my last
My last name is assholo
And I'm stopped at little bit later but
Derivation
Go down a little side path
Tell you all about
What's going on
Interesting
I can either prove or disprove
What rhymes with most
Great my gut
Tells me it's not true
This is Mike. Talking
I don't know
I'll let you decide
Corner in Mosel
Trump
U.s. military leadership
It's almost smash Isis that Obama
Checks out and show
Confirm
On the show
Because we have the sources that came on with the courage
That
Obama and end
Inotorious
We will we will we will not help
I'll kind of nice and take over that was our military compromise
Your father's later anytime
You made that agreement
To begin to Segway out
Bilateral
Laterally three countries involved
I mean only time will tell how it feels like he probably did make that a
Agreement
Majorly because
He's still bombing his own
Like really
You really get into murdering your own
You get you get a taste for it
Next thing you know
I mean his dad was in power from 1971
Empower from 2000s
Timer for 17 years
Secret Patriot
As we all know
I want to do this screaming again
No no
And our military
Are military and Russian military
Secret
They had to because Obama didn't negotiate that treaty
In concert with the rush The Rush
Woodrow gun Obama inmate
Is Secret
I'd still the only person who has the balls to talk about it
Is Alex Jones
It seems like that would be the single greatest deal that
That anybody could have made regarding Syria
At least four
You know
Compared
Can go
Sure
I don't think he thinks
I don't think he's made
Syria
I don't know I think that
You are the child of a dictator and you become a
Dictator yourself
There's a certain
Standard of living
Used to
Going to England just isn't going to status
I mean if he can take his billions of dollars and go to England probably set up shop I would go to England
Island
I will get the f*** on an island
Doubt
Talk about all the time
A bunch of horseshit
He was not a Seeker
Right
I would assume that is the only conclusion we can draw
Assad
Did a double cross on our military that was working against our president
Like no Rogue General
Would ever think that they could negotiate a
Treaty with both Assad and Russia
Pull it off
Go to work
Alex is like little things
Talk about
Turtle Schaefer and Mike Flynn
Saying that they won't be
Isis
Air Force
Right
Paper is as
Legit
Bunch of bunch of bulshit
But we got to move on to this neck
This is where I
Complains about how
How crazy is Jabez
Which I mean we can
Call relay
Everybody but it's got its perks
Imagine my job
My job
This is just what I'm looking at on the tops of my stats that I haven't read
Not a true story
That broke
Broke somebody
Is there
Last week we broke it Monday or any nice day
Iran
What was in the daily mail today
Secretary of
One of the pups
Francisco
This whole thing is coming down ladies and gentlemen
Right
What is the timeline curious what the 2018 Olympic gender
Regulations look like
I was a regular talk show
Take your call
That subject alone
Amen
Can compete as women and women compete as men
Men just want to go Dominate and get gold medals
The men are chivalrous
The racing
That's enough of that
I'm reading
Google news headlines
It's
Ha so hard you got it
You got to read on the Fly
Now if he was if you actually was like
The lookout tough
For 4 hours straight
With really nothing to
F****** tough
Everybody wouldn't
He wouldn't say that
How to say like I've deeply research
Leo zagami coming on Brett in about how the Vatican gay orgies with Coke
All this all your books
Look up look up on Amazon look up Leo zagami books
They're all Illuminati
Hello
F****** love
Former
About warmer
How do we know that I guarantee either I guarantee their website to make the argument that he's still in the Illuminati
I guarantee
Powerful organization is going to let
Amigo hey guys
Listen up let's make the Illuminati great again
You guys are fuk it up
How would you
Like Putin kills
Journalist
If
If he's like if you're in the Illuminati
Which a secret governing body
You got to kill him
Putin
Yeah that's one
Advocating for killing bigamy because obviously
Play he wasn't India
ShopRite
But if I was in the Illuminati
Huge hole in his girlfriend absolutely everything massive
Why can't I suppose because he thinks he's too public baby yeah that's what they all say
Breckenridge
Something to my side now it's just
Imaginary enemy
Yeah so
Next clip
I wish my enemies were imaginary
Very very
Me too I wish one of them wasn't myself
So this next clip
Rebelled against
Totally normal
Tiny scar
Scarface
Alex Jones
Has red
Either either die a hero or live long enough
It'll be on my tombstone
Alex's red
Something
He read
An article
Yeah about how he
Gwyneth Paltrow
Now
Alex Jones is the king
Pastrami
Completely false argument against himself
Father uses to deflect
From the fact that
He doesn't really understand the courtesy
Being levied against him
Anthony gets just really weird
That's really weird I think this is
The sort of a sales pitch but it isn't
Body Works here in the military for
4 years
Just chat
Got got shot down
Okay
Irritable bowel
I said listen take this within a month no problems all done
Sure
A lot of stuff so advanced
Because
I'm not here
Important
In a bunch of
Pictures of criticizing me
Really don't care
Palpitations
Nope
And they showed as proof of my cooking us a bag of coffee
That we buy for like $8 a pound the very best organic concentrated
High quality
Grown in the mountains of Chiapas Mexico Guatemalan coffee better
Totally organic
Covered in iodine
Cinnamon varieties
Good and bad
Because we only
Mark it up
35%
Nobody does that work
So I will get back to the rest of
First thing
Walking back be like map
Is Wal-Mart a couple of ads that I didn't
Alex has started
Maybe this Prosser guard will work for you
You're still giving us money
And that's great cuz it's fun to be operation
Food still a win the writing on the wall as far as
A possible cuz it seems like the sales pitch is
You might not need this and it might not work but we need your money to keep up firestick Global exactly
Maybe it'll work I don't f****** care
It helps if it doesn't
You still
Payforit
Is the master of
Strawman
After what he's done
You've taken these articles and
Because he sells two kinds of
One of them
Is just normal coffee
What's the other
The other one is wake up America immune support
Mushroom
Now I'm back on board the reason that this coffee is meant
It's not
Now back off.
In this article is like in this case
Reishi mushroom
It's by
Just quote from this court
Phone got more fungi with a load of supposed health benefits current research shows that no scientific evidence
To support the claim
That reishi mushroom
Petit vour increase stamina
The reason that it's
Included in here is because
Paltrow's product
Spirit.
That features Rishi bossk
Also it's
Featured any wake up America I mean
Further
Cordyceps
Maps mushrooms
That
They're supposed to
Actors in natural aphrodisiac
An improved
That's also when the Wake Up America blend
Coffee
But there's a whole nother mushroom
This bets that cordyceps one is in
Gwyneth Paltrow
Little product called Sun potion
And it's also
Found in
Chiapas
Farmers
EXO
These are being attacked because
Because
He uses the same
Pseudo-scientific
That product
Now
Look
That might have been a better strategy
Strawman argument
Coffee's great
The reason you have to do that is deep
This article
Is
Bulshit
Like these mushroom
Like these unproven herb
Are being sold by three different people with very different package
Tilted
Different audience
Right
That's the mark of b*******
Well if
Infowars
You would look at a good product
I can be like
This is obviously nothing this is fake bulshit
Sun potion and be like there's something
Buyer
You would look at Infowars and be like this is obviously bulshit
So that you take criticism on
Alex and the mentality of this like
Quick Fix Magic
Right
I mean it's interesting
Sandpoint
Infowars super male vitality
Group sales
Sex.
Similar
I'm in on sex
Kelly song about 10 years ago
Is dodging the criticism
That
Yo it's a bunch of bulshit
A lot of the FDA is the supplement industry is like billions of dollars
Puryear
Yeah
90% of supplements
Magic
They are placebos and sometimes
The placebo effect
Stronger
Sure it isn't
Possible that take
Supplements actually does help you out
But not because of Any ingredients
Jubilee
I don't care
I don't know
Anybody for
Enjoying
The benefits
Placebo effect
I'm not real two people making millions of dollars off selling people
Under The Lights
Auspices of
My chiropractor
Is this
It smells like willful
I like naughty
Engaging with the ex
Bring up coffee alright I'm going to say if they say I can't sell coffee
Rat boom
It's a dunk
It's like
They say I can't do
Sprite
Supermarket
Yeah you're saying that you're dumb
Alonzo
I don't think I could ethically live with it I would feel
Very guilty about it
Feel guilty enough people donate
The show for nothing maybe in the future we'll see
But like Knoxville
Is there somebody at the door
Now those are
Wichita
I will be if I try to sell these pills
Yogaville VA
Snitch
Elmo Farm
For 1795
Wow
Yes this is the this is the product we make the least amount of money
Cuz I just wanted to have a great coffee
Everybody
That's good
And I just find it
Is organic mulch Mountain Coffee
Cuz
Done
Exercises big Plantation
This is really organic and rum
Wild Kratts
Call Certified the rest of it
Proven
Why is the Washington Post come out
A bunch saying I shall
Supplement cause you'd suck wax up
Just move on to this next clip cuz this
Is like
I'm so glad
He threw me a softball on this
I can't
So there's a CNN article about the genetic lineage of the Egyptian
Apparently
Studies
Testing
And found that the people of Egypt
We're not necessarily Africa
From Asia and Europe
Rat
Cool
However
Alex
Runs runs the ball downfield
And immediately just Falls over on its side
It's just what the DNA test
What
24 years ago
The first
Global historian
Play the also said we should have a world government teleport people
Model 12:00 today
Wasn't very nice
Father of what you call philosophy
He said there was an ocean
Flying machine
Powerful
Daddy blew up the entire Island
Anime the temperature get cold
I would come up with that
A couple things
First plant was the
Plot of Disney's Atlantis
Which
Great movie
Underrated
Underrated how great.
Herodotus
Play-Doh also breed
Xenophon was
Contemporary play doesn't
The story ends
That's a little
That's a little bugger
Now
Scholar
I'm also crazy
I love Atlanta
Okay so
I'm here to tell you
Is taken the movie
Disney's Atlantis
Not Play-Doh
Pizza Plano Road about Atlanta
Intuit
There's two
Dialogues
Socrates
Right
Critias and Timaya
Those stories
There's no flying
There is no darkening of the sky
Yeah basically and I believe I believe prettiest is the longer one
It has
Ditto
It's app
Poseidon's land
From
Divine
Lineage
Become decadent
The end of the story is cut off from the
It did not survive today from
Original source
In tomatoes
And they all lived happily ever after
A minute to talk about how there was
Fought on behalf of
The Greeks
I am saved Greek civilization
From slavery
Punishment
Gotcha in one night there was earthquake
Bi-Lo
Which is not really read
Too far into it
You could say oh that's because of a power source they create
But that is not immature
At all
That's extrapolation
Now further
Where did you get these ideas Play-Doh
Where did you get them
I don't know
Guess what there in the text
Don't understand it actually read
Timaeus or critias
If he had he would know that in
Actual tax
It explained
That Plato heard
A grandfather
So long the great ruler
And they told him the Mets
And he brought it
And told Plato's
Patronage
His fathers
Diana got passed on to him as though.
Come up with
You can read
The passage about Atlanta
It's very short
It has all of those
And further Alex don't want to f****** bring up sold on my man
You don't want to do it
What
Because he was one of the best rulers in all of history
Can't think of any reason
Save this
The Greek population
From self-destruction
Oh yeah it was a cousin
The Second Amendment
It was totally Prosperity base
Renaissance 1.0
I believe that would be Renaissance - 0
Dino
DS Stasia
Wherever
Right everybody was forgiven of their debt
Because tons of people had become a higher class
Civilization was
It was exactly
Applied successfully
What time is it
Civilization
And Alex's baby have to know something about that
Reply to the modern
Ruling class
Call the billionaire Elite who were sucking the lives of their portal
And even sold on back
Then
You know whatever so I can
Wayback
Year that was
Was aware of the fact
Social inequality was going
Completely destroyed
You've known it forever
Cuz it always happens that way
It happens that way
Literally every time
Exactly
Why doesn't anybody ever forget
So Alex in order to tell his bulshit story about it
Site
The Disney movie and claim its with Plato wrote about instead of actually reading Play-Doh
Knowing what he said about it last
Susannah where that came from
So long guy look into it
Ruler
Play-Doh
The Republic is a little bit weird
There's a lot of stuff in there
Publix
Really the way that I would
Do it but you know what you going to do
B b stretch
To say that he is bi template of the modern
Who's that at the door
How do you spell on how have you been doing do you have any good ideas
You're busted
Well I will shake off the burden of that.
Are you forgiving me of my bus
Wonderful you're dumb
You should read the things you say you read
Funny
10:30 read it but they literally said that
Quote from Atlantis
Character is saying
They said that there was a an unimaginable power source
And it's not
Anywhere
Not in Play-Doh
He was a great
The Road to El Dorado
I don't know if
We already knew that
But it's fun time
Rihanna
I also will say I've read a ton of other stuff
Crazier about Atlanta
Much less
I've some of that stuff matches up with
Some of the lights
Theosophist
Helena blavatsky
Those type of people who have like
Channeling sessions
With people about their past
Atlanta
Puppyworld
That has some of the
Pieces of what Alex's sort of
Espousing
When we talked
I'm last episode about
Randy Cramer and his
Holographic regenerative medbay
Future Technologies are globalstar keeping from us
REI
Specific
In this case he could say like
I watch the Disney movie with my kids about Atlantis is amazing
You can't say that he has to say like
Play-Doh
If anybody
Who listens to
Infowars
Will ever read
Anything that
You can go check it out
Stuff about Atlantis and there are like
Real world
Equivalence of that idea like Pompeii
Is is that thing
Kind of concept of
Look at this
City that was an instant
Yeah but
Exact
Do you have islands like that
To the bottom of the old
Is there is a volcano
Possibilities that it is
Based in some reality
True story to it I believe in Atlantis
Fanciful
Care that it's
Irene I don't go with it being a
Very real allegory
I can look at some of his Atlanta stuff
There's cautionary
Everybody
Be the best time for me to announce that in addition to that's what they want you to take coming back
I may be restarting my paranormal podcast that I do solo
But that will be behind so
Never who cares
Let's get back to CNM
Alright I'm back to cnn.cnn much b******* they are
Okay
In the stratosphere
Hey sweetie I can wait too good half-hour on this s*** right here
Because Kathy Griffin got fired
Before they launch
Frittata
The CNN is Isis
Meme
Has morphed
And they've changed it now to
Propaganda campaigns based on Trump
That's footsoldier
You're not working
That's nothing new
I'm just glad all out War
When people breaking their conditioning
Responding attempts to silence and muzzle and stifle speech
But just intensifying
Getting my head chopped off
Meme machine
But now the maps are just absolutely completely
Oh I love that Leah famous one of Muhammad Ali
I think it was Friday
Cuz really distracted
You could hear it in his voice cuz he's just watch
Of course producer producer has just started playing me
Performance
Vegas missing over and over again but
I want to see a recommendation
How about we are real people's heads
Fake love
Why don't we put
George soros's on some of this
Save
Islam assisted
Bubbles
Achilles
Team logos
Going
Prove it prove it
The means going
Better hundred eighty thousand dollars
But
Show the check
I believe
Seven or eight people have been paid by
Maybe I'm willing to believe that
Because like
It's been
A month-and-a-half
Heathens
Keys made it like
Oh no this isn't good enough
Cuz you don't say later is
Bigi everybody's gotten online but that's not good enough you're not on the news
That's lazy
The $20,000 is
Play out the other 180,000
Singles how many shirts
Sole bright
See if I you made a profit on this
I don't know those shirts
Like five bucks
Store with free shipping
He might be
You just might be taking a bath this might be a lost leader as they say
So they're going to talk
A bunch about Isis
They get distracted
Buy a collar
Listcawler call them
I think the
Probably in the 5:45
16 year old Ray
Alex is not really recognize that it's a child
He's talking to
And they do not care
I made this
Nonsense story
And we've hit every goal by your support and by God's Providence and we're now preparing to go to the next level
Which isn't completely ready to kill me
Gobble
Unisom plus be spared
Humble person
Oh boy
Infowars other things you're doing
Give me your money
Make yourself a bank. Go ahead what's your political points
It started but after I started watching you know us for Trump and stuff
My dad watches and forwards as well
He's a warrior he was in the Army I'm going into the army I'm getting ready for that
My dad they wouldn't even let him in that first actually it was a famous story all over the news
He walks
Simpson from Michigan
Because they wouldn't let him in cuz they said he had a foot problem so he walked with combat boots and he walks straight all the way to wash
Until he got
The general and told that they want to take them back
So they took him back and he got into the army
And he went through all of that to get in
And I'm really impressed by that
That's awesome
Listen I want to thank you so much for calling and God bless you bless you
You must've there's a couple things here
I tried
Define distort
I don't have been researching time but I look
I could not find anything
Based on keywords like man walks from Michigan to DC military combat boots
I don't know if
Whatever
Perversion is not accurate
In terms of
Functioning with
Adolescent
Mental process
Is childish
Dimensions of a foot problem
Put on
You missing a lot of details in there that did not have the plot of the Disney movie Atlantis
Is her talking about how I wasn't for Trump
And then I listen to you
A couple times
That's how it works
You know you are
Dumb down and radicalized by those
But then the other
The other thing
Super funny
The inability
Connect the dots
Between her
Theoretically heroic father
Who had a foot
Condition wasn't allowed in the military walk to Washington
To become a soldier
And Donald Trump who faked a foot injury to get out of don't know
Parallel
Don't think about it
These are things you don't
The problem I have with that
Is of course
That is a very common
Story as far as far as the military
There is that like
I'm going into the military and they are
Very high percentage of the
Hard right
Hops that list
All of this stuff is built around like
I don't want any of these people with authority and guns
Believing b******* ethology
Numbers of
Not going up again
By the way just to give you guys
I looked into the
Information about
Professions and he is not
Army people
Here's another thing
I don't think I'm going to play it on our next investigation episode
But I found a clip from 2015 where he says literally
Eighty percent of our audio
Is on the radio
Radio listeners are our secret weapon
Now if that's true
His audience is
Way smaller than
Right
Because if 80%
His audience
Is on radio
And
Those numbers are
Very available
Smaller audience
The Kim Komando Show
Right
Has
F****** audio
Crazy
I like
I know what you doing
She is saying the population
Kings of cities where he's in the market
Yeah I think that's what he must be.
Cuz that's how you get to 40 million
Or whatever
80 million a week of every city
New York La in Chicago that make up a big chunk of it
Yet three stations in bumfuk Idaho
That's going to make up a little chunk
Pennywise
3 station
Susan Idaho that's about
30 million
Can people right I probably get 10 million / Idaho
Carry the zero
No
Liana Brackett is back what was she doing
She's apparently caring for her elderly grandmother in Florida
Which is code for
That's very sweet
I would I don't know if I would like it if that was true
I have no reason to
To doubt her except for
Her being involved in a
Completely lie based
Stretches The credibility a tiny bit it is believable just seems like a sweet lady
Did you look it up and see whether or not her Grandma's been dead
For twenty years I've not I don't care
Even though she's dead
Okay
Iran
Conversation
About the CNN
Florida
Infowars.com
News team shut up
Will expose your identity if you don't come out
Or we will destroy you
In the news
Blackmail
U.s. code
Well the reason that they're claiming it is a misrepresentation
Temptation of that line from
The story where they reserve the right
To give out here
Published
This guy is
Identity if he can
Continues
To post meme
Games that are flagrantly
Maybe they shouldn't
Phrases that way but that's not blackmail
The biggest issue with that
The writer
Is the one
All of that
That shitt
And that clearly CNN's legal to
It's probably a policy position
Yeah that was not that
He's the one or she's that I don't know who
That that person is the one getting
All of the death ride
That's all of that
Meanwhile some some lawyer in the background
His name is nowhere near this thing
Well actually
I mean I get you get into a car accident
Do you have mesothelioma
Come on down.
You're going to walk
So Alex I get weary
Coming from cuz
In his mind
Because he's dumb
I have brains
He doesn't know how to read
He see something like that
And the way his brain processes
Is
They're threatening him
Post
Future
We're going to talk
Weirdos on the internet
Have responded
That's the sort of narrative
Narrative that's what they would do
Like that's what the alt-right would do is
They wouldn't even bother blackmail
There is actually a reasonable
Yeah
Now that's a good that's a good point
There's so much projects
In terms of what Alex thinks
The globalist would do
He's doing let's get through this
McAdoo
Make some points
Is tragically dumb in the
Glipizide
Now I still Lottery
We should have a
We should have a double date with
Usually added me and Carrie Callahan
Come on
We raise money online to get them money goes to
Charity
Stickman
At a prison or whatever
F****** alright cause that's the end Macado's
Charity
Terroristic threats
Finish report
Julian Assange breaks it down
Reporting
That are
To take choice to do all that stuff
He
Requested anonymity when he was talking with
Because
The anti-semitic ship
He had been posting
And the past would cause
Major problems
It would destroy his life
Consequence of his
Sprite and that's why I argue
Dino Dino your position on it night time
See the light of that too
But
Do not do that
To somebody give them a chance
To make good on
As opposed to
Complete destruction
I agree with their response to
Agree with the apology
Giving him
Cover I don't agree with him
Like
I mean I think it's
Too good I think it's a very good thing leprosy
Two Docs
I don't I don't buy it
Kobe report
But Bistro publishes home address
Someone else Fox would be like
Call look at this f******
Can sell out
I didn't go get them
Somebody would blackmail
And also this
This paragraph
I need a private citizen
They're going to go ahead and
Ruin my life
This is why
The fort
Destroyer
That's a little dramatic
That's a little extreme
You know the static Gulag really went after
Against Jews
Thyroid
They were super against people posting racist memes about Jews
Globalist
This political correctness social engineering
Understand
Different color
Whatever
Cars
I like I like
Leanne Macado's ability to spin-a-yarn
Duromine
Cheese if you're dumb
That makes sense
But it doesn't match up with the fact that doesn't match up
But the truth
That guy isn't saying
Please don't
Things
Like
He just apologized for being a dick know what happened
He didn't realize the magnitude of his actions
You didn't realize oh s***
People are really hurt by
Me being a f****** jew-hating a******
Right people
Beavis
I think I can
Constructed where I marked
The Jews
Can you work with this guy which
How else
That. Well
No I am to let's say I don't know you
I have a grandmother or grandfather
Had to wear
F****** Star of David identify themselves
I in German
Let's
Yeah that sucks
Yeah that's a real Alex not being able to
Think that he saw racism as a child
Maybe you don't
Understand that experience
And I'm not saying I fully do myself
But I've heard it from people
I empathize
I understand
Small degree
And so what I believe
Wholeheartedly
Is
Vnn
Figured it out
Which is
Unsuccessfully
I need soon as the outside world
Hoped
I was like
We'd like to talk to you about this
He was like
Randall middle child
Who I mean
There are varying reports
That's the most credible is Imperial middle-aged
Not a fifteen-year-old
Folks
Yeah they're trying to pull that Narrative of like
He said he was sorry for those fifteen-year-old nerds in a basement
Adult well if they if they do some if someone
Are Anonymous person on Reddit does something that everyone loves
Then it doesn't matter
You do something
Assholes
But
CNN
The reality like
This is so cute I got it I got to Apollo my God
My God happened in my life
Where everything comes
The Poconos
School Pullins
Oh no
Shouldn't have stolen this
Shouldn't have a habit of
Stealing these Rice Krispies treats
Yeah
Absolutely
Situation
His tentative
Is forced
Certainly
In the Sun
That
The real world
Start looking
Forest
Innocence
Will threaten
You with
People actually care
And you got to deal with
Responsibility
Anonymously
Like
He didn't eat his apology
He didn't hide behind
He said
This is this is something that's wrong and I did this
And I agree that it's sort of hiding behind
The idea of
Audio Addiction of me and culture but I also like
Expressed earlier I think that's real
A real thing
And I don't think that
It's cowardly of him
To bring that up
As much as it is
An insightful
Be that as it may
My eye itches
But definitely
Securing the show off
We got a little more but
Alex has a variant
What's going on
How they discovered
Birthday identity
The way Trump is very
Bloody severed heads they say murdering
They say the guy's a hero that shot scalise
He just puts out an old video WWE with somebody else
Logo
It's not Hillary sad
Do the president did some video shoot
I would say
Ultraviolence
Exposing
Jamaica versus other people and resisting
Maybe there been some other
Three of their employees had to resign
This will be gone from our conscious
But be that as it may. This theory that the Deep
Is behind is
Yeah
I don't post
Annie
Cuz I know
That is very easy for
You know crazy people who have a lot of time
Figure out who people are by their Pope
So they figured I'd like a single reporter figured out who which is it
It wasn't wasn't
The director of the FBI
They found his Twitter feed
Followers
Had to do was just cross reference
It's a bunch of different
Post
And there it is
I don't know that story and I think I saw some post
I thought it might be
Lakeside
Interesting
About the Deep State being evolved
But we're not here
The Deep state has nothing
Sing better to do
This guy made a meme
We've got
We are up to or not
I'm trying to
To get this f******
Fake rush it to fly
Guys we need a day off
Let's take a m and f*** with this guy
Do whatever yeah what's up
Let's fuk with this one
Another dumb Theory
Involves username
Online name
Noticed a black it out not to give the user any attention
Don't they get now the new memes about to be in the hundreds of millions of views per hour
So when bingo
We should be pass
Glycol we need to protect
Children won the children are not f****** watch and see
They're Not Innocent anymore
Did the amount of pork
The day of scene at this point
Themself
Are on Xbox calling people the worst
Things that they can
Totally
Sis.
Well it's
Let me see rules
I have to worry about most of the
Except on those Phantom
About this BNN
Punchline
To the whole thing I will play if you pick up
On y
This is
Hilarious
Beehive
I bet my bottom dollar that got this from other sources
We know
That mainstream media
No one
I mean every phone I've got is its come out
From the sheriff department
You get it
That seems like a way larger problem
Text Dennis Montgomery
Is it that the sheriff's
Department that's Joe Arpaio
The wiretapping
Just he's using that again
Really
Yeah
I mean for the problem is
The problem with that being Dennis Montgomery is that is also a very real thing
That is going on
No that's true
That is one
Hundred percent
Montgomery
Being used
Much like the gay cocaine orgies at the battle
Regency
Full display
He does that from time to time drop-in the Arpaio
Stuff is all just that
Hours to fergo listen to that episode cuz
I don't think we've ever done a better job of burying his bulshit than that one goddamn
Just
The force of his stories
Frozen
2nd Dennis Montgomery reference
Beyond
The
I know he has to
He has to
To turn this from
A
CNN
Looks happy
Right into a
Part of his overarching
Narrative
You know
They're in touch with the Deep state which
Still further makes them
Heart of the enemy
Right so they're not just they're not just part of the enemy as a news
Organization that attacked
Your Trump guy
They're part of the enemy in that there
Connect
To this
Larger nebulous organization that is not going to meet
Take Trump down
Kill him
Of course
But
This is a team that seems
Extreme
It's boring
That is born
It's really boring
Stewart there's nothing to the story that they're talking
Thousand
Theoretical my timer
And then he throws that in there I guess I guess to spice it up
Eid
Essentially just use unrelated information
For claims
XO he throws that stuff in
George Soros
The collaborator
You saw the the party
The guest list
Rodger Stone
But it used it as a way of life
Complain about Valerie Jarrett I think something like that
Of course
That there that's exactly what I was going about how
Mika Brzezinski
You got
Ivanka Trump to hire a globalist Soros
Activist
I don't f****** know I don't care
That's that's basically what happened
Mika
Globalist
Associate
I don't know
She has some vaguely middle-eastern-names reveron
She's good friends at school, Aberdeen and Valerie Jarrett pedophiles
Party in the Hamptons with Soros
And then everybody evil
Yeah brother is Ivanka and Kushner
We don't have a ruling class that exists outside of any kind of
Laughable at the
Somewhat agree with you to certain degree I'm willing to believe that there are
Just sort of
You know high-society things
I swear you have your there with your
I'm willing to believe a Chuck Schumer maybe doesn't want to talk to one of the Koch brothers
Maybe
Maybe not I don't know
Anybody give the money
Excluded from our world we live in I wouldn't even know the first
About that
Witches are all at some f****** Bungalow party in the Hamptons
Timmy is f***** up
Slightly in the sense that it like look at all these
Opulent motherfukers their riches
To the extent that I don't know the context
Maybe there was a fundraiser going on something like that there might be some excuse
Why they're all there
I don't think I do
It's I think it's just
Indicative of this
Complete the
Like that's my
The big
The big issue up with like with the with the help
I am a very
Pissed off about partying with 65 year old man
Facebook invitation
It showed up as received
Well actually I targeted Twitter at at
Yeah
Just like the just like the health care bill
Did not have any Town Hall
Constituent
To be f****** insane about it
They just
Divorce themselves
What they have no connection to regular people
Insanity
Lego
Elected officials should be
Instead of this lunatic group of billionaires
Citizens united
I loved it. I loved it really really save the Republic on that one
We need a so long
Anyway
Probably won't have
July 5th 2017 Alex
About a fart in the Wind
That is the CNN story
Spend the whole lot of time
He has a second part in the wind in this
Goddamn stupid Vatican Coke orgy story
That's not going to go anywhere
Beyond
I guess he was just kind of racist for a bit
MN told us about Assad secret plan
I love you thot
What would be the
I'll also he's full of s*** about it
Forgot about that
There are 344
Yeah I was no point in even talking about
Exactly God killed
The Atlanta thing
I want that's the type of Alex he's just spinning Yarns
I wish you would have spent an hour on that really expose how little he knows
Breakdown of
By the way I have recorded a hour
Orso episode of a podcast about Atlantis
Yeah well I'm going to record a different one about the movie
I would love it
College
Underscore we're also on Facebook
Just knowledge fight upon their we
Can be found on iTunes
Okay
Is right.com
Dude no please know this
There is a lot of
New things that will be,
Thirlby
Episodes
The me and Marty derosa's podcast that's what they want
The first one is available to donator
We talked about Elisa Lam
For the classic episode from
Nayana a year-and-a-half ago or so that I re-release
New ones
And like I said I'm
Restart my paranormal podcast
That will also be four.
Any amount
Ewok leveling up
You can get
So if you would like to do that
Please do
Oh my God
I want to cut that out but it's too God damn it you have become
The devil that you hate
I also have
Medical bills
Aspirin
I have
I can't even improvised bulshit medication
Anyway
New Jordan has been fun is there any
Good news
There's one
I'd like to get
Off my chest
What's that burning me all week I'm worried about you really like to get this message out to the world
Is the only thing on my mind while the doctor was cutting up my face
At is pink know what
F*** you John Rappaport
Alexandra Thurston color