Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
It went real fast
I would like to start the show by apologizing for not knowing that that was
Flugelhorn
I I mostly over you know Chuck Mangione from the children
Sanchez
Run Tracker
That's on me
Anyway
What's your up right spot
Back to the Eco challenge show that alright I was thinking about it I finished
Didn't I realize what I liked so much about it I have a structure it was
All inspirational it was all positive
Yeah everything about it was
People trying their hardest
With people that cared about
I am trying to finish
Write like the first half of the show had kind of a focus on what team was going to come in first
And that was like
Pretty
Proud of
Even after the winter
Still just as excited about like are these people going to finish everybody
Everybody
Goodness no it's fantastic
You know and I think that there's so many shows that are about kicking people or like
You know being certain there's a shot
Freud aspect to him any of that
Whenever somebody had to
The quit or got hurt it was
The tragedy when people
Pushed through and tried as hard as they could but
Still didn't make the cut off
They were congratulated for never quitting right
It's just
Rate
Made me feel very very warm we watch the documentary my partner and I are about
This woman who is running the Iditarod
For like
20 years and she just
Could not
Get
Further you know she was really good
She cared a lot and then all the sudden she starts coming
Second second
Second over and over and over again
Helping people
He could have one like twice but instead
Somebody got trapped behind her and she was like
What kind of s*** in your life
That's great even with
Despacito challenge is like a lot of people who are old-time Adventure Racers who are like
Pasture Prime
Fifth grade fifth grade
Anyway I recommended
It's the final table of outdoor
The Dig real beef
The weather wasn't the second
It's either that could have been
The Absurd production value
Maybe maybe a little on the pricey side for a computer
So whatever
Follow up on
A few months
A few months ago few weeks ago I
It said that we were starting to eat
Eat healthy and do these this meal thing and all that
I have lost
5 lb
Wow
Yeah that's not yet
Your place in
I know right
Unique games
About eating healthy for me
It said
The food taste
Fine
John I used to order out all the time and I like the taste so I
Yeah I know it's
You do some of it taste okay
You want to serve it
Beautiful enough not like a giant thing of mac and cheese or don't need help
I don't need
It works
Well
Congratulations
It's very
Weird
But I think that may be having a
A different relationship with eating good since it's not like you hurting yourself is maybe positive
Play better I haven't
Myself with a bag
Cheetos for a while
I'll pray today we have an episode from
Because quite frankly I wasn't a situation where
I've got some side project
I'm working on when he talked about eventuate but also like
On Monday's episode Alex
Was talking about
Advice about maybe you should kill your family
I do
Know what is more time out Worthy
Locked up things
Imaginable and actually I went back when I was editing a sewed and I looked up that story that you mentioned about the
Guy who killed his brother and his brother's wife and it was very similar
Do that
I was a little bit disappointed that I didn't pick up those pieces of clearly
In preparation of the episode but
It did seem like I was
Kind of what he was touching on a little bit
There's a weird feeling that I have
Personally that like whatever Alex says he's going to eat his neighbors
A million views on Twitter
Maybe it's time for you to think about kill your family if they like vaccine
I didn't see that go viral yeah yeah it is
MC Hammer saying it the demon face go viral
That is a real bummer that we exist in that space where people loved
Infantilizing
Your neighbors
But then it goes
Really
Only difference
Open Total voice
Between it's time to eat your neighbors and it's time to kill your family
Chinese difference
Yeah I just looked up my families starve
I will eat my cookie
Can eat my neighbor
Hey and hey
Maybe it's time to think about it
It's a family affair
If you're really hungry you might have to eat your family too
Extra
Loophole in the
I will say that sometimes it
It gets
Disheartened
Yeah and I'll push through that
And will get back to the present day on Monday but
I was just like I don't I can't I can't
Imagine something worse
The nest
And I can't imagine
How mad I would be if there is something that's worse and no one is yeah
Dealing with a lie
That's really f***** up and I'm in the Press
So Jordan like I said where is the past
Yeah and I will get down to business on that but first
But say hello doesn't be washed
First
This is just a theme I guess
Parton from my life in a demon Feast make you some hot tea or no apology
Text Martin your 11 is the policy wonk anniversary thank you so much you are now the policy walk
That's great cuz I do think that we should try and brand one anniversary as a
Policy
Suggestion is alive in your partner
With really in-depth things
About tax code
And Healthcare law
Yeah I don't think we could pull off C
666 is the one
Anniversary
Sure technology
Control it now before it happened right I usually am not in favor of some of your ideas this one
About
Preemptively the 650
Anniversary
Text Kevin thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you Jeff
Extra so I'll see my cuz I care so much you and I were talking crap
Heroin
So good
Freakishly large
23rd of June
I wasted a bit of my time listening to the
Episode prior to this
So the 20th
Does that was over the weekend
It's a repeat
And I didn't realize it for a while
Speak highly of some of his broadcast
I took me a second
Why are you defending yourself about being drunk on a boat yelling at people
Do the exact same conversation again
I do you cut your hand the people who started it
Not
Baton
It's going to be all that interesting for us to go into gear
But there's a couple of there's a couple of points that I found
Very Illuminating
I am excited to
There's not a complex drop that will come in very handy in the future
Oh my God.
This is going to add round out our Zoo crew
We don't even need
Alex you're really dumb
You're a traitor,
Salman Ali
Terrible
Talking to
We're not doing this
Shut it down.
Syfy
Of this year
June 23rd episode
And this clip
I think is really illustrative of why it's dumb
To try and talk to someone
Like Alex karev
I think that you're never going to really get
It proved he's talkin about the Charles sells Supreme Court
And we talked about that quite a bit in our 2003 episodes
So far
Here is his take
Akon people who try and correct him about the the rule
Supreme Court rules
I'm individual
For trying
Little form
Literally
Jog
I'm sorry
Apropos
Federal ruling
No that's not true at all these random people absolutely correct
But boots fascinating about this
Is at least in 2003 Alex seems to have an awareness of this
Extinction
Between the headline and body of article
That distinction is
Gone is present-day awareness
That you need to read beyond the headlights yeah we want to start barking
Viscerally insulting
Have you know
Decency
Cool
Yeah I think
These people are emailing him or correct
And
He's just
You can give him exactly the right information
It'll just about. You need to read deeper
What you don't understand is how to read these documents
Actually mean the opposite of what they say
Yeah if somebody
He's telling you
You're not reading something right
Because you are engaging with what it says right
Then you are
What do you say you know like you have to go to First print
Suppose we agree that what are we talkin about
A book that you've written in the margins of the book I'm reading it's a fundamental disagreement about like
Take what you can
How information is taken from source
New receiver of information will then leave me alone forever
I don't care who that over there but don't f****** pretend
Don't pretend it's anything other than an art form
About the notes
Barracks
Story on this day
And this
Is fascinating
Minecraft
Huge problem
And
He is on the exact wrong side of this issue based on his political principles
Wayne
Auburn internal
A 1988
If they are found to be
Really
Brevard
Now
During art class
Alicia calls
The year
I don't know about this art
School Story art class got out of hand real quick
Is really interesting about this guy
Police officer in Falls River
And to look
I was just trying to prevent this as
Police state
Kind of things
Zero tolerance for all this stuff
Eat Jam.
Right right right
I don't know what the art
Exactly how it relates
To the police guy getting fired for smoking.
Application
Fall River Police Department has a zero-tolerance policy on smoking
Officers whether they're on or off duty for a very specific reason
I wonder if you can guess
Could you can you Workshop in your brain why
That might be the case
They're the only cops who carry around hand grenades at all times
Yeah they all have cartoons and TV
It's because they don't want to allow for
For any insurance claims that prevent things like smoking linked heart or lung cancer is being work relay
So if you're disallowed from
Smoking at work
And you have one of those conditions they don't have to pay out in the insurance
You're right I should have assumed capitalism was the problem
I need money somewhere along the line the fun case for Alex and I are both
Against this thing before
Completely different reason
I'm opposed to the world because they can take
Clearly don't care if some
One smokes or not they're just trying to
You know save money by not having
Play some cops health
Right I was supposed to because he's created a fake version of the story to present
It's just yet another
Example of the New World Order takes over
It's discipline human resources
That's so f****** annoying every at all I can't come on man
Is there nowhere
Alex seems to think
This this
Bizarre notion
That
In this case
The cop should have to go on trial
It's not the cops
Jeffrey
Has nothing to do with it
Do the feds put people in bathtub acid whether they do or not is irrelevant
This is a human resource
Not allowed to face my
Volume don't work for us anymore nobody's nobody's
Put into jail
I got in trouble back when I used to work at a subway cuz one of my co-workers saw me eating a meatball and snitched up
Did not have a chance to face my accuser
For the ship
You're done for the day get out of here
I did not get you processed
Are you going to assume that you've eaten the meatball I could have been anybody you can't trust that I wouldn't
Accountright
30 snitch you can bring in
I need been proven that eyewitness accounts
Easily
It looks very good source
It's payroll
Alright alright
Bets to Vaudeville
So
Like legitimately convinced
That somehow
This smoking
Of the
The cop did
The crime
That he needs
To have due process
S4 right
It's so ridiculous
I like it
Import
Tobacco
The cops
Forgot there's no right to Due Process based on employment
This is a completely silly thing that Alex is coming although maybe it's not the worst idea in the world
Maybe you'll be good
To get rid of at-will employment where workers are seen as disposable Commodities they could be replaced in the song
Have to prove their case in court you don't think that to Alex would appreciate think you're going
I know that's what he saying but I don't think he's saying that I think that Alex Wood
Totally be in favor of this
Considering how huge an infringement that would be on a business's ability to operate within the
Mythical free market
And considering how many big government processes we need to be put in place to make sure businesses adhere to this ain't gave their employees
Affair day in court
I wanted to find a goddamn Alex
Millie Weaver in court
I want it I want it I want a case of Alex Jones vs David Knight
For firing
Alex call Steve Steve pieczenik
Human resources
If the cops use fire drunk
Terminator
Appoint the corkage
Decide whether or not
It is valid for him to be fired for smoking when there is a statute that says
You can't be fired for smoking that you can challenge that statute eventually but it doesn't have
Anything to do with whether or not the person who
Snitched on you smoking was anonymous
You want due process
You have to face your accuser You're Not Innocent till proven guilty
Also is
He's making it sound like
Is there was an anonymous tip
And they went to the cop and they're like man
Somebody said you've been smoking
I've never taught before in my life and I like pulled his jacket open and pulled out a pack of Marlboros and Alexa
Put it in the evidence Locker
Austin B
His back and it's courted him out of the building
It was just like a man you can smoke
Spend a lot of time on this story and I just think there's a
Fundamental problem with it that if you spend
Time thinking about what the issue
He's mad about it yet realize that this flies
Completely in the face
Of every weirdo conservative idea he has
The idea that if this one like if he got his one wish on this
Except the unintended consequences for the tear down his entire house
Like if he accidentally got one wish
Spay today I'm going to Grant whatever the first thing you say on your show is
This would be the accidental labor Revolution that we've all been waiting for
I think it's some modicum of this is probably could be good but I think that if you had to
Like have a court case for everybody fire
I don't think that's productive I don't necessarily think that by advocating for accidentally
I don't know maybe if it was that much of a hassle to fire somebody
Betraying better and treated well
Maybe maybe
I used to manage the theater and go to court every time I watch fire skid
Would have been a pain in the ass
So Alex is a good bit of time on this
And I'm starting to feel like maybe this is going
Going to be what the whole show is about maybe I'm getting a little bit
Feel like I'm walking
Been through some mud
And then this happened and I
Saw the light the sun coming out from behind the clouds
I was like yeah
The difference between Harry
AR
Call Matt
Fifth grade difference
Between Tolkien
In Harry Potter
Token
What's in a reference book
Prefer Magic
Is the Harry Potter books actually taught people how to do magic whatever
Huge problem
Let's just stop there
Before we before we go any further
And because every five seconds I just be like
Expelliarmus and knock the f****** microphone out of your hand
Just for the joy of it I wouldn't
Exist because I've called people who like Harry Potter.
Somewhere I do like because actually what I was saying is
B Generations version sci-fi is better
The fantasy that appealed to my child imagination is different
Then this Generations in that alienate
It's made from the pop culture and I feel sad about that people like the things that I like it
Do a lot of them
I'm disconnected they like Lord of the Rings good safer
It doesn't
To a certain extent I guess I agree with
Lord of the Rings
You need the ring
In order to do all of the absolutely do not need the Rings
To do magic
If there's wizard
Character dies and comes back to life through Magic
Wait
Gandalf
Oh
I didn't consider in the main character
You're right
Did you like the movie
I love Daddy
So what are the great things about doing is it doesn't teach you how to do
Actually
I believe the David Lynch version does
Teach you that if you yell loud enough you can explode
Oh that's good
New Harry Potter books
Which one
Just got released
Ryder this 2000
Secrets
Snow
House of Cards
To think about it
He's wrong
RedTube
Wow
Which
The ones in Harry Potter I thought you was talking about the first one cuz it wouldn't be like
Could be bringing about the movie the first one was on the solstice
Philosopher's Stone was released in 1997
This was June 21st in 1997
Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone came out on June 26th
I don't know how close you have to be to the solstice for to be a conspiracy but I guess 5 days is good enough
What are the other nobody nobody expects like on the day
You know you get like I know there's a 3-day late fee there's a 5-day Grace.
It's like paying rent
I like the the
Big piece of evidence Alexander
It was released
Maybe if you maybe if you learn how to speak Elvish in token you be able to do magic
Maybe Alex just sucks and reading Elva
It wouldn't be the only language
There's more
There's more evidence
Justin was just one book came out on the 12th
The second book Chamber of Secrets came out on July 2nd 1998 which was not a solstice
Third book The Prisoner of Azkaban
Came out on July 8th
It's the fourth book The Goblet of Fire came out on July 8th
And the fifth book The Order of the Phoenix which should just come out on July to all right side June 21st 2003
What's the summer solstice
Hey there we go lightly found one
I think that's the new Bible the fifth book The the
JK Rowling
Here is how
Ucreate
A grande
Spirit
You really Spore books released
I have a bunch of other like summer release dates when you know baby kids are getting out of school
Plenty of free time that they would
Would have to read books for
For school
If you go on summer reading list that parents would
Be more Act
Dubai
Bulk of them mad also it like
The Tempest
Like what magic is fine and what magic is not
Huh
Because I'm sorry I can't say that in here
We're not on sale
See if you rhyme while
Stirring
Bubble bubble toil and trouble
Macbeth taught children how to do magic
The script
For the magical ritual is right there
Yeah
I don't know I wonder if the Harry Potter thing is Alex just
Heats education so much
It's a school books about school Furious
I wonder if that's it like he actually thinks that like well if you read this
Kind of like going to hog
You know my favorite character infection is
Sandwich
Cuz he clearly never had an education
I would love it if like
You just got to sit and talk with Alex
Turned out that
He like
Just got a little bit drunk one night was a relief
Through the Harry Potter book
He came for the Sorting Hat
You have nightmares
Does nightmares about the Sorting Hat of Slytherin
No one will ever know
Assertive
We're looking at this and then recognizing that nowadays Alex
It's probably pretty into the daycare
You know what
The thing that's different about
Tolkien and Harry Potter
Is it Harry Potter taught people how to be more race
I do think there's something
King of of the fun
Okay this is teaching kids how to do evil magic
And you know
18 years later
I'll defend
The
The author
Who is teaching kids how to do magic
Stickman
Unreal
So it's not the only thing that's demonic though
You know the Harry Potter is pretty demott
When I was
When I was 10 years old when I was 11 when the first book
Came out my church got ahold of it
And they gave it to me they were like read this to see if there's any
Real magic
Really
Is this okay to give to Children's or is their children or is this
Demonic I didn't know it was like yeah
This sounds
So familiar to me that's
That's what I do remember hearing
About that
Like I do I know I remembered hearing stuff about people who had that I never experienced that like first
Time
Those books
We're coming out
You like my mom was even reading
Yeah and I like I thought I feel like
Extremism didn't touch our sort of religious
Community will I will never forget this
Because it was a weird moment
Of both like
Growth
And insane cognitive dissonance
Coming out of the first movie
Smione
And what's up with my family
Rights and my dad said who is
Super conservative Chris
My dad said like
After the movies like you know what I liked it
I liked it because they solved
Problems
Without using
That was how they won in the end it's nice if not using magic and I was like
And the reason that that's
Both
A good
Interpretation and insane
Is because he was afraid
To see the movie
Because there would be too much Magic
Usher and it would be evil
So
It's like
Yeah okay. Okay alright
I worked at the movie theater when one of them
Came out I don't know which one
Like a third one
And a friend of mine
Who worked at the theater with me sauce
Hey came out he's like
Don't watch a movie is so funny
Scary
I thought like valve
I watched it like a week later it wasn't scary at all it's like what the f*** is going on
Movie that I will watch that movie
Okay
Summation
How to say about Harry Potter
Alright
Do you get it you get it now I do like the idea of Alex being like I Repent of rock and roll
Oh my God
Listen to rock and roll I Repent from Rock I stopped listed I'm a happier and healthier person
Just listen to Kris Kristofferson by yourself
He also sings along with a lot of like pretty
Demonic leaning Rock later is
Career
Excessive gas coming on the show Scott Goldberg
Scott
Goldbergs
I don't know Alex mispronounces it like 30 times
And they have a nice moment is like ice
But anyway he's going to have this guy on and
He points out that he disagrees with him
Okay
They're all here
I got pumped when I heard this
Because I was like okay so you're going to have to people
We're both arguing that foreign troops are being brought into the United States and they're going to argue about whether or not the government
Is behind
Right right
This doesn't happen this this is not payoff at all
It doesn't they don't argue they just talk about how far and troops are
Cummin mechanic
I know it was
Balloon deflate
Yeah that's it that's like
Marvel versus
Does DCR give
In terms of
My surreality is better than yours
Yeah and then in the end you don't really even argue
About that
Pretty good
You know what's great
Cartoon people who draw
So Alex is not too
Surprisingly opposed
Affirmative action
Not right around this point 2003 there were two Supreme Court decision
When's that were regarding
Affirmative action
Especially regarding School admission
In process
These two cases essentially if you took both of them
Together
What Vicky
Conclusion that they came to was
But having a point
System
Or anything we're like if just by virtue of
Being of a minority group you got
Appoint
Or if there were quotas
That's unconstitutional
Schools can't do that right
Having some consideration about the diversity in the makeup of your University in terms
Admission
Processes
Narrowly
Is okay
It's not something that is considered unconstitutional
Alex has a bit of a weird take on all this
And the good old boy Network
Preferential
Show me side there for sure
Yes
That appeals to some people
Inasmuch as there are these Fat Cats In The Legacy Folk
All this s*** handed to them on a silver platter
Some people
Mike Hira clip like that
And get tricked
By that being very appropriate
I accidentally agree with him being like these minorities
These are also getting all of our s*** that's kind of amazing
Is exactly like
Big fat cats
The people that
Are crushed underneath big fat cat
That's boots
Yeah yeah what Alex is saying is basically that there is this sort of three tears
There's another one
I can't believe I can't believe
Yeah that's it
That it got to this
Essentially what
Behind the argument that he's making
It's pretty easy to miss that
If your
If you're just listening we can order
That is the real kind of affirmative action
Realize that you're internalizing a fairly racist perspective along with
I am at suck
Are you racist or Super 8
Sometimes I'm very generous
So Alex call and this guy is Dad
Either doubting
Thomas
He's the sort that would see the holes in Alex's hand
Metaphorically would be Alex's documentary about Bohemian Grove
Sure and then this guy is that
Did Bohemian Grove is all evil and devils
Far afield that metaphor
Is that doubtful even if you saw evidence of something and Alex
That's cool
In Arkansas you're on the air
My dad is a minister and I was telling him about the
Bohemian Grove in
Anything
Something that kind of shock
He said you know what
Even if I see it with my own eyes
Communication
Turn books
See all this proof
I believe it
Pretty sad huh
Believe a lie and
You know
Oh wow
Yeah
Dad not believe me but I prefer human cry
Some people say that's the ultimate sin and his response to that was
Oh wow wow who would have guessed that some people would think that it's blasphemy against the Holy Spirit
Unforgivable sin
Maybe it's not believing
Jesus said it was honor thy father and mother so in this
Particular Circle
Alex is 180 away from who is committing the ultimate sin
Let's not surprised
Yeah I would guess that this is a telephone problem where the dad is actually saying
I don't find this evidence
Compelling
I can't get this is bulshit
You can put as much b******* in front of me as you want
I'm still not going
By the arguments being presented cuz it's b*******
Discolor
It goes off the rails a little bit cuz he has another question
Garlic
I don't know
Another question
You know what the animals
Looks like the Jewish protocols
We sure thought
Protocols
Score
If you can if you can take a whiff
Anolon a softball question like that that is how you do it
Wow that's pretty bad
I think
I think there are some people who don't know what
Ton
Maybe maybe you're a layperson
You may not know
About the alcohol Protocols of the Elders of Zion
Maybe you don't know about it or maybe you've heard of it I don't know who wrote that I have no idea
But if you're someone like Alex
Where do
Plus
Of your audience
Believes that they're real
Mbara plan
To take over
Western culture or whatever
You have kind of a responsibility
Do you have a position
You could have the responsibility to
Especially if you're not
Convinced that they're real
To be able to tell this caller
No this is a forgery this was this is not real
Complete yet
You can't just play like the game like I don't know maybe three Levi if not
I mean we did an entire episode on it the idea of somebody
Asking me like
Do you think that this methane text
To kind of
Hopefully do something about climate change
Is actually the Jewish protocols trying to kill us all
I would be like
Listen
You got to use what you need
To believe what your
Haha
That's probably it
I don't know what they could be
I'm not saying one way or the other I don't know
Familiar with what
You're talkin
You have responsibilities be familiar with it when you're
Do you know this
Deep into a career in conspiracy I would say
Especially when your worldview is essentially swapping out
Jewish people in the pros and cons
To be Elders of Zion and just putting in
Whatever I want envelopes
And I think also you have a responsibility when you recognize that this person is
Probably younger
You know you talkin about his dad and like an argument with his daddy sounds Kong
Like this is a this is not necessarily a person who's fully formed in a lot of ideas yet
Your you're
Just this responsibility that
Just being
Dropped
Disgusting weird
This
Sometimes going back
2003 is
Is on some of these calls you know you hear a younger voice
And you're almost like
Trappe eye or at least I suddenly have this like
Cut 2
January
If this dude called
20 years ago it is entirely possibly like 3536 and he could be in there
You know like how I think that's
Crazy
This dude could you
Just calling Alex
F****** Jones
What happening this f*****
This guy wasn't there because
He was actually in court over firing
Hangover termination
He was he was trying to
That's better solid Alibi I'll give him that one
So Alex gets to this author
The guy who wrote Silent invasion
Again here's
Yours is a
Earlier
So Alex and Scott
Are there big point is that tyranny
Is
Hear from you gotta face it
Sometimes even these dudes who do this deep research and stuff check
Sometimes even I can't believe how bad it hurts so bad it's
So bad
Urban Warfare
And now it's come out
Call absolutely
Don't have days where I don't want to believe
Days that where
You're going up in is America
Believing in the ideals that are
I still to this day
Just sometime
Just wanted to go away but
Only lasts about three minutes and then I realized
And I think a lot of people
Just pulled out of my face
They can't be out there at the pond
United States of America this is
The beacon of freedom
Throughout the world or what used to be
I wanted to go away fretted
Took me a long time to
The grips with
The truth and I opening
Experience
The showed him like what was
Crawling under the rock ignore
Did you see the rock on top of all the bugs underneath and what have you
Be kind of would expect that like
You know
Continuous path is a new world order researcher after this point after 2003
The word out like Alec
Scott's currently the host of a radio show and podcast about the Las Vegas Raiders
The NFL here seems like he's been pretty able to go back to
The Gruden situation
He's he's not too I don't know
Seems to have
Closest
Oh man
I think it is really f***** up though
That
The DHS is a horrific
Organization
He's right
But there's no kgv
There's no hidden
It's just it's just
Pop's attic
Oh man
Sure that's what it is
Yeah you're right it's just not a good book and sensationalizing it in the way that folks like Alex do doesn't deserve
Legitimate
Criticism
Just f***** up
Yep so they talked about immigration a little bit here and I think this is bad
Disease
Mexico
Telling mothers
Chico in Spanish
If your
You can get better care in the United
Go over the Border even if you're arrested
Because they know that once they cross over the Border
People can
Can have a child here
States in America
Our hero but
Alex is just like pretty great replacement to eat
He's dumb people will vote the way the Democrats want them to and they've been great replacing us since the beginning
Man
Yeah I why I think that sucks
I think it's a horrible perspective that Alex has
They're just
They're bringing in
Educated
Did people become
They know that
They won't learn
I don't know about freedom
I mean
Just what a name
Insane weight of
View people
I would I would suggest that if Freedom it actually does exist in any real sense
Everyone in
Inherently
He knows about it
You you would even Turtles
Viscerally be able to understand what freedom is
Elaborate
Private property document you need to understand
In order for freedom to really be captured
I don't even I don't even mean to go to first grade
To know that when I'm in first grade I am not free
Trapped
School like that's
If you knew it
I also think it's like kind of too
Perspectives that you can take
America
If you hear that there are people let's say in Mexico who are being told that if they're pregnant
They should risk
Fleeing to the United States
And getting arrested
Because they get better Healthcare in order to
Protect their child
You can go down the path of like
Look at these manipulative fuc
Or you can go the other direction and look at it like
Wow that is a terrible choice to have to make
What can we do about the situation
That exist
You know it's a difference of perspective to blame as opposed to
Address how can you hear that sentence of like
Here is the choice that someone is faced with when they get pregnant
Either
Maybe die Where You Are
Or maybe die somewhere else
But somewhere else maybe your baby has a better chance
A slightly better chance
There's no way to look at that
In a rational way without going well
Anybody who is just
A b getting pregnant
In existing
At threat of death
There's a huge problem there
So before we ever even get
To the United States
What the f*** is going on
Wait a second are you telling me that if you're trying to do better for your baby
The country will just go
We're going to have to
Pick up you and then send you back to die
That's f****** out of your attic
Control may I present to you thought
Freedom
You know what I don't think anybody's free in those scenarios
So Alex's dad as we know is
And he's done some work for
From CIA fellow
But turns out he was
A lot of clients
So turns out
Remarkable
This to all people who could have information that Alex
Hopefully there were any lieutenant colonel
All the lieutenant colonel's got their Dentistry work done by Papa John
Definitely
Okay
Alright so
So the
The check
The checked Army
Sure
There at the border
To invade the United States
It's a shoot border people like a border patrol people
On us soil
That's part of the
I mean just the Czech Republic get a cut
Of the United States after they overthrown
I don't think the Chinese and the Russian government are going to
Carve out Iowa for the Czech Republic of Maine
No sir
I assume it's kind of a combined effort towards the Water World Government Shoreline
At that point there will be
Pecan trees
Look at it from that prism from the larger perspective
I think that Alex is telling the truth
She's not
Ucbh
Trouble
Oh yeah oh yeah this is got to be a violation of some confidentiality
I mean everybody who goes to his dad should be in very big trouble like why are you going to Alex
Jones of Infowars his father
I'm telling him
What do coral code
Secrets is there a some kind of an agreement I don't know this
Just listen here listening you would know
I would have
That there's some kind of a professional
Navigation
Like I do like if you're on the gas or whatever and you're like passed out stuff right
Keep that to yourself like the doctor-patient confidentiality kind of
I would think especially if you're the top border
Pro person or in the CIA
Wgno the videos where somebody's
Driving their kid home and they're all drugged up from the dentist
The dentist while you're drugged up in the chair although now I want to see a YouTube video
The top guy in the CIAA
Why why don't we all just
Her down
And find out where
The top people of all the organizations get their Dentistry
Rhino
Outdoor warehouse
He gets around he's really good
So this. Guy I did not think there was much
To his
Perspective is very
Standard
Kind of un Invasion New World ordering on Sunday
And I also didn't
Feel like I had much respect
For how he was describing his
His process
Yeah I had one of those one of the sources of my book
He was very afraid
Compose
Look
But you don't want them until your kids anyway
Either you're going to
Quite get more people on
All come together
Country
I don't trust you anymore
Look I can't do the
They're going to kill my kid
I'm going to kill your kids
If you don't put this in my pocket
Yeah I think it's a little Boolean
I don't I don't I don't feel like this is how you should treat sore suck you man
You coward you loser
I demand you produce the things that I know you must
Cuz you're already assuming
The Source materials
And you're behaving as if
This isn't how you
This is not what the game is.
That's very rude
At the very least
Is
Etiquette
You know like a lot of having bad bathroom etiquette
You know the
I think a lot of the time it's generally
Talk to people too much
Reminder on business has the one specifically next to you and starts of a Converse
Station
Out of your out-of-pocket
Am I think that Alex actually has a pretty decent complaint here if this did happen delay
Globalist
But you need to understand something
Really want
Larger one in there was wine
I said
On the record
For the record
Yeah man
That would be
The highlight of my life
Hilarious
I want to be in a bathroom so we're just suddenly be like you're Jordan
Yes you will believe that if you're a listener the show and you ever run into Jordan in public
Don't say we love your show
Please say we're going to get
Buggy rides at
Otherwise
Otherwise we won't know for
For sure
Based on Alex's stories about like
Seeing demons
Teleport in
Into people and stuff
I think that
His credibility in terms of the details of the story or maybe a little bit sketchy
I don't know who this guy is
Was Lionel fella is but like if he has a good sense of humor
Maybe he wasn't if he was joking
Pasala Joker joking and I do happen to me and they were joking nothing like f*** you
Dude
Bump elbows you have a great time
Amazing
But so that's
That's a
Whatever the case
Probably something rude happened in that bathroom and I'm not I'm not for it
For some reason of Paula topkins ghost in the bathroom the monster in the bathroom B
I think it was awful
Freak Wharf
Where he's he's like a
You know that scene in horror movies where the guy goes up
To the goes up to the sink
Is it a real loan
He's just like all man
I just need to get
The water on my sink.
And he looks up in the map
I realize one day I was in my own bathroom
That if that were to occur
The monster would have to say
Excuse me
F***
After after
We have this
Protracted boring interview
We Outta some more calls
One of the things
Started to notice
He's especially during this.
And even
I'll tell the present day
Alex has
Like standard
Call Ursula like
Carlos is a guy who calls in all the time now
House phone
The reason that we could pick out something like old man house phone is
Because
He called in a bunch and always got through there's this weird British guy who Alex seems to not like much
Who calls in quite a bit
But he gets through
A lot
And then
New World Order
The other conspiracy about polish Hot Dogs
People putting ketchup on them a lot of thoughts about
I want your origin story to have been
Called in one time
When you were real young and not remember the
Exact date
And then to discover it on the show that would be In Crowd
First of all
No thanks
No.
Don't think
I want first of all I wasn't in Illinois
I would have to be pretending to be in Illinois
Missouri who's really into ska
Then maybe maybe we will have a
Conspiracy
Okay
Is it cool to wear rainbow suspenders
Get off the line kid
What kind of ride is your favorite mine the Zoot Suit
That's more sweet
So we have one last trip here and I just think it's
The bad summation of this episode
Here are several
Yeah
It was so good I'm going to re-air
Your shows rebroadcast
Wikipedia The Man episode of Seinfeld
We're really going to play this one a lot
Syndicated
So dumb
I think that this show is episode was a little bit light
Oh and actual content
Not a whole lot going on right but that cop story you think is pretty funny there and then
Alex's
Discussion of Harry Potter is
Anytime we get a nice cultural Touchstone it's always really important
You just experienced
Whether it's
His take on the Watchman for his take on
Oblivion
Other take on Oblivion
There is an alternate universe where
Fiscal is the guy on Infowars
And Alex and Ebert
I have been working together for you
Sure I think that would be great that would be great Alex
If Alex is
Career does Fall Apart
You know it,
Months and years
I would like to
6th and Olive Branch
Vodcast with him where we talk about movies
He just talked about man what do you think this is about
I mean I would I would legitimately watch a movie with Alex
And just be like okay
Now I want you
To tell me the plot of this movie
Tell me what you remember happening in order
I just want to see how your brain
Yeah is this real
What is real and what is not real secretly real or is this the nonfat
Start a movie podcast
Weeds first episode
Dune
Round Table
So Jordan
We come to the end of this and I have to say that
Harry Potter is evil don't read it
Cuz if you do you'll get magical powers
I would also like to say it
1:35 a demon face
Say no
You have other plans
It depends on it like ass at the very least ask
The follow-up question like what type of
Feasting upon demons or are you on the menu
Definitely
But
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan
Alex
Birthstone colors