Damn important swetik
I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Alexa Duran works by the author of Alex
Dude
Jordan Jordan
Quick question for you
Switch price
Is it the best spookiest of all days
We're recording is on Halloween
You can't hear this because because we're recording this
Audio thing but I'm in full costume
I'm Frankenstein's monster
We're just hitting the Warriors going for it and we got together to record this podcast around
A lot of wasted effort but
Feels good
You know it's funny he was a little bit like
The Gift of the Magi thing I told you not to wear costume when you told me not to be both trainings other
I like
I like Halloween is much as I like any other holiday
I've always had a
Dottie is not good
To be surprised to hear this
A softball for candy
Is the candy based holiday and
I'm thrilled for that.
I'm excited for tomorrow the TV on sale
And unlike the other candy holiday Valentine's Day you don't have to enjoy anyone else
There's no exit
Dictation if you want to just turn off your your porch light you don't have to worry if I say anything to anyone
Possibility to give these kids can't even bother yourself
Bibarel
I thought Halloween was evil
So we would legit
Shut off
All of our lights
I'm going to a
Backroom so no one could stop by and tricks
Yeah I know that this is well-trod territory and probably even a little bit haky but I really
They hated the guy down the
Street who would like
Act like a corpse
On his board oh yeah you totally
Probably yeah I remember the
Exactly
Have to that guy's house
From my house
I like
Know what would you get out of there
I guess he gets the knowledge that he is
Hundreds of children literally to the point where they remember the pathway to his home
83077 bill
Feel like I got to avoid that
F*** that guy
Recently got to the new James Blake album it came out
Few weeks ago
Fantastic
It might be his
His best album
No James Blake he's like he's a British dude who does what you would call like almost over
Are you know like imagine
Pure tones
Voice
Never really slow down dub music
Okay
Very strange here in words
Really good
It's really good
Describe but it's really good
To describe it I also would need you to find them
D'Angelo
Sure
It's one of the greatest songs ever
Define
Alright
Jordan today we are checking in on October 29th 2020
It is you know it
It's Friday's episode from my last week
Where the present
Let's look into it it
It's kind of like me
Why are behind my back where twisted my arm but I want have a Spooktacular
Halloween Spooktacular
But here we are in the present day
We'll just have to live with it
New I walked out there
Do first
Jordan ever mentioned by mail bag gift of green Russian soda I hope it was still enjoyed
I think it was
I received a recall
Sorry about that
Bill from Toronto got a nice message from Bill from Toronto it turns out
I heard about the show from a neighbor
That's community
We're talking about never considered that a neighbor might give me any recommendations or anything
Toronto and rarely your neighbor
I'm a policy wonk working on the railroad
Thank you so much and I'll probably walk
All the livelong day
To follow up with
Remarkable restraint
So I think I'm going to probably butcher the
Pronunciation
Next
Make an assassin
It's a belief listen
That's kind of thing but
Magnificent magnificent
You're not about to walk
I'm a policy wonk
To the shoutouts
Lizzie bones
Thank you so much
Happy belated birthday present clay thank you so much you are now what time
Democrat
How's your 401k
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Sneaky
Hey Thursday there's always a loophole anytime we try and close one door they open a window
Yeah I mean I was really committed
To the Ole thing of no more birthday shout out but it turns out
You're a traitor
God no
This Is the End
Table into a miserable druid
Start the beginning of the episode
Some covid related news
I wanted to show you this whole stack this morning
This is just today
Local newspaper
Doctors remember
Or telling you to remember
Nobody
Western world
They say we don't know why an NPR stories and
ABC stories
These others just say it's just a new saying just get used to
Strokes
Blood clots in lungs
No one knows what it is
Yes
So this is a headline Metallica's reading from
The times of India not from local papers all over the United States
He's entirely misrepresenting the point of the Arctic
Alex wants this to be something related to covid vaccine side effects
That's not what the article is actually even
About at all
This is borderless an op-ed about the fact that while we often think of heart attacks or something would only affect older people
Younger folks do chameleons
And heart conditions to just at a lower rate
General reason cited
Nothing to do with vaccine
Quote well conventionally vices were blamed for hurting
Youth in their twenties and thirties today face the risk of
Developing heart disease
Due to their sedentary lifestyle stress and diet
If you read the art added pollution but I'm going to guess the timesofindia doesn't want to add that
Throw that interview like if you read the articles
Discussion is not about a phenomenon where
Justine sencakova
In the last seven and a half years ago a medical college has treated about 7400 hard page
Of these 4.1% were less than 40 years of age and 21% under
This article even discusses the
This is an issue that
Particularly more severe in
Amigo area in
When India because
A high incidence of diabetes among
The Goan population
Could be one of the reasons why more people in there you there
Detected with heart
The reality is just that even
Before covid vaccines were a thing that we knew it exists or even
Covid-19 we do it exist
The rates of heart attacks and young people were on the rise
Although Americans are suffering fewer heart attacks as a whole
The rate of heart attack
It's for people under 40 is in
Increasing
That was from a Cleveland Clinic article published on April 26th
The article discusses many of the same variables as I timesofindia article sedentary lifestyles
Compounded issues of diabetes and increases in general stressing
Hmong population
This is just a subject that the medical community is
Disgusting and paying
Super gyro
I want to just take it headlines that reflect
The long-standing
The concern and lying about them
To use them as a weapon in Atlanta back
All of a sudden people have been studying this thing for the past several 5710 years
I have started
Saying things like pay attention to it and
Is it by minutes
Covid
Obviously
Discovery but yeah
Great
Has more on this headline FM he digs even deeper
Into a sad hole
Sad reported holes
World
Dallas and it's on the side of the buses there
Doctors remember
My body's too young
Weather report all of the western world
Spotted
In wit by
Durham Transit
Normalizing this
So Alex on a meme that one of his employees on Twitter
Who's the picture of a boss with it
The cow on the side saying quote
Kids have strokes
To know the warning
King science
This has a caption that Alex was reading that was added to the image
Spotted in Whitby on Durham Transit
Are they normalizing on WhatsApp
To come
So the argument is that like more kids are going to have
Strokes that normal
So if I understand correctly
Somebody
Probably
In Whitby
Globalist
Took a picture of a complete on globe
Anak
Haha
Health is
Important
And then turned it into a right-wing meme to disparage the covered backs
Tell everybody they're going to die or allow Google
Text to demonstrate their telling you the kids have strokes
Books in order
To make you not worried when
Kids do have stroke
Yeah they can just turn anything into bulshit Gap
This is bulshit for a couple of hours
The first is that this picture that's used in the mammoth
Is undated
So honestly who's to say if it's even a recent image
Could have been at the cow that was run for a public health campaign in
For all we know
The second reason is that bad
Include the link
Two people who paid
For the add
It's an organization called achieving Beyond brain in
Injury
This group was started by two mothers who mad because their sons
Had Strokes early in life
Advocacy and awareness
This group to help other parents who were in The Situation
They were in
And how parents know the warning signs as the bus
Rustic outside
Rebecca De Manos son was 14 when he had a stroke
On April 12th
The bean Vermillion son was 10
When he had a stroke
On February 28th
Along with raising awareness Amtrak to help families with
Children affected by Strokes the organization is really about the bigger picture of you two of supper
Brain related injury
For instance many of their scholarship recipients this year had trauma-related brain injuries like
Who was hit by a bus
Strokes in young people it's not a new phenomenon and the work these mothers are trying to do with
Really admirable stuff
Because there's a very important variable that's brought up in this
2015 article in the
The journal vascular health
And risk man
Strokes in young adults are reported as being uncommon
Comprising 10 to 15% of all stroke
However
Compared with Strokes in
An older adults
Stroke in the young has discs
Fortunately large
Economic impact by leaving victim
Disabled
Before their most productive
Debeers
Anyway this organization dedicated to helping
Make sure the children who suffered injuries don't get left behind they put an ad on a bus
Canada
Somebody took a picture of it which is now being used as Auntie covid vaccine propaganda
Repulsive behavior from top to bottom
And the transmission
Alex
Reporting on this meme without any context about the organization
The put the cowl on the bus
Incredibly irresponsible
Just disrespect
The all-around
Yeah you know sometimes when they're inventive
Kind of
Have fun or interesting
In this situation this is just
F******
Sad
Yeah
All across the board
Everybody doing things is
Sport station is sad lazy everything
Yeah this is awful
The group allegedly behind this billboard is from all indications
I'm doing really important work
And the only end result
This is Maybe
Targeting them
Is being part of a conspiracy to normalize stroke
Yeah you killed
Two birds with one stone
You know you get to make a conspiracy and then you get to bother people who are doing good
That's pretty disgusting Wing wants all the
Pretty disgusting
I recently
I know maybe maybe it's cuz of covid
I know everything's okay
Publication the second-most
Populous country in the world
Rajkumar
Very popular 80's movie star over there in Bollywood
The covid-19 vaccine
He's doing fine pugs
Valley.org
46 years old
What
Weird
Really
Odd way to Enzo it is
Set the passenger
Puneeth Rajkumar is a sad bit of news
Popular actor in only 46
Six when he died for
From a heart attack
Alex is lying and making s*** up and Order
To use this dead man's memory is a prop
For his anti-vax propaganda
Easy pretty thrash tomorrow's a huge star so it struck me as a little weird to imagine that he was
Just now getting this
He's also really public face for healthy living
Things this didn't sit right with me at all
If you look into this for
Even a second
You'll find that he got his first dose of the vaccine
Seen on April 7th
I know this because he
Tweeted a picture of himself
Getting vaccinated
I don't let you can't believe screenshots like that we just said there was it was there a date on there
5 minute had to have been prior to April 7th
Time travel alright well now we're talkin
I also know that by June Denise was helping the Indian
By peering and psa's about the
The importance of Public Health measures
Including getting vaccine
I guess I can't
Definitively prove when he got his second dose but Alex
Is presented no evidence
And he's expecting me to believe that one of the highest paid actors in India
At the first shot in
April then work to the vex
Collision awareness ambassador
And somehow didn't
Get the second dose
Until late
October you get busy
You get busy Dan that's safe life
Also small point but not every movie Made in India is a Bollywood movie
Bollywood tends to refer to the movie industry in Mumbai which is
Was formerly known as Bombay
Bombay Hollywood makes Bollywood
Pretty thrash Camaros from the south of India is more associated with the kannada movie
Who's that insane
The other thing that he was known for
Was being the son of the
Sanely famous actor Dr Rajkumar
He was an actor but he went by doctor
And incidentally
He died of a heart attack
Attack which illustrates the family history of factor for
Who needs to have
Higher incidence of higher likelihood of having a heart attack
Seems like there are many many many explanations
0 of them are the vaccine
Alex is a monster he's willing to make s*** up about people who died as long as the story there.
Profit off of
The real piece of s***
Real piece of s***
This is Harsh at the gate yet
Worse
Oh hey
That's just
Legend ice
Every second shot
It's not even anecdotal is just not
True
Is lying about another beloved celebrities death in order to make
Cuz shity argument better
In this case is Australian broadcaster Russell wolf
Who died in his sleep on October
At this point I don't believe
That the exact cause of death
Is public or noun
So I can't really speak to
To that
Anti-vax protesters of used wolf staff as an argument against
The vaccine
You shut up
Wolf himself
Tweeted that he got the SEC
AstraZeneca vaccine
Being on August 9th
Over two months prior
His passing
There's no evidence at all
Vaccinations are related in any way this is just
Disgusting
Stuff
I'm listening to this episode of the Mike
I want to kick the Epis
Yeah man that's
That's
I have to do that
I don't know
It's like you intellectually I know he
He's a narcissist
6 Psychopaths
Who has
No care for others
It's just him
Right
Like
Emotionally get into a place where I'm like you know what I'll do
I'll lie about this person
Death
Yeah kill more people
Alex Fields someone lied about like what is love
Just after something like that
Spurious argument
Just the roots repulsive Behavior
And you know what
I was experiencing this and I'm like
Time window Davis
Spooktacular
Is pretty sure
Not long
I mean like even this episode is coming out in November
I might be able to release this episode a little bit earlier so some people can listen to it on the Halloween infection
Nighttime Halloween Magic
Adult
Maybe some people who don't have kids
They might want to enjoy your Halloween on the Monster Mash and
Episodes
Simultaneously they sync up at
It's Pink Floyd all over
Starbucks
Is the point where
If I was a professional I would add a lightning sound effect
So I was creeping around on Alex's website
Through like old screenshots on the way back
Machine in the archives
And I found an interview that is long buried
I've never
Seen this before it is Page
Is almost done
Accessible
This is an interview with a guy named David Benoit
Here's the title of the interview
Author of 40
Teen things witches hope
Parents never find out about the occult and the real meaning of Halloween bringing America to its knees
Well Dan
We've got a winner
Yes we do so f*** Alex Jones
Holyshit
Good God you are really getting me scared
I know it was a Spooktacular for me
To Halloween
October 30th
Twilight 2002
We have
Alex Jones
Having an interview with a guy who's written a book
About the 4th
13 things witches don't want you to know
Exactly what
H49
Can I actually disabuse you of that notion
Come on
Here's where Alex begin
The preceding
Every time I follow one of their rat holes
I find
Now we see David and California the Aztec holiday of human sacrifice with black Alters
Putting worship we hear about these different
Meanwhile
Don't
Talk about Jesus
Yeah man
You can't evangelize it's
School or you can
Yeah
I mean when I was in
In school they have alike
Meet you at the flag
Anything you know where I was
Is quite a bit of it.
The other school is
Isn't it supposed to have like
Coordinated organized religious
Activities
New World Order
Oh yeah you know I was going to say that he shouldn't bring Christianity into it
Because Christianity seems to be the one trying to terrify people about imaginary witches
Is where is witches or
Actually do magic
We don't know that
Harry Potter is a guidebook
Why would
Probably actually be a little bit
Uncomfortable doing
Episode
If we had made some progress
December 2003
A little bit more of that
Then he doesn't the president
Yeah and we also know that
F****** things
The Harry Potter and witches are real
Sew in with those pieces of information we can now do this
Is Halloween
Interview I wish this whole episode was available but it
Unfortunately
Feel about Geddy Lee
Sprite feel about
Rush you know like
Robbie moored specifics on who's the devil
Devil worship center Prague
They're less rock and roll wild frog
Everybody was at the Prague is a weirdo
What
Videos with prove
They worship the devil in Subway
Sure Limelight all about the dog
I will put a bed again
I will choose free will
Alex loves free will
Yeah but soda
Is the devil
We wouldn't be able to
Follow the devil if it weren't for free will
Good point
That is a good point.
David Benoit
Today
Am I
And that we got
Halloween
Day of Samhain
I Am 1000 years ago
I don't I don't know if
That all the tradition
1000 years ago
Continue to
Anyway I was curious about
David Benoit
Look into him
Okay
In June of 1984 David was lead of the Lord
Went David began
Glory Ministries list exposed
Truth of the damaging effects of rock music on society
The only solution being regeneration by Jesus Christ
Mad he was only a
A few years away from correctly hating rap music
What's so fun about that backstory is it
Really
This is June 1984 so we can definitely tell what was on the charts back then
How is the music industry's really into themselves today they leave a lot of evidence
84 I-10 84
25-count think so
The three songs made it to number one on the charts in that month alright
You're never going to be able to go
Let's Hear It for the Boy
From the Footloose soundtrack
The Footloose soundtrack. Let's Hear It for the Boy
Not even
Denise Williams
After Time by Cyndi Lauper
The Reflex
Spider and Duran
Satanic so maybe you should look at
It may cuz maybe it was like what happened it may cause him to
To jump off of the lakes in June
In the chart every week
You know
You probably has a sense of
It may hear the things that made it to
Number one was making waves with
Hello oh that's great
Later on uses a hook for one of the best Busta Rhymes songs
Give me some out
Collins was the world on fire doing
3 weeks
To the top of the charts with against-all-odds Jesus Christ I'm going to be honest
I don't like Phil Collins
I do but
I believe we can agree to disagree
Who can sign decided to look at
The entire Hot 100 from the week's relevant to this possible conversion and
Here are the songs that I
Are possible that made David into a devil fever
Sister Christian by Night Ranger
I want to break free by Queen
Because Freddie Mercury is gay
Yeah but I mean that's just too good
Even and even in the 80s
Is everybody hated gay people but they're like
Freddy f***
Can mercury or David the kind of guy who could be afraid of a lot
The only other one I could think of
Maybe
And that's the heart of rock and roll by Huey Lewis and the News
And that's because the heart of rock and roll is still beating replies but it does object that's true
If you'e Lewis is the one who's like week
You can't I got to stop the devil music
Then you're too far gone
Born into this guy's bio I found this nugget
David has the rare ability to communicate his message to young people as well as two parents using humor and interesting
So
Has me going into this interview that I weigh
Connect with
You know who doesn't ever
Connect with the kids
A Christian who says they can connect with the kids
With humor and
Who's scared of the devil rock music
You're scared of all music I want.
Going to put on some Bach
Oh my God
Alex real scared
Some stories about Halloween
I don't know I need a citation
Day of Samhain
Kingdom
Diane Western Europe thousand years ago right
I ended a shopper Halloween early like five little skeletons in medication
Serious issue
This is running rampant apparently kids are being kidnapped in the lead-up to Halloween
They're little
I found it it's covered up in the back back of the
It's so sad but the idea of little skeletons coming back to life on Halloween
You got to admit that
Jumping up out of the ground just
I think that if this is
Is covered up in the back of the newspaper Alex should be able to find those articles
Paper and put the pieces together to make a
Specific case
Can you cover something up
If you publish it in your knee
Newspaper in plain sight baby I understand why you would say
Hiddeninplainsight because you think it's in plain sight Android
However it is
It is not hit
Whatsoever
I just need more information
His might just be a
Fear thing
Yeah I do want to make sure everybody knows
There is no shame
I'm pronouncing it Samhain
Sure
It's written like that I get it
That's fine I never heard it out loud until I was like 50
15 or whatever of course you don't know how it's pretty
Your fault
Sure not your fault
Another
And giving kids those like weird
Orange adore Brown wrapped
Half-eaten peanut butter
If you're going to get one of those kids that's
You might as well put a razor blade in there cops
Garbage I would rather almost because
Probably wouldn't
Eat the razor blade
And then I have a lawsuit
Play one of those peanut butter candies nothing to be mad
Can apples for what I was kind of
Folklore
How funny is that somebody's like
Kids are getting hurt
Because they're eating apples on Halloween
Think of a single person that I know who would have gotten an
Even like a
Like a caramel apple or something
Like this is the wrong night for this get the f*** out of a Twix
Doesn't have a razor blade in it I don't care
So you might ask
Halloween
Google what is the
Well
Ben Wise
Blackout lower joined by David Benoit Glory Ministry
It's a great to have you on the world I brought
Thank you very much
Absolutely
So you know
Premise of Halloween is that Facebook witches believe that
The playoff between the natural and Supernatural that is tennis
During that time so they can communicate with the Dead
And
I find it quite interesting
Halloween you can tell when Halloween was coming because you hear it
See horror films in death movies and stuff
Store hours a day 7 days a week around our country
And talking to the dead is not something that's new
Sumner
Went to the witch of Endor
So now we have
Murder block
Rice salad
Care about all these wicked things happening
Okay
Unless they want our guns
Wait wait wait
You're mad at the witches about Second Amendment issue
Just got hit with the I think I just got
I do think that it's pretty impressive to be able to
Combined a conversation about how Wiki
Can talk to other worlds
Gun rights how are we how is everybody just talk
Think about it like
Well which is believed that it's when the veil between things and everybody's talked
Two Spirits before that's
Just a regular old
Saul talk to the Wichita
I just had an interesting thought
If you are somebody who legitimately believe that witches are around and they can do magic
You should know that your guns not going to be effective again
That's them
Like you should recognize that gun rights are meaningless if you're up against the witches
Well I think
Governor
I got a team of witches
Overthrow the government going to need to learn magic I really I really think that people
Quite understand what the Imp
Applications of magic being real
Trust me I do I thought about this
And it is it is very silly
It's very silly
No
Very silly I want to know which 14 things which is Due Amici
They don't want you to know that they are opposed to
Five hundred bucks right
Right now that the number one thing
Witches are real
Yeah probably
I would bet a million dollars
Sorry I don't know if this guy's book
Is actually called like the 14th
Or whatever 14 simple rules for dating
I don't know I don't think I would want to read a book by him anyway
No idea seems afraid of high school
Kids
San Mateo County Times
2002 highstone St
Nejsem Club
Transparent
An outrage
Found themselves to satanic
Society
Call presno the club James Doolittle
He originally started
The cab with the friend Matt
2 rifle things a bit alphabet
But now
That the two Juniors have cited
Pictures of Anton LaVey
They say that Satanism helps
People Express themselves
Is satanism
Return Man
It's back
It is a natural state not have to be crushed by religion
Google public school
Harry Potter in the Deep
There
I remember be
People shooting a brick about wickens
Combining Harry Potter with wickens
Just being like
If they believe Magic
They definitely can't tell the difference
Between wiccans and Harry f****** Potter right
I got nothing against
People who were
Interested in
Something like a wicker or whatever I do I do
I don't begrudge
I would argue though
These
Kids
Benoit's Hawk
About
They started it just to f*** with
It clearly said that just grateful things up a bit really said I was
And then
They found that
They like
Had some good laughs
Is in there or whatever
I'm going to guess
Is it that is a Dismount from the club
You know what I mean like yeah I'm going to guess these guys are not saying this
After graduation
Even go so far as
To say
But if someone in the first
Quotes as we started the
Club 24
Good thing Zedd
Quote says
We believe all of it now
You might
Still be getting
You f***** with you moron possible
Presentation is that they're saying they believe in our vehicle so wonderful
No they did not say actually the devil's real and Wheeler
Not worried about high schoolers having weird
Fun
Club slippery slope
Let him you let high schoolers have one slippery slope funclub with the Devil
Next thing you know the reading critical race Theory and it's all over
Over for the wrestler
Went to HighSchool with
I might
You know like
Not much
Yeah it would be something that would be interesting to
Outside of that
I don't know it all
High School
Columbia
And like Rockbridge was the other High
If there was a Satanism Club over at Rockbridge
I wouldn't care
Yeah
Not my business many generations
David Ulta
Freaking out about what
Isolated children are doing thousands of miles away from them
Is going to eventually be like
Oh maybe
This is dumb
This is a show in Texas where adults
Or talking about high schoolers
In San Mateo California
Perhaps
In this situation
Those children are more adults
Maybe
Pictures are protected by the government
I don't have to do that
I'm sorry what now
Cannot hire or fire person because you cannot fire a person because of their religious status
Did they say they're there
Discrimination religion
Discrimination
Oh absolutely
Okay
Alright oh man
To be a fly on the wall of people whose
The largest problem is
Witches are getting jobs
You're not even allowed to fire someone just cuz they say they were which
Yeah I mean like you know the same rules
The protect
People who have
Religious beliefs
Or going to religious
Applications like being a witch
It's right are the exact same rules that protect
People who work
It is no it is wild who how when a religion gets
To put its boot on the neck of other religion I like
Religious protections are terrible but when they've got the boot on their neck they go eat
Hebrew just protection
Which is definitely not cuz of us
So we get back to Harry Potter
Shockingly
I don't know if this is true cuz I don't remember Harry Potter
Yeah
I'm sorry if this is true but it just sounds really dumb
Here's the thing with Harry Potter
As I got a whole
Water stuff on Harry Potter's not fact I've got a brand new book out entitled
And I do talk about Harry Potter
You know
Five of his
And I know in my presentation how easily this for a child to go from
The real witchcraft
The way way way way
Okay no.
Dude I like Dumbledore does die and like snake dies right
But he kills Dumbledore Dumbledore told him to
Secret lyrics
John Cleese ghost I remember from the first one
Is it
Four out of the five professors
Well okay so this is just that every dark arts
Professor
Can only be there for a year
Parker Stevenson
Yeah but
I mean
Wait for the fuk what wait wait till four out of the five dark arts
Professors are dead
Oh yeah they just
Right
Yeah I don't
Five dark arts professors at the same time
So actually one is still alive but will later be bad
Furthermore furthermore if we're going to start treating this
As a
That for
We must also admit that
Ghosts are available
To just about anybody at any time goes through and play
I do think that it is strange that he's
Concerned about these
These characters being died in like Harry being able to talk to the dead because
You can easily go from Harry Potter's website to real witchcraft
Techno time then you could talk
I'm frustrated I'm frustrated by this
Talk to the Dead
That's a no-brainer
Right he's not offering me talking to the dead I got to wait for that s*** f*** that give me a couple weeks of a core
I want the you-know-what can I want to talk to the gym
It's a crapshoot
Like really boring
Yeah that's true
Just make it more interesting than you were a life
Philosophers are like Taylor Swift
We worked 18 hours a day and then I died
I couldn't breathe
What was the Industrial Revolution like choking today was a child labor
I died at 10
Thank you for creating our modern world
I'm the kid who discovered maybe we should bring a
Canary with us into the coal mine
To talk to you I just I'm just saying that some people are dumb
Didn't read too much
To look
What do you do if you don't
Particularly Harry Potter
You're going to tire wear
Treating Harry Potter's relocate very much.
Somebody who's like Harry Potter's real and
At school
If you don't read Harry Potter
So many parents
Call me
That in the classroom they cannot eat
If a child is not Richard Potter books
How they confront
Right at the main entrance or mosasaurus options Giants
Harry Potter
Teaching Aid
Piled up there
Really popular book
I mean yeah also we can solve that Barnes & Noble problem
To their God
Yeah you got you got what you wanted
No words
Displays at Barnes & Noble
I don't know if I believe that if you don't read Harry Potter you flung
Cuz I don't think any
School I don't invited the stuff to believe that it's cool would have Harry Potter be a mandatory
Peace of curriculum
Do you mean considering the fact that apparently has two parents at any given School believes that Harry Potter's real
Also it's casual reading
It's it's good for like
You know kid learning to read a lot so many different
Examples of
Peaches
Math
In a way that would like it.
I find it difficult to believe that
It's some teacher if some kid was like
Look I'm not comfortable with reading this
Oh okay what are you
I can't see that happen
You know what's ironic about that is that
For so long you do think this is
This is just like casual reading
You were to put that through a critical appreciation you be like
Oh
She was a Turf all alone
Of course
I should have just paid attention
Four out of the five Turks on the Buckeye
Yeah probably
So
I don't know I don't
I didn't cut out that much
Trump interview
But this doesn't make sense even if you listen to the whole thing
You know I
Missionary
Play this woman to the Lord and after leading her to the Lord then what he did was he
She said would you please talk to my husband because he needs to be safe so every morning he sit there and drink
Check with Amanda
Share the gospel with him
They got deathly ill
And I went and did blood work in the man fed
The doctor said
Lisa Richards are you working with rat poison
Michigan someone's rat poison you
And what it was
Coffee with everyday
Would you put a little
Not enough to change the taste
Calls Amanda guy right there
And I thought that's exactly what Isis ideas right now
Little dos after little dose first was Bewitched
Buffy the Vampire Slayer and everything else Charmed and
And they all available for our children and
They were actively recruit
At night and it's
Turning in
Titanic
Soviet-style
What what
Like I get the metaphor the
Obviously
That's we can shorten it but that's fine story is obviously like something
Pamphlet or something
You scared of non-believers my God
Anything the Bewitched is a little bit of poison
Sabrina the Teenage Witch is a little bit of poison
Yes I get that
I just don't get
Military on the streets
What an event
Shorter jump
I guess these people getting sucked off in a hot tub
Yes
Being a little bit over
Sexualize
I don't know I don't know
I guess that is also satanic
Text to Alex
I just ran
I'm going to have to
Go with
If you are
If you're telling me you know like
Did Sabrina the Teenage Witch it's all there just
You don't get to participate
Culture anymore
It's not for you
Maybe sometimes you just don't get it
Can you also be scared of like Touched by an Angel
Like you should be scared of
Christian shows that are about supernatural
Here's the problem
The Christian shows that are about supernatural s*** almost always wind up
Hand waving things away with
Very similar explanation
To it was mad
Sure
So there's a conspiracy
And that is at the school
Want to give kids
Computers
Some people might
I think that this is because
Technology
Is advancing
And computer literacy is
That's pretty important
For kids being able
Navigate
A lot of the aspects
Does the new modern world end
Interconnectedness
So the show is set in 1984 that were afraid of rock and roll Ephrata
Good Witch
And we're afraid of
Computers
A c b y schools together
So you know
Objectives of the school system must make sure that every child has a computer
And that every child has access to the internet
Cialix
Is that
If you type into your search engine the work witchcraft
340 1005
John Edwards
They supposed to talk to the Dead
If you don't believe that people can engage in necromancy
It's not really that threatening for a kid to be exposed to it
Lake Princeton
The kid I was exposed to the idea of telekinesis through the X-Men
Holy s*** I wanted to do it right
I tried and I
I couldn't and I realize it.
Fictional ability and I was able to in
Enjoy the X-Men in a different way
Completely wrong the thing is
Is the X-Men didn't give you
A roadmap to learning how to do that unlike Harry Potter which teaches you how to do math
I would argue that Alex
And David have not yet made it to the staff that I
Cross when I try to do telekinesis limited watch
Progression of understanding
When did X-Men first came out 2003
Last week
I think this is really stupid
Who's bad I think that if you
You have to believe
That kid
Can be turned into Magic
Witches
In order to be worried about the
Lincoln
Anyway
Alex
The guy who needs a respite
You know like
Oldest military on the streets there's soviet-style propaganda and Chloe's in a hot tub
Which is walking
Everywhere everywhere
Government has them
This is a guy who needs a break
You need to place that he can be safe
And then they also have another program on WGN Beyond
And these people
Communicate with the Dead
Tell my wife
Yeah
Absolutely
So
Everything but the
To the end of the age of this kind of related to a football game or basketball game
You can always
In the final inning
You can see them
Since the last 2 minutes of a basketball football game is intense
I know that they only have a short time to get it done
Some 19 years ago we were in the final Innings of the game and they were really
Trying to
Cool do realize we've been in the
Fourth-quarter overtime
For several thousand years ago
It's been a long overtime
I would argue we should end it
Jesus
God and Satan tired everything
Find we just move on it's like soccer rules
Will be an interesting proposal to try into workout
Between God and the devil
The devil would take that
He's going to be a holdout
So eight you remember
The man Michael Dukakis
Yes I do remember a man in the tank looking very strong
Do you think that he ever did anyting over
Berkeley satanic
I don't know it's getting into tank is overtly satanic I think
He likes Texas big gun
Nobita do one thing
Maybe we forgot about
I got a woman at salt that I talk about in my presentation
And she's a witch
And from
Laurie Cabot
It was a known as the official Witch of Salem she was nominated by Michael Dukakis
When he was running for the president knighted states of America
It would be good for America
What
Well it's amazing
This is not just a Democrat
You know also it was very well known that mrs. Reagan went to
Astrologers and things like that as well
Really nailed it that time
So what the event was talking about is that actually true
Laurie Cabot was named the official witch
To Salem by Michael Dukakis back in 1977 when he was the governor of Massachusetts
Pictures of towns all over the world
Decision was basically recognizing toothache
One there's a
The tradition of which
Shitted
Massachusetts Indie Northeast in general
Into
Cabot open what she claims is he
First witch shop in America
Back in the 70s
Excel's dump pills do you want to be mad at some lady selling incense and bath salts I guess that's a fun game for him to play but
Shouldn't you be a witch
Or a warlock for the magic that these pills do on your body
Armenia
It's like being in like what like 1920
San Francisco be like there's this man going around
Calling himself the king of America
What is a democracy
It's all a monarchy
Yeah
There was a person experiencing homelessness
Columbia
Andy Warhol Burger King
King crown around he called himself the king of Columbia and a lot of people would salute him and
I'm just treat him yet
Yeah
Diderot democracy
I died of a well I mean here we are the reason that I move to Chicago
Takeover of it Maher show
I can say for sure that it is entirely his fault citizens united went through the Supreme Court the way it did I had to
If we ever knew you had a coup
He overthrew Darwin Hindman
Alex
Shakira
I'm running with
Now
Based on what we know from his later talk we should know that
He
I had a lot of running how many he was there which he tried to recruit him slept with a lot of them
Yelp
Honeypot everybody a bunch of cheerleaders
Cheerleaders little bit differently back in 2002
Floating
Softer
Women's arguments seem a little bit better if he was talking about like
I hung out with
F***** cheerleader
It'd be a really forceful testimony
Certainly up
To the
Actual experience
I've had run-ins with powerful witches kind of increase his Mystique almost
Giving him a kind of full caloric
Figure
Did you know early on in your career
Well I guess
It kind of works
If you just do it later just mostly forgotten about your brother too
So it looked at this pain while guy is
Best news whenever he's talking about like being able to connect with
The kids I think
No
He's just getting really boring
About to Halloween
In here
Number one more history on
On Halloween
Somebody protect
Information is always crucial
You know I think that's
Zoobilee Zoo
Understand
What does
What the whole thing is all about
As matter fact
You know I wrote a track
Last year entitled Halloween a trick
Are a treat and I give them
The difference
Traditions like for example
Come from
Talk about the jack o'lantern you know that
Came from Great Britain
And Jack was
Reneged on it
Ended up having to get a cold
They trick the devil and they put it into a turnip and then he had to walk
The pace the Earthen
And stuff like that
It would wear masks
Because they would be afraid
That
After going to the baelfyr the bonfire that they'd be afraid till they figure they
It scares a ghost or scare the spirits Away by wearing masks
Animals
Oh absolutely Associated Press reported that
AP report
Two
April 2002 26
Devilman
Turn back on and then he put his head into a turnip
What you going to do
Addresses of adjoining like teens
Listening to that being
So bored man this guy
He knows how to engage us
Interesting fact
Rock and roll being
Of the devil
Obvious
Yeah totally off
Yeah
But there's some
Not so obvious things
Why would like to warn you
Some movies
Maybe there more fiction
Again
When you get to talking about the dead and talking to the dead in the show you
Here's the thing that really gives me Alex
Is that there's the obvious
And when I
I've done things on rock music.
And talk about the obvious
But
Settle
For example like
Talking to the Dead
There movies like
And where boy is
Supposed to see spirits
Stop nobody can see him and then you've got ghostware
They've had some
Hey buddy nothing either those are subtle
Wasn't the tagline of the 6m
I see dead people
Freddy's of the movie
It's called Coast
These are subtle thing
If you
To present to me as being a
Religious scholar
I think you would like that
Glory minutes
And you also believe
That movies are real
I think it cheapens Your Glory
If you know what I mean
But I don't think you're ready for this though
Okay
I've got ghostware
Jaitley had
Also in the movie
Lion King
Show me talk to his father who is that
And there's a lot of questions you say why was anything wrong with it well
You know I had one guy two
Christian
College one day film it's been awhile and see it that way the way I saw it was
That symbol is like Jesus
And he was talking to his Heavenly Father
How you know he is
Exactly
Yeah we got
Lion King ep the rabbit
I am afraid of the world
I don't
Anyting
To look like we have to keep going on This Thread about the lion
Because he's he's pretty concerned with the Lion King
Some people have given him some rebuttals
That might actually like it was what about this bro
Well I have I have a problem already with his first rebuttal which is I Saw The Lion King and somehow is a metaphor
Jesus
Struggling there
White down again for this because
Sorry whatever lion comes up Mike must go down
In-N-Out is
Stiletto hammer
Holy Spirit
Do you only miss one minor problem with that analogy and that's it
Father
God and
Send it to be a god
The New Age movement
Jesus father has always been God is always been in heaven
And therefore
He's never had to Diana's
Send to be an ascended master
Nefarious messages
Of Mufasa
Okay give me one second
So if I
Star Wars a really need to understand this correct
Okay
Because of
Ghost
The Lion King
Subtle
Because of
E.t.
Because
Bewitched
Haha because of Sabrina the Teenage Witch
Buffy the Vampire Slayer
We need to take our kids out of school
School is where those Pacific
Things are found
I did think that that was a strange leap not to be the conclusion of this
Stupid conversation
How about Rafiki I don't understand
That was just too obvious
Timon and Pumbaa who are they
That's if I mean is based out of
Nala is Joan of Arc
Oh my God yeah they're scared
These guys
Would absolutely go ape shitt if they ever heard of Esco
They would be over for them if you like
Crowded supposed to be joking
There's a chorus I don't get it where they from
Does magic this is devil real
So yeah man if you have Harry Potter in
School
You should be able to
Covid-19
Interesting also is
I was
Call my lady from Knox
Tennessee
Under the Hogwarts
Score for Witchcraft and Wizardry
And get into a room
And so when I told the principal I didn't want my daughter there
He said okay then water little note
And we'll take her out of the class
But you know what my suggest
She wants to that is
If that offends
Harry Potter
And go out of class
Felt lonely say that
Offended about praying in school
Yeah why don't we sue them
I don't know I think there's a slight difference between like room decorations
Around a popular book
And
Sort of
Communal
Enforced by the school organized by the school
Religious
I'm interesting about
Is that that is exactly the
The point of
All of the rest
In the same way this is a big part
Right now the right-wing is making up a way of fictional
If you put the victim of in order to consolidate their
Insane
Power already
CRT in order to get rid of any kind of
Troubling history
Let people see Harry Potter in schools or
I say
Just to be
Fair
We should allow
Prayer to be in schools all the time I'm just saying
Baroness Dandy baroness
I'm going to maliciously misinterpret Harry Potter as an actual religion
Absolutely
In order to justify me bringing religion into
The schools
That will eventually be in
Enforce
The obvious thing that he doesn't
The point that he's really
Is that Harry Potter and Christianity are both equally
Now what you think of the children
Play I'm refusing to think of the children ever again
You're at your monster
Now
Think of the kids
Who don't like Harry Potter
They're off
Exercise like Harry Potter
And I was fine just happened to you
Yeah why don't we sue them
More importantly
Precise the children
You're a weirdo for leaving
Exactly
He called her a muggle a muggle is annoying
Harry Potter's books
Supposed to be a non
Which
Are sorcerer
It's a natural person someone who doesn't believe in
When the girl left
Could you imagine what
Uprising with BMF
If someone
Like a
Hindu or say a Muslim
I didn't want to pledge allegiance
The flag of didn't want to say in God we trust her or had to pray
Amanda leaving about 2
Mother mother
Muslim Muslim
All kind of lawsuits
You know what it is
Alexandra
Does Christian
Don't say
Don't say the only
100%
False
Real thing that you
You said Diamond what if
Kids were rude
To minorities and
But here's the other thing
So ridiculous again one of those things about Harry Potter that
A close reading would analyze so f****** differently
The thing about Harry Potter
Is that the slur that Wizards use again
Wizards use the slur mudblood against
Wizards with non-magical pair
Right
All fine and it's a horrible thing to use the mudblood
All of them use muggle
All the time
Yeah it's like no problem whatsoever just this slur about a class of people
Just all the time it's those types of thing where it's like all this slur is bad
For the people I like
Find a gift layers around for all the people that aren't involved with our funds
Story
It's silly to be like
The trauma of people calling her a muggle
To somebody of a minority group and write
It does
There is not an uproar
Give a s*** about that
You would be like well you got to take it on the chin if your Traditions are different than ours are
Or whatever the f***
The only thing that's important
Is that we are always the victims
And you should do whatever we say yeah
Because we're the Vic
Yep ye
The pray in school
If your dad Harry Potter
But there's another thing that you should
To be at 4
I'm not
You know
Stay out there
They're taught how to handle us
You know
If you think that's the case then why don't you let the
Teachers peach seed
Start please frequently
Russian novels that are out there
That argument is pretty cute and I think it's kind of funny that David thinks Harry Potter is in any way similar to Left Behind
Hematic lior
Like the intent of the writing or evenly
Equality of the book
It's silly
But there's a much bigger problem
To deal with here
The books of Left Behind are very
Very specific
Sickly a story about a
Pre-tribulation rapture
The Rapture happens and then those who are left behind in the rapture
It's essentially the whole point of that 16 book series
I don't care about this at all but Alex think
Pre-tribulation Rapture preaching
Is heresy
He's a strong post
Trib guy and it's pretty funny to hear someone bring up left behind on his show
And see him not get mad about
Worries about the suggestion that left behind be taught in schools
Probably more so than Harry Potter left behind
Before
Yeah you should be furious about the idea of life behind being invoked on his show
Hate to be exact wrong image
All of this
The tribulation in the rapture
Actually is insidiously
Teaching
Patriots and the Christian
Do not be ready to fight
Furious and he's not concerned about
Somebody saying
Pre-trip might be real
This is the novel series being recommended for children in public school seems very odd
Yeah
There's also a very strong
Difference between
The notion of a school
Teaching Harry Potter
Allowing
Behind
Recreational reading
I read like five of the novels and then I was
But they kept going
Yeah
I think that if I recall correctly when they made a movie
Of that
My dad got like a pro
Press copy
Or something they wanted
Cameron
Original one
Very not
EverBank memory of emails how dumb Christianity
Look
There's
They don't do anything
And that's why
Kids are called
In school or whatever
And and also
I will say that this is an interesting fact
The David Byrne
This is next
It's an interesting fact that would help him connect
With the children
Eminem
Immediately lose
You know I read the other day
Spiders
They have their venom is more powerful than the Black Widow are we doing this
The reason why most people don't know that
Is because the daddy long leg
Spyder cannot open its mouth
Enter the human
You do not heard that red.
You know that that Alex
I forgot just like Christianity
What
Hold on
You know
The jump
The jumping spider we are watching
Level triple leaps of logic
Should I cannot understand whatsoever kind of indicates do you what their act
Actually talking about what they're actually mad about he's not mad about Harry Potter
He's mad about like feeling that people are too gay and Alex thinks there's too much
Mosquito Indian dating
They don't feel like
Their ideas are in Kent
Control of public
Education
You know that's really what they're mad about that I care about him
Book about a boy wizard
It seems like Everywhere I Go
The world that I had B
Beaten into me when I was a child
Is not the same
These people are
Yeah
Just f****** stop
And one of the things I find also
And to take the Monstrous nusenda clear over homophobia out of this
I'm trying to have a
Clunky metaphor
Many clunky metaphysics
Think about this
The daddy longlegs venomous
True
But it can't bite you because
Cuz I can open its mouth
Stop big enough to bite you
Stroke of Luck on our
Now he's saying that the Christians are like that there more venomous
Then other crew
Great let's leave that aside but you aren't venomous nest
You think they're unwilling
To flex that muscle
So are use that vent
Christianity I know not like the daddy long leg
Can't bring itself to buy
Physically
So is this is analogous at all then the Christians
Can't physically used
Is this power they are unable to exert this
Quote on quote extra venomous snakes that they have
It's not a choice
Through the daddy long leg
Nature
Their jaw
Right
I would say the metaphor might make more sense if you said that Christians were filled with Venom
And
You know they didn't bite
People that they just
F****** bothering me
You don't do you know what
You know it's teaching the kids devilry
Venom 2 carnage
Carnage
Is really really upsetting
After the
Stupidity and nonsense of Harry Potter and Rafiki being the Holy Spirit
Really f****** upset
Atheist
He just won't say anything
Tell me what they all you could never get prayer back
America
Is loaded with Christianity they just don't need about on everything
Christian stations
Be quiet go along
Oh yeah
So I can't tell if what he's saying is everybody love to pray after 9/11
Or if you think you said we can't get Pro back in
School let's blow up some buildings and see if you pray
Either way
They could go either way
But it's at least
Inarticulate
It's in articulately deliver to the point where
I think those are both readings up
Write what you could have said was there no atheists in a foxhole
Sure he know that is if that's his in
Intense right
Then that's what you should have
No one is
Is going to then create Fox
Foxholes in order to create Christy I wasn't like what we should do with the
Creative Foxhole Chris
What would you do is wish
To kill a lot of people
How to make them get into foxholes and then they will be atheists anymore
See that's what God wants
Has to do dance and that really was like wow
I think that this is
What is a convertible
You keep trying to say like people were very religious after
If that's what he was trying to say he said it
About the worst
And most
Irresponsible
Short you know I mean
Verb for me
If I was going to listen to his
We could do all of these things
But we stay quiet
I would ask
How many APA
Or
How many I mean
Let's say
How many elected representatives throughout American history openly profess to not having any
Play Just beliefs whatsoever you don't want to play this game because they'll just argue that the most
Presidents are secrets
Secret atheist there was never any point
You know George Washington
Was the only president who didn't
Read Harry might as well
So can you imagine
Going back on
50 years
Telling a church
Search about Harry Potter cuz David Benoit
Again
Process
Changing People
Exactly
See if I Carlos I was thinking the church the other day that's 156 years old they were celebrating 156
Anniversary
Could you imagine
If I came to the church
And said that there would be a boy named Harry Potter
And that he was going to be attending the Hogwarts School for witchcraft
Willow tree
Emmett children would be reading the book and end
You smashing what they having at
I said
The people in that church
Not anymore
I don't know how many churches
Necessarily were using Harry Potter Ivan I don't know what they would use it
I don't know what youth group
Need to have assigned reading
Miserly other than the Bible
Well I mean you know the power goes out
Keller and the blight
Spell I guess there are some
Youth group
Churches
Bam Harry Potter and maybe that's what he's responding
So proud of you go back to 150
26 years before but like
I mean I rather be
I will tell you that like
Gulliver's
Travel
If you got tiny people
I told them that children would be into witches they would be like
You're fuking right they are and we got to stop them
Let's go let's get our torches and pitchforks because in 1856
We totally believe riches witches are real
Google that can make a bath
There were witches and other things
Different rate for Harry Potter
Also Frankenstein the book
Churches probably mad about that came out in 1818
Do you know what they were
I'll tell you this
Do you know what the
The book churches were most mad about with us
It came out
The f****** Bible oh yeah they had a lot of us about that various books within it and
The canonization if there's a lot of trouble.
You don't even want to know what happened when they started printing it for everyone to read
Cancel it. Joking kind of Shadow ban the Bible
Bible traveled
Same direction is born it traveled all through the same Underground
Corn traveling
System in the
15 f****** hundred
I don't know because we're in 20 21 blackjack
That
The end Was Not Mere in 2003 to as it were
Yeah we were
If so we got some
Cafe
That's the trick
It's so far-fetched when we reported
But when they start saying it
Seafood
Everybody's doing it
Online that we deal with everyday out
In northern Europe
Are only a few years away is already here
Crazy
It went to Walter Cronkite or when somebody else gets up there are
You know.
Dan Rather catch
Cop or somebody like that
If Walter Cronkite did deliver this news that we are a few years away from being the as
Aztec Kingdom with human
Sacrifice in Witchcraft and all this s*** I would say
You crazy too
I would not I would not give him
You know why he's respected
We didn't say s*** like that like that the reasons that people were like oh I can trust
What's this person
Not to say shh exactly
Think that maybe there's
Is a little bit of backwards
He's so respected but if he's
There were witches
Lake Nona.
He's respected because he doesn't it
And do that s***
You could be
You could be to have a better job
I wish I had more recordings of like
That type of old man whining of that like I don't
Understand the children these days from from every era
You know so I could just bring it like in in conversation with my family or anything like that
Bring that out and be like
Hey are you really mad about that is that a huge problem for you is that a huge culture issue that you needed.
But they look at the other ones that you are just as important as is
I think we talked about it before I even if Jeff
Check myself a little bit about that whenever is there something that I just
Don't understand
Tik-Tok
Talk for me is a little bit like
It gives me that
Sort of
If I were
A little bit less examined in my sort of daily life I might be like these
It might be something that I would feel like
This generation is really loss
Recognizes her something
Pardon
I've been left behind
That's fine
I mean I just acted one of the major problems is that it seems like the generation after us is just
They're just way better people they're more connected they're smarter
I think it might be airing on the other side pendulum swinging a little too far
I get that I get that
But you know what
You know Greta doesn't have
Mark on her
But everybody else
I've been talked about these microchips as a matter fact you realize that when Harry Potter first came to America as far as
They sent out 300
Little
Stickers
Can you do Harry Potter
And it's a scar
All these children got these little Bay stickers and they were all
Forehead just like Harry Potter
You start looking at that in Lion King Simba
Annoying it on his forehead
I shall
News & World Report sometime I get it to go
Had a child lunch
Walmart right on his forehead
Orca Browns forehead microchip
I don't understand how we're also like getting
So far afield from
Witches
You know like
This is supposed to be about witches on Halloween and now the Lion King is being used to
Put forth a
Microchipped
Conspiracy like I really
Think they lost the thread
I think it would go so far as to be evident
For them
Not actually believing witches are real and just using it as a cudgel to get through their other more important
Yeah it's kind of
A splitter that they can use to have their other agendas
Yeah I'll be more interesting
Cool hey I think second amendment rights are important
Because witches are coming
I hold on all right what else you got
Also there a little bit of fun
Because witches are real
Maybe
But they're a little defensive
The people think the
If they're bad
Because they're against the witches
Is or something so stupid
And then all of a sudden they're not so bad
There's a long time
When they jump that line from which your make-believe for now
Well so what I mean freedom of speech
Dream of religion in America
They're grabbing our kids and doing this well website Glory Ministries
Stop, Lincolnwood on infowars.com what will you be doing
Samhain this Halloween knife tomorrow
Tomorrow night I will actually be traveling and I'll be doing some programs down in Florida
And so I'll be
Mara
It's not that I won't be praying about
Things because I realized
There a lot of children in
And here's another thing even if Alex
This was not an occult
Practice and talk day
Anybody
Take their children
Neighborhood
Taking candy from anybody
Okay
Don't trust
Anyone where you supposed to be looking at community and neighbors and
Okay
Your neighbor obviously I do think sending a child
A young young child alone
I think that is dangerous hurt
Reasons of liking you never know who's out there but they don't even front like what if the
Trip and fall and hurt themselves
You need to get it but that's your responsibility
Apparent
Now
The other thing I think
Is being very clearly intentionally misrepresented here in a very hilarious way is be like
For the longest
This time they said witches were bad
But nothing and they're not real
People would like oh they're not real
And now everyone's like
Who cares
About the cares
Is not Society being like
Yeah they do magic
Alright
It's been like
Who cares
Little different than Society just being like alright will accept it as a real and they do magic all the time
Don't worry about it
Regulate cauldron sales
Get the f*** out
Yeah this is really dumb
Yeah sometimes you know if
See the thing about being a witch
And I'll tell you this
Is
The only reason that they can believe
Even witches
And also
Convincingly argue that they aren't
Is that because there are magical rules
That they themselves imagine exists
Did they then impose upon which
Like
If witches were real
Red magic is real
Explain to me why eyesight important
Or distance
Or anything along those lines which was like holyshit
Alex
Is blowing the whistle on all of our which
Let's take away his voice
Biggest boils one day we have to go to the doctor
Yelp
Well you can be like not enough they can only do it if they have
Lock of your hair
Yeah I'm either have to be limitations in order to make this
Make sense within the actual world we live in
Yes there has to be an explanation for why there aren't Magic
Google things happening all the time
If it were this
Easy to learn how to do magic
Score possible
To learn how to do magic
Keep a secret
Because it's f****** Magic
What are you
Talking about
Jordan do you think you should trick or treat
Okay
You guys are not in agreement
KC hat
And all these
Rapist in
Peoples Neighborhood
Stats for 364 days a year we tell our children not to take anything from a stranger and then one night of the year
We walk around
Picking up anything that can
Secondhand something
For Halloween for little
Portable skeleton
Okay prove that lets
See those law enforcement numbers if there's a responsibility
You owe their poor little skeletons
The coverage of this very specifically in order to get the word out
About the evils of
I guess Universal
Kidnapping ring
What's going on on Halloween
Now I think
But this is really f***** up
Because I thought this was about witches in Harry Potter and then she
Apparently it's about your neighbors being
Creeps yeah
Yeah I mean
I thought I'm supposed to be afraid of the occult not the predatory guy who lives down the street
Know anybody
Twitch
Culture
Isolate
From anyone who can disagree with you
What is a
If you wanted to say that
The trick-or-treating is bad
I mean
Whatever you want to say about candy is fine
Part of trick-or-treating is that it is a communal ritual
Frightened that you go around
Two complete strangers home
They smile
You smile
They give you candy always
Complete strangers either if you know people in your neighborhood.
It reinforces
Community thing where you dress up and then
People answer the door and they're like
Good this is good and guess what else it is
It's about
Realizing that the people around you are
Are just people like you that most of us
Are f****** chill
Except for
Tri-tip
Yeah I think the message is basically don't trust anybody
Except those who would be willing
Going to join in with our paranoia exactly have our community of paranoid weirdos who are scared of everybody else
Cannot go meet other
People
Different background and Leslie looks different with a gun
Yes absolutely I'm there good people I just
Call isolation ship
We have One Last Cry. Is that the interview at
A real eye roll
Vitamins from Packard airport little
Portable skeleton
Camera shop
Well they don't need to
Perform human sacrifices
Thank you so much God bless y'all
Take care
Boo
Bizarre political messages
It just gets thrown in release Trail icon beside the
Anti-abortion the pro-second amendment two kind of stuff
Now we're talking about witches
Happening Here is like portal
Which Wich
Is a terrible that use magic they've they're worth the devil also trans people are evil witches are the ones were talking
What we want to talk about mainly are witches
Abortion is going to kill everybody
Absolutely it's like
Are you
Yeah it's
Pretty over
And and
I don't know
I wonder if it's
Function of like there weren't as many people listening
So this is this
Build swap
Could just get away with this
But look we need to save us
Spooktacular we needed a little break
We have to do it we never do this
We never did interviews
And we never did special holiday episodes of all
Exactly
Enter now every holiday
We're doing themed holiday shows Valentine's Day
Alex Jones
That's what I need Alex sings Why do I get a kick out of you
Champagne doesn't Thrill Me
They go look at me now
Dial Josh
Is it me you're looking for different Tony singing hello the little threatening
Is it me you're looking for
Officer
Internist actually get
Present
I just found his behavior so abhorrent and I was like
Wait we we got to do all the way
Are you those first few
Clips at a table that I was genuinely like
This is going to get
Was that I was poking around on the website
Uncovered that interview
And honestly if you see the name
Author of 40
Teen things witches hope parents never find out on the occult of the real meaning of Halloween bring America to its knees
Resist
I can't have this interview sitting in my archives
I like
Think I will get to it in March
You've got a break while the Iron's hot
Andiron is now cool
Happy
Happy Halloween
Paintballing
Happy salmon
To anybody who celebrates her and happy
Happy Samhain to anybody who does
Maybe we'll be back
Website
You can go for my website and learn
Witchcraft Magic
I think we also have don't kill your family. Calm down. Thank you too
Also we are unfair
But until then
Alexandra Thurston color