Airjordan.com
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
Jordan Jordan
I started watching finally a said watching Better Call Saul
And it's good
That's basically
Oh yeah very enjoyable
I expected honestly even from the height
People have surrounding it
I've enjoyed it a different way than I expected in go well done
Folks
Play the nice show
You know it's but what's great about Better Call Saul
Deeply funny
Certain situation down it's so willing to lean into how funny
That it can be and then in the next
It can totally change the tone and you're still in
Yeah yeah there's a lot of like emotional feeling there's a sentiment and then also good comedy
Oh yeah well done something has actually lived up to
Exceeded
The hype that I had in my head
Tell me to watch something
I'll put it off and then I'll watch it no back alright or elected
Socks
No one told me to watch that
No that was all you
Myself to watch that
AE86 always excited
What's up with your brights on
Is and I we went to see Sylvan Esso at the Aragon
Ballroom affair
Fantastic
Amazing awesome
Finally a music act that I've heard of that you that you bring up
But
Remember I showed you that the clip of them doing the life
Performance I believe so the band all together in a circle plan yeah yeah I remember that
That's a bit
This concert was really really great but it also helped me remember that I'm not just an old crank like tomorrow
Alarm music
It's better with a live band
It's in Tavares their live show touring is the two of them the producer and the incredibly
Talented singer and it's
It's great
Dave the music is really good
But when you got a couple of drummers when you got
Guitarist when you got
Real musical instrument
It's just better
I think that's the premise of the roof you know it's so good
Today we're talking about finally getting back in
Into the present I would save this is a sneaky snake episodes
Technically I think the Sneaky Snake was Monday when we had asked
The Spooktacular Sneaky Snake tacular
But today you were getting back to the present we're looking at October 31st
Halloween
I got lots of Halloween
The Halloween
Romero basketball
Many dream 23 after I
Fell down and broke my
This is Sunday Show Halloween
It stinks
All right how are you doing
Go to talk about and you know all that
If I had to rate it in terms of Alex's shows it's not in the tub.
Not in the top to you though
And we'll get that business
Looks like little moments say hello.
So first Wyatt thank you so much you're an alcoholic
Thank you so much you're not you
Kinsella
I'm a policy wonk
This is
I don't know if this is
Open find my inability to
Pronounce names
My fiance is Irish friend
Pronounce my name Craig but it's pronounced
Craig
Thank you you're now a technocrat
Correctly
Doughboy
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
How would you pronounce the
Gray obviously cray
Dash
Geha
Craig
No
If he's talking about Irish
If you talk about Irish
Is Beyonce's Irish friends and family pronounce his name Craig
What is actually crazy Dash
Ge8
Okay okay
Here's what I would say knowing what I know about how Irish people talk
I don't think he's Irish no he's not Irish but it's Irish that's important hooker
Because they're pronouncing it more like
Bike rack
Which is in an Irish knot
It means good
I'm actually spelling of How It's actually pronounced
But not one for How the Irish people pronounce it
Yes it's probably that anyway this mystery we shall not be solved
But thank you
Call Hitler
Probably added me out saying that it's a Love Jones your child Hitler
I did
I'll Hitler
Hope we don't accidentally use that for
Irritator Heil Hitler
Show me startup today's episode and there's a couple of
Maine stories
Alex's
This is preoccupied with
And the first one is one that is going to annoy everybody
Across-the-board
October 31st broadcast
Wow the info
Rideable amounts of this year
Diapers.com
In the Charlottesville 4 years ago
Leading the
To stir up racial conflict
So that they can try to derail on election and make sure the demo
Democrat
The monster
Caught red-handed right during the national firestorm
Basically every newspaper and every so-called news TV program
Attacking Tucker Carlson and by extension
For daring to say that January 6th at
Ngos Bob
Provocateur
What like the Red Cross
Small minority of the million people that were there for
The break into the capitol
Alex has never and will never present any compelling evidence that either of the unite the right rally it's what he says
17 of the capital
On January 6th
Where provocateur
Or somehow run by shadowy forces of the government or some unnamed NGO like
Red Cross
This standard is required to claim that something is proving his solo on this show that he can just get away with saying whatever he wants is
Proven
How do I answer the current situation it has to do with a dirty trick
Types. That the Lincoln project pulled on Virginia gubernatorial candidate Glenn Young
They had five people dress up in
Khakis and hold tiki torches near younkins bus
During a photo op and voice
Support for the GOP Canada
There's number of angles to this whole thing but I wanted to say up front so it's totally clear that I am entirely opposed to what the link
To project it
The first and most important reason is there the kind of stunt like this
Disrespectful to the folks
The community in the activists or at the unite the right rally
Head very least it seems like a co-opting in a very
Crass way of their experiences
The trauma
And using that as a prop for a political rally
Second this just isn't in effect
Do strategy and it's tailor-made to backfire
The intent was allegedly to create a spectacle that would highlight younkins bigger
Patreon shittiness
There was never going to be the out
It's kind of hard for me to believe that the Lincoln project
A group of Republican strategist who made their brand just not liking
Trump know that the right-wing media as it exists
Wheatley tear this apart
And immediately shift the conversation to being about how this done proof
The left is just creating fake white supremacist to be mad at it make you scared of
And how January 6th was really the Democrat
That's when you get
Right down to it
I cannot in good faith believe that the specific people who run the Lincoln project would be so naive as to not know
That this is the result that would happen
Actively hurt the cause of their pretending
I find that difficult
Yeah I mean I all I saw was Republicans dressing like Republic
I didn't see a stunt
At all
Sure
That means like you could
Problem is like the various people that were actually the people who dressed up may have been Democrats
Themselves
That creates the entire Opera
Pics of
A Democrat
Dirty trick or whatever
As for what Alex is saying all this
Is completely detached from reality
The Lincoln project
Is not the left
Has Alex Glenn
The Lincoln project sucks
And it's not aligned with the lab
Even as left-leaning as the Democratic Party
There's actually a bunch of Republicans who read the room and they realize they didn't want to be on Trump side and decided to work
Conservative
Target it's desperate to find some Republicans who
Evil
I'm a 2020 report from open
Secrets pointed out the following
Quote the Lincoln project reported spending nearly 1.4 million dollars through March
Almost all of that money went to the group
Board members and firms run by the
The Super PAC spent nearly $1000000 with summits
Strategic communication
The Firm run by Linkin project treasurer
Reed Galen
Another $215,000 went to the tusk
Digital
A company run by Lincoln project
Advisor Ron
Tesla
Both companies received a little business from other Federal committees
Since Trump's
February 20-21 peace on the optical input Huffington Post reports that over 50 million dollars of the 90 million dollars the Lincoln
Padres dad quote
Gone to firms
Controlled by the group's leaders
Really strong
Suspicion that these folks are just rotting
BMW further Persuader this
I would submit to you the response at their co-founder Steve Schmidt gave
When asked about their financial schedule
Quote
We fully comply with the law
The Lincoln project will be delighted to open its books for audit immediately after the Trump campaign and all its Affiliated super Pacs
Do so
Explaining the cash-flow nearly 700 million dollars that flow through the organization
Who's the girl by Brad parscale
A Kush
I don't know if I could come up with a response that makes you look more guilty than that but that one wasn't that good
We'll open our books
In the exact same way
That the theoretical evil person that we don't like
Should open his books and since he won't
We won't
Does proven were morally Superior today
I am a youth you are and these other evil people kind
They do it when some other person
But yeah there's a game of
F****** Domino's in three Lee stupid
Just like a
F******
Pouring water in an uneven
Tile floor below sea level just like
Wherever there's a hole to be filled with money they will find
What are the primary things that spark suspicion about their business model of the Lincoln project
Outflow to Lincoln
Jack folks other cup
But the real kicker is that they spend a suspiciously high percentage of their budget
Producing their ads
Elizabeth 2 article in opensecrets points out they spent $19,000 on an ad against Martha
McSally
But only one
Quarter of that amount was spent on ad placement
Quotes with the rest
Spent on production
These are of course production cost
They're paid to companies that are run by the people in charge of the Lincoln project
You can write those off
That's three-quarters of the budget go into production cost is just
Suppose with that OVI pro-trump Super PAC
America First action
Production
Costed
2%
Quote with the rest of their budget going to add buy it
The Lincoln project are not anyone's friend but their own
And to drive that point home think about the fact that if George W Bush was president right now
Their organization wouldn't
Exist
They don't really care about the things they want you to think they care about
They just want you to think that they do so they can
Can fundraise
Also they had to cut ties with Hunter co-founders John Weaver after multiple allegations of him quote sexually harassing young man looking to
Break into public
16 to the surface
A credit they did put out a statement denouncing Weaver in January 2021
Do the opposite of their credit they knew about the quote at least 10 specific allegations of harassment since June 20th
What if I choose to ignore it
Until the outlet the American conservative began reporting on the allegations
Anyway
This stupid stuff that they tried to pull the young kid event is exactly what you'd expect from
It's flashy it seems like
Just making a point but it actually
Isn't and it's red meat for the right wing
Media
The important thing to understand about this is that regardless of the motivation for their actions with
What the Lincoln project date is counterproductive then they should just stop
No I mean ultimately
The Lincoln project
Exist
To create
Groupon
Put people more than willing to lean into whatever right-wing narrative is already being created about
The Left End
Safayet giving them more power
And because the Lincoln project
Theoretically separate from the
Go to parties you can have
The Lincoln project doing
Exactly what the right needs the left media to do that they're not doing
I don't I wouldn't
Controlled upright I wouldn't go as far as
Is what you're suggesting kind of and I know that you don't mean this literally but that that kind of does and up
Getting into coordination
Mike Eichner of coordination is
It's just that they are smart enough to know a spot where they can
That's that's what I'm saying you can make a little bit of
They can get a piece of the attention economy and use it to fundraise totally and make a lot of money
I mean cuz the thing is
What can happen if I'm not saying that it's like collusion or that they're they're operating in Cairo.
I don't think they were saying I just wanted to close tonight that's why I really really understand that
When there is
A spot for
V
Left media
But the right wants
Hate right
The right will always go to that left media as well
Because I hate it so much
In the same way that they are afraid of their own media so they can
Constantly go back to that
So there's a Griff
To be made there
They make it
And it just so happens to dugdale perfectly with what they already want
You're right and I think the other thing too is
By doing these stunts
And
Also
Being like we don't like Trump
They allow themselves to be portrayed as actually democratic
Useful the media slobbers all over themselves to portray them as
Non-stop just like look at what these
Brave conservatives are doing they can be painted as actually secret Democrats
By the right-wing media and it allows them to perpetuate
Recycle whole graph
Does there
It's not even hard
It's really about is that the left is freaking out
Because Tucker Carlson is doing this documentary thing
About the Patriot Purge January 6th
Yeah they're mad that people are mad at Garba
Tucker's
All week on Fox
Freaking out about
The three-part series that starts airing tomorrow night
After celebrating and it's only available on
Foxnation.com
Tucker's ratings are going to go into all-time high need to be covering it all week
The biggest highlights and proof
Chagas watching Tucker
Play the left like a fiddle and really
Corn sheller fraud is a beautiful thing
Even more satisfying when
That it is a little bit
Let's just say
Cool
I do
Pathetic because I
I I don't
Thank you
Is dealing with reality that Tucker Carlson wood
Throw him under the bus as if it helped his radio
Yeah whatever the through whenever the wind blows in another Direction
And get his bow tie back
You didn't wake him up he showed him a profitable lainho to
Be able to
Heaven audio
Yeah I know when the wind changes
He and John Stewart are going to go on a tour debating for
25 cities in six months or whatever and that's
They're going to be millionaires or got all over again
Whatever the case maybe Alex
Pretending that you woke him up somehow and like this whatever Tucker is doing now is somehow like
All this is B sincere version of of
Rye Rye
Is Brandon now is give him
Thermocouple
Give me a couple years
See where he's at
Anyway
Is really just about white
Under attack they are
White people
Everybody
All the major corporations
Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan
You name it saying
I hear I got copies of it
Critical race Theory training put out by the CEO sign by
CDL critical rate
On the critical race
Terry training
Call AT&T employees
White people
The problem
Sonic says white being white is inherently a genetic trait
I'm being a bad person
100% Hitler
She's being reversed
To say
What
Are you f****** talking about
Trailer slave
Death was that
So yeah he didn't have too much problem with wait what
I kind of wonder if he actually even understands what Hitler was up to
Why did Alex say that Hitler spoke about his
I I don't I don't know if you thought that maybe he didn't
Act on the things he's
Maybe that
F****** weird with say those things in the media came up with this fake narrative about him doing
Doing those things he was just asking question
Dad and I don't know the media always tries to hate people who ask questions
These are really
Quotes from AT&T training materials
This is a story about race-related training that have been leaked to a journalist who then made claims about the material without
Actually
You know he wasn't actually citing stuff
From the material
Those claims are the things that have been repeated by figures in the right-wing media presented as being from the actual documents
Close to a writer's interpretation of them
I just wish this was hard
Haha
Brother Bart AT&T released a statement saying that the reporting on this is quote filled with misinformation and an Acura
Receives
Journalism question for actually releasing the documents of the
In question here so I can take a look at the
See for myself
What are the problems that jumps out to me immediately when I see these.
Documents is that it
Clearly what amounts to a printout of an interactive web
Platform
Basically our program
Huge selection of links in different sections which obviously will take you to other pages that service resources
10 formed
Point of the X
Undergone
What are the big things that constantly parotid about this document is that each of the employees that if white people want to know who is
Responsible for racism
They should look in the mirror
Yeah that formulation isn't it
Ton of Articles covering
This attempted a scam
And here's what that comes
Is it a section of length
And it goes to an operating the Chicago Tribune titled quote White America if you want to know who's there
Responsible for racism looking
Yes those words do. This document
Is pretty intentionally ignored by the people trying to drop outrage about this
The op-ed was written by delete glanton
And for the most part it makes a point
Probably article quote
Racism is no different from any other chronic problem
It occurs as long as it goes on check
Black people for the most part our power list
Stop racism
If we could we would have done it a long time
Time ago
In many ways the soffit share some common themes of Martin Luther King Junior's letter from a Birmingham Jail
Particularly the part about it being Gravely disappointed with the white moderate
You know it is everyone is heard that we don't need
Me too
Belabor that
I'm okay if you don't know look them up
Play thumbs up it is essentially an articulation of a challenge
For people who are not race
Us to recognize their inaction
Jennifer actively AIDS racism
Continuing
And that the change needed to get where we want to go starts within your own mind
It doesn't take away people are evil or bad it's
You know that's the interpretation you might expect a racist to Havasu
Because it's kind of threatening to race
You can either be anti-racist racist or you can
Facilitate racism but
You can't be
In the middle
The thing about white people being genetically racist isn't actually from the AT&T materials
But if you didn't read anything past this latest articles about this you might think that it was
Actually just another misrepresentation
Know something from glass
Zolpidem
The Chicago Tribune
American racism is uniquely white tray
Black people cannot be racist towards you
Racism by definition is quote Prejudice discrimination or antagonism Direct
It against someone of A different race based on the belief that one's own race is superior
Black people cannot exude a sense of superiority that we have never
Experience
I guess if you want to get mad about that quote you can do that but it would be good if you were mad at the actual contest
Fake version of what
This person say
And that's all that's going
I ran over this this whole document from AT&T and honestly it's a well-intentioned but dorky attempted a
Listen to appear to be doing their part
At the end of it there's this 20 21 day challenge
Suggest some questions
Consider it's a bookstore
But it also includes
Suggestions on things like how you should stay inspired
They suggest you quote
Create a soundtrack for justice playlist that fuels you
Orkin service a conversation starter with people of all ages
All right well now I'm at
Had their suggested soundtrack
Conclude such a dork Is the Love by the Black Eyed Peas
Brave by Sara Bareilles
And Roar by Katy Perry
Wow I mean that you just don't get more justice-oriented into playlist
There's some good tracks on there to love to know that beyond the Moon is on there
Okay but there's also three songs by Macklemore
So take that for what
Wow
Dream of the day Macklemore walks up to Gil Scott-Heron and says
Did I do a good job and then Gil Scott-Heron served as a cold ass honky
The journalist to publish this Sensational article about the document is a guy named Christopher rufo
And that might not be a name that
It's familiar to most people but it probably should be
He's essentially the entire reason that the right-wing is up in Arms by critical race
Rufo was
Read some documents from an anti-racism seminar put together by the city of Seattle's office of civil rights
And after you reported on it as a scandal
He began to get other such slideshow sent to him
According to a profile him in the New Yorker quote rufo noticed that they tended to cite a small set of popular
Anti-racism books
By authors such as
Ibrahim X kendi
And Robin diangelo
Ruffa read the footnotes of these books
Sometimes they pointed to academic
Scholarship from the 1990s by a group of legal Scholars who referred to their work as critical race Theory
In particular kimberle Crenshaw and Derek Bell
Ruffo follow depth
Brad and decided that the entire idea of anti-racism is actually
Kind of a Marxist
Plot
Which I hate to break it to him that's exactly what the John Birch Society was saying in the 19th 6
When they were opposing the Civil Rights Movement is brand-new.
New thought did you see the the video on Twitter going around of like the guy who
Who is like what's the biggest issue in the election
Why are we jumping on all he's saying is that the biggest issue is
He doesn't care about the bread
This is about white people dominated I think the reason the people are dunking on that video is
Because
The follow-up Quest
Is what is
Brighton
Benjamin wallace-wells the author of this piece in the New Yorker correspondent with rufo and this is how rufo explained his
We've needed new language on these issues
Political correctness is a dated term and Bill reportedly does
And apply anymore
It's not that Elites are enforcing a set of manners and cultural limits there's
Speaking to re-engineer the foundation of human psychology and social in
Institutions through the New Politics
Pics of race
It's much more invasive than mere correct
Who do the mechanism of social control but it's not the heart of what's
The other frames are wrong too
Cancel culture is a vacuous term that doesn't translate into Apple ID
Program
Woke is a good episode.
What is too broad to Terminal 2 easily brushed aside
Critical race theory is the
Perfect Villa
We can say race
But people won't just say oh they're saying it's about white people versus everybody else last September rufo. On Tucker
Carlson show and put the term critical race theory on to the right-wing media is mapping from there it's become the new way for conservatives to express
Racism
Well maintaining an appearance of social acceptability
I also hate to inform conservatives that they are just repeating themselves again
Illustration I'd like to present to you
Passage from a 1981 interview with Republic
Strategist
And Rodger Stone Buddy Lee at water that guy was great
Quotes
You start out by the way whatever I say and it's a hard-r cuz I'm not Dave Anthony
Quote you start out in 1954 by saying and
Play 1968 you can't say and that hurts you backfires
Stuff like forced busing states rights and all that stuff and you're getting so abstract
No you
I'm talking about cutting taxes and all these things that you're talkin about are totally economic things in a byproduct of them
Is blacks get hurt worse than white
We want to cut this is much more abstract than even the busing thing and a hell lot of more abstract than yelling
NM
Hey you know what size you know it's great and not doing anything about a pandemic that disproportionately affects
Minorities over-the-top
Holding racism in abstract in Marc deblois that's kind of a
Standard operation
A conservative so
It's not surprising to see rufo found a new term to use to play that old game and he thinks he's a genius
Anyway Trump saw him on Twitter got him covered
BC and help too I had that he helps
Executive order
Great
I am am
Just just
Love that Lee Atwater
Say it
Doesn't matter
Right
And you can see the exact same thing
The New Yorker
New Yorker article about Roofing also a bit from Kimberly Crenshaw the law professor who coined the term critical race Theory
3 years ago
I think your take on this
This is pretty much exactly
Quotes reform itself creates its own backlash which reconstitute
Problem in the first
Play scrimshaw said noting
But you made this argument in our first law review article in 1988
George Floyd's murder in led to quote
So many corporations and opinion shaping
Institutions making state
It's about structural racism
Creating a new broader anti-racism racist alignment or at least the
Potential for what
Quote to this is a post
Did George Floyd backlash Crenshaw said
The reason why we're having this conversation is that the line of scrimmage has moved
As she saw at the campaign against
Critical race Theory presented a familiar effort
To shift the point of the argument so that
Rather than being about structural racism
Who's George Floyd politics were about the seminar
Was that a proliferated to address structural races
I think that about sums it up
Anyway the guy who got mad about the corporate seminars and stumbled into a shiny new buzzword for races
Do use the hide
He mad about and hopefully he's going to get
It's Maritime on Tucker
His career
In the city
Scam
F*** all that really built
Are the idiots who run
I like
Everybody who
By the rules of
Television to
Pretend that this is
Valuable
Don't
With this garbage
If somebody says oh critical race Theory just go
Okay your problem is race
Get rid of the critical in the theory
Your problem is
Via
If you want to have like a like a conversation like this
Stay on Tucker Carlson
Some show about
Critical race Theory
I would just roll up a news
Or just
A trailer house
Whenever you says it's good
Or he just
Doesn't talk about some Praises buzzword for a while
You get a treat
So
Story number one is basically this Lincoln project
BIG Story number 2 is
Jim Acosta p
By myself
Anybody else he just tells you discredited
A joke
Touch him Acosta
He tried to Gaslight everybody in a 7 Half Men
Don't take him to 20 minutes
Burlesque
Play it.
Play it stop because
He saying about myself Carlson
Is what
He's doing
I'm rubber he is glue
Yep yep
Promise of another
Just like
Analysis of a clip
Yeah I'm going to take this
Inch by inch who segments 20-minute right
Thorough always kind of got excited and that happens cuz I know Alex is just going to
Like
Find words to hinges
Responses on and by who
Contacts that could disagree with him
Classic
I was looking forward to that
Towards the end of the episode
The problem that system and establish
But has with
Tucker right
Emblematic of the fact
That
The GOP
Is waking up
To the New World Order
Oh I thought that
Was absurdly easy to be a billionaire off of line
Do the a disorder rhetoric is exactly what leads to people getting hurt
Terrorism
Now it's
Is that the GOP is waking up
He's waking up
The New World Order the global list of the great reset the most of it
And the whole neocon arm of Karl Road and George W bush
And the rest of them
Are becoming completely
Delete
Attending anymore
Power in the park
Whoever Trump certifies
Never Trump supports
150 bus races
Indoor sloth
150 +
Wanch
So technically isn't
True like a he's also mixing things up here cuz like every talking about general elections or primaries is
Trump's endorsement doesn't matter in
The general really
I mean just really matters in the primaries
But you pretty close Alex
Is pretty close
It's disturbing as hell so funny that
When he said races
I was like I was like well obvious
He said racist
I meant it was like out of 150 racist T supported only two losses like
At least you're honest
My time for Trump in the Battleground primaries in the 2020 election
He went
21 and 2 among the candidates eBay
That's even an improvement from the 2018 midterms where you went 50
Keenan to the solid record yeah
He has a slightly less successful batting average when those candidates get to the general election
But you know the numbers drop there a little bit
Honestly
That's not the claim that Alex is making or at least it's not the relative
He's saying that the bush types of loss weigh in the Republican Party in the Trump is a kingmaker in the GOP now
The only metric that's relevant there is how these candidates do in the primary and Trump's numbers are undeniably solid
How's the general
It's worse than bad
Like
70%
Something as opposed to a bit higher in the
It's terrifying at all it really speaks to is
How badly they water catering
Just bought a dictator really funny watching the Democrats right now because it does feel like they're mad that
Lying to their electorate about doing something and then not doing it
Doesn't work as well as the right wing
It feels like they're like
This should work
They do it all the time
They lie to you
Non-stop he didn't do any other s*** that you said that you wanted them to do
Still Love Drunk by can't we just lie to your face
Because
Their version of the Lion
Is aspirational and it doesn't actually involve the same sort of bloodthirsty Miss and anger
At the right-wing does which are the appealing parts of it for a lot of other folks who get tricked by it over and over and over and over again
Not going to Trump because they think Trump is going to give them Healthcare they're going to drop because they think Trump is going to let them murder people they don't want
Want to live anymore
So I Hope Springs Eternal
It probably will be with us for the rest of our lives is that every single election will be stolen
The case here in the Virginia gubernatorial race
Infowars
Tom
Virginia elections director says
Tuesday's results may have to quote wait
Until Friday or maybe longer
Because of Maylin
Vote absentee voters
Were you signing it certified you've already voted
This is a large
Porsche
Sing Ono
We don't want to go vote
Because of covid
A shame replay
Piles of all these extra
Been waiting deserted warehouses
Or until the next middle-of-the-night a few days later
And then pull the van
And the next
The balance that are all
Canidae
To the machine
We saw the footage of that in Michigan
In Pennsylvania
We saw the record of that happening in Arizona
All the places that Trump won
2345 or even up to 10 times
The numbers he won
Nightwing
Trump
One by one point 2.3.15.2
Also Stacy barely won by a fraction of a point
This is too many numbers
If you're listening to this first of all
None of that's true but also if you're even like listening to him and you like this is like my God I can't
Keep track of all these numbers
Alex can you please find a folksy way to help me understand this
Grandmother for
Suspicious music
Bedtime
Looking
Add behind the couch
Georgia
Crown
Tablecloth
And watch this
Crap steal the election in front of us
I was talking about the
Alex's child with a two-year-old like
The table right I'm still kind of stuck on that order of operations problem so I've got like 10 x
Parentheses
2 + 2 points
Finest
-3 points for areas that is foolish
I do this because you don't understand crazy mess you must
Crazy math in order to
Non-euclidean geometry
Beyond Vape
So a bit of what Alex is talking about like the end there was a Georgia
Video that's a bit of fiction that the right-wing media
Put together to service
Debbie 2020election was stolen from truck but it's b*******
That file is like the Left Behind movie was dead to rights proof set
We've already lived through the
Chirp
In Georgia there was a pipe that burst
State Farm Arena where absentee ballots were being processed at approximately 6 a.m. on November
4/3
There's also a video that made the rounds what appears to be people pulling balance out from under a table at the State Farm Arena vote-counting are
That video was for about 10-15 the night prior and it nothing to do with the piper
Some Anonymous weirdo called The Hip Hop Patriot decided to combine the two into a compelling story
Put it out on Twitter and from there I became Alex's real
What is so easy
It's a way better scene for a detective novel The Way Alex is telling this story but none of it
True
It's a problem right
That's also why detective novels are way better
Then realized lumbo would hear this one more thing
Give me one more thing
Also after what we learned on our last episode about how
Evil Halloween is
I can't believe Alex allows his children to take part in it
That seems really dangerous there are so many witches out there that don't want Alex to know all this yet they're doing to
To his four-year-old right now about it if this child gets
Tootsie Roll
You have a positive association with Halloween
Devilry knife
Cable lousy
Veil Between Worlds is that it's finished
Woman child Alex's Mormon child got to become a witch
The power that that women child is going to have
Because of the lineage of Alex Jones
The Terry Pratchett witches
Is every time he says
Which has edges
He just make me laugh so much child
Nonsense
So anyway Alex has a national file article
That he
I don't I don't know about that
I got to make a correction on the Fly
Michaud
Ryder
And this article
The drastic changes the various
Election laws Nationwide
Almost
Consent decree by the governor's
Legislators it was not
The law
Talking about like
Steve Allen
You can vote
Why the whole election was a fraud right
Election
Redone
That's why Mike lindell's right about Albania
The political will we need to stop worrying about reinstating Trump
We need to start working on stopping a fraud
And the general election
Rectify
Way way way way way way I thought we were dead already could have swore that we were not going to make it 3
To the next election Alex just have like a little tantrum like a week ago
Everybody who gets the vaccine dies within six months to a year how about the end the end the rest of the unknown
Vaccinated who survived this calling will have to beat down the global hat
There's an election October 2024
Deadly off
We need to really focus on getting out the vote after the f****** zombies arise from beneath the
Earth with their vaccines to destroy well I mean honestly we will have to have a very uncomfortable conversation at that point about whether or not
Zombies going to vote
I mean
I don't know
The question
No matter what we choose it didn't look bad in hindsight
Be real pissed at us a week ago week and a half ago everybody
His dad cuz Alex is in a bad mood cuz he lost that case
Judgment
Hey look we got to remind yourself that they're always
So you think you're going to die in 3 years that's actually 30
Do you know this kind of Discord
Thing is a poker another thing that's at will you call a towel
We're going to die in
That's just kind of annex
Stream Sensational bulshit thing to keep the audiences
Keep their emotions heightened keep them scared
In order to
Funnel their attention towards the
Political project
That you helped to push in the midterms
That's essentially
Alex
Engagement
Again it should
Harder
You should have to work
Carter
You really don't
It turns out you don't get just don't
Well you know who doesn't work hard
Brown
Baseball swag
Of course so many false flag
The very same crew in power today
Attorney general fingerprints all over it that he was fully operative sadly evolved
Nanny fast forward
Two things like
Were you just get a bunch of democratic operatives
The dress up and taking torches and to go out in
Then you have a leftist mob shows up actually Believing lyrics
Fight on seasoning
Huge explosion
This is stupid and obviously not true but man it's so weird how Alex is somehow proven that all of the high-profile electivire
Silence by bigots in history
Those are real
It's so weird and you would say
I think that the party and the people pushing
Horrific
Racism
As a matter of course
Would also
Probably be the ones at fault for the terrorist violence
They claim I mean they but they would be
Yes
They are not cuz otherwise they'd be responsible
Although I hear that Joe Biden's fingerprints are all over the OKC
So I
Trying to think that he was just a senator in Delaware
I'm interested to see how Alex Wood
Spell this conspiracy
Just tells me that he was freestyling
He just said whatever Paul yeah yeah
That might be fun to say
Indeed OKC
That's a big swing that's a that's a pieczenik level swing if you can back that up with secret.
Deep State sources in the state department
That you used to work with
For sure
Sometimes though you have
Some things that appear
Appears to be
Media manipulation
Sure
But
If you don't know anyting
And you're stupid
Right sometimes
Your ignorance about things
Is actually the cause of what you think
Is Media manipulation
Wavy Wayne baby
Bway baby
Movie with baby
Ball sack
Come out
Happen again
Friday
There were people with tiki torches
Winding up
Republicans bus
They were there officially with the
We don't know of
Enough
The warehouse is the Democrats do
Bring in the dead of night this time
Stop
Torches and the media enemy see all of them ran with all the white supremacist are there supporting
First of all
We're call anyone ever claiming that Jane Roe a
Actually gotten aboard
The case was entirely predicated on the fact that she
She couldn't get in divorce
And which is why there was a loss
She wouldn't make a good person to pace and access to abortion case around for very obvious reason
She had access to
I think if people just assume that you got an abortion because of the association with
But I don't remember ever learning that or the media implying that
She gave the baby up for adoption and I feel like the only way you wouldn't know that is
As if you never really actively looked at
Into the case at all
Seems like a mind-blowing bit of trivia for Alex but like I said I suspect that's
Just because he's an idiot
A couple quick points though first the fake protesters didn't say that they were officially there with young
They were there
Supposed his supporters
It's not an official wing of this campaign
Stupid second I never heard this story reported as white supremacist
The tiki torches at a Virginia rally
By the time I saw this was already about how this was a
PR stunt
Lincoln project
Third how could the Democrats
Ever not have enough fake ballot
Everything it election is as simple as Alex seems
To think it is they can just print more
Like is this dumb
No no no no no
You're not understanding
The FED controls inflation
Okay to many ballots the value of the ballots goes down
That could destroy the economy entirely elections would become Fair
Making them the ink is not
Now that's true again I'm not the
Democratic Party
Do they have a little bit more access to
Postage money
Pink money is it where I do like that
Arbitrary
Look dude don't know if they have enough warehouses full of fake ballots in order to swing this election so they have
To send out fake
T torch guys to make a young kid little Platte
Vine
I do love just arbitrary all man
These guys are evil
Unstoppable incredible however terrible with infrastructure and paper cost
Well actually
There are evils they run everything
Wedding to do paper jam
We've all been there
Devil can't train people on copy
No
The guy who fixes a copy machine died of covid
They can't get it fixed
I needed to get the Lincoln project
Send up some every time
Text the last time and then I'll enough of them more like well we
Just won't fix your copy
So Alex believes that
The Lincoln
Can project essentially
Alana grenade
This is your party who did this
Because it blew up in their face or whatever right Lincoln project
So that's a kind of
What's the story
Come to the rescue
Lincoln project went on CNN
For what they did
Republican
That's like saying that Bill Clinton is a wrap
Thomas
Can or you can make it
You are
What's the Democrats for getting the blame for the false
Well here comes as fast as they could almost
Fall of themselves
Oh no that sucks calling it a false flag is a little bit rich
But also Alex left in the middle there because he knew he'd f***** up in his list
But it was too late to do anything about it
Not only could you say that Thomas Jefferson was a republican you could say that he literally founded the democratic-republican party
Also known as the Jeffersonian Republican Party
Republican party that we know.
Today but none of the parties resembled
Themselves
100 years ago
Also great whatever no nothing party is made a very strong comeback.
The wig
Lincoln project
The same as calling Thomas Jefferson
Center Republican
You can hear him laugh
At least I'm not having a bad day today and I'm going to tell everybody hit billions are going to die tomorrow kind of interesting to me because
Is he knows so little about Thomas Jefferson in terms of these fake quotes that he throws out all the time
Clear awareness that he's like
He actually is a Republican
That dick for half a little
These actors
Who were it this is why I brought this up with the beginning of the end
Scuba
The people who are pretty
Tiki torch wielding people
Figured out the
Twitter
Tarantulas
Other people
And they're well-known high-level dinner
Disguises
Bachelor.
Glasses
And they're not blinking
The Lincoln project
Party cutouts
Project
Posing is white supremacy
White nationalist
As well
Posing as everybody
They really are Democrat Party
Operative
Well
Georgetown University
I think of taxpayer money
Coming tsuyu to shut you up
This is how Alex is trying to rationalize why he's being sued for defaming
Brandon Gilmore in the United States
A suit that is going to trial fairly soon probably
Having troubles with that
The little espro a high-profile that the Sandy Hook one but he's learned his lesson
So the people who portrayed the fake white nationalist in the Lincoln project
Start very well may have been Democrats
But even if you prove that they're involved in politics
2nd Swing to the left
That still doesn't prove they are engaged in this stunt under the any official auspices of
The Democratic Party
You think about it for a second who else you going to get to pose as white nationalist Adagio
Dear Ally other than Democrat
Probably highly motivated young one
That's the pool of people you might be able to get to be
Hey it's political start Where can I
Yeah I don't forget it'll I would also have to be somebody who's like wait a sec
You want me to go to a place where horrific violence happened and traumatized
Yeah I would love
To do that I'm on the left
Yeah I kind of have to be not not that
Full of person
So this point we are we get back to the AT&T manual
AT&T
Mets
Did this is just
Racial re-education
Is not true
AT&T says
Racial
Re-education program
Assert
Category education
White people are the problem
The article infowars.com
John
Tanty
The whole world problems
Inoculation
No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No
Gonzaga
Supernatural
I don't think that
Hey what'd you come away
With from
Reading these are looking at these documents is it that they're arguing that it's the only pray
Problem or even the biggest problem in the world is
Is this a problem
Also toxic waste dumping is a weird thing for Alex have on that list
Find me of white people
We should just ask Corporation
Nicely know what's right
Wait no
I don't like that AT&T does
So these Lincoln project people who went out and did this
Could be I already called it a
Language is a little severe
Party has been caught in a racial fall
Call flag for their operatives posing as white supremacist and the chain is what Republican Party
Just a standard thing they do continually and
Do not want you discussing it
And we believe Jessie Smollett really got attacked
Don't you believe that
Turn out to be
I think that
If you are the Lincoln project
You have a responsibility to understand their right-wing media ecosystem
And doing something like this so trance
Apparently stunts
A PR stunt
He's not going to really stick
Is a negative thing for young
Buddy will stick
Inside the right-wing media ecosystem and then
As a resulting example of
Something that had to do with fake races
Yep
And will be something that could be used
To keep people
Problem
Rekha
Synchronizing larger societal issues
It'll keep people crap
Apt in that to that
Space
That facilitates
The racist
Violence
Yeah that's
They believe is fake
Yeah and when you say responsibility
That is true
I would also say that if
You expect
People who have worked within the Republican Party strategy and
Play It Again media
Situations
For most of their lives
It would be hopeless
Leslie naive to think that they didn't already on
Probably it's at but I don't know I don't know their heart
That way I know Alex's art
Taka renny's excited about
Along Comes
Tucker Carlson
With his
Big report coming out from fart series
The plot against America or the federal government
Open Leah Brandon
America
I told you they were announcing the Bible
Anybody questioning Alexa's a terrorist
And then I'll go to the school board and say
Appreciate you
Teaching that white people are inherently bad
Is a total Nazi crap
Because of what
Way cigar is not
You're naughty stuff
The official US government stratagem
The National Security Council put out by Joe Biden in June
I got a lot of news you're a lot of stuff to cover
Because this is
Alex is actually selling himself in
Incredibly short here
He called this when Joe Biden got into office
Alex has been claiming that the homeland security apparatus is about to be turned against white people for basically his entire career
This is one of these instances were illustrate that Alex said they should 15-20 years ago really doesn't make him sound like a psycho
Make him sound like a broken record or a boy who's crying wolf in a really racer
This way
He doesn't help his case the January 6th was a
Plot to turn counter terrorism against white people if you point out
Did he said the exact same thing about almost every other terrorist act you can think of
Turning the power of the State against white people is why Alex claimed they frame Timothy McVeigh for the Oklahoma City bombing
Why I would spend so much time pretending that the FBI was going to frame a white Patsy for the Boston
Vomit
Did you go back to 911 that's even part of his
Conspiracy there
Passing things like the Patriot Act only happened because the state wanted to make you afraid of foreign terrorists
But it was really about giving the state more power so they could actually use it against white people
Or Patriots
Alex
Is a preoccupation for Alex because he's racist
These would be the stupid rompers
Entire career in
I'm going to go on the mantle what he's doing right now
This is another time that he insisted the sky was falling
In-N-Out
Don't really have the
Perspective of hindsight
Is happening in the present
Right2know
Bazooka be another one of those
Really hope
That's that
Clip of Owen Shroyer
Burning up
Flag and saying
Fuckbay LMS
Patriot Purge documentary
Contacts to the whole thing you know
If you realize that
The people leading the rally
Are themselves saying
F*** BLM
Burning flag
I'm and Alex just talked about something you know like when you
When you think that should also play clips of Harrison
Broadcast b a on April the capital is falling
Because it's going to be a patriot
So we need to know
Exactly who the Patriots want to purge
Probably want to get rid of those people to make the Patriots look better right
Boo
Systems freaked out
Freaked out because Alex and Tucker when
When they talk about these sorts of issues
Short and they bring light
Stewie globulus false flag
Variability
Interpol future false flag
God
Carlson hammering on it
You know that they've got the system scared
Because they are so freaked out
Richarlison raises this
I raised this because
The elephant in the room
Just as sure as the sun came
The next year before the midterms just like they did Oklahoma City in Downey
What would be real life
The Oklahoma City bomber
Look it up
Clinton said he owed his
Oklahoma City web
Do web search do an image search will see the headline
Air Force 1
Hours ago
Film books you name it
Right
Exactly that
Provide specific citation I'll look into it
I suspect this is just Alex putting The Dramatics
Spin on the idea that Clinton saved his re-election with his
Response to the Oklahoma City bombing
As The Story Goes his numbers were terrible and it wasn't looking good for him getting a second
Then the Murrah building is attacked and he shows up and gives an amazing
Speech that Comforts Oklahoma and the nation in this horrific MoMA
It encourages a path forward
Many folks have said that that speech
And Clinton's leadership
After the bomb
Play the major role in his re-election
It is Bill himself ever express
Feeling that way I don't
I think that would be too surprising
Don't prove that he did the bombing in order to get reelected
It's still this giant leap that Alex wants us to make
It's f****** dumb
Right yet mean
Do you really think Obama would have been elected without a massive financial crash
Obama's not going to be like
Good thing that financial crash happened otherwise I wouldn't be president
I'll be back with all this being said if you look at gallup's approval ratings for Bill Clinton you'll see that he was hovering
Around the mid 40
3% approval prior to the bombing
46% the week before
1051 percent for the neck
Next two weeks
By June 5th it was back down to 47% and around there
Consistently
It didn't go back up into the 50s steadily until November
I just think it is a little bit of mythologizing
Sing based on how good that's
Spirit was after that
And how that did
Really some at him as as a strong leader
On the day MLK died
Tide is there different we're on the day the government murder dive okay
I think that
More to the point about this stuff too but
This is not freaked out because you're going to blow some kind of false flag they're playing
Cuz this is going to get people hurt
This inevitably leads people down to pass
That leads to viola
Man not good
No-sew Alex likes
Pretend that he does a lot of stuff behind the scene
He is a man with a hydro with many heads does he likes
To say sometime
They contributed to Tucker's documentaries
Apparently
YouTube background logo
Bigger than this documentary
That we can trim it into and then
Tucker footage for
You're going to see you tomorrow
Morgan
So desperate to be associated
But that's
The people saying like oh my
My God like
Tucker's just doing Infowars
And insult
Tucker
They're saying that I better
F****** use this to play
Yeah probably good
Wagon to a horse
And the reality for Alex's that he's
Guilty himself in competition with people like Tucker Glenn Beck
You know they're better than you
This is actually incredibly interested on Alex
I agree with him at 1
Hundred percent is a watershed moment
Talk show host
Probably the end of the day smarter than I am
Not hard
But when it comes to firing people up at fighting tyranny and not backing down
Having the Holy Spirit
I got more of it
I'm not trying to brag it's all glory to God
To get people fired up at a guy
I completely 100% agree with this
People like Glenn Beck
And Tucker are smarter and better host
And a TV
Alex's job is not to be accurate
He's not there to be a good
Broadcast arrojo
He's there to incite people
To f*** with people's emotions
Use information as a weapon
Whether it's
Accurate or not
And incite them to action
That he will then later
Call Volkswagen it's very odd but even he's like
My job is to incite them to Action Now obviously whatever my fans do stuff
Number to do that how could you even claim that I said that was a deep state
Nonviolent
Politically
Alright buddy
What a dick
Completely accurate also unfortunately shows
Too much self-awareness
To accept that he is unself-aware of so many others
Also
Is this
Plus years
Cuz the first 56 years I didn't understand not calling at USB
Push by gods
20 years ago
Was just like a voice in my head
Almost episode
You are going to relay the what will pass
You're going
Myself
Baptism in the
In the
Wilderness
Oh my God
Party strategy.
Jones is the John the back
He's the main engine our computer studies
He's got to be stopped
This is delusional nonsense
But also I don't think it was a democratic
Party
Documents said that Alex was a voice in the wilderness
Victor was
Just a term that is used Like a Rolling Stone piece about it
Like I don't I don't think it was just an article
Absolutely do not believe that the government doesn't like party consensus
The wild profit
I know some somebody who's writing a profile added in that line at like we've moved on
I think
It's kind of
Bucked up
Think that
There's any
Reality to Alex's even his own subjective perception of twenty years ago he had a vision and
Prophetic
Dreams that he was
Supposed to lay the groundwork
For this holy battle like
F*** this this is this is
Unhinged
Nonsense pathological
Self mythology
Not just like
You know
I
Was called to this
Now
I didn't say anything or feel
But now that I'm claiming it
When I was on air
Definitely would never said that
And now it's too late
I won
I beat you into submission we have that perception of Alex and maybe that's our
Position
But there's another position and that is Alex
And that is the key is the light of the world
Him and his buddy are the only option
We're now the light of the world
This fight against the new world order the fight against the great reset
Does America is in control as we are sometimes
We're still the best help this planet
Not clutch want to thank you all for your support and keeping us on Arab
We have two more excitable historic time to be alive right now
Actively destroying the world
Our political movement
If I'm in the man
Is the span
Because that's how they see it as well
What it is
We're going to come back
Desperation
When you hear him talking it's Jeff Zucker
AT&T
Evil Global Corporation
They had America at the PT but are just now realizing
Sleeping giant
Is coming up and separately
We are major awards has to do a lot of the projects were launching
Black Friday comes early
We launched
The first two weeks of every November we wanted early this year
Excitement
Play Black Friday comes early. Lobster call Shirley
I like the defensiveness about like I wasn't
I thought this was a bit player you didn't he did a little baptizing
Maybe you did a little faith healing he wasn't that big of a
Also I like the defensiveness about that
After he says that him and his buddies are the light of the world
John 8:12 says quote I am the light of the world that Jesus speak
Well I mean Jesus was a while back
And now he needs an assist
Osher I little like blasphemy is an issue but I'm not
Yeah
So Alex
Complains about Jim Acosta
A couple of these clips
Just cuz they're like
What I could take that I could beat the course on this
Omigod omigod it's by Alex Jones
Shelters name which is fun events for a timer
But
This is the beginning of the review you finally get
It's to his Jim Acosta review
And I will say
My review this piece is
Dorky
City Pawn
I think it might be old
Not surprised it up that's not
Surprising Alex's review is he comes in hot
Here is
Acosta
Truth
Is releasing his big
Blockbuster movie on Monday while the
I've been calling for a sequel to Dune
As in
Crazy as a loon
I'm crazy and alone all you're going to calls conspiracy theorist
Crazy and white supremacist
Lunatics conspiracy theorist white supremacist me you're about to hear it
Was he
Was he referencing something
Tucker said
About
Dune
No it was just trying to
It into something that is kind of
Culturally relevant right now it's over written
That's what he was trying that was the point
The kids are clamoring for a sequel to Dune
But Tucker thought they said loon
That's the joke I thought the Tucker actually said
Made that mistake that seems far more reasonable man writing that I think that you
B not watch
Enough of these like 24-hour news channels
I don't know if Alex me to deposit their tours
Respond
How to get a writing job in TV of Jim acosta's got one
Well I don't know
You might not write all of the
He better
I think there's a stash
Should be fired
He continues with the the dude metaphor also it's not just a one-off
All flags have happened in this country
One of which may have been January 6th
Darn
Global domination
Packer season shop is kind of 8
Timothee chalamet
The comparisons and there is Tucker
White wash the whites
Capitol on January 6th
Anna gets more Sinister than that
Where is Petaling
Propaganda
That the Insurrection was actually a
Flag operation he has floated this before
It's ridiculous
Government was ratified
Ridiculous conspiracy theories
Just like
Caught dealing
Again all the uses of hyperbole all uses words like
Stupid dumb
LG spiracy Terrace white supremacist
Oh yeah Alex's
Complaining about people
Call I mean
I can't imagine what would happen if he said something about the way Alex looks being similar to a demon
That he would be up in arms about somebody who would throw away basic human decency like that
Here someone looks like a demon
About level no
Vampire
That's frankly offensive a little anti-semitic I'm going to go there
Selected according to
Jim Acosta there's no false Flags
Some other flag
But there are potholes
Big enough for Alex Jones and drive a monster truck
Alaska flag
Flags
Did you guys lose the states pieces
Rebel flag for everything
Thousand American flags
So you're now demonizing a million people that contested election
Because it was a few
Johnny Reb Flags there that that's all he's got
The giant white supremacist
Uncle Junior
I don't think that's all he's
Scott
Cuz cuz the next clip has something else
Republican Congressman Denver riggleman who is working
For the January 6th committee have said at least seven white nationalist groups
Were involved in the writing
Get Universal
Some of these guys are the Capital One in universal
KKK
Almost
K-bus they have
Is led by the FBI
And the FBI goes and creates the plan grow
And then advertisers and then pays
Short bus
Literally
What
Of course they're Works 7 White
Scribs
Kmart working with the Southern Poverty Law Center ATL
Democratic Party
This is kind of how you know Alex is ripping this and kind of freestyling
Is because he was like oh yeah he's bad at the Confederate flag that's all he's got and then immediately there's
There's a point about
How the January 6th committee has released seven
Supremacist white nationalist group
Edit order to that's exactly counter to what I was saying
Is that all the KKK are fake
Are all the FBI
Response and his rebuttal in order to suit whatever new thing pop rap
On whatever thing he thinks he can
Whatever thing is like a hold on the rock
Call Matt work
Little bit off on that
Finding Nemo is popular amongst the kids but Trump is finding Nero
Roman emperors
Grapes
There's no kind of fun do you want to try one
No
I get I get I get the enjoyment in it
A little fun
This is going to be your version of my Clips where Alex says damn
Navigate me to credibly enjoyable I hope you have a lot of fun with
I'm not doing it anymore I'm not doing it anymore feel free to
I'm never going to go to bed and defend
That style of writing for a new piece
It is very cringe-worthy United States
F****** government
You like your
Reading app
Pop's Pizza
About the cat of the week
Yeah
Yeah totally it's inappropriate
Doodle boy like Lulu
Alex
Man this
Creeped me out
A republic
Tucker Carlson Democrat
Psycho by charity
He really wants to see
The New World Order
He grew up in the family
But
Red
Well
His family's own goodness
My world
Or was it nice like his dad
Are step moms pyramid of death
Pawn shop
Charge
How do I know that
Well Tucker told me that to my face
Show me other people
You got to stop being naive
Call Bednar
Admit how much trouble we're in
I recognize who our enemies are
Stop
Listening to
Stop even debating
Where I am
Breaking my
Phone
Rule here
That is giving it
To the system
It's Alex in Breakers rule because
CNN said his name every time
Anyone says his name
On Twitter for a while
It's so annoying
He breaks
Everything we're not
We're not talking about anything in the news here's what they
Brandeis
That's what I'm here for
Other thing too though is that like
Alex doing this
Is weird soft taco
Ramble about
How great talker is in his
Family and all this
How do I know cuz you told me
I think that
Anytime Alex
Reports
On something based on something somebody else has told him
You should know that he's an idiot
And you gullible as hell
He's the guy who hung out with Steve pieczenik for like 20 years
He's a guy who got duped
By Rodger Stone
This is not a guy who has a good b******* radar do you know how I know that rich people
Orr betters and should be in charge and are absolutely looking out for us I guess you're not going to say because rich people
That I needed actually is because rich people told me that okay
Yeah and I believe how could you not believe them damn sure how could they like
You can't get rich by lying they say they're better people so they wouldn't lie
Actually interesting will you bring bring that up cuz Alex also is incapable
All I can do shoot straight I can't even control myself and I don't want to tell the
Can't even lie
She physically can't lie all my
Why did I see
Pink parody is even pause
Possible it's not
What kind of idiot am I at
Charlie Brown Lucy faulhaber
Every time
They're running at that football
So also something that keeps happening much like you getting dupe
By trying to be
Spiracle
Another thing that keeps happening is that whatever Allen
Watch breaks his own Rule and does these
Coverage
The things away
Pops up in it joke
He gets kind of bored once
Once they get past the part where his name comes up
Listen to it
Not wrong is that all this is not plot holes big enough you can drive and Alex
Downsize monster truck through
Definition of faith
What holes are your claim
I just kind of runs out of gas cuz he's not involved anymore on the argument to the
The content is I know you are but what am I
EXO
Once you've lost that purr
Personal grievance you don't have
Yeah you try to make the impersonal personal
Here is
I think this is Elias
Sklep actually of the Acosta
The coverage
People
Are using
And that's your fire
Weapons
Country
You see people walking around and take
All of them by the way ramerica
Tucker has already described the insurrectionists as Taurus
So they were just tourists while also
Carrying out a
False flag attack on the
You can't have it both ways
Pause again
You can't have it both ways you little liar
Are you take a 10-second clip
5 minutes
I watch the hookah do something
No shows
He said a very small group of people got roped into a riot
And then the police were ordered to stand down
Waved in by the police
Neymar fights
600 people have been arrested
Over 400 were non-violent
Some of them are still in jail in solitary confinement
That's what Tucker was talking to
Try to fall Flags
They tried to make this much more violent than it was
Provocateur groups on record seeing a guy
It's all on record CNN
I'm sad that way someone did plant two bombs at the RNC and DNC headquarters
Where's the night before January 6th so
If you don't see people with bombs are bayonets in
The videos of the capitol
Yeah you might want to look at
Surveillance videos of the FBI's release cuz they're you
Goosebumps also I do appreciate that they are absolutely Taurus
And the police stood aside because they were tired of fighting when you go on vacation and you want to go to a big
Monument or something like that
Sartorius
Any new fight the cops into submission
Cuz you can't pay
You're whatever animal what if it's closed
You got beat up enough cops
Apps to where they quit
In order to get those hot dogs
Get out of 50
Peacock was amazing diculous
Also are the antifa leader that Alex is claiming Sienna and paid to go inside things that's Jaden X
Score John Sullivan
CNN did pay him first
Some footage that he got inside the capital which is actually the exact same thing but Alex
The staff did
If it satisfies the climate
It's getting paid him to incite a riot then
And so did Alex
That was just trying to claim that he had like 40 and people men behind him to burn down the capitol
I control whatever you don't have a government willing to do anything to
To correct a violent overthrow of the government they're going to make up stories and then try it again
Did do something
Locks
In order to punish the
These people
Just people
The people that got robbed
Pelosi's dad for Drinker beer
You gave Democrats
Charges dropped burning down Federal Building
You let them go
You got to let somebody go for
Especially when he's been in solitary confinement
I think that sentence served
Okay
No one should on Nancy Pelosi's desk on January 6th
Capital piston
S*** wherever they wanted
Electrocuted mess behind
In addition to that a guy named Eric jancar
Who was part of the storming of the building
He claimed that in his defense
America
Considered shooting on Nancy Pelosi's desk
Although people were chanting for someone to do so someone
Also I think it's a little bit
Before
September 2020 if I recall correctly
Some YouTuber s*** on Nancy Pelosi's driveway
This just gets mixed up in
Conflated
Alex has turned it into some guy s*** on Nancy Pelosi's desk
Solitary confinement for 8-ball print the legend buddy
Listen
If you sit on Nancy Pelosi's desk
You do get some respect
Formation
As long as you don't try and overthrow the country
Grape you in
So Alex
There's actually one more clip here I believe in relation to the cost
It has to do with the Costco rightly pointing out that hey guys
Trump was president
When that happens
And Alex
Zakk Wylde what movie was
Bbbb
As well
Which is a reminder that
Oh yeah
This alleged false flag operation
Shut off no one was even
Advice
The trash
99% of his staff or left
Pyramid threatened by people
So now Trump was in charge for 10000 National Guard
The Democratic Party
Refuse them
Threatened
Totally tried to request troops but was blocked is actually the exact opposite
Military times
Precise timeline it is
On December 31st 2020 DC mayor Muriel Bowser extended a request an invitation to the National Guard to come helps
Support local police
In the
Several hundred troops did respond to they were posted in DC but
They couldn't work
With the Capitol Police
Specifically they were not allowed to work on federal property
Without approval from the Capitol Police
Score outside the jurisdiction of Mayor Bowser
I did not
Approve that
The federal issue
That is Trump's purview
If the Capitol Police had appropriately coordinated with local law
National Guard troops would have been there
They failed to do so
I guess the bucket
Don't stop anywhere Corvallis
That's that's something that like
Over there
Kitchen Nightmares in 24 hours to hell and back
The Gordon Ramsay show where he goes in the fine
Small businesses that are struggling and they're about to fall apart
Maddie tries to help him out
Enough love that show
I love it when a business gets help
And it's very funny to me that they can make a lot of
It's very funny to me that they can make a show about it
Because every episode is essentially the exact same thing
Gordon Ramsay goes in there and he says
Hey
Do you want to run a good restaurant
Professionalism and accountability
That's literally it like generally ultimately
And the
It's so obvious
Once you like
Just hear him continue repeating that like
Oh
Does somebody continuously blame other people for ship
They're probably the problem
Yeah yeah there's a there's a trend
Sometimes things are other people's fault and there are other people's problems
Constantly somebody else's problem always somebody else's fault
When you're the president of the f****** United States and it's somebody else's fault guess what
You my beautiful be the problem
So Alex
People have been enjoying
Jeff Foxworthy's okay I'm not going to do it
I want you to I don't want you to come except I'm sort of
Pleasant roasted in this Jim Acosta piece
Because again
He is only mentioned
Free right now
Gets distracted by big
Covid news
I've got some big covid-19 news but I tend to start the shows with that
So I'm in the in the broadcast next segment weather
Infowars
Alex Jones Show on your mind
Positive
Covid-19
Hospitalized or die
So yeah Jen sake White House Press
She up to
I am tragic
I don't know if this is
Big breaking news
It's a minute snooze
Are also that British thing is just that Gregory support we talked about in the in a previous episode that I totaled
Bulshit
But yeah great
Weird noises of how you can tell devil-worshipers
How they make sure they come in contact
The jump through portals
It's it's so crazy how you
You can tell when someone's weird noises
Fugitive didgeridoo did seem like he was trying to make this sound of the music
But what he did decide to make a sound like a
Didgeridoo
That's my version of constipation
That's the problem it wasn't a bad pun about something terrible in pop culture
Alex
Have some claims about Jim Acosta about how bad he is
Another there now
Not accurate
How do you suck a monster Guinea runs around event
He personally runs around internet he's just
Horrible
He's riding League was in the CNN that you know said
Trump
Junior butt
5 years ago
CNN did that in
Acosta's in League with that I don't know how
Is necessarily
Something to Jim Acosta dead
Also another problem is
That they reporting on that story
To do very
It's a retraction automate
Porting on that that wasn't done by Sienna and that was actually done by Z
Zeke Miller
4 hour timer
So Alex is mixing those things out because who cares
It doesn't really matter really
Nope nope so what are the things that I think is really troubling
In the recent
Past
Was
That clip
From a turning point USA meeting
Where someone asked
Charlie Kirk
What time does
The time start using the gun
Elections are we going to let them see that you're alright
That you so clearly are teasing us with because you're trying to Griff but I'm not smart enough to figure that out so here we are
So Alex is very predictable
In his discussion
This he says that the person who asked a question with a plant
Are all the people who called him asking the same question plant
Answer the question well
But Alex would have gone a little bit differently
You would have also added some insight meant to now
Got this plant
When do we get to use the gun
Is all they want to set us up that's their plan that's their overall agenda
Can't wait to watch go battle League when I physical
Which is totally true Bravo kudos to tutor
Continued
MSNBC sang
We got to take
Got the mother effing white people
That we've got to kill Trump we got a
Kill all these people they're the ones
Thousand times more than I've calling for violence so I would have a response to a question if
Is it time to start shooting people
I would have
Ronin a bunch more stuff to f*** with people's emotions and make them scared and feel like they're in danger
More likely to use guns while at the same time I say ah to trick
That they they want to trick you into being offensive
Anything you do violent is defensive
Cuz they're the ones who were superb
Charlie
What you're misunderstanding about answering that question
Time
Was
I guess
When Timothy McVeigh
Bok Homa City
We should have been using guns from the beginning
You can't tell people that so you need to say it without saying
You should just say now political exactly that's exactly what you should have said better though
So Alex comes from a tradition of deep into communism
Of course all of his
Heroes and role models are Dum Dums
Right
They're cold war holdouts in
And even anti-communism as another metaphor for
Another euphemism for just
Right right
When I say I don't mean someone who's supposed to
Chicago sort of a tradition
Babe
It has tendrils all over the place
Yeah conspiratorial mindset definitely
That links up with all kinds of historical Frameworks
Spit blood libel be at the protocols of the Elders of Zion
All these sorts of conceptions about the New World Order
If the Illuminati right
Uses
Opposition
The communism as a man
Who is
Against social welfare programs
Against
Bob Wright
Four people in minorities disenfranchised group
I think you can I think it might be able to do a little better than that
I do think this could be
Something of a mislead a misleading name
I do recognize that I thought about that for a while and terms of like
How I frame
Thanks I mean
I think there's a more precise term I agree
I wasn't criticizing your uses
But yeah
That that is just such a
Great
Brilliant and accepted way for them to get away with saying we're White supremacists
At everybody
Just being like well they come from an anti-communist tradition of
Just like
They come from a we should Blacklist the Jews tradition where they come from
What black people shouldn't be allowed to drink from the same water fountain
Extradition you don't understand why but only because they don't want black people to drink the water fountain
Riot States right
It's the rebel flag there's nothing wrong with the rebel
Flag Day
Who do I bring this up
Because
What are the
Hallmark's
Particularly of the early anti-communist Folk
Is
Severe red-baiting
In Russia
Apparently though Alex has one of these
Neo anti-communist
Let me just get this out there right now
Power structure
Globally is is Beyonce
America
Sold out American power to build up Commons China
Polygon with
Corporate Alberto,
But now the Communist Chinese have double
Crosstown
What are Samurai
Just like you want
Screw you
I thought you were mad about the genocide
And then you've got
Russia out from under the New World Order
They got their own problems not not
Romanticizing that but they're definitely not Hollywood
Got all that going on you got the Midwest
All over the world
Leaving people on the West Coast
We're winning
A world ID vaccine passport
Carbon taxes
Because they're getting their ass handed to him
Now
Now the power structure works
Talking about how we're starting to win the fight
Thought we were already dead
I mean
It just it
Disorienting and then also just feed the the framework that he lives in now we're like
China and Russia are the good ones
Omar is really bizarre
It is kind of like
What he thought was supposed to happen with 9/11
I'm coming you know like they're making you afraid of foreign enemies
To bring that home
Is tradition
Is to make you afraid of foreign enemies
And now you bring it back home and you should
You just be afraid of anyone in the world in a densely populated urban center
Yeah
Now there's something to that
Alex plays a clip
The show but before he does
He wants you to know
That the globalist
The same people who ran Obama
Play run by
I mean
The distinction between the
That's nice yeah
Same people that control Obama are the ones that are controlled by
Bagatelle Obama because he's so evil and so hateful and
The Star Chamber tribunal level
He's actually in there with the top global
What's an otter album
Oh, is that the table
Stop.
Plus I'm grandma
Bill Gates
Warren Buffett
All those people at the table we got the.
They decided the world belongs to them and they've all got a lot to literally depopulate you and your family
Virus 1000 times worse than covid-19
And let them March you
Or you going to wake up and wake others up and say hell no
I'm not going down your rattle
Looks like Alex is doing his job of trying to incite people that sounds about right
So I'd like those document
About the people at the table exactly
All I want
What are the
Huge hundred people and people with big old ego
Yeah they're not going to be sitting cramped at that table eating with only 14
No no
I would like those documents because I've heard a lot of different things about the relative position of Bill Gates over the course
How does this work with the
Team of 12 group within the hundred
Or is it even is there another hierarchy within the hierarchy I guess there's like
88 people who are at the main table
Like the Kids Table adults the Council of twelve sitting over there
Straight
Okay
Alright
AMV
The people who are at the Kids Table they don't get wine
See this room saying
About the table that's unfair
Does Obama get to tell joke
Obama
Got to this table of 100
Just cuz he hates America so much
When
When are you
I would argue that there's a lot of people hate America
I should be at that table if that is the prerequisites like Tyrion either you running
I told you this is not like the best Alex Trebek
Married
Discussion
So deeply race
Cyst under tongue
Anyway we will be back
Episode
Sprite.com your family not used to
I'm glad that this is a remembered
Also we're on Twitter
Emilio Emilio mdzs
Spirit writer
Alexandra Thurston color