Air Jordan
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about
Alex June
Quick question for you sure
Jordan is given up
I've been watching the new season of Survivor as it as it goes
Ben
Frustrated
Over the course of watching all of this
Season about how far its
Come
From its original premise right
How complicated the rules are
If I were to try and explain to you how to
To play Survivor now
I have no idea how I would I couldn't you take hours
Of me being like Okay so
So now here's the thing
Hidden immunity idol
Okay okay if I put that aside for now
Now that's a no I refuse to allow that to happen this season
Advantage
Do you have this piece of paper disadvantaged
Tribal Council you can
Ask one person though one question
And it can be either do you have an advantage or do you have an idol
And if they do that
To give it to you
Right
F******
Ridiculous is turning into one of those like what is it with you remember those murder games that you would play the youth group
Where everybody would hide for a while and one person was a bad guy then you met up at the end of going to be like
This person was there yeah but the rules are amazed
I cut I was watching
The people now you know it's like they're very simple rules
The kids game where you die
Pheasant season 12 of Survivor
If I can find some food
Find some food at TGIF no calories in you to run this footrace later interviewed voted at
There's a lot more just like okay the game
Now it I have no
An idea last night's episode was the second part of a two-parter
Right
Cancel
Did they were supposed to be merging the tribes
But instead of doing that
There was another twist
And that was that one
They did they split into two tribes
And half of them
1 immunity
Okay
There was an uneven number of person who was left over.
Map to the f****** Exile Island where Jeff Probst bus
Sorry sorry sorry about
He got on the bus at least showed up on a
Barbie boat with an hourglass
A hammer
If you don't break all of your fingers by
Set a timer to sound of God through this hourglass you will be dead
I said if I got that I would change profile that I look at the hammer
She had to decide whether or not to go back in time
If she decided to break The Hourglass
Then
The other
Half
Of the group
2hype
The challenge would get immunity that the other people would be vulnerable
To be voted at okay
I was just sitting there like why are we doing this
Drama Dan but it wasn't more dramatic
Irvine Lake
It's still two steaks are set the same
I do I do appreciate that like okay
Well
Here's the thing
Are you bringing back Tyler ever going to say pick one of the other
That's Amir
It's a very simple explanation
How old we kind of like Survivor there up a bit you know come on
Let's go for it
Hammer destroy the very
Embodiment of time so I think afterwards after the episode I was reflecting a little bit
And I
Think I give up
I went out on the show but I'd like I give up on caring
It will be an experience
Do you and I I don't know if you recall this directly but do you remember the
End of 1984
The year I was born
The book
Sure
You remember how he is
Beaten down so much that he just loves
The state
I'm putting up with
What about you what's your birthday
I've been doing some yoga
Some things about is my second time doing it ever last night and
I got in trouble
Because I was being verbally corrected on something that I was doing wrong or whatever
Through me like
Just hearing the voice
Through me so much that I just fell over and began laughing and just being like
I didn't hear a word you said you don't like how I would be laughing
Seton no according to the people that are in yoga now or whatever you're supposed to
Be all quiet and s***
Right but anyways
It's fun to be reprimanded in a new place for being loud and laughing
Going to hit every possible activities
Where people can be angry at me for being loud and laughing
You kind of got to take the rough with the smooth who I mean because like
Basically we've
Creative podcast
You know people enjoy it
Somewhat because you're allowed
Are you my whole heart
Another settings
The other direction
Well I'm glad I look forward to you showing up on Monday to do the podcast to me like look what I can do and then putting her
Look behind your head something weird feet the flexibility
My partner I am going to defeat
Yoga and then never do it again and then once I am one side
I feel like I'm confident I will say this is
Is dumb and quit forever I wish you well
So Jordan today we are going back to the past
May 4th and 20
5th 2003
And the reason for that
Is because
I don't
Know if we were going to have
Enough lead time
To do the episode that I wanted to do
For Friday
Alright
And that is I realize that Alex is going to be talking
Almost
Exclusively about Tucker's Patriot Purge documentary
Hey people have gotten
Touch of Italy
Please do an episode about
Patriot prayer
It does seem like that is our eventual end
I've been resistant to do episodes about Tucker Carlson for a number of reasons
One I don't want to step on the toes of there's another podcast that does Tucker I don't want to
Other people's intellectual proper
Hey can't do it every time any other podcast
The talked about Alex Jones we I have obviously been very
Sure that I just don't believe that Tucker
Richarlison is a sincere actor and
I don't
Think
That he interest
Me and the same way as Alec
I don't want to talk about any Rich pricks
You know I mean like the but that kind of childhood
You know that kind of just like
He's in our take it either take your ball and go home kid
I've lived long enough
To watch
His
Various incarnations
And I don't find him to be
Like a person with that
With up with a solid ground under
Vitas
Hagrid
Integrity sound
Positive
Integrity
He's done
This s*** that is a good point
Shades of some things throughout Alex
His career but there's
What you could call it a coherent through line
Not really for someone like
Right right right
Don't interest me as much
But
I think that the intersection is so high here that will
Probably have
2:30
Do something about papers
And
Alex was apparently do background work on it so kind of
So I can so I wanted to do an episode about that but I realize we probably wouldn't have enough lead time by the time at
It was all out
And everything for this episode so we'll be on Monday we'll talk about that on Monday
And for now
We're back in the past
Enjoying
The smooth Breeze
A 2003
TNT
Which is doing 2002
Let's take a little moment to say hello
So first
Jordan's Afrikaner accent in the episode 104 sounds like
Kiwi Richard Nixon thank you so much you are now policy
Now I kind of
Are you I'm hearing kiwi Nixa to my head but I don't know how to make it come out of my mouth if I could
God I could do it loud
I'll just go back to the 104
I'm a policy wonk next
Thank you so much and I apologize
Raiden
Editorially
God of thunder
Thunder right
Alright for me I will
I'm a policy wonk
That's the people from Manchester but I don't know probably mispronouncing it
Intimidate
Sion our policy
Wonder there's a liver pueblan
Iowa Book
Lilliputian Gulliver's Travels Evil Book
No one will ever suspect that tiny man never becoming president
So here we are back in the past and
Oh wait we have
Figure it out what we were looking
For in the past
We know that Alex does think he's fighting the devil
And so is likewise don't want to keep
Keep going in the past
Answer
My initial justification was
See what you think
Thanks more about Harry Potter this is right
Listening over this episode
That's what our new mission is
And so we'll get to that
In the middle of this episode before we do
Here's another contact drop that I just think it's kind of cute
Maryland
Hey I'm here
I don't know why would there's just something Sherman I really
That made me laugh so hard Barney's I'm so excited
I enjoyed that
Although you've got that Barney
Five kind of tone to him that's it that's perfect
So we start here on the 24th
And Alex gets into talking about
How the feds
They said damn tracks around
A bit about the anthrax letters that
Like that were sent to me in the wake of 9/11
And
We don't need to rehash that
But there's a piece of this narrative that I don't believe we've gotten a
Into that I think is worth exploring
Congressional
A Night to Remember
Real
In 2001
Inoculation
Smallpox
We talked
We talked a bit about the end of the FED sending Anthrax narrative but we didn't talk
About
The angle of it
That is this
Bush Administration folks being on Cipro
Before the letters got sent out
That it's a pretty
Consistent thing that he uses as proof that they had Advance knowledge that anthrax was going
Going to be sad okay okay
Here's what happened with this
Completely insane lawyer Larry klayman who is still with Judicial Watch
At this point great in 2002
A quote access to documents about last fall.
2Pac
Asserting that top officials may have known that the attacks were,
Took B based on the fact that you know there had been
Information that people are on Cipro for back fat
Confronting several years ago
You wanted to know if Bush ever called him an a******
Cipro is an antibiotic that can be used as a treatment for someone who's a
Exposed to Anthrax but it's not really the kind of treatment you would want for inhaled a
Switches with a large
Concerns would be
With the anthrax
Send these letters
In fact Cleveland clients in the suit where workers at a Washington
Wheaton post office
Do employees at the facility where they work
Could handle the anthrax letters and made it died
Because they inhaled anthrax
Switch again
That's why you're really going to be concerned about the situation
Not so much
You could get it if you have a cut on your hand you could have a different kind of
Exposure
The death kind
Is the one you don't
Sure the issues it wasn't until after this
After
For September 11th that the scientific community
They may break through
In terms of antitoxin therapy
Soda really effective against
Instant hailed anthrax
Like anthem
And
Rexi rexi Bakuman
Did you just curse me I think I did
I prefer anthem
That would
So at that time though
Let you know after 9/11
These treatments weren't available in the only real option that was on the table would have been antimicrobial agents
And these antibiotics like Cipro or doxycycline
The risk of these members of the Bush Administration would have been taken by exposing themselves to a ax
Even if they were on Cipro would be no
It's a bizarre
Do you know what's the weirdest part about this
This is something that people never talk about those Anthrax letters
They were really well-written sure like
Collectors like a bank like
Letters to a young man o to a young Poet by renier real
Basically like calligraphy
Amazeum
So if there actually is a vaccine against Anthrax called biothrax
If the folks in the government really wanted to protect themselves from a false flag attack that's almost certainly what they would have
Actually what happened in the real world
On September 11th
Text George W bush and many members of his staff were on board Air Force One
What are the people on the plane was White House physician Colonel dr. Richard tub
Tub was understandably freaked out and he decided to make a decision just in case the worst case scenario
From an interview with tub
Quotes
The thing at that moment I was most worried about was a biologic
In the unlikely but high-risk scenario I thought there was little harm to be prophylaxis in the staff with Anna
Biotics
It seemed like almost science fiction
I gave everyone on the plane a week of Cipro
I hope by the time they ran out we to figure it out
The fog of War
Continue my shirt
An antibiotic like Cipro wouldn't necessarily be super effective at preventing you from being harmed by anthrax
But you have a better chance
Spell the sooner you start
The reason that some of the Stanford given Cipro is because after 9/11 the way that's doctor wanted to cover his bases
Because if they're
Had been a biological attack
Start the antibiotics
Because he waited
You couldn't get that time back you're sure sure
This is an incredibly stupid conspiracy theory because it fails to take
Into account the very clear explanation for why someone working in the White House might have been given Cipro around that time
There was a feeder on 9/11 that they might have already been
Expose
Also you see here outhouses using the story to drum up fears about forced vaccination
That's because he always
He's does that and it never actually ends up happy
When you go back and you listen to him be wrong about this s***
This specific s*** over and over again
He's being wrong so
That lady really use that to inform how you hear him talking about covid in the present
Just another wannabe
Yeah it's the same thing whether it's real or not outside whether there's a deadly virus or not
Vaccines are killing people or whatever
Can hear him tell the story cuz he's like
Talking about why would Bush Administration people on Cipro months before
The the anthrax letters
It wasn't months
Before
And there was a reason because it was on 9/11
Big zits
It's suspicious the way
He ortix
Articulate
But it's not actually sisters
So Alex has a big headline for the day
This is one of his varsi
City Stories
And it's about to the Houston Chief of Police
Coming out and saying
There's no justice
Okay okay
Criminal
That's quite quite a quote from the Houston police chief never heard a police chief that far
Throwing it up
Call work on their asses
So what happened is it there
Concerns about the validity of the results that were coming out of the DNA crime lab in Houston
After at least one person was found to have been wrongly
Convicted based on inaccurate results from that lab
Audit of the lab and there's also
Swear not good
It turned out that the lab had a leaky roof that they've been trying to get funds to fixari what
Since 1995 what did you just say to me
So you're telling me that the f****** thin line between convey
Eviction for
25 to life
And exoneration is a leaky roof only issue that was indicative of the
Troubles in misallocation not being able to allocate funds
Bright
They're only two analysts work
Working in the lab which is way too few for a city as huge as Houston
Wow that's great
That's real great stuff not only looked at the State of Affairs at the lab
It also reviewed historical cases
Identify potential evidence that came out of
The lab was closed in December 2002 and going back to the early 1990s the audit found quote major
Issues in 43 out of 135 cases
But they looked at
Definitely
Bed that the prop phukmi
So many of the labs potentially flawed pieces of War ultimate leben
Confirm by independent test
Remember of the errors that they made that were major issues
Some of them were not
About the
Accuracy of the results right
The process and stuff like that team they actually got it right in the confirmed
Surprised we also got a ride but fuk up
If we knew we were going to it might have
Reliably got it right
But unfortunately there was that one definitive
Case where they were responsible for this wrongful
Also this audit uncovered a total of 52 cases
That they had on their books
That hadn't been
Confirm by outside testing
And doing so at that point would likely be
Righttime us
The possibility of other wrongful convictions result
DNA analysis during this era
Cannot be diss
Yeah
The big
Big
Yeah
Other areas of the Houston Police
Department lab actually be pretty solid in the audit
Various for Toxicology trace evidence and Firearm test
Did a good job but that
DNA part was a
Serious
Serious bro
Yeah you know the thing that everybody uses to convince people and says is a Smoking Gun
Evidence you know that that that small part of the process
DNA
The Houston Police Department suspended the lab and Internal Affairs reviewed any criminal and administrative violations
Could have been made in the running of the lab in this resulted in a fair amount of Hauschka
Like a bunch of people resign
The da open to grand juries and possible criminal charges for the labs operation but neither ended up returning any and died
There's a massive review going on
The errors that have been made in the past with the lab woods and.
Still operating
And I'm certain that the police chief Clarence Bradford said
Nothing really
So what Alex's
Is a legend
Do you like the idea of
Police chief
Just napping
I just be it like you know what f***
I'm going to tell everybody everything
This blue wall of Silence
A f****** done with it
That mother f***** killed
People yesterday I did see some comments that he made about like
The prosecutor is wanting to win as opposed
Do Seeking Justice or whatever
And I think some of that might have been affected by the fact that he gotten
In trouble with the law
And he has just had a case against him
For like perjury
The birds are the little bits
When you have somebody who's me a critical of the justice system
Even over the chief of police
It's kind of relevant that they had just had a brush with the law
I don't know
Is very serious
Like the really serious story in the way Alex
Discovering it does a real disservice to the reality within the audit and
You know baby since project
Cyborg
They were trying to make sure whatever
Information that could be gleaned from this could be used to Free People Who
I've been Rock Lee
Convicted whenever I mean I was John ra of True Crime is railroaded and put
Put in jail unjust
You know like it's not like we have a small number of those documentaries just floating around out there
That s*** is
Pumped out on the regular pernett play
Flexo
So Alex has a bit of a missed telling of this
Does Houston crime lab
And I think again
This is what I really want to make is like this is a serious story
And Alex
Turns it into a joke
By reporting it for later
Hair
And I
This is a disservice to actual reporting
Story like this
Requires actual
Cuz
It's a big big deal
Police chief here we've never convicted a guilty man not once
0 *
The Christmas party that's what it's all for
It's turning this into a cartoon story
Do anything about you that makes you mad make you mad
Didn't plan that you're fighting against at the half of ratman yeah okay
He's worried about crime
Naturally
Play there's no justice in Houston
Texas
Is great
Because they allow you to have.
I was just know how he would leave
Estate
Where you couldn't protect
Himself in his home from the roving gangs of
Do crackheads or breaking into everybody's house
50 guns
Come out
After that
Alex
Gets into talking about how in Texas
I don't know if you know that I don't know
When people
Break into car
In Texas specifically in Tech
Intex
What they do
He's the only break into cars that are parked on the street
Like outside your house that's on the street
He'll break into it
Driveway
Okay so we're operating on a safe Zone rules traditional tag rules you know like
With without
Running around
Busting down doors
Raping and killing
I don't do that
I want a car broken into
Car broken into
We've been robbed as well all of the neighbor
Because
Robbing our car
Strange sort of weird
Discussion that he's having with himself on a figure out the ethics
Of shooting someone for rifling through your car
Did have a little bit of a philosophy class kind of vibe to it where he's going like flipping Okay so
Alright
I do think it's right to protect myself however
Is the value of the objects in the car worth a human life
On the other hand
Does that mean that there are
Any valuable objects that are worth a human life
Should it be
$30,000 is that what I should
Kill a man for minor in college
Can tell you that
Do usually lyrics
Explore a little deeper
Send what I was doing this is not a good philosophy class
And you'll hear that
He got to the point where it's like I don't know if
It's worth killing someone if they're robbing my car the first thing he thought of was the hassle
Yeah yeah it is true that his biggest problem was I have to go to court and I have to be like
I'm do it on purpose
I was worth the trouble
That's the that's the real problem with killing people
Something afterward
I've killed a lot of people
The killed nobody
Spelling of it
Lot of people
How much of a hassle it is slow
He's a sick motherfuker likes to kill really f***** up
He talks about some of his stories
Excited
During this next clip sure which is really weird
Really weird to hear him talk about stuff like this when we know that later he'll tell these stories about how he killed people
Through Queen
Back in 2003
And I was never a big deal
Almost
I was always involved in them but moaning in okay
Hornady I was constantly Jump by all the black people in town
Who gets into fights whatever stuff goes wrong in a baseball game
Play a little bit of a rough Sandlot
That was a sure you know what man when you getting
The fights
And the coaches
School would hear about it
They would punish you and just
The folksy a sway
Work it out
Around
Running around the track
I'm around at the Bannon
Bruise across your hind in
What is the murder
I was going to say it but what's
The time that this is 2320 years to go from
When I got into a fight my coach make me rant
6 people surrounded by the f******
Denver Broncos
And let me tell you I'm like
I liked it because I was so mad I get the time
To prove my Warriors
Strike this story really
6 Byron
It's like starting with a 1950
Is idyllic sweet place
Whenever
Stop
It's starting with like
If me and my friends with Jason hoop down the road
I meant like a couple years later the story is f****** sleep game
I was forced to kill my friend
Watch my friends die
Every year one person had died
Did die.
To keep the school open
Yes they were the exact official lamps
Of course
The 2003 version of these stories is a lot more
Believable very believable
Sounds like an actual story it's early relatable I remember when I play bass
Football in junior high
I
Drop to the coaches ring
He was a football player that you was in the NFL
Super Bowl rings
Accidentally
So just carpet nothing happened
Like you're running
You're running laps
Which do you prefer
You know what to do
There is a relationship between the
Looks at you and your ghost
Alright fine I don't start running away
You know what I know now that I actually articulate this and say this out loud
I wonder if that actually was
The Super Bowl ring
Because I bet it wasn't
Something else now looking back as a 37 year old person
Receivable that he brought a foot like a soup
Super Bowl ring
2A Junior High basketball practice
Would impress the hell out of everybody there hard not to say that to I do know that he did win a Superbowl
Okay yeah he absolutely did with who
The Giants
Jerome Sally
Coke salad
Yeah he
I also all right kids
I coach
Steve Young now let's go get 8 points today
I also had an issue with like he went to the same church that I went
He knew me but
Before he was my coach
And that also kind of lied to him by
Having a little bit of a damper on me a little bit
But yeah I look back on that
I had to have been
And some other sort of rain
I know that I dropped a ring that was a sentimental value and in my head
I thought it was a Super Bowl ring
Forever I didn't throw up though murdered a lot of people
Show me the story several years ago for the first time I remember we were hanging out at a bar after we recorded the show and you are
I can't believe I can't wait to tell you the story
Drop the Superbowl ring
Murdered six people
Now my coach
Was actually in the Super Bowl
So I told you at the beginning of this episode that
We have a new reason
To stay in the past
And that is
That
Are you forgotten
In the timeline
A 2000
Is when
Greg Davis the governor of California has a recall
Against
Okay it is just starting up here and doing
And that leads us
Something very important
You will all enjoy that
He also
Creature like Arnold
Alex
Hates Arnold Schwarzenegger
I believe
Believe that this. Where there is a runoff election
The recall will be
I think he's going to go nuts
I think I think it's going to be a really really interesting.
Iamsu
Christ he hates
Arnold Schwarzenegger
I am right or know why I feel like there's something about Arnold that he should enjoy
Like you should see something in Arnold that reminds him of
Masculinity of some sort writer
It seems like he would be attracted to that
I'm sure you wouldn't want to articulate to somebody Howard
Activity is too strong men but I think that would be odd
I don't know exactly what
The bone
He's picking
But
I know that
He had a website that he was running there was like Arnold exposed
Like he goes all out against Arnold Schwartz
And does Jesse hate this is Ventura hate hate Arnold
I actually haven't heard Alex bring up Jesse Ventura much at this in this 2003.
Probably
I don't know when.
Ventura run
Good question and I don't remember
It's hard to remember the crazy Governors from each state
Just like Howard Texas there's no such thing as
Is Justice because of all the DNA tampering
Spell every state is at a
Super insane Governor at one point or another
Just stop
Being governor
Rhizome
This would have been the rise of Michelle Baca
Reasonable
Communication
So I am now
Staying in the past
Under the guise of tracking Alex's coverage of the Arnold Schwarzenegger gubernatorial run
That's what I'm excited about now
I'll come up with a pun
The 6th day
Collateral damage
I also I'm still interested in seeing it when Alex gets
Accept the reality about the bass part
Oh yeah I would be interested something else that I'm still tracking
EXO 2003
Time frame
The next episode we do in the Press
And he's going to be like
And the bath party is still in power in Iraq
I'm taking over the global
So I Alex talk to you about
A cousin of his
Make a sparkly
Maybe it is
Yesterday I don't know probably
Respect family
If this is Berkeley
His resume is much larger than house DJ and former Infowars employee
Get some real serious business
Bergstrom Air Force Base
You familiar with that
I'm sorry what
Intelligent someone Illinois 911 I'm watching
TV on
This is absolutely a
Happen without them letting it happen
And I'll tell you what I can tell it just like it is
So I don't know if Buckley merge
The police or the military but
He might have been doing that at the airport
I mean if it was Buckley's
Job that would explain why it didn't
Happened
And when people say Alex is like CIA and s*** like that
This is the kind of the reason why
Some of those people get those theories of it if you'd like
My cousin is merging the police with the military
How can you
Maintain that level of
Like familiarity with your cousin if your cousin is literally implementing what you think is the f****** end of the world
Your cousin is killing Posse Comitatus
Agree to disagree
This color really touches on an important dynamic
In response to a national tragedy like 911 he convinces himself there's no way that something like that could
Did just happen
It had to be
Conspiracy decide
The reason that conclusion happens
Before he goes out looking for information
He's actually doing
He's less about seeking truth and more about finding someone who will help him feel sick
Cure in the conclusion that he's already come to
He wants to be the choir for someone else
Preach to
And now it's filled that role quite well
Almost no one gets convinced
To follow Alex or believe what he says because if they were using the Rational part of their brain
Or they're engaging with the information he puts out
Will be almost impossible to take him seriously
The path is often more like with his collars describing where there's actually no persuasion necessary Alex's
He's just saying the things that they
These folks are craving
Or someone say based on the feelings that they have
Surrounding
I don't know not
Not feeling comfortable with the Rand
That dynamic
Is also really really active in the present-day stuff about Kobe
It's something that
Is worth
Except
The chaotic universe is ultimately the fundamental
The problem with everything that we do right now
It does it does lead to a lot of like bad thoughts
Patterns
So the chaotic universe that we live in is
The therapist
What
One of the products of the
I like talking like that
Richard literal product another one is that there have been a hundred different versions of the Hulk
So many versions of the Hulk
Oh man that he hadn't even seen Avengers by this point I don't feel back on Edward Norton
He had
Been almost
Cast of the event
No that was Guardians of the Galaxy part of the Avengers universe
So Alex
Okay
Government
And
New World Order
She certainly was bringing people together
Really bring the information to the table not just screaming
Unplugs her infowars.com
I think
There's just not been anyone so much like Fred Hampton in my life a lifetime you know somebody who can bring together all
All of the lower class doesn't matter what race
Doesn't matter what Creed
Bring them in
I think that I have some bad
For Alex
And like
The people who
Super racist
Also
The new world order plants
No they're just there's a lot of races tonight
Yeah I think Alex is real problem is more that they pick a racist without teeth
He would he would prefer that he were to go on these shows
So he could be the racists
I need a really nice teeth
Gotten braces away
These people are being
To Publix
Glee contemptible
If I were to go on there and look good
Yep yep
The Hulk apparently is mine
Punisher
What about the other one
What what what are they
Before this or after this I think he must be talking about the angry one cuz I think the angli one
Came before the Edward Norton 1
What's
His dumb face
Took over as the Hulk for The Avengers
You know the angry Hulk was the 2003 one
Okay so let's see
Norton would have been wet like 2000
Eight or nine or not far away the Incredible Hulk
Yeah right here at Redwood Norton 1
Damn wow
Crazy
Marvel has dominated by adult life kind of brutal fashion
Shocking that you nailed but like a both of those and it makes me question
I know that I watch
I don't remember the
Here's the worst part was bored here's the worst part
Never saw both of
I've never seen one of the Hulk movie
That is weird
Phone calls as you heard the siren
In the back all those guy
I was on the phone
Amber
Skip a little bit upset at
At this next caller who brings up
Certain radio house
How about who is this
Give me very many Clues
Important
What is dwarfed by all these other issues
Bright
You're blind
Yeah yeah
Now you can't see that Harry Potter is demonic
Because
They released
One of the five books on
On the solstice
Your blinds
I mean it tracks
Apparently some host
It was on the radio does neocon was talking about
How Harry Potter isn't evil
Alex does not enjoy this
I believe this is Michael Savage
Find a bit more about Michael Savage
Throughout this
He gets another call from somebody who's like hey you know why I was trying to turn my friends on
I told this guy to listen
As I told him
And then he told me
And I called the FBI cuz that dude's crazy
He tells this story twice
Okay
Then Alex brings in his guests
For the show.
Is Ray McGovern
Been on quite a bit like an hour
Intelligence analyst
And
Alex wants
The caller to
To tell Ray this story
It's just it's heat I got so many times
It's not even a good snack terrible
No I am
Pray that you
I'm allergic to lipstick
Another word of it
Price told the story for the third time
And now I am
Cycling is the FBI called them. They want to put
Put me in jail for
Yeah
Exercise instantly it fascinating that
Michael Savage
Is so hated by Alex
At this point
And like
In the future I will be like
He's always been a great hero
Sounds like you would Survivor you know you
He's just been beaten down by so much Michael Savage over the years he's like
The stuff I like to hear don't think that's analogous but that's fine
Interview with Ray McGovern for about the
Like rest of the show
And I find it very boring
It's basically just a Iraq sucks
They got her at the country the water
Why not
Feels bad for the people in Iraq
Totally the right tank
He says something that I would have thought
Freak out about
It's kind of disappointing but he does
I feel
Alex Meadow
What's going on
Being done not only to these children
We really can't blame
From the farm said they hoped
You want me to get my way into
Clearly
Nationalized
We can't pretend to have the answer to these things
Plan going in weho
What happened after the war
UN in there
Inspectors bag
Should be something
Leads to fireworks
Rosa bring them to devil
Amanda doesn't lead to a fight it's really
The frontman for evil to step in and fight
This battle for Anita internationalize
I can't believe that somebody would say that to Alex
Two-Face and Alex
It would not react like
Yep
Part of it is at this point Ray McGovern
He's kind of somebody who has some credibility
And I don't think Alex
Wants to lose that once again
Imbalance
That's leading to Alex
Text being a
Scaredy cat
Alex's
Incredibly low status comparative
And I think that's
That's why he
He does point he does speak up and as I got out of the un's actually bad
Ray isn't having any of it
It just it just leads to them talking
Conversation
Alex says one thing
Breakout of ignores it and
Says another
I wanted to be a fight
That's such a and that's also one of those things with Alex
It's such a tale for me in is
Is like regardless of all the other s*** like somebody who's so
That aware of
How status and balance should change the way that they to the point where it's so obvious he's just a bully
Like that's what
Though every interaction with a status and balance shows is Alex
This is just a bully
But it is also a bully with a bad radar
Yeah that's true he could bully like Bill Ayers
That is true that is true
Hell yeah but that's because billares is socialist monster so it should be easy when you have the
Power of the Lord behind you to say get
Behind me Satan radar
Yeah I also think there's something
I just I just
Feel like if you believe that the UN is an instrument of trying to
Explicitly
Brumby
Beginning
Has been about bringing the new world order a One World Government
We're just going to be run by the Antichrist and Satan if somebody is
They like woah
I think we need to bring in the UN in order to
This master.
Is happening in Iraq
International Solutions are necessary
You should not be able to move on to any other subject
Until this is
Cleared up
And if you have a fundamental disagreement just feel like thank you very much
I cannot talk to you cuz you believe in the devil
Exactly
What I do what I do when somebody says something like that is ice cream a barking like a dog
Has like a political opposition
To I
International Solutions
What's the problem
Stat with its the devil
Because it's more interesting
Pokes his listeners emotional button
Sproodle
Anyway we move onto the 25th
Because the interview is not really all that good
It starts at the show saying something
Anxieties
Really fun
Really silly
Your
No I'm sorry
We are going to address
World government
Wait a couple years and see how much you talk about Hillary being
Jesus man that is not relevant to his call Arizona family but this point becomes
The only relevant issue
The only thing that's ever been important she's been working with the devil since she was born outside in a dream prophetically in that
That's why you can say
F*** it you don't need to pay attention to Hillary Clin
What was the first hour of this episode is Alex
Yelling about how he's the one who really supports the troops
And honestly
I do
Wanna split too many hairs about
Because
Most of the point that he's making
Is
And that is if you do support
Troops you should not support sending them into an unjust War where people are going to
To get killed
To be in a situation where they could kill
Civilians
And have that on their conscience and that's not an arguable thing
Support the troops
Sport health care for veterans and
You know like all the stuff yet
Fine point
Good job
It's about the almost the whole first hour so here's a little tip
America
Holyshit man
The left-right paradigm
It really is a clear articulation of what
He believes his politics
To be in that is that the left is Super Evil Superbad
And the conservatives are actually just
The laughter pretending to be
Exactly
But they're the last
Conceives of himself as just like being
Conservative
When he's
Extremely far to the right
Alright the problem with the neocon says that their
Democrats are the problem
So it doesn't matter what you call yourself
Anybody I do like as a Democrat
Yeah it's problem with the left and the right isn't that like they each have problems
Hey things that there are like okay this is where you're wrong here a little bit
It's vert the same thing and they're all to the left of him
Yeah that's what it is
I'm so far right everything is to the left of me
Able to trick people into thinking that he's Above This sort of thought of me
He's able to trick people into thinking he's sensible because he has sensible positions like this
Supporting the troops
Doesn't mean
Supporting them being used to
I have this
Nonsense War
And also I think he's a
Hipa blowhard
I get a tear in my eye
Play The Star-Spangled Banner and I cried
F*** off
Ridiculous
Imagine
Trying things up
Pledge of Allegiance
Hasn't it
Dealt single-tier
Let me pledge allegiance to this thing destroying me
Christ I only think that that could happen
If it was the
Culmination of like a really
Traumatic
Experience
Movie kind of experience
Independence Day
The movie the movie independent at the end we say the Pledge of Allegiance
Attack of the
Coleman is just giving
When is Big Air this is the Independence Day for the world speech
Then we got a we got the dude flying up into the thing the whole thing explodes and then Bill Pullman leads you in the pledge of
Allegiance tear
Tear
I get it in those circumstances that's open
I got it did Jeff Goldblum survive
Sequel
Status imbalance
Will Smith
Did not
What about
The movie
We get to mi amor Harry Potter
A call from a guy is like a man
What if
The release
Release of Harry Potter is Justin
Distraction
Alex says
No okay
John Deere on the air
Yes is the Harry Potter rollout on
Somerset
The time to divide
Confirm Bohemian Grove
Don't know
Fact
Christianity
Winter or summer
Basically what this is all about
Alright
Okay
So which is do the exact same thing this Christians do but which
Is there a called Christians are in a call. Cuz we're right about things
Because God is real
He gives us
The powers
To banish demons control Magic
What sort of Christian book are you talking about
Later sold the Christian book stores that are like persuasive or like Bible study
Kind of book
There's a book in its
Just about a character who happen
Since to be Christian I don't
Think it
It wouldn't necessarily be a
Persuasive book
Towards like a vengeful eisinger
In the same way that Harry Potter isn't trying to get you into witchcraft it's just
A child
Who goes to a school cuz he's a f****** wizard right
But isn't he kind of implying that
A book written by a Christian
Similar to Harry Potter
Would specifically have the unspoken
You should join Christianity element to it a Harry Potter 2
Because
It only makes sense for him if
That's the case for Christian
I mean if possible but I think
One of the other thing
There's an undercurrent that a Galaxy
Does lamenting
And that is that if this book was
Is about a child
Like Harry Potter
Who is destined to go to a monastery
It wouldn't be as cool
Is Harry Potter like freaking out about like oh my God
God I love this book where the kid becomes a bucket
What is Umberto Echo Road
Christian iconography
Interest
I think it would think it would it would have a tougher time catching on not because of an aversion to Christianity in pop culture
Just because
That's not it being a monk isn't as cool to care Trail as being a wizard because there's
True
And semiotic professors don't necessarily relate to the the children
Trends
These days
So are the same color
In like a man
Hey man
Then we're going to the Grove this year he's going to go check out the Grove
Alex's note
Amen this color brick
Break some important news.
Am I going to go out there with video this year
3 years ago
I don't know
I gave copies of that tape
4911 type to Ralph Nader and
Congressman John.
Lincoln Republican
Professor
RFK
Junior
Sodus Point
Wait you know Ralph Nader it does seem like he is like hey Ralph
Send him a little text message I got this thing to get you
Pretty impressed
Wait wait till you heard back from telling me that Ralph Nader
Sent you a message saying like what
Cat really did find something
Yeah yeah they got together
Videos pretty good
Listcawler
So this is a big deal
Wait a second
Is this where RFK Jr goes crazy
You never know it could be a nuisance
Yeah they sent after
After they watch it
They seem to try
Answer
Attitude on television at night
Coincidence maybe they never watched
From the
Green Party
Guardian is now currently running
Republican
Presidential nominee
Converse on feet
Man really hard
That's disappointing
He just like mailed them the videos I never heard back
TV the next couple weeks ago and he's like well clearly Mater about me
This is definitely not
Talking to the TV
No
Hahaha
I am Darrell Slater did not run
Republic dependent for the
2004 election
Arabic part of that was sorta like they weren't far enough for Ralph Nader
It was an electoral strategy
Yeah I wasn't it wasn't so much that Alex Jones is
His video blew his mind that he left the Green Party
Oh man Ralph Nader
Leaving the green party because of
Fahrenheit 9/11
I think it's really fun the way that
Alex responded to that caller because there was a moment where he thought like
Oh you know Ralph Nader I need a really did like my dad
So disappointed
Oh man
Certain point
He's got to learn not to get his hopes
Yeah that's a terrible idea I don't take any of these colors seriously
11 * 99% of callers to most shows
Don't really have any information and 1%
They really are on it
800% of Infowars collars
Are going to lie to you about knowing whether or not the TV is speaking to
Interesting Lee 99% of Alex
Scholars have
Career in intelligence
So we talked to unreason 2003 episode about Alex
2 conspiracy about UNESCO wanted
Destroy the family and how that's bulshit
Doesn't work
We are
Yasso Alex's belief
In families
Systems
Being
Heteronormative and one man one woman
Right is not it
It's it it's not based on
Something that
Changeable
It's based on his belief that God genetically engineered
Humans to be that
Yes only system that works
And to do otherwise
Is an affront to God
Because God could not have thought ahead
And saw people not acting
The way you want
Right
Crazy so what you could do is you could I don't know
Statistics about two-parent households
Swear you know it's a woman in a woman or man in a man
And they would show obviously that you're four to five times more likely to be
You could find that that's not
Uppercase relative
Similarities
And household
And it wouldn't matter to Alex you could have any statistic you want because that's just
Statistic has nothing
Things to do with disproving
The god genetically made us
Statistic
It's
Can never really actually be had no but Alex will throw things in like
Four to five times more likely to end up in prison
If you don't have a man in the in the home
What am I to Matt
You know here's what's fun
Here's what's fun about the
Have you ever noticed how the answer ultimately will always be because God said
And yet somehow there are so many things that they also want to
To say on top of
But you know if your ultimate answer is cuz God said so
Why are you telling me that there are statistics
6 to back it out cuz you don't want to start with that cuz if you sound like a
Crazy religious zealot you got it right
Washington Post
Apparently has an article about how they're going to the Bible
Okay did you hear about that the Washington Post
Victor
Sure
Doing the Pharisees calling for the death of Christ
Oh wow
How to switch that around I assumed that the ban would be on the Ulta
The Passion of the Christ wouldn't actually come out until then
NextGear buttocks Point many advocacy groups like The able been given copies of the script
They were little bit
Concerned with the waves
This story was being tall
One thing Mel Gibson was taking a Greek
Review of artistic license
Seemingly I mostly anyways the painted Jews as being evil and bloodthirsty
Given Gibbs
Subscript Behavior I would
Say it's probably
Also I do
Realize this until I was checking in on the passions release date but they're actually making a sequel
That's due to be released next year
Wait
Yes it's 2022
Oh I was going to say I was like you can't breathe passion that Christ
I don't know it's the next sort of story within that
Millier
This is going to be a huge mess I think I considering that Jim Caviezel is that the play Jesus
In the years since the first one he's gone
Wheatley and saying and is now a big qanon guy
Risen beyond what even Jesus could have hoped
He's particularly big on promoting adrenochrome related conspiracies which of course are really just a modern-day rehashing of the
Blood libel
I do not look
Look forward to this movie coming out because whatever accusations that horrible
You can't imagine how
Amplified they're going to be
F******
While
Yes we are going to make
A movie
About the most
Famous Jew
Of all time
To make
Sure everyone hates
It's the Jews
I think there's even just a fundamentally offense
Something about like Jim Caviezel playing Jesus again
The fact that
But active promoter
Avanti's American Spirit theories
It seems
Yeah
I mean birthday but even then Mel Gibson was part of his
I'm sure he was part of his dad's church at this point in time and they were
Violently
Anti-Semitic
It's not like anti-Semitism has caused a problem in for his career
Yep
I'm not looking forward to the movie coming out
No good time
I also think that in 2000
Forward that movie came out we weren't
Nearly as
Crazy as a society as we are now right right all right
That could
Really do some
Public damage
Really hope not
Yeah I hope so I hope not too but
This is cool I mean we got to get
Deceive it children's
We need children killing the people who hate this movie
As I recall
I was in college at
The time
And my dad I was a religious studies professor
A third of the letter to the editor
To the local
Wallpaper About the Passion of the Christ.
I remember walking
On-campus one day in The Preacher Brother Jed
Who was like this campus preachers
Yeah
He I remember Waka
Walking by and hearing him yelling about my dad
That's hilarious that are really funny
There's like whoa
I think it's worthwhile getting angry over iMovie
Yeah yeah
Especially especially a movie that by your own book should be considered insanely blasphemy
I didn't
I didn't have enough awareness of
I'd like what campus preachers were kind of like at that point
And so I waited until he stopped yelling
And II went over like a you know that's my
My dad and I please just
Stop yelling. It about by my family and then
Who did a little bit of a Beat
And then he called me a seed of Satan
And started screaming
I want to love it
That's good stuff
Another call here
On this episode
First hour is just like hey
Supporting the troops
Me and got it
And this one guy
He is calling him to tell Alex
That he has had been pulled over a couple times
And this last time
The police wanted to search his
His car right and he said yeah sure go ahead
Alex says that too
But also turns out that they didn't
End up searching
Scar
When telling it it's very boring story
Don't know what
As part of a conspiracy New York
It's about squeezing us
3 * 1
I did and they said
Alexa
Coincidental
Yeah it's
Contract work
Okay
Good thinking
How do you get to be that Psychopathic like confident you know just like
Oh you know what that sounds to me like they're doing the regular old thing they do
Somebody gave the call down to harass
Sure
Bye
Natsu
Searching your car
I when they ask you to give them consent
Weird
Yeah yep
This is so stupid
Wow so you're white without saying your way I gave them consent to search my car and they didn't
I do I do think that there's something really toxic
About this interactive kind of interaction with his listeners
Use Alex as a credible
Conservative person
Story of Metallica's responsibility
A call came down and probably just trying to harass you for the foia request
I just think it's unhealthy people down a bad path
Yeah yeah that's it is like
You're calling in
You know
You could get two things
When you call in you know you
You can get one or the other
You can get
Confirmation
Or you can get
And
They're you know Alex is always for confirmation
Just at like
Hey I think they're I think the government out to get me and kill me and at the end my entire
And Alex could just be like
You know what I am going to conspiracy guy and guess what I can tell you this one time
You're totally fine
Totally safe
Person in the history of the world has no idea who you are
Play-Doh trailer
You're totally right
You're going to be murdered anytime go into the forest by myself
And the evidence of this is something that could easily be a quince
Absolutely
It's a Hallmark of this. Of time
For Alex on his show
He's that he
Is obsessed with the idea that nyoka
Conservatism
Has its roots in Strauss
Straussian thought
Right he talks about this article that headline is neoconservatives dance ostrowski in
Right like you talked about this
Is all the f***
Right
EXO discolor
Call Zack
Let's talk about Irving Chris
Right Bill crystals dad
One of the leading thinkers in the nyoka
Conservatism
World
A.m.
Listen carefully to this clip
Because I think this is clip
Clearly reveals
To people who don't know anything about what they're talking about but don't want to let the other one know
They do real
.
The most prolific
Neoconservative
Reserving
And when you
You are not alluding to Leo Strauss
No
Okay
You know anything about Leo Strauss
Familiar
If you want a really fun
For the weekend
Information
Political Theory
Because this
You're talking about
Trout
University of Chicago
That is a damning conversation
Wow Irvin Crystal a father bill kristol is one of the big figures in the oak
Conservatism
He's also someone who had straussian leanings earlier in his life
When people talk about Strauss their 100%
Across-the-board talkin about Leo Strauss
So Alex saying he's not
Is ridiculous
That is a clear indication that he knows the word straussian but he doesn't know what he's talking about
I
Assume
I assume Alex think
Neocon
Play the violin
Well I'm guessing that's it
Also straps did teach at the University of Chicago and he's very much associated with that school so this caller is off base
He's even talking
The confusion I think is based on the fact that there's also an economic philosophy
Be called The Chicago School of economic
Backspace on the work of people like Milton Friedman
This is a term that is used mostly
Describe economics
Professors at the University of Chicago which isn't necessarily related to the scholarship with Leo Strauss
Who taught political science at
The same universe
Because this collar and Alex don't really know what they're talking about it's impossible for them to disambiguation these terms
They're basically just talking at each other
And it's really
It's really strange
Did they really telling
Damning things
Are the collar saying
You're talking you're not talking about Leo Strauss
And Alex says no
He is
The fact that he doesn't know that
Write is a problem and then says do you know anything about Leo Strauss not enough
That's right
No no
Absolutely not
So much if he knows nothing about anything I comment on I know nothing about
So
It really is a fascinating glimpse
M2 how
Corley he grass
The basis of this subject
Jack's yeah he's big conspiracy
About the nyoka
Conservatives is that they're all secretly
Democrats and liberals based on this straussian ideology
Nope his basis for attacking nyoka
Conservatives
Is
Nothing
Here's a house built on sand
Essentially Whitney he's trying to
To talk about
Always
Interested when
Alex instinctively knows
He's in weird territory
For him you know like
More than willing to talk s***
For forever but if he gets something where he's like
I know
I'm supposed to know this
And I know I do
So I'm going to try and let you I'm going to try
Tease out what it is I'm supposed to know from you
And then I can
Compare it back
Back to you so you think I know what I was talking about from the
I can let you
Or I talked for a while I'll find something and accurate that you say Alachua to that invalidate your point
Family conversation
Yeah yeah there is also a dynamic as it play here
That is
Unique to whenever he's on the phone with
Somebody I think of the other pretty good
Radar
In terms of like if someone's going to be a problem
Like if they have information that could be a problem
And that is what you see there early
Is it color talks more it'll reveal
The depth to which I don't know any of this
And yeah that's just
That's good it's good Instinct on his bar
Quite well
Oh man
Alex just being like
I know some things but not enough to talk
Talk about it
Could not be more of
8 l
It could not mean
Anything
More
Yep then I have
Have no fur
So the Washington post about banning the Bible apparently that was really just an article
About Mel Gibson
The Christ being
Daisy you are but they're going to be in the Bible next you don't like that movie
You have to be in the Bible
And Alex's defensive that is an article that he read in the BBC
From a year before
British broadcast
Germany
And other
Anti-racism framework is being discussed by the EU in 2000
Listen to one guy named Lord Scott a pint of that
The framework would outlaw the Old Testament as well as the very
What I'm going to call Ava
Time
Series of Adventure novels Bagels
Somebody says there's something wrong with Tintin I have no idea what they're talking about
It's fun to just say that he didn't like German
Krowd
Yeah that's
The problem
2021 end all this
Still very much
The stuff happened
I mean it would be it would be interesting if
If somebody was like hey
Alright
We don't want any books
In schools
Or
Is that that
Promote genocide
And then you're like okay well
Canaan and they're like
What I mean the Bible
Of course
Man fathered in
So you eat you may notice
Vapes like the ATL is complaining
About
Mel Gibson and Passion of the Christ
And
You know all this
This is going to lead to
Obviously the outlaw
Christianity and so therefore
The ADL is coming after the vet Bible slippery slope
What is retinol
Okay
Gotham
You heard from the EU government 39
Women are manners
Wow
So yeah apparently
Women can't wear dresses
In TV shows
Plays in
And then stuff
This. This is why they're so good at obstructing Prague
It's because they don't even give a f*** if it's Act
Actually progress
If it's even like
Imaginary thing that someone might do
Cacophony of
Howling screams
Of whining is so loud
That you can't even be like
Gives a s*** about the
Well it's like
A lot of the petty Grievances and nonsense
But Alex brings up it does remind me of
Toll booth
Yeah I'm terrible Trivium
Milo move a pile of set a time
Basically Alex's
Does a lot of the time
Each grain of sand do you have to move over as a distraction that's not really
Based in any reality
But somehow you are expected to clear it up
Right and it's just a slow you down so you can't free rhyme and reason so if you want
If you want gun control you're going to have to
To start with proving to me that guns even
Exist
And that means that Steve pieczenik is the spelling bee
Alright Infowars
Okay Joel skousen
The horrible din
Okay okay was the conductor
Who would like makeup
The sunrise come up to my bracelet when you ask me for a name is the moment the name is gone forever
You know like if I had if I could have
Oh you know like the conductor 5-second
Then you asked me the name and I'll never remember Alex's Milo
Rodger stone is talk
Alex Willow
Cuz he's been on Infowars for so much longer
Longer in
Pass
I think the Trump years was your day of the UB covid stuff is me at the doldrums
No you are in the village
Fantastic the Galaxy's board
Probably true
Who was
This is going to bother me
Regretting this strongly
I short-circuited you was a cop who cares we got to go alright anyway there's no more clips
We've come to the end of this no wonder you were so willing to go on The Phantom Tollbooth Radford I don't like to talk about
The rest of the episode is just Alex
What's doing his news
The end of the show which is Justin reading
The same headlines he's already talked about
It's quite boring
So yeah I think
I think that also lets not
Levon sad that that
Fitbit anti smell
The idea that the ATL is going after the fire
How could they
How could the ATL go after a book that was written by
The ATL I mean not all Jews are exactly the same
Yeah and it's
It's the it's the conception of this like their fur
Pretending that there
A adverb
ABC organization
League
But what they're really about is crushing
In Christianity
Some some narrative routes
Tropes
We get to the end of this and you know there's not there's not like a
Kitano stuff that happens there's some interesting
Sing things
Trends that are important to point out things like the way Alex covers that Houston crime lab story is a disservice
List of the reality of
The story
It's important to understand the ways that Alex is actually
Actively
Doing
The opposite of help
In cases like that in terms of the news
He gives people a worse idea of what's going on then if they knew not
Right
And that sucks
Leaving them in a more manipulator bulb
Harry Potter is still going on Trevor still mad about that.
To be tracing if you thousand three
Is the Arnold Schwarzenegger gubernatorial run
I promise you I'll come up with a pond with a really likes
Specifics like
If Harry Potter is leading you to become a witch
What in Harry Potter is real and what's
It's not like are giants real are centaurs
Real like what what are we talking about believe the Giants are real because
What is true
Yeah he's written a couple of books
What else
I mean Nabi
Pixies are Pixies real house-elves houses
Will boy now we're getting into all the anti-semitic one
Jordan
But until then we are also on Twitter
We're fighting that go to bed Jordan Becca on Monday set
But until then
Neo
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work