Shred-it
I have great respect for knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
Giordano Giordano
Sure
What is your bright spot today
Today is a little bit like sort of on the cusp
On your recommendation I've watched
Some later season episodes
Of The Amazing Race
No
But I I I watch 1
That was the
Sri Lankan
Twin sisters
Survivor
Okay
But I guess the bright spot is like
I hate
He's contesting
Most of them kind of all suck
Poorly drawn characters most of them are like
You're playing up whatever the
Fuckyour supposed
Persons of every task
Have to be related to a monster truck show
Who won carrying tons of bamboo who this is like a monster truck tire go f*** yourself
There's a couple Seasons where you have like a father-and-son Duo kind of like that and they are f******
Straight up Cat's in the Cradle like level like you know I didn't get to spend as much time with him when he was young like that s***
You were just watching your like ok-58 crying the whole time I started the second
Season and there's a dad in some team and its
The dad had prostate cancer and then and then his son got testicular cancer
Is almost crying talking about watching his kids ghost
Generally speaking
Characters
Credibly
False
And
Acted poorly
But I
Enjoyable anyway that is like I really
Dislike these people
Get a kind of charge out of that maybe that's why people like reality TV
Is
All the challenges you know
How they they show up somewhere and they like you can go to this
1 or you can go to this one
They always make it seem like it's a Chase
Huge choice in
To go like sitting across the entire way but if you if you like every now and then you can get a glimpse
Then they're like right now
The camera pans
Turn left
Yeah I that is fun and I also
Be like
Sometimes
The things I have to choose between doing
Anyone who hasn't watched the show when they get to a thing called a roadblock
They will have a choice
It's of two different tasks they have to do one
Sometimes they're about as hard
As each other and
Sometimes one of them
Acquires
Another one is like
Eat a croissant
No I ran out again you'll see somebody at their build bill just have a
A couple of scenes and then the third one they're like
6 hours later you like cheese
F******
Yeah yeah
Choosing like The Simple Solution like watermelon
Pyramid do is f****** hard
And now the Sun is setting
If you're getting a divorce
Okay balance is bottle on your head or find the Earth
Mantle okay fine okay
It's a dumb show I hate it
Guided anyway what you write about
Lite-Brite Spider-Man is I went to Whiskey Fest
My partner and I went to Whiskey
A couple years ago my partners
Bought us tickets
Kind of the one of the things that we really have in common
Dial
AIDS
Exact
So we were going to go is going to be a whole bonding experience we're going to do the whole thing you know there was a
The thing
Years go by
Whiskey Fest
Cancel that was the main thing that happened
Gbd
So we were going to go but then she's she's Abby elderly persuasion so she had a bit of an illness she couldn't
Makeup
And you couldn't make it and she was supposed to be getting a tattoo
Going to go alone that would have been really weird plumber
It would have been a million times Saturday than I could have imagined luckily my partners
Tattoo felt
And I it was not what I was
Expecting okay
I thought it
It was going to be like a tasting thing with everybody tiny bits
It was
You you did text little tiny bit
It was more of like a
Car show
Lego people with their weighers yeah yeah like Jack Daniels had a big ol thing in there
You know it was it was very strange it was not what I was expecting and we stayed there
Literally what I was expecting when you said Whiskey sauce
I just don't think you hurt you so you pitched
To me is something that is like high-end
Classy you got to wear a suit
Happened I think what happened is it was going to be that
I doubt it okay well let's just
Make it
I doubt it could babe
It was never that class so weird because I did not sell or destroy
Tribute sky
Bourbon or any types of whiskey
I'm just there and they're like okay
Next we have a seminar my one
You don't have a seminar was full of booze
A seminar on
There's a really great peanut butter whiskey
I'm sure I had that like a year or two ago I was good it was
I was with somebody who is like a
Bit of a snob too and they're like
This is fantastic
Yeah it was time I also got it with the health Ranger let me use in town
Yeah it was fantastic and the lady to
Was like okay
Going to pour some cranberry juice
Right on
Wonderful
Not bright spot
As promised we will be looking at to the old
Richarlison documentary Patriot Purge
Alex Jones claims he did the background work on and probably is going to take credit for course
I wrote the whole thing
Tucker's actually me
Eye Prosthetics we did a Faceoff kind of thing interests
Except the Face-Off
Anyway
This
This documentary sucks did the Patriots win
I don't know what that would mean
Well I mean were they perch
No but it would
Doesn't look great by the end of the document
Yes
Gotcha
Julio Alexander's hand was cut off
Got it
So I will get all the Myriad ways
It's terrible
Let's take a little
The first librarian mobile
I'm a policy wonk librarian
Blippi library in Mobile
Hypermobile a man
Will be back
But until then we have a website thank you so much and I'll probably want
Google
Bestway food canes
Next
Donkey also
Donkey donkey and I just want to say happy belated birthday I missed a message alright
That was just last month
Anthony
Like to say hello and I'm not a big fan of narcissistic
Technocrat
Money off at heroin
Is freakishly large
Thank you so much I think Mingus actually was the one who originated paranoid narcissist
Charlie Mingus
I like the complete randomness of you pulling Fats Waller
Can I tell you why I know that
Sew in
What would it have been
Middle School I think
I was in the act
Club or acting class or whatever and we did a musical called we Haz jazz
Enough people to play all of the roles are
Who was the main kid who like was super into jazz
The play a jazz musician
Another part in the
The play and I was Fats Waller
I I can't I'm sorry but I cannot imagine
Any story of you like
Before
You know 8th grade where you don't
Still have the exact same voice you do right now
Like eight years old year you've got a deep solder as a baby I came up I came out of the womb
Baritone
Yeah I don't know I also look back at my my younger years and I project
My voice and appeared on to my younger self
Jordan we're talking here about this
Patriot Purge
And it's very
Closely related to a lot of Alex Jones
Stop syrup
It doesn't it feels in the ballpark in
I texted you about this
I think that there is
A shocking overlap
Some really
Particularly important difference
I mean the kind of
Stop the Tucker is putting out here
Hannah stuff that Alex
Put that routinely and I hope that is something that we can explore its
Think about as we go through the
This contact
The first important thing that I want to point out and I think it's really important to understand about this series of documentaries
Is it they're designed to be just as much of a marketing campaign as they are an exploration of the events
January 6th
They were very specifically aired only on Fox Nation
Fox News online streaming platform that requires a
Access
Platform allows Fox to disseminate some of the more f***** up content they would like to are normally
Stuff it might attract a little bit too much
If it was on broadcast television
For instance there currently on season 8
8 of a show called The firman Diary
Detective Mark Fuhrman discusses important criminal cases
Also the Fuhrman Diaries shouldn't be confused with the fermentate
Which were 13 hours of recorded interviews where Furman said all sorts
The racist shiting an active participant in racist police and Pratt
That's why you gave him an online
From the transcript
I'd like to point out that is a hard r
Boat driving a Porsche that doesn't look like he's got a $300 suit on you always stop him
Another excerpt
First thing anything out of an endsmouth for the first five or six sentences is a f****** lie
I mean you know that's a little arbitrary
Sure what about this
Is a discussion of how he treated as suspected gang member
We basically tortured
The four policemen four guys we broke up
Their faces were just
Mush pictures of the walls of blood all the way up to
To the ceiling and finger marks
So trying to crawl out of the room
Great they're great where they came from but the point is
Giant pile of s*** as a person
His expertise of the cop is also worth
Fox Nation has made eight seasons of a show where you presented as a credible
Expert and the host
Wow
Just terrible
Fellow piece of s*** to Nancy Grace has a show on the network along with your good buddy Robert Jeffress
Boring ass Fox News style contest
According to an article in Forbes
In June 2020 the Fox Nation
Between your two hundred thousand subscribers somewhere in that range
No
Which is not super great numbers
Then in February 2021 it was announced
The Tucker Carlson it signed a deal to create Fox Nation
Exclusive content
That's including his truck show.
Richarlison today
Images allegedly in-depth investigations called Tucker Carlson
Say what you want about this guy but he's incredibly good at making sure his name is front-and-center on every project
Betty does
Crossfire was really just about the Bowtie but now that he's a man every project
Is Tucker Carlson
Send something or it doesn't get made
Unless the Project's get that man
Contract to do the next Madea you know like that's what we got to do. Tyler Perry just put his name on everything
Exactly
Perry Madea
Was Tucker Carlson present threat
Attraction
Tucker Carlson today
Desperate
Everyone expect by may there's
Script numbers are gone up 40%
Tucker Carlson
And started making
Exclusive content
Tucker Carlson is the marketable franchise player that talks
His shows are really essential to attracting viewers to the Fox Nation
Platform
Where did Mendelssohn be drawn toward programs like hearing Mark Fuhrman's dump takes over
You could watch geraldo's a reboot of
Cops
Anyway this is an important Dynamic to understand when you begin approaching
A topic like covering this documentary Patriot perch
At least some element of this presentation is meant to attract backlash
Which will in turn increase
Subscriber count
Apps for Fox Nation
This isn't to say that nothing in the documentary series is sincere
Just important
Recognize that
Some of the marketing and branding surrounding it was intentionally Sensational for the sake
Driving traffic
I am selling some
With that caveat out of the way we can begin to touch on the meat of this show
I watch the series a few times
The argument is this
As best as I can
Intel
I need to clarify that the messaging of these
Three episodes is a little bit out of
I was thinking there's a couple of points where logic
Turtle eating
Consistent
There is essentially an overarching
Sing conspiracy that's being
A group of folks who aren't specified maybe the Deep State maybe the globalist
Maybe the permanent
Government
About mischaracterizing the things that happened on January 6th in order to present
Conservative
Christians as terrorists because they want to use the national
Security apparatus
And the Patriot Act
That's the right way
People have tried to denigrate Tucker by saying he's going full in
Infowars
Exactly how right
Right they are
This documentary is a Slicker but less gel-filled presentation
Conspiracies that Alex has been pushing for like
Like 20 years
The real substantive differences that I can identify is that in Alex's version of the story passing the Patriot Act was
Who were the reason
Eventually using it against
People where is in Tucker's telling
It's kind of just a happy accident for the back
That I mean good for
Sure the globalist protector break finally
Pictures of did not have to worry about one aspect of the plan for what
Alex
Lowe's
Tucker and
Documentary
But if I were Alex watching this IB
Terrified
I'm feeling about as obsolete as
Woody
In Toy Story 3
If I were him I would also realize that it
100% time to innovate
As far as Thompson said when the going gets weird the weird turn pro
And there is no-one weirder than Alex Jones
If he wants have any chance of retaining the mantle
King of the Fall
F***** up right-wing mount
He's going to have to take some kind of a big narrative risk
You know because he's got to stop
Beating his own path
Through the woods
Easy use
But yeah
He's going to be left in the dust
Better funded and less
Clearly insane demagogues yeah apparently can push the same sort of s*** that he does
What does he want to be like someone who's
Just riding along
Find Tucker ride
F****** ego the size of pics
Coronavirus
If you never believe we're here
Successful he would lead to his own
That's that's barely
Regular piano
At the very beginning if he's so far out there and he
He succeeds enough
To drag everyone to have then
They're going to be better people
We sucks I kind of look at this and I feel like it may play out
Is that
Right now Alex and Tucker are in an uneasy tag team in the wrestling world
Another there their tag team of people who Maybe
Haven't gotten along in the past or whatever but they're really just a tag team until they inevitably break up in 5
Sooner or later
Tucker's going to hit
Alex with the chair
That would be the blow off today
I guess probably
McDonald's
I wish Alex all the worst
With whatever is coming
As for me I don't really difficult time trying
To figure out how to cover this ship
I think over the course of this you'll see like I said so there's some
Real similarities
The presentation has to Alex's work
But also some really important if
It was my sincere intention to cover all three parts of the series but I think you'll see why it would just be impossible without me
Bring my laptop out the window
I did watch
The series in its entirety if you times but today we're just talkin about the
The first episode which is
Densely-packed
With complete bulshit
Auto next episode to cover bit about how Alex
Just talked about the release of the documentaries which is kind of like
I don't know
A less fun version of my Caravan
Body project
I'll try to come up with a good pun for the name of the series but all I could come up with his Danza sucker for Tucker
Ditto massage to the great 1999 album by kurupt
The streets is a mother Tucker
Going to go with how about
Patriot dirt
My bad I was kind of trying to
Trying to make a Tucker Pawn
Yeah
I was just trying to Pawn off the the general vibe there I don't know how to make it
Other than like
I can't not
So let's so let's start off here at the
Beginning of the documentary where
The theme
The premise
And playing a bunch of clips
Better
In support
Of his
Narrative
In the Years After
Media
And the Nationals
Security State between
Al-Qaeda and Saddam when he talked about the war on terror
Exaggerated
Traps
Deception
Between Al-Qaeda
And Saddam
There are other
We know they have
Associates
Events 9/11 is Saddam Hussein's weapons of mass destruction
So the argument that opens the first episode is almost staggering in
Presentation
Sevilla basically like an SAT kind of formulation we're lying about weapons
Sons of mass destruction after 9/11 is do the Iraq War as blaming whites
Supremacist for January 6th is to the coming Purge
Of all white Chris
Conservatives
From site was all about the war in Iraq
Starting
An idiot to me how he conveniently ignores that he was
Is the people he's talking about
He's a ghost people who push the b******* in Annapolis
Turned against it eventually but we'll talk about that later
Anyway he seems to forget his own past
The bunch that's a very
Consistent pattern
Call to forget your own past whenever you are exactly the thing that you are telling people to Jesus or is
Before we go any further I want to take a moment.
Discuss
People in the crew
In this documentary
Behind the scenes
You check out a little bit of this
You might end up seeing if something is rotten
In the state of Denmark
Credited writers of this film
Or Tucker
And a guy named scooter Downey
Scooter is a filmmaker who directed Lauren
Southern's latest offering
Called Crossfire
Here's the problem here's the problem
Problem number one
You can't have it like
Here's Hitler's minister of propaganda
Scooter
Scary games
Studer here's the leader of the SS
Weebly
Evil if your name
Scooter
Lauren Southern's latest movie called Crossfire
This was a course the follow-up to her
Completely full of s*** film
Farm lands in borderless so anyone who would work with her after that point
Automatically is suspect in my book
Scooter was also the director of a film called hoax
This was an attempt to make a documentary about how the media is all fake news and they lie to claim the people like
Alex Jones Mike cernovich James
Keith Gavin
McGinnis Lauren Southern
Stefan molyneux are liars make the light to make them look like liars
Proven by interviews with Alex Jones Mike cernovich James O'Keefe Gavin McInnes Lauren Southern
Stefan molyneux I kind of think
They might have I think they might have a conflict of interest as far as
Developing
Scooters work
The rest of the crew is mostly Tucker his team from Tucker
Open tonight in Fox producers
But this scooter character being the only other credited writer on this project
Pretty interesting Staffing decision and by interesting I mean transparent
Yeah it doesn't get that
Yep this is the problem
Now now that we're going from a CNN piece to this
I'm sitting here like
Why isn't
Tucker cigs
September 11th we were listening to Jay-Z
And now they're starting World War 3 like I can't not do it
It's got to be there may have to stop at scooters
Get on this
I don't like your rhyming please don't do that anymore
Beer
This is going to take forever
You'll be here for a week
So Tucker is talking about how they're trying to make you afraid of
The white Army the white
White Terror Army that's behind all of the stuff like you're saying
Need to make me afraid
The very same
Kurupt intro
Is the most
Regal threat
So I don't know if it's
It's Colin Powell who's
I don't know if it's the people who are pushing their rack what is Condoleezza Rice
Behind trying to make us afraid of January 6th
I don't know if
So I don't think anyone is saying if there's a white Terror Army that's just sucker
For creating a ludicrous strawman to argue again
Really doesn't have a leg to stand on again
Ansari Larkin
Which is a bunch of violent white supremacist and white nationalist groups either ideological
Quote Trump
Really won the 2020 election
Campaign or who recognized that that's a really fertile recruiting pool for them to
None of us are allowed in Wyoming
If we are so upset about this
These corrupt people who got us into the Iraq War
Considering these supported
Promoted
Centre branded as an intervention by populist so you know who plays up this anti-war credibility but it's not
That's for reasons it will get it
Ventilator
It's just super weird
Like I said earlier
Tucker insist on calling up he's corrupt
Delete from the Iraq War era but
Forget what he did
Child with Millions upon millions of dollars
Who supported the Iraq War
And you can't trust these wealthy Elites who supported the Iraq War
Also that clip that played of biting the end there is absolutely
Play correct
An analysis compiled by the center for strategic and International Studies reviewed 893 incidents
Definition of damask
Terrorism in the United
January 1994 and May 8th
2020 900 webcam where whites
Their number showed that one
The vast majority of terrorist attacks
Simplot Sunday night
What states were committed by group
Defined by a right-wing ideology
In the six years leading up to 2020
Proportion of attack
Text carried out by right-wing groups has
With almost two
Two-thirds of the attacks
2019 being done by right-wing groups
And over 90% of the period between January and May 8th
Right-wing groups are responsible for a greater percentage of terrorism than any other type
Group for almost every year on the chart
With the exception of a few years in the early 2000
After 9/11
And left-wing groups
Like the animal Liberation Front and the Earth liberation
Confront carried out targeted attacks
Against the property
Play can take proportionality because
Paper gets chilled out
Accepted terror attack
Further these researchers found that religiously-motivated terrorism has killed the most
People in that time. But that's only because of 911
However if you look at the data more granularly you'll find that right-wing terrorism is a way bourquin
Threat
In 14 of the 21 years but
Between 1994 and 2019
In which
Attacks occurred
The majority of deaths resulted from right wing attack
In eight of these years right-wing attackers caused
All of the fatalities and
3 more
Including 28
18 and 2019
They were responsible for more than 90% of annual fatalities
So sure it's
Absurd to try and pretend that there's a white Terror Army that poses a threat to us in the United States
It's mostly because the right-wing has some experience of the terrorism game
And they have four
Decades follow the Louis beam leaderless resistance model
Y'all be like somebody's got to stop that white Terror Army but now we're all like
We can't stop them
They're Oliver
Kind of know
They kind of know that if there was
Harambe would not work
It's almost like
Because they pay
I had so much cover from people like Tucker
Dawson 400 years or so
Figured out how to get away with all the
I love this shitt
Well
Still be operating within a certain plausible deniability
Sure
A lot of this documentary is just based on Tucker ass
Asking loaded
Good questions
Is that alright
Supposed to
Give you a knife
Children dead
January 6th is being used as a preacher
Strip
Millions of Mara
Exactly
How much are
Darren Beattie
Revolver news is one of the
You in me
Actually
What are the few
What's constitute real reporting real
Definition of tariff
There's so much of this like
How much is it was alive
Why would you make
Why would you make a battery
The end result of it is like hey you know what
Media got it right
Little bit but not much we never got
So he has this guy Darren Beattie
Who's the head of revolver news
If you'd like
Legit offended me
On this thing
Greedy is a great minister of propaganda named scooter Nobita must do the video
You much for me I can't handle that was probably about the first point where I almost
Just said f****** okay
Darren Beattie
Bernews is one of the
Supporting
What actually
The establishment
The worst single-a
Vertical violence
Civil War Donald Trump supporters
Killing police officer
Maga
Bloodline
Officer Brian sicnic died after being hit in the head
They beat
Capitol Police office
The fire extinguisher
Fight
Age of 42
The fire extinguisher
Fire extinguisher
Problem with this
The New York Times has quietly retracted its story
About the death
The capitol police officer Brian
There is nothing
Which are involved at all
And the paper is backpack
Possible
It was never
Pinhead at all
First thing that I want to point out this is very very important
Is the Darren is
Way out of line referring to shoddy reporting that was later retracted and corrected
With blood
If you want to say that the media was
Was eager to blame officer sickness death on the Trump supporters at the Capitol
Be my gas
Use the term Maga blood libel is a disgrace
And honestly that is a
Disqualifying ComEd
I can't I
It's awful
The blood libel is an Insidious false accusation
Pittsfield Generations event
Peace Medical
Conspiracy theories
Who played the countless deaths
Untold suffering
The Coop that turn to exaggerate Trump supporters oppression
Wheatley unaccepted
Especially considering
Percentage of the people
Apple January 6th rally
Qanon followers
Who believed the police kidnap children
Torture them and drink their blood to get high on adrenochrome witch
Just basically nothing more than a modern-day version of the blood libel
F*** this dude
Right off the bat
It is
It is a
Time-honored
And effective
Wait for them to kind of neutralize so much
Horrific
Fix it by just claiming that
No it's happening
And using those terms to the point where it lowers their
Affect
In elf
Darren baby is the news editor for revolver a headline aggregator that's clearly looking to
To become the Drudge Report for the modern unhinged right-wing news can
Consumer
Alex routinely grabs headlines when they're to yell about networks like Tucker's
In the business APUSH
This guy too
He was formerly a
Trump speech writer
Forget this
He lost that position in 2018 because he was too closely associated with white nationalist
You know how much of a bigot you have to be to get thrown out of the
The Trump Administration
Like Steven Miller stay the whole time
The whole time
Hold on
Giving a speech at the 2016 meeting of the
BHL make
Can club which is basically just a group of high-minded intellectual race
Sister Nazi
In a 2013 article in the Village Voice splc researcher Mark potok describe them this way
They're essentially advocating for a country which is either completely inhabited by whites or Dominic
Hated by whites
They are inside
Lactaid Kinder gentler Clan
To give you some idea of the
The ilk that hang out there
Spencer was one of their board my
So baby got fired from the Trump Administration for being too closely associated with explicitly races
Spoke and then transitioned into
To being the racist media is new favorite link aggregator
According to Tucker one of the
A few journalists who's actually doing reporting on January
This is nonsense
And to allow someone like Beatty to call something
The Maga blood libel without dealing with his
Very unsavory past in the fact
Sizable amount of stalkers audience
Believe
Actual blood libel
Is astonishingly bad stuff
Block this
As for the issue with offers their sick Nick there definitely was some bad report
Going down on that front
I can't I can't
Dispute that my cat argue with it
But I would really like to see taco or Beatty try to make a coherent argument that this reporting wasn't done
In good faith
With the information that was available
When new information came to light these Outlets made Corrections
Retraction
Even this
Steven B documentaries side
They claimed that they were
Quietly retracting
Yeah I don't know what I don't know how you qualify the
Volume of a retraction but put it in their paper
Quietly
Officer sicnic didn't die until January
And most of the media that covered
The story about a press release put out by the United States
Capitol Police
Department
From that press release
Officer 6
Nick was responding to the riots on Wednesday January 6th 2021 at the US Capitol
Was injured while physic
We engaging with Proto
He returned to his Division office and collapse
He was taken to a local
Hospital where he succumbed to his injuries
The release goes on to say quote
The death of officer sicnic will be investigated by the Metropolitan Police Department's homicide brain
This press release wood
Very strongly lead one to believe that sickness
Kids suffered injuries in the line of duty at
The capital
I thought you died upon returning to the office
From said injuries
They literally say in the press release that it's being investigated by the homicide branch
I'm so it would be pretty reasonable
Take from that.
The Capitol Police Department were suspecting that this was a murder
And that was the information they were releasing to the public at that
On January 8th the New York Times reported that
Picnic it been hit in the head with a fire
This reporting was based on two Anonymous sources with inline 4
But by February 6th
Keep the times had done further examination and
Updated their articles
To reflect that this might
Not be accurate a
Information that have been supplied to them by their sources
They did that
Because they're good Journeys Catholic
All this was done well before the DC medical examiner release sickness cause of death
Did die of natural causes after having a
Stroke
By April the Associated Press was widely reporting that even though there was an issue
Chatter that
There wasn't any evidence that any of it lead
To his death
Tokaido
No
I don't know where you're going to point
Probably the cops
Sure
They were given by the cops Tucker documentary about the cops giving the media in
Inaccurate
I also think that
You know I
I don't
Necessarily know in this case
How much you
You could prove that
The police gave bad information
It may have been good faith on their part which again is the point
Not sure doing any investigation into anything that is actually the root
Or fundamental
Surface-level b*******
People like Tucker and bd1 apresenta world where the mainstream media just makes up these stories out of thin air then reports them
Push their political agenda that's what people like Alex
So most of the rate with media does
However the reality is much more
There been an outburst of violence at the Capitol we're sick
Nick was on duty
Shortly after returning from
His brother has confirmed that
Picnic and told him that he was pepper-sprayed twice
Apparently he collapse
In the capital and they resuscitated him using CPR
The Capitol Police put out a press release that
He died of injuries that occurred on duty
Two law enforcement sources have provided information that was later determined
To be not good
But no one knew that at the
Time
It's complex how these things work and people like Tucker and Beatty want to simplify all that in
Easily digestible narratives or the media wanted to make Trump supporters look bad
So they made up
Conclusion about officers
Text app
If they wanted to have a real conversation it would be about how the media particularly the 24-hour news channels need to be a little more
Careful do not engage with the news that their report again
How it might be wise to try and maintain a little bit of journalistic distance from the subject that they're covering
If I was the only
We complained these dudes were making then
Can still f*** himself for the blood libel thing
But that also
Sections of the media have some room for improvement so let's move
Do a post-mortem on
The things
You could you got wrong that you could have done better on
Fine but don't
F****** pretended
It's this black-and-white nonsense
But and I'm going to throw this out at
Cuz I think this might be what
Really important
Which way is going to make you the most
Okay well then that's the way they're going to
Really shocked me here
Is it Darren Beattie didn't just call this Maga blood libel once
He said it twice in a matter of minutes
Clearly felt like an attempt
To enter a catchphrase
There is no no such they there is no fire
Which are involved at all
The paper is backpack
Admitting that it's
Possible
It was never even had it all
New York Times
Attracted
Story
They move to a different
Haters
Spring
Bear spray into the face
Of officer
Brian six
It was bear spray
Set killed off
Revolver news
The video shows
No spray
The container
Sure enough
Eventually
Immediate Med
Right
DC medical examiner
Capitol Hill Police
Bryan Singer
Died of
Officers
Nick died of natural
What causes
Did not die
And yet
Reporting that
Deadly mop
The murderous mob
Mob deadly January 6th attack
Trump supporter
Weird deadly
Is a blood libel
Okay
So it's fair that the media Outlets like a time-saver tractor article
Included this information but
What to do when they go
Get things wrong it's actually a good sign
The sign of a
Journalistic Outlet
Media that they said
Lies all the time they use a clip of them saying that Brian
Technique
Was
Correcting themselves remember how the media they say is lying to you
Also came out and said the thing that is not a lot
Track here is that he's trying to argue then taking credit for winning a
A completely separate
The determination did come down the sickness
Did not die as a result of injuries suffered on January 6th
Wasn't attacked
Cyclic told his brother that he was pepper sprayed multiple times passed out and had to be resuscitated with CPR
Experience may not have contributed to his death but he was the subject of considerable violence that day
I don't know what point you use Missouri winning other than
Cuz I was defiant
Just disagreed with
What people were saying and I ended up brand
Emily being right I mean they're trying to pin
Deadly mob as
Only being based on Brian six
As opposed to that
A lot of people died that day
So yeah that's that's the next point you can see here's the idea
To push that the coverage of the event
Is a Maga blood libel because it was based solely on the idea that
Sicnic it been
But like you
You bring up even that's bow
Bulshit
What may play the clips of the broadcasters calling the Bob
Murderous that's
Kind of Acura
The term murderous doesn't
Require that someone is
Committed murder just what they're capable other Dorsey
Seem to be intend
To murder
And I would say that a group of folks
Saint januarius
Qualify for that even if you just base it on the whole thing where they were chanting
Mike Pence that one is definitely murderous I would say just via
Existence of a regular old person holding
Plastic f***
Zip tie cuffs
Bats of murderous
Best thing to do I don't know
Never seen those specific cups
Used without like an intent to harm seriously I don't know
The mob was also absolutely dead
Kevin greeson died of a heart attack
His wife told reporters that he suffered from high blood pressure and well I have no solid evidence
The basement song
The excitement and stress of the unfolding Riot could have easily raised
Is heart rate and blood pressure
And the same could be said for another person who died
Ben Phillips
Initially it was believed that Roseanne Boyland was
Trampled to death by a bunch of people who are trying to storm the building
Her friend who was there told reporters that was how she died because he was there and watched
Trampoline
When the medical examiner's report came back and turned out that she had actually died of accidental acute amphetamine intox
Application
Ethan Ethan
Instances are fairly loose in terms of where you might want to sign real response
Sensibility about the deaths put
It was a very deadly mob
Honestly the only reason there were more deaths
Probably dumb luck
Coincidence
Yeah I mean
Maybe you'd like the
The simplest thing that is
So already in
Infuriating about this
Is the idea that we are
Taking this all the way down to individual a
Doctors at January 6th
People
Set up all of the circumstance
Necessary
Brought all of those people there
You know right well that's because
That requires a mirror
You got it
Immediate needs
Mixmaster called the event of January
Deadly
That's a false premise that's being put forward by Darren Beatty and Tucker in order to help them brand that reporting
Anyway that's deeply offensive and
Probably really popular with folks he hangs out with that the HL Mencken Club
Yeah probably love that s*** hand they have
To get together and laugh
Evilly
Whenever they use stuff whenever they use blood libel to apply to
F******
Cackling ghetto like an evil witches in a f****** that's cartoonish levels of evil
It's gross
So
There's this
Idea that there
Kind of floating
Makes death
And they're reporting around it and The Branding of everybody as
Murderous deadly bloody people
That's the whole reason
The people were taking the event
Of the six
Seriously before getting arrested otherwise we should hang on some nonsense
Innocent tourists just looking to find a little
Memento from the Capitol building
Just as not exist
Mass destruction
F*** you
Folk music
Ali Alexander
After 9/11
I spent my early adult
Growing up in a
Post 9/11
Fun World with an Arab name
It's open season on hate towards Muslims and Islam
At one point in 2012
Had to have a member of Congress
Dfbguide get me removed
From a
Watchlist
And now
In this
Post one
I'm on a list
Yet again
Because I've been deemed
A minority
So this is a really smart game with Tucker is playing
You can easily demonstrate that there was an accurate early reporting about officer sickness
Cause of death
Be as big a deal as possible and
Explanatory for everything
Possibly make it
Explanatory for
That's why the game here is that the inaccurate reporting about sicnic is the reason that the folks
Enforcement made it a priority to go after people involved in the Rye
I can say with absolute confidence that if sicnic were alive today literally everything would have played out the same
Just without the early inaccurate report
The government doesn't need a cop dying to take the storming of the US
Capital very seriously
That's childish bulshit
Yeah you have to be real dumb to believe this dumb s*** you have to be so
F****** stupid to believe this
Speaking of childish bullshitters Tucker's next expert on the documentary is former regular Alex Jones gas tank
Complete lunatic and felon Ali Alexander
We covered this on a past episode but just
Ricky's anyone
Hear that before he got involved
Republican politics
Ali Akbar as he was then known got arrested
4 quotes
Stealing several items
Fort Worth woman and later quote he broke into a van stole the debit card and attempt
Did you use it
He pled guilty debit card fraud and had to repay what he stole it got four years probation
Everybody got involved in the McCain campaign at the local level in Dallas-Fort Worth
I got some hot water there after he was accused of quote
Endorsing voter fraud tact
Alright seems a little familiar
We talked a ton about Allie and how he's a Christian salad on a level that even
Kind of doors
Alex himself
He's a complete lunatic
And he was deeply involved
Stop the steel campaign
Itself grew out of the voter intimidation campaign that Rodger Stone
Started for the 2016 election
Also called stop this
Trump won that election know so they didn't
End up having to do much stuff that anyone would remember in that
You know why this didn't happen next
I don't want to rehash too much but Ally himself because honestly he's
They're kind of pathetic but
Very accomplished
Scam artist
Only really need to know about it
Like just to get us answers
Caliber
Is that he was the third wheel on Laura Loomer and Jacob wolves documentary where they went to Minnesota.
Try and prove that a lot Omar was married to her brother
You do got to give him some credit for going straight
From debit card fraud to stealing election
Tough to do a little bit of
The transitional period to it some other other scams
Allegedly
What I do find interesting here is how Tucker is using alley to express this feeling of being singled out in Moline because he
We had an Arab name
Is Tucker recognized
But his professional activities director
Contributed to the difficulty Ali had
In those years
Tucker was Pro Iraq war and then decided it was a bad idea to
Conveyed
However he didn't think it was a bad idea because war is a bad idea
In a 2008 recording of an appearance he made on the radio show hosted by Bubba the Love Sponge
Tucker said quote
Iraq is a crappy place filled with a bunch of you know semi-literate primitive monkeys
That's why it wasn't worth invading
It wasn't an opposition to war that turned Tucker against the Iraq war is a Feeling
The people of Iraq were less than human which is
Definitely part of the mentality that led folks
To look at all Muslims
InFocus Arabic sounding names
Suspicious unless
Inhuman
Another clip from 2,000
6 included
Tucker talking about how is a Democratic candidate in the 2008 election came out and promise to
To kill as many quote
Lunatic Muslims as they could
They would quotes
King and the Tucker would vote for the
This hypothetical
Candidate would need to have the right kind of message
Quote I think you mean to say look
I'm a bigot okay I'm a bigot I don't like it
Islamic extremists
Like if you're really heavily into Islam I really I'm sorry I just don't I don't care for you that much
And I don't care what that sounds
Like you can call me a racist you can call me whatever the
F*** you want
Tuckerman Auto money of being a part of the problem that Alexander is now on a Tucker Carlson documentary complaining about
But the blame is
Solely on other people these people just a f****** pack a loser
It's nonsense
Yeah
See why I hate this s*** easy to be good
Stuff
These guys
Would not be right-wing loon
Text right it's
Zoe
Easy
To do this s***
Yeah the bar the bar of Entry is not high to do good work you don't go anywhere near
You kind of
I think generally have a scent
That doing so will impede your ability to do good work later
You might reach some really high heights but you also probably going to go to jail
Tucker Carlson
I mean
Look he can't be happy with this Cami like Siri
You gets great ratings
AMC
Gets people
To be mad at him
He makes a lot of money
But
I don't know it
It seems like a boring in life
Why why
You do it just being a psychopath for
But you know you don't even have fun
Ali is a huge liar and I gave him
Imply
Bastille what's the most law-abiding movement
That this country has seen in modern
None of the stop
He'll rally
Police report
I think that's why we had
Conspiracy
So that last one was a crystal ball one of the House of rising on the Hilti
TV
Avis Clippers play to somehow meant to imply that she was supportive of stop Bastille efforts that Ali was engaging in or that in
Larger picture there was stealing in the election
She actually said about alley in.
Bastille
I could have made this radar
Because of that
Additional reporting
Gonzales
About how much of
The money in the hole
Stop this.
Amount of it
Ashley went to any
Sort of like
Legal efforts are Alexa
Obviously I think
Election fraud
Oh okay
So okay
So is she
Man I'm guessing that you would
Like to be used that is this documentary
That is
It's just on
I don't appreciate it
Let's glow lovable
Play kicking a leaf eligible owed
Clip of hers
Those are from two different broadcast for crystal balls
Clear light come on
That's just cruel very specific examples
I just liked it I was able to very easily find a clip of her literally saying stop
Steelers bowls
Anyway d-clip Tucker is playing to reinforce this idea that Ali Alexander
Stop a steel shed had bipartisan
Computers from Crystal Ball talking about the Democratic Party
Handling
I'll be Iowa caucus
There absolutely was no by party
Some support.
Castillo ladany meaningful way
Also about that whole thing about no police reports being filed it stopped
Does the O'Reilly's
What about that one in December 2020 were four people were stabbed and quote at least 33 people were arrested
There was a woman arrest
Super result today November 2020 stop the steel rally in the Idaho at the Idaho State Capitol
A man was arrested for tearing a woman's mask off at a November 2020 stop Bastille rally in Pensacola
That assault was actually caught on tape and went around social media so Allie should probably know that people are aware of that one
4 people arrested one of them for spraying Mason the face of a legal Observer from the national lawyers Guild
At 8 November 2020 stop at the O'Reilly in Salem Oregon
We could go on I'm sure there are more but I think
The point is clear
There's been plenty of police reports in arrested
Ixtapa steel rally
Saying that their work because it makes him feel better
That's the case and as an added bonus
It allows him to continue his woe-is-me act
Steph is all bunch
F****** horseshit
I I do
Love
I do love
The unironically use
Of a crowd
Chanting Christ
Is king that's a way to
To prove that they're non-violent
Right like historically
A large group of white people chanting Christ
Texas King leads to black people dying
Every time
Not just about the Crusades
Absolutely
In Latin
So I
Fix-It one of the point
I will I will build my house
Liar
Here's Appliance
I will coordinate the US Capitol Police nearly every day a lot of
People don't know that. If you actually had a permit
Capital Plaza
Grounds latte we had
Permit
20 to 50,000 people inside the president's Park sitting there at the very front I'm dead center
The president
Route
A trump campaign staffer walked
Me and says only there are people leaving the over
And they're already 10,000
People at the US Capitol with your presence
And the present of Alex Jones
Why don't you guys walk down Pennsylvania gather people together
Positioning for your Valley on W 8th
Our boy got a little bit of a cameo
Stop the steel didn't have a permit for the use of area 8 of the Capitol grounds on January 6th
An event called what
Nation under God
Have been granted a permit to have a rally with
50 or less at MBS
On area at
That day they had a permit it was all totally legal this permit was
Thought almost certainly because Ali knew fully well that he would never be able to get a permit himself
Stop the steel rally
Never be approved
Sent to the limit for a permit on that lawn it's 50 people
It stands to reason that Ali had used a dummy organization
Get a permitted spot where you could then do a
Pop up stopper
Steel rally
Amy permit application itself
Fascinating things
Since in the report filed by the capital coordinator he documents his conversation with the organizer of the event
Steven Brown
And says quote
Purpose of his event does not give me any idea of what he wants to bring
Attention to other than it's a First Amendment.
Menstration
Weird
Initially they want to be largest
It's closer to the Capitol building itself
Area 9
But it was already claimed
They were offered space on the other side of the building
Decided not to take it because they work
Convinced that women for America First was going to have a rally over there
And I didn't want to mix it up with them because apparently they don't like them so they took the
Smaller lot
Number 8
From what I've seen women for America First is very confrontational
Communicating with brown decor
Later started to notice a heavy overlapping
This proposed
I explained it
Here's that stopped the steel in one nation under God is one in the same due to the similarities in affiliation with Allie Alexander
I advised mr. Brown of Micah
Concerns of not being able to regulate their numbers to 50 persons or less
If his event is it
In fact one in the same Capitol Police will not be able to accommodate his event
Due to the participant number being out of Regulation
Any public safety issue
Her mr. Brown he communicated all the rules with his group to include the 5th
Persons or less
And they're aware that they have to keep their numbers regulated
50 person
You get a pretty strong sense that what was going on is a bit shady and if I had to make a bet I would say that Ali and the folk
Books with one nation under God that that rally are lying to the Capitol Police
It's an order to have a permit for a rally
I was going to get out of control
Even if the capitol hadn't been storm
And if Ali's rally had attracted the crowd that he was clearly planning for
The Capitol Police would have been overwhelmed it would have
Turn ugly
There's there is clear in the
Fusions of
Moline
I mean it was
Was kind of obvious when on the permit application they would like to understand any to be fifty persons or less he said yes and
And then...
Mwahahahaha
Erica permit
Area where they're allowed to have
50% or less than even
Before the capital of storm
Cukur saying that they're leading 15 20000 people
Like
There is absolutely no way that this is in keeping with the terms
If you walk
If you look at the capital coordinator stuff
They are talking about how they will not be able to
Uphold their end of the bargain and it will be a public safety issue
That is kind of funny that
Even on the documentary he's admitting to a crime
To the permit office
Shady ass liar
Details of the permit application
Process
It's a little bit stronger that he was planning chaos in advance
It's just a particular sort of chaos that ended up happening wasn't the type that he was looking
Sideways it's made us look bad and so now we have to make this shity documentary it's all
Love your fault
Another kind of chaos we were looking
Looking for come on
I do appreciate
Tucker Carlson really rolling them.
Because
He's going for
Like like what's happened
And here is embarrassing they're trying to incite another overthrow the country
No other way to put it they wanted to overthrow the United
But it but I'm
Tucker's got to look at himself and realize
Bright light
I'm not going to be robes
Like in the terror
You know like he's got he's going up against the wall
On his third glass of scotch at Whiskey fast he's sitting there and he's thinking
I could have been somebody but I f*** it made a documentary where I'm treating Ali Alexander like a serious person
Fog God
Give me another Scott party I'm going to go to the seminar
Do you think your inciting the revolution doesn't mean you're going to live through a buddy
Holy
I have a tough time
Think about like
You know what you're saying I could have time to Insight another
Event like January 6th
Solarium shirt there's there's definitely
Incitement
Towards something that
It's being done by most of the right-wing media
This overwhelming sense of
Watch this
Like I get bummed out
I get bummed out by seeing people like Ali Alexander with like good
Production value
YouTube
Tik-Tok video completo
Totally
You shouldn't be the camera that
Films
Is worth
10 to $20,000
Betsy investment going into the lies you are telling me
What's actually being dumb
The content is just so
Bad
Apparently bad
Like I don't believe that the people who made this one keenly aware that.
They have to
If you work
Get Fox Nation
Making a
Tucker documentary
You have to know what
I can't believe that anybody who would be aware enough of Ali Alexander
To put him in a documentary
Wouldn't also be aware of what a shady liar here
And they chose to put them in anyway so
He's going to get all the concert
Going to pretend that we were against them the whole f****** time
The question
So
Being a real Atlanta suspect
Really fast
Call 911
Sure
Why don't they why do they know who the Mastermind of this one was because they didn't clearly announcement
Some of the
Some of the key sets
Come to mind,
Adidas
Murrah Federal Building
Oklahoma City
It has been the better part of a year
And The Mastermind
This supposed
Have never been fat
Then who did
Tucker's asking a question he was based on a false premise
The basic idea is that if he gets erection wasn't planned by Ali and stop Bastille it must have been planned by someone and because the
Suspect
As fast as the cases of Oklahoma City and 9/11
You know who it's sufficient that we don't have to Mastermind
Anyone within 20 minutes the guy said
I don't know let him go
See how it goes
Whole thing is dumb for a number of reasons
First being that there doesn't need to be a mastermind behind the events of the 6th
In order for there to be loads of coordination of little things that were the sort of things
Attempt to lead to a huge problem
Mixed in with some things that might have been accidental Orca win
Princeton
Ali and his group having a permit
Specifically for an area meant for
450 or less people when he's trying to bring thousands to the Capitol
Bad planning
Because at the s******* like Ali I'm not going to give him the benefit of the doubt
I bet you didn't know that more than 50 people would show up
I believe that his actions definitely or at least
Intentionally severely irresponsible
Conversely I would be willing to bet that Trump saying in his speech that everyone
Want to go to the Capitol and he was going to go with them
That might not have been playing
Happy access
And for the people who wanted s*** to get out of hand
So that when Congress so was it was there they wouldn't be able to certify the electoral vote even better
Congress members would see the chaos and be intimidated into not
Again we found suspect number one
The moment it has
Also Osama Bin Laden was a huge suspect immediately after 9/11 cuz he's already bomb that
A building and he said he was going to do it again was really easy to figure out
Pretty easy because
Police found a rear axle of the Ryder truck that have been rented by McVeigh to do the bombing so that was a pretty fast lead
Tucker says that McVeigh was arrested within 48 Hours of the bombing but
He was actually arrested
For the night when he was pulled over for not having tags on his car
And also for
BB gun
Take a little longer for them to figure out that he was a suspect in the bombing but when they did he was already in custody
Have they found Terry Nichols because he
He gave Terry Nichols
Brothers address
Police what is a prism
And maybe Bill Cooper
The guy who knows I would agree though that
Pretty scary that the FBI has been identified the person or the
Dakota Coronavirus
Mastermind who planted bombs
The DNC and RNC headquarters yet
But I'm not sure if that helps Tucker's case at all so I'm going to
We go ahead and
Call that one APUSH
Yeah let's
Sleep that one out
So obviously
Agent provocateur
You're right
I mean I've got to be a big piece of the
Conspiracy
Not the end the people who did it where the people that they
That
So it's got to be a jumper box
Pretending to be people
That we say that they did
In order to frame the people who didn't do it
The people who are so peacefully
Chanting crisis King
Agent provocateurs baby
Alexander
Then who did
Co-conspirators
Route middle-aged
Journalist Elijah Schaffer
Casino
The election
Revisit
January 6th
Who were mad about what they saw to be an election
50 Cent was unfair rig fortified
It doesn't matter what you say it is
They were just angry and a lot of them just got
Caught up in the front lines of Chaos
Oh my God
The game maybe
Getting out of control
During 2020 Riders
Cosmoprof
Three billion dollars with a damaging
Until about two dozen people over the course
8 months versus David Dorn
And is very last moments
On Earth
He's a foreman
Police captain
Store treated Riders
That were left wing
Kamala Harris
Twerking help
Instigator
Criminal
Giving the narrative that yours no consequences for acts of violence even on federal ground
Cases being dropped from the federal Siege and Portland by leftist writers I believe that's part of sending a narrative
Gas like the right-wing
Into thinking that they could Riot to and get away with it
So you can see how I hear how this documentary itself isn't
Internally inconsistent
In terms of the point it's trying
How to make Tucker intros dissection
I'm clearly implying
People who were responsible for the riot we're agents
Provocateur
A comments make no sense in that context
Elijah saying that these were moms and dads were gas-lit by the media into thinking that they could write and get away with it because the left
That would imply that these moms and dads did riot
Probably
So because they thought they
I could get away with it
What's the time
Left doesn't get in trouble so why should they
This is how a child thing
Documentary that says I'm rubber you're glue
You say about me
The members of his political Community to this extent
It doesn't look good
Even sort of
In contrast to the earlier presentations
That was being made in this documentary that this is all overblown and the blood libel against
Text Maga and now there's agent-provocateur so there was bad things
You wouldn't have agent provocateurs if she didn't get
Pretty out of hand a bad f****** things happen
Yeah I mean
I feel like an interview with a trump supporter saying we came here to show them that we mean business does not
Support his
Conclusion that they were
All just out there for a month
Yeah I don't I don't think you have
Have agent
Who carry out their work and then like the result is like
Nothing really have
Usually usually bad things
Are the result of
Provocateur
Explain to me
How will provoke
Couture
Gets a
Crowd of thousands
Do something that they instinctively don't want to do
On account of them screaming Christ
And you
There's an agent provocateur
Sure
That person has malicious
Make this argument if you actually want me
Me too
It would beat the way that they would do it would be to like
Attack the police so the police gas the crowd or something
Like that and that met Angela proud enough
Turn off the fan.
Daniela
That would be the argument that would be made
Shockingly without evidence
The evidence is hard
So also Portland is a part of Multnomah County in Orem
The Multnomah District
Attorney's office has a dashboard
Taxi protests related cases that they've handled
Nov 1108
Eight cases that were referred to their office 197 or accept
The prosecutor
Of the 894 cases that were rejected
881 of them were public order
Switcher
Pissant nonsense
Conversely of the person cry
69 out of 180 one of those cases were accepted with night
18 also
Additional
Facing the possible charges later
In 45 additional cases being rejected due to
Efficient evidence
I couldn't get a charge on
Her property
Crimes 81 out of 135 cases were accepted
In 21 out of 33 weapons
Grimes Works after
Deferred prosecution
The comment Elijah made was
Specifically about Portland but really he's trying
End point a finger at all the protests from last year in the wake of the George Floyd killing
The Narrative that's
Perpetuated by right way
Is that the right one quote
Get in trouble for stuff that the left-wing folks get away with
Sexually complete bulshit
An AP analysis of over 300 Federal cases that resulted
Incidents connected
The George Floyd protest
Quote
More than 120
I need to find dance across the United States of pleaded guilty
Or were convicted at trial of federal crimes including rioting Orson
Conspiracy
More than 70 defendants have been sentenced so far have gotten an average of about 27 month
Behind Bars
At least
Can receive
In terms of five years or more
The same sort of phenomenon is probably what your
You're going to end up seeing
The relation to folks
Put the January 6th
Reese's
There may be a lot of folks who get arrested but a whole lot of them are going to have their charge
Just dropped and they'll be cut very generous deals where they plead guilty
Do some nonsense misdemeanor and then they end up doing no jail time
That's what's going to happen
Little people who made me broke the windows of the capital or
Did
Do things like hit cops
BMW going to jail for a while
Could happen
Three important thing here
Is is how the right wing
Media propagandists
Their mind work
Works how it works
Summerlake Elijah Schaffer of Glenn Beck's Blaze Network
Everyone on the left who was protesting didn't
Didn't get in any trouble
That story is real
Feels real and it makes it
Mad
It's not real
The anger is real and it's the massive part of the right-wing persecution complex which Eliza Elijah uses
Make a ton of money
Not connected to reality
They don't do
Follow-up work
And check to see if
Any of the people on the left-wing who were arrested got charged
Because if they did
The fact that the profitable and satisfying anger that they use
Is Ally
Taper with total
In the capital he was just on the
Capitol on January 6th
He was the guy who tweeted out a picture of Nancy Pelosi's open laptop on her desk
With the comment quote
Breaking
I'm inside Nancy Pelosi's office with the thousands of revolutionaries who have stormed the building
I guess the question I'm left with
Cuz if the people store in the capital that they were revolutionaries or if they were moms and dads who got caught up in the excitement
I don't know if Elijah knows the
Motherfuking loser in this documentary I hate these people goddamn this is really really bad
This is really really infuriating
That's that's
F******
Blue Boy
Laughable I mean that's
So f****** easy
It's so easy and it works
It's so easy that work
It's because people
Will instantly hear a bunch of middle-aged white people chanting crisis King and go
They can't be bad
The only thing
Ceiling
That is
Attractive
And what makes this word
Feels like these left-wing protesters
Never get in trouble if I stay that way
If I say that I feel good
If I look it up and I'm not right
I feel
Back feels good
Police reports Everett estopa Steel route
Beagles good
It feels good to cash that check too
You bet
That's why this stuff works
Hearing it feels good to them to appeals to them at comfort
You got it it sucks too much bad person
None of what I believe directly
2 people chanting hang Mike Pence
Or Jews won't replace
Believe leads directly to that anyway this is all the media
The media and
Party leaders create the environment
And it made the January 6th
Violence Alba
But inevitable
Were there other at
It makes you wonder by Magic
Tears all over the
And this is not exclude
Right-wing riot
January 6th
Give me the address to cause trouble
I don't know
Oh you don't know they just look
Text you proved it
You proved that everything
Yeah I mean if if you replace
It's like all of their subjects with like
Where is there
Are fairies in the crowd floating around giving us.
Cost to get us high and send us
To the capital it's possible if there are some people who looked a little bit shorter than you might think
I think the
This is week
Internment of Elijah's argument we need someone a little bit more
Substantial in order to help us with some gravitas
People that look like me
Give me the latest
To cause trouble
I don't know
Someone who might do with security analyst
Waller
4 years
Waterworks
Professional
I'm a senior analyst
Her strategy
At the Santa Fe
Security policy
And my area
Has been
Political Warfare
Psychological warfare
Michael Waller is an analyst for the center for security policy which the splc list doesn't
Extremist group
The group was established in 1988 by Frank Gaffney Junior a former Reagan administration member and it was a c
Super super hawkish group during the Iraq War
Gaffney himself wasn't inside or an advisor to
The Bush Administration had ties latest 2000
You can find him writing op-ed
It's about the Patriot Act
The most important
Piece of
Security legislation adopted since 9/11
Please
In 2006 an article he wrote that was published by his own organization the center for security policy
The real question that should be asked
The present to Judiciary Committee hearings
And that will surely be posed when there's another attack is
Did the Bush Administration engage insufficient surveillance
Not too much
Was it wise Annika
Concession to civil Libertarians to restrict the use of nsa's Signet tools
First by requiring that one of the parties must be outside the country
Second but they are tied to Al-Qaeda or an Associated group
Should we be listening to everyone
Is the real quick
Analyst at
Seems like someone who starts
Civil liberty guys like Tucker wouldn't be into
I'll wait Tucker had their president on the show at
Osher
Sure
Also it should be pointed out that the center for security policies main thing is islamophobia
And in the years since 9/11 they've been
Think tank that has caused
Considerable pain to the Muslim
Community in America
With their promotion of ideas like
Creeping Sharia
They also released a reader Series in 2015 about what they call civilization jahad
Which is their way of saying that Muslim immigration to the United
It states is actually calling
Asian Andy quote
Free violent step in taking over the country
Wow
I'm not bringing this up for no
Michael Waller has been published by the center for security policy
At least 2,000
He was an active member of this group that was severely pro-war
Pro Patriot Act
Pro acting like all Muslims are terrorists
Three things that this documentary is pretending to be opposed to
In 2003 Waller Road in op-ed that argued that members of Congress who opposed the Iraq War should be tried for
For treason
Congressman who willfully take actions during wartime
Damaged morale and undermine the military are Sabbath
Tours and should be arrested exiled or
Cocaine
When is he's kind of a
I would like a military dictatorship please
Thank you
Waller's a documentary because he was at the Capitol on January 6th then eight days later he published an article titled
I saw provocateurs at the Capitol Riot on January 6th
It's a dumb and overwritten article with literally no proof of anything so I'll save you the trouble of reading
The people in camouflage
Sing like this blind soldiers they weren't militia people there actually
Plants were there to attack the capital
Why the protests
Provided cover for them
Right but they were militia people and we know cuz we have there
This guy wrote an article
Oh okay probably a plant
There's some young people who
Acting weird so he could presume these fake Trump
Supporters we're antifa or something similar
No proof that they were fake Trump supporters at all
Just making that s*** up
Obituary
Just a little weird or maybe there were high
Trump looks like drugs too
Everybody likes it
But the old windows didn't cause any
Any trouble that Waller saw
It was a camo wearing people who he is more concerned with the ones who are literal Terror
There was a scuffle and then police threw some tear gas
For a few seconds I saw what look like police in a tussle with some archers up
Upfront what appeared to be an organized group in
Civilian clothes
Disorganized
The group are the cell I called the plainclothes militant
They fit right in with the Maga people
The evidence that he thought they looked organized in that they look like
Maca people which is
Proof that they're plainclothes militant
It's trying to look like Maga people I don't understand this is
This is not convincing because you're using real words and you're acting like we're in the real world doesn't
Mean you're not just describing f******
Hydra from a comic
Right
His next piece of evidence
That there were agents provocateur
Police because
Is tear gas canisters hit a little girl in the face
Someone yelled forward
Do not retreat
Apparently the use of the word
Was suspicious
Because it sounded like a quota military operation
Hey buddy if
You think it's weird that Maga folks are throwing around military term
I have some oceanfront property in Arizona to sell you a military term is more likely
Play to be on the left way get the f*** out of here must be of what the FED plant
Definitely when you were selected on the whole thing later Waller.
Decided that people encouraging folks to
Push forward was actually quote
An organized cell of Agents
Couture
The Corral people is an unwitting
Apollo 14
Behind the plainclothes militant
Tussling with police
After thinking about how best to lie about it I've decided this lies the way to go
That legitimately there's zero evidence
Since this provided in this article
Box that Waller had which I don't find persuasive
Piece de resistance of this argument is that for the chaos that already got going in the Capitol was already being so
Waller saw group of approximately three dozen
Quote YouTube
Briskly singer
Single file
These people were wearing
Uniform
Like they were like in military uniforms
And we're taking the capital before disappearing quote under the scaffolding beneath the
Wow they're good
Provocateurs were wearing plain clothes
So they could look like Maga folk but I guess these people are identified
These people are identified as agent provocateurs cuz they're like
These other ones are
Not too
Let your
Yeah yeah it's almost like it doesn't matter
Who or what you are
What matters is that it looked
Bad for rich people so rich people are going to make money off of
I think the
This is probably a dramatized
The count of something Waller saw but
Even if
Group of people wearing
Camo and acting like they were in the army
That doesn't mean that they were agent provocateur
MPR reported
Nearly 1 in
5 people charged over the alleged
Involvement in the attack on the US Capitol appear to have military history
And that's not even counting for the militia weirdos
Cosplayers
Nothing in Waller's account actually proves anything but it's good enough to be proved for the right with meteos desperate for flimsy of
Wouldn't this event was
Exactly what it is
We did it we know somebody tell us we didn't
Jay Michael Waller is somebody who appears to have a fair amount of edge
Education in the field of political Warfare B
Even so.
To take this seriously
Just because of that
Who require a serious amount of using
The appeal to Authority fallacy
The argument is coming from someone with x
Forties but it's also a really bad argue
Still
Yeah this is
This is feeling a little bit like Tucker
Botanicare
A fun bit of trivia about Jan-Michael Waller
He was also the expert who was interviewed to climate antifa was a gang filled with agent provocateur likely
We run by a 50 to 70 year old person who's been involved in orchestrating Street violence
From the Shadows
For decades
Lauren Southern documentary Crossfire
You may recall was directed by
Scooter Downey
The co-writer of this Tucker series
Yeah he keeps
He's he's been operating it out of secretly out of a home for Extraordinary children don't know if you know it
This Crossfire was released on December 30th 2020
Prior to January 6th
So maybe Waller isn't is unbiased
As an observer of the events that day as he might want to protect himself as being
So ridiculous
I don't hate him as much baby
Just another
Ship guest
Nothing is being proven here it is everyone's making me mad
Hey all you need to do is conjecture that maybe the people at fault warranted fault and then they're like wow that's great
Gives a little bit of a retelling here of his
His
Most of the interview is basically just him
Saying like I know about the stuff I've been involved in things
And then
Retelling what is in that article but it was Article there's more.
Detailed
I was helping this old woman across the street I gave somebody CPR
To save their life before I even made it
I'm a hero
So hear you guys talking about a little bit of stuff and then
Tucker
That's a brilliant pivot
You can start seeing different units of agent
On me
Statue of peace
And they were assembled in various places on his walkway
Golden members of the crowd trying to cause trouble
One of those
Full-time left-wing Act
Call John cell
John Sullivan what he does best
Is agitate
He causes problems and that's what
He's known for
John Sullivan is categorically not one of the people that Waller was talk
About
He's someone you can definitely argue is not a good influence and people on the left
Didn't really want to associate with him even prior to the
It could be fair to say that some of the things that Sullivan was saying had
The potential
To be inciting that day
But that's also really Far Cry from demonstrating in any way that he was there as a provocateur working
Under the auspices of anybody
I just don't get how the fact that the night
Before it happen
Hold your horses
It is not going to be in the hold your horses do not tell me if you tell me like that
John Sullivan what he does best
Is agitate
He causes problems and that's why
What is known for
On the left and the right
And he is the person that organizes all of these are bad
Android
In Utah
With his Group insurgents USA
Journalist Taylor Hanson
Yeah yeah
Taylor Hanson
Really
Really pulling out all the shipment
Pretty sweet that is unreal.
What kind of where I was almost like I quit
You're not doing this anymore
Taylor Hanson was on Infowars the day of the storming because
Inside and was apparently present when Ashley Babbitt was shot
It's interesting the Tucker discredits him as a journalist but weirdly
Yahoo news article says that he's actually quote
Activist
Connected to a group called
Baby lives matter
That's not actually accurate he's not connected to that group he's the founder of it
You made a bunch of headlines
For going outside abortion
Can clinics and writing baby lives matter on the street
Yeah that's like most journalists that's how you get your start
September 2020 he claims that he was beaten up by 4 antifa Black Block members
I'm not really sure how much of a journalist he is he honestly seems like more of an anti-abortion activist who has a pretty solid
Backstory
Be mad at the people he uses
Protesters
Real though Taylor Hansen might be maybe the worst person to have in this documentary is a talking head for once
Specific reason
He was on film
In the Capitol at the scene of Ashley Babbitt shooting and no charges have been filed against
He's a walking refutation of the central premise of this documentary which is the people who stormed the capital of being jammed
You should not have him in
Their documentary bring way too much attention
Also as you brought up in as you predicted
They conveniently leave out the part where the night
Taylor Hanson joint Owen Shroyer and some other journalists
Been filming themselves burning a black lives matter flag and honestly
I don't know why they didn't mention it in this documentary
It is weird
It's not like Tucker's audience with
I think that's a bad thing to do be like of course those guys didn't storm the capital there burning black lives matters Flags
Here's a clip of them doing that Taylor Hanson
Fence expert a journalist
Documentary
My good friend
Heckler
Just going to do a
Little
Black lives matter in Richmond
Ceremony
Seems like he's a good person to interview on
I'm critically for this documentary
Totally just a straight down the middle unbiased journalist here definitely not erase
Anti-abortion activist Deli pretending to be a journal
How is it not
So easy for
Like the mainstream media to report on this documentary which they've done
At nauseam been like
Covergirl's new Patriot
First thing and not just like Play Taylor Hanson
Saying something in the documentary
And then play that f****** clip and be like see and we're done
I don't know I don't I don't I don't know if it is that slam dunk
Yeah I don't think
The people who this documentary appeals do would be turned off by burning a black lives matter flag but I mean really
That's unreal
It's pretty shity
How do you not burn how do you burn
Flags and be like where the good guy
What insane person that I don't know I don't think that the ACT
Itself of burning a flag
Is bad
I think it depends on the message
It's trying to be sent by it
Understand I understand but like
That you're not burning an American
10 Flags
To protest a f****** War
You're doing it maliciously and
Spiteful
Polly like
And almost like list
Back to that I haven't I haven't heard that in a while
It almost feels like an initiation
Kind of thing
Like boys written all over
Taylor light it is exactly this is you coming into the name cereals
Piece of s***
Sunnyway Taylor was
Like I mentioned
Interesting the way that this is presented in the documentary
Journalist Taylor Hanson
While living in Utah he was attacked
Buy membership John cell
Group
And it was
No ride shortly after
George Floyd
I was riding my motorcycle downtown
For some reason there was you
She was Car Rally in
I had no idea what it was not
Between
Ended up pulling over
And that's when I asked
Actually person counter John Sullivan
And his group insurgence USA
Ban antifa attacks
Ruining my biking
Basically just I mean I actually had a gun pointed to my head at that rally
Pacifically
John Sullivan
Look I don't know if Taylor was attacked
Multiple times
But he made
The headlines
The Christian Post in September 2020
What he was beaten and bloodied when he claims he was attacked by auntie
Problem is that wasn't in Utah
That was important
Pictures on how
From this article in Christian Post of the
His face after the meeting
Exactly the pictures that are used in this documentary
Taylor Street Taylor Hanson
Weird
That's I wonder if
Liars lying about things again
I mean I wonder
I just
Just f****** just be like
I was
Attacked by a group of black Muslims
And they were all the lgbtq they were all of them they were every Boogeyman
You've ever heard of they were antifa they were communist they were every
Just say they were every
These articles about Taylor's assault
Mysteriously absent from them and from Taylor's account at the time is any mention of John Sullivan
Actually
Specifically says that
They didn't have a gun
I'm thankful they stop
The beating when they did and didn't use weapons
To inflict harm or death upon me
I was going to try and be cute
Facetious and pretend that Taylor was beating up twice
But decided to keep the second one
Secret until now
Emma Tucker's producers just accidentally used the wrong photos but I'm f******
Tired
Occam's razor tells me the Tyler beaten up by some dudes in Portland
He's now trying to rewrite the story to involve some new flashy characters like John Sullivan
Heightened
3 globalist
At this point the documentary I realize that were
Still on
Episode 1 of this b******* and
Exhausted
The claims are being made or Sensational in full of s***
People being treated as experts being interviewed or pretty much all
Well-known right-wing frauds
Then propagandists
It's almost unbearably shity to try and view this as a serious project that someone like Tucker would release
It's so bad from an information standpoint and the people he's associating with her
Deeply troubling
I suspected
He liked his audience he knows that they won't hold his inaccuracies against him and I
I guess the
Hanging out with Shady weirdos is basically his thing now
Yeah that's
That's really sad
Him
It is for me
Yeah well I mean it's really sad for you but for him like
For them for Alexander for Taylor and for those
To be in this documentary
Huge cat
Hugest aspirational for the amazing for them they're in the big leagues
Tucker's given them shittin AA or time you know if he's presenting them as journalists
Important
Activist
F*** off
50 Cent
Sad you're going down in
Flames if you're working
With Allie Alexander
Talking about John Sullivan
It is you're either like if you're gone
Associate with Allie Alexander for long
It's going to bite you in the ass
You should not do it it's probably going to be a bad idea
Go the path of Laura Loomer and Jacob Wohl I'm seeing a gate of gates in their future
Conversely
You're trying to use Ali Alexander in order to like squeeze some juice
Out of him yeah I feel so sad
Not much juice left in there
Nope so there is a FairPoint
The comes up in that is that the FBI has
Ensnared people in the past
Oh yeah if you want to go FBI is bad
You're not going to run out of example
Only has the
Federal agencies
Citizens
Those things are true but that doesn't justify Tucker's in
Intended conclusion
Mainly that this is what happened on January 6th
The good old Patriots
Snared by the feds
Before being true doesn't prove the second
Impart like you just needs to do better this is
This isn't like a dozen
AJ saying they've done false
Flags in the past so why not exactly
Something is possible doesn't prove that it did happen
This is childish
During prohibition to the government
Poisoned a lot of booze and killed a lot of people
Yeah that's true
Great that doesn't mean that they're poisoning your booze now
I understand
So like I said people up and we got it
An example here
FBI agents were essentially the
They made
The crime crime
You scarcely need to go back
Three months
To the so-called Capital seeds
Exasperated
From memory
I'm from the national
And that is the so-called
Whitmer
Kidnapping
You'll explain what you kidnapped.
Put her on trial for treason
All because of Michigan
Covid lockdown federal government
Awarded an alleged plot
To kidnap
The governor
Of Michigan
In a manner that is
Included
Shockingly enough
Storming the state capitol
According to reporting BuzzFeed
Michigan State play
Enter the building
Capitol building
Interesting parallel
Definitely could be an interesting parallel that proves it
The same shadowy forces that did the false flag of January 6th
Also staged the storming of the mission
Capital or you can say that the right-wing of the pattern of taking over Capitol building
One of these is an almost embarrassingly simpler explanation
Right-wing militia folks take
Can things over like the maligore well that's what they do
Are you like to occupy especially government
Control thing while pretending that they have a right
Twitter whatever
It's a normal thing for them
Every year
Also these folks have yet to prove that the feds were responsible for the plot
The kidnap Governor Whitmer
The alleged leader of that group Adam Fox
Definitely isn't an FBI informant which you'd know because most of
The claims that the FBI's at the group up or just right-wing media sources repeating what his lawyer has said
In his defense
There's an ABC news headline but you could choose to report in to differ
What is depending on what you wanted
Can back
You could do with quote
Michigan Governor kidnap plot dropped out by FBI informant
I would strongly suggest that the FBI was behind this s***
That's no part of the headline
You can use the entire headline though and that is quote Michigan governor
Kidnap plot drugged-up by FBI informants
Accused leader claims
Because that's the reality
If you want to you can go and read the criminal complaint
Against the members of this group in Michigan who were charged
And it's hard to Come Away with the impression that anyone
What's that up
Quote
In early 2020 the FBI became aware through social media that a group of individuals were discussing the violent overthrow of certain
Government and law enforcement
Components
Among those identified Warcraft
Through electronic
Communication
Crofton Fox agreed to unite others in their cause and take violent action
Multiple state government
But they believe they're violating the US
Constitution
They decided to hold a meeting on June 6th
It was a confidential informant for the FBI was recorded the whole thing
Quote they discuss different ways of achieving their goal from peaceful Endeavors to Violent actions
At one point several members talked about state governments they believed were violating the US
Constitution including the government
Michigan
Of Governor Gretchen Whitmer
Several members talked about murder
Tyrants and
Taking a sitting governor
At that point they realize they needed number
They were pretty small group
Play reached out to another militia group that was based in Michigan
Unfortunately unbeknownst to them
This militia group already had an FBI informant
Sent back in March.
Flipped a member of the group when they brought him in for
Questioning about how this militia group
Was trying to collect the local law enforcement members
Home address
So they had
This group
That they had invited FBI informant into
Animalistic
It was already infiltrated for other reason
Here's the worst
Sing that they do that's a thing that I hate the most about them is that they are self
F****** stupid
They use it as a smokescreen there likes nobody could be this stupid
Believe me to suspect that like pulling off leaderless resistance might be
More difficult than it seems
L A really useful you know how they're like a man Alexander the Great
So great that was another leader this thing deep irony that in order to pull off leaderless resistance
You kind of need
A lot of grapes
More leaders now
Do you have these two groups which
Both have moles
Innominate decided to combine forces and it's just Anime
Embarrassingly sloppy affair
Reading over this criminal complaint is just a laundry list of pointing out super illegal things these dudes did while they were being Secret
Early recorded
Just because there were feds in the group doesn't mean that
The feds entrapta
These people
It's a sensible question to ask him
By all means it should be a point
Brought up
And they're happening
Instances of that in the past
Cast of people getting jammed up
But the fact that something
Possibly be true is not the
Same thing as actually being true
Based on the available information I don't find the argument that the winter
Whitmer kidnapping
Plot was a FBI setup I don't find that convincing at all
I do however understand how dudes like everyone in this documentary me to believe it's fake
Yeah it would make them feel really bad not just to be caught but also to be caught being
Dumb as they really are
Whenever it comes to light and you read about it you're like
Like if you want to take if you want to take over mission
Then you're going to need at least two nuclear weapons
Before you even start
Start with the Upper Peninsula need that tune
Negotiate your
There's no way that the government is going to allow you to do that unless you have it
At least 21 of which you have
Does that off
In order to prove that you will
I think this is a very restrained option I think I'm doing this right I'm just saying if you want to if you want to overthrow the government is going to take a
A lot more ground
So I'll leave you to that planning
Move on
This next clip
It 1
For like
Tucker to have Gaston like this Darren Beattie character he's lying about the FBI
Whitmer kidnapping
Got a weird when Tucker as the voice-over person decides to lie to
Well it gets even better
18 conspirators
Undercover
FBI
In other words
2/3
To the people plotting to kidnap the governor of Michigan
We're working directly for
For the feds
That's quite a percentage
This isn't true
It's basically just a misrepresentation of the headline from Buzz
The FBI allegedly used at least 12 and 4 min
Any Michigan
I didn't initially understand exactly where Tucker was getting the 18 number from because
On October 8th the FBI announce they file charges
Michigan militia members
With at least six of them being charged and connect
Directly to the
Governor Whitmer
If you read the court filing you'll see that there were two confidential informants as well as two undercover employees mixed in with
Folks were plotting to
Kidnap and
Ultimately kill Whitmer
Because they did
Horrible job in operation
Insecurities
They weren't
Convince to do this by the cops in their ranks they were just so dumb that they had cops
Recording all of their meeting
If I had to guess
Believe this is
This narrative about 18 people
Going to 12 out of the 18 people
I already informed
Is it
Songs from a headline
Of the story in the Gateway pundit
It was a setup
SBI used at least 12 informants in witmer kidnapping case with only
Add that together
If you only go based on that headline you don't look any further into the story
Add those numbers together and get 18 people 12 of humor feds
However that is not
And it's either an indication
Nubian too lazy to report this accurately desire to willfully 278.
Information
Any responsible reporter would know that there were quote eight other men charged under Michigan's anti-terrorism
Statutes for providing
Google support
The plotters
Tirolesa
People who were charged with the actual conspiracy
Not plot
Charged with providing support
Some of these people aided in like
Speakingout wittmershaus and wanted hosted their meetings at his home
So that kind of stuff
This is what these other eight folks did
Okay
Imagine your
Staking out
Governor whitmer's house like
Who's going to end well for me
I can trust these weirdos is going to go great
You'll notice that I was actually a total of 14 people instead of 13 I said we're charged on October 8th
That's because one other guy got
Didn't charge a little bit later
Anyone
Eating a narrative the 12 out of the 18 people involved in the Michigan kidnapping
Simplot where feds
Is this regurgitating
Far-right media talk
It's unfortunate when just an average person on the
What street does this but it's horrific
You talk or doing it in this dumb documentary
That implies that the standard he has for information is so low that he could report
Is based on a misleading Gateway public headline
Or that
He knows it's misinformation and included in the documentary anyway
Having grown up in a world where Tucker Carlson has been a public figure the whole time I'm going to bet it
It's the second one
I don't think
I don't think he's that dumb
And also that
That's probably why it's on for
Because there's anybody really going to demand
I will
Think anyone's going to do it
Mane Attraction as well
So we have we have another
Piece of evidence
What's the Darren Beattie is
Going to prison
Year of
Love Y8
Clearly
Does that mean that
Deep state did it might as well be
It's that flimsy
It gets even better
Many of the individuals involved in this
Have been associated with a very same militia group that the government is attempted to associate
With 16
I don't think that's
Proof of conspiracy the same like as much as
Thanks it is maybe they just all
Oh
The reference to the fact that there were members of the three percenters who are
At the Capitol Riot on January 6th
And that some members of the group
Involved in the witmer kidnapping flower also associated
With three
Supercenter
This doesn't prove or even see
Suggest that the events are related
Really just a reflection of how three percenters are pretty f***** up folks of a tendency towards doing f*****-up and violent thing
Presumably in the name
Of Defending
Yeah
I don't really understand how this details being presented to some kind of
Support for the documentaries thesis
Good kind of work
Better
The opposite way I mean that's a little bit like being like a hossino did you see this
Three Oaks
Keepers were also members of the clan
That's obviously a conspiracy by the FBI I couldn't have brought the 7-Eleven because I have 50
Slurpees
See if so facto you fool
There's one more piece of evidence
Being presented
Please come like in a
Dentistry
Dumb dumb
And if that isn't
I'll give you the cherry on
Hello
I'm Steven
The head of the
Detroit field office of the FBI who presumably oversaw
All of those aging presumably
Actively involved in inciting
The Michigan
Kidnapping
Subsequent to that
He was quietly and
Suspiciously promoted
Position within the DC field
Where he now
Oversees the investor
So this is the reference to Stephen jontrona II
Okay
There's a lot to unpack in their 30s
Second clip
The first thing is that Darren Beattie who's talking
I'm here has absolutely not proven it
Anyway that the FBI agents in Michigan were quote
Involved in inciting the plot
He's asserted it and Tucker has provided inaccurate information that he thinks
But nothing so far has established this grievance
Come close
If he's wrong
Fbt is wrong
And the FBI agents in Michigan in that case didn't do anything wrong
But who cares if a guy goes from one FBI office to another
Meaning of haughty I watch
Amman
Climbing the corporate ladder
Second BT's claiming that don't wanna was
Liam suspiciously promoted to a higher position
After the witmer kidnapping case so many loud
Loud enough
Fishman going to the DC FBI
And also the FBI's literally put out a press release about it being moved to the DC field office on October 13th
It doesn't seem very
Quiet they did it to
Suspicious lady
Informed the Press
What's going on here at a bunch of throwing those words into blank creates suspicion
If you read the press release about his promotion you'll learn that this was only sort of a
Promotion
Previously the special agent in charge at the Detroit field office
Went to DC
He was assistant director in charge of the Washington field office
Both of these are supervisor positions at the top of the office hierarchy
It's just that the LA New York City and DC offices they have assistant directors in charge as
Boss as opposed to
The other 53 FBI field offices in the United States
Better run by special agent
Symptom charts just cuz they're bigger office
I get it this is a bit of a promotion
Since you'll be overseeing a larger FBI office but his bio makes me think that he probably also wanted to go to
DC because that's where he spent a lot of his
His career
From 1998 to 2004 he was at that same DC field office
Swear Aponte
He spent four years teaching at the FBI Academy
After that he transferred back
To the DC off
He was there for another six years before going to St Louis and then he ended up in Detroit in 29
He seems to have a pretty accomplished career but also one with roots in DC and I
I don't think it seems suspicious at all that he would be offered that position
An accepted
Lateral move
On CNN
I can come up with a
Better cancel
Pleurisy
So this
Raikou
He was named special agent-in-charge over the
Detroit
That position only became available because
The person previously in that position Timothy Slater
Have been transferred to lead the washing
DC field office
The same position
What happened was
Right they transferred him out in a
Vance of this guy taking over the Michigan office to lay the groundwork for the eventual overthrow
It all makes sense now, together
I didn't even think they were going to fit and then all the sudden whenever I put
Push them into the spot where they were supposed to
Stupid
Just in case that like there was something we're like the Detroit field office was a like a farm system should be
I went and check the other people that's not a pattern
Dad I thought like maybe be really interesting.
Things that this is a smoker
Can Gunn kind of Revelation but it's
Really more of a who cares
If you don't believe all the b******* about the Whitmer kidnapping plot being an FBI setup then all that happened here is that a welder
Respected FBI agent-in-charge of
Field office
Was put in charge of the larger FBI field office
Even if you do believe that the witmer kidnapping
FBI setup that still doesn't make this
That good of a piece of evidence the January 6th was a setup
Books like Darren or Tucker Alex for that matter
Understand what it means to prove or demonstrate something
Thing and I suspect a large part of that is because their audience
They don't incentivize them doing so
The attention economy that they profit off of is
What's more interested in shocking twist
Sensor surprise reveal
Blow people's minds by pointing out
But the head of the DC office used to be the head of the Detroit office
And then take credit for having proven that the large event in both places were secret FBI plot
The actual content and arguments being made or mean
But they leave viewers with the feeling of having
The something was revealed
Bro I'm at revelation
Is being sort of
Sidetracked
Can perverted
Into like convincing
The audience
What's that
Hey
They proved it this is
Can you believe it dude
You have no idea I'm going to throw this one out at
Okay
So there was this
Like famous neocon guy
All right and he supported all of these
Middle-of-the-road Rhino policies for the longest time
But then
Okay and this is going to blow your mind
Then
Then he saw an opportunity to make more money doing something else
Right
He took a job to do that other thing
Even though he didn't really believe any of the b******* because he still that neocon
From way back when Dan do you get it
Controlled opposition from the neocon
To run the new populist movement man next thing you know you're going to tell me who used to wear a bow tie
To tell you that he's
I want
How to make clear that you're not suggesting that that was that was like a clearly
Keisha's total voice but if not I just want to make sure that no one thinks that you're suggesting the Tucker Carlson is legit
Neocon as a plant control
Saying that they're choosing a specific at the eye
To go after not the head of the DC office
At the time of the Michigan overthrow
If that's the guy who would really be running
The other guy
Well they're trying to take this
FBI agent lion
So it won't last boyfriend
Sort of
Putnam's humpback of course they did a great job.
Chaos of January 6th
Incitement
Entrapment
No decent
Believe that
Recently there's evidence
It makes you wonder
Second war on terror
Citizen
What else are they
I just was like I'm not I'm not doing the other one
I don't care if they're just as stupid
The blade
Bulbs
Face-f***
IQ of someone
Who knows what they're saying is
Isn't true saying no decent person would want to believe this no decent person
I want to believe this so you
You idiot
It's you f***
Kingroot
Watching this dumb documentary
Very fact that you want this s*** to be true
Tucker Carlson is letting you know you're a f******
Pilot s***
I'm generous reading of his comment
So what do you think
I mean pat-on-the-back all around
Glass of champagne
Totally I break out the bubbly
When you nail it on the first take I don't need two more episodes
Yeah I'm just saying when you got all the information
Out in one app
Episode
Ironclad
Airtight
Just let it stand on its own
How you think
Like when you have
A documentary
The experts that you have
Include Alexander
Taylor Hanson
And Darren Beattie
About
Go fuc yourself you know
I mean
I think
Part of my problem with this
Is also
They're wasting a lot of money on this production
Because we've seems yeah we've seen better ship
Cheaper
Maybe you know
But this isn't good
Some decent production value problem
Yeah yeah but you know it's not good
It doesn't have to be good
No I know Telugu
Subscription I know but I'm just saying that you could cut some
Corners in a lot of places
Susan save money on the production
You probably could but you don't cry number one problem prizes
Watching the documentary I found to be a pretty chilling
Experience emotional archives
Stefan molyneux
Poland documentary which
At least had the
Cathartic ending when he realized he was a white nationalist
It like the entertaining bombast
Fake crying and sometimes interests
But something Alex makes
Usually has
Yeah it really is
The package
Bigotry just being delivered in a more presentable pack
One of the things
Things that really troubled me watch
I honestly don't know what anyone
Can do about it
This documentary is full of obvious and transparent lies but Tucker's cultivated an audience that doesn't really care and they think
George Soros controls all fact
The impulse you would seem to have would be to spread the message of his thing is bull
Loudly
And as publicly as you can
Come and watch the thing I
Think that's what the goal is
Well if you get people to scream about fox
Nation
Foxnation.com how dare he do that on Fox Nation
Dot-com
Release this on Fox Nation because Fox News wouldn't let him are it on his show
It's no more unhinged or offensive than anything else he Arizona regular basis
This was released on Fox Nation as a promotional campaign I'm a left-wing mainstream media backlash against doubtful of
S*** this documentary is
Please into the campaign at least a little bit
I don't want to seem like I'm trying to say the Tucker should be ignored or anything like that I'm just not confident the people in the mainstream media
The ability to address this kind of material without f****** up and
Socially just
Spread
The documentary to a wider audience
Yeah I don't know what to do I like that was
A big part of life
Walking away from this
Being a little bit like
I mean yeah you know
It doesn't seem like it would be too hard for media members to
To just go out and be like hey listen
So we watch this whole Tucker thing
Obviously all he's really trying to do Israel us up to get more viewers to his f****** web
Guess what
That's what Tucker
Not today
Like just say out loud on television not today Tucker
What do we say to the god of b*******
Not today
I feel like a fair amount of this
Especially the promotional campaign leading up to it
I don't know I don't know it
There's an interesting
Element to it and that is Tucker
Bike spaces
Is just straight-up Infowars
The dignity above it
It is just the Tucker
Is
Less
Transparently nuts
Spitaliks
He doesn't fake crying and
Screaming and
Endive
Get red in the face and like
Talk about how he used to murder people and what have you
The same content and when you look at it
The same people
Alexander these are the same folks who are running their just moving up the
Lottery up now
So
I think Alex
Should be scared
Tucker should be scared too though cuz this is
Does not like
I don't
I don't think this is a road
Goes very
No it's
Kind of a flash-in-the-pan to try and do this
Like a normal TV
I mean
It is it blows me away again just
Because it's like
How long do you guys think that this is sustainable
It's not sustainable you can't Terrace Edge forever
It's going to explode
And you did it and it exploded on the 6th
And that was an opportunity to be like
Let's Tampa tape
Tamper this s***
And they leaned into it again
So it's going to happen again
And the idea that they are going to be able to come
Control it
Seam sewing
Sing to me
These kinds of
Tents
Situations and events
Will end up happening weather
It's by
People like Tucker and Alex
Facilitating it or buy them not
And Their audience turning against them
Because they're not hardcore.
Going to happen
It happens every time I
Believe that you would be that stupid
And
Egotistical to think no
Just because I've seen this play out
Over and over and over again throughout human history
I'm pretty sure I'll be able to
That to hang my hat on
Controlling B
Populist mob of
Murderer
I don't know what to do I don't I don't know if
But I regret watching all three of these episodes
And I'm not talking about this s***
I do feel like I've done
I do feel a little bit after watching the draft
Listening to this
Alike
This is where the coyote and the right-wing media is the roadrunner
Need to be smart
Just need to be one step
I had just fast enough
To stay one step ahead
Of every attempt
If Tucker and his next show by saying
It's going to be a
Infuriated I've already looked him in the eyes
So I will be back we've been brought to you by Acme industry absolutely
Can find us at our website
Youtube.com
They also were on Twitter
Benito Emily orbz
It's Clark I'm Daryl run
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color