Air Jordan X swetik
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge fight
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
I love you
It's around where's the author of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
Students
Indeed we are Damned
Jordan's a question for you
Why don't you go first
Well my bright spot Dan and I never thought I would say this my bright spot today is
The DMV
You know what before you tell whatever story you're going to tell her I want to say I
Always enjoy going to the DMV in Chicago
When I was in Missouri
Always miserable
Chicago I haven't had nothing but positive experience the
The place on Diversey I had to go get my license renewed
Cuz it was expired by about a year
And I had no idea because I was getting all those texts
You know the scam text from the DMV where you like that
Is it expired you need to
I got that at the same time that I got the regular text for a little hard to tell the difference now
I don't and I think that I don't
Know anybody who keeps up
Looks like well I got 3 months
It's something you just kind of
Goes on the back of your mind
Infantile somebody's like you
You can't buy that
You need a valid license
Yeah
So the
The DMV on Diversey
I went there
There was a line out the door
End it
Well I thought we were going to be there for like 23 hours were people who saw the line and then just left
They
Banged it out
In 25 minutes they got there like
Dave and it was
Suggested they were
For good
It was that the whole
Group of people there
The tiny little office that we're working in
Perfect harmony with each other it was bananas to me yeah everybody was having a good time everybody's like
I'm useful this is what I'm
Rushing this
Everybody's smiling and talking
Into each other
I talked to three other people who couldn't
Help would be like
This is the best DMV I've ever been to the times I've been there they've been pretty Pleasant people to
Like it going to go have this like
Your character in your head is like grumpy sure in DMV for today
Chicago Idaho
Goodonya Dr amazing real happy for him
Mighty Mite BMV my bright spot is I've got a new desk and I'm going to build after we get done
Recording I need and I'm very excited about that I've had this
Corner desk
That I came with mismatched would the one end of it is sort of a lighter
You call it a cream color
The color of the other side is like a grayish Brown
Stupid I tried to get the
Like replace
They sent me the wrong one again
Forever and I'm excited to throw it out and start fresh
Remodeling the office so very excited about that
Been with us since day one
We'll miss your desk
So Jordan say we have an interesting episode to go over our last episode
That we were going to talk about Alex Jones as a response
To Tucker Carlson show
Docu-series
But you know what I kind of got to
Thinking about it I'm like
Why
We know what he said
He said he loves it
Is the best greatest thing ever and it's all just he made this possible
The truth it's all because Al
So instead we're going to do is when I get to look at
The present we're going to jump forward we're going to be talking about November 8th
I'm close to that
I so I'm excited about that before we get down to business
Little moments say hello to some new walk
First light
Draves
Next Levi's thank you so much right now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Ella
Wyatt thank you so much
Juvenile
Finally Jordan we got we had a technocrat in the
Okay you say hello and thank you to a technocrat
He's wwjd equals what would Jordan and Bam do don't live by that
Advice but thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Crikey mate that's fantastic have yourself a bruise
How's your 401k doing brother
We got to go Full Tilt Boogie on this watching all right
What's the business
Making that money off that heroin
Damn so good
But my neck is free
Ida Claire
Infowar
Yes thank you very much
I wanted to say one quick thing before we get into the episode and that is that
I got some feedback
Back on our last episode The Tucker Carlson Juan
About about
Using names of protesters
When I was making illustrations of people who have been arrested were like in protest
And I want to say thank you to the person who pointed this out on Twitter
And that
I didn't mean to you know I right
I reflected on a little bit and the statistics
That we talked about really do make the same point
And I didn't realize there's a bit of a blind spot
And the reason I'm calling this out is cuz I went back and I cut that out of the episode and reposted it
So that's not in the episode now but
It was
And in case anybody was
The curious about that or whatever
It wasn't removed secretly
I'm trying to do a little better
Future being aware of that you know till it's a little bit of a
He was caught up in the idea of like if I point out these spell
Pacific's
Then it really helps drive home the point right and in bed
Reality
That is totally fine in the current reality
You can't
So anyway that's
What's that
Morgan Stark here on November 8th
And I can't tell you how much
I'm excited to talk about the present-day Alex talking about some important business
And so here is where Alex's head is at on the this day
Big exclusive news ladies and gentlemen
I saw this last week
And I thought maybe he's just taking an unplanned vacation we're going to sit back and wait and see what happens
Friday and came out that
He had
Only gotten sick after the third
Pfizer shop because he's a good-looking obelisk
Third round
That's when the scientist and I've heard tell you that the real
Side effects taking pretty much guaranteed
And we have a lot of different sources
A in Hollywood
But also in law enforcement
And they have reached out to us
Broadcast
How's it going
Everybody who's
Well I guess we
That doesn't sound like Alex
I guess we can't do an episode about the 8th the storm
I was really glad to do an episode to have a great episode of
Getting us to go 3 or 4 hours and Alex does come back and it turns out he's talking about Gavin Newsom
Is it that you was talking about
That's the whole thing
My God
Alex is in a very bad mood so it looks like I'm going to die for what
I am going to put him in the corner
What to do Jordan I guess
You know what we could do what could we do
You know we talked to Jon Ronson recently
We could we could play that for the people
I don't think anybody would want to hear that Dan
That doesn't sound like something
I'd like it Miss 80s broadcast I feel like the public would be interested
Let me say this real quick I'm glad that that went reasonably smoothly cuz I
As soon as I hit the theme song I realized that I forgot to tell you
Pretend We're doing the regular your improv skills are fantastic
Thursday I'm given
That's throw it to that
We were thrilled to have a conversation with Jon Ronson and
About some of his experiences with Alex
And the various
I thought
And perception
Could not be cooler cooler guy is awesome to do yep so enjoy that and will be back on Friday
See you then
Hey
The folks today we are thrilled to be joined to having a little conversation with us
Is the author of
Them with extremist I heard of him before psychopath test another one
Another word and then also there's a new podcast.
The people to check out
Things fell apart ladies gentlemen
Thank you so much for joining us Jon Ronson hello
Are you guys doing
July
50 mm people have
Credible
Acknowledge
Alex Jones I like that that is being treated as a social positive
Because generally it's like this guy knows too much about Alex Jones I got to get away from him
So
Understand
Identify you had that series that from back in the early 2000
Bi the secret rulers of the world
I believe it was just the one episode I can't remember
No it was just rude
Applejack
In the mid-90s
No sick of gross and conspiracy counts
Cultural extremism
Light-footed Triple-S finesse with cardi B and
Did I talk to me about this
Residential
Flange nut
So I thought I want to do something about the recipe
Finishing
Gatorade
Heineken
Yeah they write newsletters
Yeah so how do you
How do you make
And then I had a
They open
Lathe
Fitness Secret
Room
Come inside
People in the world
Hook up with them
I'm going to travel the world looking for the secret
Plaid update iPhone
Inevitably we will be disappointed when there is no actual room or the room is for
That is that is like if Ponce DeLeon is like oh we're going to find this f****** Fountain to use
On a bat or or like to adjust
Despitefully Thor's buddies Lego where to find it keeps you 80 years old forever
Sequoia
Documentary producer
And I told him why
Tell Jen
Adidas
Similac
Annoyed
Heather Feather
Get a device can I would definitely stop the trinity
What are the best adhesive
On what episode of that you went with Alex Jones to Bohemian Grove
And I'm sure we'll get into that a bit
But also with one of the other episodes you went to Bilderberg right you went with the gym Tucker
Who's another big friend of Alex Jones is
Right I'll Kentucky show
Most of these like
Miss Elizabeth
To text Claudia Sven who would telling baby
About the secret room
Build-A-Bear
One of them said iMusic died Washington DC
Triple chat
Dedication is life
So
I went to Washington to meet picture
Sad
Good time
My mole inside Build-A-Bear
He said it was an accountant so for one of the people who was going to build
He said that yeah I know what that beat
Hotel
Airport
I don't get it go
Can I come
Yeah it's a
Find
Looking at like Jim Tucker's things at Alex's. Cuz he's been at he was in I believe endgame
Make peace with him going to Bilderberg it seems like
Did he let you wear his hat
Is the only quite right now it's a great hat you should have taken it and he's got 30 more
Smokers you always have that light coming in through the smoke
Tired
Sorry for interrupting your question
Yeah it was it's amazing that he
Gratefully lasted so long
Couple of months later I was going to be set
A Portugal Africa
All the tests
As long as he did
Considering he wrote for The Spectator and you know like this kind of it anti-semitic rag
Yeah
I'm people
I'm busted noten
I don't think so naive
The auctioneer
When are you I was going to go with the sky
Portugal
Lisa give day
Trulicity
I thought you know I'm not
Antivirus apps
I'm just kind of like
Go Idaho
I think I probably gives you an ability
U2
Not by us yourself as what time would like
A decision that this is stupid and the person I'm going with his a monster let's face it we might find this f******
Who knows
The famous
Think of it a lot before.
Donut
Scooby-Doo
Russian
Maybe it's a ghost maybe it's a guy in a mask Noah's writing a screenplay right now about a journalist in
The Nazi going to find gold or something
Infiltrating the Bilderberg Group because we were chased Away by the henchmen sure
I remember that clip from that episode that was very
High tension
I already captured
Hey
Encompass Health at a Chase
What I do
Syed documentary
I could be dancing capture it but I think that in Fenton
Anti I found the British Embassy
I'm as being a journalist
I'm being tailed right now
Diadaptasi
I love you to the Bilderberg Group
Hello
The good news
Is if you know you're being followed
That probably just tried to intimidate you
Wow wow
Wow
What is the Dangerous Ones know that you'll think that they're not dangerous if you know they're following you
Hanging out with someone like Jim Tucker probably introduced that level of paranoia in
Alright Johnny
Name is Terrance you need to get to the airport in 30 seconds you're going to be gone for a long time old life is over
Olympic Drive
Back to England
You know what I think I was conflating
That incident that you had with Jim Tucker and the Alex getting tails
In endgame
Because a game and then it ended up just being someone who's going to like chili
It was not someone tailing him at all
Fix those up in my memory
Right
Freaking out
I pulled the fire alarm
I believe Bilderberg conferences
Use convince
That the globalist I pulled the fire alarm
In order to Spook him and get him out of his hotel room
Or something
And I I don't I've just think someone pull the fire lie do not argue it was his crew that pulled the fire alarm
Nothing was happening in the hotel room
Boring visual Justin Timberlake
Black paper
Alex
I'm fishing at my white coat and then the second time with it
Dab
Outside
Alex
Just going to do a real
Thorough interrogation of this
Guest worker
Delete. Clint Eastwood's character
But it has been treated
Which when we would meet
Bohemian Grove
We checked into the motel the night before
The Occidental loves
Alex and Michael
G7 Kelly and shove his pen girlfriend who killed
He will only go to the Occidental Lodge
That's what race is he is
Sorry
He doesn't show up and then his bed sound selection
I've been the next voting
Arabic
What happened
Adidas
Stop
Without life
Yeah just a little
Java
It's interesting that like that is kind of that that to me reads as something that's been
Consistent you know like just this
Preoccupation with everybody is looking at him and
Like it's not but nowadays it's transformed into like
He seems to believe that demons can jump into people
And so like when he's out in public you'll see somebody and then they'll go back at him
And it's a demon that has come into their body
Austin hits
Grocery store in Tomah be like I got the devil and it's because of being in his jumped inside the
Apparently only he can see or something I don't know
You know like that kind of offending of
Everything
Revolves around
At a certain point
Yeah I mean it's it's almost like he has to become famous in order to justify believing that everybody's always staring at
Whoa you know that's that's
I got to go
Offend
Famous person
A boyfriend wants sex
No one
Add acid to pad so hard to
Oh wow
Scuba Alex I think Alex
Today
Finally
Show
Okay so often
Build-A-Bear
Infiltration
I mean I said much longer
You did and I am sorry to get off track here
Just real fast you didn't end up interviewing some people who went to Bilderberg
You you'd like to Jim Tucker his whole thing is like nobody who goes there will talk to anybody
Categorically isn't true I mean you interviewed some people even on film
Yeah yeah
Membership
Is It Michael Dennis
Exchequer
Infinite light
Governments in Britain in the 1970s
The story about 2
Even even even if you do meet somebody was very willing to talk to you that's still like
You can still break in
What I meant when I said that what you told me about
Confirm
To say that we would strive
Into a One World Government
Is exaggerated
Not totally unfair
That's what he said today
Affected
Audit week
Business
The labor government in the 70s
The business was a good idea
So weird
Yeah
Instability of the world
With Becca
In the hot initiative
Jackie Hoffman
Define Peach diesel visual
Competition
Politician
So
Video
It's just so much more banal because
It's really just been being like how can we make the most money
Potentially
We would like to attract more money
Yeah yeah
ABC Kids Atoka
IP said to have
Can I see some of them
Audi
No
He said put up secret with private
He said no
Speak freely
If they take the caddy quotes by. Turn left light
IQ
260 half dollars
I heard that explanation before the Christians are crazy
Lopez
No I I I think
There is
There is that reality and then there's the
The reality of the stories that are told
About
Things
Like the distinction between like a one world government that is basically
Along the lines of
You're not not a total One World Government button idea of international agreement
Anybody that is able to
Step in when their crimes against humanity that our country is carrying out
Or something like that that's the distinction
The real world is generally the
Do you know International body they can enforce International laws
ND
Fairytale version of it
The conspiracy theories towel is
Central thing that is run by Bill Clinton that seeks to crush guns
Webjoint. Long weekend what's the year they planted physical today yeah oh yeah
For the last 40 years they've just been
I'm preoccupied with
Taking away
Right-wing people's guns
They've been trying to do that and
Can't figure out how to do it
I'm accused the president's the keys
Prime minister
Ipac Nissan
What about this
Chizek man
The presidency in the Bible
Privatization
Thanks for the
Took that as a compliment
Wicked
I'm coming politician from the idea
Is
African
What bacon should disappear should have wise words
One story I was told with
In the late 1970s
I think around that time.
First became prime minister
What's the Bilderberg
Waze
With quiet
Mouse didn't say anything
Dotty's
Magnum sabadito
I told her that
Lots of ruining a great opportunity for networking
The next day she gave like a Bixby
I got much she went to New York
I would see what's New York
Like other Bilderberg people that you drove around to introduce
Hot like so.
Have Million Miles Away
Iron Lady
You're going to really need to up your Evil game if you want to become prime minister so give a f****** speech
NOAA in the same ballpark as like
A business seminar
Like people or people who have
Lots of connections Within
Could talk to other people have connected to this person
Pretty cool
You know that that
That's not the same thing as
You know being like hahaha she will rule
Or whatever
Yeah
Yeah and I think that that distinction is kind of tough to draw sometime
You know the area where the
The themes of some of the things that
The conspiracy theorists say
Are no fairly spiritually accurate in some ways
But the
Particulars of the narratives in the details are generally
Way off base
Well I mean you think you think of like all the billionaire he's evil billionaires choose the leaders of the world but then you look at the America
Consistent minutes like
What you can't become a an elected official without a lot of money behind
Find atleast on a high low level so who's giving them that money it's a small
Phone number of people
And it feels like oh well if we if they give you the most money than they have chosen that you will be the next
Elected official
You know what I'm saying
I think the reason why you have
You do boo
The substitute
What I said
If you can see the yield sign in the world
Jon Ronson would say you listen to too much f****** Infowars
American inventors
About face
Is the culture War
The distinction between Bilderberg Group actually is
Especially you
Weather today
Yeah I do have
Too many of my toes in
That like
I bet Alex Jones world
Then I've only been able to access a lot of these things through
Claims that are made and then looking at the specifics or looking at the documents
And things whereas you have
Open to people and you've been to the
These places
Yet so I don't have much more of a familiarity with
A lot of this than I do that allows a little bit easier speaker
Then tense up.
My
Yeah. I totally got it you're right I maybe I was a bit
Completely embarrassed and Alex as well
I show it I think it's the best thing
IBEW talentless gita-youbi-kamu boiled at spelling.
Text
Gp3 the one
Yeah well maybe I do something like that and then I move on to another one
But you've been in Alex's
Long time yeah yeah I didn't
Plan to
It was I think I probably intended something along the lines of what you're describing maybe like a year year
Year-and-a-half
But he's just so fascinating
Used Rubik's cube of insanity and weirdness and he always surprises
Like it
You know there'll be like just the other day he was talking about how Maybe
You know if your family
Is pro-vaccine maybe it's time for you to kill your family
Straight up in a bad mood
Fast food so we told you that maybe you should kill your family a better mood meter
Three fair you said things happen within a family it's a family man
The family
Questions to ask
Fast
Do you think
Like like I'm stressing
Fatheads
David.
It has gone
Oh yeah yeah
Yeah that's that's something we wanted to ask you a conquest
For sure
I jumped out to me when I re-watch the episode
Where you at him went to The Grove
And it's just
It was shocking
Much less dark Alex
You know
Yeah I'll be reminded of that
Yeah
Absolutely
Deprived
Nazi
I'm going to say
The time I was spending all of my days with the Nazis we were severing together
Coming in
Alex
Sapulpa
About
Oh please please
Appetite
Easy person
Be around
I could be sober
Millard old
He's the one of the most tallest people
Seems like be annoying
Tiring to be like
Yeah I don't like that
Alex
Stop
What a present
Call Leticia finding Alex
The only one
Raelynn
It's very funny very good qualities very as one
The one thing I would say is that
Arabic stop
Witch with me
I'm infiltration the Bohemian Grove which is one of the greatest
That's my last talked about fail
Tumnus towards capacity of course
What should I do
About
Democracy
Department
On a personal level
Isabel
The middle
Did you say archery skills
The great Bowman
I'm singing and son at 7-Eleven
Where we're from where America
Can sorry about that
The reason that it blew my mind that that was a possibility is that Alex has such a gun guy that
I feel like you're being hunted by a bow and arrow
All of those things
Black what are they come closer oh yeah
It's closer to a guy
Yeah and I agree with you 100% about the oratory skills like
I think
Even going back to our earliest episodes
Like a caveat that I always have to kind of
By myself
Very talented at a thing
And unfortunately the thing
Bad
In a very bad way
But
If you if you just
Take it as a ethically neutral thing
I don't know if I've ever seen anybody who has the ability to say nothing for so long
With so much passion
Yeah
District 2001
I went on now
Wiesbaden showpo
Notes
I do talk about Alex Jones
I got the same thing I said like
Jesus
He just talented
Bill hats
Like crazy
People hacks
Ripple effect
Play
I wanted to actually ask you about that C-SPAN interview because it's something that I have
Thought about it quite a bit
In that interview you save it
After going to Bohemian Grove
You told Alex that he was playing with fire because he was misrepresenting what you guys had experience there
And saying it was like this demonic thing and playing up those elements of it
Right yeah
Yeah that to me his response you said was I'm not going to tell the listeners that
Earnest
Right I think my whole
I did without it
Complications two decades after
At he's at
Playing with fire
Used
I heard you say things that we both know out true
I'm
Sad
That's awful
Welts
Like 13:11
If you fake
I think he's faking it and I would say
Example sometimes
When I met Jesse Owens like 5 years ago
Alexis cameraman
Whistleblower
I said that to him
Einstein
Was just completed
Ensenada
I think
I just was with that beam adonyx like it would be back Saturday to you
We got to think of it probably
You know that was back in 2003 when you went to Bohemian Grove new weather
Had this conversation
I bet he was
Much looser live
Maybe maybe he didn't even have that million-dollar Empire to protect
And at the same time who knows how
The years went on
Convincing yourself of your own story classic
We going to be careful what mask you wear because it might become your face kind of thing you know
Yeah
At the hospital
Completely
Fully realize this dog
Which system
Alex's is a narcissist
Narcissist
Relationship
Truth
Then I think that the pizza people about NASA
Daughter
Stop mean
That would Jetson him by the Rob
Traxxas latrax
What is a f****** alien
Can only have 12 psychopath sitting there being like of course you kill your brother again so you can see that guy
We saw the psychopath test
It says no
Between truth and light in Alex's mind
Like if it's lying doesn't make him feel bad
Then
Question 2 Davido 224 the shirt
That pushed it is
Elijah
Just like this
Is that expensive
Mine's wedding
Noggin ethical concern
At times
The budget is going down
That point you made though if the
The distinction between whether he knows he's lying or not like
Do the truth
I also think that that's probably the wrong
Place to look at it
Quartet
Pizza Hut
Then
Then the truth is
Truth is whatever matters to him right you know
The reason I brought up that point from the C-SPAN interview was that also in that interview talk about the
What was it the Phantom Patriot the guy who ended up a year later going to Bilderberg with a bunch
Two guns
I'm sorry Yaya
As a result of
Being an Alex and it's being dark secrets
The documentary that Alex put out
That's kind of
Where
I think the most interesting part is like
Whether he's telling the truth or not actively or aware aware of what he's doing or not
He knows he knew enough
To know that he wasn't telling the whole story to his listeners
And
Probably was aware that this guy showed up
Bohemian Grove because of his comp
Like yeah
He's aware of that
That connection
He hasn't Staples
I said a lot of things
Grady surprise me
Lawyer
That he spoke about it
Yeah
He made a meal of of that
Someone needs to go check this out without was also what he said about pizzagate
So
Yeah
Psychological
I'm sorry this
Here's to the Goldwater rule so we can't allow you to do that
I always just wonder like I think the most important question for me is always been
Vietbet level 2 witch
He's aware the influence that he has that leads people to do bad things
Like the Phantom Patriot or
Any number of other folks
Like a couple in Las Vegas who shot a cop
I always Emily
Curious
Because I don't know
B major
What is the capital of
Can I see you about
Ghetto how is and how could I figured one of those stories about it we think he was in Spotify
Try Road 7
Talk to his lawyer
I got your daddy didn't want to
Understandable
That connection is really into having you literally wrote the book on being publicly shame so
I think the feelings that one should have or one you'd expect to have a like
That was bad I shouldn't do that
I couldn't do that that was bad
Some guy went to the place I told the story about with guns
He's going to kill a bunch of old people
This is no good I should probably
That doesn't happen
And that's fascinating to me
Yeah I know I mean
I've not seen any evidence of
I've hidden cadogan
Wow
No no but you know that's kind of why I was asking you I was wondering if
Well I mean
He lying about
About
In anatomy that said it was the size of a baby
Within the hotel
Because he went he infiltrated
Guide
If I Ruled the World
Completely unnecessarily
Amusingly okay goodbye
We haven't had these two
Outback
The other one
Yeah
Naked again
What you
Exact statement anywhere
Like
You can do that at a coffee shop
Actually just had a thought about your guys
Infiltration of a human growth like
You went in the front and Alex use a little bit of subterfuge
I've always thought like well he could have just walked in the front
But probably he couldn't
Like he probably couldn't
Control himself
Like probably like act
Really weird and I mean he would see the security guard be like you better kick me out of here otherwise
Yeah you're right it's
Gaps in my memory of my life
Tell me about it's me
Every moment
Drexel oil
Lawyer who infiltrated
Gravycatman
Happy by Northern California
Guide
And he says
How to cook plantain
Red sapote
More
Reply
Addicted
Are you going to get yourself killed
A dollar
I go get that way. Kill
So we can read
Is off the table
The Ritz
Scrappy go to the local Eddie Bauer
The drive
Looking like you belong
He said
I'll come with you
Eddie Bauer
Weather looking like
Slightly exaggerated
I bet Hitman Mike
Practice B
That's one of my favorite parts of your your your filmed like
Big do multiple takes of Alex talking about nanotech
Insulted by
Daddy's microprocessor statue the size of the molecule
When do you think
Recommended the next one
Bison Pro-Fab
Abbey Ted's tobacco
B Ed
I agree
It's not great at Improv
That was
I know that recently he's posted a number of really old videos
Of Alex on YouTube
But I don't know I don't know other than that
I assume death row
Quite the opposite
Oh contraire
Download
Alex show
Bad thought of mind
That's it
XO night
The Inheritance the round
They struck
Oil
And it's wrong
A doggies
Wow great good things happen again
Alex
Transportation around like
Even when there's a video that he posted of Alex
Psych
I think you can pre
Or maybe during the like look like live TV.
You know the key they clearly
Had some
Long stand
The connection
But like I loved and I loved the two of them because
When they're doing this practicing being preppy
They're walking down like a porch
They're walking and they need to go back to where they started to do a second take hit your marks
Remarkable practicing Sorkin
Dialog okay
I said to them
Any contingency plan for
Stadium
Caught
I'm going to say
Runaway
I said so
I did I do think it was wise of you to advise him not to bring a gun
That was that was smart
Oh
About that time did you ever talk to Alex about like religion or any
Anything because he thinks that the people at
The Bohemian Grove
AR
Literally Satan worshipers who
Work for the literal Christian.
Like this isn't
Yeah the Java Jive
My friend Marty yells at me fairly regularly as a as a reference today
I got that loud
Noxious person
But there was something about being with
Rick the lawyer
Live by art by Chris Raider with Without a Face
You telling me that I was going to be fine
Could this guy Rick
Looks so much like he belongs like
He couldn't look.
Antique Garden before he was obviously a lesser demon
Right there's no way that he wasn't a problem
Did I view the Alex I hope so
Galaxy filming at in the bag
Set navigation to f******
Traffic light
I don't think that's an Alex's film
Baby
Yeah maybe it's been awhile since I've Revisited at 2
Yes it that way
In My Memory that was a
There was like exchange cut houses
Giant redwood
Next to the
Giant owl weapon bookkeeping
Sacrifices about to happen
I'd like it was like
This isn't like a weird
Sparklers sparkling flag
John Williams
Vacation it something you do that you do Broadway is weird
Yeah so what movie
Lighthouse
Today Show.
San Francisco
Playing
The office
Just get two drink tickets you got to go
Feel like I could get a setup
The Bohemian Grove
The passage to the underground tunnel
Brett meatball man spend 10 minutes under the Getty and then
Amazingly
Reckless life
Tesco
Lynn inside
Yeah
So
Hilarious
Alexis Alexis Looking-Glass
It has the XX in his life
How is
You had the perspective that there was a metaphor involved in
Of course demons on the other side
Which kind of leads back to work question you were asked
Jason Jordan
Zealotry that Alex demonstrates now
He's so
Bike
Satan literal Satan Focus
Like the globalist exist here is an umbrella
I like if you had a flowchart it all goes up to the big guy
Satan
Could lead to the story about Alex
Good life
I would think about it. So if
Katagiri when he was a high school
It would be cool to be high outside today
Distinction is
Was it hail Satan like rock and roll or what was it
There is a literal Devil with hooves
That walks around and possesses people
And I must fight them
That's a good question that I don't know the answer
Namenda
I don't remember
If I need liability
You do you spell Korean
Korean physicist
Yeah I'm done
Kelly
She said was to answer
He's Pizza that she's Jewish on the show before
He was one of those things that people would always
Attack him about it was always really kind of gross
Like
Your wife's your Handler for Mossad or something you know like all that nonsense
Well I mean what's the point
Infection with
Austin
Okay
Yeah
I think the word liberal means
Conceived
Mantra and concentric used to being Progressive
Meaning like assertive
Leaving Monterey
I'm Alex
Tommy
Electric Bakula
Yeah my son so so much of his earlier career seemed to
Like that like
Regular guy kind of stuff
Heimlich
I can't remember if it was in your documentary or another one I've seen
He's talking about David Icke and he says the David Icke is like the
The turd in a punch bowl
Half from that to hanging out with David Icke and saying all the same stuff if they would like
Like he does now
It's it's that's really interesting
To maim like
Yeah
It is right that control and that's where the presentation of
II
I may or may not believe crazy stuff
But
I'm going to talk to you about Banks I'm going to talk to you about communism
And that's gone now it's just
Exactly
I'm not going to talk to you about
You betcha
You right that's all
Gone
Masa for Doria
That's
Woodmore
Academic
You will do that globalist government overreach
Big black people
The crazy bastard.
Spanish favorite in Chester.
Why didn't
But it seems
Plausible to believe that it was a metaphor
Back then
You know
Yeah that's something that I find like
One of the things that I really enjoy looking at with with him is
The things that are different from different
.
And that like
Almost everything that I see
From the earlier. Of his career
Someone could make the argument that he's not being literal
And I would believe
I believe that like
This is
You know child sacrifice or whatever is
It's still within the realm of like
All right you're talkin you're talkin
Metaphor here about being
But now it's just not
Definitely
A gray area
When I do them though because the way he was talking to
Bohemian clothes with like
Maybe they actually online
Balenciaga band
Maybe we really did say it
An actual human
I think the word baby was always in
I think making out
Black baby
Chants of them
I could I could be something maybe we saw with the adrenaline flowing through you that day
I don't know
I had one thing that I wanted to do
And that is
I wanted to tell you a few things that I would set about his early life
And I want to see if you think that these lineup
With the person that you knew
When you guys went to Bohemian Grove
Or things that you know
Save a couple things here
So the first is he believes he's psychic
And that his career was preceded by prophetic dream
B12
The only
Adobo Bowman
You know what this wasn't
It's something to do with the tape
Application
Los Angeles
Caught with Alex
Psychic
What's hepatitis B
Yeah yeah
Translation something went wrong with the title
Dina Rae
I didn't watch the stereo
I remember Alex
Veering towards
Did they somehow cycle
Raised
Or was there a magnet
So that was
I guess that's
Very slightly into the hole
Pappadeaux buffet
Nothing I can maybe he's he's beat that up
When you went to Bohemian Grove with Alex on 2,000
Do you think the previous to that he had killed anybody
I have seen some
The catfish show
I remember we came out and offended face was coming into the parking lot
Expensive
Freedom
Yeah
I did not believe Alec
Defamation
What he like
Toe kick about goddess
The guy who I
This American Life
Yeah I wouldn't be surprised like he
Keeping
Jared so badly that would permanently into
Mr. calculation through
Maybe.
I killed that was kind of my theory for a bit but then he tells a story about how
He's like.
Someone's guts out and watch them die slowly
And so I feel like that
Doesn't quite match up with that other
Even
Further exaggeration
Possibly
But you know
You know what I like
Is
The Munsters
ProTech
Extreme violence
Black black
What he did today
Family Guy
I have a I have another question
Yeah if people want to hear that. Sorry that this American life is called the Jabberwocky is the name of the episode
Alex in Wonderland
Electric scooter with the Jabberwocky
First two stories the first tortillas
Add lollipop lollipop Natok
About
And I started in
You know the hounding
Ivan the second hostage
StoryBots electricity
Write as as as far as the teenage years goes
One of the most interesting things now I think is
How much Alex
His dad has
Become a part of the mythology
Like his dad has been CIA dentist who talks to all these
Lieutenant colonel's and who gets all this information that he can then pass on to
The Alicante was the smartest kid in Texas and he was this smart and he was recruited by the FBI for UT
Erwin spear exactly tried to get him into the globalist program cuz he was the smartest boy in Texas
What is Dad said no this is evil I will not
And then he told Alex all this stuff over the word actually
He told someone else about it now it's overheard it at the dinner table
This is
More the human resource director for a while
Rob Jacobson at quit
Or got fired at weenie put that EEOC
He complained in
And Alex's dad was the Human Resources Director who replied to that
Or was quoted in the empress
That's about it
I don't know if he hasn't
Experience in Human Resources it seems like a Strange Fire
Has to say about it
Yeah we've been outside the studio before
We've never gone in Belize gone to the building so to visit pilgrimage
My parents live in Austin so it's Uno
We've used that as an excuse to go in like
I was really underwhelming
I thought I would feel something being outside the studio
I didn't feel anything
Yeah it's funny joke until place
Wish I could
Smooth now but
Pizza place
For the outside
Domestic
That's probably for the best
I mean
You know what to put a neon sign up there
Crazy conversations happened here in the middle of destroying the world
Yeah
Anyways questions I think you were getting at is did you ever meet Alex's dad
Okay
No
It's something interesting I always want to try and unravel cuz my sense of it in the real world is just like
Is that was a John Bircher from
Wayback
MN
All the rest of the stories are basically
That's kind of what I say
But but I don't know
I always I always like talking
With people who have
Some
Interest in this stuff that I'm very interested in
Because it's
It's not
Two common
In my
Let's a personal life
Like to have people who are
Willing to have an hour-long conversation
About something like that
You know a lot of times these topics are kind of
Darker
Uncomfortable and people Veer away from that Palazzo
I actually had another question I wanted to to get to is this
In preparation for this I like I said I re-watch
The episode of The Secret rulers
And one thing
Really stuck out to me it's kind of chilling
And it was at the end
Of the of the
The peace
Alex is driving
And he's talking normally
And then he switches into performance
It's mode
Aw
One time
God could have caused
Wasn't
Dab
David Barker
So I can watch the wrestlers at 8
Have you done that
David Goshen rail exhaustion
Onyx is doing
Yeah it's Buffet
2 MB
Well I was
Try
Whelming
Sensation of
Thinking about David Alex
Is it
Time snack
Like it's in I don't know anyone who's Palisade
Ocean 2016
Black by the time
He let me go
I was laced with something
Yes
Film
I want to go out with you head and how could I
Dr. Gracie
Right
Exhausted I would like
Rolling Lobby Austin
Mesa weather
Go back to the hotel
Alex find out Alex dude form of hours only
Never slows down
Some of it might be drugs
But or his supplement
But also also back in his early days like
That work ethic is insane
The amount of work he had to put into
Piano doing doing his show those documentaries back in the vhss days
You know that is not easy stuff to self at it and
Dusty fix
Good job Bohemian Grove
Hugo film
Jesus
Carousel
San Francisco
Princess toon what's not interesting
What was that one might have been rushed into that would hit that one out to the people's quick
How many types of weed seed have do a pre-recorded big and have so many mistakes and it's like you can do to take
You can do
Yeah
Yeah maybe I'm giving him too much credit for the editor
Anything cuz now that I think about it a number of his documentaries or just him sitting at a desk
It was like I need
In your time with him
Did he ever say like
You have a point
Never did he ever even meet you halfway and towards like
Okay I can see where you're coming
The telephone when I
Accused
How about something to eat
I got that way
Lovett Library
That is
You're lying
But the big consultation between us Wichita
Meaning of owls that immediate Bohemian Grove
Refuse
Patrick Swayze
The woods
Corrected me
Remember
Philippine government records Florida
Would going into that little wooden Booth so that would
Send
Confidence
The Facebook
The Giant
I'm not entirely know I bet I didn't heard that I can always just assumed it was cuz Athena the owl is hurt
Symbol of the goddess of wisdom
Like I kind of just assumed that was the connection
Classical thing
Other stuff downloads
Wildlife
Coincidence
Yeah that was I don't I don't know
I want to try and do a live podcast at Bohemian Grove but I don't think it's ever going to happen
And I don't know too much about the place other than
You know what I what I've seen
Yeah
Externally it's never really interested me too much
Yeah I've always wanted to perform a human sacrifice in the middle of our show
Show me find the most interesting
Bohemian Grove
I can remember is that
Positive mypassinfo
Lambda
Wanted to do The Manhattan
K'Nex
Bhai-bhai guess
Gave the speech to gossip
Porchetta
It's a connection between Bohemian Grove from the
I could see Jack Parsons being at Bohemian Grove very easily that is
Went famously cold at the
Luckiest Place 1118 sir or something along those lines yeah that was that it was on that tape
Good work next
Interesting
Connection
Confirmation that Oppenheimer
Start of Manhattan Project there was that just
Floor
That you know of
Without looking
Feeling
He's at that age.
Documents
Effexor
Well it isn't
Kind of
Believe it almost as like a shark tank
You know the Green Brothers like a shark tank for the powerful
Picture ideas about power
TED Talks
It's like a trade chauffeur for billionaires to
Yeah but I went like it either
How to protect that you try to do to the power
Yeah I like most things it's actually really boring
I just remembered one thing that stuck out to me to from Alex's obsession with the old people
On the streets
Now watch
Buddy South band Pig on between Southampton
I feel like that's not weird I've been to like bonfires in the woods
Okay I think it again this is something I like
I caught member whether I know for sure to do with the by Bachchan
That is a Bohemian Grove
It's about these guys
Where you at
Midday
Look I've never
Magnificent
The Cremation of care
Is we are building
Capital ships available in the market
Place with fake power
Shuffle bad
Sylvester two week vacation
Wicked
Chuckled and then the troubles goes
I will be back
Today
Well done sir
Welcome
Fire
Cat
Jessica
The I am jump
Cabela's what drug can
PIX11
Flashlight
I see it is just
One of the guys who made the whole thing they're a bunch of old dudes there's some prostate problems he doesn't want to tell everybody
A part of the ritual
The night before
Cody's
You remember why you still do those exercises you do
Sadistic
Crystal man
Document
Bacchanalia
Little bit of distance
The place where you can cut loose and do things like
Little bit of away
I hate I hate to go back to the pissing
I mean I may need to just for the sake of like
It's still it seems like a side thing of the ritual of like letting go of care
You know like it's it's one of the manifestations of letting go of it's not like
Hey
Look rule number three is we piss everyone
The reason that this sticks in my mind
It's because every time Alex talks about the elites
Mistreating us
Not every time but very regularly he'll say they piss on us
Edit
Going back in and watching that
Sticks out and he's had so much
That these people were peeing on a street
It seems like a preoccupation of his b pissed
I think
That painting is probably more appealing girlfriend
The main thing
Educated World reaction
Procurement
Now now I'm dreaming that it is the main thing yeah
I'm sick of you right now
Yeah
I must be free to pee
Well I'm willing to accept that it's more of a thing that I had then I realized
That it's not
Cisco's
What other question I had was
What what was your experience of seeing
Like Alex
Come
That like
Joining up with Trump like when he
When he became a trump fan
Seem
Weird to you as it did
Yeah
It was
I thought it was just
Worse
I felt lineup
All the people I've interviewed over the edge
Like if you said to be one of these people is going to have
I would definitely
I hope it's not
You hung out with knobs
Lisinopril
Of the BS
Chuck
Actually
Yeah
But even taking the proximity to power piece of it aside
Like
What are the things that I've always thought about Alex
This is like he was Ron Paul guy for for many years you know like
That's a really fun thing to do because Ron Paul is never going to win
It's never going to
To be an option for you to be the person
Who is alongside the elected president
You know and
I wonder
If the getting involved with Trump was because it seems like
This is an impossibility
Yeah and then they sort of backfire
I don't know if she's happy
Quickly or not so I can show he probably has
In case you would want to be games
Sure
He was watching Alex the results
We're coming in
I'm looking more and more likely
More more
Worried
Black
Upset
Overwhelmed
Black history first insta
I've made a very bad choice
He was drunk and was like if the culmination of like a 52 hour marathon
It was a disaster
Yeah I did actually I did watch election Night Live
And it was
Was kind of heartbreaking
For the reason
That Lake
It's like
Owen Shroyer Alex Jones Rodger Stone of the up drinking champagne
And what they were doing instead of celebrating Trump's win really was they were watching
Video streams of Hillary event
Where people were crying
And like it was Multicultural group
So folks crying
And then it just a bunch of white people laughing and drinking champagne
Juxtaposition of those images.
It's something it's never really left
Really ugly
Yeah
That's how you know that
That tracks with the because they didn't enjoy Trump's win
They had that they didn't want Trump to win but they enjoyed the winning so much as it created the same thing could laugh at
The story that he just told about Alex getting increasingly nervous is
Because whenever they again out later on when they're celebrating
They can't just be like hooray Trump won they have to
Fixate on something that they actually like
Damages the tears of Multicultural curls
God
And it would have been a cash
Bonanza if Hillary is locked
Because thing in the world
It was the same procedure
And why did he did
I'm at the
What Alex is I could have watch it you and I can make more recent stories
Chrysocolla
Alex
Let me to watch if you do that I feel like
The domain
Ready
The stuff you said about
Dhaka
You know I just
How to spell Eli
He died I could call it still
What stuff
We got excited
Call all boy
Ball man get rid of it I mean it's part of the globalist plot to replace all white men
Men with people who will always vote Democrat well that's that's just like
Related issues
Politician I can't talk. I'm under the
Togetic cheelai
Gymnast in the ballet and Sheila
Lifting the other side
Los Angeles
Bus 26 hours a day so she could
College
Best
It okay go to that setting
Yeah man the amount of disgusting s*** he said in the intervening time. Between Billy mangrove
7 is more than enough to justify
Whatever consequences May Come
Yeah
I also remember him talking about you turning on him on his phone
What email
I'm not sure if he ever said
If I called you out by name but there was stuff about like
A journalist to lures you in with soft speaking and
That is stabbed him in the bathroom so it was
Kind of discussion
I always enjoy getting to tell people that Alex has talked about them
Particular way
We've got a lot of them
To that I watch
Watch too much of Sisyphus garbage
Couple of emails deepest I got off of you.
Waze
Do that sand baby
Loving you just heard about some of it here I mean that it clearly didn't impact you at all
It doesn't several years later
To do that
The bassist
Alex would it wouldn't be that big building David dresses
Waco
He was waiting
Smoke right
Melissa
Xraw mirabai Ceiba said he had
Inspired
The cast of Rambo
And he was like at your work
So yes
Lexington with all of that
Stage nexersys
Stabilitrak
Christopher gartin the minister
Yeah he would later turn on Bogue rights Alex definitely does not like that dude
Little bit later on
I think that there was a
Strong suspicion
I'm on a lot of people in The Patriot community that Beau was a fat
Are or something along those lines you fell out of favor with a lot of
The books
What day was
He's been on Alex's show quite a bit
Yeah usually
Apparently regular gas
Indian poker
Tool
At the house during standoff
Oh wow
I didn't realize that Jack was one of them
Let's Nacho
How old is how I feel
Which was Alexander Weber story
I got to wait for check check today that he's never been to
Wake up with them
Local radio guy with
Videotape
Everybody on the road trip to Waco
As we drove in
Light rock
Listen to no not that
Fabian Nations
Fullback
Honestly what he saw
Alex
EBay
Oh my God
85in black delicious
Pacific Ocean
People who use a lot of short wave
I'm ready fiber Sedlak Austin hipster
Router routers
Really famous
Code
But I never like I never knew you
That he would have
Money and power
Or proximity to power
Dial Waze news
That he was going to be today
America
Wow yeah
I can totally see how you would get that impression but it's amazing to hear that but that was your
Like what
Were you were you aware like at the time I mean obviously you weren't like hey I'm meeting the end of democracy but
Future you were you got the sense that this guy is going
I could never do what he does
Presumably improvised monologues
Like how
Always
I think a lot of people who don't know like who just know from clips
Some 700 listen to his actual she'll probably get the
Bouncing off the walls saying all kinds of
He does repeat himself a bit and it's
It's kind of
But it was quite monotonous
At times
But
He has the ability to make it feel kind of knew
He sells the
Feeling kind of
Of excitement
When he can
And then sometimes you can't and he storms out of the studio
Like that with no
Competition
1150 Iowa
Likes
The only light
What's good
Isn't isn't a ball of Coronavirus
Talk about and think about
6/8 hour Lexus
Which would not imagine being a bear for the laser pointer out
Road Truman Summit
What's up with you
Safelite
I went to become like an hour or so
But I met some people I haven't seen in years
Big chop drunk
Decides to go back
Should like you do baby safe and got to find
Applause
Just like this
7:45
You can made it back
Just in time for internet
Where was I I'm going to have to start it from
I think was good
He was he was a little less off the farm
Then somebody's out there like Alex or her David Icke
Humor those people do you have David I don't
Alex Jones
Mythological
Think about that guy you wrote behold
Play that the conspiracy world
Waiting
Christian car decals
Persnickety
Yeah
We we we covered a couple episodes of Bill Cooper's show The Hour of the time
And I've listened to it number more of them
And it was really interesting is
Is that that heat
He also Lacks
A lot of that excitement that Alex brings to the table
And so it's within the documentary conspiracy world the radio
Conspiracy world
It was a vacuum that nature aboard
Alex
Fluid
Desperate
Live
It was like I listen to Alex Jones or someone else it was Alex's line
Sleep sack
Nelson Sanchez
Being entertaining
Yeah and I think that's one of the problems with the present day
Is it now that there aren't those in impediment
To beat your own content producer
There are
So many other people who has maybe flashy production or in the ability to
Produce something quicker maybe to get a conspiracy theory out
Any kind of
Create a competition in the marketplace
Of bad ideas that wasn't there before
Yeah
What one thought I had is
Hear it hear it then I'll let you know when
Even back
Then he's going to
Be huge or he's going to be
I think
I have a conviction
But I think that there will never be another person like him
Do you have a feeling about that like I don't think anyone could do what
He's done
I mean the whole isn't there anymore you know true
Voices explained
Futuristic
Stop
LaFollette
Plasma is bad as Paul is he seems to have some restraint
Like you to look at the
Sandy Hook stuff like he was a voice who were saying stop cut this out
Yeah I wouldn't believe that just based on people talking
Cuz they're all liars but there's actually mail
Alex Trebek then where Paul is trying to get him
With it with that
That governor on him you don't like not letting himself do these horrible things
Don't know if he could
Do what Alex
I mean to a certain extent it's almost like you have to now that you have seen Alex
Then you know the Faustian bargain of like removing all
Governors
Removing everything that would you know
Inhibit you and that is going to lead to where we are now
You know like there's so you already know how it's going to end if you choose to be Alex Jones
Which is a fascinating thing for me
Some people take that bargain
Speaking of things ending maybe I
Bye
It's been an absolute Delight to talk to you today is that the idea of when we started the show that
This would ever be something a conversation we would have
Is its
It's baffling to me that it wasn't even
Close to something we thought was possible
I'm the number of people who lie
Tweeted to say you going to do this
People with dming Mala peopleready beg
Tune lesson in this field
These guys
Great
Oh wow
PlayStation
If you're not a journalist known in the field stay out of John's Peak Downs
Don't hurry
You got your got your yet we'll be talking a lot I think was
Your track record is amazing
Thank you so much
People getting that check out your new podcast I thought iTunes and everything
All the places things fell apart it's not on all the places I think it's only on the BBC and apple pie
Podcasts right now this right now
Couple of months it's only
Cupodcast view Indian actor
I'm BBC sounds in the United Kingdom
In three months time
It's going to be like available after you I bet you could listen to it now.
Stephen connects the out to Alex
Alex Mack
Bay Bridge cameras
Very cool work side
Hopefully it's loud and
Incoherent
Alex
In color