Important
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Fix-It around where's for The Elder of Celine little bit about Alex
Jordan Jordan
Question for you what's up
My bright spot today is
Bright spot in his that I did finish making this
Congratulate
I've been sore for two days because of it
And I'm also now really freaked out because we have switch
Like iPhones
We had to unplug all of the mics and everything in order to move
Stuff around I'm so scared that this
Is it going to be completely f***** up
Let's see what happen
It's a move towards like a little bit of
Renovating the office makes it sound like
Turn down a wall
Moving a few things around to make it feel more like a working
Read
Decorating but decorating sounds more fun
Turn it into a work work the area
We got that process being in
In-motion
Is a
It looks really
I think it was a good
There's a place for
For the printer down there a little Shelf
For the
Space X actually a shelf
Like my old desk was just an L it was there were no shelves no drawers nothing
It looks more like a cafeteria table that it
My bright spot Dan is of course we had a wonderful interview with Jon Ronson
And everybody's
Response to that has been
Very very
Pine-Sol by bright spot is how great it was that we got to do all that
In Spanish
Was really hoping it would be
My desk
Carroll's open your bright smile also be my death
Really surreal week
Anime Tucker Carlson episode on Monday and then
Interview with John on the highway
On Wednesday
It's been a little bit off the beaten path
Indeed
It's felt very disorienting
And then you add that to a new desk
And you did just like I don't even know where we are anymore
It is a whole new world yeah I feel completely untethered to the last 600 episodes of our show
And now I've got new headphones on I don't know what
What
God
So Jordan say we're going to get back to normal
Switch when we talkin about November 9th
And
This is
Dumb show
There's a couple of parts that are incredibly fascinating
Really f******
Stupid alright
Amazon talking about all that
First Jordan
I think we should say hello to
Doesn't
So first Getty museum thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Solenidae
Thank you very much litotes motherfuker thank you so much
I finally realized
Start paying immediately
This fella is actually an old friend of mine back from the days of Columbia
Excited to say hello
Lego and I couldn't find the Hallmark gift theme for 600 so here is Ace
Subscription instead
Just about your now policy walk
Thank you very much
Start this episode hear about
November 9th
Contacts dropped
But it's also kind of a game
Alex calls somebody a loser on this show
I need you to try and guess
Who that person is now think about the news that's going on right maybe
You know good sort of
Picadillo that Alex has like
Vaccination
It is so okay
So my first instinct I want to say it's AOC just because she drink that soda and people responded
Was was that before or after the night
We got to consider that were a few days back here
Good point
I mean it seems too obvious
It seems too obvious but I'm going to go ahead and I'm going to go with
Kamala Harris
You are incorrect
Terry Bradshaw
Everyone talking s*** about Aaron Rodgers
Terry Bradshaw gets agates
Taking down to page
Terry Bradshaw Terry Bradshaw I'm sure he has his problems
4 super
Happy professionally he's not a loser
He's one of the best quarterbacks of all time I mean if you if you want to measure it by those statistics
6 bad it's not all about Rings or whatever
That's a very strange thing to do I mean you might you might say that he's kind of
Dorky commentator
Is generally a s******* I'm sure you know I mean you can't be in the professional sports world for long
That for that long without the
It seems like it's possible but I don't know
He's taking him it's just about Aaron Rodgers
Anyway Alex opens
The show with a
Jack dance
Bombshell
Piece of information that will be
The number one story throughout this entire episode
Repeats this headline about
1000 f****** time
Here we go
Ladies and gentlemen Tuesday November 9th 2021
You are a regular
You'll be able to hear me read you this headline
You just saw the headline front and center
Shannon says people are taking three shots and have quote no antibodies
Or covid-19 and are catching
They're answer more shots that's like saying
If you cut one of your fingers off with a meat cleaver
Way to fix it
The cut-off three more
Maybe slit your throat
Hang yourself
Or shoot yourself
Or drink cyanide
Put the baby in the microwave
Give fibroids
War on
Logic and reality happening do war on logic has been waived
I mean
Is the one that
He's waging right
Now
Haha
Because that one is intense and years-long
As somebody who
You're constantly bang on this drum but somebody who studied
Pharmalogic
Can College
I don't
Know if there's a war on logic in the same way that outer space there is
He's on the wrong side of that
I know from what I understand
If
If and let's go through let's try this life
If getting shot
Increases your immunity to disease
And your immunity
Decreases then you get another shot
Would that not
Exactly like
If you
How to finger and then you chopped It Off
Yeah and it would kind of be like throwing a baby in a microwave
Maladies
The one thing
Here is that Alex is correct about this
Does headline say quote
Three shots and one booster later this man has little protection against
Covid-19
However Alex's misrepresented
The contents
The story
This is about a guy who had a kidney transplant in 2019 and has to be on immunosuppressant
Drugs for the rest
Have his life
The article is about how he does not have antibodies
Despite getting vaccinated
Which event serves as a launching pad.
Discuss how many moderate-to-severe Lee immunocompromised people
We're having difficulty with creating my antibodies
This is really shity but it's also not totally surprising
And since this is the case with many vacs
In fact it's one of the really strong rebuttals to the whole anti-vax argument about how like if you're vaccinated why do you care if I
More.
That's really weird
Is this headline works for Alex if he lies about the content
But if you actually engaged with the body of a text at all
He's actually covering a story that
Pro Universal vaccination
Very weird
The really great case study for why Alex can never afford to go any deeper than surface-level on any of the stories
Seat covers
If you actually gets into the meat and the details of the topic
He quickly have no legs
To stand on his narrative
Completely collapse
So as an exercise I track
Text through this episode
If he ever said anything about
This article other than the head
Not once not once
He just says the headline about
X
And at no point discusses how it's about immunocompromised people
They had line is about 1 supposed
Pacific person who was the recipient of
Kidney transplant
Ridiculous
Adidas music
Hey there
You know they're saying
Get the shots it doesn't matter just have to might as well be Saline
I wonder if headline writers
The editors in the the people who put those leads
Shop Fair
I wonder if they have a real awareness of how much
Damage they into the
Visually can do
Isn't it it's an interesting
Hope they don't
Because it's more careful
You don't believe when you lead with the headline like that Alex can absolutely do that another
These people are going to read the body the article so it's
So you're like immediately the first line of defense against after it's sold out its someone enabling 22 right
Articles with headlines like that
The headline is fair and it is a summation of
The story it doesn't capture all the relevant details like
Has little protection
Why is that spelled out in the head but it's also not like
I think from a journalist
Call totally absolutely
In a world where disinformation wasn't
That's such a big problem that was totally fine.
Text more when I'm
I'm thinking of his like
I understand that according to these certain neutral atom
You're good
But we don't live
Yeah and I see this conversation, periodically on Twitter and up social media the idea that
These mainstream media Outlets
Big media entities
They really need to have somebody Wonder
Understands this information on the payroll right
Because if you did you could be like you do you know what's going to happen with this headline
So it's not as useful to
Folks
Like Alex B
I think the theory for why that doesn't happen is because there
Concerned they would make less money
Maybe
And I also think that
There's also a pretty solid argument to be made that
If you did play that bit of Defense
The enterprising people on the right with the analysis
Media sphere we just find a way to still make the same disinformation
Actually help
Is going to be one step
Find the newest yeah
Yeah
So Alex wise a little bit about this article and then he lies more about something else
Free shots in one booster lighter three shots and one booster later
This man has little protection
Resizer in moderna now have
What you're both based on Ivermectin
Your why not lie about that
Interesting
It would be
Surely some new deadly virus
Populating
Okay
Obviously not true
Even mean for a pillow to be based on Ivermectin put
The general claim Alex's referring to here is
Just it was a meme that went around on social media
People were claiming that the Pfizer pill is
Just repackaged Ivermectin
Hey when does Florida State College Pfizer Mexican
Oh boy
It does not take much
That was a fun story but it's just dumb
The Pfizer pill is an antiviral drug where is Ivermectin is an anti parasite medication
They operating entirely different ways and have basically no can
Connection
Fact check on this claim they talk to Doctor William Penn
Trivia
Professor of infectious
Diseases at University of Virginia
I got the best of nation I could imagine
Quote the only way they are alike is that they are both
Pills
This is Alex's relationship with information just like in a nutshell
PCS claims in memes on social media money
Yeah they say the things that he wants to believe the reports them to his already
Just up
Pathetic state of
I mean it
The little bit like
Like how
Abraham
Vampire Hunter
Hunter is based on Abraham Lincoln
You could say it's bad
The horror movie
I would love it if instead of tomorrow's news
Today in Florida started with
Based on me
Did Alex Kim Dover
Glanced at a me but now he's going to yell about something for an hour
Great
Seriously you should take this b*******
The Alex Jones Show
Minut
Impressions yes
Alex has
So I went to the gas that's going to be coming up
In the second hour and he has a bombshell
Piece of information
In about California pilot
Okay this is
Is this is big
Kuru
Coming up
Are we
Journalist on very respected also scientist
Major inventor
Who has sources confirming to him that Newsome
Partially paralyzed with Guillain-Barre a
And that is why he has not been seen
Days and counting
Moderna shot
14 days ago
Well I mean there's
No other possible
Sure
Also this guy's not investigative reporter at all we'll find that out later but
Also this is pretty bad timing
Coming for the scoop
To drop cuz Gavin Newsom made
Appearance of the vaccine clinic on Wednesday
The day after the scepter
So does recorded
And he was standing up walking
Sitting and looking very healthy
They got f
Sdr2 stand up to
Questions in a reporter asked about the rumors that he had an adverse reaction to
The vaccine
And that an anonymous source had said that he
He had
Gavin Newsom
Yeah well that's made up I had absolutely no impact whatsoever from bacova
The chat Noir from the original or the booster
Absolutely not no fee
Fatigue even though sore
I was busy doing things for
Come on man we'll get to that later
Respected investigative journalist has to say about this
Actually invented
An early Mouse
He's actually
The early search engine
Yeah but he's also gone off his rocker
He actually does have some credit
It's to his name
Investigative journalist I don't know if
It's one of those
So Alex
He's internalize this
Nation about
Allegedly Tyler Newsome Heaven gion beret
And he's decided that he kind of wants Gavin Newsom
Also doesn't want to say I wish death upon him
Kind of got a dance around a little bit
Fare well I mean it's
It's interesting to see a little Shuffle
He's doing
And only very very clear about this
Anybody
Really
I don't take Glee in the house Fallin Governor Newsom is but I
I hope and pray
God works
His miracles here
And that Newsome either be spared but repent and come out
He needs to die
That would be a blessing in California
Take it to go to the park or go to the mall or go get a hamburger
Go to the doctor go to school I mean there
Experimental deadly shot
Some dies
In California before our children died
Express
Yeah
He decided to take it
I asked God to strike him down
I always like it when I wouldn't do something like that where he's like backing
Fourth all over the place
Starts with
Let me be absolutely clear
Who did the absolutely clear
Hey not
Jupiter Ed
Myself a bunch of times but I'm being super clear about that all right
First preference
I want
All the kids
In the world to have a million dollars
Beach but if we can't do that I think Governor Newsom
Some should be killed by gun
I would like God to strike him down so if it
Listen to the kids
You know me you know that my first preference is no one gets hurt and all
Get a million dollars but since that's
That's not going to happen
I would also strong lyrics
Cute Galaxy
Has claimed that he doesn't want anyone to be hurt
I think he wants a lot of people
Strongly
We've heard him
Furlough
General lien
Consistently
So apparently Alex's changing the story a little bit now originally it was
That Gavin Newsom had Guillain-Barre
Maybe it's something else
Where's Governor Newsom
2 weeks ago
We had a source coming on the confirmed with my chores for saying
A partially paralyzed that has Bell's palsy
Beyonder a Bell's Palsy same
Different names
This is so not true
We're just going to go with that one you would only say that if you are making s*** up
Totally that's for that's braids
Hopkins Bell's Palsy is an unexplained episode of facial muscles
Weakness or proud
Conversely Guillain-Barre is a full-body autoimmune condition where the body's immune system attacks its
Nerves
Sometimes Bell's palsy
We can accompany
Ombre but only an idiot would try to say that they're the same condition with different names
Which is why
Alex just said that cuz you the f****** idiot
Yeah
That's that's real bad
Pretty pretty silly
It's hard to hear somebody say that and not
Just go there's nothing you want say
You're just you're just free
Yeah I almost I almost
Be your friend
10 Vietnam grudging way
Anyway also another thing that Alex does besides a lie is
Promote memes
Around
Everybody should share
Live show fiza broadcast today so you can share it
It's
Oh my God
Young people
Are suddenly dying everywhere
The man says while he's reading
Laptop
He looks up with his coffee in his hand and says oh wait
That's completely normal according to this
I'm going to guess
But this is some
Formulation of the
Guy sitting at a table
The house is on fire any like this is fine
It's some sort of version of that or some sort of take on that I'm not sure
I think that Alex was a serious high-minded person I don't know how much time he would spend
Promoting memes
Yeah I mean there's too many Ben Garrison
Comics out there so it's a waste your time on me
Yeah I know you've seen all those dogs before
But have you seen a dog
Label
That's true
We do need some labels on this ship I do like that song though
Give Me Back My Bullets
That's all I could think about
Fun
So we get this
Investigative journalist
Showing up
Play the gentleman by the name of Steve
Kirsch
Nearest Alex giving him a little in
Intro
Well we had dr. McCullough in studio with asset last Friday and he knocked it out of the park the true leader and he said listen
Bauer Speck
Really
It's on the ball like no other is Steve Kerr son
Absolutely
He's really been organizing the top Minds
That wasn't fighting this incredible
Rollout of tyranny that we've been witnessing
Alex just didn't say please
Is before
I've been trying to get ahold of that guy forever
And then you gave me his email address I'm at work
Crazy Steve has a really interesting
Sting figure
Like you made Millions like I mentioned that money founded Infosys
Which was basically Google before Google
Right like it was early search engine
Or not evil enough
And after that he turned his Focus to philanthropy
An early in the covid epidemic
He started an organization called covid-19 early treatment
Fun twitch stopped
Provide funding
The research that was going into existing already approved drugs that could be effective
Infighting covid
Which honestly is a great
Thing to do cuz no one was doing it back then
And the possibility of what
You could find
Is really
Important know that the problem with you saying something
Open like that is now that I know he's on Infowars right eyes narrow into a very ripe horrifying like
How is this anti-abortion somehow like a nut kind of level of I don't care
Early on in the pandemic of funneling million
Dollars
To research
They could be from a bowl
A wonderful thing to do
There's a drug out there that has promised that we're already familiar with
We were going to know that
Unfortunately he kind of lost his mind at some point along the way
What are the grants that his group gave out was
$25,000 which was given to a researcher from the University of Minnesota named David boulware
It was meant to study the efficacy of Hydrox
Oxy chloroquine
I found that there was
No benefit
To taking the drug
Didn't accept the result
And the interpretation of the research
And things fell apart from
As the pandemic has gone on he's shifted from promoting infective drugs
Being convinced that everyone's trying to conspire against
Drugs that he's decided are effective
Like hydroxychloroquine
10 + Ivermectin
This is predictably spoiled
Spiraled out of control into basically and
Strong anti-vax
According to a write-up in
Technology review quote
In May all 12 members of the covid-19 early treatment fun scientific
Advisory Board resign
Citing curses alarming dangerous claims and erratic Behavior
Most of the scientific Community has lost its patience
For him and the only real rolly is left
Play the hero to the anti-vax community
That must reach the point where he's going on Infowars to talk about how vaccines
Evil and Gavin Newsom may be paralyzed
The desperation is a little bit depressing
But it is what it
Yeah I mean it
Hard not to see the exact same thing play out over and over and over again whenever it comes
Comes to money and Sia
No no you don't understand
When I pay you this money
It's to come up with the conclusion that I want
Why are you coming back with something
It's not what I want you don't understand how money
Also I'm curious if Alex knows that one of the other medications that
He's pushing his like a potential covid
Treatment is Luvox
Which is the present
Pretty sure Alex will be again
And that even if it was effective against
That's covid and then I could help him not have
Yassin's
Yeah for everybody but it also is one of the antidepressant for the ape
I'd really be a pickle
That would be tough if it turned out that my meds
We're also immunizing me to Cullman
He be like damn it I don't even know what
Also I wonder if Alex is going to ask this dude about
The company that he founded
I'm called one eye
It seems like Alex is so obsessed with the idea that the globalist want to create digital IDs for everyone that they can use to implement assoc
Credit score
Important to ask this guy
Steve about how he founded a company that was
Nobby who's building an ID system that could be
Conceivably seen as the backbone for such a global esteem I would
Be curious if he wants to ask about that
It doesn't come up with Alex has no idea
Mark of the beast Unlimited
Probably going to ignore that one
Anyway immediately undercuts his own argument about Gavin Newsom here
I'm not quite sure where to start should we start with
Into the details
For close to two weeks
His face is paralyzed
After two weeks you can look completely normal
So he can go
Supposed to be
And so he
Totally normal
Now
Excuse to say
Well you know I was out of commission for some reason
When you look at all the
You did your investigations I did my investigations and they were all consistent with someone who is
Yeah what are these investigations
Call Jerry Irving
Someone was talking s***
That's mighty sweet of this gate
Inquiring minds want to know
Is your face paralyzed
You keeping score when Gavin Newsom finally appears in public if half of his face
Paralyzed then he was injured by the vaccine and he was in hiding
If he appears that he's totally normal that he was injured by the vaccine buddy
He's already recovered
Google really fun game that's being played where no matter what ends up happening Steve gets
Supertime that is predicted
Came true
Here's some free advice
If someone is pretending to have great insight and information but they also make
The prediction that boils down to a situation where both
A and not a
Gets to be claimed of the win for them
Don't listen to them
They're idiots
Also
It's important to acknowledge
But Newsome was
Missing or in hiding
You just cancelled his scheduled appearance at the UN climate Summit on pretty short notice
Even before he gave a press conference at the vaccine clinic on that Wednesday he was photographed it IV Geddes very so
Subtle and restrained wedding on November 7th
2 days before this episode released
Who was recorded
Even beyond that he claimed that he canceled his trip because he has Young
Young children and felt really guilty about the idea that both of them
Both him and his wife
Will be taking this trip to
Scotland during Halloween
Whose kids would end up missing out on trick-or-treating
August was actually an easier decision for him because he was only given a 3-minute speaking slotted
Pat Summitt
Just kind of hard to justify a trip around the world
For when his Deputy could
You just go
And for the level of nothing you're going to do that's just I mean
Alright so here's what it is
Alright
Go to cop26
You can give you 3 minutes Peach
And you have some nice
War
You can go to the wedding of modern royalty f*** around
I say something like let them eat cake and then we all move on with our lives
You know that's a good day and an article that I was reading made a good point and that is that like
In the past
When there have been
Rob black Republican Administration
It it been boring
Important for
Let's say the California governor
To be like Saturday
That was being taken on by the GOP
Has president
That roll
Is less import
And so him showing up there didn't really matter as much as it might've ryra in other years
The question comes into like
Please have the last Publika
Appearances
You know why
Cuz he had an
Giant empty
B space cuz he was scheduled to be in
Yeah that would be
Typically makes a lot of public appearances but his calendar was empty because it was Friday
Scotland
Yeah I know he had nothing you needed to do so you could take familytime up chill and go to this
Getty wedding
I do like to have that would
To be accepted
I would like nobody would be in like these people wouldn't be like oh that may
Makes perfect sense schedule and there's nothing
Taking my schedule then I don't have to do anything till Hangout
They're they're like now
If you cancel the
Then you just got your back
Schedule did you have to go do immediately have a backup schedule
Yeah
It's the simplest explanation and it makes
He always double books
Every
It's just in case
Might be
Very dumb
Cigna dumb Steve has a position that is just
Unfounded
In reality
This
Vaccine is the most dangerous
History
Then
The previous record holder
One person per million vaccinated
Just for 800 people
8 different ways that we go and look at that
To show that there are over 100
50000 people that are bad
By this vaccine
To get into these eight different ways but it doesn't really
Every single thing that he discusses
About
Substantiate this stuff
Is based on misrepresentations of bears
Useless to conclusions about causality
I kind of stopped and it's like it's so disappointing
It's so such a bummer
Much just very state
I was assuming
That the only place he could get the world record holder was the Guinness Book of World
Sure
You needed someone
Come out and certify it though if you want to go get it the book
That is true how would you how would you observe that it would be hard
I need to be
Omnipresent
Okay
Steve
Has this
Kind of flawed thinking
Where
He's put out a million-dollar bill
That his data is right
No one is taking
He's been proven right
I'll take it right now
Even
The number to people
Are killed by
That you easily
Whatever
Nobody
Really
Because nobody's taking
Well
There's a couple problems here you'll take it other people would take it too I'm sure
People on Twitter have taken it and proving it
But I also think
Okay this is not a good way to
To determine whether or not people disagree with you
Because people might think you're a s******* ensure I just not want
Engage that might be part of
People not taking your back
Like the World Health Organization is not going to take this back
That's true CDC is not going to take your gum 10 billion dollar bet
They're busy
There aren't
There aren't many things that have been scientifically proven
Viable
I think
Maybe Buckyballs are the only things attic
Exist scientifically because two scientist got
Drunken bet each other who
Make a better believe that the
1918 actually was solved by game of bags
Little known facts
Americano mower
So if there's a
Barry
Interesting
Buona Beef
About
The entire vaccine program
Between Steve and Alex
And actually this should be a deal-breaker
And Alex shouldn't be talking
This guy because
He fundamentally disagrees with the Baseline parameters
That Alex has
That this is a global depopulation
Action plan
Steve does not believe that
And because Alex wants to retain some
Some kind of rapport with him
Cuz if that's really popular in the community
Alex has to kind of be like well
You know
It's just a theory that it's a DE populare
God this is really pathetic
Yeah
You were saying that they're idiots they don't know what they're doing
Ignoring the facts of the science and just
Moving forward is suppressing
The illnesses in the problem by big Pharma
Have somebody similar problems and so are you saying
They're just idiots from a top-down or are you saying that
They're certain compartmentalize groups that don't know what's going on because
I believe my doctors
Global Force depopulation plan
What do you really think the route
Area of some speculation
I didn't know before they Circle
Yeah I think it's wishful thinking
Garcia said the vaccine is the only way out of this pandemic
There is no other solution
Early treatment doesn't work
It's vaccine or die
Magical thinking
Yeah yeah
She is right and they want to make sure that the vaccine Wars
Somebody's looking the other way
Right there
There
So
Just wishful thinking
What's going on
Yeah so
Apparently
He's talking to somebody that he doesn't really want to fight with
He wants to retain the relationship
The idea that the globalist a depopulation plan is a matter of some speculation
As opposed to something that's been.
Documented and Alex has been proven
You proved it
420 f******
10 years has a plan that dates back to the age
Which of the devil
Talking nonsense
Yeah I mean if this is
If this is his level of
Conviction
I'm starting to think he's not actually a psychic
I'm starting to think that you're the medic goddamn thing he says
What his prophetic dreams are way off if there is
That easy to tear down I suppose
Hey look the globalist
Exist now that's a matter of some
Speculation had said in the pet groomers are
I backpedal tomorrow you dumb
Dumb dick
Alright so
Steve I have no respect for really based on his present
Except for disagreeing with Alex
At least that
Take some like
Do you have the position
Yeah yeah I guess I respect that
But if that's not doesn't mean
Yeah I do respect anybody
Who doesn't immediately yes
And to Alex's bulshit I'll give him one point for that
For all the
Misuse of various data all the other points are gone
Yes and then this disqualifies
If your
I 840 example
Vaccine efficacy goes negative to like 104%
Which means that you're twice as likely
To get covid if you've been vaccinated
Opposite of the story
And we are records
Headliners morning explaining that their answers always more shots
Give you a negative immunity compared to one and immersing the answers more
So that's just a
Steve reporting
Fake misrepresented bulshit
I was a article in the expose that video about weed
Episode 209
And then you hear Alex
Just trying to connect it to the headlines
But he's not even talked about the body of the article
From the beginning
Main story of the day
I I think that anybody who repeats that narrative about the UK
Stuff is just like
Well you're gone you're not even serious about this
Find the most
Disgusting about it is
How
You can miss remember
The lies
Is told about an article
So much
That when you were
Keep them to Alex
It is almost as if you are referencing a
Completely different
Story
Making people feel like oh you're back
Get up with different research
Yeah played it being the same research you're just so bad at remembering you don't even bother getting right
Yeah yeah it's a bummer
That's a real bummer
So Alex has a little bit of information
May or may not be from a man
Maybe if I roll video okay
It has to do with stroke
People getting Strokes
And then something really terrifying
Are there different shirt
And you're a between 61 and 65 depending what test I've seen
I'll be patiently today let's go
Give me the shot
Simple form of trial that 65%
Blood clots
I'm sure
Cancel my Twitter account
I just got a notice breaking
Social credit score
Unsurprisingly Alex is going off
Very suspect
Sinbad piece of information making
Disclaim
It's not from any published or even unpublished study there's no data to fact
This up
Like I hinted at the
Viral video that is posted by a guy
Dr. Charles Hoff
It's not from
I like
A bunch of doctors in
Between 60 and 65% based on their patients set
Just one guy who made of
Video Gray
He's provided no evidence or data and the thing is that even if he did produce data that reflected what he claimed
Still wouldn't mean anything conclusive
Claims that he's done D-dimer test
Song people who recently got the Cobra drag
And it's 62% of them had elevated
D-dimer levels
Isis argument goes the elevated D-dimer levels are evident
What's a blood clot
However according to a fact-checking Reuters
Quote
D-dimer is a blood protein
Speed released when a blood clot
A blood clot
Begin
To dissolve a breakdown
When the D-dimer level is high
Handicap because of
But there are other
Possible causes
Including
Currency cigarette smoking
Inflammation
Or Advanced age
You could just be an older person
Sure elevated levels I do think that all those people who say that there are
Possible like their ammo
Possible
Causes for the
Same like result
Their obvious
There's only one
Different cars
Is coming to the same result that doesn't make any sense
I mean you're speaking truth here Maya
It look if you chop off your finger
You know that's like
Put your baby in the microwave
I can't dispute that or else I would be
Waging a war against logic
Even if Hoffa
Perfectly collected set of data that showed elevated D-dimer levels in these people
Still wouldn't prove that there is a high rate of blood clots among them
He still have so much more work to do
Before he could read anything close to a conclusion
But you wouldn't get that impression if you just watched his viral video
It's pretty emphatic about reaching a conclusion
It seems like what happened here is that Alex just watch that
Warsaw being based on that video
Any decided to do literally no further work on the subject just chose to
Report this as definitive because he's a lazy f****** liar
Also I just check Twitter and
Steve account is still up
Maybe he got his account locked
For posting some ridiculously false s*** but he didn't
It kicked off
That's just him exaggerating
Victimhood and being excited about it and then Alex
Just pretending it's related to him coming on his show
So he can exaggerate his own victimhood it's
The fun game they like to play
Now they're not busy
Their nuts
It's not like anybody's Victor
Do they got the time to
Find fake Waze
So
This is an amazing slip of
Patong on Alex's
Quite funny
They're discussing how the sea
CEO of Pfizer
Sir hiss said that
People who
Put out misinformation about covid and covid vaccination
Their Criminal
Because they've caused
So much.
I mean
You know but I figured the CEO Pfizer
Saying that other
People are the cause of so much
Anybody spreading misinformation
I mean that would mean that the Surgeon General
Rochelle walensky
I think that's
Right they are spreading misinformation
Order directly using the term
Get a function of the head of the CDC said
All they've done is lie.
Is yardstick he'll go to jail
He'll go to jail too
That indicates to me some Awareness on Alex's part
He's spreading disinformation
Piplup
It is there is a little bit of it this time
If I'm going they're going and they're not going to go so they can't get me on Instagram and by that yardstick
Because they're not going to jail how to say
Because ivy
Some b******* about that man's being dumb
Spreading misinformation
That is
Damn I murdered somebody what I was hanging out with Bill Clinton
So I know I'm getting off scot-free
That is okay
Maybe guilty.
Fun anyway it turns out that Steve's Twitter did not get
Yeah so my Twitter account was not to say
Suspended
And so
My Twitter account
Not suspended
Because you
I think of it as a badge of honor that
Then I'm getting their attention then
I've gotten those emails
Before black when I used to have a Twitter account
Mine
I'll get those they have to verify your account
These people just
Fetishize victimhood
So much
It's outrageous
Yeah I mean
It is it is a little bit of that like
These people really
Should we victimize them is that what they really want
It is something they want and I don't think you should give them what they want they'll pretend that you're doing it anyway
Goodbye
So
McDonald's Steve Steve takes off
Bad batting average of people named Steve on Alex
That's a real name that one's up on Infowars is usually repeated and it's always
I wouldn't I wouldn't want to Jordan on Infowars
An Infowars
Steve
Is equal to a real world
Scooter
So what is exactly what it
The rest of this episode could be a bit offensive
And difficult for some folk
Because Alec
What does start talking about the
Travis Scott concert
Oh
No yeah
And so if
You know that's something that might
Be difficult
I would advise Maybe
You want to skip the rest of this episode is Alex is
Pretty gross
And on the
I'm so here is him suggesting
At that concert
People who died there
It might have been a demonic sacrifice
Devil
Blood sacrifice
I wasn't sure about this over the weekend
I saw the advertisement
Houston Chronicle
What was Chad
I don't know if the artist
Travis Scott
But the organizers certainly is classically satanic
Sahel iconography
And demonic invocations
Classic tape measure
You got everything else to it
Holyshit
I don't like
Slither using class
I think you should put your own spin on it I think this is the problem with this guy
Is that they're just repeating old satanism
You know you got to put your new spin on it
Yeah
I think that this is a really
Disgrace
Angle to take on this
Because
You know there's there's obviously
Failings that happened
On the structural level between the security
Folks
There were
Corners cut
In terms of
The venue in the
Putting on of the show
And those are things
Things that could probably be solved by greater regulation greater oversight
In order to not have that conversation Alex is turning this into a demonic sacrifice
And that's
Really pathetic
And disrespectful to the people who died
I've never heard
I've never been like
I was
You know over the weekend
I wasn't sure if it was
Was a blood sacrifice
Dot-dot-dot
I've never said
And I've definitely never followed that up with
But now I am
Then I just bet I did some research
And I'm glad to
Discover again but it wasn't for the
10 million
YouTube time it was not
High blood
Yep
So I'm going to play this
I'm going to play all this like
I can order of the things that Alex says because I want you to understand how disorienting it is sometimes to listen to
So he's talking about this Travis Scott concert
Amen
He jumps onto a completely different top
That leaves us to that
Notify is lgbtq
Make some more
Politically correct
Tool
I hate somebody just because they
People use identify less than 1% is this
Advertising
This is BS in the same groups are not pushing
Pedophilia this destructive
Make you die alone and then
Once the majority of people are not heterosexual or don't have relationships
Family courts across the country
Our children are taken
To be given to these people because they don't have children
It's a nightmare system
Hunted like
The opening scene Planet of the Apes
Leg running from the system
Okay
Alright
I think there's a pretty simple
Reason
Explanation for why they're Rising rates of people who identify as lgbtq Plus
Is that the umbrella is larger than the others
More
I guess nuanced understanding of different identities and different
Attractions
I'm at the other thing is
Luther's greater except
In society
Some more people are not afraid
You know of
People don't have to hide their
Reality
As much as maybe they had to
To the Past
I would even go so
So far as to say that
The rising rates
Self
Purporting
Probably
Did you too
People no longer hunting them
Has he literally literally good
Yeah really hunting
That's not to say we live in a perfect
Time now where people aren't still persecuted
For getting them I'm literally talking about they were hunted like
With dogs
Aha
A fake thing that
Pendleton exaggeration it's like the most dangerous game was real there's a reality that
The rate
Of people who are lgbtq
Thank you
Maybe are no different than they were
6070 years ago almost exact
But we didn't
No because people were
Unable
To live publicly and openly
I think
But that is probably a better explanation than
Fertilizing
I have anagram
Gay conspiracy in order to
Make straight people hunted to their kids will be taken away
Yes.
Yeah I mean the only way to look at those numbers of like
Oh look
There's a rising number of
People saying the
Is to recant
Sexualize the past
Listen think
Look at the
Sheer number of people
4/4
To live
And also this 39% number I'm not
Totally sure I wasn't able to
I didn't dig deep enough to find the actual study
I saw Daily Mail article
Is working off of and there were some red flags around like
Article
That number
Anyway now that we've been
Incredibly bigoted home
Homophobic transphobic all across the board
2 hours blowing hard about rituals and how Travis Scott concert with a
Ritual
Every culture throughout human recorded history has engaged in rituals
Because of rituals
Or archives are powerful symbols
Ben unlock areas of our minds
And compartmentalised instincts
Of our ancestors
That's why
Geesh or butterflies and hummingbirds fly 345 thousand miles
The place they've never been
To make a nest
Because it's in their genetics in
Their instincts
It's programmed in
And so when you see a big event like happened this weekend in
Houston
With more than 10 people dead hundreds and hundreds
Wounded and trampled you ask
How does this happen
And then you see the big portal
Play Crystal Ball
Hands above
Shut on Saturday
Special broadcast
It probably wasn't consciously a Satanic ritual well I have to
Where's my cell phone that because now that time to study
Wow Alex is making a correct
Weird
It's so weird that he never correct himself on things that he is
Flagrantly wrong about
But on this
He said it wasn't a conscious Satanic ritual
I think it was on purpose
You know what
Over the weekend I wasn't sure if it was a Satanic ritual and now I'm sure and then over the earlier part of the show I was
Pretty sure it was unconscious Satanic ritual
Sky's the f****** worse
You can look at this isolated say okay they didn't mean
Whoever set it up and designed it
Travis Scott
Weird seeing strange
While people are flopping around
Do you mean like the older
Spirit
Program inter-dimensional e
These events
Not by the colors in a lights but by the art
Types of shows you
Humans are all basically psychic once they all get on one wavelength
Leslie take control of them
Killed
Daisy don't make sense
Are you laid out like that like it's pretty clear-cut
Cuz I wasn't sure about it and now that he's a
Explained it clearly
I get it
Bobby IV there's no other explanation
There's a demonic wavelength than anybody gets on it when you're at a concert and then
And then the government has
Has power over you
Justin
The government wants to do black magic
It's cuz they have debt
Sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry
Old Black Magic
What are the Middle Ages that goes back to Solomon's Temple and back to Egypt
They believe in all this
And they believe you need blood
For power you need
Pay claims to the spirits of these aliens
Tilly's Hannity's of
Dead children and or virgins
Anybody get killed but they really they're going to give you a lot of power
That's what this is is is a bunch of demon creatures coming down and grabbing people's children and taking them
To hell
Yeah so they have
Studies demons that you know they get power and then they have to
Deliver the blood of children
Vergence
Alright
I have a visit I have a serious problem
Yeah me too
I thought we have different
Turn serious problems. Problems
I don't understand
Are they
Are there are there rituals real
Or do they believe
Clarify
Demons themselves are real and they try to let me try to clarify your question
Are you asking
Whether or not
Demons are real or if these people doing the rituals just
Believe
Since to be real but they're actually not
I am asking
What does Alex
Masking from Alex point of view
Alex's perspective the rituals work
That's what I'm asking
Because we've had this conversation
3 * 40
I'm not saying that it's right
That's what they believe is real
It really sounds like Alex is saying we've are succeeding
I actually do know from other
Conversation
Yeah he tries to pretend that it's just what they believe right because that's the way you present yourself as a less
Insane person
Like when he's on Rogan show he'll pretend he doesn't believe it
Fairly regularly about
Believing that these rituals and they are demons that are being fed by the blood of children of virgins and
This is like
Dark Ages s***
When you cry
Narratives
Alright
You got to have some rules
Sure now I need to know
I got to have like an isolated list of
Who can do magic
Everyone
Everyone but I mean like what magic is real you know
We got Harry Potter magic is real
You said the name of the boy who lived
And then we go to the Aztecs in the Middle Ages are all real like what
Rrt
Now let's get even weirder with it
Any Asian religion
Dunes Realty
Okay
Secondary question
If the demons
Grant great power
For child sacrifices in the blood of virgins and stuff
Aztecs
Still like
Top of the world
They did a lot of sacrifices I think we all know how all of these
This civilization fell somebody forgot to do the sacrifice
Every human endeavor human civilization is ended like this
Actually I guess
The rebuttal to that or the answer to my
Problem is
Alex would just say that
The globalist have done
Secretly play more sacrifice
All the rest of these civilization itself was no longer valuable to the globalist so then they started a
Different one or because abortion
Okay all right we've talked ourselves through this
Isaac
Question is the Alex does believe that the rituals work
And
Things that the answer to your question is
The anybody
Can do these thing right
You've got to do something
Contact the demons first commit some horrible saying or whatever to open up the port
Porthole
To hell or something
Right right
Alchemy real
Can we turn lead into gold
Probably
I just
You know you when you open it up
These rituals actually summon literal demons now all bets are off
Can you throw bones
Exactly
Probably
Disgraceful bulshit
Melanie just lies about Kevin
Gavin Newsom
11:30 Pacific in it event today didn't show up he was
The Getty wedding
But
They say he's going to be at a vaccine clinic tomorrow in the morning so we'll see you that's
That's true
It was about vaccine clinic and he was also at the Getty wedding
I was just making that up
Another gas
Bad that wedding really does
Cuz I was like well
One of the
Piece of evidence that he hasn't been in hiding all this time
Bring that up pretty bad about that
I think we can all agree that it was tasteful real problem
It was just
Stream I like I'm so mad I can't
Stop laughing what I think it was
Classy affair
It's a parody of real
Okay
Your disgrace
So how is another Gaston
At the end of this episode
And it's dr. Stella Immanuel
Who is the
Pro Hydraulics
Chloroquine Ivermectin doctor
Want to believe doctors in the world
Who believes that
Various
Gynecological problems are caused by sex
What have you
Don't like your vulva demon did it she believes that
God was giving her vision
Back in 2011 short we are now living in Revelation
That something was coming
A Christian Hospital
Read the book of Revelation is today's news
Also The Avengers
Instru
I mean
Is that predict
Programming problem
So yeah my dude
What is it the 22nd of October when the 4th still open which
Dragon that was so
Sure
You know it was gone after
Sealers a sea lion
Yeah so we got off on a
I think if you listen to Stella you would think that
Revelation is upon us
And
If you get sick
Go to the f****** hospital that's dumb
Hospital
Pictures of driving people to stockpile on these medications
Maybe maybe you don't have covid-19 couldn't
Text Babe
I mean
Medical advice
You just love Sia
Especially whenever you see it portrayed
So
So there's
The phrase
Is the shots
Apparently
20K
There is not been
Time in my life whenever we have not been in the book
Congratulations
Then the mark of the beast has not been on the
The tip of everyone's
Officially the market
Anybody shoot
Bible
Biocell
Alex right now
Excitement
Tell folks where they find your book your website
Paul Joseph Watson
Cannot be happy about following that up man to lead the world in prayer
Nepal
Yeah boy
A little bit disappointed to hear this goes for the last
Years I've been operating on
Something that UPC symbols worth of Mark of the Beast
So many marks of the Beast which one
Prefer
In order to buy and sell you no like
Obviously with the scanners and
Southlake
In order to buy this you guys have a symbol on
I got at least there's like alright I get where you going with us
See I know I've always been a big
Bigger fan of the social
Security number being the mark of the beast because if you're undocumented
Then you'll go buy stuff though but I mean
That's why the shot is actually a fault
Nothing here too because you can still order things
Things to be delivered point where you can't go out in public
If you are on vaccinations you can still order ship
Contactless delivery still exist so
Bible had no idea that drones would be able to deliver things
Never was going to work
The first bible really should have
Proceed
People leaving stuff at your door
Dropping things off
What is Passover but the original home delivery
Fair enough
Oh yeah
It's like when they take away your
Unless clip
And it's not
Stella Immanuel prayer
That's
But I don't know how well I would have done
It might be one of the most
Disgraceful things
I've heard on Alex's show
I'm excited for that
Might be indicative of
Something
Maybe illegal
Definitely on ethical
Cialis for people that like I said everybody
Open OverDrive
This is a spiritual battle
Alex
Stella has
A promo code
Promo code Alex
For his listeners to get a dis
Discount on Ivermectin and hydroxychloroquine
I don't know
For sure
Haha
But typically whenever you have a referral program like this
Sure you get a cut
Like when I was 22 ammo code Alex
Set my pillow that was because they had a
Sort of
Yeah
So I wonder
I-10
Some kind of a financial interest
Stella Immanuel hydroxychloroquine
I'll tell you that
I don't know
I don't know what to
To think about this
I know that in the past
Alex has had like
Max Keiser tried to screw Alex
Is he at a Bitcoin kind of thing
So you could do this
Alex's on board with this
It's one of the boron
Yeah yeah that one's bad
Alex is promoting all of these
Ineffective
Skewers
And simultaneously
Has a promo code
Stella videos website
For people to buy
Said ineffective
Snake oil salesman
Go from
Hounded
You know they had to do all this
Is work
They had to but if they is they had ever
Dreamed of just like
Okay
All I have to do is give people a promo code and they'll just
By this ship I don't know
Even convince them
Banana
Amazing
So we we reach me on here and I hope
I don't know.
Probably invest
Navigate that
Beguiled
That's that's unfortunate
Back to Alex after this is a weird week
He's gross
Because those aren't those aren't supplements those are actual medications
Do you know
Real drugs you didn't pull this b******* with like
Yeah that's
DC doesn't give a f*** about think they should
Yeah right the reason that you have to go to Stella Immanuel cuz you need a
Prescription for the
This is not good
It's got to be illegal
Heather should be
Remind me to fix that
Yep
Yeah so sorry about that lot of disappointing
False prediction
Gavin Gavin
The governator than he's
The gavinator
So that was a bummer this Steve guy is nuts and Alex has decided
Concerts
Ritual
Fun
Any white will be back next week
Twitter
Underscore fight not go to bed Jordan
The sex robot
Holding
Alex