Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Dot-com
Around and talk a little bit about Alex
Jordan Jordan
Question for you
Yes what's up
What's your vibrates but today might be a controversial Brightspot Metro maybe one that people won't
Come on board
Okay and that is I'm excited
Hi-C
Didn't realize it until maybe like
A couple weeks ago but
Iambic
Pump the Chicago winter is coming
You know like I didn't realize how much I enjoy it you like a winter
I know I say that and then it's going to be -20 like Irish music
Is the nature of the Beast
Yeah but I don't think I could live in a place that didn't have a winter
I am it's kind of nice
Rattata little bit of snow
Yeah,
It's a it's a it's a nice thing to have the seasons change something for you without you having to like move
Over something
Like I just all I did was just sitting here for a while and things are different
I think the feels like the leaves fell off the trees
Like within a matter of a couple days overnight
There's a nice sunny day and then about two 2 in the afternoon it's just like it's going to be winter forever now
0260 I guess in this case
Fall probably the best
Sure but then
When is pretty good
As much as I love
Benno the island
I don't know
I like fight my might miss winter had that the winner is I'm an indoor kid
I'm an indoor kid man you know I don't like to I don't like to be outside much anyways
It's super cold
Give me an excuse to get back inside that much quicker
That's true and if your indoor kid
I can just
Bring snowballs inside your house
My bright spot Dan is surprised it was not
You're right but as well but
We had a bit of a fun time watching wrestling with the want to go watch
Aew full gear pay-per-view
Yeah off-air crossover episode I believe Isabel
Jerk people are calling a hanging out these day was a goddamn
There's a fantastic time
I haven't been to their place in. You know it's just great
I am going to keep the my review of the paper
Myself
Logan has not going to be a controversial
Probably not
So Jordan today we're going back to the
Past about June 27th
Okay on this this year episode
1 reasons for that was that last episode of the present-day
And I think I got it I got enough ass
Real dick
Did the bean
Some things to learn on this
This year podcast
I wanted to take back
Then find some mediate stuff to go over and I did I found something
Is it going to be really interesting
To get into some
Perception
That'll be busted
Maybe
Weather perception
Mark Mack in Mayberry r.f.d.
Text my partner's two cats are named Tom and Bosley and she didn't get why
Was funny thank you so much you're now about what you want
It's not the globalists but eating disorder that consumes kids f****** eating disorder thank you so much right now that was he want
Next you can't say that on the hpg network
Strange aliases
Not this one though hello you're not
Mr. Jones and me look into the deep state
They're rather desperately Global list
They're coming for you oh no no that comment for me I want to beat Bob Dylan thank you so much you are now if I was you
I'm a policy wonk
I like this message
Then I got this person
Thank God they included
A clarification that
Big habitat clarification literally Counting Crows rapper
And I really appreciate that
I don't know if I would have got that otherwise would have been interesting to see you read the entire thing without knowledge that it was
Is lyrics
Yeah that would be fun
Technocrat
Heroin
Freakishly large
Jay-Z in Olympia it's not
2 letters
Is Jay-Z a
The Illuminati know not the difference
Sister Beyonce
Do initials
We start off today's episode with some triumphant news for some
Castle possibly if he news for Alex
But he interprets
In a strange way
Good morning hours yesterday
If you hate me
You're calmer
Did you care about more
U.s. attack
Excuse me sir is text because he cared about black people
I think this is an interesting take on Strom Thurmond and why people would call him racist
Wow this is full of s***
Princeton's even in the information that Alex
Provided in just back
I clip you might end up like if you
That's all you had to go on you might ask yourself
What did Strom Thurmond go from being a Democrat or Republican
It seems like something that maybe was a big decision for him I wonder if a lot of people at the same time
From being Democrats become Republicans short version is that strong was a huge racist in the Democratic party wasn't race
Enough for him anymore not anymore so the longer version is that in 1950
Text many Southern Democrats or Dixie
Secrets as they were known after they went a little rogue and
In response to Harry S Truman sporting some civil rights
Hi in the 1948 election
Dixiecrats were really pissed off about the Supreme Court
Decision in Brown versus
Board of Education
Which rule that racially segregated schools were
Constitutional
In response
112 of the 138 members
Congress from Southern states signed what they called
The southern Manifesto
This document
Insisted that the Supreme Court had no right to meddle in the matters of Education
People of different
Races had to go to separate
Protecting that right was critically important
States rights
Dan it's not it's about the federal system getting out of our business
To protect the Constitution
Absolutely
They pleaded that they should be able to
To keep their whole separate-but-equal thing
Then going and blamed efforts to
To desegregate on quote outside meddler
What I've never heard that
But they have been f****** up the
Progressive Movement for so long effective
Overtime
Defeated outside Battlers they warned
Integrate schools was going to destroy the amicable relations between the races
Literally that's in the southern Manifesto
Declared the intention to resist
Forced integration by any lawful meme
So strong Thurmond as a southern member of the Senate was a massive fan of segregation
It was a losing battle he was fighting as the tide was
Trending toward civil rights
F****** hard
That brings us to August 28th 1950
B7 when Strom Thurmond embarked on the longest filibuster in history
Derail the Civil Rights Act of 1950
A large part of which have to do with protector
Black people's right to
Well there is that
You filibustered for 24 hours and 18 minutes
But the bill passed a couple hours after he ran out of space
YouTube essentially nothing except making sure people throughout history would remember him as a record-setting racist
Play forward a few gears in lb
BJ he just signed the Civil Rights Act
Active 19-6
Is it outlawed
Discrimination on the basis of race color religion sex and national origin
Discovered voting issues public accommodations public facilities education and employment discrimination
I'm so easily imagine the races were really not happy about thought they weren't
Stokes lbj's assistant Bill Moyers has quoted Johnson the saying quote I think we just delivered the South to the Republican party for it
Long time to come
After he signed the bill
And at the time he couldn't have possibly known how right
The cracks were there cents
The Truman Administration to embrace of civil rights
NFL BJ shape was the
Just too much
The Republican Party would sooner
An attempt to win over white Southern voters by explicitly appealing to their races
This was essentially the point where the parties
Completely change their identities from what they were previously
How many of the Southern Democrats
Became Republic
Are there still some races democrats for sure but a lot of the heart
Corfo
Looks like a guy who
Would speak for 24 hours straight to try and stop like
Guaranteed
They just made their job
To the Republican Party
Santa Baby
Not to put too fine a point on it but Strom Thurmond has essentially synonymous with race
Even though he did so often as time
I like a vote in favor of making a holiday in honor of Martin Luther King jr.
His legacy is impossible to separate from his horrible racism at a time when it really mattered a lot
The fact that Alex
Can't even accept this
Very clear reality of History
Indication of how entrenched his own races
Even in 2000
He's a little publicly less
Angry about it
You know what what
Wild about
The Strom Thurmond thingy
I remember in my
Freshman
I'd like
History class we were
You're talking about
The president pro tempore of the Senate being fourth in line
For becoming
President
And I was like who is who is that now and then
Well they usually just give it to the oldest senator
And it was Strom Thurmond at the time and and I was like that's really funny it's the oldest Saturday
And she just looked at me and she was like
Yeah I wouldn't
Like Strom Thurmond if I were you
Do you know what your job should be
Hey Strom Thurmond was a giant racist who filibustered for over 24 hours
The end civil rights as we knew it it's a good it's a good thing
Instead she was like
You know what don't work
Let's just hope that
The top three stay in
Stay in line
So Alex has a what about game
Play with Strom Thurmond
Come on man be racist because someone else was
Really
His
Tired
I got viralix I wouldn't want to get into a big
Discussion about this too cuz
The specifics and up
Making this argue
Fall Apart
Sooner or later when you're defending
Strom Thurmond you're going to be the guy who says something and you go now I didn't mean that in a races
Thurman segregationist views were not just in 1957
They're all so well after that point like when he left the Democratic party because they were too against segregation
A taste
Alex does make a good point about Senator Burr
I will admit that
That was also a piece of s*** and was deaf
Muttley in the clan
There's no real evidence that he was involved
Mcclam passed around like 19
50 though
AliExpress the great deal of regret
About being a member later on
In the name of fairness though I don't think it's right of me
To say that it's cool to look at bird differently because he
You changed later in his life
When I'm still sticking at the Strom Thurmond even though
He did change a little bit as time went on as well
I have a perfect solution to this problem though and that is to say f*** both of them
You got it yeah
Now the only reason I'm really getting into this at all is be
Because
There's a
Perfect example that Alec
Looks good use to make this same argument
Hunt better
But he doesn't
Which is strange
Alex
Instead of bringing up bird
You should be bringing up George Wallace
Considering that he was a hardcore segregationist
Has he famously said segregation now said
Aggregation tomorrow segregation forever
What was what
Antique races and he was running for the Democratic presidential nomination
Turn all the way up
The 1976
There's a reason
Examples of racist in the Democratic Party
I'm at because he has to believe that George Wallace season 2 racist
Or else his entire world you suddenly starts to look really racist
There's a huge problem that he was a candidate that the John Birch Society was most into and that alone to make
Alex not want associated with a
Very clear racism in body
Then there's the other question that is disassociation would bring up
Which is at the book
6 credits with changing his life
Is none dare call Atkins
A sea which was written by Gary Allan
If not
The most popular writers in
Speakers of the John Birch Society
It was also George Wallace's speechwriter
Honestly Island was his speech writer on the presidential campaign
The first of which launched in nineteen
MP3
The same year
He said his famous quote about segregation forever
It's not impossible that Island had some hand in those words
Then you have the issue that one of the big backers of Wallace
1968 Independent party run
A president was Willis carto
The white supremacists and neo-nazis who founded the Liberty Lobby
Hip-hop was the spotlight
Baby holocaust-denying publication that was edited by Alex
Friend Big Jim Tucker
Who is Alex's MainSource on Bilderberg Inspira
When you pull on George Wallace unravel in Waze
How to make it to clear that out
World and his formative influences are all profound racing
That's why even though George Wallace will be perfect
Example to demonstrate Democratic racism at the time
Strom Thurmond
In civil rights.
Alex wouldn't go with
Bird who has the
Is a decidedly racist past but no real indication of that Clan Association
I'm continuing into the p
. we're talking about
The out can't afford
To use the perfect example short
I find that really interesting
That is Irene
Cuz I was sitting there listening like
Don't you use Walla Walla
Instantly the moment
You say Strom Thurmond I'm like yeah it is good buddy George Wallace
That's the way
It works
Add for him to just have
To sit there and be like
Who can I find
Alex doesn't like a lot of these
People in the Republican party at this
Molly's neocon
Are all secretly liberal
They only want segregation a little bit
George W bush
Trent Lott
Orion Alex
Is crosshairs
For the wrong reasons
That's not your fault
Cheerleader
New World Order
Wow
So I guess if your male cheerleader you getting
I am
Boggle
Why
If that is what you would expect but it's like I'm above all things
Yep that's all things going on right now man must
Adhere to the strict
Rules and roles that I have delineator for them because they're
Divinely-inspired or something
It's like you don't even know anything about male cheerleading at the time
There's a massive competitive cheerleading shoot going on in the male cheerleaders
Incredibly important
Building building a base stand on
I need to create another version of V like you can't trust a male nurse
I totally
These things are fun
Excuse me
Stewardess
No sir
Sir sir I know you're a man but
If you're doing this
Job
Ridiculous
Publix
Alex
Augusta on the show that somebody that I have not heard on his show before
Character by the name of John Andrews
I was at the point
Who's the president of the Colorado State Senate
Controls on what identification
People could use
Things like the Consular
Dracula cards
Like the Mexican consulate give out these identification cards
Let's do Mexican Nationals living in the United States
And he's mad about the
And so we're going to talk about it a little bit
Listen to
Hey knock it off
Settings
Empowering fellow
Call I mean that's just so you know undocumented immigrants
Photo IDs at the Met
Can consulate can issue to Mexican
Animals living outside of neck
These are very helpful particularly for Mexican immigrants living in the night
Red States for a number of reasons
The first is that they allow consulates to be able to track and locate people much
Easier than they would be able to otherwise in
In the case of like an emerging
The second reason is that they are considered valid ID by many states
Special and immigrants have any
Imitation status
Best to apply for a driver's license
And
It allows them to pay taxes
Further sent to the matricula card
Is a valid ID they allow folks
The ability to open
George's
A pretty important
1 things they
I don't do is confirm
Any sort of immigration
Status upon the holder of one of these cards
It's just a secure official
Difficult to forge form of identification
Who makes everyone's life easier
If you guys are super gay
So essentially
Because States and America won't
Give people ideas without
Having already
Got photo IDs or whatever
This has to
Has Mexico and their take Hannah
Being able to
Know where citizens
Mexico
Society then-president of the Colorado senate about a bill he was champ
Call the Colorado house bill 1224
The secure and verifiable identity
This act wasn't designed to have the Mexican consulate
Stop issuing these
These cards because that would have been a violation of the 19th
63 Vienna convention on Consular relations
Instead This Act was aimed at making it so stain Local H
In season Colorado could quote
Only accepts
Secure and verifiable document
Which event was
Defined as not being these things
This was essentially Just a Bill designed to make immigrants lives more difficult by doing things like making it so people who
Have Consular ID cards
Can't use them to get drivers license at a bank
Folks like Andrews often try to catch their motivations as being about keeping people safe and making
I'm sure the people can't exploit the system
But the reality is that this kind of bulshit hurts a lot more people than just on documented immigrant
It'll be really naive to imagine that Andrews isn't aware of that
In 2006 a report released by The Brennan Center for justice title.
Citizens without proof
Which is aimed at analyzing the effect
These restrictions on getting identification
Navigation have
Or have the potential to have
On US cities
Themselves
They found that 7% of US citizens do not have ready access to the document
That's that would be required
Where to get a driver's
Under these new laws
But I just don't have the documents to
However this number actually goes up to twelve percent
When you only include people who make under $25,000 a year
Additionally 34% of women of voting age had a document they prove their citizenship
But it was
Something that included there
Current legal name
Oh yeah well these are like real difficulties that people who
Citizens would have under these restrictions
On the sake of
Essential
Racism
Wolves control
What they consider like
Trespass
Yeah if you if you if you
If You Can't Ban
People
Then you can just
Make their lives
Miserable enough
That they want one of
That's
The other
Just let you know what kind of a s******* this guy John Andrews is
Summer
Excerpt from a speech he gave at the 2019 Western
Conservative Summit
The theme of this Gathering was
Defending religious freedom and America's First Amendment
Segregation now segregation then maybe
Asian forever
So he begins by extolling how great and important religious freedom is
Unless every American is free to honor God as conscience may God and obey God in the Public Square as long
Is no one else is armed
Unless we are free and that precious way we are not
Free at all
So far so good
As long as he's talking about all religious beliefs and also the absence of religious belief I can go live with him
Absolutely. You lose me pretty fat okay
Preserve the Conte
Now let's talk about what freedom of religion does not
All right I will speak with tough love
From the heart
With no animosity or ill-will toward any person
Let me please hear me carefully
Who's somebody originated the belief system they claimed exclusive right to revelation
The command from above
Harness that aggressive claim to a burning sense of victimization
The wound from within
What Loose Cannon that would be
Suppose its claim of Revelation included a totalitarian political and economic
I'm not subject to Reformation
Set forth in a holy book not subject to revision
Suppose it's legal Scholars and clergy insisted the day is coming when that book must govern all mankind
On penalty of death
After whoever would refuse to submit
Suppose finally the biz belief system have been around for over a thousand years deepening its evict
Complex
Reinforcing its unbending absolutism in its dreams of global Conquest
Until today commands the allegiance of a
Quarter of the Earth's population
On every part of the Earth's surface
I'm talking about the belief system called Islam
Speed now what
So odd about that
Well
Hello to get mad I was worried that he was a radical islamist
Exact
Same thing about
That's so weird
Islam isn't protected by the freedom of religion in 2019
He goes on to clarify a statement by saying
It's true we all know Muslims were likeable neighbors or capable coworkers
Decent patriotic American to humbly love Allah
That's not what I'm talkin
Think about what
But that's absolutely what he's talking about
Horribly murder is totalitarian victimhood obsessed
Cold that includes a quarter of the world's population
Cute including in that plurvy nice Muslim neighbors he's pretending to not be talk
About
This is abject demonization
Of all Muslim
Pretending to be an opposition to Terror
Just a few paragraphs after he says that he's not talking about the nice Muslim Neighbors
He literally says
Quote
Simplistic approach of
Just granting unconstitutional quote on quote freedom of religion
Religion that doesn't believe in Freedom and have no doubt Islam does not
That approaches civilizational suicide
Wow
MSP she goes on to say quote
I'm sure some of you will disagree with me
So will some other speakers this weekend
They will tell you that a good and faithful Muslim can also be a good and faithful American
Sorry
I don't see
See how
Wow that's on you yeah
No problem easy that's an easy fix yourself
He goes on to say that Americans name their two enemies who are marks and Bahama
Oh man it sure seems like it
Just that
Ever suck
2003 is apart of the Colorado senator
Intense hatred of Islam
He's a
Xenophobic assholes reviews America as a white Christian country
Denny's dedicated
Pursuing pilot
Let's support that view
The only thing I'm left in confusion about
Like when I look into this guy's leg why is he not
Still a regular guest Infowars
Is is he still elected to anything
Well
Then he should be
So I I I find this guy to be certified
Boring racist he's a real piece of s*** he's a real piece of s*** I don't like that
You can just
Still say things
16 years after that
You know like it you should Ned like 16 years of the longtime for the world tonight
Change
That's brutal
Yeah
1/2
Susan about bashing
Usher and then
He goes on to cite somebody that it's
Almost
Amazing
But he would say
Starbucks
Mexican
It's about the rule of law and weather
U.s. tax
Sovereignty
Seriously
At the Congressional hearing
From Iowa of all play
Iowa long long way from
Border
Congressman
Steve king of Iowa
Fold-up going
School principal in
Suburban Des Moines
Spanish guy
Decatur
Find an ad
Immigration
In Kingston
Your problem
America
Educator someone
Start the molding
Good luck brother
You didn't cross
The border the Border cross.
Brenda Pratt
Getting this corner
Country backing
We want to thank you
Bring it back
Actually improved
Condition
Which we lost
Pretty pretty amazing story
Are you telling me that
Noted
Massive racing
Steve King
You're from Iowa
Spoke to a very real person
Who told him
Always taking Iowa back
Do you understand that correctly I heard that was like wow that's not a true story
Totally true story
I love I love it's really fake
Story that Steve King told
Is now being repeated this Colorado state senator to Alex
To defend his race
Political ideas
This incredible racist made up a very racist
Story that I am going to
Share with you to defend myself and say that I am not a race
Still there were no there was no rush
Teacher who told Steve King Theory colonizing
The country that they appreciated that America had made some improvements to the place in the meantime
I love it
That's just a story that
TaylorMade
The push the button
White identity victimhood fetishize
A & H
There's so much subtle and unspoken racism the built into that story
Quite awhile zanpakuto but
I think there's a couple of point
What's the jump out
As the most
Interesting
The first is that the story is meant to evoke the feeling of someone taking advantage of the hard work that you've done
These supposed Mexico
Kinfolks we're going to take
Country overall
Exploit
The fruits of our hard labor
This is a particular fear for white nationalists because on some level they're aware that this is exactly what the United States another way
Western countries colonialism
And that without the exploitation of other populations
Internet resources
The affluence that they enjoy today
There's an unspoken admission of we have
Being all freaked out about some terrifying foreign group coming to enjoy that affluent Sonora
Spent that's on some level and expression of guilt
These folks will never really processor be in touch with
Which they should probably get
Get some therapy
The second thing is really f***** up about this fake
Story that Andrews is relating
Has to do with the characterization of this fictional Hispanic guy
He's telling Steve King that he's part of this effort to colonize Demoine and the rest of the United States
And you'll notice that a
Specifically points out that
Is presumably a legal resident
The United States
This isn't explicitly laid out in the story but this is
Details that exist in the telling to make the audience afraid of all immigrants
Even if they're here illegally and fully.
It's the same mentality
That exist
In his 2019 comments about you can't be a faithful Muslim and a faithful America
Targeting and demonizing the entire group
Yep all pretending that's not what you're doing
Absolutely ND idea.
At subtle like
Just saying presumably he's a US citizen
Is
Is a
Simple way
Saying
You can't tell if they're US citizens are looking
Even if they are maybe they're not
Locked up
They might be on document everybody could be an illegal aliens are just
Based on your site
Go ahead and assume
Yeah
This is how someone like Steve king or John Andrews camp
Pretend that their politics and beliefs are about Nash
No security or the rule of law but the actual message they're putting forth
Is one of white nationalism and xenophobia
Just because a Hispanic guy that Steve King made up is here legally that doesn't mean that he's not also part of an effort to recall
Colonized
States
Black
Also it's really hilarious that the example Andrews when
With immediately if somebody who's like
An expert on these things
Steve King
Someone who's synonymous with white nationalism and racism in the same way that Strom Thurmond
Another generation
To another level
Yeah I think this says it all
NPR
When Steve King lost his re-election bid in
Headlines a little generous
Quote Iowa reps
Steve King known for racist comments loses re-election bid
I think that's generous
That might be generous
I would even I would have even gone so far as to challenge him back that Marie Le Pen kind
Hey
Steve King
Massive racist
Lose his re-election bid
Suez
Yeah you don't want to get bogged down though it's a hassle
Call you racist
This initiative
That John Andrews is putting
4th and that is this
Idea that you don't want places to
Except these matricula cards
As accepted
Four forms of identification
Sure because then you can make it so they can't use them
To get a state ID
Her driver's license
Immigration
Status
Even if you get the driver's license
It doesn't mean
Haha you're now
Secretly a magic via citizen understand but you want
Every every official Place do not recognize this
And Alex has a really f***** up way that he talks about how like
All the states need to get on board
I do hope people visit
Colorado center.com and learn more about
Their states
We're increasing the US Congress
Wow
It's really interesting as a thing for Alex to be saying because it absolutely contradict
Literally everything he believes about the balance
Between Liberty and security
He constantly rails on things like the Patriot Act
Is biggest
And fairly defensive
Problems with it is that it was sold to the American people using fear
The idea was that if the folks
National Security
Expand their abilities
Operate there by encroaching on people's Liberty
And that would make the next terrorist attack more likely
Because National
Security could have stopped it
If it just been able to use these expanded ability
If I took Alex seriously about his beliefs meant anything to him I would say that this was really strange and hypocritical way for him
Support has a bill
Against accepting Consular ID
Because I know about as much about him as I do I know that this really isn't the contradiction
Because in his mind the Patriot Act people so it's bad glasby Colorado bill is designed to Target
Satisfying
This is not a small point and I would be remiss if I didn't point out that
These state-level pushes to use the fear of terrorism
To restrict various forms of ID
From being acceptable
That was the beginning of a trend that would come to a head when Congress enacted Public Law 109
13th in May 2000
M5
This was a part of the quote
Emergent
Supplemental Appropriations Act
For defense the global war on terror and tsunami relief
Page 82 of the bell in division B title to section 202
New standards were laid out for what documents are necessary for States
To determine a person's identity
For any official Purp
Including issuing IDs or driver's license
A naturally
Mchire
And states were required to adhere to a federal minimum requirements
In terms of what they consider to provide an
Predictably
Alex and his weirdo friends were all up in arms.
The Furious about the real ID act because
It affects the only group that matters to them
People who look like them
They tend to forget
That the precursor to these evil ID laws was their own agitating against
Accepting things I Consular ID
As acceptable forms of identification
And at the same arguments in stoking fears of imaginary Mexicans trying to recolonize
Or terrorist hiding an immigrant communities that they used
To pursue their goals
We used to push the real ID Act
John Andrew saying like we're pushing Congress
Got to take action on this on the federal level
The thing that is most annoying about Republicans concert
Italy hoisting themselves upon their own
Is it they have to Hoist the rest of us on it with
You can see that this is one of the really great examples
That's really clear about how Alex
Coming and going
Yep.
Create a problem and then also profit off
Complaining about that problem being created
How to get
Plastic created at all mean
Single-handedly
I guess you can make the argument that Alex will be fine with these real IDs as long as they
They were run by the
State of the post of the federal government
And that may seem like a good appointed first but it's not
The first reason is that if the ark
Is that you need more restrictive rules about identification because if
If you don't thoroughly terrorist attacks or Mexico
Things are going to recolonize the country
That's not a state-level issue
If just one state has superlaks standard for identification
Then there wouldn't be any
Stopping these imaginary terrorist
I'm going to that state
Using the Consular ID to get driver's license which would then be recognized by all the states
Implemented these restrictive ID guidelines
Man that seems so obvious it's
It's like let's say that they like you handled
Gun laws at like a state level
Enter some states had really strict gun laws in other states that really Lacks
Gun laws
Like say
You were Illinois right you're living in Chicago and then just
Just like a mirror
Mirror miles away
There's the gun laws were very very Lacks
You know it
That wouldn't cause trouble
I'll be totally fine
I think I think there are many things that are appropriate to be run state-by-state
And then there are other things
That are larger issues that affect everybody
And those things kind of need to have universally applied policies or else they're useless
I am stopping terrorism is one of them but that's the argument you're going to use
Or the recolonization
You don't want you don't want Mexico take an Iowa anytime soon then they're going to vote first in our primaries and that's
Going to be terrible
Yeah it's so this federal-state distinction that Alex abusive just doesn't
Makes sense in this context
And the second reason
This isn't really a case
Where that like
State federal issue thing
Is it
Reply cuz the federal government wouldn't be taking away of the process of issuing the ID
If that's still the state
There will just be a new more restrict
The minimum standard that states needed to follow
That was on a federal level
So Alex has John Andrews
But he sucks
Another Gaston blue guess what he also
Interesting
More
So just to be clear Alex hasn't demonstrated in any way that it's easy to get most
Consular IDs
Has he proven that undocumented immigrants get more government
Assistance nor that they have more rights
Then citizens
All evidence
Switch points
Do the exact opposite
In every facet
Only his
Extreme White
Victim complex
Next weekend
I don't love that Glenn Spencer is Alex's other guests episode
Whole thing might as well just be one long attack on immigrants particularly those from Mexico that's right
We talked about Spencer in the past but it's been awhile so let me refresh your memory a little bit
He's that total a****** who founded a group called The American Border Patrol who essentially pretended to be law enforcement Garden
Border Iraq
This was really the Vanguard of this type of activity since Glenn was doing that s*** back in the early 2000
Flash-forward to 2019 any of militia members deputizing themselves to guard the Border
In actually detaining immigrants
Larry Hopkins was arrested for being a felon in possession of a gun which
You should have been arrests
Before long
It's a 27
It was in 2019
Law enforcement just let him go over those
. of time
The ended up becoming the leader of a group called The United constitutional Patriots who engaged in a whole lot of kidnapping
Unlawful detainer
He was a good boy you got to let him out what do get ahold of my Bailey's a good boy get him out there
Straight
Inspired in no small part by Trump and Tucker and Alex
Wisconsin fear-mongering about the Immigrant Caravan
Set to blow up the southern border
Also his group's former spokesman James Benzie left the ucpn
Start his own border militia called The Guardian Patriots
He was arrested inside the prison
For 21 months on two counts of impersonating a border patrol
Anyway the point is in the front
In the present day we have a lot of right-wing xenophobic
S******* to think they're entitled to cosplay as law enforcement cuz they're white
Glenn Spencer was one of the leaders in that world and probably a hero
To all the Dum Dums
Out there today
Glenn is also one of the main proponent
Flam conspiracy theory which
This is essentially the belief that Mexican immigration is an explicit
The plan to take back over these Southwest
Splc quotes
Spencer from a 2000 rally
The dream of conquering asplundh
Lies deep in the heart of the Mexican
Can psychic
This explains why some are willing to risk
Death their goal is more than job
Conquest
They believe what they're doing
Is Noble
They're defined
The Gringo to take back what is rightfully Mexico
To which every Mexican in the world replied
What the f*** are you talkin about
If you believe what Spencer promotes
It's really hard to see how you could be so against illegal immigration for this reason but somehow totally cool with legal hemp
Immigration
It seems like just sloppily
The sky is white
Nationalism
Migrate illegally then they'll take back their country but if they migrate legally
Then they won't
Take back their country
He's make it easier for them to migrate League
Your argument
He said if they migrate legally they won't take over the country that's an interesting argument I'd like to see what you would have to say today
That we should just keep them all
Also it should be sad that Glenn Spencer was also a fervent anti-semite
In 2008 he posted an article on his blog titled quote
Speaking the Unspeakable
Is G
Who's controlled Hollywood brainwashing Americans
Speaking the Unspeakable
Yet has been spoken for thousands of years
The Unspeakable
Repeat it Non-Stop
Is an article he argues that liberal Jews who control Hollywood or trying to insert pro-immigrant propaganda
And everything they release so is too I guess make America less white
I think that's a
And it wasn't
I'm smoking it anytime before then ever
It's at the end of the article he includes a link to an essay titled understanding Jewish influence
By Kevin McDonald
McDonald is essentially a Neo-Nazi
And if not that he's at least the academic who most neo-nazis point to in order to
Defense attorney or not
Honorary neo-Nazi
Splc article about McDonald in the three books
She wrote about Jewish people
Quote
McDonald's basic premises that Jews engaging
Group evolutionary strategy
It serves to enhance their ability
The out compete non-jews for resources
Although normally a tiny minority in their host countries Jews Like viruses
Is destabilize their host societies to their own benefit
McDonald's
Because this Jewish
Group behavior is said to have produced much Financial in intellectual success over the years
McDonald's claims it has also produced understandable hatred
Tiles
That means that anti-Semitism rather than being an irrational hatred
Produced is actually a logical reaction to Jewish success
Another word for Nazis like many other anti-semites were only anti-semitic because they were countering a genuine
Who is threat to their well-being it's not their fault
Spencer LinkedIn McDonald's essay in this post is what you might call
A towel
Who's against immigration but he also believes that the Jews are the ones
I'm trying to bring an immigrant somehow is in
An attack on the country and produce
Pro-immigrant propaganda Hollywood all this sounds right
I have many Jewish friends and they have been extremely instrumental in fighting illegal immigration
I fear however that this small handful of patriotic Americans are far outnumbered by liberal Jews
Uno have total control over our media
While
Who was the precursor to the modern militia dum-dum
Patrolling the Border
Is one of Alex's favorite guest
Hey it's always nice to go back and see what the pass
What's a non surprise
How it said there's a narrative satisfaction even if there's not an emotion
No Satisfaction
Wow
So Alex
Doesn't talk much about Iraq
The war
You still again
He believes that there aren't weapons of mass destruction which good on him
But he does have some interest
Takes
Okay that I enjoyed and I I looked at you a little bit
Alright
Thousand
Gold bar gold bars so real quick that question about Tariq Aziz I can answer that very easily share
He was actually also not the foreign minister at this point that was a
Position he held from 1983 to 1991
At the time of the Deputy Prime Minister of Iraq
Yeah it's pretty important
Episode 27
2003 and Alex's ass
Where is Tariq Aziz as if to imply that he's somewhere enjoying his life or whatever
He was captured on April 24th 2003 and held in Camp Cropper
Bring back that sure
Remain in custody until June
15 when he died of a heart attack
Alex is super wrong about this one after the heart attack
Iraqi Republican guard has made off of gold bars a bunch of times I just kind of ignored it cuz it cuz it's too
This time I wanted to dig in and see where if I can figure out where this idea came
I think I
Okay
Apparently in 2003 some US soldiers in Iraq detained
3 people that they stopped
In the car that they felt might have been heading towards the Irani and border
Their probable cause to search them was the quote
The drivers paperwork and ID didn't match the
Vehicle registration
In the bed of the truck that soldiers found 999 bars of quote
Crudely made non minted gold bars
They estimated were worth between 80 and 100 million dollars
Obviously this is weird but to make
Things even stranger quotes
Days earlier solder stopped
Another Mercedes dump truck on its way towards the
The Syrian border
Hauling a load of
2000 gold bar
They look very similar to the one seized on Monday
Send
In June another truck with 1100
83 ingots
That were suspected to be gold were intercepted by soldiers
At a routine checkpoint
This is very exciting stuff
So these will definitely not be gold bars that were used
To pay someone off
Because there's an article in the Chicago Tribune about this
These Bars
Aren't pure like the bullion found it to Fort Knox
But crudely melted bricks of
The jewelry so yeah so it's most likely that they're all a bunch of rich people trying to smelt down their bulshit at
As they flee the country
The gold that Saddam Hussein it encouraged araki citizen
To donate for his war effort against Tehran
Call Rich busy
Has Matt many Rockies recall where expect
Did the cough up
325 lb
The gold or face a visit from Hussein's Goon Squad
The speculation was that this was asaph
Fisticated and organized group plundering the wealth that Saddam had hoarded
That's kind of exciting
By August however there been some analyses on the gold bars and it turned out they weren't
The gold it just look like it
New York Times article quote
Gold colored bars
Seized by American troops in Iraq appear to be melted down shell casing
Made mostly of copper rather than gold
Okay who's mostly copper and zinc
Check it out
But it seems like
It's almost certain
This real-life story is the one that is distorted into being by globalist paying off back party officials of Republican guard
It's not like the United States
Didn't
Pay a s*** ton of money and then lose
Never find out where it went
Or if they did they didn't tell anybody
Stop the bear enough
True but not
Not the claim we're assessing
It's believable that they lose a s*** ton of monkey
Corrupt
But it's not
Yeah Alex
Spencer calls
Kirkland's
Is going to be in a little bit
We take a call
And this guy is a
A complete weirdo
And Alex
Jumps in
Very inaccurate JFK
I believe
DirecTV
My God
Pretty-much apparel
And during the Cuban Missile Crisis and I just liked
Say that
I feel in a way that you're kind of the same way
By trying to bring out
People
Search you're being Direct
I got in the same way to try and see
The world
President
Woke up
War
Declare war
This is a fun story that Alex is telling about JFK would like to see aren't disconnected
Kid from history
So what are the things that Alex is doing here is that he's intentionally fudging
The timeline of events in order to
To create the appearance that things are more
Connected than they are
Operation Northwoods was crafted and presented to JFK Secretary of State Robert McNamara on March 13th
1962 then breathe President Kennedy
Alex is claiming that
Six months later Kennedy was assassinated but that didn't happen until November 9th
You know I wouldn't sound as compelling Northwoods a man year-and-a-half later he was assassinated
Yeah that's a little bit
Disconnected
Compress that timeline and you meant much more suspense makes
It sounds more like causality
I don't want these things to feel closer in time and the audiences mind because that makes it feel like they're connected
Or even like one leg to the other
It's a rhetorical trick
As for the other stuff
Most of that's not true either
Whatever you might say about JFK one thing you cannot
Deny is that he was promoting globalism right up to the
On June 10th 1963 if you want
Before he was assassinated Kennedy gave a speech at that commencement
For American University
Which is what I was referring to
Easy fun. Video
This speech was about the hope
For reaching World Peace
There's a little path
Some say that is useless.
To speak of Peace our world our world disarmament
And that it will be useless until the leaders of the Soviet Union adopt a more enlightened attitude
I hope they do I believe we can help them
Conduit
JFK supported World law which necessitates The Collector
The body the kidney
Enforce that law like the UN
Wait is that why they
Speaking of the UN
Later in that speech he says quote
We seek to strengthen the United Nation
To help solve its Financial
To make it more effective instrument for peace
Development
Into a genuine World security system
A system capable of resolving
Disputes on the basis of law
Seems like exactly
The sort of thing that Alex's version of him wouldn't say okay okay let's
Throw this one out there
Haha
Patriots
Murder JFK
The globalist from taking over compared to Alex is running interference
To make it look like it was the global us all along
When in reality was the
Sure
I'll go for that actually Timothy McVeigh
On September 20th 1963 even more closed
The date of his assassination
They gave an address before the general assembly of the UN
I don't think Alex would love
The sentiment that was expressed in this speech
The fact remains that the United States has a major nuclear power does have a special responsibility in the world
It is in fact a threefold response
Possibility responsibility to our own
Responsibility to the people of the world who are affected by art
Decisions
The next generation of humanity
Alex doesn't think that we have responsibilities to the rest of the world whether or not they've been effect
Goodbye our decision
Like one of his Heroes
Is Ron Paul and his big thing with one of them was eliminating literally all four
Foreign aid
The fuc
Slogan is America first
Cheese's in that speech from two months
Before he was assassinated Kennedy talks with the UN about how essential International cooperation is to facing the
The problems of the day
And he brags about forming the peace
Score
He ends his talk with a list of things you'd like to see in the world that Alex
Could make conspiracies up about all day
Quote a World Center for Health Communications under the World Health Organization
We could warn of epidemic
And the adverse effects of certain
Drugs as well as transmit the results of new experiments at new discoveries
Eventually you my good buddy Bill Clinton will become Secretary General of the UN
Do you think about
Alex would be like oh my God
A global
System of satellites could provide Communications and weather information
For all corners of the Earth
And I'm sure that
Late model used to track you
Listen to Satan would use to
Obviously have
Let's actually that right now to work
Oreo
A worldwide program of conservation could protect
Check the forest and Wild game preserves
Extinction for all time
Alex believe the conservationism is a globalist plot
To destroy the beautiful coal and natural gas Industries
By power shortage
Destroying the Amazon rainforest
He's being out there trying to
To prosecute him for
F****** crimes against
Humanity for destroying the rainforest
Alex
Would be really disappointed to see JFK on this side of the fence
Have you would really hate this one
We are opposed to apartheid and all forms of human oppression
Like Alex doesn't like the
Apartheid
But opposition to it is a communist plot or at least that's what him and all his predecessors on the John Birch Society think
We don't like the racism of a part-time we just hate that it
The Communist trying to end apartheid
Greatly enjoying it
It said they're going to keep doing
But it's the Communist that we don't lie
Come on
Anyways
JFK that Alex believes existed as a fabrication based on dumb conspiracy books that he read as a youth and not based
Austin reality
The speech that he
We gave that included the line about secret societies
Which is what I was trying to
Flight with this American University
Bee speech
Include the line about secret societies was from April 19th 61
It's quite a while before the relevant time period that Alex is talking
Think about
It's one of the big
Pieces of evidence that always go
Gets thrown around
Like every single
Conspiracy documentary
Conclude that line
About him mentioning secret societies secret societies
You know it's never going to not be
Alex is trying to present the JFK heard about Northwoods tried to warn people and then he got killed
He's just mixing up the American
University speech
Because it fits better in a
Timeline it's all bulshit
1861 from
Society speech
Julie misrepresented by conspiracy theorists
Why here's the passage that they always use
The very words
Secrecy is repugnant
In a free and open Society
And we are as a people inherently and historically opposed
The secret society
Secret Oaths
The secret proceedings
We decided long ago that the dangers of excessive and unwarranted
Concealment of Burton
Facts
Far outweigh the dangers
Which I decided to justify
And that's why I f***** Joe DiMaggio's wife
Naturally is used to imply that this beach with a screed and a warning about secrets
Forces at work behind scenes
True
This passage was JFK's soft
Ming's things up
Before he asked for
Increased secrecy from the Press
Regarding official matter
Here's what comes
Just after that whole secrecy thing you see
It just about every
Conspiracy documentary
No official of my Administration whether his rank is high or low civilian or military should interpret my words here tonight as an
Excuse to censor the news
Stifle dissent
Or cover up our mistakes
Exhort withhold from the press and public
But they deserve to know
Apparently that is what we're trying to
But I do ask every publisher every editor and every newsman in the nation to re-examine his own
Standards and to recognize the name
Nature of our country's peril
In time of War the government and oppressive customarily joined an effort based largely on self discipline
To prevent unauthorized disclosures to the end
In time of
Clear and present danger the courts have held that even the privileged rights of the First Amendment must
Yield to the Public's need for Nationals
Security
Today no war has been declared and however Fierce the struggle maybe it
May never be
Declared in the traditional fashion
Our way of life is under attack
Those who make themselves our enemy are advancing around the globe
The survival of our friends is in danger
And get no war has been declared no borders have been crossed by March
Troops no missiles have
Open fire
If the price is awaiting a declaration of war before it imposes
The self-discipline of combat conditions
Then I can only say that no war ever posed a greater threat to our security
If you're awaiting a finding of a clear and present danger
Then I can only say that the danger has never been more clear
It is present has never been born
He is saying in the speech
We all hate
But
You guys are going to have to stop
Reporting some stuff
Because I wear danger cuz the Soviet Union
Listen listen listen listen you don't want to you don't want to erode public trust in Torrance
Institutions right that would be
That really sucks up
See what is things I think is remarkable is that context
Is almost always missing
From
The conversations about like these peaches better
It doesn't mean
The point of this
Wasn't exactly the
Opposite of what
These people tried to presented at but the point will always
Please just be that if you say secret societies regardless of
The context of it
We can say that you were sick
Regardless of whether or not to warn the good people exactly
Saying those words you were giving a code then people
Need to unravel
Sure and then your
He was not planning to abolish the Federal Reserve and his proposed lowering of taxes wasn't completed by the time of
But it was eventually signed by LBJ in nineteen
Before
Also the quote about scattering the CIA to the wind
Is almost certainly not a real quote
He didn't appear in print until a 1966
It was attributed to an anonymous source
3 years after his death
There's no corroborating evidence that there was a position he had or that they ever said that
He was definitely upset with the CIA after the Bay of Pigs that's true but I want a quote about scattering them
To the wind is
One that is very dubious sourcing
Unlikely
I don't know Alex should know more about JFK
It's really hard to know stuff about history
I think whenever people confidently assert
But they know something about it
Time. From the
The past
They're almost always wrong
Because just in order to know something happened
You need like a PhD level fee
I think I think
Alex is invested in
Allure
Fun stories
Total and so why
Did you threaten
Your ability to live in a fun world
Full of myths
And lower Trail
True reality of things
Complicated and there's detail
I mean people really want to believe that there's a lock
Ness monster you know what
Alex
So this is this is something that I really love when it happened
Nobody can really tell like
So earlier in the episode
John Andrews told the second
Story that he heard from Steve King
About a teacher in Des Moines
Trying to colonize America on behalf of
I can't be racist let me tell you the story I heard from
Steve King
Bright
So we heard that
Now here's Alex Bri bring it up and embellishing
Sing it later
So Erica
Mexico the entire country government of Mexico
Okay alright you see now
Coming back is what we're saying here
Glenn Spencer like he was living in California and agitating against immigration
He decided the California was a lost cause Arizona
And Alamo
Santana might be in play
Santa Ana the ghost of Santa Ana is is definitely involved
You can see how Alex lies
Like
The story of the John Andrews was
Telling the LIE it
Itself
So the state of maintaining the honesty of it or kind of low
We're saying that Mexico
African government is involved the consulate is sitting at the IDS just a
To generate the whole idea
Had multiple people community leaders
Who have come up and told him we're taking it back we're taking Iowa
I like a good
I like a good UK
Can trace it back and even then the story still alive
It's riddled with so many lies that when you trace it back to its
Source you're just
Appointed there isn't even anything fun or interest
I think they're just like
You've lying off of an even another
Steve King made up erases lie
John Andrews heard it
He told it to Alex
So now Alex is embellishing on it
It's ridiculous
End end
Like I look
Even if you're on the right
Wouldn't you agree
Somebody telling you a story that is
So perfectly tailored to your hair
Hatreds
Shouldn't that give you a little signal of like maybe this isn't anyting
From
Looking at a lot of this
Conspiracy stuff
That exist online
Seeing
How information
Is processed
I don't think that a lot of people in these worlds
Understand the notion of
Too good to be true
That is a 4in idea more perfectly tailored it is the more perfectly believe it fits
Quickly into what I would expect or whatever hoe
Especially when it's presented in meme forms
Super easily digestible
Got2b
Do you know if it's
Conform soap
Perfectly to your worst nightmare
Baby
It's just a dream
So Alex has this glowing in this production
Infor Glen Spencer
Patrol
What
Totally Vindicated
Yeah it's Alex's Buddies
Glenn Spencer
Just pretend fun let's act like cops came
That's great
A lot of good people in their lot of good people just think hey you know what
I need to go get a gun
Because an imaginary line
Will make me
Me feel better
I think that also this
Introduces some Dynamics for the interview that make it not
Very meaning
Are you sure it doesn't
You start off very adversarial
Now I don't
So he has some foam prop
Glenn and
One of the phone problems happens
Just after I don't think that this is like
Intentional
At all
If they were into
2 conspiracies
Big idea
Talking about all the other media that has had him on
MN his phone mysteriously goes out
Cleaver on with
We were on.
CNN
Richard
That's interesting because Alex's premise seems to generally be that these people won't have folks
Glenn Spencer on
But now Glenn does on the show and he's saying that I was on with Michael Savage
Who Alex's said is a dirty neocon beat
Call sure they'll have them on something
Right right right right
Put the heat on but what does that mean they won't put the heat on Laurel Bush meaningful heat is Alex putting on
That other people what are
I mean
What is so hot
But he's putting on Lord bush
I want to know in Concord
Creeper other places are not putting as much heat
Lotaburger chili 50
I find it
To be it sounds like Alex Grambling
It's almost convenient
That the phone cuts out there
But I again I'm not saying
I'm not saying that
The Producers hung up on him or anything
Man
He needed to save
And you got an opportunity to make
Save
But it still doesn't
Make a lot of sense
I mean
Speed with which he said we got
Cut off
Normally he waits
Just a little bit low
No no no
You heard aspie
The he gave just
A few months before this
Alright
Calm down
So Glenn gets his phone back working
And a half
He has said
That if you hear a bing bong bing bong sound effect in the background
That is the alarm
That one of his sensors has picked up an illegal
Crossing the border
Gibbs butcher sensors put up around the board
Sensors on the border pictures of people
Jesus
Christ
Holding Lea
Only do so much in the world of bowling ball a perfect game and then what else you going to do
Maybe you got to protect
Borders
So there's one thing that I do a
Claude
Glenn Ford
La out in this clip after
His alarm
Goes okay
Wanted to have you back on
Arizona
We just picked up five
5 people
Exact location
An hour
But we will eventually
Actual locations
For that
These people are attacked
Murdered and robbed
Mexican band
Oh
Okay okay
That's all
Look what up whatever she has to tell himself to not publicize that information
Fire tell himself that it's Mexican Bandits that are the that are the risks
Do telling where they look
Locations of these migrants are
Haha
Cuz they at the end of the day
That information isn't going to these
Weirdo f****** right-wing militias who think that are
Countries being invaded
So good
Keep information to yourself
We don't listen listen
Listen
I don't want Ben
Bandidos hurting
Okay
I want me and my buddies
Know that the others bodies would never
They're never
We wouldn't hurt anybody
We want to protect them from the Bandidos
Right2know
And that's why we carry the guns in case we get into a bandit fight
And and there's a stagecoach and we got is there we're going to fight on top of it
And then we'll save the Immigrant
And Save
Forcefully
Bit of a bayonet
General directions
That he gave someone my kids
I pick you up by 2
Undercut is on point
I do like whenever the overconfidence of
Will never find
This
To the beginning
Of his interview he does say that if you hear that bing bong bing bong go off
That it's my
Getting whatever and then miraculously in the middle
So weird
So it's so great such great timing
Like
Exactly what you would want to do
It's create an alarm
That goes
Instead of just some sort of an alert or something weird noise
It's got to be the
The bat-signal it's got to be over so it's got to be overdone
Overwritten
There's a big
For each individual that causes the oh my God we have one last clip here and it's
Glenn talking about a plan that he has
City morgue
For anybody who wants to log on to our website
It doesn't work as a driver's license
I got a thing
But if you did do this
You might get in the international trouble if he is actually going to sell
Consular ID
That's a serious problem
I would advise him not to do this
He was doing this and he was talkingshit
I think it was funny about it is that if it were to go down
The way that he wants it
To go where everybody does this to subvert the
The system
What we'd find out is that
Everything would be fine
Thereby disproving his whole this
What is the problem
Argument possible
They're just mad that other people have rights
I don't I don't like
Back in my day when I was young
I didn't have to deal with other people having right
And I feel like that was a better system for me so
So like I said that was the last
Honest-to-god
There's another hour of the show
Alex
But
I can't fight
Find that last hour of the show
Okay yeah the place where I found all these episodes
And so we only have these 22 hours of the show
Now
I picked a problem
Boring call
Or something I don't I don't know if there's anything nefarious
Apps
This hour
Speculate wildly
The amount of like
Stuff about
JFK and the bars of gold and
And somebody figured like even without whatever dumb calls
He takes on the 3rd hour
I'm
Satisfied with what we've learned today I like a good JFK conspiracy
There's never a bad time to tell me lies about JF
What's fun to about this is it was a a sort of
Scattershot
Anything but all over like what happened
LOL everytime you go into depth of JFK's conspiracies you just find out something that disproves
My man just yell Northwood that's fine
Horrifying
So
I enjoyed going back
That I've been reinvigorated
I feel like
Back on track
I like it
Jordan
I don't accept
We're also on Twitter
Omniome Leo I'm dzx corkum Terrell run this
What the sex role
Alex
Birthstone colors
I love your work