Knowledge party.com
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B
Need money
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Acknowledge
Considering the altar of Selena little bit about Alex
Jewels
Jordan
Longtime listener
Survivor
Write that long of a listener for that
It did happen quicker than that I would like to admit
Brightspot
I've been looking around for something
To fill that void
Scratch the itch
Some Amazing Race
And I think it's fix
I think it's disrespectful to travel
I also hate everybody who's on
Pretty much everybody sucks he's a good reason
They're pretty
Other countries and then just do basketball tricks
Third grade one of the episodes that I saw one of the challenges was they had to sew a garment
Yes and so they were in a Garmin
Workshop and then the other one who's not doing the challenge is just doing basketball
Anyway
I found
The Australian version of Survivor of course
Australian Survivor is my bright spot
I think it's fun
Basically just Survivor but with Australian accents
And
None of the b*******
At this point of the bulshit
I've just started what years back in this
Are you on season 1 they only have a few seasons on Paramount Prime
Placer whatever
Season 4 I think is the first season that they have
A couple episodes in
No twist
I think there's a hidden immunity idol but that might be it
This is
This is Australia we don't do twisty straightforward that's not a knife
This is the knife I found
Very refreshing after the
100 different rule changes American Survivor
Why you don't like Survivor
It's refreshing to see people playing
The game that I remember
It being the show
Loosely what I remember
You at the War on Drugs released a new album
It's one of very good album
And two because many people are describing the War on Drugs
This is one of the best rock
Bands currently today in the description and this most recent album
Is absolutely a Willie Nelson album
What can we can we just get it cleaned take of you saying that your bright spot is the War on Drugs
My bright spot is the War on Drugs
I love incarcerating people who don't deserve it
My favorite
Well that doesn't need to be taken
Totally out of context
Yeah I know it's a great album and it is 100% of Willie Nelson record it's it's
Just a great Old Time Country album with more updated
Distortion
I love it
This is this is continuing in your tradition of giving
Music recommendations to the folks
And it's fun
It is so Jordan today we have
Interesting episode
Go over I'm torn
You're torn yeah
Because there's a part of me that recognizes that
Alex just lost
The Connecticut
Lawsuit
He's cold and ashamed
Lying
He's all out of faith
And we should we got to cover the present day we got to cover November 15th
Blackjack
You tricked me it like a motherfuker there's another part of me
Cost to dig even deeper into the past
I'm very conflicted
And I'm not sure what I'm going to do
But before we find out okay for the break
Are you
Dario
Commercial break as we literally have to say hello to some moolah
First help I'm stuck in a policy wonk Factory your now policy walk
Next chaotic asexual time crime Loki thank you so much you are now policy walk
Go Tigers Red Wings lions and pistons download Chicago Sportsnet you so much you're now apology walk
Interesting, Chicago Sports
Reluctantly thing
I don't really have a position on that but I should be because otherwise I might get beat up
Chicago
Blackhawks fans get made
Next
I'm a policy wonk
Are you very much Justin alright
Here's the deal here's the situation what is the deal or sit
I want to make a compromise
And that is what do the present-day up
Episode but I have an out-of-context drop from 1998
Is an out-of-context drop from April 7th
We're following the pattern of History
I'm probably
Good chance
Percent chance
That I will be killed within the next 5 years
I'll say this for theatrics and I don't say this to scare you but we need to go ahead and
About where we're at
Image Group psychology Realm
Wow 23 years in
I will be murdered
I think coming up all the 23 out of her is it what's the what's the is that the silver anniversary
Which one is that pearls
I like that a lot I think that's really fun
But I do think embarrassing
Are we living in like a
Quantum suicide
Situation where where do
Just living in the wrong Universe where he
Keeps not dying on A50
50 shot it's possible I found some of these old episodes
B
I made from the late nineties and also
Choice clip from this episode
This April 7th 1998 episode
Hey we got a night and we cannot drink
We shooting party
Not because it's wrong but because we need to maintain our Focus supplements
You know enough about the body of the temp
Just what God gave us
Tony's changed a little bit
So I guess we got to get to the Press
Alright
Jordan I don't want to do it
Okay then let's not do it okay
Okay well then let's do it
Can we just
Put it off a little bit let me let's not do it let's put it off
We'll do it in a little bit in a little bit are you TT before the break
First like
I feel like
You know Alice isn't immoral
Go troubled Cheryl
Will you talk to Mark Bankston the
Got the lead attorney
Once and that seems like way outside tomorrow
Hey folks I were thrilled to welcome back
Tu VI the podcast delightful guest someone who the audience
Really took to
Sam's favorite
About all of that Council for the Sandy Hook
Texas courtsmart Braxton welcome back
Good to be here good to be good to be home German
I'll tell you I'll tell you earlier today after the big news and everything was going on
CNN invited one of us
Come on and then talk to them
Speak to Anderson Cooper tonight in primetime
And I told my partner man hey I think you got to do it I got tonight
Anderson Cooper
Well thank you we appreciate your making time I mean it's
It's an intense stretch of time since we last spoke
I'm in today we recording this on Monday which is the day
That the Connecticut's default app at the great Connecticut diesel
What they're calling it so it's it's got to be a whirlwind
Well you know one thing it proves that is that what I was doing on this case your last
You know it wasn't December.
Random off the reservation saying
It wasn't some wild west s*** that happened down in Texas
This just happened
In the in the
Stoic state of Connecticut
You know there
I mean I have a whole different thing way they run things up there
And
Toosii
This happened there with another judge saying yeah this is
This is beyond ridiculous is farcical and I will let it be farcical for so long
Just out of allowance on who my who the defendant is
I'm just not wanting to say we railroaded this guy but he has been so horoscope for so long and now is finally the time
Different judge different plaintiff attorneys
So like all like that so many different variables the only thing really
It's similar between them is Alex and his behavior
Is that
I love that it reinforces my concept of
If nothing happens
Then this will happen
Because of it you know
Like if you do the exact same thing in one Court in Texas
It will happen in another court if you do
We we live in such a system that works like that in our world's been so fake
For so long
That you're not yet the idea of like a
A uniform
Field theory of law
I bet there isn't one it's just like once you get to a certain point of like
I'm not playing ball takes offense
Want to give anybody like the faith of over where
The legal field doing Kumbaya in Ralston
You have to understand that this is when
When when you know you go to the Westminster dog show in like a lot of people are going to
Different opinions on judges of which dog is the nice
Dog or whatever
But if you just bring in a random mutt off the street with names like they're all going to go you what's what's going on here
Schema and when you have a
Defendant who comes in and injuries the court but I just like as his own personal playground or whatever
Like you're going to get the same reaction and I think I am doing some looking into like past examples of P
People got hit with default judgments
Like a lot of times I think it happens to celebrities who don't want
To have the unpleasantness
Judgment
So I think I think that that was his behavior kind of
They note falls into the same sort of like
You been researching all those cases where we're celebrities just at one point or another decide the only way to win is not playing they just
Finley
Ironic situation
Is he was there to play
Said he was trying to play whatever game he was going to play
And it was so important Vincent to the court
That that even
His behavior their it wasn't you just don't see this that much you know we we talked about it a bit of these hearings of other cases worth
Under pretty egregious circumstance
But to Sia really a first
Celebrity high-profile case
Either the default with not just a celebrity walking away
Like typically they'll just
Not show up yeah yeah
Yeah it's a bit like Alex was invited to play a game of chess and then is like way
What if I ate two Chutes and Ladders and shattered on your face does that is that down to the game
Everything everything passed Candyland is too confusing
Meatball at the same time
Remember he's doing this
In two different cases in two different places on toots slightly different timeline
And has to keep whatever
Whatever shell game is happening has to be cuffed up in both cases on an on a 2 to 3 months
Flag timeline to stay consistent
He's not going to be able to
Consistency know that you have both sets of cases
And that the conduct that ended in default judgement
Was totally separate conda what happened in Texas
Totally different stuff
So much of it is they would discover stuff going on up there that's affecting their Discovery and I be like honestly I can't even breathe
Busy telling him about the other stuff that's going on in my
All the stuff you saw about Google analytics and all that
The final trial balances that they brought in some account did a bunch of stuff that's it
I never got a chance to talk to that
I we were done before that even happened and it's it's stunning that done if I hadn't gotten
Metallica back in September
Now just because
It's fun
Real
But yeah that the difference between the two cases is absolutely stunning that he has two very different styles of wall and he lost them both
Repeat the behavior you're saying it's different behavior that caused the default judgment but they're like
Related
Family
They are cousin
Epicenter of obstinate Miss kind of
Yes but it isn't variety
In in in in Connecticut
Things work on a
Connecticut
There's a pretty high set of Demands you got to keep the briefs coming in on a really regular. They're really regimented you're showing up at monthly
Status
Directions to having to work really hard to try to keep their heads above water genetic
In Texas you can go long periods where you're not before the court and if you're a bad litigator
You can get yourself into some Norma's holes during those periods of time
Didn't help also wasn't good for them either
What was what was studying about his in Texas
Their transgressions are mostly just
An abject
Not even just a refusal but you didn't even show up to play kind of ideas of Discovery they didn't answer the discovery that corridor
Do it and then they'd expect to show up in the next hearing and everything will be okay
In Connecticut
They actually tried to do the stuff and that's actually maybe what got them in more trouble and just took longer is that the stuff they did
Was really absurd
Enso
The offense and disrespect in Texas was really something
But the
Absolute clown show that was what they tried to fix
The situation in Connecticut with maybe even worse
So they in Connecticut they demanded like
I don't know bank records and he gave them a shoe
Another call I can speak of his from what's in the public sweetie
What is stated in the bleeding from what I can gather from what is stated there
Is that they work
They were asked to have their account they're QuickBooks person press the button on QuickBooks that produces the subsidiary ledgers and all the funny
For the company
And then they said here they are
Debut
And then a little bit later on they discovered because of some weird irregularities in there
The important actually we printed that button then we gave it to an accountant
Well he said that the Figures were misleading the figures
I believe it I believe the technical term for accounting that is cooking them
It discloses
Identify
Deposition weird asking the ladies
These are the files that you produced
I think so
The accountant
Nobody says anything
Earrings about what's what's going on in there
Honestly like
Again the difference between two forms
Getting him try to pull that stuff down in Texas cuz I would have
Your honor your honor your honor we had all of this money that was
Covered in like filth and dirt
So before we gave it to you we send it to a washing machine I don't understand what the problem is he
It's a problem. I'm glad you brought that up actually because that was one of Alex's
Defenses on his show
Today
When he was responding to the the default judgement
Connecticut
It was that
Oh they said I didn't give them bank records I gave them a spreadsheet
If they had changed
Some numbers.
I mean it look I want to make clear tutu
Pittsburgh people are listening here
When I say that I'm reading the public records when I'm telling you about what's going on Connecticut
But but I cannot the docket
Describing to you about
An accountant
Going out and then making the the numbers that were misleading turn correct
That's not Pagan from the play
That's what they say
Vaping
Between friends
I like I don't I don't know exactly what's going on
But what I do know is that the end of the day they like they just
Did not produce the things that the court one of them to produce and they can't do that now and now in Connecticut
Forever to reach that point
Because a lot of procedural safeguards
In Texas we start hanging trees outside the courthouse
Operation
Courthouse
You go into like I'm in Houston got a place in a different one now but then at Austin Courthouse where he's going to be
Where I grew up in Fort Bend
You look outside the direct window of the courthouse you are in there is a giant oak tree with a straight
You know horizontal branch
It's been trained that way
And that bike. Bread you know what that is
It's this weird imposing Legacy of the Texas legal
And day today today it's theirs murderers
Call me back
Largely alienated and disenfranchised in and not
People who have the power the state of raid against them and perhaps unjust way
Alex Jones is going to have to spend two weeks not courtroom looking out that window
Is met you know that's a good feeling that he has to
Be in that courtroom
Oh I believe it place to be
Thursday aggressive imagery all over that Courthouse it is a scary courtroom to be in
Especially especially when you're in
Advantageous situation perhaps
I was looking into it and it's the rules
Texas
Do not mistake in our that you have 14 days is that right to like
Try and get a default judgment put aside
I know you're not not quite right on that
You'd be correct
Get the idea was
He just didn't answer the lawsuit
I found a default judgment was entered then you found out if she's got 14 days to get up there okay
They know I wanted to feed the stew
He really has 144 can I get in Sky baseball he really only has one appellate option
Genies default judgment
And in Texas that's an emergency appeal
Known as a mandamus we have a weird name for it
And I've heard that term used a lot by sovereign
Citizen
It's one of those like classical 18th century terms that like
We're only involved when ship captains were involved in
Maritime law
But it but yeah so it's an emergency appeal they don't even necessarily 6:45
Take it up if they don't want to
It just really stopped options Arlo
But they do get a shot at that
That not clock
Running out very quickly sure I was curious about that cuz it seems like
It'll be bizarre it be bizarre to me it's like
You didn't try and do some
Nothing like that entertains deal
I mean there is a time limit on it so he's not too great at keeping up with those
Rising 2
I'm going to be here on time
Making a debut at a wrestling
You don't want to show up before you're cute
He does have a mark trial set
You sprayed to go and you do want to pull the rug out from them. Maybe I don't know
I'm cool baby something
Ellison his calculus could be that
The last time he tried to appeal
An adverse ruling in the house on Casey ended up owing me $25,000 for wasting my time
Roll the dice again go for it I'm
That hasn't
That has b-negative stimulus that might be enough
To get you. I feel like my baby not do that again I think I think the greatest irony of all is that there's a good chance Alex
Wind up an illegal immigrant in Mexico
Goes around
I mean not you joke about it but but there's a place to turn you always have to be prepared
Pursue assets wherever they go
I knew he wouldn't be the first person to run on their judgment like this
That's for sure I've liquidated everything and bought a
Coffee Farm in Chiapas
Are you ugly picture like a kim.com situation really
Pirate Radio station are they wouldn't let him invest be closer to your John McAfee situation
Weathers bath salts and murdered neighbor
What are the things that I wanted to ask you about it cuz I think that
I find this fairly interesting is that like
The Texas cases
If I understand correctly the defendant didn't that is all Alex
Right
No
No that is not so that's not okay
So in Texas you have
Generally three defendants
Jonesing cell
And you have is two companies that are
Again at the time we follow suit
The two companies we talk
Primarily
Which is Free Speech Systems LLC
Infowars LLC all over the website as it was at that time
That company
Does not
Exist it's app
Paper thing
Employees no Revenue no assets
As far as we can tell
The other entities that are being sued up in Connecticut
Infowars Health LLC prison
Planet TV LLC
Also completely paper entities totally
A detour bunch of manatees that respond off in 23
Teen right around the time of the divorce to try to reorganize the business none of it really seemed to take off I don't really understand why but they
Put every egg in the basket and Free Speech
The really intermittent that's really in its Jones and Free Speech system so we have some assets personally as some of the corporate form
Everything is under Free Speech systems right I mean like
Supposedly like
You can't look at a document say this is a subsidiary of
LLC
Cbna
Instead of like a
Horizontal affiliate or something like that
Alter ego
It's just all Alex Jones
Hashem
Before there's no set
Separation between Jones and his businesses or any other businesses
I'm sure that that's not intentional to confuse people
That organization
Strategy
Yeah I know it's
It's totally aboveboard business so they would never do that
The other defendant in our cases that is not up in Connecticut
Which is just
Delightful is Owen Shroyer
All right that's right
Owen Shroyer
Is cuz he had he went on and said specific things about new huh
And went ahead and put his
Now that is something I guess I didn't think about did Owen Shroyer also have a default judgment against them
Oh wow
Okay
I think that's the last talked about
I would say that the non rich guy getting a sub
Judgment against him is far more damaging than be very rich man getting his
What are you
What do you do do in shorter besides run his credit
But you don't you don't collect anything
Which I'm not sure he does
That's going to be a text
Homestead exemption you can't go collect that
If if if he has any non-exempt
Property I don't know what it would be like I don't understand him to be a rich guy
And it really even you know most rich guys
A giant judgments it. I just ruined his credit never buy a car again
14 I mean
Now
Satisfies Jordan sense of justice
Satisfied mind sense of judgment when you asked what are you going to do to Owen Shroyer believe me the answer wasn't
Ruined his credit
That was not your hope okay
Possible difficulties about the
The six
From his ear he got in trouble
From that lets
I don't know if that was
Criminal
Nothing
Oh my God
Mega X
I would have I would have destroyed six fewer cup
Fox if I were him
Flew too close to the Sun
You know it's funny when you one of the first questions you got it you got to ask the guy when you're in deposition with him
He's got an author page on Infowars
And it's like
I am its they haven't updated in the wild hinox that's like still
I am
Well known for my confrontations with
Carl the cuck and AIDS Skrillex
He most known for that
I'm going to see if I can change that for you
You did not show up for deposition correct
Thank you for that
His deposition right now is currently scheduled for December 3rd so that should be fun
That would be so much fun. I feel like you're not getting them before the feds do that's a good thing as you know we brought them
Little concerned about that
You're putting off your deposition forever and he's got
Canning criminal indictment
Nothing is as yet
They've been
For the past
Three months they just been on Infowars making noise as much as they want would not challenge not whatever they'll finally get to know God
Answer question
I would love
To see Owen have to sit like in a serious Circle
Stance
With adults
I'm at be asked like so you're the cock Destroyer huh
Just see how he divided by Childish
I just like Court stenographers happen to type in on their shorthand
Machines
Duck Destroyer what's
Very strange things that court reporters have never had to type
Okay you got this guy who's kind of passing himself off as a new thing
Write like he's delivering Journal
And then like in the same breath like you know after the break I go after
Carl the cock or what you do whatever it is
Is he taking his job seriously enough when
He's doing Carl the cuck stuff who cares
Making accusations that the you know mess
Casualty
Surviving
Father is a CIA agent
Has anybody ever have any anybody taking any of this seriously
Yeah he's he's an interesting like sort of the middle case to because like he started in St Louis doing
Like sports journalism
I thought it was going to be a Barstool guy right have some pretentious
About like what he's doing as being sort of journalist
Irrelevant
Pretend the past never really worked out any only really got
Success by yelling at Carl the cuck
Yeah and then Alex being like this is fun
I'm going to hire this guy
So
Came on my radar
My radar when
Oh gosh Sailor Man costume told him about Venezuela
The Red Scare
Yes I I that's how he liked came onto my radar is he
That guy and then and then like I you constantly just see videos of like
12 year old kid destroys Owen Shroyer
So I just thought he was a ridiculous guy and it was weird that when I got these cases
I understand a little bit so I kind of knew who was in the Sandy Hook
I knew that was robbed doing that whole crew and during rain all this week
But like
Owen Shroyer showed up and it to me was like what's like your
The comedy guide
He wasn't even like working for them what in that relevant. Exactly lien High School
Cuz you comes in 2016 feel like what he's doing these things in 2017
It's weird though because he becomes sort of
Jones's hatchetman
He can't talk about the
The family specifically so he wants to talk about the family he sends Owen Shroyer
Beatles video about Erica Lafferty and confronting her
I don't know just goes off about
I don't understand what your problem is man like Wolfgang halbig
Most reliable reporting possible in this event and I don't know why you're trying to butt heads of people were trying to figure out what happened to your mom
I think it is
I think a lot of that
Good beginner slightly motivated by trying to prove that he belongs in that
Space like that Alex Jones Infowars face has been very clearly on that path
Have like I want to please Daddy
I don't know much so that I will never be able to buy a car again
The English guy
I threw him under the bus so now I can replace the English guy you know that's probably okay
Yeah I like
I don't
He is an interesting case and and people aren't talking about him enough in this suit
Because he is
Is June
And people don't realize that that he just
Got on and did those marching orders and did those things and he's just as much a part of all of this
Yeah it's one of the things that we've kind of looked at over the course of us
What's doing podcasters like who is The Heir Apparent
What who is the person who supposed to do this after Alex
Has a heart attack or
Phone number to report of possible ways for him to die
It always seemed like Paul Joseph Watson but at some point
He seemed to want to distance himself a bit
Kind of clearly Owen and that was a disappointing point
Pretty much everybody
You know when I came on this cuz I was probably
Less busy saws better in touch with right-wing online media
But
Like I said the last couple years too
Stomach at right
No offense to you guys
Like for instance I haven't been keeping up and seeing what Paul Watson career looks like right now in
And how much it's still part of Infowars what he's trying to carve out for himself but it seem like that's what he was
Doing in some way and I
I figured he was going to be on the level by cabbage Pirro is going to like
Eventually be that kind of figure and he started this site called Summit
Dotnews that was basically just like
No news
Blog kind of thing
Another Gateway pundit
You know but I think that his mistake
Might have been getting too involved
In like some European
Politics
And some British stuff like
Nigel farage and those folks
I think he got pretty hard in the UK
They were at least slowed him down like kind of with a speed bump
Much less relevant
You know why we were on this case you could also see another Heir Apparent trying to develop themselves and Robert Barn to his tribe
Oh he was given an Excel
Yeah he was really giving it ago
Desperate for like online engagement and my
Just to have like
The raveling
Clapping seals of right-wing Twitter just clap for any crappy pretends he's doing
But like the idea that you haven't able to like successfully monetize that into making yourself a star like
I swear it sets that your right-wing grift
Right now it's so easy I saw a digit not to lie completely change the subject
Alex Berenson the decoded misinfo guy had started a sub stack in the dude he's bringing in a Million
Any you're on that sub. Just like blogging three times a week about covid
Robert Barnes how can you work this card and not be like
Just that I don't know well I think
I think Barnes f***** up because he obviously couldn't make a patreon
And so he tried to get on locals
I think it's the name of it the Ben
Not bad Dave Chappelle
Dave Rubin and Peterson
Patreon clone
I don't think that's as is lucrative
There's there is something nice about how easy the right-wing grifters is how easy you should know when to quit
Quit you know
Like if you fail within their first month
Just give up you've already failed forever exactly
Exactly
It was weird to see and I always wonder about that with Barnes Supply
You're hosting enforced
Words that go like anymore
Decide they got some new guy likes Alyssa
It's not like I mean
It is like
And that's best of your best compelling stuff like that what do you have better than that like like
If that isn't enough for you then something must be really wrong because there's just not they have a lot on offer
Are you going to just go to show
The Infowars is Alex Jones always will be Alex Jones without Alex Jones is in no Infowars
100%
Fascinating
Personality and then craziest underlies all of that nevermind
By fascinating personality of course you mean very well-researched information
Ball and some of those great debates of the 1950s and 60s were William F Buckley would get in there
You can't help watch Alex Jones not really feel Shades that you know of
Yeah
I bet to Barnes really quick another thing as as that was all happening like him a sin
Ending in Infowars and being Alex's lawyer
Me and Jordan were both like
Alex
He's trying to take over that's what I was thinking
He's literally watching you go down in court I mean like presiding over devoted and he loved
Absolutely right so you got scared
Why would you ever go back at the terrible idea going to finish
Hanging Tree outside
YouTube
It's not good if somebody who's clearly wanting to become like an on-air
Personality tala is also the person
Who gets paid more the longer you're in
Working a little against purposes
And I you can never presume this about the while you presume that he's getting
Paid by the hour to be important not paid by
Aiden shows
Through all those things work I mean if yeah but if you want to diversify your Revenue stream uo
Also get a TV show on top of your love practice
Is very generous
What is a good his this
You know regular lawyers
Do things the regular way even though we're like absolute Pirates and going after who we go after it like
We had when we came to these people inside yeah you're just a guy you just like
Send me money in crowdfunding me too
I accept donations in Bitcoin
It is strange but I guess it work
Boss
That's that's
Wherever wherever there aren't slapp lawsuit laws I think he needs of these there he's the Batman
States that don't have slapped
It's really interesting because you tried to come in
You know I'm going to take out these slap
This is
And then like every little other thing I've ever seen him do is go to a state without a slap loan file some crazy suit against it
Hitman on Eminem panesar to the most important constitutional lawyers that has ever practiced
According to Alex
Yeah really
Antonym for the word from the from the hearings the elephant in the room is the marker and on time I yeah
The other like weird
Guy who's like branded himself a First Amendment lawyer who kind of came out of
I mean like it at first he was very much an anti First Amendment lawyer in a way of like
Working for p*** companies to
Go after people were posting their p*** videos online and stuff like that
And then like
Switch gears off of Valley and bunch of stuff happened tonight and
You re all about that on mine
But then he he he switched into like I'm now First Amendment crusader
But it's it's weird how every single
Like anytime you see Miranda is involved in that like you like oh I understand what the defense
Going to be like then
It's great
Yeah I can understand like
Okay let's say I was going to be some First Amendment defense lawyer which I'm not going to be
I would be proud to do list on my resume
A Nazi that I represented right
Or like a cake a cake
Writing like I'm in there defending his free-speech rights
Principally
Not like doing a bunch of underhanded stuff to do it but like sure
Maybe I'd even be proud if I have like one or two or even three Nazis or if I had
We're Nazis are five Nazis or something like that
Your number for Nazis is way higher than bye.
Weird Cavalcade of people around this guy
Through my switch about Mark and dogs get involved in these cases
Yeah
When we discovered what his professional history really is
When when we discover the things that he has done in his career all of a sudden like it stopped being about like this guy seems weird maybe hangs around.
And so we brought a bunch of briefing about that
Our courts said no marker and Ava cannot come anywhere near this
Will not happen
And now there is Dave actually launched an appeal on that
Like they understand the default judgments have been interred
They have an appeal those yet
Margarita's is appealing already
That's important we need Mark Randazzo in the in this
But I'm going to be occupying the next bit of the parties times is that in so
All of that anyway I know something I'll follow this case here that's all we'll be online at the court of appeals website follow along
They're they're trying to appeal Mark Randazzo being allowed to be involved in the next stages of medical case
During these last stages exactly
Development
Indication Case Files you can go look at it
Resume your ears now we representing young man in who is that used to be in the shooter in Parker
And totally falsely
A ninja that a different voice
In that case longtime corporate
He's been in that case Connie Merrick towel
Is representative.
Appeared for all three years
I can enforce cases we've had
Now we're up to the seventh floor
But in Parkland it's been just that one lawyer the entire
I've seen towns named like like
Historically like you've been around with Alex's stuff
For quite a while
And insult his name's on all that stuff so he's been around 4-H
Maybe more than a decade
Well in the midst of the Fontaine case real recently after the default judgment since mother things went down
Eric Chou move to withdraw as counsel
And
Filed a motion with the
The court saying
I Can't Tell You Why
Communication
But my continued representation
Would force me to violate the Texas disciplinary rules of conduct inviolate my ethical
Nobody knows what that means
Nobody has any idea what the conflict is what the unethical thing that he would be forced to do is what did he notice
You can speculate a million different ways Under the Sun but from attorney-client we don't know
And he withdrew now in the front in case they have no
When you say we don't know what that means I disagree we know exactly what that means we just don't know specifically what to do
Your honor and Alex requires me to wear parachute pants every time I go to the courtroom I cannot
Will you do that
Let me give you a like a
Superba 91
Right.
I don't think it is
Right like if I'm representing
And I've been representing them for three years whatever in this year
And then all of a sudden I realized I find out
For some reason
That that
But that client and who he suing
Is actually Somebody I Used To
Wright's Lake
I'm straight or something like that
Like I see you when you come to me and you want us to Target
And I'm representing you suing turn
And then somewhere in the suit I reckon I realized
Oh s*** I used to represent Park
But I didn't know that because they must a different name they must have been named something different back
That could give you that would lead to the same result
Right now
It is
Is you be able to disclose that
Because like your representation Target like that's all
This is something inside the relationship somebody.
Relationship itself and therefore nobody knows like
Even though it deals with that relationship you know that there's something up to go going on there
Your honor I would like to withdraw Alex just watch
Better Call Saul and he's got some ideas
Would be
This client asked me to do something 6 months ago
And I thought it was all above board when it happened
And I recently discovered facts that say that's not above board and now it
I will need to reveal it or leave one of the two
So we don't know if that kind of conflict exists or not we don't know and so
It's just so
Deranged
It's
But that's just got to develop I think actually
Alex's said that that case is already he already beat that one
According to his public statements on his side I believe
If your lawyer quits you win right if you suck so hard your own lawyer quits the government
Like there's nothing we can do
Yeah what is argument
Is that
That suit
Is against Free Speech systems kit Daniels and the company because Kate Daniels going
Alex Jones never did like pre-approved his article to get on and say something
Individual
Right but it's Infowars in Kate Daniels
Are defendants there so I was like hey I'm free but all your money is next door at the
The studio at Daniels
Independent contractor literally never met the guy before honestly have
What I hire someone named
Kit
Please
But the hiring process
After Nero is awesome
I think Alex would take offense to it you can't have an old-timey Western hero that are not Alex
Yeah
I have a couple more questions I wanted to run by you if that's alright
The first one that was
This is more of a sort of like a personal
Sort of sense
Did this come as a surprise to you seems like it did the default judgment in the kinetic
McKay's
No no I don't think it did
Okay let me put it this way
I'm no not that
Default judgment was coming in Connecticut price for about 3
Like that seems pretty obvious to me that that's what they were heady
Yeah
It really is
I'm not mr. I'm just looking behind me
You know what I mean like I'm I know where we've been I know where they're going
And I see the orders they're getting and I'm like
I remember being there
An insult like I know where they're going and they're just going right in our way cuz it's the same place there's nothing like you said it's nothing to different about it
It did surprise me
I guess it's what really surprised
Once they were in super hot water and check
That they didn't wise up
Little bit
Indian change their tactics a little bit both in Texas and Connecticut
Damage in Texas and not have this happening
That is surprising
After the summer I
I'm not surprised
What's happening
Battery app
Yeah I guess I guess the thing I guess you were saying was more surprising is
32 different
Sing
That got them in trouble there that then in Texas
Couldn't give
Default judgments against them for anything then
Really give it a try
And so yeah I don't think I was really surprised
I was surprised when I didn't get it in 2019 cuz I really thought I deserved what they did
Ridiculous
But I understood what was going on a chance on a PO begin their whatever and if they come back and they decide to go play nice
Give me another chance
When they came back after appeal this summer and then things just were
Just a mess just
Falling apart
I knew something was up then when they had the whole thing up in Connecticut where they released the playoffs information to
Hillary Clinton and all the weirdness I was like
Okay like any idea this was going to go normal
Is it.
Somi
There's only one way it can go through the water can only roll one day
What weight on the show until I knew where it was going
Sure. I think I said that
Today obviously reporter
Call me off the hook
I said 21 reporter
I always knew we were going to beach on
I just didn't think it would happen in this ridiculous
Bleeding a little bit that it didn't happen
Actually kind of
And part of it is
That the case is so
Obviously meritorious
That you don't need the default judge
You don't need it
It's it's
It's ridiculous like like
So and when Jones has the default judgment it allows him to point back to his bag out Railroad
Never found guilty
Yeah it is all just you know and so it does
Deflect
But I think on the other end
There's the other in that it is almost kind of poetic
That
It demonstrates like what an absolute ridiculous character use that he won't even participate misu try to respect the family's ability
Have their day in court against them
Yeah yeah this does almost even proves our case
Dial
You can even participate in the lawsuit without being completely malicious like
Yeah.
Elevated but I am your right
It sucks going to be like
Everything's in the hand of 12 jurors and you can never plan anybody
Yeah I think I think maybe some cold comfort is that you know you can really look at those as
Sim being basically a coward
And not being willing to engage with this process
What you can only assume is probably
Keen awareness
Was not going to win this is going to very much loose
I think that masculinity and bravado is such an important thing to him and just sort of
Being able to look at this and be like well you couldn't even stand up and and face
Responsibility and prove yourself right
If you are if you were right the largest problem though is it seems very clear
To me that once the case was brought
And his lawyers actually spoke to
To him he was essentially like okay
I've lost
And so we managed to do is ring the end
F****** democracy out of it
For an extra few years
It's a good theory but the
Problem with that is that
I really think the Jones was led astray by
Really bad
Feel like some people came in and told him you are going to win
You're going to be a Larry Flynt Hero at the Supreme Court if you don't and you are going to win and we're going to vindicate
And they feed his own BS back to him and say Yes is all Global shows are coming I know two people who have said that to him
Oman Air
Also please do not fill in an amount for this check
It's very interesting that
They have stronger Malone this idea that
He doesn't
I'm not
Look
When we depose dimin some of the stuff we asking about Discovery and and I really do feel some of it was honestly yes
The lawyers
That's why we went out for the lawyers on now. Does B
But
I think they really did at some point the worm started
The turn that the only way that these lawyers could
Could convince him that there series of
Billiards wasn't
Due to
Really bad
Potentially actionable things on Jones Beach
Like Mike
If if
You got to said Jones has the right to bring them
Malpractice if there was nothing you can do that there was malpractice
Is done in the ways case was.
I think we have a next chapter
The I think what
Seems to be from
What we see how the
Court proceeding to play.
Is it they convince them
But know this wasn't a result of anything that we've done wrong
It's because the system is rigged against you
Near the kangaroo court this is a show trial
I don't deserve that
From my position like from everything I can tell based on
My hours of listening to him
I don't think anyone needed to convince him of that there's a conspiracy against him
The beginning
He was going to win
He was really going to these Court
And he was going to prove himself right he was going to embarrass me and the globalist and all of that
I got your man
Like like that
Why do
He really did think that for a while
He was relishing
Watching me fall on my face
That was something could not wait to see happen
And when it didn't happen every time his attorneys came back to him and said you owe more money now you have to pay to
We owe more attorneys fees now
Then they just convince them you're getting railroaded
Not that we're doing anything wrong until you're getting railroaded
And then
That's what caused him after the default judgment just feel kind of free to speak out like
Is because you just met
J's on his show
Singing that are judge was by Cano's satanic animal with the globalist pedophile pizzagate people or whatever
Nnn like
Has now just done the worm turns out you now you just don't play now I'm just not participating I'm not
A lady's people game
I'm just expecting that you speak
An absolute circus
I don't think anything's going to happen normally Ultra
Yeah hit his prediction today was that he's going to get default judgment in the second
Stage of the case as well
But he also is claiming that he's not being allowed
To participate
In the
This Wing is
Is penalty today
I'd be happy for respect whatever way he would like to
Seems like it was his choice
That's the radio version of the
Hold me back
Again I'm doing
Why I like to come on your show I know it
Weird and I know we custom say weird stop and maybe we're a little bit
Different than
But the problem is is like
Mainstream media is really bad about getting these stories wrong and they're really bad about just taking whatever they want
And using it to this
Do their agendas in Jonesville used at 2
So I do like to use this kind of form to stay
The things that are being said
About the conduct of the attorneys about the conductor
The courts
Plaintiff
They're all this b******* number to true
Like it's not true
Yeah and it's it's so disrespectful to see a person
Who's already gone through all these wings
An ending now gets these orders against him and is now just like no that's that's why I said like I can't
I have to get on here and tell you like these things that are being said by Jones out of his mouth are simply not true
Well I think you're preaching to the choir
Travel from here right like Derpy Derpy people watch this s*** and it's not just the people you think right
My
My words are kind of being washed a little bit and end when I go out on Tuesday if I was to go on MSNBC and try to fit
What I'm trying to say there I ate would be butchered to hell
But when I'm here with you guys I think I can save the realities of what the public rec
I've had to sit by and watch him get on his show
The most insane things about this case
That it it feels liberating to be able to down
Say the three things are truant
This is a wreck
And people will take my word
And we definitely appreciate you being willing to offer that perspective
And I come talk with us
Said that means a lot
If that's all right before we leave
We were running on
And I'm sure we just ramble when we go down together
I was curious
If there are any consequences that he might be facing in Connecticut that are different
Then the possibility of what he could be facing the Intex
If they're both Financial
Yeah they're both Financial but I mean
Those one difference is Texas content walls are a little bit
Horseshoe
We can just send you a jail if you're an ass all too often
Judges doing prison people from time to time when they do things that are wrong that happens less up in Connecticut
But yeah we're basically looking at the same kinds of
But judgments
And writs of garnishment Richard attachments
And just like I guess assets wrapped up in that who like okay
Yeah you didn't leave the ability to Levy against the
Corporation itself and all.
Eichler's there's a lot of
There's not a heavy-handed stuff you can do to enforce the judgment
I mean what you've described so far though I cannot imagine the nightmare
After all of the legal aspects are over
Just that like
Okay
Let's a portion what it is that we need to give to people
Through two different courts
Through two different lawsuits through multiple plaintiff through all of this stuff
They're going to have to find a really really evil account
Stick it out of some of that s***
And we're going to have to find some some pretty aggressive accountant some yeah yeah
It's
It's like CSI accounting you know what I mean like it's going to be some stuff like that and so. That'll be I mean who knows
How long is The Last of course cuz you get out early
Burdick
And so we'll have to see where that goes there's not always thought he go to the Supreme Court have some great First Amendment
Knocking how dare you
You can go up at 8
I wasn't that
Disrespectful like I was
That much of a contemptuous
That's never going to work so you really don't have an appeal
You're right
That we when you talk about like always champagne time yeah when you have both sets of cases
Default
And therefore you know it's neither of them was a fluke they're not get no return
Yeah
The turkey done
It feels like the appeal Avenue he could have would be like
Taking it to the Supreme Court whether or not people can have default judgments
Legal concept that seems like
Possible thing for him to engage in
And I don't think he would win that
No not mean like why would you at that point I mean it's some point you're going to
Close up shop and figure out gas
Pouring good money after bad so I don't know what's going to happen
Cricket you know I want to say that
The only thing I know is we're going to go to his trial
I don't know I might just be a piece of paper
Well Alex has sworn that he's going to keep going no matter what
Even if he loses all his money he will continue the Infowars
And I look forward to that
I look forward to the possibility of us having
More high-tech skills
That would be fun
Overnight
Thank you so much for joining us I think we should
She probably every we've been
I feel like it's been about an hour and a half
Longer than I anticipated but I've had a great time too
Play the whole hour like
You want to let the paper on my
Patron but
I think our audience particularly likes long episodes oh yeah so
I have no problem with that
They they yell at me when it's a fit when they stop having episodes that were like 3 hours long
I don't know
They're weirdos
Thank you so much my Facebook this is an ongoing thing we got to keep it up
I can't wait for the next update
Bobbitt we'll figure it out
Alright
Have a good one
Alright now that the 1998
And
Conversation with Mark Bankston
I feel like I'm an emotional place where I can actually get to this
I'll do it
We'll talk about
About November 5th
I think you have to leave the studio I don't think you have that I think you're just too mad to talk about that the crew
Yeah we start here on the 15th and Alex's
Concerned that
Patriots
Getting jammed up
Except for Kyle Rittenhouse
SWAT team
Being denied trial by jury
Being imprisoned this is the weaponization
Sherry
In this country there still
I'm honorable people in the Judiciary like you're sitting in the Kenosha
Actually doing a fair trial
Poros control Jones Austin Texas and
Connecticut
Corruption
Mafia level organized
Just just
Sweet lawlessness
Here's a great example of
Overhead shot please
November
Associated
Brush
Jones loses lawsuit over Sandy Hook
Oak conspiracy
Yeah
I wonder why he chose those
Two specific
Cities for where the globalist have really taken over
I don't know
Rodger
Some of the examples
Of the Patriots were getting jammed up or pretty fun to cuz it
It's James O'Keefe
And
True
Steve Bannon getting indicted
I just think that's really funny that Alex
Steve group cuz he hates
Basically called for his death I mean who's not calling for anybody's death these days
I had it at such a traitor
That he definitely didn't do that I said he did
I'm so Furious that he stole in the name war room.
But also he's a great man standing up to the globalist
Very confusing but whatever you have to do in order to make your own Vicks
Jim Hood being in our losing these cases by default
I have to fit into a larger narrative in
That's a perfect way to do it
So Alex's
He didn't actually lose the
These cases
Which is 4
Play the sidelines of the associated
Rush
Jones loses lawsuit over Sandy Hook
Conspiracy
Now what really happened
Just came out
Again
Now it's
November
Default there but before I show you this
What's happening in Connecticut
Father of Sandy Hook victim
When's defamation lawsuit against Alex Jones
That's from
Did I lose the suit
Elementary School
Klamath shooting ever happen
Goes on to say I've lost the suit
Contacted AP they said suicide we're not changing
That's the level here if anyone wants to understand what's going on against Infowars that we deal
MarketWatch headliner was Associated Press 100 times
If your list
Cling to this let me see if this is the tone you're getting
There are headlines that I lost these cases
Is now writing the present
Right but also
They've lied about me losing cases in the past
So maybe this is meant to sort of implied
They're lying now
Right and I lose the cases they've lied about the cases before
That feels like the only interpretation
That you could have to him bringing up this
Other headline
Discuss
The current headline mean I guess the other thing that he's trying to say is that it's like a propaganda thing
To make you feel like he's a loser or something I have no idea what he
Are you saying other than
Maybe I want
Yeah
That's the sense I get which makes it so confusing when he immediately
Says this
Contacted AP they said suicide we're not changing it
Level what's going on
This didn't happen
The singing Texas
The thing in Connecticut
Wait what
Why'd you bring it up I don't understand what the point is here sometimes they like maybe I didn't leave the floozies
They did not lie I lost these f****** case
Got to be honest
They're straight-up I lost be
I just was soaking
Confused by like what even are you trying to get at here
I can usually suss out like what
The point is
It is almost like a nervous tick like he just has to
To bring up some
Whataboutism that was the only thing that came to mind or something
Map to be a roadblock
Send a text with Alex discusses the default judgments like the other ones he's been
Subject to auto repair
Guilty
Hookah
No
Show me somebody doesn't show up
Position
I was reading the news for you
California
The judges just do that
Yeah we know you should do
I need a source on this
Democrats in California
Alex's correct that diesel judgments are uncommon but
Because most people accept their responsibility to
To take part in legal proceedings
Society typically like if you are innocent you want to be able to have your day in court before you're innocent
Absolutely
Is there a Tetra sure
If your
Guilty
I guess probably don't want to go to court but you have a responsibility to
If you don't go to court
Sure
I guess just
I mean I guess dragging your feet was an option for murder cases all alone
Even though this is rare as it's not like
Beautiful drug
Never happy
And Alex should be super were this and his buddy John McAfee had a
The default judgment against his neighbor in Belize who was murdered
Forcing people judgment is one of the preferred strategies of high-profile people who don't want to have to engage with the legal system and civil case
Like R Kelly and Cuba Gooding
Junior dip
It's not hard to think that Alex's
Refusing to cooperate with the discovery process
Because he is something he really doesn't want to be
Like the exact nature of his finances or sources of fun
There's probably a good chance he knew he was going to lose these cases if they ever want
To try also
Lose anyway why not protect your business secrets
And simultaneously create a situation where you can claim you weren't actually found guilty
This is a good
PR strategy
But it probably won't matter
And it doesn't affect the real world
He's going to be on the hook for so much money
And it's already too late
Generally for him
To do all that much about it
He might be able to get some kind of
Appeals going but that's not going to go anywhere he spent the last
For years dragging this out
So much so that people
Went through it
Entire f******
President
Ticket
I'm really interested to see what happens
Throughout this case
Pretty much all of his legal Avenues are exhausted
And like we talked with Mark like there's the possibility that he
He could like
Want to challenge the validity of
Default judgment share but I don't
I think that would work I think it's a waste of time and honest
Leslie
Like
I don't know
I like who would be in favor of that
I mean
From what I understand
Appellate judges are somehow even more
Unconcerned with human life than most other.
I just feel like
I'm getting two two judges in two different states
Having to send them cases that they default judge
I need to wait another three years for me to handle
It seems incredibly unlikely
My process is going to be fun to watch
Or at least into
So Alex has something really gross now
Is it dealing with the system trying to
Kill the first
What happened
You don't know what really happened
You think about Sandy Hook you think about the name
Brainwashing
That's such a disgusting expression of Alex's out of
Control narcissism
Like how dare he be so self-centered that he thinks
When you hear the word Sandy Hook
The first thing you think of it
Miss him
I study for Alex for a living and he's not even the first thing I think of when I think of Sandy Hook
He's just an absolute monster who can't
Experience anything in life unless it revolves around himself
It honestly kind of makes me sad
Because ultimately what you end up realizing is
But there's a fair amount of people in the world who base their political beliefs on what they
I think is researched information
But it's really just a product of Alex's Moody narcissistic helper
Yeah and that's
Really a bummer
Yeah I mean that millions of people have allowed their reality to be shaped by a narcissistic out of
Control Manchild is probably bad
Yeah
But have you considered what would it be like if everybody was rational and reasonable I mean obviously if everybody was rational
We would be murdering each other in the streets
Should be a lot more boring
If we everybody was rational
It's definitely true
But
That sucks
Cuz you know what you
Pick up when you think of Sandy Hook
Complete tragedy of the event
You don't think about Alex Jones
And him having the
The gall to say I don't really know what happened
At this point in time
A lot of people have told you very specifically what happened there oh yeah you got very wrong oh yeah
Laudable
The prediction about the next
Phase of his trials now that he's lost all of them by a default
And he can make this prediction come true on his own
Decide
Default
We're going to double default
They're going to double default
And not even let me be at the
Child decide how guilty
Is a joke
Kangaroo trial if we oughta show trial
Call a ridiculous fraud
What are they going to be freaked out
Spent more money
Fighting this
I'll probably ever
The CEO of Pfizer
Came out and said that
People talking bad about the vaccines are working for
What do you do with this commercial commercial sound like you're drunk
Another commercial I just woke up
3 in the morning is recording on the f****** self
I'm also I know for a fact that you have a standing invitation
Into that courtroom
Creepy voice
I think about it
He's eating my ears Dan I'm wearing headphones
I want to see
Getting double defaulted in the
It's going to be his fault if he does
The trial is about determining what is a fitting Financial penalty and if Alex doesn't cooperate with discovery on this
But like by refusing
Turn over the appropriate financial documents
F*** around and get another default judgment
If he cooperates though and nothing has every ability to use every opportunity to
Can shut down Alex's show except
Himself and he can talk big all he wants but I have absolutely zero doubt that he
He would quit
If you didn't have the flashy Studio
The weird pill line that he runs
Himself the ability to travel wherever you want
Buy things like
The ability to pay a staff together headlines for him and work out all the technical aspects of the show
He would quit in a second if you didn't have those
You'd be losing essentially all of the things that allowed to pretend to be a legitimate show and sets him apart from any
Dumbass whole on YouTube
Who makes videos about vaccines are evil
He beat a washed-up guy wet his time and he didn't get anything done
The hungry Young Buck
Conspiracy theorist
To probably resent him
I'm trying to take up space in their world
Siphoning off a tension and possible donations
They could be going to them
Personally I hope
He does continue to do the show even if he goes broke just
Because someone who watches
Is the show I think he'll be a fascinating narrative Arc
I don't think it's going to happen though I don't think Alex has the humility to go back to being a DIY guy absolutely
Imagine trying to do it by himself
Makes me think of Steve
Pieczenik and how his wife has to turn on the record
Computer for I was if I was wreck
And I was looking at the looking
The tea leaves
Cuz I be like I got to get out of here otherwise I am going to be working on Infowars 2.0 with
My f****** dad for the rest
This is my life. I need my inherited it now
Being handed out
Yeah I eat I think
I do agree
Can stop his show except for himself
It's just a matter of
You know what you're willing to
Except sure
Doing things
Ford no money
Are you willing to accept
Are you willing to knock
Be able to grandstand the way that you do but I don't think he is I just I think he's
And you have to figure you know it
If he loses that
Status goes right back down to the bottom tier
It's going to be open
Season on cannibalize
You're going to get
Points Zoe's
Easy for s******* all over Alex in that realm we already see it now like when he shows up for these interviews on like Rogaine
Dinner with Patrick bet-david
Paul
Like you just get too wasted
Dumbass
I'm like eventually that'll wear out if he wasn't like
I have to show that look super drunk on a YouTube show
Yeah
Fun fun
So people keep asking Alex like
How you doing
How you doing man not well there's trouble
Superbad
How you doing real bad don't worry about me man
Job
And I'm like what
Forced to wear mask
Taping them to their heads
And screaming at them until they're bad because they're white
Won't you think of the white children children
People ask me how I'm doing with these lawsuits and I say
Don't worry about me worry about the white kids that one that one really is saying the quiet part off of
Also don't ask Alex
How he's doing if you want to know how
Alex is doing
Ask Alex whether or not the world is going to end well actually that's really interesting because this next
He's talking about how the good times are over for America
Know that you're in a good mood are over
Roaring 20th century women 21st century
Is abruptly hitting a brick wall
What's the surface
Brace yourselves like when you're in a really bad car wreck
Side of a highway in Bangladesh
What are you doing
Suburban
Suburban Inn
Shut off spun around backwards
50 ft magnet
Plunging into trees
And got away with just concussions were saying brace for impact
It's so hard it broke
Both our chairs back
Flying over the main
Would like 20 years
It felt like forever
Bracing for impact
That's a wild Tornado Story
I don't think I've ever heard it
Before and I've listened to a lot of his show
The part of me wants
To say that's probably bulshit but it's actually possible that happened there super deadly
Have been documented cases of people being inside cars that are actually picked up by tornadoes and they survive
I don't think it's a super common thing
Although there are plenty of tornadoes in Texas
Slits
Conceivable
I don't believe it but I'm open to
To the possibility of it being
It's it's that that's where I'm at
It's closer to
Oh I think you probably are happens
Come on
It's been
How long
It's been more than five years
It's been more than five years and I have not heard
This totally awesome story about surviving a f****** tornado before are you shiting me
Watch a lot of Degrassi
The Canadian team show I'm aware
And one of the things
Camille never forgive them for Drake
Me and my buddy Nikki gifts one of the things that we were taken aback by is how like
Yeah a lot of the stuff in these episodes are things that happen
Into
Do you know people in school
Difficulty
Something growing up course
Cast of kids
Everything
Happens to them
Not likely it's a bit of a little outside of the norm yeah and I
These kids are lucky and unlucky it's just nuts
I feel the same way about Alex like
Possible that you're in a car and you survive the tornado throwing you into a tree Shore
Motherfuking nonsense things in your life
Living in a never-ending the Days of Our Lives episode where everybody has an evil twin and s***
It's going crazy I know don't know its Passions
Because
You notice that we're about to hit a brick wall just after Alex has a really bad piece of personal news
It's almost like
He's about to hit a brick wall in the form of really heavy monetary penalties
She's projecting that feeling of eminent trouble out of the auto
He's basically just lashing out at them and trying to make them feel the same bad things he's feeling
And it's a childish
He talks a bit about the
Case like just the same sort of stopped like
Georgia
I didn't really lose
That kind of stuff at the beginning of the episode and I was like
Ticket to some
Give me something
He's got a story here
About the new
The new Pfizer vaccine
Formula
United Nations in absolutely ruthless
Families
Have even
Nbcnews and others reporting that old
Okay it's true
There is a heart attack drug being added to the children's vaccine
But it's not for heart problems it says
Bass
To the shot
Are you going to research it has nothing to do with being a base it's not saline water
Oh my God
Jose just flipped the vaccine
They just come out and say hello
You're right about his had the heart attack drug
We just don't put saline in the shots anymore
Who's a bunch of bulshit question here is tromethamine
And it's been put into the Pfizer vaccine that's definitely true
But it's not related to heart attack
And the exploration of replacing it
Little more complicated
Alex's make
Methenamine
An ingredient in the moderna vaccine
In all along
And the reason is really straightforward
Trimethylamine is a very effective preservative
If it helps increase
Drug Shelf
This is actually a really big deal because one of the arguments advisers made about being unable to
December vaccine too many parts of the developing world
Is it has as Reuters but it a quotes
Storage requirement at ultra low temperature
Which of this will help address
Tromethamine is used as a stabilizing ingredient many vaccines
Even a homolog diabetes
Medication
Reuters notes that it's also used as a stabilizer in many fragrances and cosmetic products
As for the part about replacing saline it's not that it's replacing that saline solution the way is out to sort of
Implying
That feeling is just salt and water and you can help used clean wounds or reduce dehydration
The city limits being
Replaced by the dramatic mean is phosphate buffer
Saline which is a very
Something different
Perfect from
The standard Saline
Solutions
Phosphate buffered saline is disodium hydrogen
Phosphate added to it
In this has the effect of helping
Stabilized
The pH level of a of a solution
Attitude
However for the needs of this vaccine tromethamine can do what PBS can do and then some
It makes more sense
Switch that up
The thing about this being a heart attack. Drug is also kind of
Dubious
The traumatomy itself
I mean isn't a drug really
That you give to someone to effectively reduce their risk
I'm having a heart attack
The primary connection between this drug and cardiac issues is the tromethamine is used to
Treat metabolic acidosis
Which is a common side effect of someone
May experience
If they're having
Cardiopulmonary bypass surgery
It's not the tromethamine to dresses be hard
It's used to deal with a common side effect of the bypass surgery it
Itself
In the interest of total fairness it is true that a small amount of heart attacks are thought to possibly be due to metabolic acidosis
The causal link is a little bit iffy
There's an important qualifier
Doesn't really help with heart attacks per say
It just helps with metabolic
Acidosis which is
The condition where a person's body is too acidic
Or where the kidneys can't filter the ass
Acid in the body quickly enough
The acid base level in check
Typically this
Connection
Between metabolic acidosis and a person having a heart attack
Kissimmee elderly who are experiencing difficulty with other
Games like the kidney
And generally this
The situation is that someone
Has late-stage
Chronic kidney disease
It's not really
Relevant
Did that story that Alex is trying to tell
This doesn't even work as a conspiracy theory for Alex
The point of the globalist plans of the vaccine is supposed to be to kill everyone off
So what's up
Does it make for them to create a vaccine that gives
People heart attacks and then change
The formula to include something that would stop people from having
Did they like change their mind
What the f*** are we doing
So
It's going to kill everybody
Anywhere from two weeks
25-year
Two weeks to 100
So now
The globalist plan after having already succeeded as Alex's said
I mean
Right everybody who's already taken the vaccine is going to die soon
Leave him then yes
They have effect
Actively put heart attack bombs and everybody
So that you don't need a new formula
Nope
But it does address some of the issues of stability of the vaccine
Itself
So that is so it's a better murder
I guess I guess that might be the way that
I guess you stumbled onto possibly a way that you could twist this for a kid
Conspiracy
They're trying to make it more shelf-stable so it can be given to more parts of the world to give heart attacks
Two more people
But Alex's house
We've stumbled once again upon a better
Conspiracy theory
The well
Dammit
So Alex is mad about
NBC or MSNBC anchor named Stephanie ruhle
Song about how Americans
Can pay for
Inflation affected Prada
There's a little bit tone-deaf
But Alex
Is
Is a little bit off base here to
NBC anchor
Stephanie
Rule
What's a salary
Tiffany ruh
Ellie
I was asking that your answer on that
What's her salary at NBC News cuz she's
Sitting there
Telling you that you're getting $40,000 a year as a single mother
You just need to learn that you had it too well
So Stephanie ruhle absolutely does
Like millions of dollars a year at MBC although I'm sure she does
If I was wants to talk about how she's really rich
You should
Salary
MBC
HP a conversation of her activity you in
The world of hedge funds
Which I'm pretty sure brought in way more money than anything
ABC
So she works
Hedge funds
So much fun
And now she's on TV
Yeah she's on MSNBC isn't Tom steyer
She told everybody just paper
Yes she did say that the average Americans can afford to handle inflation and well she's probably right about most of the people in her
Circle
That came off as a painfully unaware state
She's gotten a lot of backlash and rightfully so
I'm not sure that her make
Dumb comments on NBC's really the hard-hitting news that Alex likes to imagine he covers but
I don't know I probably just leave this alone with him and deal with him or press
Issue like everyone's dying
Yeah I mean you know in my book
F*** her
Of course but also like
On our list of s***
To deal with she's way low down there really rank
Unless you're just drying
To engage with the attention economy engage and get some points off of that
And then it's all forgotten the next day so who fuc
Yeah
I think I think that there is
The conversation to be had about like
People in the
24-hour news networks people say stupid s*** on there all the time
And maybe maybe doing a better job
And in terms of some of that
Get any
Closer to achieving that
By talking about the individual in
Instances
And making a big deal out of the individual times
People say stupid s***
I don't know
Tybee I might be wrong in that but
It seems Mighty trivial for something that I like
Thank you.
I mean the D idea of
You know like
TV news requires a
Top-down rewrite
All all
Page one get f****** rid of it and then start over
So what one of them does I really don't care
I hate I hate to
We can never really go back I don't think but I don't think the 24-hour news channels are really approach
They're bad
But I don't know what to do
Anyway Alex is convinced that this Stephanie ruhle makes millions
5 million
Salary at MSNBC is 150,000 a year
But she
Decimated
So I guess the correct
So
There you go
According to pay scale the average salary for news anchors at
NBC is
60 9370
$18
With a high range being 100
Ben Ten Thousand
No one is presented a shred of evidence to prove that she makes 18 times the high end of the salary range
But that's the salary that's listed for her on one of the very sketchy celebrity net worth type sites
Sure the two million is the figure he'll get from legit
Is the name of the website it's run out of Nigeria
Most likely Alex chose this one because all the other sites that you can find the site
Significantly lower salaries for her it doesn't work for the point
He's trying to make
A lot of them
I have figures like 200,000
I was just talking s*** about the
Does two million a year.
I think part of the reason that he thinks of his even within the realm of possibility
Might be that he makes millions a Year everyone else does too
Media and I make millions of dollars a year
So assumably that's just a guess on my part
The story about how out-of-touch Stephanie ruhle is I need might be just
Exposing Howard touch
It's a
As per usual
Wapo
The Washington Post
Here's another one Washington Post
MSNBC both
Call
Republican
You're not allowed to be a Republican
Rules prohibit media Outlets
Referring anyone who's the Republican as normal
Politically correct
Krampus
If I'm not mistaken and I'm not we're just
Months removed from Alex going on and
Extended campaign pushing for the outlawing of the Democratic Party
Even if the Washington Post said the things he's saying it's kind of childish for him to have this response
Let's do it he's just like
Doing what I do
Do that
You just mad about Jennifer Rubin going on in MSNBC show and saying there should be rules
Go to call Republicans normal anymore
It's not normal pilot
For whatever
This is a far cry from Alex literally advocating for the outlawing of the democratic party on multiple occasions and again
Such a trivial story to be spending
Time on
At times it feels like it shows just a grouchy old man gets mad at cable news
Disney wants to yell about
Yeah that sounds about right to him now he's just sitting on his reclining chair with
Glass of scotch
Set matters like I'm mad at the ladies
Jennifer Rubin said something I don't like
I I mean but if
If one day we just woke up
And you were about to listen to the show
And all the sudden you
Just tired
Lineup
Lionel Lionel Lionel and Alex came out was like
I hate bookbags on the train
It'd be the best day of my life
I don't know if I would enjoy that I think I would lose interest in you
Pretty quick
So Alex
Has buddies in the real me
Josie
They've been getting in contact with
You don't have a lot of people I know a lot of great people
Texting me
Apache hey
You know the inside baseball on this you should respond
But they're pumping out
Every newspaper
Japan to Germany to the United States did you know
Tens of thousands
Posted
Stones found guilty
That's a judge
Totally abusing their discretion
Absolutely. Invasion
So yeah Rogan wants a statement
Maybe Tim pool cuz
Spell except
Contempo pool is in town we know that
Truth imagine imagine how sad would that be
Quite
So yeah Alex's getting jammed up
Judgment fraud
When we talked to Mark
One of the things that we discussed was the bank record
Scan the way Alex
Who has an accountant
Clean them up a little bit to be a little
One Step a little bit in the right areas you know Alex talking about that
Default
Respect
Gave them
What I said or did
Just give it to another planet the default this and I want to make him do it all the way and then they just said this isn't your real thing
You can't prove a negative
They said well
Not
QuickBooks file it's insane
It's a spreadsheet
Database
It goes back to the beginning
QuickBooks
From this date to that
Spreadsheet
That's what I'm defaulting for
Spreadsheets can
Every transaction at this coupling
That's outrageous
They were always going to be salted
And they're always going to do it at the
Appeals court level 2
Illustrate the whole thing
That gives us the time
Forward
This is not my battle
This is not my War
This is kind of like
Chihuahuas that has
Rabies is biting me in the leg
I got
Allegory
Chihuahua chewing on my leg
Rabie shots later
Triage things like
Cash
That's a little bit of
Confusing I guess I understand the point of his metaphor
Somebody needs
Call QuickBooks
Because I mean
Obviously they had this massive oversight where you can't like choose what dates you want to print out the files
Like there's no way you can own when you go into the QuickBooks
Software you can only download all of your finances or none
Is really specific about that
I don't like Half Steppin
File from date today haha I'm QuickBooks
I insist that I my software is only used
For the entire history of a company
Another
Work QuickBooks
It's going to take awhile to download your files there's a part of me that legitimately
Thanks like maybe Alex
Doesn't use QuickBooks
Like maybe the issue is that like his finances are on like
Sheets of paper
Something maybe that's why
If you walked into his office and there was just a big like
Gallon drum of receipts you be like
The HR representative
Torino's like maybe his nephew is
Everyone get paid
Bullion
It's strange also did the
The attempt
To be like I'm not even mad about
It's so great
We've hit a massive roadblock and everybody's going to die
I'm not a
I never actually even really cared about these laws
This is essentially the same thing that happened with the Chobani lawsuit
Defender
I will die or be proven right
Apology
It's
Blustery nonsense until there's a decision
Loses or is going to lose
It's a turning tail and be like I didn't really care about that at all
But also the country is gone
Bonded us
Incredible news
Think that what's happening to me
Infowars
I know it's a symptom of the disease
Disease of corruption and
The end of the country as we know it
This is Modern Warfare run
I spend my time
Talkin HBO or talking to
The Wall Street Journal or
Running around trying to defend myself
Fake fangs
The implication of what Alex is saying is that if he does
Doesn't stay focus
Start the work
That he is doing the Pacific
He's doing correct all hope for the planet is lost
Narcissistic garbage no no
This is a rational
Clear-eyed understanding of the
Current circumstances
You put all of the math
Together
Get the order of operation
Worked out right at all
Cancels out until you get one mad
Look I mean the world will disappear and everything will fall apart if Alex doesn't interview with v
Meanwhile he'll go get drunk broken podcast the place where if he closes his eyes I imagine
He thinks everyone's
Like every time you might not understand object permanence
Everything is predator predicated upon whether or not ice
BND
I like that
In terms of
Such an illustration of narcissism
If I stop for a second
Do address
The fact that I just lost these cases
If I give it
Comment
Do a media Outlet about this
Do we we will
Lose the world
Hey bro I mean it's it's
Fun
Like
Default judgments
You know as we talked about with Mark the first time
You know they were like
This is exceedingly rare and they only use that they only really
Teach these in school you do now we've got Alex is an example of a teaching Law School
Why not
Remember
That in Psychiatry School
They're going to use Alex's of narcissism example as well he's going to be taught in a lot of different schools
Sure
Play exciting you might be taught in a rambling school to if there ever is such a thing
Cuz he starts talking but
Does Harry does a professional ramble about how he gets to stay in
A quiet place
The most
Opposition
Coupon
How you can fight back against those cuz we're very close to winning
Infowars
In this position
Champion for Liberty
Whiteboard app
But I also want to get knowing the end these evildoers will be punished will be.
False Flags
Blame me for them and others they already have
January 6th
Somebody's gotta.
The coward stand-ups
All I ask you if she's that you pray
Rainforest
You spread the word about the broadcasting
So we can go into this fight
B strong
And give it a hundred and 10%
Please pray for Infowars please pray for
Please pray for my family
Pray that
Focus and Clarity and
Calm
Steady heart
Mind and
In the high place
What quiet place
King David talked about
The most high
Quiet still place
Of the most high
You're doing great
The place
Home
Focused understanding
I am just
Moving forward and Cecile
Completely separate unrelated entirely amazing that shift is just
Professional
Wow
I would ask that you pray that God keep me in the place of the most high also free shipping
I mean
Just that you know how much I hate Commerce in religion pushed
Together in the way that he
He combines
The two of them
So good
Like a Prayer
Prosperity Gospel.
Teacher-parent to like you you and I and many other
People that the strategy
But at the same time like
He's consistently done it
4 years
Must be effective
Success
How many different Prosperity Gospel Zone more than one jet. Very successful way to do thing
Yeah I guess so people like to hear lies especially of God
What is telling them
Yeah
Not boy
So Alex went to San Antonio
Recently
And he got himself a
An interview with Mike Flynn
General Mike Flynn
Wow
Oh yeah real hard
Yeah I'm busy all the time so at this point
We hasn't aired that interview
And even like talking right now I don't believe you
Please put out any of it
Some thoughts about the
General Flynn
Let me just say this right now
Got an interview with a general Flynn
Saturday
Crowd of 5,000 people
Cornerstone Church
T-shirts
See him
Basically
Accustomed
To being a civilian leader
Gebrakan
A person that can be George Washington 2.0
Better suited than somebody
Like Trump
Understands that the
Yeah
Just
Wit
You want to do this again
You also didn't we hate fun for awhile
No I don't think so
That's fair that is fair
Mike Flynn
Alex has been
Rudy on board with
For the most
Possibly when there was a
The chance that it look like he was flipping on Trump
Remember a little stretch where Alex was
At least not into it but
He likes
I think I actually agree
Could be another George Washington my perspective
It's the dark version
End of our first president
We made some comments that we're going to get into it later when he was speaking at the Cornerstone Church in San Antonio over just
Before this
But it's also important to note that this was part of it wasn't
Just like a speech at a
The church that was part of the Fairly qanon leading reawaken America Tour
Other speakers included Mike Lindell Rodger Stone.
Q. Street Fighter
Former Overstock CEO Patrick Byrne and of course
Stella Immanuel the Ivermectin Doctor Who believes that we're living in Revelation
Lumos wizard promo code on her website to Alex's listeners can get 5% off their drug purchase
Very nice of her to do
Creeps and Weirdos were advertised speakers
Strangely missing from that advertisement was Alex
Zohid
Get a speaking slot at the event
No s*** god dammit either he was a surprise guest or they
Thought like we can't put them on the poster
It's too too much
See
That's
I think that's unjust
I do
I genuinely am mad about that they are ostracizing Alex
Compared to those murderers of idiots
Like what are we talkin about based on the assumption that Alec didn't just show up and
Mother like I will give you
Street Fighter talk I'm sure he could have five if he wants
Doesn't animation from the poster based on like we do honestly he's here
It might just be that he
Was unplanned
But yeah the clip I saw of his speech was mostly what you'd expect
It's just meaningless platitudes about how his enemies work for the literal devil are
How this is the most important time in human history
Mountains for General Flynn his speech was a little more into
There were news stories covering how he said quote if we're going to have one nation under God which we
We must we have to have one religion nation under God and one religion under God
As the founders wrote in the Constitution Dan it's so f***** up I don't really even know how to engage
Beige with it like
Today these are the people Gathering who yell about the Constitution all the time and there
Hero worshipping a lunatic ex-general is advocating something
In direct opposition to the First Amendment but I think we should do
Arkansas
Situational Duty
Which of course is to overthrow the United States government and turn this into the Opera
Chrissy just like the founders intended when they wrote that Constitution that specifically outlawed
Little bit f***** up or at least like
You talkin about
Eclipse
What was the last hope for the world
There's a time and you have to believe this almighty God is like involved in this country because this is it
This is it
This is the last place on Earth
This is this is The Shining City on the hill
This is the city on the hill the city on the hill
The city on the hill was mentioned in Matthew okay
It was mentioned in Matthew but then this guy by the name of wind
Mentioned it again
16:30
6030 okay before the country was formed
Just cuz
Several hundred years after Winthrop said that Reagan said it
So now
Flynn is assuming that was actually goes on to mention that Reagan said in the sort of part of the
The connection right but Reagan was just
Based on his stated beliefs on the way the cunanan the other right-wing communities respond to him
Splinters of the potential to be there George Washing
The first president of the Fundamentalist
International
Dictatorship they so desperately want to be
Yeah that's wild
I remember that
I really am blown away that these people with
The constitution in their f****** pocket
It's looking up
General Flynn
Obvious
Bulshit about nothing
I'm thinking
I want to overthrow democracy for that
That's what I want them
Wow so the global
Control pretty much every
Base because if you just Define
The globalist has anybody you don't like
Yeah you can say they have both
The houses of Congress
But you know they don't have they don't have the minds of
Most the city
Controls for election fraud
Portage School District
Enmeshment
After 8 year old girl
Hold them
They should be in prison Palm Beach County School District has ended a mask mandate just days after a second
School Board officials
They should all rot in jail
Face coverings
There's a fun story and I can see how Alex would want to present the idea that this
Greater shame to school board
The impetus to stop a mess mandating is Bob County
Palm Beach County Schools but that's for
And the children will lead
Florida's Department of Health had released an order that prohibited schools from having
Could opt out of
This school district however decided to go again
And that order
The second grader Alex is talking about it
The daughter of a woman named Bailey lashelle's and for about 2 months cheap
Suspended for refusing
Wear mask at school
Ultimately it wasn't her activism or the mom having her eight-year-old daughter go on Fox news shows
That ended the school district map
Text message Mandy
The decision was based on a Court ruling that
School District was in violation of the Department of Health order
And the fact that children could not be vaccinated
I am at local covid rates at Fallen traumatic
Decision
I was made to not lie
My parents opted out of children wearing
It's fun to imagine that a second grader yelled at school board and they were so taken aback by the truth
She was spitting at them that they
Howard and stop requiring masks but that's
Not true I throw this out here
And this might sound crazy
So if a noose
Food Network
Is
Rabbit
For any content that reinforce
Is there bull
They will grab up
Anyone
Anywhere
Who is fulfilled any part of their narrative
I put them on TV
Is it possible Dan
That might be an incentive
For people who want to get on TV
It might be
Or run for Congress has it seems like if you just
Sly about b******* and they your there's a TV network
Yeah
Alex does end up playing her speech
This
8 year old
And I don't
Really believe she wrote it herself
She might have I don't know but it
It's it doesn't strike me as
These last days I feel the Sword of Damocles hangs over all
Right
Stuff that I'm not sure eight-year-olds
Fully would be able to process but maybe you can I don't know
I don't know this kid
But it's
It's a little bit dicey
And it me saying that
I know that Alex would come back with something like what about Greta thunberg
Sure and I would say that there's a big difference between a teenager and an eight-year-old huge
I don't know if
An eight-year-old really
Necessarily be on Fox News
Giving anti-vax
I would even say that an eight-year-old
Being there giving a message of like climate
Control climate change
Awareness
I'm not sure I'm comfortable with that
Even
The kid
It's their parents making
Decision
I would say an eight-year-old saying something like
The world is better
That's totally great but that's
Vague very vague
Cousin eight-year-olds would want to keep it Bae
An eight-year-old saying I hope the world is better is a very inspiring message
Talking about carbon emissions
I don't I don't know what it would it brings to the table
Yeah
I'm comfortable with it in the same way that I was uncomfortable like
I don't know
10 year old who is racist
Exploiting children Dan and I don't get that
I just now
I only
You really decided to talk about this at all
Because what Alex says
Okay and my town for this because I think Alex is going on a protracted little bit of a ramble about
But how he's disappointed that his daughter
Just be honest with you
My oldest daughter is a wonderful day
And she want to go to public school.
High School
You just recently figured it out
Call Steve
Because the mask
She just wants to
Go back to Bravo
The way she wanted it
She said I don't want to be
Like you I love you I was
Thank you but I don't want to
I'm glad you're doing it for us
What she said
I want to go to school anymore since they want to let me wear the mask
Private School summer
What's happening
We got robbed
If you wish to go
The Graduate
I understand that
Sometimes your children don't do the things you'd want to do sometimes
Following your footsteps
This young lady
He's doing exactly what I asked my daughter to do
Go in there you need to get it fixed
Let them push everybody around that's
Our family does is we bleed
My daughter down
Oh God this is
Oh God
You know I would like
I would really I think
The problem with me not having kids
Get the thank you from
The kids that I don't have
That I didn't later on goat
Tell jokes about that more
Talk about them on this podcast or something along those lines
You're welcome unborn children
Get a sense
That there's a little bit of disappointment on Alex
That his daughter would not be his proxy
I'm in this fight that he wants to have
So he could get a lot of attention
That you don't want to go to school
Stand up in front of
All of your friend
And tell them that your dad Alex
Jones
Says
He thinks
Is all bulshit
You don't want to say that why
Give me any reason
You're telling me that it is very
Delicate moment in the duration process
Want to alienate yourself from literally everybody around you because
You're taking a stand
Publicly for my b******* I can't sing I can't think of any reason why
I just
I feel
Like
This is unhealthy and Alex should
Be
Expressing things that are
If I was his daughter I'd be hurt by
I will be furious
Time processing hours
Text talking about this eight-year-old that he admires
And being likewise what I wanted my daughter to do
I mean
That would be tough so f******
Shuffle
That's awful the new to somebody
To it because then there's the
I mean Ender was always
It's your Alec
Texas kid
Obviously
What's a f****** blackmail threat
If you don't do this the next time
I'm going to go on my show
And keep f****** talking about
It makes it clear that if you don't do the things that I want you to do
They'll be disappointed
And it's kind of
Likes is there's a similarity in here my love is
There's a similarity in it like if you're a high school basketball player in your not very good and like
Your do do you go to a game
And the opposing team is I have a really good player on it anytime it's like
I wish I was
F***.
I'm taking that kid out for pizza later none for you shitbag a slice of
Pizza Big 12
I get this eight-year-old on my show. My daughter
Anyway Alex Goes to calls
And he takes a call from a guy that has a dangerous
Let's go
Mike in England thank you for calling
Welcome to your life
Take my call in
Praise God
One thing
Text to but you haven't really told
Truth about it
Do you know a guy named David
Bronstein dr. David Braun
Yeah he he
Clinic on using
Iodine and
And when you do
Talk about using nebulizer
Nebulizer
Didn't really get it
How sexy
My wife and I were
We use X2
Do two drops of X2
And you have to really cut
Down on the
Recommend
The food safe
Cut it down like
Dixieland
Light
And every time we use it
It is
Just cleans the lungs
Cleans the song
Because that's where the
The majority of the ins
She's going to transfer into
Listening
And then it along
And it did
People just need to know I think if you interviewed
Dr. David
Maybe.
Because he is
Basically built on that
Fully aware that most people are deficient in iodine
Edina
Another substance was not
Atomic iodine good save good save just talk about the iodine don't talk about other guys basically telling you to inhale bleach
Listen listen
You do what you want to drink a little bit of a sad you don't want to drink a lot
So one thing it's super important to point out about what this color is dark
About is that
Food grade
Hydrogen peroxide is not food
That is a misnomer and it's just called because it meets the standards
Clean things
Places where food is packed
Kitchen handle
They can also be used in things like bleach
Pink flower
Please that is also
I guess it's close as we get to
Right
Cleaning out the
Score some
Context the type of hydrogen peroxide most people beginning from the store is
3% hydrogen
Peroxide
Food grade is 35%
There are some medicinal uses that makes some sense but it's a pretty much all of them are
Topical app
Applications
Like Stockton and corns or disinfectant
Small cuts
But even in these cases if
Got to be super diluted
Which is why the stuff you buy it
The store is 3%
I hate to say this but
Just because this guy is saying you should nebulize and inhaled
This bleach cocktail instead of drink it
That doesn't make it any more safe
This definitely can still be toxic
Particularly if you mess up your
When you're deluding
I would say that Alex has no idea who David bronstein is he was bluffing where the caller asked but this case he might
Exactly know who that dude is
Since I want to valak
Is anti-vax
Patriots doctor
Nicola has promoted him at the
Snow
But man f***** up f***** up call
Imo
What did you inhale
Hydrogen peroxide time consistently Blown Away
Because
The one truth about Humanity that
Stayed consistent
Through arant
Tire history
Is when people feel bad
A lot of them are going to try and solve it
With poison
That's a very weird thing that is
Stayed with us
Bumbleberry f****** beginning
Yeah
The Abbot
But it's kind of like
This eating poison ivy
Pissed off
Toxic
On some level maybe it'll kill the bad stuff
Right now I get that beat the idea of
2 -
I was worried about this color but I was even more worried that Alex is kind of Intuit
Medical doctors on Atlanta folks talking about what they would do
Help themselves or studies out there showing like you said
Highly diluted
Hydrogen peroxide
That alone
Cleans out
A few days while
Colonizing
According to research
We just talked about all this stuff here on air
And we probably should make a bigger deal.
Please.
But I have to say this but there are not studies that show that inhaling hydrogen peroxide through your nose
Clears out covid
Before it has a chance to hurt you
Why would anyone do that study that's just really dumb advice
There are some ideas for nasal irrigation
Or mouthwash
I like that type of thing
But it's not
Ingested
There's no compelling evidence or actual studies that show this conclusion but there's some ideas that if possible
Even then doing a nasal rinse
It's with a diluted solution is a bit
Inhaling hydrogen peroxide
Which there is
No evidence is effective
And in September actually
The Asthma and Allergy Foundation of America released a statement people that regardless
Do not put hydrogen peroxide in your inhalers
Dangerous to this and no good evidence showing it helps at all so
This is definitely something Alex
Should not be doing
It's like we're living in
I'd like
You've never seen black book
We went and saw Dylan morning
You remember the bridge
What are the worst days of your life
Famously loved
In in his show Black Books
There is a moment where he is really really sick
And he's by himself any looks over it is oven
And he sees the oven cleaner and goes
If you can clean it up and you can clean me
So much of how people think
That is all that space
But this caller does
It's not good
Anything else
Yeah one thing I think
Because I have a cement
Asymmetrical Warfare
Against
And they're they're using our good graces
Politeness
Against
Basically murdering Janice
I need to see in the lightness be enough
Data and information out there
Doing some Nuremberg
Two hanging
I think if you want you star
Doing one or two of those
The people that are kind of like
Well they told me to do it they're going to realize that
They're culpable
Violating international law national law
Amanda numerous local laws
This is for Real
And their life is on the line
But I think that would be a major current
I have a couple of concerns
The First's are there local laws against genocide
I don't know if like
Lake County Board
Cover that kind of maybe there is
I don't know
The second thing is this is
Is dumb for a couple
There's some stuff that we should talk about but
This being on Infowars this is
Because
Nuremberg trials were like a world
They should be against
The idea of a Nuremberg
For 2 because
On principle
They shouldn't even be in favor of
The first one
Becky it's
It's strange it's
It's kind of strange to me that this this formulation
I thought you jogging a note that I was blown away
By how we went
From
Because end I think this is how this dude thinks is like
I guess it's because we're so polite that there were allowing them to hurt us
Anyways
We should hang them
Like it is pulling this just
Not hanging people
It's something that Alex says a lot
And that's that
Probably with the caller is requiring back to has responded back
Either we've we've been to cut we let them get
To this point we let
The globalist
Do this by not killing them already know it was just Christians during the eighties were so quiet
You know they just blew it nothing to say
They let everything go to s*** you know
Frankly handled the AIDS crisis
Is better than anybody Emser
It's also interesting that this caller starts with the letter
Inhale bleach
So they know if we're serious
Let's poison ourselves and then kill everybody we don't like I don't understand what's wrong about
So Alex has an interesting rebuttal
To this guy he has a take on it that I think is
A little bit weak
I don't want anybody to go out
And shoot
Do you know any of these minions are or actual globalist
Because it's a global system
Spiritual
They would use that as a project
Are resistant to be Financial spiritual
Physical in a nonviolent way
Things like that
But they
Are going to go ahead
Just keep moving at us in a violent way
And showed a certain point
We do need to take back some governmental systems and
And then we do need
People that do knowingly
Population of sterilization weapons against the
This is a strange take
For Alex to have
Cuz it's it's essentially like let's not kill these people instead
Let's take over the apparatus of the state and then
Use the state
That way it'll be okay
Counter to some of Alex's
Large believe now and
This is
This is never happy
So there's never been sort of like a
Opposition
Action Party the
Kind of a minority that decides to then over
Overthrow the government
And through the government
Justify their actions
Despite them being incredibly immoral
Federal government overreach
Right so I would assume that he's not talking about winning
The presidency and then
By using the Federal
Crimes
To prosecute these people obviously it's not International laws
Believe that exist
He's going to kill pouch
Extradite
Fauci Florida
He's like let's overthrow the Texas governor in install the lieutenant governor is the Supreme Overlord of the
Texas f******
Ethnostate
I'm sure you would have liked
Dan Patrick more than a habit
Oh yeah but yeah if this is weird I don't I don't I don't find any more comforting
People because the
The idea that he has
More f***** up.
Target these people we're going to have to
First overthrow the government so we're going to kill a bunch of henchmen first
Civilian
People not involve people who don't even really care conceivably
Conceivably you could be talk
I'm about like electoral politics
Poopy talking about winning officer
Did Rick Rick Reverend
Shinsou
Anyway Alex story about covid
He's got a he's got to get into
Good job
On the news
That's the reason you have covid symptoms even though
Causing the coven
Do covid-19 strains found
With altered Spike
Protein
Breaking today
One week after
Soros arrested
Which people said all those going to be new strange we need new vaccines the old ones didn't work
Not quite
This is only news because Alex doesn't understand the topic
Buddy covers
It's not surprising
To see the possibility of a kovarian showing changes in the spike protein and that's part of what made
More transmissible
Stanley office
I mean it's almost
Inevitable
French officials are investigating a new strain that they've detected but it
Entirely clear as of yet how
Print this train is going to end up being
According to an article in a Reuters it looks like researchers are interested in how we can possibly hide from PCR test
Since quotes several of the patient
Since delivered negative PCR test
And we're trying to positive result only from samples taken from blood or deep in the respiratory system
However even if it does end up being
McKay's
France's Health Ministry said late on Monday
Literally analysis did not suggest the mutation was more contagious
Or more deadly than earlier version
The virus
There's a lot of information yet to be learned about this variant and it very well may turn out that it's
It's not a huge deal and the vaccines we have are still effective against it
So it's
More less
An academic issue
Or it could turn out that its ability to evade
PCR test
Means that an alternative screening method might be
Be needed in some case
Those are possible that significant enough mutations to the spike protein would make it resistant to the vaccine
But it's way too early to jump to that conclusion
And that's what Alex
Essentially doing
Intentional are you telling me that it's way too early to jump to the conclusion that Bill Gates
Finances
The creation of a new variant of Delta
Covet in order to
Continue killing people
And blame the Patriots
Even though the facts
He's already giving us
Is going to give us
A definite
But he's also added something so you don't get heart attacks.
Exactly
Smorgasbord vaccine information
Dizzy to buy
Trying to keep some of it straight
So Alex complains
You know about this but also you should really know that he's not taking this very seriously it's not a big deal
He is
Having to spend time
Energy
Knowing we didn't do the things they said
Killing lawyers
Default us years ago
Nobody's ever given them all their banking
The judge is crazy
Give Them All to him but they're going to default
Because I wanted to show the world all that
There and follow their political orders
Outlandish
I told him all that
Is very seriously
No idea that I already know all about the
But I was born
Researching this information and actually hearing family
Walkabout
Things that they witness themselves
What
What does that have to do with taking this case
I mean it's almost evidence that he's not
The k-series
Yeah
Just
I don't buy it
I don't think this is a good
The Avenue
Promising promising to take more calls
Sure promises he's going to get to it.
And I will do the effort.
Salmon in the world on shoulders coming up
He got sued for Sandy Gun for reading of Zero Hedge article on air
Questioning Megyn Kelly
I think she was saying
I just shoot him
They just default to knowing
He never gets me 94 even subpoenaed him to be default
Well you can't even do that
They just said
Your default
You're not even a person
As a is very clear from our conversations with Mark Banks
Tried to get Owens come in for a deposition and he did not respond
So many times though this is a bulshit piece of nonsense Alex's
Is it spreading respond almost as if somebody might have
You've told him
It would be a bad idea for Ira's don't worry dues got this one exactly
Yeah who's got the goods
Oh boy so Alex said he's going to take calls
Commercial
I thought we're going to go right back to golf
We do not immediately do that
The Masters new type of warfare
Comic cultural spiritual warfare slowly shutting down the economy
And then
Why you blaming the general public blaming White
Are they
What is it about white people the Volvo's don't like
Christian ethos and what happened in the West
About
500 years ago the Renaissance the idea
Person
People having basic rides
People having free speech people having right to a jury
Gutenberg printing press
What are we doing
What is this
Destroy
Don't you understand the globalist
White
People the Library of Alexandria
Would never have been
I think is really interesting is the way of it like this
Singular person
Gutenberg
Is Pratt's great man do you have history
He came up with that idea out of nowhere
Lexi movable-type Innovations now man ever thought of it before and I never thought of it before
Hundreds of years before the process history is engagement
Different cultures are in conversation with each other
Well I guess you're right
Like I don't have a
If this is just
Deeply deeply white supremacy
F****** Wild
Did not know the massive interplay of trade and
Everett
Between
Furiated legalist
The concepts that Alex's is fascinated by it
Insisting that white people invent
Did like the very basis of freedom
What about snot
Not based entirely or created a whole cloth by European cultures
I mean it's it's Porsche it's like he said everybody in sumera was white
Lakeshore
Looking fine what are
10 books
Text wifey
This sucks
Yeah that really sucks
Calls
Why aren't you Skyler in Washington
God bless you. Peace be with you in this war
Near me
Thank you I
I just want to cover this end
Beasty posted this
New report
Titled 100 kids in Virginia given wrong dose
Call me back.
But we know it
Nationwide
Charlie
And
Disturbing
Walker try and cover it up
They use this to
Excuse
Expelled
And then I use this
Excuse to say that they should reach
Vaccine regimen
Possibly more.
Backstage
It doesn't make any sense because this call her and Alex have the story backward
They're saying that these hundred kids and Virginia were given an adult doses of the vaccine three times
That's what they were supposed
But that's not true
In reality according to a story in the Washington Post quote
The doses of Pfizer vaccine given at the clinic were diluted more than recommended
According to the health
It's not clear if this is what happened in this other case but in another incident and Luda
County Virginia
A pharmacy was administering incorrect dosist
Children but their mistake
How to make sense if you don't think about it too much
Children's doses R1
One-third of the standard dose
So you might
I think that you could dilute 1/3 of a standard dosage
Just like that
You cooked up a child here is that the experts don't actually know if that's something
Invech woodwork
Constable Ronald B okay
But they're not they're concerned that this wouldn't deliver a full dose
And they don't have the proper information
So there's some concern
If this is how the dosing is being done
Yeah I imagine that
If I
The people who designed the vaccine
Acknowledged that some pharmacist was just like oh well if I have three little cups I'll just pour a little bit of this vaccine
Sitting there each one
That's probably not the way you want to think the pharmacist probably doing it a little bit
More carefully than describing
Wasn't saying drink
You know Alex and this caller are workshopping a
Conspiracy theory about a story that they have in
Entirely wrong
Yeah that's cheating
What is the point of this show
Things that are wrong and tell people they're right
I guess so
So Alex gets another call
Forgot who's an investigative reporter and I thought I thought
I thought I was very excited
Hear from this investigator see what he has to say
And then I quickly got disappointed also his name is Ragnarok
Alex Jones
Ragnarok here
Florida I was just want to call in
And
Work for
Orlando
Examiner in Florida
I was covering the
Mama's minutes
Pushing a lot of them
I had
One of these days
Illuminati
People
Email me
Commenting on my
Particle
This is about where I kind of decided
You're not investigative
What I'm saying is true the other 50
And just rebelling what
Freddy Cannon
What I have
I responded
To that
In kind
Six months later after he said
Send me that
There's a great story
Me too
And I got
Fired on 1123
Twitter
YouTube
Google
All of them called up
Orlando examiner is if you don't
This guy
Going to terminate
Contract
At this point I'm pretty sure Alex's
Does eating because he thought story and he's not interrupting it
Like building on anything not trying to derail
Territorial
I had a illuminati globalist send me an email and then I responded six months later that I was fired
Surprised I'm not here
I've been experiencing
My voice
For about 11 years
Everything you're going through
Through
It's a battle we got on your hands
Vaccination
The mandatory vaccinations
It says
The creators
Whoever takes
You become
Of the ones you have that pack
We're doing that with that they own the genetic material and it's crazy
Oh boy
That was a long walk
To get to atom theory
Yep
Yeah
Yes all in all
Myself
In a position where this is
Cregan
Episode
That's story
Soured Beyond any hope of
Pinterest
Really put
Some air brake
On Alex's show Adara
In
10 I've already stopped caring and I kind of understand why Alex ends up doing what he does at this point
Gorilla calls
He decides he's going to play a statement that he record it probably during one of the commercial breaks
The Democratic Party
Philanthropist
Financing
Facts on the 2nd of May
The First Amendment this country
Financing
Judiciary
Buying up
The judges
Paying for all the DEA
Pulling into count
Political opposition Arnel
All the time
I'm here
I have spent
Millions of dollars
Fighting these fraudulent Sandy Hook lawsuits
In front of a jury
It's too dangerous
But users of dead children
At the Sacramento
We gave them all of our documents all of our bank records
Things that have nothing to do with a defamation suit
The judge in Texas and the judge
In Connecticut
In lockstep shed
Jones has fail
To get my
Alex is the victim
I mean they did everything right
Didn't say that you failed to give them.
They got
Plenty of.
Document song
Summer
Were
Suspicious Sarah wild way too many documents
Situation
So I mean he just did everything
Egregious
They're taking our first amendment rights away
It's so egregious that it's going to turn people on like it's going to wake people love buck up
Obviously
Because the establishment is in its death throes
Edgewalk control America
Target leaders of the populace.
Opposition
Demonization
Intimidate
In England
Is it
This is nothing
What is judicial
Intimidate me and others respond
I'm going to put
Films
I don't think
That's going to
Times he said he was going to make more documentaries of work already
Even what he had
Plenty of money and said what he did was buy a fuk
Yeah so the bombing of Britain
During WWII lasted over 8 months
1940 to 1941
United Kingdom declared war on Germany in 1939
30 happened
I'm going to need to see Alex light some sources on this 90% against to 90%
4 figure in terms of British
Support for the war cuz I
I can't find anything
Comes close to that
There was a spike and more Allen support for the war
At the end of the blind
But it also coincided with when the Soviet Union officially enter the war
These motivators could be working in
In concert together
Also there was a spike when the US join the war so I mean like there is
Historical things
Yeah anyway the point Alex is making about Germany hoping
To demoralize the British with a blitz but that only making them more in favor of the Warriors maybe someone
But only if you interpreted really generously
Also an important point is that the enthusiasm
In Britain went up when the blitz ended not while the bombing campaign was still active
This Dynamic kind of hurts Alex
This metaphor but I don't want to put too many hairs it's just
It's something that he brings up over and over and over again
The only really has maybe a hundred
Sort of word block
Fits that man where they need to go
Pick a word block
Write a metaphor
More life
So anyway Alice's. He does this
Think that they plays his is statement
And it's just
More of the same
Deserted like I got that up
Since 1990
This is what they have been working
Towards Dan yeah it should have happened within five years but
Timing was off I think they f***** around did 911 look there 10 years behind we all know that there
Plans are always right
I got some some other stuff got in the way
So Alex
Brings on this guy named
Drew Hernandez
And he is a guy who is
Is an activist
On the right
A big s*******
And he presents himself as a journalist kind of
Like lives
Stream stuff
He happened to be in Kenosha live streaming
Been called as a defense Witness
In The Rittenhouse trial
There have been some concerns
About him being
A little bit
Too much of a bias
Agree with those concerns
Is I'm not biased to anything except the truth
And my rebuttal to that would be a buddy
You're on Infowars
You got problems
You are biased against
The truth
Play Alex has a little bit of a bull session with this guy who's
Dangerously close to being offered a job
What you talked about how the left and wokeism is a new religion
Swab came out today is going to be a speech
EWTN
Bilderberg Group
Of all those bubbles organization
A president
Sherwin the board
Openly said we're creating a new religion of the Earth
Everybody hits the religion were humans are bad and Evil
Going to make sure
For the good of the earth I mean this is
A very Authority in system for the elaborate
On your point about how they are in a
Price of religion
That's a really good point
Does it mean when you take a look at this from like a Biblical worldview that's the endgame
Lucifer and forsake
Now we're going to get into something ology because
That's what is going to happen with the Advent of the anti
Christ he is going to be a superstar that is going to unify the world
Usher in a one-world religion One World economy and one world system
And we are seeing this unfold right now I'm not saying that we are literally living
In the Book of Revelation right now cuz there are some precursors that need to take place
According to the Bible but we we are literally watching right now is
Referred to as the spirit of the anti
I Christ because this is the grand finale
Before the second coming of Jesus Christ
Oh boy
So quickly application close Rob isn't the head of the World Trade Organization
The Alex all of these
They organization
Asians are basically the same thing so it doesn't really matter
Also cluster I was giving a speech at World economic
Make Forum Summit that took place last weekend and you didn't save it
Things I want to say this is clearly insane
Also
I don't know if you remember this but I was listening to this I remember
I hate this guy yeah I remember him being like journalist baby that's
He's one of the journalist baby
Sounds like a whiny baby
Yeah I got really annoyed
Can't believe
Leave that you up
Ayers Ayers the thing about
Being a witness
I understand cuz the judge
Is a piece of s***
And that
Not Unusual
But I mean if I'm on a jury
I would like
The defense to always Quest
Are there anybody to always question their Witnesses
Do you believe that it's Lucifer's plan
What's happening right
Cuz if that's the case then I don't care what you have to
Do you believe that when you were at the protest in Kenosha
Do you believe that the devil was involved
Believe
That this is part of end times prophecy
Absolutely State of Mind you were in
Affect how you experience things
I mean I don't even care if it's Mike
That's the information I don't believe you
I just think this guy sounds like a baby
How much further does it need to go
Better than
For your own babies your own children that goes beyond politics
Wavy on politics
Radeon democrat-republican
It's even when people think that they can dictate
And control
For your own babies over you as a parent
How the hell could you ever allow that
Universe
Oh my God
If you don't saying
Pre-planned because God knew it was going to happen but
Yeah I thought you doesn't mean death or Grim Reaper
The name is derived from the Sicilian word for sickle
The name comes from people who had the occupation of
Sickles having that name
Much like Smith or Miller or occupational rooted name I was going to say
It's like an agricultural us-based
Like they got something by the last name farmer
Perfect sort of information for Alex to throw around because it means nothing but it has a tendency to blow idiots
Mines
I mean
Just just that
Some people just can't
Biore
You know
It's not your skill it's not your skill but this this
I don't know how good they look
How many wood do people touch their baby
Play call my God
This guy too
Have a credibility problem
I find him
To have
A bias problem I think he's annoying
That doesn't really affect
The judicial Park
No also I think that
Him saying things like this next clip that I'm going to play
I think this is a problem
For him being involved as a witness for the defense
He's going to talk about one of the people who got shot 10 people that Rittenhouse killed
This is a person who has
Some
A history of abuse against children
Perpetrator
Okay it is exaggerated by Alex
And
True but I
Minimizing the fact that he's a part of
Now here is what he says
Just awful
How do we get to this point child molesters
Show me open
Joseph Rosenbaum is
And what
Exactly why they didn't want the trial because they knew if the jury know this
Jacqueline
Because my house was a minor
When Joseph Rosenbaum was charging him from behind
That's
Something that I think is impeachable as a witness
Him expressing a mentality that maybe the
The jury would decide the
He deserve to die because of past
Actions
I I just don't I don't think
You should be anywhere near that courtroom
That's f***** up
That's just f***
I think being on Infowars is bad enough but then when you're expressing these kinds of
Opinions it's
I I just don't I
Because he's basically implying
That
It's okay
If it turns out after the fact that something about a person
After the fact that's crazy
People and then I put somebody off a cliff and then I was in court and they were like
But did you know this guy was also a murderer I'd be like see I'm totally off the hook now maybe the jury
You would think he deserves a hero here
The law
The jury wouldn't be like aha
I don't care about the person he killed
No, again
Solutely mature adult person
Alex is a
The word my man
America he need to wake up
What's the reality
Look at the culture
Look at education look at politics
Look at the Grand scale look at the entire world
Look at the
Justice system the so-called justice system
It's all being subverted
Right now you need to stand up for what's true for what's righteous and what's honest
Because it's either now
Or it's never
God
That seems also impeachable as a as a witness if he has these beliefs about the justice system
It doesn't it I don't know
I'm not
I'm not happy about any of this
Speech I was longing for the story from 2000
Bring back Ragnarok
Anyway
I think
This is actually exactly what you kind of
Expect
Deflecting saying I did everything right. To blame these people Jambi up
If it's fraud
That's exactly what you
Should expect once
It's over there's no reason to be angry anymore
Like that
Greer is
Yeah useful sales motivation until the actual
Door is shut
Just a matter of
PR campaigns
To make sure that your revenue streams
From the audience
Doesn't dry out
I think he's doing exactly what he needs to do on that front
He's also being
Over Glee
Also
Being real stupid
Android
Be hanging out with her
Baby
You know here's something weird
This just this thought just occurred to
A-OK
Alex
If the vaccines do murder everybody
Will be off the hook
So shouldn't he be rooting for people to take the vaccine if he believes that people who take the vaccine will die
Guess who took the vaccine
Judges
Jerry's
Lawyers
Shouldn't he be like
Hey everybody
That I don't like
B vaccine
Well no because he
He believes in humanity
Cuz he loves people
And he doesn't want to
That was the closest
Taking a good long while
Integrity
Decency love of fellow man honestly
Yep
So we end this
Sort of state where I think we're in a holding pattern until we know kind of what the damage
Is there going to be
Because I think
If there
Considerable
Alex might be in very big trouble
If it's not
He might be able to
F*** around and have some
Money bombs
And maybe make enough money to
Coast Brew
Maybe
No cuts
Maybe slim down a little bit
I don't know I just can't think of any way to
Go to a jury with anything other than
And Infowars
You know what I mean like
Listen
This is not going to
To stop unless we stop it
You know what I'm saying so we have to either either he stops Infowars
Or we
Awarded judgement so high that he has to stay
That seems to be the only
Option for me otherwise what's the point of any I understand where you're coming from I just don't know if that flies in
I agree with that
I agree with that but I mean honestly what's
What's the point of any of this
If he's allowed to continue doing it
What's the f******
You know
Yeah I mean I guess
The point
I would
Want
To seek is whatever it is
That the families who were
Suing him
Watch
You're absolutely right on
I think I think that
You know I don't
People might
Expect the Derby like a big
Change
I was like
Is tone
Because he lost
The suit solutely not snot
But I mean that's kind of my point
This behavior isn't going to stop
Because he gets
A
Huge judge
This behavior is going to continue for as long as he doesn't show the only option
To make this
A
When
Is to end info
If he does and Infowars then you could just do a podcast
Absolutely
I'm just saying that that's what I would be
Understand
I don't know where we'll see what happens
But for now Jordan we have a website
Yep we are also on Twitter we are on Twitter at that knowledge underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan
Also we had intended to not have an episode
Today
Because I wanted a little break
This Sneaky Snake was so sneaky
It's stuck up on us
You know X necessitated us having an episode so if you've made it this far
Sewed on Friday
We'll see we might have an episode on Friday
We might but Bonito
I'm Leo mdzs
Text Clark
And now here comes
The sex robot
Alex
Christian color with huge fan I love your work