Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Stripe.com
A little bit about
Alex June
Quest
My birthday is possibly uncharacteristic
Maybe people wouldn't take us to me cuz I don't like violent video games sure
Other things like Donkey Kong Country and maybe you know
Games where the violence has you jump on somebody
Cartoony stuff
But V I just saw that Grand Theft Auto 3 Vice City and San Andreas
Released on the switch
And
Over the Moon the Moon
The ship
Out of those
When I was younger
17 on word or whatever
And there's just something about it I don't really like the violence aspect of it as much as I can
Unnecessary violence
But dear
Such a great like open-world but not too big
Right
Kind of vibe I like
People telling me what to do like going on Mission and stuff it's fun
Fun
Yeah I remember playing those games and being like well but I've seen my friends play this and they just commit violence all the time
I'm going to walk to my next message
I think also I've started on three
There are some criticisms of people have it
Some of the aesthetic of the original version on the PS2 are are gone
I kind of agree with that like it's stylistically a little bit different visually but I don't mind
I don't mind that too much
Just get a thrill out of finding a hidden package
Active great you're running around like why am I on this rooftop oh haha that's why
Did my bright spot is a little bit of a Twilight spot
I'll tell you what begins with breaking a commandment
1st and
Since you've gotten his desk
I have coveted
I've covered it either later this s*** out of this desk told you was a nice day
So I was like I'm not proud of this but I had to get myself a new.
I want I didn't want to I just couldn't
Look at my own old desk I understand more right so I got it
And as you know about how I buy things I
Found my price range
And then just ordered it no real consideration no no it's probably the first thing check it off like I don't care what
So it's
Huge
Way bigger than I thought it was you got to be careful about that complicated wow
I'm so proud of myself
I completed it
And then the next morning
I opened the drawer and the whole thing
The whole drawer fell apart as if it was just like a guitar to Absolute cartoon
So my bright spot was
Successfully putting that thing together does feel good it's a great spot is that it is already falling apart
Another bright spot
So Jordan today we're going to be going over about her and Day episode about November 16th
Can't remember what the real fast
Furious line is and what the wrong one is that I've talked myself into that one.
Too early to care
Doesn't matter anyway
It's
Bucked up
Also Alex premieres a bit of his interview with General Flynn
General Mike Flynn
Scott answer will be taking a brief detour to go over that interview
And I'm excited to get that business
Where's James
James Gregory
And from Arkansas
Are you very much Randy and candy
Octopi
I don't like I don't like some of the content that we're going to end up talking
That's been going on I'm kind of f***** up it's just
Today Show
Yep
So we're going to start here actually not on the episode but we're going to start with a little video that Alex put out
Where he is
Really embodying his current spirit this is a little little video
Infowars
Saving for
I'll look at
Democratic Party
Real quick I just got to pause it
You got to write it on the phone
I made a note
They want to take us
We've got to
Fight this in court
Go to the jury trial
Default
I am so guilty
So I can't
Without your
Infowars
Important work
Please go to
Shaving for
Make a $10
Wealthy people out there
You're free speech
Wealthy folks
Don't start Spanish
Money
Promoting Liberty
Little Lou's
The world
Please go to shavan
Comics
We're banned everywhere else
The fight for the neck
Never issued
Didn't work this year
Stand up for you
Self tanner
Jennifer America
Rich people cough cough Elon Musk Joe Rogan amazing I love it
I love a good appeal to rich people's sense of dignity and their love of the First Amendment
The First Amendment so goddamn much
This is what Alex.
He has absolutely no standards and doesn't give a f*** about how his actions and words affect other people
Total dick
Every now and then he gets
Himself into trouble
He milks left trouble for all the free press that he can
You get out of it presented himself as a persecuted victim the whole time
If he's allowed to he ends up settling any makes quiet apologies to get himself off the hook like you did with James alefantis
And Hum Dil Kya
Well that's not an option or
You know someone important Infowars end up owing a lot of money
You better believe that an emergency money bomb is coming right around the corner
Oh yeah we call that pretty
It was not a not a ambitious prediction
Pretty obvious
Anyway you did not require any psychic powers
Merely deduct
This doesn't have anything to do with Alex being able to afford appeals or fight the good fight to clear his name
Defend the First Amendment a rubber Bowl shade he thinks he's
Doing
This is trying to trick the audience into pay and what he's going to end up being ordered to pay for losing the suit
This is basically the equivalent of being a teen and like bacon your parents to give you money to pay off a speeding ticket you got when you were Joyce
Riding
Alex wants someone else
The face the consequences for him
So we can continue as flagrantly irresponsible bulshit that'll end up leading to more consequences of the audience at the bail him out of them
Don't sleep very sad and childish and I hope you out in southern fall for it again
But I think they might not
I think they might not be totally convinced you think so I went to the Gibson to go pay how's it going to destroy two million.
And I weep gifts ended him
Percent of it
Set time
To find their way to that page
To donate
That's okay that's a Gibson to go do not pass go do not
Collect
You might have banged this Kong too many
You might be fishing in a dry well
Yeah and I think that the audience sees the idea that like
Joe Rogan just got 100 million dollar contractor Spotify
If you believed what Alex says and really think that this is that important
To millions of drop in the bucket that from Rogan
Easy
The people who are going paycheck-to-paycheck or
You're good people in the audience why do why you trying to build them a broken nose it's b******* to
Nobody wants
To pay for it
Anyway
Good luck I'm excited to see how this one goes
Dirigo can start off on the 16th
And here's Israel
It's really huge and got me having butterflies right now
Having a really big ones today
Go down
Because I have butterflies
Never been this strong it's like
On fire right now
Coming
Madison
That is some energy right there there's some big stuff
So a big stuff
If you present yourself that way
The world is right around the corner
I got to have to guess that all the world's nuclear powers are going to start a war against each other immediately or I'm going to
Lose all of my money I don't know which one what you don't understand is me being rich is the only thing that is holding back he had
I would not be surprised if he believed that on sublevel
Alex's
Is high
But he's high on fighting
I'm high as a kite fighting
I would not be anywhere else.
More I don't back down
Justin Moore the Universe album.
It's just things I could never even imagine
What is hat on
Did the show Myspace
Top your head blows off
It's just so
Amazing be in the quiet place the most high
Like the philosopher dolls Berkeley I mean
Like
Little boy let's just start with Cee-Lo
Merry Madagascar
I was looking over his
Is Wikipedia page
This pattern of him saying horrible things
On Twitter and I just have terrible thoughts
I want to enforce upon people and then I don't want to face any consequence
Cut this clip cuz it was too long
I don't really care that much
The next commercial break he comes in with crazy and he's just like
Just singing along for
Oh boy Let It Go For Me Maybe I'm crazy
I would like to see the upper end of Alex's register
Probably not great
Alex gets to this clip
Of Mike Flynn the interview
Let's go ahead my friends
Very important mineral short Club
The intro of the hour-long
Interview with General Flynn
Crowd of 5,000
And we're also on Thursday
Welsh
Patrick
The interview
That really is people listen to it
Just the battle plan of victory
Plays this little clip it's like a Sizzle reel kind of this interview
The Flint review is I'm going to call it don't you dare come on I'm taking it away from
The part that's hilarious about this is that the overarching theme of the clips that Alex plays
On his show saying that Alex was right all along
I didn't get any indication that the interview was a battle plan for victory as much as a preview almost entirely
That doesn't surprise me since he's a narcissist and having people talk about how great you are as kind of the road.
Anyway I didn't
Feel like I got a good sense of what the interview was about from the sizzle reel so
Like I said
Let me watch the full version
See what I could learn
And I was really particularly trying to figure out like where is the battle plan
Right cuz that's what I was saying this is
There's like useful information moving forward as how we're going to achieve Victory we need to divide
The certain groups we need to flank them etcetera etcetera black battle
It's mostly complaining
There's a lot to complain about
Text a little bit
People that are
You're following what I'm doing or what's happening
In my life and ever
With all of this
Stuff with the
January 6th
That quality
The yeti
Insurrection
And crucifix
Because that's what it is anyway.
Local sunset
Nancy Pelosi
Pilot
Operation that they are
Doing
To basically
Steal away
All of the
The other ask
What's happening
Across this country
Do you like you got the Durham report
Never comes out of that the
It's been a lot of things drop
A thing dropped
Recovering
That stuff up
Did anybody try and s*** on Pontius pilate's death
Not that I'm aware I don't think there were I don't think he had a desk
That's a good point
Hi I'm trying to follow this metaphor
Who is Jesus
Are the Oaks
Keepers Jesus
Collectively
Who's who is Nancy Pelosi
I mean did somebody bring something to Nancy Pelosi that she said washed her hands of
Like did somebody say
Hey
Nancy we want all of these insurrectionists to be free or whatever cuz they're the Messiah
She was like nah dude
Wait no that's even back when she would have been the one saying no everybody here is fine but don't kill them qanon
Brabus then the crowd is chanting for Mike Pence's death
But she saying don't kill my my face is Jesus
Wait
This is this is a little confused I understand the desire cuz Insurrection rhymes with crucifixion
I appreciate that word play
I understand why you want to get as biblical as you can for the audience
System
I don't like it when people get both reality
And unreality wrong
Speaking of things that are questionable
In terms of reality
Do you think that Michael and thinks that the 2020 election was stolen
A boy that seems too obvious a question over to go with
No actually it if you guys but then I'll follow up question
You think the 2016 election
You got that right
I believe
9 months
That I believe
Mastiff
They just didn't have
Balance
Send machine
Donald Trump
Ran the table
The outdid the algorithms
I know this word everybody's
The algorithm
Beat the odds
And then four years
They tried to take
Everything
Stories
Still being
Until what they decided
Right after the
We're never going to
Another
Election
We're not going to
Control the out
And so
10 covid
Covid
Control
Very very smart
Military
At its finest
And what they did was
Kobe King
To bring into
So yeah we got this whole plan
Yeah
Very elaborate
Of course
16 election
Was stolen but Trump did so well
Dover Road to the the voter fraud which is
Meredith
Because they're like
Bach
He's too good
What we didn't we didn't consider this
When we were rigging the election we didn't consider that it would be
Be possible that someone could be so popular that they would overcome all efforts to
So we have to get covid-19
That if you've started invalidating even the election
Since You've Won your argument is let's never hold elections
Kind of plan ends up getting towards in this interview as well
Young Kim
Yeah and
In Virginia and he's basically saying that that was the same thing they were trying to steal it
Even if we win it's stolen is this is this is not
The good a good path for us to go down there is never away
No Alba
17 minutes into this interview
That's probably 35 minutes long
All day
Alex finally
What can we do to fight back
So maybe this is
The battle plan
Here we go twins response
Might be a little cliche
What are some basic
The American people
Congress
What can we
Moving in the right
Concussion
So first of all
Courage is it
Decision
What
Courage is not so
DNA
It might be
What
So tell me it's possible that courage might be in your DNA
Explain to me how courage is both a decision and something you were innately born with
I don't know
Okay that's good well I think it's just a cliche thing that sounds fun
Courage is a choice
Honor is a choice for life
Station
A poster or something
In there
Almost entirely boils down to like
I think locally
I don't have Global ramifications basically
More cliche nonsense people
Some truth to it but it's
Kind of
Idea that a lot of people in
Organizing
I've already known for a long time
Secret number 56
I'm
With stupid
Yeah it's
It's trite
That very least
And
Not groundbreaking
So one of the ways that you can act locally though
You got to get in there to those School Board me
It's so fun with it
School board meeting has there been
So much
Visibility about school
School Board in school board activity around
You kind of said yourself
School Board
Part of it is is
Is that we have taken
Take it take it
For granted that all
No Alex
The sky Alex
And who is he what is his background
All the sudden
Democratic Socialist
That are honest
Educate
Haitian system
Is the way to
Entire culture
Country
Been talking about it for decks
Open that happened
Donald Trump
Been going on
For decades
It's not so much that there is
Something different going on with school boards as it is
People have figured out that they can get
Viral videos really easily like
Yelling at school boards
People just
Stop them
Twins getting any stats about socialist on school and what he's doing
This is just an attempt to encourage more intimidation and chaosity
School board meetings because they're the perfect Target for right-wing education
School board members probably aren't going to argue with you you just get to yell whatever you want for a few minutes then you get to post a video of
Yourself which encourages more people who want attention to do the same thing
It's a self-perpetuating cycle
Another important people who share Alex influence politics
Don't have sway in most school boards because they took their freedom for granted
They don't have sway there because they don't care but the actual work that
School boards do
And their politics would actually advocate for the elimination of public schools and the school board
Here
Yeah and I mean your argument is is more like
Hey this teacher wants you to read and you're like oh well that's it, socialist
People who are drawn to servicon school boards generally are power-mad socialist there people who care deeply about the community they live in
Often dedicated to educational issues
This is slightly idealistic on my part and obviously there's some folks who aren't
Like high-minded and totally altruistic
But being on school board generally means putting in a ton of extra work that
Sweetly thankless and generally poorly compensated
According to the National School boards Association quote
75% of small district school board members
Receiving no salary
A lot of school districts have elections for board members to so that's an added hurdle the people left
The clear in order to get on the board
It's not
You weren't paying attention for a long time and you can give a f*** about the fact that you
You could have voted for somebody else to be on the school board you dumb
Dumb dick
I mean
Is your
The problem is their argument has
To be like
All of that time that we when you weren't paying attention
All this evil stuff was happy
Not like the reason you didn't have to pay attention is because
Everything was fine
You know
So now it's like I've been doing this all in
Secret despite the fact that if you were to go look at it you would like
I haven't cared about my school board in my town
40 f****** years I didn't go to school here I don't know any of the kids here
School Board
I'm some a****** who's doing nothing but I think I'm going to go bother the school board
Dreadlocks dreadlocks weirdo can go scream at the school board
Could have done that 10 years ago
That big a deal
The flavor does your right now
Bright Eyes this is bad
Slim
You jerk
Anyway
The best most of his battle plan is like
Fuqua School Board find out who owns your local paper
I don't know if there's a battle plan
I think a lot of the what Alex wanted out of this interview is he wanted
To get Flynn to say that he was going to run for president
Girardi travel
And I just
Accelerate
Declare
America first
Morbid
But I
Just can't wait to be
I like that
Part of the discussion about like come on you should stay running for president is like
You know Trump wouldn't think you're betraying him
Healthy
Hey Hey listen
We want you to run
A president not full well you will not weigh
It's a waste of your time
And
And at all the end of this your main job is to
To give all of the stuff that you have worked hard for
Does somebody who has literally never worked a day in his life
Sounds good yeah that's good stuff
So we get back to the episode proper and Alex has hope you know he's always right about that
We've heard this
Predictions about where we're going
I would covid vaccine
Living in denial is only what this take place has so many people
I got about 7 to 10 a year
AR 1 hour
Saraland
One-Shot Superbad
Chad they're just normalizing
What they're doing
I guess the conservative estimate that he's making
7210 covid vaccines a year
Maybe one a day one an hour
Exaggerated 65 *
Right
So that's why you're sleeping
That's a good question
You have to wake up in the middle of the night and give yourself a booster
Alright then the 365 is only * 17
Right but you got to take one shot in the middle of the night just to hold you over so I have to change it to like a
A broken up sleep schedule
Sleep 3 hours at a time let's call that 19 shot cuz you got one before you go to bed one when you wake up and then one
To boost yourself
Before your morning
Or possibly the government will mandate you can only sleep in like 20 minutes chunks
Sure that DaVinci sleep cycle and let me throw this out so you could take a shot every hour
Every room
Is altered to be like a Indiana Jones booby trap room where if you step on
On a certain tile
30 vaccine shots get your
Or it could be like the hatch in lost where the counter
Cooking down to an hour if they cash out
Browse the electromagnetic anomaly you offered crash a plane
If you want me to get the shout out.
Stupid
Anyways he might be fear-mongering a little bit though
Okay so what are the side characters in the story of Infowars that I think doesn't get enough play
Definitely does come up more than you'd expect is Alex's wife's tennis partner
How much it comes up and
Better comes up at all
We've not heard from this tennis partner in a while
Here's an update
This one was bragging to my wife yesterday house
Can you take a 7 and 10 year old
Getting worn lady she said well it's just Darwinism she wants a killer kid
Coshocton
Where We Are
Okay
Got cut off by the brake
That's very
Yeah
That's very funny
Imagine Alex's wife
I didn't even warn her
Yeah
She was talkingshit
She was just
She was just showing off that's what her husband doesn't
Run an outlet designed expressly destroyed
Children does it mean to brag about your children getting back
Strange phrases
So we're going to get into a little bit of Alex talking about
How many abortions
If you paid for
Somebody's doesn't quite match up with some of the other comments he's made of the pasture
Timeline issues certainly come up that'll happen
But
I always
I kind of after the initial shock of him
Admitting on are that he's paid for overtime
Abortions
Shock of that
I don't want to talk about that too much
Cuz I don't want to give the appearance that
I would be in anyway judgmental of someone
Making that decision
Yeah we have no moralization
Possibly be Michigan
Construed
In this case
You kind of got to bring it up cuz of where the conversation goes
This is a mess
My bad boy
My first Access TV shows 28 years ago
I planted what I was a Christian but that I wasn't a bible thumper
Judging people
Explain how the left when control
Women and men that had taken part in abortions by saying you're a sinner you're going to hell you killed the baby
And then they commit and hardened their hearts instead of hey
God will forgive you you got set up you got lied to that was a human life you know your heart
Just ask God for forgiveness the Holy Spirit come in the ass and you'll be freed of this weight of what you were involved at I know I paid for
Quite a few abortions
And I and I
Shotgun facing
So you're sorry to those children you killed
I need to get on your knees and you need to ask forgiving I did
Taken away from me and then God said
Here's your mission
I was like
17 years old
You're going to go to work and I was like
Yeah that timeline doesn't quite work out for me based on other comments he's made in the past I mean
Wow
It's if it's that young I guess his Dad paid for 10 of worship
Plus I think I was already understood I believe so
Seems like his dad doesn't feel too much guilt about it he's not on the record
Speaking about this headspace that he's in he's like I killed these kids oh no
That leaves him to confess to murder again
And
Murder
What
And then God said well.
Body parts
I'm a sinner
Tell you something God
Forgave me
So you trying to give this impression that God has forgiven him and then all the
The guilt is gone and
You know all this but like that is absolutely not true
No he is
Intensely motivated by some kind of a
The guilt that he feels about this
I mean it would be hard
To think to yourself after listening to that
Oh
Repentance
Gives you
Clear thoughts and
Calm of mind
Free of heart that allows you to see everything clearly and your motivations or are just totally above board
Seems more like I'm going to throw this out there
I bet he is
Daily by his past and it tears him apart inside leading him to do and commit terrible thing
And exaggerated
The Sims what he's committed like I've murdered people
For you at all
If Alex
Is the embodiment of repenting I would say that it's a bad thing
Yeah but forgiveness is good it's good to forgive yourself forgive yourself
The devil put pressure on you and use them against you
Manipulate
That'll wipe it out
Doesn't mean you're perfect
Those weights are gone
Sure they are using an allergy of
Christmas story where
It was all bosses
Carry on his back
Fraternity
Not a Christmas
Feel that way when you committed
Crime in sand
Get rid of it it's a long way back from hell
You don't want to cross that line
Glenn Danzig
What is happening
He's quoted the philosopher Glenn Danzig and Gnarls Barkley on this episode
Okay alright oh yeah it's on his playlist today so that was A Christmas Carol
Talk about Jacob Marley
And I believe if I'm not mistaken
The chains represented his wealth
Representative being obsessed with business
The more money he made the heavier his chains were
Not really about sins La Alex's describe the heads and their ironic punished
Yep
So
Alex is a is on one
As you can as you can
Can see he's rambling about
Killing people
And how he has done that in the past you are sure which is great. Start sure
Gets into talking about how the man needed to get him off
Off-air
Because he was giving too much truth
I hope I have a few thoughts about this that I wanted to
Okay we knew this day was coming
We know what's going to happen because we got operation lockstep and we had sparse 2023 2025 and we had
All different in-game documents
We know that they were going to scare for disease X
12 years ago
But they would bring out the virus
Lockdown
Play Bring Out up a vaccine passport global
Travel passport
An internal passport that would have a carbon tax attached to it
What in the document
Right around that same time China started developing and social credit score and infowars.com
And prisonplanet.com
Infowars
At the time
The time
The first report on all of this
Special
We've done the research we've been the tip of the spear
That's why the enemy so upset that's what they wanted software
Ago
Finally banned on Twitter 6 months
About to release lockdown
Bring ID out of the system here's the documents
What do you think they thought when they saw that they said get him off now
Shut him up how the hell does he know all this well you guys brag about it
Is a fun story but it is not it's not real
That's not that's not accurate at all
The beginning we're all
Not real operation lockstep not a real thing
Nope just various documents and
Scenario exercises
Completely making s*** up about
This is this is what I want to get to
I don't
Think
The idea that Alex has been yelling about them releasing a virus
Sense 1998 right
Give him any credibility against
His credibility what at it cuz I can see her again at your argument is if somebody just keeps saying something
Think that might happen and then when something similar happened you just
Takes credit for you
Sure that sounds suspicious like maybe
He doesn't know anything you just saying I like the way that you constantly talks about a coming
Economic collapse
It doesn't actually is it cheapens the prediction
If you add that to all the
Somebody's made that have
Not come true to the globalist nuking American cities
Rides a big one that he was pretty obsessed with
That
Wrong about that you just ignore
I'm using s*** you shitted predicting things
Let me throw this out
Because this
Conspiracy theory
Is going to
Break the case wide open alright I'm interested so
Alex is right about ever
But
The globalist
Knowing that he's right
Don't do it when he says they're going to do it over and over and over again
To make him look insane but actually that is what Alex believes
Yeah cuz he's talked about like
Occasional maybe maybe they won't do it because we've talked about it we publicize their plan
Exactly
I don't know
It's ridiculous
It's not it's almost
Painful
It really is
Now
Also painful
Is Alex's
Deep-seated hatred of women
Yeah yeah that's in the
Boy listen to
Statistically women are
10-20-30 X putting on the study more likely to get in a van
When a man that pulls up and get in
Both mental just run or fight
Cuz I know it's scary
Courage because they're not naive genetically
Men
A program to fight
Women
To try to
Get along there buddy and try to
You eaten
He's back a little bit sokoke sure don't hurt me everything's okay
And then she ends up
You know what a basement tortured for she's killed
You know you really really gotta believe
Inherently genetic trait otherwise you have to been
Deal with the fact that we actually live in a society that suppress women
For so long and so brutally that
Fbe that just acquiescence seems like an almost natural state of being as opposed to constant and
Near Weber
Just banana
Genetic
We can't do that
Yeah
I'm baffled
Constantly end up in in situations are listen to the showtime like
Kimball I'd listen to that
Hundred thousands of hours of a show
I still like
Can't believe you believe that you believe that women are genetically subservient or something
Acquiescent what about
Slipped and I'm going to throw this one out
Cuz cuz we could easily bring up example
You know you could easily bring up like
Greta Sundberg
Or like a Sonia Sotomayor
Something along with someone more in Alex's laying maybe a park
That's anecdotal that's not enough to prove that
Genetically
Maybe we're not dealing with Sally's loves anecdotal s***
Say
There was a time
When women weren't allowed to vote right and the only way that they could get the vote was if a lot of them got
Together
Yeah
What would be possible cuz genetically they can't do that
Nevermind I was wrong about this the whole time
This is pretty gross
Women and children are way more likely to go to Stockholm Syndrome
And maybe that's a survival at maybe it's best sometimes
The Romans every other ancient empire with a takeover area would kill men above the age of 10 or 11
Women and girls
Because the women and girls would sell them for Saint each other
Within a few days
Tututututu make their children survive
Her husband
Cut up and tortured to death
Going to give those Roman centurions the best b****** of their life that evening
Kill her children
Real men need to come in
Chapters
This is BS
Yikes
There was a look on your face like
Maybe halfway through that
Tablo JetBlue shop
That one was like wow really going to do it huh really really really enjoy the I'm sorry I have
To talk like
Accurate
And dumb
Illustrate that point without the b******* that's very unnecessary
His description of Stockholm syndrome in this case
Works but almost in the opposite that he likes
Come syndrome actually describes the phenomenon where your
Traps as the
Vacation
Stockholm
You're trapped with people who are in your socioeconomic
Status
And then the cops are evil
And you are like oh I guess
In this situation
His way of getting women out of Stockholm syndrome is to walk up to them
Scream
Which would suggest that they should stay where they are with the people who are not scream
Yeah I do think there's a couple things first I don't
Know if
Stockholm syndrome even a real thing
But it's not
It describes the phenomenon of cops being assholes
Second
Alex seems to be
Saying
Inglot women are weak
Damn they are susceptible to
The Stockholm syndrome because they want to give b****** to Centurion to protect our children
Now
I think that his solution to this is
We need to control
Aggressively
Threatened women to do what we want them to do
Dissolution
You do you catch more flies with screaming in their faces that they're lied to
So Alex
Believe that this is the end
My friend
Godzilla
Everything perhaps because
Videos a lot of money
Soon
Going to be fast.
But he likes to bring up this metaphor of like
You know it's
We're about to get pulled into Riptide right
Gets sucked under water
So what you need to do is take a big breath of air
And that's what he's all about
He's all about telling people
Get a deep breath in
Sure right
Bad stuff in the most more predictions what's to come
My job before they cut off all the communications
A cyber-attack
Wait people's informed so they know what's going on at Ocean you getting the riptide you feel it sucking
And it don't fight it pulls you under
Statistically it's going to pop you back out 30 seconds to minute or two
Going to pop right back out but
Joshua
I'm just here tell nobody
HD breath
I mean
They want us dead they want us out of the way they made the decision
Emergency exit plans during martial law they got their underground
Bass
Cards are going to kill him
Lcog system self
This is just the end of everything
Controller
Okay
So
Maybe there'll be a fake cyber-attack or maybe a real war right maybe they'll nuke
Again another new predict
Subliminal Russia
And then they'll get to all the Senators into their underground bases available access to
But it's all just
The trap to kill them both in their underground bases
To what end I'm not sure
Is it raining
Yeah I think so and that is because once ship pops off price editors become Dukes
They control
Parcelsapp
I would like I would like inside into the conversation
If we're down to two
Cyberattack on the others real war who's on the like
I know we could save just never attack
Be super easy
No one would die I mean a few people cuz you know cat you know who pacemakers but that's were evil so we're fine we
Or
We could kill billions in a real war which do you want to go with
I feel like that
Conversations
What but do you don't understand how evil the globalist are and how much they liked
The kill people
Extreme love to kill people but also are putting a heart attack medication as I see you.
Text when they get it okay great whatever
Okay
So dumb
Alex seems pretty mad
I wonder if you can guess what he's mad about
Oh man I just don't inhale executive branch
Oh boy
Then I'm going to go with the build back better at
No-oooooo
I'm going to go with the other legislation that's being proposed you you might
Real consequentialism
Important information I think that your first instinct would be to think that it was that he's mad that Kamala Harris
Would take over for a while while Joe Biden was under
Still racist to ignore how meaningless it is don't know but there's bigger issues
Pete budajudge had a baby
Weather in New York
American flag
We look at that do look what a, he is look what a traitor is
But you know the every photo is him just that fly
Why do they do that
Start my bike
Because they're now going to get ready to get ready him he's served his usefulness
Budajudge had a babies
In the hospital bed thought you were so dumb
Hospital scrubs
Look we had a baby
Haha
It's some kid that got
From somebody else
I mean
Multi-month
Do men have babies
Gaslighting
All of it to mind control
Oh my gosh I mean
I'm gay too. I need to be vice president
1518 hour work days
Shrugging of a slave's people living in
Container
But it's alright
Cookies what what's the answer
So one thing that's important to remember about the context
Clip is that that was not actually Ric Flair
Dating back
1517 years even
Conspiracy theory Protective Service
He's trying to take away straight people's children to grab them
The gay couple
So when you
You hear him talk about
Very against
Again adoption
This this is painfully homophobic
Where is does Alex really think that the reason of the working conditions in apple factories isn't more tightly regulated
Is because Tim Cook is gay
That's
Dumb
I am deeply homophobic
It's obviously the function of Industry more than it is cuz we can't regulate capitalism
Cuz because
I feel like you're saying that this might be a result of unregulated Kappa
Right and I think you're wrong
This is the
It's cuz gay people
I can get away with anything
Pink
We think that they
Are telling us they actually had a baby
I don't know cuz it sounded like he thinks that they have brainwash us into US thinking I don't know
Really had a baby I don't know man had a baby
I don't know
Sounds like he that's what you say
Blankets
Close but I don't know man I just think he's really angry people
But that's the problem
All of what he said
Just boil it down to just be like I
Cuz otherwise it sounds like you're mad at a scattershot
Nonsense
Yeah what he saying doesn't make sense
If you believe him to be tolerant
You're a massive big
Guy back on the show by the name of
Seaperch
I don't know if you remember this guy is an adventure
The early also is
Entirely convinced that Gavin Newsom was paralyzed by is actually what
So Alex is going to have him back on to do that
His face looking partially paralyzed as
Horses that usually goes away about two weeks
Children are vaccinated
Pinkerton's written about that as well
On his sub stat account but I wanted to
I just all this cardiac news and information
I coming out first but yeah that photo there you can really see that
Book study paralyzes different
Doesn't has the devil on the other side not on that side
Really dramatic
So there's a video going around that purported to show one side of Gavin newsom's face
Drooping that's proving that the vaccine gave him like Bell's palsy
Video was edited
Manipulated by someone
Fake first before editing is widely available even on newsom's own Twitter page
The cardiac
Stuff that they're talking about it's all just
Stuff that he's misrepresenting there's data on
Responding to again
But this is kind of fun
Steve is sad
Oh no no no debate I don't know this is a complete disaster
You don't should not be given to
Anyone
Under any circumstances nehme comorbidity
Doesn't support that
And nobody seems to want to debate me on this
I have tried to debate anyone in the medical community
Accuse me of spreading misinformation
Just wants to debate me that's the best way to silence me as to debate me nobody
No you'll be mainstream
Academia
Nobody in the CDC
Nobody me a PA
They all want to just ignore everything I'm saying because
Cuz they don't want to confront
What's going on
Unfortunately you're not in any of those groups that Steve is
I would say that because he's a weirdo
Is that what you don't want to be seen with in public
Maybe you ought to get into the mud with this this kind of
Idiot I wouldn't do it now not mean I would do it but if I was one of them I wouldn't do it
That's why I'm not one of them
NYU be open Tuesday
So
Steve and Alex were talking about this the vaccine
And they're saying like it's going to be
Such a disaster for the medical community
And no one will ever trust them again
Right and the mainstream media no one will ever trust them but they realize we've had the vaccine for month
Months and months are plenty of people are not dead
That's true
But I want to focus on this part of this
They're talking about like the the
Trust is going to be completely gone no one's going to trust the medical community or
The mainstream media ever again
Because of the
The whole charade of the vaccine
Chef
I don't understand why they're bringing that up
They don't want people to trust the mainstream media
That's exactly what they want
It's a good boy. It's a really dumb for them to be all like cono people won't believe you anymore exact
Actually the outcome I rely on to make money
Or take got off the board
You're going to destroy
Police and end in The credibility vaccines for Generations
Destroy medicine you act like this
Absolutely and that's exactly what they're doing but it's not just
People are not going to leave her doctors anymore
I said that's what's going to come out of this door knocking
You're not going to believe anything that Congress says
They're not going to believe anything that the mainstream media says
And they're not going to believe any of the three-letter agencies the FDA the CDC
In the NIH
That's what's going to come out of this
Those are all positive outcome for Alex
Exactly you shouldn't trust doctors you should get these zinc and iodine supplement
Vitamins all of this is exactly what Alex would want
A little weird
I I just
Here's my vet I want an itemized
List of what
They do trust doctors on now
Like they clearly they trust them on like
Cancer right now just rub some dirt on it
Like guys I I mean I don't know yet there are diseases and s*** that are unquestioned by these people it right they would maybe
Broken arm broken Armada it somebody will set their broken arm for him right
But why is that okay and not
You know it's like
It's All or Nothing if you think that the medical establishment is murdering
You can't be like well I mean if they give me the vaccine don't murder me but obviously if I broke my leg I need to go get
Mileiq think they're not creative enough to figure out a way to kill you with a broken leg
These doctors are evil men of doing it for a long time but can kill you if toenails
Problem
Yeah I just think it's a little silly for them to pretend that they have any investment at all in people
Having faith or trust
Authoritative sources government agencies
It's their business is to erode that trust and there's nothing they want more
Rendered obsolete by a mainstream media performing exactly they want to live in a society
Heidi where everyone is
Comfortable and has no
Bulshit flying around the people are profiting off of heavily
Speaking of bulshit here's Steve disqualifying
Himself as someone who should listen to
I just read all these articles and studies
Where people were shot
Especially take a booster
Meaning
Before the shot
Product to me
Yeah if you look on the exposed
Website
They did some really nice graph showing vaccine efficacy waning so we
16 GPS to work
And then goes down
20 and then goes negative which means you're more likely to be infected
If you get the Maxine amazing we talked about this at a previous episode this is a doctor said of his.
If he's somebody who would find that to be compelling
And not look into it a little bit further not recognize that this information has been
Manipulated very transparently I don't think I'm going to trust him
I mean
If you give
Give me any graph
That clearly has white out on it this is crossed out
Pizza Hut
Permanent marker
You don't ever get
To get listen to again
Ya-ya-ya among the many sins of
That expose article
Together did take out lines of data
That didn't work for his
That is
Disqualifying
It was wrong
If somebody asked you for like some accounting information
And you didn't want them to know the full accounting information so you took the let's chat brand
The QuickBooks file
And then gave it to another
No do that
If you're not
Convince
Jose things
Shouldn't be
You're not convinced by the fake video of Gavin newsom's face
You will be convinced okay
By Steve
17 pieces of details and information
What's targeting in the Newsom
Yasso
Look I'm not 17 different sources
Different pieces of evidence
And they're all consistent
With the hypothesis
Bad Gavin Newsom is vaccine injured
So I went to his substack which I should say he's
Heavily promoting
I think that's the game
But I found his article Gavin Newsom is lying about his vaccine injury
And here he has his list of
Point 1700
It's grown to 19 what is the only do prime numbers must okay so I think it was probably like
Qanon excited 17 no s*** better add a few more
So here's the first one
His kids were in school on November 1st through 3rd during the climate meeting when he was supposed to be there
So what was it
Excuse for not attending by Zoom
It couldn't be to be a good dad since his kids weren't home so what was it
Why didn't they explain it on November 1st
Why do we still not know
How come none of the fact-checkers ask this question
Could it be the fact Checkers are biased
Or
Could it be that you never looked for the answers to that question
Fuse number 3
Alex Jones reported his sources confirmed that his sources observe doctor's we're going in and out of his house during the
The. The Gavin was out of sight
So one of his
Pieces of evidence
Is
A second
Hand account of third-hand information, Alex and now he's using this article to make an
On Alex's show that relies on evidence that he got from Alex
You know that Ouroboros of far-right beliefs
Adjusting penalty
Quotes this is number eight
Gavin had his bad
Edcite away from the camera when he appeared the lighting was poor in the folk
This was bad
And the shots were law
We never saw him walk on camera during his first public appearance after the recovery.
I got your number 12 quotes
Multiple Twitter posting suggested Bell's Palsy Oregon Beret syndrome
Just multiple Twitter post adjusted that I don't know what that means
Suggested
Sure
Here's number 18
Clearly I'm not the only one with suspicions here and then there's a hyperlink to
Check out this meme page
I want
To see that episode of Columbo where he's like
Just one more
Check out this meme
The last one
There's some people who tweeted saying you did
Deers
Audi's list December 19th
I have more but it would compromise sources
What's the temperature
Not fair. This is a really stupid list
Oh man I want I want to go back to all those 1920s drawing room
Now we get all the suspects
Together and solve this together in the same room around the dinner table I want that but with this level of information
I wanted to be like
He's does Steely Dan over there he jumped up side and then we saw somebody from another town over whom
Friend of his over there who said that maybe one time you did it
I think it is Steve Kerr's is more Hastings than Florida
This is bad so you don't have to believe Steve
But he has another reason why
Still right
I'm now at
The stage where I'm willing to risk some money
Alright I'm rolling now willing to risk
As of yesterday
I just put on an offer to say
Gavin willing to bet you a million dollars that you're a liar
So I'm risking a million-dollar
You don't have to believe me
At all in my analysis
And what the evidence showed
All you have to believe is that there's some millionaire
Who is willing to risk a million dollars that he's right so he probably thinks he's right
And
I can guarantee you
Gavin Newsom is not going to take my bed
No way no s***
Wow what a great past the governor of California is not going to dignify this b*******
Yeah I'm going to take home
Billion Dollar Bet
From now on anybody want to bet me anything for a million dollars this was on November 16th you said
This got bumped up to 5 million
And then on November 18th
Is an update on his
I've raised my offer to name your price in a private email to Jennifer Newsom
No response so far
Wow
Unlimited money for a blank piece of paper I'm impressed
We make the Guinness Book of World Records for highest price ever paid for a blank piece of paper
Gavin newsom's wife he's harassing members
I'll give you any amount of money
Wow you know what in order
Debate me order to disbelieve this you would have to have an operating premise
With I mean I'm sure no evidence
That rich people are willing to blow a lot of money on stupid ideas
You would have to believe something so insane
But no one
Whatever believe
Better rich person would blow their money on a stupid thing ever
A boy
So we won't last clip here and it's
It says Steve explaining exactly how this bet would go listening to this
Imagine
Imagine a world
Where is sitting Governor would engage with this bull
This is how it will play out
Imagine
A governor of
California deciding
I'm going to get involved we're getting some great fanfic that's so dumb
I'm offering a million dollars
All he has to do is give me a piece of paper
List all the doctors
That he talked to
For the purposes of discussing
Vaccine injury
From the time that he got vaccinated
21 days later
I don't want to know anything else
That's it just a list of doctors
On that piece of paper is the permission
Becky G to those doctors and
He orders those doctors to discuss with me
Any conversations relating to vaccine injury
If Gavin Newsom
Is telling the truth
Kill give me a blank sheet of paper
And I will give him a check for a million dollars
Now
To me that's a deal that most people
Shouldn't refuse
He's reviewing
Nothing
About
Any others
Personal medical information
The piece of paper is blank
And Heat
A check for a million dollars
You got your well-known guy you got plenty of money so
Well what's stopping is
Him
Not telling the truth
And that's why he won't accept my bed because
When he
If he's telling the truth
He's going to hand me a piece
The paper that is not blank
And the piece of paper isn't blank
You know immediately
That he lied to pee
So basically not engaging with this stupid bet
Is proof
Perceive that he's right
Ridiculous
And essentially you know the reason
You never
Talk to you even talk to this guy.
What he's doing is essentially
Engaging in blackmail but without Leverage
Give him a blank piece of paper
That's not going to be the end of it you know in the same way that if you give in to the demands of a blackmailer they're going to
Continue the blackmailing released
This is going to be a thing
I were to tell you I know you saw a doctor
It's this f****** stupid
Pointless to engage with this nonsense
But it plays
Her PR stuff in the right-wing media going to let you can say
So if you have his conscience was clean you'd have no problem I give him a million dollars
What's what's what about that is that
Even a reasonable like conservative who
Buys into this as being a good idea
Would never take that bet
It's a stupid person who's like
Oh you're going to pay up
You're not no hand to there's no strings attached
You f****** liar
In the personal they would never believe that even best case scenario it's still
Not good
Like okay you got a million dollars but you had to
The public really engage and justify and sort of give credibility to
It's the one like Steve as being worth
Do your time and engagement oh yeah and that alone is publicity that Steve couldn't Buy
Yep forget substack
Which is why he would never accept
Is it from somebody who doesn't have that
To offer
You know he's never going to accept this bet
From somebody from this
Cdcr the FDA
Because why would he's going to give him the juice
Frank Newsom or if it's somebody on TV or if
Somebody like that who we can turn it into a spectacle around that of course
Yeah that's what he's going to do
Probably not
Conceivably quite rich
Clearly it does seem that way
So this episode was gross in a number of ways
I think I think you know you see you see a lot of pretty explicit chauvinism
Homophobia
I just
Just outright bigotry all over the place
Just really taking those box
Yeah yeah
It sucks
It's hard to believe why people want him off the air.
Hard to understand why people would be like you suck
Oway
Jordan will be back for another episode in the near future but until then we have website
Yes we are also we aren't underscore fighting that go to bed Jordan
Omniome Leon dzx
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work