Alexandra Thurston color
We are a couple of
Novelty Beverages and have conversations about Alex Jones
The reason that we do that
Because you know a lot about
That's true
Conversely you know a lot about novelty
You forgot last week
Punishment
Whatever I don't know
Azul coconut New Jersey
For the show
Because it looks like
Let me not really but
The pieces are a little bigger the coconut pieces
I are bigger than most
Will be tweeting a picture of this
Buy Twitter.
Parsnip
That's no good
Not good
Gross anymore it's too it's too kind of milk
The coconut
Is too soft
You know what actually don't mind
You got to
Okay
Alright
You know something I don't
I don't mind
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you for joining
So by donating to the show at knowledge
Support the show be perfectly clear
Thrilled if people are donating anyting
And I would not be able to make it through the week had it not been for
Sometimes even if you have a full-time job to go to the doctors
Three times in a week
Write a note to buy a suit
Her friend's wedding
Stuff like that little bit that we make some donations makes
The huge difference
The terms of me being able to eat
So thank you call also now of
To give that
Go to statement Isaiah
Keuerleber
Appreciate it
We're doing another investigation
Sweetheart invest
Navigation
And last weekend
Open face traps
Lost
Carrie Callahan
It's beautiful
2 hour interview with David
And got owned
Pretty much
August
18th
2015 pickup
On August 9th
Okay
To August 26th
2015 about the other day I'm specifically
I told you it was one of the most upsetting episodes of his show that I've ever listened
Well it turns out there's a lot of stuff that happened in the summer of 2015
Maybe we don't remember happened
In such close
Succession with each other
That's just a little bit
Distracted
Let's
High-profile murder
That happens
News coverage of it
He's less than tacky
Tacky
Malaysian plane
The camp so we can do is start to show off
The fun out of context drop
Oh my gosh
What's up
I'd like this Vicky this is terrible he's not having fun in contact
Also I don't I don't think we've ever played an instance of him
I'm talking about Rachel Maddow being a man
All the time we were able to
Slipping on ice
Example of
Rachel Maddow
He ends up saying that for her like
I would say 20 times
But they're going to take
Pretty amazing predictive powers on a Chevy Spark
At least in regard to
Caserta fulfill his
They're coming for me narrative
Either 12 or nipping at his heels
I would also love to crash
That's where we start on August 19th
Nice
Country-fried bigotry
Alex Jones
Stalking
About
Frank Marshall Davis
Being
Barack Obama's dad
Oh yeah I remember that I remember that one
I want to say that I don't care
About what
The reality is I'll take Barack Obama at his word about who is
Also if it is the truth that is Frank Marshall Davis I don't really give a s*** about.
Weird
Well Rory scovel
Is perfect
About that
Are you saying that the first black
President
Also
Are you kidding me like right field that the craziest
Something that ever happened
Dude you did
President crazy
Add black
President is insanely High
We're on the other end of his presidency is over I don't see what game
Was being played by this
40 year long, Frank Marshall Davis being his dad I have no f****** idea
You really need is a Centrist position
Lighthouse 40 years from now guy who inspires liberals but still commits War
Cry
Maybe
False flag by Trump
How else could Trump become president if we didn't rile up all the race
No totally put that that's the other thing that I wanted to talk about
Is it
Premise
Is that
Is Barack Obama
The whole ten yards
Was cooked up by the Obamacare
To trick people he wants to trick people off the scent
Of the Frank Marshall Davis line
Different layers of mulch
I don't know
I don't know what is
Alex Jones is
Acknowledge
Was that he got duped
Some fake
Ploy that was
Utilizing only races
The fake story of of Kenya
Is fueled
Racism these globalist
They knew that they could get Alex Jones to jump on board and all of these people if they just
Braces
Frank Marshall Davis
To do right
Chili Obama
Is Frank Marshall Davis is Dad
And also a Time
Call Desert Eagle
We're onto something of Alex
Callahan
Executor is the clip from August 19th Aries
I want you to keep
Keep track of his phrasing
Strikes me as very racist
Is father
Misty Lee
Was incredibly black African
Budget
Looks nothing like you
Got the bone structure Marshall Davis
Text
Getting a right there at the end
No these nuts
Is not
Jermaine to his
Normal verb
But Obama is a mixed-race man
Do they still have no idea how that's a possibility like
I like
MSP
The only thing that raises were doing when Obama was running
Why don't you
How do you redeem
I made that is just bi-racial version of hasselt
Do a racist
The obvious reasons why
Is because if you are area
If you are at all black people treat you
Its roots in all those like a racial death
Kinlaw's
Earlier than that I apologized
Make strict rules about quadroon
You can't
History of trying to class
Ossify people and it's always to protect whitening
Always
The game is
So
Have fun
Call somebody
We'll have fun
Continuing that Trend Alex cuz it's certainly
I protect
Due to our future 50 years later
Yeah
We have some problems
Racism in the world and
Are sad about it
Try to recognize that wherever we can even in our own
Selves
But
Galaxy like
Costantino
And that is that
It's really the global
That's really
Thoughts on it
Come together
The technology we need to gather on the resources
Movie asteroid
Because basically
What we're facing
I don't want to fight with dementia lorazepam
I don't want to fight
With the
Will the Nation of Islam I don't want to fight with the Catholics
Stupid
But it's going to destroy us in the end
And the globalist have totally betrayed the people that follow them
It was always there too just to make it even worse
I does intractable
It's out of control
That's why I have such a big problem
With people that
Conspiracy theorist about all this
Avoid that reaction
And from people that is don't
Spell crazy b*******
Doesn't make sense
Just like
That's why
Evan
It's like all the stuff demented that's why I frustrating
No you can't have
His argument is the globalist
To trick people into being racially accepting
But the real game
Getting everyone mad at each other
And that's why
Yeah but
Correct
No
Andy doesn't prove that any
Alex Jones is a real not
Do not
And a sentence preposition
Aurora talk to the dream
So at this episode he's also talking a whole bunch
About Hillary and her server
I issue that's popping up
Course agent believes every single rumor about it
Going to be on the show
He also talked about how she got on Snapchat
For her campaign
Everything just disappears on its own
Vanderbilt football
Not a good if I were like
I don't know
Goodbye
Play
Gametime
The reality is that you didn't really do anything majorly Ali
She did not
Especially with the servers
That was any different than past secretaries of State
Done
I in some capacity or another
The same ship
Varying degrees of
Tillerson
Having a fake pseudonym email address
Be that as it may
Trolling
Yeah she's trolling
People who hate her but
Like I think
That liberals
Per se
Maybe it maybe it's not fair to blanket
With liberals
But she didn't realize the response
That the right
Alright would have
I know they're both are such bullying snowflakes pushback against
They begin to cry like little girls
Trolling on the right most of his become such a white noise
Guys just shut the
Or you just blocked
People on Twitter
Indian do you move on with your life
The response that people on the right have to be
Controlled is
Vile
And you spit it out
You seemed like the
Text woman
Human
Why are there no conservative comedians because they understand jokes
F*** you
You've clearly never seen Dennis Miller on The O'Reilly Factor
Hilarious
I bet if you have a free like 15 minutes if you want to have a great time go check out the eclipse from the majority report
Where's Sam Cedar and
Andy Kindler breakdown Dennis Miller's appearances
So funny
Moving along
On this August 19th episode also
Alex
The body
Jesse Ventura
We're past the point where he's bullshiting
About his court
We're not doing
To talk sense
Alex
Hey Jessie Ventura is position is
Fucktrump
No it's interesting you like I don't agree with the things he's saying at all
But I liked him and Bernie
In terms of
Wrestling power away from the two parties
Write with philosophically
Had we known at that point the consequences
I would I would taper it a little
Rather than rustic
Control away from the two parties
Only Consolidated it more around
See where he's coming from
You know these two candidates on the right
Are mixing
Get you make some good points about that but into
Some immigration
Jesse Ventura
Proposes
Described as a thought experiment that Alex thinks is a literal suggestion
It's a little weird
Bernie Sanders
Exposing
Come in
Keisha
Frotteurism
U.s. citizen
America
Get everything for free
Overall
To do that or being leashes and the politicians that allow those laws to be in place
And so are you
About the fairness issue with the first thing that you could do that Alex
McDonald's to get together and lead the charge to take down the Statue of Liberty
Nice
Chester That's Country
Alex
Every immigrant immigrant group in America
It's going through the same thing
Italian
Whatever it happened
They all went through the same thing nobody wanted them here
Everybody wanted them kicked out older coming here they're taking out
What states on the Statue of Liberty
Well then we should take that symbol.
Illinois legal
Doesn't
Because they're poor or something I should have our values as a society
And Alex thinks it's like
Right and then the other thing is Alex saying that immigrants experience
Is David Hollywood
F*** you
One thing I don't understand have you ever read a newspaper from
History
Editorials
Every Todd like when the Irish came over you can go back and read editorials
These people are going to destroy America and they're not even real people
Country weather
These violent skirmishes to bring it over here
In our resources
It's such a boring
Is it things are all like Hollywood
Meanwhile
To make his argument
Hollywood tells the truth whenever
Where is the line
There is no luck real
Meltdown
John
Gunn Bagel giant gum
Just give the Statue of Liberty a gun
None of that still great great
Rebuild the arm
It faces up
Got a gun in it and every
It shoots into the air
Every time an immigrant comes in and shoots off
Also I think that's a great feminist
Make it an hour
Hey babe I'm glad you brought up
The idea of guns
Because this next
Clap
Alex Jones
Discusses his feelings about immigration
Realized
That a lot of his
Fears
About immigration
It's not about
It's not really about
You know them committing violent Acts
Did uses
People like every time there's some story about an immigrant killing somebody like
It's not really about
Clippy sort of spells out
What the
Endgame
The he foresees of immigrants
It's coming in is
It actually took me it made me pause for a moment
There's a globalist industrial plant
A different political balkanization
Those beneath them bad that's just
And the Italians of the Irish all the rest of it
Other immigrants the Chinese were treated terribly
Welcome all
The problem is the Socialist the Ford Foundation
5060 million illegals
Adam basically all vote socialist
Don't take the guns
And you incentivize
It's not fair
Go to Mexico
With my wife
Welfare
I don't personally I don't think it's really reasonable argument to
Say what other country
Please do
In order to
Rationalize our talk about what we do
Potatoes
I could have phrased that
Better than
We should do everything
Conception
We're going to be there going to be
Yeah like socialist benefits and what has you
I'll become a voting Bloc
Everything goes back to God
He just loves gun
Can we just give them guns and then put the
Guess what
He have plenty of
Like
Okay so here's what we do
But here's what I
Here's what we do
Outlaw guns
Pretty much everywhere
The Americans
Okay everybody loves guns
Go to Texas go to Arizona go to those places
Not least
What
Those are going to be even more deserts very soon
Yeah
But they deny that will be
It's gorgeous mazos
Already live in Texas
Basically a desert
I got property taxes even cheaper out there something about you can set up a studio
The gun everytime you go
10% of a gun every time you go to church
Alright I'll give you the holster today
Preacher I'm completely fascinated o b how all roads lead to Gunn
Ben Alex Jones Is Mine
Kind of going to be a through line through today's episode does spoiler alert
This episode is going to go up to August 26th
Really
Change it all
He's still in a position where he's like
I don't really trust them
Your stated I trust Jesse Ventura just you way more
He still talked about loving Ram Paul and wishing Rand Paul would say bigoted
Tell their it's it's not like the position hasn't evolve
I love Rand Paul but he doesn't hate the Browns
People enough
Yeah he needs to be needs to turn his dog whistle into an air horn and then I will f****** get on board with him
This whole thing is
Is like
We keep getting close and then it just
Horses
What what happened to thought it was over we thought you'd made his pivot
Stop talking about Trump's mob ties
He's definitely not said at any point to the end of this
Episode 26th as it were
That he supports Trump he hasn't said he endorses him is not
Ollie's
Yeah and he's apparently at the gun even though in the past you said that
I don't know Trump has said he
Sports weapons near me
Yeah yeah
Which should be disqualifying for our
You would think
I don't know it's very weird I don't know what it like
Is there a race
Wii Sports
Like is it
But I also hate immigrants
Like which is stronger
Like push comes to shove
I think I think
Three options in there
Alright really weird feelings about
I love it
I've made huge progress and figuring out his
Chimera
Here's a nice bags next time
Here is Jesse Ventura coming
Alex
And Alex doesn't get it
You can't handle it
Disprove something
Jesse Ventura is King
Statue of Liberty
Alex Jones
You heard
We talked over to tiny bit but as soon as he says that
Alex is like 3 seconds of Silence his responses
No that's the argument
But
Even further
In this next clip
Great shots
Statue of Liberty
Call Tumi Tumi get rid of the Statue of Liberty without the walls and we took like Canada
Canada to
The 9/11 hijackers electrically came down from Canada and harm.
Keep out
Will end immigration and all that stuff and then
Because it's those people that Harvest our agriculture there are slave labor
Do we have in the country
Again
I'm not
I'm not for illegal entry into the country but the point is
People who have been in college that have created this problem
Epass the programs that are out there
Somebody was not a citizen qualify for government program
That shouldn't happen
By the same token
You put up all these worlds and stuff
We really want to be the United States or land
Order and what what'll happen if you climb over the wall is that
What'll happen if I climb over it to go to Mexico
We are behaving right now
If you read your free were just like 1930s Germany
We're looking to put blame
On anyone but ourselves
We blame them for older cars are going to welfare yuck
Doctor's name is Scott Walker just gave
Box 250 million dollars of welfare to build a new Arena
Wisconsin-Madison education to do it
Corporate welfare
Factory back to it again
We're going to be
Type of a country where we're going to put walls up and all that stuff
Then we have to be like these Berlin
And you're going to have to behave us suck
Nobody speaking into the country and nobody sneaking out
Seterus
African population
Anonymous
Jesse's killing it but also the thing that I think is really important in why I kept
Alex is citing statistics verbatim the David Duke cited to him
No s*** do statistics about Africa population
America
Wow before
He is like this weird information sponge rag doesn't realize where information
He's he's citing
David Dukes
White nationalist positions right in an argument
That really has nothing to do with
What they're talking about
Where Jesse Ventura is dancing circles around
The reality is that you got to
Completely border off of militarize the border is coming
East Berlin
Might as well
Yeah might as well
I love it that I wanted Flats
Some point
Just Jesse Ventura
Hagen
Talking Alex Jones to the Woodshed for like 20 minutes
I think I might just put a link up to it cuz it's so visual
Watching Alex Jones
Beaded face
Headed with facts
We're coming at it with like
What you're saying doesn't make sense
Why do I have them
I love you Jesse Ventura
I wish you would make
Wrong
Yeah
Musica
A little beta cock there's no bigger beta cock than anybody
Call themselves
So she'll also has an interview with Martin Luther King
Juniors
Nice
Who was involved with Martin Luther
Yeah
She's involved with
Samantha abortion
Campaign
So she comes on for like 10 minutes
Talk about how
Abortions not great
Alex tries to make the interview way more important
But it is and I don't think she
She doesn't seem to have much awareness
Has any idea what
Inconsequential
Beano
He's coming up
So
Absolutely
Mad about
Fake stories
Course this is one of them
About you just gone to Europe
If you were call
Where
Vacation videos with Rob do basically
Amanda
The story about Adam
This is a story about how is difficult for him getting back
To the United States
Launch the TV networks
I can't get all the other work done I need to do when I have anger issues
Which is all the time
I probably had
Maybe $1,000 worth of stuff
My mom some plates
Some jewelry
Girls Bibles
45 skirts
I forgot to keep all the receipts
Customs form
Just to be completely
Kashmir
Going to go 1500
Well Uncle Scotty really 1500
And I'm just like
Runs Benghazi Islamabad everything takes money from dictators and you're here interrogating me
I'm not scared of you
Call Alex Jones
Of course
What's a gated
You know I haven't
You do don't you
You said you should just
Drive
I was watching
People that clearly weren't coming in all you're so close
What if
I don't think you're importing things I go on
Because you can go
Blah blah blah
Not just be there in
Probably not going to work
This is about a week
After he got back from Europe
So he's done
Let's call it 25 hours of radio static
Something tells me this is a ballast story
Maybe he got stopped and had to get something like that
Baby
Like what
Stonehenge
Also even in his lies
He's like
Seeing people who clearly words
Alex
What do those people have
Comment
I mean yeah even in his fantasy scenario
Assholes because if this lady was like really
Hey you know what are you declaring
Pet Society
Declaring
It was a good idea
Apparently didn't misinterpret
Yeah it's a crazy
No
Yeah 1227
Literally saved
The 14 words
I mean there was overlap
But this
Strictly speaking if you guys don't know what we're talkin about there
I have
Phrase that they use
It's 14
I can't quote it
From memory cuz I'm not
It's good
It's like we have to protect the
The future for The Offspring of our race
A lot of people have noticed
That
Donald Trump
Beach in present day
Right this moment
Wanted to give
Screen door submarine
So you gave a speech did evoke a lot of things about our people
And the wasp
Protect
Sing the future of the West
Stuff like that
Old which is code for what
Well it is and it isn't it is because of the contacts that we know of Donald Trump
We know things that he said in the
After we can use that to
Inform what he saying
That's right there's the fact that he spent like a year-and-a-half
Trying to
Push Obama's not a citizen
Narrative
Or not
Outside of the bubble of that speech
Anthony give the speech
Sarah Palin
Tweeted
A link to
Conns.com
Young conservatives
What you put in the message
What you what you put in the message was about
Donald Trump said 14 words that will shock
But there is a possibility that
That is auto-generated Tech
Based on Bianca
Conservatives website
Cuz if you try and share that that link
Facebook
Apparently a message about the 14 words
Comes up at the auto Jen
Gotcha been the case on
Twitter but even if it was Sarah Palin
And she can't be oblivious
She's white.
There's there's no doubt about it
Come on I don't think that Alex has ever said anything about that
I don't know I haven't heard it
Listen to Friday's episode I'm not sure cuz that just happened on Friday
Yeah and I even if he does he's going to be
He's not going to mention any time
There's tons of Neo-Nazi code
It's slipping into popular conscious
People realize
Like whenever you see 88
Heil Hitler
Like
Yeah age of the 8th letter of the alphabet 88
Is code
Community circles for Heil Hitler
You ever hear anyone mention
14 or 40
Teen words that's always run
Especially online
Will be
88 a referee
Prince to Triple H the wrestler
888 is a WrestleMania match
Between Hitler
It's actually Heinrich Himmler okay
We just sat up right now I'll get back to you
The closeout be August 9th
Episode
From 2015 Alex
Thought
About abortion
And we always like
Keep track of his weird feelings about those
Especially considering his
Who paid for them whether or not he regrets them right
Misinformation opposition on the Center for Medical progress videos
That are still
Stretching
So he just has forgiven himself and everything is good
Is my gut my gut tells me
My heart says it's alright
Good Christianity right there under Alex based on your own
Alex if you're listening
I don't believe
But you do
So you know what you just did
Feel like I don't know how many abortions you paid for but In that clip
It's plural
Which of them probably
150 women before you were 16 I imagine
There's tons of dead babies
Hey
The Center for Medical progress videos
Don't show the reality of abortion
So not only
Did you kill your children
What you did
Was you and made them indoor
Horrible medical testing
Where they were born
And sliced up insole
I like meat
That's what you did to your kids
Alex
Define I forget
You got really intense
I'm sorry
I'm just saying you got real
I really resonate with
Terrible Tupac
Really Cooking
Drive me now
The idea that you can because I experienced this
So much
In my younger days
Church
These
The sort of Evangelical version of self
Apology self-forgiveness
Because there are bad people in the world
And when people get the idea how I can just forgive myself
In terms of being able to just do whatever you want to do is really violent tendencies
Season they would get into
They initiated
And then afterwards the church will be like
Don't look you just have to
Forgive yourself talk to God don't worry about it yet someone else
Not a productive way
To organize or integrate
Behavioral Improvement
So like
Not least of which because if
Because what that
That justifies everything they do
Wallet the same thing
At the same time the
Evangelical
Those are
On anybody
Any Rangell
Absolute to the point where if somebody who's not one of our church
The crime
Their representative
Well it's
It always gets back to race
Sure
Committed a crime
It's not it has nothing to do with God's
Forgiveness there
No
Justify their own behavior to the point
Let's just all call ourselves evangelicals and then.
Have to be like
You tricked us
On this one
We forgive
I'm into it
Tell me I'm not into it
Alex Jones decides to
Start the show on
Cuz this is really bad and it involves Paul Joseph Watson
I know I'm sorry
This is like really really bad
Distractions are out there
As they
Population
Is
The injuries
Paul Joseph Watson has
Cowardly hit behind the idea
Conservative Outlets
Disgusting
Which is code for their racist articles on Breitbart
And not
Electric
Has gone on record
But he has
Very
Thoroughly
Laid out his family has three
He's dressed this
He like
This is incredibly big
Suggest
And it is
It's not a good sign for your argument
When
Your best
You can come up with to receive it is
Suggest
That the person who is it
You is lying about their race
That seems like a really bad position
Come from
Also
Your evidence
Is a 1995 police
Kentucky from Kentucky
Yeah where they list
That was it which sets
You didn't look it up
You didn't do f****** anything but
Found one tiny little thing that you
You can hang your hat on
And then
Justifies your in
Tire bolts
This argument is a good guy
Very good human being
That's for Breitbart
A Paul Joseph Watson
Infowars
As a whole
Because one of his classmates
Classmates
Came out and actually gave it
An account
On Facebook
What happened
IMDb salt
Chongqing was the victim of
I hate giving any
Sort of like a
Trigger warning
No
I hate the discussion of anything that
Stuff like that
I feel like a
I want
I want to draw a line
Between what's real and what Paul Joseph Watson
Suggested
He's suggesting that the injuries were minor and it was one person who jumped them
I am here is the report from a gentleman by the name of
Shae Gould
Unfortunately it seems that several groups on the internet are spreading lies about an event that happened at my high school when I was a student there
This is a problem for me because they were not firsthand Witness
Nor are any of their sources
I however was there and I saw it happen
I've been asked to post my memory of that day which I'm happy to do
It involves another student
The time Shaun King
I was a senior in high school and I just walked out of the band room when I saw Shawn walking towards
Me in the hall
My entire High School career I cannot recall saying anything more than hello.
However this day no extremes to play
Because before it could happen
Quite literally ambushed by a large group of large people
He never saw what hit him
He never had a chance
Stop to count how many attacks
But the number was easily in the neighborhood of a dozen
There they were both
They were big white Farm boys
All members of the FSA the Future Farmers of America
Immediately a crowd formed while they stopped the life right out of Sean
Who couldn't have weighed more than 100 lb
If at all
I remember not being able to get clothes certainly not closing
Interfere
The attackers that form to circle around the debacle and would not let anyone in
It stuck in my mind
Four years at the most disgusting thing I've ever
It couldn't have lasted long
As soon as the chaos attract
To the attention of two teachers it was over
The attackers definitely disperse
There was blood all over the floor
I hung around and mute horror not believe in what I just seen
I had a fairly sheltered upbringing it was my first brush with violin
Fitted left
Impression
So now
In 2015 various organizations on the internet have taken the stance
That this incident never have
This view seems to Stanford
From one specific article making the observation
Public records
Do not coincide with Sean's ikaw
For example the police report says there was only one attack or not a dozen
It also states that Sean's injuries were very mine
What the article does not discuss
Is the political and social
Climate of that place in time
How these factors
The Fallout from
This is Versailles
Pronounce Versailles
Kentucky in 1995
I believe the population around that time was about to
What a minority gets almost
The death of a small rural Town High School
Is every Civic leaders nightmare
The 1995 Inver sale
It could happen
Potentially made national headlines
Had the story got now
But unfortunately it did not
And no residents of Versailles Kentucky
He should be surprised
By this point in the reading you should have survived that any investigating off
Bizarre would have felt heavy
Intense pressure from all sides
The last name Woodford County
High School wanted was for this story to be on the front page of the local paper
You don't have to interview
New school administrators to know that
The city's elected leaders did not want this thing
Been getting out because they wanted to keep their job
And the local police needed to keep a tight lid on it
So they would not look like jackass
Sean's injuries were downplayed
To just a scratch on the police
Support the Future Farmers of America guys at
Planned ahead
For one of them to take
The fall for all the
The investigating officer
Happy to put that detail in his report
Interview Witnesses
Having never asked
Ask me a single question
When you read about incidents like these it's very easy to imagine the details were left out
Memories are hazy
Things are made up
If you're having such reservations about this story please understand that I have no agenda
I was not close with Sean in high school
And I've not spoken with him since
I'm in no way related to his efforts to
Combat racism
Nor was I ever closer
Who does the Packers
Only so people will know what really
I was one of the few people to talk with their own eyes
So f*** you Paul Joseph Watson
F****** Christ
F*** you
As if we need more evidence of his lazy f****** reporting
You know it is
It is one of those things where
All of this s***
Is happening
All the
The only
Like I ate myself but the only way I can
I can really get to
For the day
Most of us
It's just kind of like
Well it's not happening where I'm
Right
Like this
This kind of s***
How many
How many times
Police office
Murderous
Not going to
To be put in jail
For killing black people
This should be something where we all as a
The f****** country
Watch over these
Everybody
Shows up
But it's
Paralysis
This of well I have
To do my job to go to work
Lititz
Repeal
You like a f******.
Like it really makes me feel like they're taking away well I still got f****** job
A good citizen.
Is infuriating
Feel it like at vets that's the problem
If I don't
I like if I don't kind of filter that out
I have to face the fact that every day I am
Right like everyday
I am at
I mean it does
It sucks
I can't travel to various places and
I'll protest
Still walking
After murder
How many proteins
There've been every single time there's been approached
And all we've done is March incrementally towards them being charged
There's not enough evidence
To save that
I don't know there's no real solution
I can't afford
To help other human beings
Yeah like just monetarily
Like I want whenever Ferguson happen
Because that's what that's what I needed
To do that's what I needed to do
And if I had gone
F****** wouldn't be able wouldn't have been able to make
Yeah like that's
The kind of thing
I would I would love to
You know
Good enough
I'm not good enough person
No because it mattered as much as I think
Think it does
Why am I not for I don't know man
I just there's just this paralysis
Of what else
In in miles
Because otherwise I am complicit
You know
Like all of this s***
It is
It is heartbreak
Anyways let's go back to the
Play issue
Better mean
Larger level
Get us off the hook at all
But I think
The fact that
We wrestle with
Memes
We're trying
I did eight will it will never be enough
Single
That was the first
That was the whole reason
Well
Why are my taxes going up in Illinois
Slater just overall Bruce Rauner
Who should be f****** hit by a truck
Water truck hit
Oh man
A lorry
As many as you can
I want to be a cartoon where there's a
Just a ton boy running over
Let's let's move along
Get to greener pastures
Perhaps
Talk to much about Trump
In this pan
Couple of little nuggets
That indicate awareness of things
Are you aware of
Alex Jones
Is sacrificing
Ufinancial
In order to
Bobby president make America great
Yeah it's
From 2015
Money
I think that resonates with people
Resonates with people
As if Donald Trump's interest won't become fabulously more
Goddamnit Alex
Becoming president of OB a financial victory
Paid to
Trump
Trump golf courses for him to play golf
Edit
No it's something I've been thinking about like
Golf this much before he was president
That's a good
Does
Opening run big
And the reason it's so expensive now is because of all the time
He's a f****** moron nobody
Let him run his own business has money
6 *
Revolve
We're all pretty clear on it at this point
He launders money for Bob's
He puts his name on shittin laundry
Perhaps doing a lot of that
So
This the rest of this episode
The 2nd
He has a really long
Interview with dr. group
Comes and wants to talk more about how his products are awesome
Saving the world from
Absolutely
House they're not
Fear monger
A bunch
While
Fearmonger
I'm going to play some fear-mongering clip
Because Alex like we said when we started this adventure
Summer was going to be like
Harry dent
Who is an economist who comes on the show said it's weeks away taking every
Single movement in the Chinese stock market to be like this
And
Now Alex
Because the summer is now in
It's
In August
He's not moved up to
Couple years ago
And Jewish mysticism
Disrespect
The elites believe in this
Like the Romans used to go to war when Mars was
A certain aspect of Vengeance or whatever
Weather
It's going on
And now it's just weird
Eman now it's just looks really weird in in the last 6 months last year by a talk to
This ominous or this
There's a sport
But also
I'm not
But everything is going to happen in September
Search
Great little trick
The like
Zabel
Right like that kind of thing
Course they do
YouTube
Behind
This fake
These these imaginary people believe in this imaginary thing
So you have to
To take it seriously and help me find that I believe in this stuff even though I'm the one I'm the only person
This is real
Like let's say a witch
You don't believe in witchcraft
How many Move Along
Was there a good luck with that
I don't believe in which
And you believe it
Basically
That's fantastic
Working with his not wanting to own up to what he actually believes it's the regenerative made beds
The holographic Med beds
From Randy Cramer all over again
I hide behind
Rhetorical devices so I don't actually have to expose what I believe cuz if I
Yeah it's very dumb
So there's more
About Doom
If it's a blood moon
But Moon's Jewish mysticism blood moon
So this next clip is a discussion of what would happen if
EMP weather
Which they're saying
That sounds fun
If you see cars all of a sudden dead on the road
You better just start getting outside
Food starts to spoil
People still don't know what's going on but you have 72 hours after
No food there's no water
Universal cannibalism
Also have the telephone
Who's that meteors that are going to be Crossing in September
What was supposedly a top-secret
Organization
To deter meteor meteor shower
I'll tell you about what happened with that project
He doesn't
The first of all cannibalism
Near Universal cannibalism
Are only
15 days away from eating other people power was out here
You and I are going to eat each other
It's 28 Days Later
But
Glitter in there he believes movies predictive programming
Weeds cast
In the past but in real-world scenarios
Generally they work together
Opposite directions, nature in
Emergencies Austin is
Usually brings out the best in people absolutely
So what you go to Eva in the in the Ukraine whenever or in Crimea
Whenever Putin was
Going whole-hog turn down there
You can read the stories about how
People
Develop their own Black Market to get food into people at a Jeep cause
Are all these different systems in order to survive this
And they f******
Did it like real-world situation my dad when he was in Greece during the time when they cut off
Because he was not a Greek citizen
And they're a bunch of other people who did that in order to help people who had money trapped in the couch
So numerous of people coming together
Also Alex
A lot of people have generators
Would be
Certainly
You take down a lot of electricity
Would you like that
Who cares
Backup
Really Creative Solutions
To helping each other that would
Come out of that another one of those like
Such as
Subtle little
The first to go.
Country
Where's Bells
Fish people in the city or trap look like
You don't want to go to court
Take a break to really recognize the comedy
Of a soup
Supposedly secret organization run by the government
Classified Britain
There's nothing here
Coming to dr. group
In order to get advice about deflecting meteors
Chiropractor
A prophet
How do you deflect against meteors obviously
Brain Force
Selenium
Obviously
Oh my God what you doing for the iodine
The sky had to put together a dirty dozen
Type of situation
You still don't need a chiropractor
Not an essential skill
We could use miners better than
If we have a team that's 50 I still don't need a chiropractor
Dad
Subcontractor cut chiropractor you don't need to tell him about all the plants you can fire
Freelance chiropractor
And Alex knows
Dino it's stupid
And if you talk about it a little bit more at want to know it's stupid
That's f****** self-defense
That pathetic
Alex Jones
Kind of out
That most of
His ideas about the world are b*******
This is all like a big chest
Prison Planet
Alex just basically
Talked about his own philosophy and his wife
In order to sort of reverse l.ron Hubbard
How to take this worldview that is kind of a religion to me and make it into a Sci-Fi book
What the f***
There were no prints
Planets
What are you talkin about prime Baron harkonnens
Cuz it wasn't a prison planet that was a great
Adun talk put me to f******
Sleep that long
Fair enough
Is done
I'm going to put my foot down Hardline
That's the end of our coverage is August 20th
The other stuff that happened
David Knight did a special report
About how the wall isn't going to work
So he's not even sold on Trump
Porter now
He also
Basically says that Trump stance on immigrants
Which is crazy
I also
America more than people who say they love them
Absolutely
Really hate
They hate America as an ideal they love America as a place for white
Yeah I also Alex's review
New Mexico
Plumlee
Robert Plumlee
Great names
That's a great name because like a CIA whistleblower would have USA won
Let's talk about
These secured information areas
Manam skier controlled information at
But I have this question about Benghazi
I don't know if this is ever been
Really handled
By the right-wing Folk
Bush Benghazi narrative
They believe the Benghazi was
BabyCenter
Done running operation
To get
Gone
2 Syrian rebels to Libyan rebels
Yeah they believe there was like
Stinger missiles being transported through there too
Terrorist organization
That we are malt Ada and Isis
And that this was an attack.
The cover-up stuff
About it
The question that I have
Is that okay they believe the Christian
The guy who got killed
Benghazi
The
They believe that
Chucky
Discovered he was going to come out with
And that's why they let him die
The question that I have is
If this is a Mastiff
Globalist gun-running operation
It's going through
Position
An incredibly important position to have
Cm
These positions are
Not like
Accidentally given to somebody
Ships that are granted by the president, put
November
Snopes look if you're blocked
The conscious Dan
The conscience
That doesn't work if you are doing this
Massive gun-running operation
Why would you want to make that
The most
Famous thing in the world
As a cover-up
That's a very bad cover up
Bombing their argument is simple for that is
You could
You just close it
Doesn't make sense
The person in charge of that area
Thunder
Pedophile blackmail
Alex Jones's worldview pedophilia
Accusations
And breathe real or whoever wasn't his
Would be someone who's blackmail
If he came out with that stuff
You just be like
Yeah
Instantly nobody would believe anything
Right
Yeah it's just so dumb and never deal with that like
Narrative
You're not awake Dan
True
Okay
So he's not subjective
These people are so
They're not
How did
I don't know
Are we really the dumbest people on the planet
Know what it is is that
Smart people
Edema this sort of world this
Wing
Conspiracy theory world is beneath them
I think it's so stupid that
Why would anyone
Realizing all the while you don't pay attention
Full stories reinforced other false stories
And then eventually we're in the position we're in now
Fret so
Like
We are absolutely
Not even you and I
Necessarily
So in what respect and Alex Jones against
He didn't say that
We don't know that for
For sure
So Jordan in the summer of 2015 you might have noticed that Alex Jones
Howard Kramer
School of Life
Shout out to having boys
It seems he's been on other weird vacation
And on the 21st through the 24th he's out of
He went
Canada
To do some sort of a lecturer with George Noory
Coasttocoastam
Wow
Solid double bill right there
Different kinds of crazy
Alex was
Canada for that
And then
It is very own specific about what he did after that
Cuz he doesn't
Just come back
That's over the weekend
He doesn't come back until
I believe Wednesday
Of the next week
April 25th
He did do a report from the road that I heard that
Said he was in Chicago
I don't know what he was doing
But it's very weird. A lot of weird trip
Throughout Summer 2015
I don't care to speculate about what he's up to
But
It's weird
Probably
Chicago and the taste
Third
Using
Chicago. 24th
15 days
Colloidal
Beef
Goes on a long time
On the 25th
About how tired
He gets
From talking to
It's a little ungracious
That's
The people is a
Exhausting
Fred
He actually
He talks to them
Unlike these ding-dong celebrities
Do the shake your hand and gladhand you remove your lawn
He wants to get to know every
Single person
Comes up I'm so burned by one liking me
Or he realize
This is all of his list
Conspiracy theories for short. Of time
My friend Marty
People on me who start talk about conspiracies
You just talked to that guy
Exhaust
He was coming up to me
So
This is sort of a
Piece of that conversation but he gets into like the
The good stuff
Becomes also and
Yet again another installment in our ongoing series
Alex tell stories
Because people don't say their listeners just at the end they go
Bottles out of the
Minibar
Mr. Jones
Attractive Chinese
What
She likes Horse Show
I need for you to check out
Both of them on the counter behind her smile
Decoration
Fight Club works
Fellow Travelers used in Liberty and freedom
Alex Jones gets beat up
25%
About the Flight Club aspect of like these people in this secret group
In their private lives you work somewhere in another member of project chaos comes in
I'll help you out
Similarity
Between his life
And
Flight Club
Isn't it his followers are planning domestic
You're right
But doesn't
That's it absolutely
Immigrant lady
Barely speaks English is like
You know that Alex Jones
I love his show
Is it
She's listening to learn English is not good
That's just a nice little aside for us
Nice little story that didn't happen
Now Alex
Alex
English for immigrants class would not
And enjoyable
Just teach yourself
Next clip
This is delicious
Be very weird
This isn't part of that
This isn't this is great
But it's also
I love it
He's talking about derivative
And where are you
About I don't even remember the context of how he's talking about it
If you thought about it or amazing
Did this might be another Mike down because it's hilarious
This is
This is the future that liberals want
Truly
Transparency Market systems
Are so successful in generating
Create unbelievable opulence
And spoiled rotten
But if you remove the swell rotten mist and bring back chivalry
We have to return total free market but also chivalry
Amor
That's why people were very very polite
50 years ago you smart
Only place where
That's what they come from
That's where all of this originates from
Father's Day
Respectful
Because if you were to shoot your mouth off you're going to have to
Make good on that check
And there wasn't welfare and there wasn't a society based on
Obsessing over all this garbage
Responsibility
Anime replace it with political correctness
All about
Pulling down the strongholds
But then you selectively can be shut down and persecuted by
He wants you to get those two things go hand-in-hand
Who owns and the rest of us I have to duel
Yeah
Yeah cuz we're all f***
You idiot you are so how are you so stupid
He wants duel
He's talking about like
Chivalry in the Don Quixote
Even like like
Slap somebody with a glove
Which
If we could keep welfare
Falcon fire
I'm not sure
Alex Jones Street
Which we're going to
A fully socialist system
Where Healthcare is paid for
Everyone has a universal basic income
Explain
One of the problems with
Dual
Civilization really good pulling a gun
You're always right
I don't see how that's possible Dan are you saying that might makes right in these if it's not even might just like
Trick you've learned if you're good at close-up magic you can be the
The king of the world
You could be one of the most
Hateful awful people
Who goes around and abuses
People
Like
Use them
Can take it to the street
You shoot them does he not
He doesn't realize that in all Western
That is
The system
He will he does realize that he just wants to be the hero
He wants to be quick draw gunman who goes
From town to town
Saving people from they even smart enough to make real
He does love gun
This is the solution
Society into place we're pulling out your gun really fast
That is
That is really what he wants
Go to that
There's like we'll never get back there
IHOP
I can see you how we ever get back to that
So
Rummy
Backflip
He's hilarious
I love it
They go to play Prison Planet
Twin dad
Don't ever really dead
You're right he's in the talk to Matt everyone's Immortal and they're all here right now
Remind me to skip that one
Billiards
Dude and Gloom
You got doomed
Write this next clip
This is
Classic moves
Where Alex
Explains that he's not a bigot
This is
This is serious
Biggest leg gay lesbian
The word mother father
This is the Purple Penguin thing all over again that the
LGBT organization
It is just an adverb
Any words
They just want you to be more mindful
Considering the who
Think before you speak
It's almost
Like to me
Alexace
Yes I also think it's on par to me with if you have a daughter don't just
By her pink bangs automatic
Give us on Don't by Bluetooth
Things automatically
Try and consider
The part of
You know Jen during that comes from weird social Norm
Yeah
Develop asthma
You subscribe to the idea that gender is
Intrinsic
But at the same time
You're reinforcing
Right
Open trench
Then the globalist
You can't
Like
Is your born with
Right
But
You have to act like
Get to
Like what
Because there's stuff in the water
Okay vaccine
Wii controller
O'Doyle rules
It's just like anybody
And tell me how to
Every TV show on turn on now it's about transgender
And it's just like it's a total agenda
Hollywood actors
Little experience required
Transgender actors for Hollywood little experience required
That's part of the
Tiny minority
Why
Which which which the elite are totally into
And Hannah am just totally controlled areas of new-york Mellon
L.a. Noire not being persecuted let me tell you
Milan
Pushed
As if it's the new national flag
This is cultural domination
Because if they can do this
They can get away with anything
Population
I don't I don't know I mean
Referring
Two people being trans
Part of an elite
Fetishes
It's probably really
What's probably
It's a low-class fetish
Who has more validity than
Yeah
I love
His replacement for
It's not about
It's about population
Wrightwood
F****** how do you go from 12 how do you make
You make the whip its
It's just hate look
Positions
I think people are weird
But look
More important things
And we got
Beat the idea
Is very much
School
Yeah you don't
Don't ever learn a goddamn thing
Fused
Any more things
Ever
Don't tell me how to talk
Saddle me with your grammar
Kramer saddle
Grunt
Goddamn
Ike
Information into his brain
No matter what
For him
Yeah I wish
What is his four ways to learn is not
Listen to others
Soap
That was based on Robert David
He'll came on Alex Jones Show
And said that the elites
Have Mars bases that they're sending children to as slaves
In the aftermath of that has gone on to suggest that Robert David Steele
It was controlled opposition
Coreg trying to set him up
Because Alex is in the middle of exposing the Vatican for their cocaine-fueled that are also not happening
Or at least at least
Very much from Gotham
But
He's like I was breaking this
I've been Robert David Steele
Comes on and distract everybody with Mars colony talk
Everyone saying that I believe is there Mars bases
Yeah there's no clip of me saying Thermage basin
Alex
I have a question
On August 25th 2015
I have a clip where you say literally
The elites are making Mars bases
Listen to
In the future loves me flying up there Elysium basis
What what you think that movie with Matt Damon figured all that out
That's real stuff they're talkin about
Mars
Bigger than major cruise liners
Intercity
Two ships offshore
So the only argument that he can really make
Based on
Things he has said
Right
Timing base
The only thing you can say is I
Billy's are doing that now they're planning on working on that bars base
You know what's in development they're building it
Still
Uninvented
Because don't they know if they get trapped
Out on the sea bass
And they lose food
15 days away from eating each other
You always forget how do I properly
Dan is somebody at the door
Hey
Who's this guy
Italic
Hey Alex
How you doing
Where we doing
I Was preparing
To play the role of Randy Cramer space super soldier
We got to work
Improv training
Together because I have no idea where you were going with a level one class
I'd rather die
Next clip
I'd like to make this argument that
It's globalist
Going to happen.
Here is an example of that that is
Wild
They were thinking about pulling off Moore Oklahoma City
And blaming the Liberty
But we expose them we backed him off
Now they're back and it's like 10 times worse than it was
So they're going to be
But they stopped
And now they're back
Well then back to their bowls
Because
For 15 years
Something like that I don't know it's it's the way it's
Integrates
Coincidence
And isolated incident were really crazy
Right-wing taxation is war against
People I don't want to have you goes off his rocker and blows up a government building
You
Kind of believe a lot of things
He believes because you don't want that
Deal with that
And realize it's kind of a logical consequence
Yeah you say all setup Elohim city was full of Southern Poverty Law Center people
And the reality was just a crazy person
What happened but because you yell about how there are more things that are going to happen
When they don't happen
Feel like
But you're welcome
Thank God I stopped you're welcome
Liberty Movement
Crazy
His in
Frenchman
No
Like before
Okay
Let's say he built a wall
His belief system
There is a wall made in
Entirely out of
No
It amazed
That's a great metaphor in as much as it's incomprehensible
Made some good
Episode on the 25th
A couple of really interesting things that have
Is that
Jeb Bush
Has started complaining about Chinese women coming over and having Anchor Bay
What the f***
Chinese companies that advertise being able to help you come over here
I have a baby
What is something that is kind of real but it's not nearly the numbers that Alex's talk
Just the way that these businesses
Charge exorbitant amounts of money
The desperate people in China
I don't think it's near me
Does a 10,000 a month or coming and if that's the case
I think it might even said ten thousand a week
Whatever it is the number is absurd
Give me same way that on one of these episodes he was talking about how the Isle of Lesbos
Population of 150
50000 immigrants on it
The population of the Island of Lesbos was 80
It's not
There aren't that many
Well let me say this
I just
That attack
Actually 100
20 million illegal
120 thousand
Don't go crazy
The stuff is really overly inflated
I am making a bigger issue out of things that are really problem
But it's fascinating because Jeb Bush started to save this
Alex is screaming about this Chinese girl babies
Situation
Bushes mirroring his rhetoric
I know it's still
It's weird
Donald Trump says a bunch of stuff that Alex Jones likes and he's like
This guy is telling the truth
Global Liberty
Bush and Hillary Clinton
I'm so much
Good reason
But Alex doesn't
He doesn't get on the board and it just makes him more mad that Rand Paul isn't
So you're starting to see you're starting to resent Rand Paul
It's not over yet but I think that might be wary losses
Flips on Rand Paul
I think the
It is growing
Rand Paul
Biology
Actually
Alex Jones believes himself.
And is actually just
The lunatic
Yes
When what he sees as like this
What would you call it
Apotheosis of libertarianism
Government
Is not agree with
Rather than
Maybe thing
I could be wrong
That's simply not a
Possibility you're onto part of it
Because Grandpa even his libertarianism is
Horsley cruel and it's awful
Yeah it's pretty crazy
Ria absolutely
Stupid a lot of violence
Anarcho-capitalist
Beliefs.
Actually truly free market requires
Tiny bit a little down the road
I think one of the other thing
Is that Rand Paul note
God damn well
You start spouting stuff off
Better just complete lies
Like things that helps
He's going to be taken to the Woodshed over it
Because he is a public
Figure that is an elected office
And if you start spouting bullshits
Statistics about false narrative and probably get voted out of office
That's well cuz at the
Time
Right but that is not the case at all nothing to worry about
Just adopting
Have
His
Reputation
With my action
Right agree with Alex Jones.
I have a public space
I think I might be a little bit of that but that also might be giving
Racist
Impossible
Alex Jones has Joe Biggs in studio interview with a guy named
Representative
They talked about how there's a sheriff in Spokane
On the last episode
He's afraid
Southern Poverty Law Center
All these people you know
Globalist
Arming our police to the teeth
Because they're going to take out gun owners
Even though most of his listeners are police
What's a load of s*** but at the same time
Dichotomy today
Clippers
But
It's fascinating
Tumi
The way it is interview they talk
About
Abortion protesters and homeschool
Protest movement
Stuff like that
It's all very wifey
They're talkin about
I never liked the way they stood up to the police
Stood their ground
It's so admirable
Wow
Ya can't
Just just
Boredom
If you're white it's
Like if you're black
Another level there's the right vs left
Because of it
And they argue that
The right
Reproach
It's riot
Course
And what they don't take into account is all the incidences
Left-wing protest being
Pepper sprayed by cops
Being infiltrated by right-wing agitator and even police
There is
Constant attack
On left-wing protesters
That turns them
It turned them into
Even the instance of the Free Speech
Demonstrations at Berkeley
That is even not a good example
The antifa stuff
Isn't even intrinsically violent
So
Well the thing is
I mean
My first thought is
Why is
Is it always
The left
And then it's obvious
Because the left is always the opposition
Why is it that protest
Stairs are always the ones who are being
Murder
Destroyed
Pepper spray
Because they represent
To the cyst
Always
They represent
Movement
Since that
To get money
Politics
What's another very threatening to the existential nature
And that's the very basis of
Liberal vs conservative
Conservative
Don't change goddamn
I'm saying I like it the way it is
Especially the
Conservative even libertarian
To be working to prop up
Send
I certainly don't seem all that thrilled about
They have no
I don't really think
We see a lot of that but again I don't want to tour everybody with that brush
Ben audet
Identifies as libertango
Well apparently
Jesse The Body Ventura
Pretty much right on it and
I think that there is a defensible position for
A lot of libertarian ideas
But
And Patriots
What is the greatest army that have ever been collected and you're stupid
Do you wait
Wait the the guys like
The Bundys
Greatest greatest
Alex products
That President Obama is setting up Hillary
Department of Justice
Go take her
Right there
Become president with a chair
But he knows the storyline
Psycho
For a barber shop window
Play Alex
Is like Joe Biden is going to be switched
Continue the Obama regime
Very boring
Bratz
She comes in to do an interview
You're a dick what it's about
Buy gold
But economic collapse
Who are the guests
Hair up
You tell them that he's bullish on gold
No s*** you are
Never
What is a
Listen I'm telling you for the 10,000
Consecutive time
I'm very bullish
He's that means a trans researcher is a
The trend predictor
In terms of how big you thought gold was going to be
The 25th characters next
Clip and you may recognize this
Exact story from
The Secret of 2017 video
Here's a father-of-three and I should hear a somebody
Ghost
Oh yeah now I remember
National chain
Cafeterias regardless of about 2 years old
Never in my life
Restaurants
And seen people talking about old ladies
The order the food
And watching old ladies
It's the same fluffy
Economy in most areas in the toilet as you know
Give me some f****** money billion dollars plus Alex social
The fuk up
I Love This Bar
Because we now see two versions of the exact same story 2 years displaced in time
It's the same story
But in the 2017 version of it he's crying
About it
I've had time to reflect
And also in the 2017 version of it
He talked about how he bought all those old women
Yeah he did
Slightly
I love being able to point that these instances of like
Oh you're working on a bit
Yeah it's like seeing us
A comic in the early stage of crying and being the hero this version is
The economy sucks old women can't get iced tea
You need to polish a bit more open mic
You're the hero
We now are going to go to
To the last day of RX
Exploration
August
6 2015
This is a bad day
For Humanity
Hellboy
Is it was a very bad what is a very bad day for me
Particularly I remember this
Very well
It's got to be bad
Going over there
But also there are a couple
Really awesome things along the way
I promise you as difficult as some of this may be
Alex Jones reveal something from his
You would never be able to predict
You should not have said on air
I'll survive I'll survive until then got you
On August
26 2015
Alison Parker and Adam Ward
Two local TV people
In Virginia were shot on
On live television
We're not on live television
Right Vester Flanagan live stream
Are there murders
Twitter
And
Alex's response
To it
Is not great
Important
Is
That
It happened
6:45 in the morning
Alex Jones gets on air 11
So that would be rubbing sticks
Eastern
Is when it happen
Central alright
The Manhunt
Happened
Define Vesper
Flanagan
Wasn't really even resolved by the time out
A lot of the information
Isn't there
All that is there
Is
We know
That two people were shot
And
Lots of people have seen
Particularly because
Know a lot of journals
I have a lot of people who I've went to college with journalism students
Some of them
I hate it
Summer good friends of mine I care about very much
And
The idea of
Being able to sort of
Place
The work that a lot of people I know.
Into
These this horrifying
Situation
It hit me very hard and I remember
This being very difficult
Shocking
Piece of
Tragedy
We listening to Alex Jones is coverage
Bummed me the
F*** out
So let's just this is how I you Begins the show
Candy starts
Father narrative
Nash on
26 day
Transmission
We are going to be here for the next 3 hours broadcasting worldwide
There's obviously been a dramatic
Horrifying
Virginia on a live TV
Of a reporter and a cameraman
Buy a disc
Or former employee
Racism
He is now reportedly just committed suicide the last 10 minutes
He goes by the name
Bryce Williams
This is just like the Charleston shooting that killed 9 people
Or a racist
White person
Race war
This
He has been
Tweeting that out
There's a couple problems with even the beginning of how he sets up the narrative
Similar at all
Except for that someone killed people in Cold Blood
Situation with Charleston
Horrible race
To slaughter black people
How to start
You said you wanted
To do he was a suicide
That's one of
In this case
There was a guy
Had
I don't know
If we can say
The instances that he's filed
You know equal opportunity
Lawsuit
About I don't know if they were true or not
Or if he was
Projecting
Racism on two other people I have no idea
But the reality is that he
Felt
Racially oppressed
Former
Stations that he worked at
You believe that
Thought Allison
Parker it said
Some racist thing
And I don't know if she did or not
I have no idea
This was a raid
Killing
It was just a murder director
Specifically
Specific
People
Whereas
The Charleston
Racial Terror
Just because there is a racial dynamic
In both of them doesn't make them similar at all
And it
Disgraceful
Valic
To play it
Play More Bounce
I promise there's not too much
What is Google ads bounces back really fast
He doesn't spend much
On the story
Charleston
Which was fully wind on the Second Amendment
Guilt was applied to white people in general
Other
Unstable
Go out until 1
Dead people all over the place
Chief among them the police maybe you should get rid of guns
Which is what
Obama told his cousin odinga
The Muslim leader
Lost the presidency
He said that people go out
Basically co-president
Ended the Muslim radical Islamic. Then
Muslim takeover
George Soros
To stir up
A race war going
MSNBC and CNN and others promote it like it's normal
Plan on
I didn't look into Obama telling odinga to start right
Guess what I don't know
That's bull
I really really hate this ideas at
This is just
The ping pong
Of races killing each other
Not really
It's the way you get to it
Excuse your back
Yeah you're excused the fact
Gun violence
Being racist
I don't
We're not responsible gun owners like us
No
They're just manipulated it a whole plan to
Yeah
Membership is being
Destroy
Yeah
F*****'-a
He's an a******
I'm going
Play this next
Clip
And there is audio that plays of the actual video
But
I can't do that no
No I can't do any of
I watched
Like the beginning of it because it just Auto played back then
I never watched fully through it
I'm sure that's what you're saying
But Alex plays it
3 *
On his
I hate the idea of playing this
On our show even the audio
But it's important
Because I'd like you to take note
This being
Mere hours after
It's horrifying
And
Alex Jones doesn't
Care about the
Examples of how
He doesn't care at all
At no point in time
I'm in that did he
You say
I feel bad for
I feel bad
Yeah but no he doesn't mean
Absolutely.
For somebody who
Constantly says I pray all the time
He doesn't even bother with the b*******
Fox Prairie
Legitimate psychic
And listen to how little concerned he has or care about
These
2 people who were murdered
In public
In Cold Blood
Easier care at all
Work
Not even close
F*** you
This is the time
Most of them
Suicide
Aren't you know you're not
How are they going to spend
We're about to roll right now
First person point of view
With the gun
With the gun out front
As he goes in
A minute
More walking around
Starbucks
And they are going to sit there and Hammer that and push that
And promote that
He doesn't give us
He's talkin over them playing this footage
He's just sort of calling it like a Visa board baseball in
That's terrifying
Just here
Tearing those guns
I don't
I do not feel
Take some comfort in the fact that we don't have the coconut juice in front of us anymore
The worst is over
With no
He doesn't even bother
End
If your
I guess I guess
Because he knows
No noses listeners are on the side of the gun
Credit where credit is due
Gun
Is up
Start shooting
It's like a blur
Easter not showing
Unedited Raw
Footage what-have-you
But deep the startling
Lack of recognition of the humanity of these people
That are being murdered it and all he cares about is guns
It's not
Absolutely not
It was a moment when I was listening to this episode I was like
I don't understand I don't understand this
Position
Cuz you he'll make the argument that
The Liberals are you know immediately calling for gun control and stuff like that
You are immediately politicizing this yet
What do you what do you what's your problem
It's it's terrifying to
Know who statistics about gun violence
There are completely lies
Interesting things that you can dig up is
FBI didn't study
And they found
That's 100
60 incidents
Active
Mass shooting
From 2000
Defined as one or more individuals
Actively engaged
Been killing or attempt
Something to kill people in a populated area
I found that there were 1,000
T2 incident
From 2013
To December 2nd
We're at least four people were shot
But not necessarily killed
So
If Alex wants to try and make the argument that mass shootings are down
Gun violence isn't a real issue
The numbers really don't
Support that
If you want to
Blame all of it on
Gang banger
Susan what-have-you
Ring out and resonate with your
Incredibly busy
They're the ones who are using guns
Irresponsible
People who aren't White
People who are wider the only people who ever use guns they respond
I am
Still
Consistently amazed
How old
Absolutely bigoted
Crazy
It is every episode 35
Unless you have no you have
Has no a
For human
Noah's mother through my journey at 6
It's been all downhill since
God
He is another explanation that we just don't know yet
If he
If you didn't have a radio show
Be a serial killer
No probably not
Because the identity
His dad would support any probably just be a crazy person
Down the street
You be out there screaming about the exact
Radio show but he
Jesus because he didn't have millions of dollars and a really nice Studio
People would see through the things he says
Most likely
If you had
Make a YouTube channel
Show in front of
The wall behind me
Audio Only
Maybe not for long
I need to buy a tripod for my iPhone
Anyway I shouldn't reveal my plan
We have one more clip about guns
Stuff a little bit
And then we can get on to
The reveal
Alex Jones
It will blow your mind
But this one
He talks about how we don't need that we got to stop blaming guns
For everything
I was just
Distasteful
Especially this
Soon after people were murdered on live television
A butt
The reason I'm keeping this clip-in is cuz a transition
Into him composing tweets
Did Hillary Clinton on air
But it's kind of
Google fi
It's not that funny
Alright
Was Antigone diatribes before bodies or cold
Same leftist
American scum
Army Strong
Social engineering
Liberal Thomas Jefferson
Crooked Hillary Clinton
No cuz we don't f****** roads play
And we cannot wait any longer
Friends of the victim
I want to send a tweet out
Utah
Which
It's your White House pushing race war
I want with all that
On Twitter on Facebook all of you because they are up there
Almost 200 million.
Charleston shooting in Virginia shooting
When statistically
There's less mass shootings
Nope
And Hillary know that full well she's got bodyguards
Hillary
Are there guns
I have a gun to protect myself
Female dog
Jordan
Or whatever
A lot of friends that are bastards appointment
A political
He's still close to like a hacky bit there
Yeah
Jesus
Let's not be able to be already talked about his he's wrong about gun statistics all that stuff
This is now going to make it all worthwhile
Listen to this next clip I'm not even going to set this up at all
This is.
School
And
I'm at the beach
Promotion
I would never do that
Bulshit
Well
July
Cuz here's how I know
He's saying he did it twice
Fire
If you go
To the beach
Add a later you're on the beach putting cigarettes out on your hand
You've done a lot of the high does not last that long if you still on
On a bender on this map
A day later
You have done a bunch of math.
You've not done
Twice
I would say you probably done a bunch
Infected you stressing
Realizes
I got to make a hard line on this
As his
And that
Like what
More
2 is like
Sing
Cigarettes
Yes. Bad about Alex
The first time I took mushrooms
I was laying around
Smoking cigarettes
I can't smoke cigarettes in less like
Repeat the cigarettes
That's the way my brain works
Only allow myself to
Smoke if I could take
Cigarette in one drag
Conquering the cigarette cuz my body was stronger than the cigarettes
Tried to smoke cigarettes
This is never going to work the rules and if I can withstand putting out a cigarette on my
Concord
The cigarette through with the
Strength of my being right
Well that was dumb
And then my break
Velvet Underground is playing
Sounds good
That's not a terrible thing
What you did was f****** awful whatever you did on meth on the beach
Did you kill that lady
Probably as I've already said
I think something really really dark half
And
She actually
Gave her an abortion
I've known
I grew up in Central Missouri
Experience of people who
One of the things that I think is a pretty good
Guiding line sort of rule of thumb
Yeah as if you do math once
I believe
If you die if you say you've done that twice
I don't believe
Most people like meth and heroin or two drugs
Most people don't.
Painkillers
I'll believe that you're not home
That's a reasonable thing
Weed hallucinogen
Those are drugs that people can f*** around with and be completely normal
If you
Take
Poke map
I mean at this point
If you're not smoke
How are you getting
Wild
And you're like
I'll try that again
Like that means something
Yeah you did twice
Did a bunch
Do you have an addictive personality
You're crazy or loot you're addicted to Super female Vitality of
Course you did Matthew Arlington Heights
It's it
Trustworthy narrative narrator
Alright well I did meth for about 6
Alright right now
That
Morton might as well be his reaction
Intuit
I'll be clear about the
Commercial ice
When I was
Really young to remember the commercial on TV
I don't know why that one
I can't
But I got the cleanest
House on the street
This is
15 years later and I still remember this song
Format
It was a commercial form
Admission that Alex makes on this show
He also accidentally admits
That you really really should not have it it
In conversation with collars
Or just in passing
He said
That I think
If his audience
Really realize what he
He was saying would give them reason
Really doubt him
A legitimate businessman
And illegitimate truth
This first one has to do
No
The first
Of the two
Has to do with
Is sort of
His is willingness and desire to court chaos
This was going on there was a bunch of me and another a whole bunch of info Warriors in and an Infowars IRA
Which by the way I think you should get rid of the comments sections on the Articles and put a live chat or link oral
Login to Planet Infowars
Real-time conversations
The comments sections of just become chaos since the David Duke interview just
I mean I want to have that type of mental illness
It's really helping the site so I'm actually quite thankful for
We are really trying
Buckley is just
Sliding lift potentiometer
He admits like it's really helped us out with our clicks and absolutely
You extrapolate that
If you take
Why wouldn't he actively do really f***** up things to get attention if he's like
For 2 hours on my show
It brings me tons of traffic
Yeah that same philosophy would lead him to lie about tons of stuff to make it more
Sensational in order to get more traffic website
Almost like
Pretty much every website now most clickbait stuff
There's no traffic
Tickles like
The top 7 things you didn't know Alex Jones eats on the weekend
You know what
I'm for it
Absolutely for it
Website don't know how to use SEO Alex makes another
Admission later in the show
Kind of like admitting that you have a sensational
Something's real or if it's productive kind of like alright
Yeah
This is a little worse
Infowars life.com
And we block him ourselves because of the claims people are making
Text email
50% off right now in about two bottles about two bottles get two free
BOGO
Did you get Jupiter
Do you pick up what the problem is there
Let's
Set a remind me what it was he
Went through there
Playing in the reviews
It's because of what their claim
Which means
Instead they can't do what it is those people say
Well that's part of it it's illegal for him
To advertise products
Exactly
Answer whenever people write reviews
Kiko's in inbox
Legally
Now if you extrapolate
He has the ability to block at block reviews
He is
Businessman
I have
No doubt in my mind you blocked negative
Give any reason if he has the ability to
It makes total sense
Honest man
It makes total sense now all these products
Make a fire star
It's the same reason that Saddam Hussein would win with like 99%
Goodbye 4.9
Nobody's 100
Guarantee that there is an employee
Who part of the responsibility is to go in and block
Degraded at the
He loves chaos
In order to get traffic
Who cares of s***
Alex your f****** up
I think you might be a liar
I think he's really close to like
Stress is getting to Mi
I think a little bit
I think it's going to lead
More towards
Supporting Trump
But I think that there is just
Climate of his position
Better making it
Very difficult
Like
The idea that you selling this Virginia shooting
It's a sign that he's not engaging with
The stuff
That's outside
What is narrative is becoming
Veteran Center
Do you like
Hillary isn't being kicked out of the race
Rand Paul isn't coming through for him the way you needs I think all that
Just going to leave him
Going to be supported
And it's going to be
Likes to say now that he never said that Sandy Hook
We like to
Just get rid of it
That's how bad he isn't this he has even gotten rid of this
Turn
Here's another
In my opinion something really stinks about this entire situation
I can't even really
Think of a mass shooting quote-unquote or a high-profile shooting like this
That didn't
Seemed like there was something more going on
The situation
We caught them
It just isn't real
I don't know what specifically happened
But the official story is a fairy tale
Stock isn't real
Is a giant
Operation complete
Uncle
We robbed
Yeah it's real Twilight Zone that you're lying about what Rob dues uncle said on your show
Play an interview with Dan
Who finds Rob dues uncle in
In Newtown
That's weird
Publix
Anyting
Even more like aggressively
Sandy Hook
So
Yeah you did not form of though I have started
Sun weather in out Santa Claus is real in the past
Asher
No f*** you
He was saying
And using bulshit lies about lies
In order to reinforce it
He's so slow
I want to talk to Alex
To be like what what
Why do you not
Your position from the
I want to call in his show and hey Alex you have any comments on the Center for Medical progress videos
Couple months
2015 price
Do you have any comment on how they are going
Dirty comment on the
Senate investigations to South Planned Parenthood
You can't do that on his show
No he'll hang up on you
With a collar trying to do what I want to do conversation for
Okay this next clip you have some weird thoughts about the idea of
Individual actions
It's being blamed on a group
And I don't think you understand
How to universalize
Is that his beliefs
Really pics
Confuses eyewear
Survival
If we don't expose the fact that this was racially motivated
Will be collectively Wayne
Who
With somebody else.
And if
But the Folk Center
Person person kills
Vice versa
Goes around killing people you share responsibility but
They're their own person and I know our audience gets
Done something wrong
And their whole world is through those
Goggle
Distortion
You don't work somewhere
If you just optimistic have a good attitude
You'll end up being successful
And that's what it comes down to
Directions to my wife
I don't believe that for a second also
A job as an adult
So I don't know what he's talking about
I don't know how he would have had time to have a job suck 150 women 46
I don't know how we'd ever job
The only times you talked about jobs it went
Is cousins doing odd jobs being forced to inhale a house
And then also when he was kicked out of school for a year and went to work on an animal farm
The only answer
Listen to the
Yeah
Norwell Orwell
Punishments
Go f*** around with your cousin
Right I don't
Maybe he had a job when he was in junior college
Before he got his public Acts
The show
I don't see any evidence that he actually knows what the real world is like
Here's the thing
Through there
Mo's Pizza
I apologize
Added value
Like whatever you said if an F
Group does it
Responsible for the Charleston
All black people are responsible for
Even though those two
Unrelated
Not the same
The Acura is not the fault of the group
At least
The group
The pieces of the group individually Arctic
If you're a member
Then
Does responsible mean
Kind of get what he's trying to
Say it
Smooth
But the idea
Being a part of Isis
This is a choice
And therefore if you choose to be a part of Isis
You are taking on responsibilities
The actions of the group
Right where is being a part of an ethnic group
It's not a choice
That's something you're born into
And therefore you
Withdrawal
You're not responsible for
The things
So then
Obvious parallel there's this
If you are an Infowars
And you commit an act of violence
Alex is to blame
Exactly well that is a problematic as logic
Orbitz
True but
Even it sure seems like that's what he say
Right I mean
It just say
Institutionalized white nationalist
Mercedes part of that but
Proof of the pudding is in
He sets himself up negatively because we aren't making that
We're just saying if that's what the logic
Leads to
But the other thing I think
It is really deeply problematic about what do you think
Is he is very frequently
Demanded that Muslims apologize
Or
Yeah yeah
Yeah it's so basically what he saying in this clip is you know you aren't part of the
White people individually aren't responsible for the acts of an individual white person
Isis
Then you are responsible for the actions of Isis
Also I think almost ones are nice
Right
Then his argument
Combat that would be
Well you don't have to
It's not an ethnic
Well I guess that's true
It's still a choice it's a religion
Is
That's true in the real world
I don't think
The Arabs is not Muslim
Different
Christians
Christians are being murdered more than anybody else around the world Dan most persecuted group in the world
Yeah alright whatever
So
Something really fun happens
Towards the middle of this show
The caller calls in
Example lyrics
All right now
Alex Jones
Request
Zappa like it's dropped like it's drive time
Audubon and then Alex Jones gets
It's really weird
About
Scaccia
We don't need you
Your mind is totally
Until the right
Don't touch that.
William Diehl
Dial
I love that song and Emma
Songs I want to play
Assign
I want to play that then
Slime album 1973
Super smart
And Young
They said the Good Die Young
It's just a real bummer you got to wonder I believe Bob Marley would have love you Alex
If I was cold
John Lennon
Trish really scary stuff
Wait and then you're not allowed to talk about it
You know when the government
Living room
And tells you if you talk about it they're going to kill you and I've already killed
People close to you
The entire government
And they kill people that Alex
Alex released the names of those people killed by the government
He knows about that Paul McCartney has been dead since 1962
You can't reveal that information
Facts about something and he's acting weird
When was
Probably
He could just throw out there like it's not like you
He's already playing fast and loose
With reality anyways
What is he going to get stood by
Quite frankly that theory is in his wheel
Play where you live
He started saying that
No one would be like oh this one's real
If you been
He started to it maybe he's
About the fact that John Lennon was a wife
Fascinated I doubt we would remember him quite as fondue
Maybe that's what he's trying to avoid
You're going to get killed
You just revealed
The secret information
The government has to come to my house first
You know what I never go to my living room
All in my bedroom
They have to be invited
Into your living room
True true
Actually recorded out
Dracula's
So
Jordan
We're coming to the end
We are coming to
To the walking away
Interview
At the end of his show
August
It is the first time
A lady named
Julia Torre amps
I don't know if you've ever heard of
Is she the lady that we heard laughing
Great
I already hate
She
As far as I can tell
Pencil walking into her little bit there's not a ton of it
Information out there in the world
She has her own website
She is
Anarcho-capitalist
She is a firm supporter in Bitcoins
She is an anti-feminism woman
Why doesn't she invest in that one
I don't know I think you should buy low
Absolutely
Obviously we're going to
Yeah she is
Incredibly
I don't want to say dumb
Because she she
Clearly has read a few things
Seems mean to call everyone dumb
But you can
Very strongly disagree with almost everything
She's terrible
Alex
Hit it off famously
They are flirting
Zohar
Millions of viewers
And I found
I found a patreon page
Of hers
I would like to take a moment to Pat RC
Because
We've never been on in
Infowars
We have a
Much smaller audience
Then Alex Jones
YouTube channel
Way more
We have more don't
Now granted she makes more money
Because it's like $100 a month
Gotcha but be that as it may we both
As more people
We have more of the public are like the Bernie Sanders man it's all about Grassroots donations
Absolutely
And when I went to her patreon page I was like
We started Apple
I was going to start a political party when I was in college this s*** party
That's not a bad thing that's not a bad name
Ask me about my positions on stuff about the new healthcare bill
Alright that's a good position
I'm going to need one more example
F*** that s***
You know what I am joined to this party
We have the
Joel
Tubi
Alex Jones
But then I realized that guy
Selling the info wagon
Is making substantial maybe we're just
If the issue
We had Millions
Then
You think those people would get more of a
Well the people
Newly-engaged
Just in the way Alex
And
She's not really advocating those things
It doesn't drive traffic
Pietersite is much
Because her positions are largely
Like just
Problematic
Extreme libertarian position
Sealand stuff you here coming out Alexa
Stefan molyneux
Nose
Asian is a crime
They hate
I hate
Preposition
No roads no school
House lights on fire
You either pay the fireman or you
Burn that house with ground Libertarians generally get around the roads are
That businesses
Where to get people to go to them and I am so you just know it's in their bed
Translated to you the consumer
Well but the business would make those
And the argument that I would say it back
Then we'll go
Only places you can talk to our stores because there was
No incentive for them to create
Rottier home or the hospital or anything like that
Deeply problematic
All of the beliefs
Libertarian
It's dumb couchton really smart
Language
Well yeah but that's how that works trick by really easily
I have a couple clips
Julia Torres
Steve and Alex Jones
And a number of them they think they're riffing
They're not
But this first one
Advocate
This works clip play advocate for child
It's the sacrificial God and we're in the people for being sacrificed to it
Because
If you call a higher authority which is the seasonal hire power to most people
Somebody else
Forty-year-old man you still call your mommy
I mean it's just
Manor woman
Point of making children
It was to keep them children until they were like 25
A bird in the jungle for kids
That is so they're a bunch of babbling
As well
Have to call somebody for anything
My father comes from the same generation
System link that you have to use Black Market
And now it's like
Brakes I have to pay someone cuz I don't have a license to do this
You can Netflix
Capitalism isn't that what you want
Isn't that what you want everybody to have a job maybe we have
Specialist
This is this s*** because you are capable of fixing something else
Sure you are.
There are so many problems
There's so many problems with that clip
They're worse
Song
Someday I will admit
Child labor was not a perv
Yeah I had to get workshops
Like their advocations
You should be an adult
Did any of the rights of an adult
Should be able to work
And the drugs or smoke
Well maybe that maybe that is
Book the idea of child labor being an illegal was in order to keep people children longer
Crazy
There's so many reasons
To not have children doing
Especially dangerous jobs which was what was going on
Working in the mines
All that Machinery when you lost those
His hands you definitely wouldn't get workman's comp because that didn't exist
You are just a person without hands from there on out
Yeah man you know what really keeps you from taking out the garbage
No hands
Except
We've discussed this in the past where that belief
Comes from
Union
S***
That's what they were
Oh you don't have a
That is
Anti-hero toilet
Get your cousin
Toilet tissue
You should really be able to know how to fix
It's your home
In order to make sure you can
Can't do anything more
Homeowner it's imagine it's probably pretty fun to be a weekend warrior
Or something like that for it
Yeah there's there's
Sears
Tons of YouTube channels that just explained how to do these
Do they explain how to take your garbage you don't have a license
Computer got the garbage
You got to go to the DMV
Seattle wait for an hour
It's terrible
Is a anti-state
She believes that
Intrinsically oppressive
I don't even want to deal with that
But I do want to talk about sacrificial God whenever they
And I got that Samantha
Also like
She is Russian
She moved to Canada
So
There we go
You know what I mean yeah well that's why she hates me
Superlit provider health
Different
That's indicative of that philosophy being flawed like different states are run
I can't print countries are different
No they all become communist
Also here's the f***
F*****-up thing
Alex Jones's super International
He's having an
Person
Because of their shared
Taxation
Is a crime
And we definitely don't want to stay
We do need a state to keep immigrants away from our country
White
Like I have
I have ideological in
Inconsistency
But when I find
I go
I don't know
Yeah I'm always I'm always trying to build it but there's a central Audiology around it
And if there is
Contradiction
At least
People
Their ideology is whatever they
Feel like that
That's why
The problem with
These are like
Anarcho-capitalist
Is
They will
Scenario
Yeah
It's
Is House of Cards
Yeah
Like
In their world
The only problem is
Then it's it's the luxury
Of everybody else knowing they're wrong
That allows them to believe their dumpster
Any of what they really wanted
Came into play
They would immediately be like
Okay now I guess you're right you're right we should put children to work
Like the other Terror of
The reality rolling back all of the liberal progress
Play 57
If it were all to go away we would live
Terrifying hellscape
But that's that's again
Trick of nostalgia
It wasn't the good old days
Remember when I was a kid everything was
Because I didn't have to
Come to grips with the fact that all my friends
You were dying around
Alex and Julia get along
If they have these foundational differ
About talking
She is pretty track
The second call it Alex Jones will believe anything on the way
No more gun as a woman I own a gun because
Because transgender
And I think all women should own guns and I think there's
Quite well
What channel is purple
Women's rights
Most females
6 plus women at a great disadvantage
Against a man isn't equalizer
And as part of the hierarchy of male oppression
Grimes
I'm a purple pickle eggs
I legitimately think they think that's comedy
Like I think I think he thinks
Everywhere
Gender roles
I think he thinks
It's funny you know what I think I agree with
I think every woman should own a gun
But
I think men should not be allowed to
Okay
Equalizer well man I already have the physical Advantage so we got to have women equalizer
What's up man have a gun it's back to being a
No I think it's how I look at it
I look at it as a gameshow the barrel of a gun that's how you look
Future No Doubt where the first
3 round
Are worth one point
Whoever wins gets 1.34 frown
Thousand points
Workarounds don't matter at 3000-4000
It doesn't even matter
This next one they're trying to rest a little bit about privilege
I'm just discriminatory
I died in communist Russia but I have privilege
Yeah well you're responsible for slavery
So that's that
Shameful
I'm sad that your family died in communist Russia that's interesting
I meant. I don't know anything about the black market
Fix a toilet that's true
Against her fam I am sad that our family trident
A little sad
The issue the issue that like
When you're talking about privilege never take into account
Is that
There is a societal bias
Against blacks
That is just
Studies have shown this over and over and over
When Julia
Oransky walks down the street
No one knows
Just by looking at her
Better family
Died
In Soviet Russia
No one knows
Reveal that information
Except by
Pahrump
She can give that information up and people can judge her
However they choose
A black person
Is immediately seen as a black pearl
They don't have a choice
About how the world looks
Is why half
White
Is not
What you would call
Is that is the part of privilege that Alex Jones
Refuses
To all look at
One of the
Foundational pieces of that conversation
Here's another part of that privilege
Is Bart
Well then there's the fact she is a gun
Did or if she were in the process of being arrested
They would respect
She would be dead
With her child in the car
There is no old lady
Oh there's so much of a white privilege
Does hypothetical
Situation
How many times
How many times have you seen a white man with a gun
Calm down
Deescalate
How many times have you
You seen a black man with a gun
Who is trying to
To talk to people
Trying to DF
Getting f****** shot then murder
That's what white privilege is
White lady interesting conversation
To be had
If she wanted to
Discuss like the male gaze
Or something like that
Because she is an attractive lady and it was same way that
She doesn't really get to choose how men objectify her
Or sexualize Herbie
You can see that if you look at, it's certainly about how
Libertarian ladies
Websites
If she wants to
Disgust you know like
Like Infowars
I didn't look at the comments on this video but I'm sure a lot of my life website
That's what celebrity
Come on Dan you're the one who's supposed to do the research
How how them
I feel like I was not germane to our investigation
Jones to Trump
No but actually
The next clip is about tree
Okay I have some interesting thoughts
I don't know let's find out
Controlled by the same Powers doesn't matter
Something else
Efficiencies seen the favorites
So that's wild
She doesn't care globalists
I guess I'm not sure if that's
You know cuz she's anti-state so it doesn't matter whoever's the
President
Yeah it's
But
She still
Alex
And when they're talking about him
Shutting down a Univision reporter was
By Hispanic reporter if you recall that was
Not a dignified Exchange
No
So I like very sad
It was a very
Weak man
Doing
I like those
Even her
Even this anti-state
Anarcho-capitalist
People lying
At the end there like
He's bribing politicians
Do you know is what you know he knows this this inside and out
Yeah you're just saying you like him cuz he's committed crimes
He tells it like it is Dan
Is close to a position on Trump
As we get
At the end hear the
Ivy stretch we got two more clips left
First one is problematic
In America
Legitimate
Schools are all Flats
Man who lost his entire career and Aspen
Discredit
Slander
Because he used the term house negro
Describe a situation where it actually happened and you had Cynthia McKinney the first
Black female congresswoman from Georgia
Support this man
So I looked into this
Because the way she presented as he used the term house negro in a situation where it was
What was right eye
This is from the Ottawa Citizen
Publication information because of a,
Rancourt fired by the university worked at
I used
A racially-charged
Two articles you posted on his blog
About the universities
Internal policy
St.Louis
Who was the director of the University's human-rights research and
Education Center
He criticized the methodology of a student-produced report alleging systemic racism
In the University's academic
Fraud process
Sheila
Evaluation to academic
Fraud implying that you supported racism and acted in a servile manner
Rancourt denies these allegations
Louis's
Interpretation
The meaning of insult
Is quote extrapolated and misguided
And
Is it defense
Rancourt called the phrase house negro a comment
Describe privileged minority members who act to minimize the concern
St Louis was the first female law student at the University of British Columbia and the only black woman ever elected as a bench
Happy Law Society of Upper Canada
Common term
You can't walk down
Look every time I go to the store
It's just
Thrown around
Like some p
People say
What up
Sure
And I say houses
But her presentation of her presentation of it is so appealing to people who agree with it already
Cuz you don't not like I don't know how you defend the idea of actually
We calling
Presenting it is
He's talking about it it in Scituate
You're thinking he's talking about old-time slavery days
It's like in a historical context
Use the word the PC sensors come in
It's like you're trying to take the N word out of Huck Finn
You don't like that sort of
Eventbrite
It's not
He did not like what someone said
He disagreed with them
Call them house Negroes twice
Yeah
That's not okay
No it's
Can't hear it all the time time
Discounts
You know what
Frankly
In his world it is a comment
That argument probably makes sense
Yeah probably is the world within which he lives
Hey maybe Julia tyranski
Reviews remarkable restraint in not breaking up
The fact that Julia transki is Russian
Richard Cheese
I just want to take this opportunity to point out that
Just because someone is Russian does not mean that there is something
Nefarious involving
And I definitely don't
Make that somebody
Was murdered in Russia
Communist Russia
It's different now
Putin strong now
But
Nevermind
We need King
I want to fight duels
Kiefer Sutherland
But I want to give you some setup
Is
Julian Alex
Having some nice rap
Alright
Thinking there
Shaking their butt
Yes
They get a call
I'm someone who's trying
To tell Alex
But he's wrong about that
You know what before we go
Like as a comic
Listening to these people
Riff about this
Horrible s***
Thinking it's funny
These are the same people who would go to a comedy show
And immediately get a
Imagine
F*** you
People who insist on
Having a clean show
Are the same people
Fight against
Political correctness all the time
Look I can't say
But yeah sure go ahead
Defensible using the term house
I'm the f******
Meanwhile Flash Forward two years and Alex's Lake
Screaming about that Shakespeare play
Performative bulshit on
But
He get this call
If the guy has been allowed to speak
I legitimately think you would be making some of the similar points that I would make
You get to hear with Alex's response to it is
And it's not great
Especially
This is you living through vicariously
Disposal more information
Sky perhaps
Because I've been
Studying
But he still doesn't poop
Anybody would have
More
Their disposal than you with this
He's better than that one caller we had
So fun based on how
Like they're living in this
Fancy Free World at the beginning of the clip
Eminem f****** turn
And if they attack
Anticipated
I think he's good-looking stud she has nice
She's good-looking guy
I admit it
How old is it
If you watch the video of this
Do Alex
Leaning closer to her body language
At this point she has just said
That you can't watch Rachel Maddow cuz she
She gets all hot
Watching it
In any other environment would be sexual harass
You're attracted to mess around though.
She's taking me out for steaks later
Bill
Is calling from Tennessee Alex Jones predictions
How much do a couple years now and
So far I mean
FEMA camps Alex
Your guns Alex
Faith Hill
I bet
Nothing happened
I'm sorry I mean you just completely fear-mongering
Bilderberg nothing happened
Easy way out
Are you a joke all or trying to make me look good are you serious
I'm serious
Well we never shed
For a moment
He actually asked
You said
Jade helm
I never said that.
My boyfriend mr. Matthau
How do you spell bottom
With a bunch of other statements about where's the FEMA camp
Emergency
In the mid-90s
When we were classified
A different program classified
For the Emergency Center
We're headed Mitch the plans
Social Security recipients
Other borders are wide open outside of shutting off power plant
Vehicles local Department
95%
Confiscation confiscation of guns and Canada
You're a joke bill you for real
Are you sure we're descending into
Tyranny
Again
FEMA camp
Where are they
You say you been listening for years you can type in the education camp
Confirming
We broke the secret documents from the FBI State Police
Federal Marshals 7 years ago
National Tires
The truth is we're not lying here
You're hoping people don't go look up he's army manual
You're just targeting people you think you're stupid
Let me give me the field will let me just give you one of the field
Questions
Put back on screen
3-3 9.40
Resettlement operation
February 2010-2012 the Army first
So that is a 10 if you may have read
I don't read the whole thing cuz it's 372 pages long
A bunch of relevant
I've also read
The things about it found the car
Really
Where are the
There are
But this
3-3 9.40
I love their more
Morning shows they have a great
Call 888 Emmanuel for operations over
The reason that they were pissed off that it got leaked is that now it's public information
People in other countries know what
The Army's operating
Procedures are
And there's a bunch
Stuff in it about
Essentially what it is
Document about best
Is the way I would put it
Ant bait
Describe
Steps
Native command vets
What's involved with taking
Hostile populations
In foreign countries
Cooperation from the host governments
Sort out
Huge group of people
Cancel
They're also
Unfortunately
This is why Alex
Freaked out
Couple paragraphs
Throughout the entire thing
There's a couple paragraph
About
Do you need
The possible need
For using internment
In the United States
Oh that's
In the event
Of a massive terrorist
Attack or
They're not
Laying the groundwork for
The the government coming in and interning disappear
Or anything like that
Just talkin about
Applications of when
Military operation would be appropriate Within
The boundaries of the United
Cases of mass
Terrorist attack
Like
The aftermath of hurricane
There were the need of people who are trained
Just say what you want about the Superdome
It was run very poorly
But that is essentially internment
That is managing masses of population
In a way they can be
Yume organized
We can be
Decently run
So it's not f******
Yeah absolutely cuz it would have been otherwise
It would have been absolute
Because they
They didn't have
In place wasn't there
The point of Hurricane Katrina
This is this is from
Pittsfield Maine
Bradley discusses a variety of psychological operations
Peruse
Including identifying malcontent
Agitators
And political leaders
Communities in order to
Remove or reduce
Antagonistic attitude
Passages like these reflect Lessons Learned From the operation of internment facility
Anorak
Recycle logical operations office
Performed in
Imagine caps
That held as many as
Tens of thousands of
Detainees at their Peak
At the beginning of the Iraq War even through the 2008
There were few guidelines and regulations
Help soldiers
Conductive mask
Tension operation
According to a former military officer who conducted
Detainee operations
Internment facility
Anorak
Quote I would have loved to have this field manual 5 years ago East
The vast majority of guidance in the manual is
Was intended for you
Foreign theater
He said
Noting that only a handful of paragraphs from
Six-speed manual
Address domestic operations
Any kind
An army spokesman
When speaking on background
Said that the current state of online postings
Passages from the manual
Significantly out of
Conflating wartime operational guide
Such as a psychological
With peacetime operation
In which a limited number of the manual principles would be applied in US soil
In exceptional cases
What is the relief effort
Such as
After Hurricane Katrina
The problem is
If you if you really take
What's that in this manual
It's not
It's not really it's
Certainly not a blueprint
For eternity
Right but if you are there's just enough there is of the
The opinion that
All of these
Disasters would be
Like what
Or and that the government would then
Use those as Annex
Yes that does sound scary
Problem reaction everything
Everything reinforce
This is the last
Yeah and I get why because we know that Alex doesn't know how to read
We know that
He
Doesn't know how to integrate knowledge
New new information into his brain
I definitely get why he would read something like this would be like
Here's the Smoking Gun we knew it all along
And it's not accurate
It's not it's not real
It's not true
I mean the thing at the document is
True but his interpretation
Really f***** up things
If you go through it
Because they're talking about
Wartime internment
Write about life
Binding people
Gagging them and stuff like that
But that's talking about
I think we're bad
I did not
Support
How you have to run things
Anyway Alex is wrong
And this guy is about to pee
Point out
Like what Alex does
And that is
The Cradle of something
True
And then lies about
Alex's response
Is f******
Perfect
That there's no way to get through
It's that Satin
Every time
You have something like that small bit of Truth
Is total bull
Just like Planned Parenthood videos were real then they were added
Because that make money
No they don't do body parts
Social worker
So Bill are you
Is
Razee
This next
Little chunk here is
Crazy
She's a social worker
I don't know what Alex is getting at
But he's really fixated as that being away
Discredit him
The Democratic Escala
Gotcha
This is what
People out is the quickest way
Describe it's about you know he has like this distrust of Psychiatry and psychology
Trumpet man this is weird
Social worker
That's irrelevant
What is your profession
Paradigm ruling over everything
Reality
Are you eating
Tell me mr. big
Are you
Have you ever been a social worker
So that's great
But you big dummy
Betsy validate this guy's very real
Argument
You take a kernel of Truth and then lie about it
Evike
What you're doing is you're trying to
To sound really
Smart and you're a social worker you're living in your own parallel reality
You're trying to Gaslight
Me
Coming from Alex Jones
Is the craziest things I've ever
Is making a very valid
That point
Is the most dangerous
Point for any of his listeners
Make them want to actually look into the
Thinks he's talking about
If
The argument that Alex Jones lies about the sources that he uses
It is introduced into the conversation
Then that whole you can look it up argument doesn't work right cuz then someone B
And that's the only thing that
That's going to crack it
So you have to fight back
Aggressively
Subject entirely social worker ring after the
Person as opposed to responding
Into the argument absolutely
Classic
Straight out of fm30 9-4 43
And that was
Declassified
Where in the government says
What are you do that was that secret
I'm sure what
He spells it out as much
In the end of its life
Augie's says basically
Where You Are
Just trying to
Make my audio you're trying to lie to my audience
And it is just a knee-jerk
Reactionary defense
Mechanism
Why doesn't
Where does he feel like
By saying money
That was it
Give me the plant
Cuz he's dumb
Like he says I mean of course he says that he wants to debate
But you just
Cannot be
No but I actually think
Take that
He think
That Planned Parenthood
Killing also
Okay I think that is a piece of it
Any sense
No
No is making a killing
The scam they're going to make up that
They're going to make up that slack to his argument would be that the globalist
Spiritual power based on the
The killing of all these
And the Satanist that magically appeared any anti-abortion
Planned Parenthood
Is just making money
Anyway
So you're not a government worker
I'm interested what is your profession
Weather
Because I just wonder how stupid you can be
And usually it's ends up being one
Social security number
And family
Footage
Myself shot
People screaming I'm an American don't put me in the camp
And the police
Those videos that he has or not
They're people who believe is narrative
That's not that's just people
And then also the next thing he's going to say
Is about this Sheriff
From Spokane
A lot of armor
Vehicles
What have you
Concerned about is Constitution
Yeah
To mean they're coming
When he's arguing
With this guy who's accusing him of taking Turtles
He's doing exactly that
It's fascinating
But also
It's just turn off new list
What do lifters
I don't know but if you are a new listener
This happens all the amount of course the globalist want
These people called in these these social workers who won't admit that their social workers
And get some more of them here in a minute
Are for the American people
Vehicles are farosh
What does that mean jackass
You are a stubborn
In the Bible
I don't have time for you
Grapes
It's a defense mechanism and
Things to tell me
Was it the former producer of Nightline
Wasn't the former NSA officer
And you don't have to believe everything
He is real mad
If you don't understand that there's something deeply wrong with most things that we are told
Senior Living in a fog of your own illusion okay
Just puts out this
I still think she's a social worker just from the way he was speaking
Answer the question cuz you don't want to say yes he rather stay.
August Wireless self-satisfied
Father mother
Drake
A giant crab
You people produce
You know what and we're sick of you we want to be led by you
We don't like you
America's throwing people like Ross ulbricht in jail for starting a Westside Wild
And and giving him a harsher sentence than people who have killed multiple people
That's the guy that the Silk Road
When you're the largest history
I don't agree with drug laws
He also tried to get
Silk Road was
Paperboy
Raped multiple people of Oppression and control in America
Scared of Independence
Because someone said something political
Is Israel the Holocaust for the first
Two years after it occurred because they were embarrassed
There was a portion of Jews
Nobody was prosecuted for
Versus Canada
Constitution
Aggregated
Was Michael Strahan tomorrow
Call
Right now let's go to kneel in Ohio
Paw Patrol
It's not great that's hilarious
Need to go to post office
Bruins
Android
How to get super mad to show his alpha male.
Quite work out the way you want it to start calling names golden jackass
Stupid
Does the name calling even though I do
Girl dad
He's a mess
What am I
Still no real Evolution on Trump I love her pulling out that quote of
If you don't get it
I don't have time
It's such a
Dumb
Pet Stop
Darsalam
Are you telling me you don't know how to add
If you don't get it I don't have time for you four year old
Arsalan
Surrounding Chicago parts
Your position is
That you are one of the only people who know.
Everyone doesn't get on we're all going to die
If you don't I don't have time for
If you don't want to be tired of those threats if you are apart of it
I don't want you
Especially when
So much of the time being like I don't want to fight with people I just want to help people
Mine
F*** you
To do is fight
Totally
Fetty WAP guns and doing
Yeah
You want someone to be like Alex you didn't read this thing you said you read I demand satisfaction
That would be that would be his perfect goodness
There's no doubt I can't draw
Okay
Our website
Dollartree.com
School
At knowledge underscore
Ralphs.com
Click the sports show button
That's correct
Also we got today
Going to have a new episodes
You think me and Marty grossest
Conspiracy podcast
Coming back
Only for donators
Somehow we love the next new episode
Will be about
Denver Airport
Space Camp
Not really no
I'm pretty stoked about it
Now it's super
I dunno what that horse
Fun
Yaddo
Do you know what's great about that horse
It's still alive
That's true
Play what you're doing the wrong person
Thank f*** you John radick love you screwed that up
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color