Damn important swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody looking back and I was right I'm a little bit about
Jordan Jordan
Sure
I hate to
Every now and again got to get a little bit sentimental maybe a little modeling sure and I spot
Is just this the show I mean like the reality of
This
He's so bizarre to me and like
The audience
The being what it is
You reflect back on
You know where things were years of the past
Nothing
Like this seem even conceivably possum
I assumed it was going to happen the whole time
Okay having an having people who listen to the show in the numbers that they do
Positive attitude
Is
It was Unthinkable when we started
The idea of being able to interview the
Plaintiff lawyer for Alex
Close to have those things daily it's there's a reality to
The the sort of presents
Examples of Our Lives
And I'm very thankful
4 +
Completely aware of the fact that it is
Is due to our wonderful audience
100% would like to take the opportunity on this holiday which
Maybe people celebrate or don't I don't I don't know I'm not going to judge to say thank you
Means a lot
100% agree
Whatsyourprice
And I'm going to actually say that this is one of the few times that we are 100% piggybacking on top of each other
All right I thought I was going to bug you in the corner cuz my Brightspot fits right in
He's our braids
I don't tell you why
Because today
You getting mad all right that's not what I'm talkin about
Recording on Thanksgiving
And many people use today is a day to give thanks
Thanks and so on and so forth and what is our bright spot
Other than a regular
Giving thanks
Four things that are
A lot of times
Hey what can I say do you want me to talk about how this is
What you're saying
And what I say to you Dan
And what I say to everyone
Is as you said many people don't celebrate
Today
For any number of reasons
Gone on record as being against genocide
Thanksgiving is not not about
The tradition of the turkey
So today
Like Bill Pullman before me
I declare this
American holiday
Tubi
Global bright spots
Okay that is what it shall be across the world you're declaring independence from Thanksgiving
I am declaring
Thanksgiving all right
Location of the neighbors who are eating turkey with their family love tearing that scream
We are in the present
As we alluded to on Twitter we posted on Wednesday we're going to have
Sneaky Snake episode
Although news had just broken that Alex
Got subpoenaed by the January 6th
Committee
Reasoning for that was
The time
Crunch would just be too severe
I'm trying to turn around an episode wouldn't have content
22 copper button
And we are here in the present day
And we're going to be covering
November 23rd
Lead the tone really
Also going to be covering
Various video couple videos that Alex put out on video that
Spoiler alert one of them is him standing in a creek
That is exactly what should have happened why isn't a goddamn Tom Sawyer
Maybe he just didn't have high water
Penny boots
I work at that business on all this but first Jordan let's take a little bit say hello doesn't do want
So first Patrick
I'm a policy
Next mohab shower from Sweden take as much or now policy want
Thank you very much
I like this one Polly sidewalk
That's nice
Thank you so much right now
Well done police
And Gerald asked that I bring this up by this is from his message
Alright I would love to mention that I had The Misfortune of meeting Alex Jones in 1999
He was nuts back then and unfortunately it's only gotten worse
Okay. Thank you so much you are now attacking
How's your 401k
Business
Money off that heroin
Usually large
So we start exploration
What happened in Alex
Immediate
The past
I'll buy going to the video that he put up called response to the January
Committee subpoena
Personal response time for him to get his message out
Right on his own platform
Exactly what we would have wanted
Play this is the pure on
Cut cocaine version
Delay none of that s*** no having to worry about like all I'm also doing my show nothing
Yeah
I've told the listener
That
You know why
January 6th
Committee
Create bylaws
The Witcher
Has
Myself and
Lied about
Show me
People I know
Claim that we want to do a
On January
This is same Democrats
Call Rittenhouse
Call shot three black
Liars
This is a criminal
This is something
Joseph McCarthy
A lot of people
America
It turned out some of the
Pretty funny how Alex is trying to use the image of McCarthyism to illustrate how he's being subjected to a witch
I'm halfway through he realize that he loves McCarthy and
You know you didn't think at all
Is the fact that is a well hold on
The funniest possible wages
This is exactly like McCarthy except for the opposite because I love McCarthy this is great
We are going to experience
A number of times where McCarthyism is invoked and it just a should choose another example cuz
Doesn't work
Which is why they're using the example exactly
Fit within their cosmology
The letter that the house committee investigating January 6th at Alex's
Is easily accessible and it pretty
Clearly lays out why they want to ask Alex a few questions
Honestly most of the information contained in the letter that they have the information that
Explains why he's being subpoenaed
It's just transcripts of things Alex said on his own show about his involvement in planning and organizing the rally
Any connection to books like Ali Alexander
Probably the part that looks the worse though is
Piece of a transcript from when noted race war fever Matt Bracken was hosting the fourth hour of December 31st
Quote we're not going to be saved by anyone above us
We're going to only be
Be saved by millions of Americans move
Went to Washington occupying the whole area if necessary storming right into the capitol
We know the rules of engagement
If you have enough people you
You can push down any kind of fence over wall
That does
Sound incriminate
So yeah it's a little that is not good
Right up there with the
The capital is falling tomorrow taken tomorrow's news was today with my bracket in terms of predicting
Storming of the capitol
If I were Alex I'd be pretty worried right now cuz these are serious people paying attention to him instead of just dumb pocket
There's now a serious people at the ability to compel testimony and request
It's that are within the scope of their investigation
And honestly from where I'm sitting I think the committee is Sabina and most of the right
People
It'll be wise to keep an eye on things so folks don't over correct
Turn this into an
Insanely sprawling new variation on McCarthyism
But for now it looks like they want to ask the right people questions
I'm out
Even after this news broke about Alex's subpoena
Another round of Athena's came out for the proud Boys The Oath Keepers and their respective leaders Enrique tarrio and
Stewart Rhodes
Anyway the point is schitt's getting wild in Alex's world
Losing all these court cases by default looking
Millions in Damages probably
And now getting
Subpoena to testify in front of a committee that includes at least three house members that he's accused of being satanic pedophiles
Is not
Promising
Yeah that's not great that's Adam Schiff Liz Cheney and Jamie Raskin in case you're keeping score
I don't know what'll come of this but I'm really hoping that his deposition is telefax
Calling this a Witch Hunt
Is
A little bit like
If you were a coven of witches who just
Blown up the king
And then they were like
They're hunting us this is a Witch Hunt
You know you can't be mad about that that's on you you're a bunch of witches you getting onto
Well you're not getting hunted because you're witches you're going to hunt because you blew up a king or whatever
You can hang out you're fine
Exactly if we act not who you are but it is very technically a Witch Hunt
Alex talks about
I knew this was
Major harassment
Really made me pee
Ascot
What
Cuz I'm not going to back down
What is the
Secret weapon
I got
He said
Talk about
Send
This whole global
Paradise
It's time to re
And show in Alaska
For five months
Diligently
Reset War
Holyshit
Here's the deal it turns out that Alex has started a new thing called reset Wars which if you believe his website is quote
He's the most important
Project to date
There's a video up on Band. Video that
Explains what it is and I'll get to that in a minute
First I need to make clear that this is not Alex's most
Important project a date
Is a painfully transparent attempt to harvest email addresses
The website reset wars.com is literally just a forum for people to get the waiting list for whatever is super board project
There's no more details on there it is just a form
Here's what's most interesting about this new website
If you check the bottom of the page you'll find a little link to the terms-of-service page
When you click on it you'll find something really bizarre
Website isn't run by Alex Jones Infowars LLC or Free Speech Systems LLC
It's not run by any business that Alex has been historically associated with
Instead it's quote presented by restore America marketing company LLC Delaware Limited
Did liability company
That's really weird it's glaringly different from Alex's other websites and things of businesses
Cease run Incorporated in Delaware on such short notice we near the Delaware secretary
Tri-states website that the company restore America marketing company LLC was incorporated on November
16th 2041 which I'm certain is just coincidentally the day after the default judgment came down to the Connecticut
Sandy Hook
Fun
Not every business Incorporated in Delaware is engaged in criminal activity but you should be aware that a lot of folks were up
How to no good liked
To use the state of their technical home and there's a few specific reasons why
The first is that there are preferable tax condition
Canton estate
Another reason is that llc's in that state are afforded a great deal of privacy but having to public Lee list the ownership
And board members and such of their couple
That's great if you're super Shady
However there's one aspect of incorporating in Delaware that seem
Little bit more relevant than the others in this situation
Delaware LLC laws provide businesses with what's known as double shielding
In Most states if your business has a debt it like let's say if it gets sued
Your personal assets are protected from being considered fair game to
The creditors
However intelli where it goes both directions
That same protection exist
But if you personally have debts creditors cannot
Consider your LLC
In terms of
Collection
I don't want to make too blunt of an accusation but it almost seemed
Cosmically Shady with Camaro
There is also super duper Free Speech systems out of the Cayman Islands so weird
That he would incorporate so ever know
Yeah the day after
It's always like this important that they hadn't done this way to dreads
What are you guys talking about
4 years
Yeah I think here's my
What's the reset Wars website
Itself a URL domain name was registered about a month ago is in October
So there was a little bit of previous I think maybe it was like a project that Alex wanted to do and then
Got to get this off the Infowars
Restore America marketing company
It's it's
A new adventure
Reset
Chester dance
What's f****** unfair reset Wars is just standard asking for Stuff
As you can tell from this clip from another video we put up on Van. Video titled
What is
Reset War
Everything
Camp hold us
In the Ferdinand
Shroyer
Our energy
Customer building
This is beyond
Tiffany read about science
Because this is actually
Actually happening
Real world today
We have discovered
Their secret
Discovered
How to stop them
Give me to put it all
Together and
System
Give
To not just
Globo's
Transcend
The next level
All of you
Martino's
I've already witnessed
You are the leader
Of the future
But must go to the next level
Albuquerque
Free directions
Humanity
Before they get trapped
The globalist for building
All I'm offering is
Boo
Grabbing us at The Matrix
Feel like maybe he just met
Make that public
Immediately instead of putting
Bring up a page to harvest contact info from people only to eventually revealed it
Keep stuff from the club list all along
I will say that there's some good entertainment
And in one of the videos that Alex posted on Baya. Videos title to give yourself to God the
Journey of recent Wars
And the thumbnail 11 is amazing
I will post a picture of it I'll send it to you to put on Twitter
Okay it's just Alex with his shirt on standing in a creek with his hands raised to the heaven no no no no no
We're not doing Jesus
And if you think
This is clickbait It's
Do not Alex film part of the video standing in a creek
He's really trying to go for John the
It's like real hard here
Yeah like crazy heart
I'm going to play the audio from that video where Alex is in the creek
Okay we're going to listen to the right I'm going to play it in its entirety the only cuts that I've made are so we can
Breaking mic
Discuss what screen size
It is I think is more important lately
What we need to know is what reset Wars is all about this the Journey of recent Wars
Batman when he said he was
Inspire to get down on his knees and pray to God
And God responded with
Hey
Keep doing what you doing buddy
You doing great
You just need more money
It makes sense to reset where's is essentially the same thing
What's the issue for me and that's the difficulty if God is telling him that the answer is reset Wars why need to make
Completely separate thing
From
The businesses he's established and have been long-running for 20-something years
Easy eats
If it's no different
Bell is it's completely different
I don't know if it's all that differ
I hate this already
I'm not even waiting for you
God is waiting
Waiting for you but God is a Freewheel. You got to reach out with your hands
Help me
I choose good I choose
Fart
Eternity
And completion
It's about
Choice we make
Understanding
Fuses and manipulate socks
We have
To another level of understanding
Fight against this tyranny
The recent wards.com
So right off the bat this is
No different than anything else you generally here on Infowars
Except that he has like
I guess he's license
Pure moods music I mean that did sound very
Little new AG on your ass
F****** Boombox from the 90s playlist
Got to do with the Orinoco Flow
Very much the same thing
Is troubling
Because I would have expected it to be different
You know if it's
Somebody's got to make a whole new thing for
You know freestyle Wars
Well I mean cuz then they
It's too close to Infowars
Reset default
Are you can't just make you're not making a sequel you're starting over it's the great reset Wars if you will
No it reminds me so much of
The original Cowboy Bebop episode brainscratch
There's this
Cult leader trying to get everybody to migrate
Electronics and I'll leave their bodies behind
Just a meat sack all of these things
And hearing Alex do that is like
We're not just sitting for
Google one step away from everybody's wearing the same shoes rocket behind the, you know
Understand
I think there is
Reason to be a little worried but
I think
Honestly this is
She's just over selling the new website totally I think that's what it is
Go reset wars.com cam reset wars.com
It's appealing to some sort of vague pseudo spirituality
Hands
New AG bulshit
And religiosity
I'm just sort of amplifying that as much as
Do the candidates get a tent
Gen4 recent Wars.
I'm just so tired of people wanting me to ascend
Why do I need to ascend let's just try and make this s*** good but is a concern for a lot of people it seems
Ascending
Bad news
And that is that Alex doesn't stay in the creek hole
That is really deaf
Little bit
But
Pretty quickly ends up
Walking
Up up
Got to think that it was a heel in his backyard
Towards the end of it you can see a house in the background
He's not just talking back walking along a trail but might be near or connected to his backyard
I don't worship nature like
Cannabis for the wicked
Are all the way
Connection to God
Love you look at the last they're all embracing the Pfizer shots
Moderna stock
They're all
Embracing transhumanism
Call the same time Clayton is there so in line with the Earth
Schoenlein
Creation
But they worship
The creation Endust worship
Shelf
Instead of under
Standards the divine
Transcendence of reaching out
The gods water plan leader getting with that natural
Go program
Or rebelling against it
What you sent
I'll say that for
Parasitical
Hypocritical high on the mountain
And I said that from Deep research
Search understanding of how this
This really works
Alex
I mean he also believes
Like
Male-dominated societies as nature
It's a going against that would be
MSN
There's nothing that man has jorvik
Connection with the nature which is why the people that I see
Support politically
They are actively tearing it apart and distance bolsonaro destroying the Amazon rainforest
By Nature
Still nothing is happening here that is in any way different
Very standard Infowars
This is exactly the same s***
I've heard Alex talks fairly regularly about how he doesn't worship nature
About religious ideas more times than I can count this is
Just boilerplate
Infowars nonsense
I will say there's one difference and it's giving me an idea
Okay
He's walking up
And he's very clearly out of
The energy to get real
Excited and emotional about it
He's just getting what do you want
How to say out
Let's do a show with
Him on a treadmill
None of these big outburst
None of this fake crying he's too out of breath and too tired to do anything but Act
Delirious
The new for my entertainment Buck I don't think that would be a better show
Yeah but I think maybe he's tired he was in
In the creek that made the bottoms of his jeans heavier
Every step he was taking
Was exhaust
So if I were somebody watching this I will probably be asking myself why does Alex need to start a new project to do the exact same
I think he's been doing for years
How do you ask myself why Alex's rambling about vague nonsense instead of getting
I'll be asking why this big new website is just an email submission form
These are important questions because they have no answer other than Alex knows Infowars is a sinking ship and he needs to reboot
So I think that's what we're in the middle on
It's hard not to see a rat
Escaping that ship
You know just like
As all of the other people around him go down with that ship all the sudden this rat
Curry's out
With the Delaware LLC
It does feel that way
I don't I don't know exactly to get a sense of
What the exact
Plan is here boy does it feel like
Life raft
Leslie I'm broken
And yeah I mean sure
My dad said
We showed up with several
A million a million dollars but that's
Because I'm broken
Lovett Lovett
Big buyer one big box
Business Partnership with
Reset Wars which totally isn't me
I'm leaving
Restore America marketing
Man that's
That's real difficult to find Anna
So anyway I'm here we go more of this this video of Alex
Taking a walk
There's only two ways to go she was gone
God's plan or two
Those are working again
Plant operations
I got a lot of excuses and lot of reasons
Showing up at the end of the day
It's about enslavement
It's about turning over your will to them
And you will be betrayed you will be destroyed
Hateful lot so angry they chose wrong
We're trying to Claus many good Souls
With the meds they can that's really what this is
Any species of crab I've ever caught
Put them in a box
The work together to get out but instead any crab that tries to get out
Bending over and grab them attack you to start killing
As long as you just sit there and dice they're all happy
That one Crab House you get out they're not about to let that happen
Hence the intergalactic crab bucket
System
For the
Chickenshit
So I'm not sure if you can tell but in the background Alex
Is faintly playing the violin part from the endgame I did hear that a little bit I was
Is really surprised that's really surprised to suddenly hear that I'm like what time. Are we in
What is happening
Did he record this 20 years ago just
Sooner or later I'm at
He must have like maybe got drunk and watched endgame
I was like God damn that music
I have is my best
Also crabs are presenting that one of the other crabs was trying to get out of the bucket
Yeah
They're that guy trying to get out of here
Saudi phenomenon analysis talking about occurs when you have a bunch of crabs in a bucket and they're all trying
Need to get out but in doing so they like wave around and knock another crab climb on another crab
Metaphor that Alex is trying to make only works if you believe that the crabs at the bottom of the bucket are somehow resentful of the crabs
Trying to get out
Inside to pull them down
You have to believe the crabs have complex intention so their actions which they do not
Better metaphor that can be made by the example of crabs in a bucket is about how sometimes doing things in your best interest can
Hurt yourself and those around you
It's individually in your best interest to run from a fire but if everyone does so you run the risk
The blocking exits
Making the situation worse for everyone
Take their time in their names
Call Bella the better outcome as a whole
And the same is true of
These crabs
Imperial
If I had higher fact
Call t.j.
The thing that I kind of was thinking about you is that like that
Dynamic
Of doing what
Prickly in your best interests at the expense of others and ultimately yourself
That's kind of Alex's career nutshell
Talking it well I mean in a crab bucket yes
Yeah it is very
Musically exactly what he is done
His entire life yeah it strikes me as like a crab metaphor it like you're the crab man you're the one who
Chilly talks about ascending
You're like all I'm going to get up out of this f****** bucket and you just wind up pushing everybody else down and then you can't get up Andy Irons
You need to be more like ants we're going to sacrifice Millions to get across the river some
I don't know
Sure
So Alex has the chickenshit
Dimension that he has discussed
He's talked about that quite a bit in the past
At least he's used that term a bunch of
Heard it before
And so that's why I quit Mark Zuckerberg
Just creating is creating the chickenshit dimension
Zuckerberg on rebuilding its
It's the chickenshit
Where are you
Going there believing you're going to find
Enlightenment all you do is find oppression and slavery
Because once I get you in their system just like the general internet was
Turn the clamp down on it and take all the basic freedoms away.
Went
The Wild Wild West
Caviar
And they're going to have all the prizes and celebrity worship for people that are involved in there
And then as soon as everybody basically is addicted to it and needs it to
Hava Java worker live
They're going to drop the boom on tape
Adult lockdowns
Four Sisters
Tractor run
On the vetiver
That's her play
Total false reality total false reality immersion
A true
Matrix system being built this is still no different than his show
That's the same picture supposed to be like
The Journey of recent Wars
And it's just
Bland Infowars content while Alex is haiku
Right
It's Infowars Outdoors
Lacentre
Infowars
Just walk
He's not being emotional he's not
There's no entertainment value they're certainly not boring man walking
That is pretty
The Dismount if you thought all this was underwhelming
Wait till you hear the punchline of this thing
Okay
Without being asserted to The Matrix parts of radio
Then TV becomes the center of the household
Piedmont dinner around it down to talking to Grandma and Grandpa on your neighbors and
Reading books you not watch TV that's desktop computers at $10 computers
But it's VR goggles and Google glasses
Linchpin forcing you into that system to use it to work
Be able to even do basic business
Because that's what all the major companies are in demand
And then if you don't behave and operate where they want your basically even
Blocked out of that system
Don't take the poison shots
How you're locked out of
Sending over and over again all of it is used
Control you not to empower
It's evil from the beginning gets it
It's a snare
That's beyond walks up to his house
Towards the azaleas backdoor
Now that was a real soft
I found that to be
Intensely underwhelming and I
Think what it was was just like
Alex didn't want to do a second take
And in the moment he couldn't think of a good pun
Might as well just ended
Walk towards
I do like those at the progression to The Matrix is from Radio to television Witcher 2 platforms that Alex has shows on
Alta computers and handheld
Computers Ocala
What is used extensively to further his career for a Google glasses
My point is that if history is Prelude and Alex would be more than happy to use VR platforms
So we could make a buck on
Also Alex probably couldn't have come up with a worse example of the tech enslavement plan than Google glasses
Google Glass was launched in 2013
No one liked it and almost
No one uses them outside of some pretty nice applications in the medical and surgical field
Alice is using this example because it's the image of
Kind of spooky
Like the man is going to force you to wear these VR goggles or whatever but in the real world Google released
Pretty impressive glasses base product
8 years ago
And no one's been forced to use them and it doesn't
Matter
There probably is some exciting applications that certain Fields will be able to explore the stuff that grows out of Google Glass in VR
Capabilities
But I just think it's kind of ridiculous to assume anything Alex's predict
Has any connection to reality
You imagine how
Expensive and prohibitively time-consuming it would be for an evil government to make everyone wear VR goggles
I know the people are freaked out about the idea of like you know
In that Mehta the Facebook commercial
VR for meetings at work
But like I'm somebody who works in plenty of offices I know that a lot of bosses can't even figure out how to navigate a conference
Call so I just can't see how VR4 meetings will ever be anything that can catch on
It's an added thing that's kind of cute
But it doesn't really add much to improve the ability of most
Businesses to carry out their business
Possible things that can go wrong
So it's not in there it would be dumb thing for most businesses to do
And also
Like this idea of
Enslavement and s*** like that or whatever like
We've had
World of Warcraft
We had second life
Like we had this stuff for a while
Where you can meet up with p
People in a virtual space we've had role playing games for a long time
Yeah it's not
People out about the like
The idea of Facebook having those
Probably going to be something that
I don't think it's going to work
The way the
He's afraid it is right
Bike
Facebook rolled out Facebook Marketplace
And like you could have been like oh my God this is going to take over for literally everything you can own
Buy and sell through Facebook
What is a
Gothic
What VR the casino losing with open Facebook yeah maybe it'll have application
Sims 4 it's small
Subsets of people are really annoying bosses
That might be about it
This is this
Skip back to
Bye
Hilarity how stupid I think
Fake people are like Millennials are doing stupid stuff
It's it's
The exact same thing
We're old now
World
What we do
It's not going to influence the future
And his his
Arguments are like
Old man grandpa being like I used to have with TV used to turn off at 2 in the morning like a f****** care
What matters if you want to talk about what the future is going to do
Is what the Next Generation
He's going to do what the Young
Your people are going
Are so f****** impenetrable people just keep saying Millennials are ruining wine or something
I don't even know what this sixteen-year-old is doing
That they're confusing but
Same time I think
That past Generations were as confused by
If the generation below them
It's just
Maybe
It was easier to create account
Show me this is a
Is particularly difficult to character
Mature generation that is
Which is
Is my point
How much
They are like the
The future's going to be this in Facebook is going to be bad and all this stuff
If you look at the numbers of what like
Teams are doing
Facebook has nothing to
Like Facebook's going away
Like that's
The type of s*** that if you need to pay attention
What's going to be the future
What are those kids doing
Facebook is predominantly dominated by like Ben Shapiro links and
Yeah I would agree with that so we should be afraid of Tik-Tok
I work well for Alex goes like
China or something doesn't even know
Get to work
So I just think this is rambling nonsense this video is about topics that Alex talks about all the time already
There's no reason to start up a new company at least for my
Content standpoint
Which Weasley strongly suspicious is a business reorganization
Situation
The fact this website is presented by a totally new delaware-based LLC Incorporated
Badly
Strongly think that's
What's going on here
It would be a little bit like if Enron was like we get it
We're sorry and then they started a new company called totally 100% not and Ron we are
Totally not Penrod
Not us guys anyway this new reset Wars doesn't look like it's anything different
From the norm so it
It's just weird that it's being mentioned
Prominently
It is video like earlier that was supposed to be Alex's statement about the news that he was supposed
Peter by the January 6th committee
I won't hold it against you if you forgot that's what we were talking about before we got sidetracked by recently
Let's dive back into the response video where we left off
It really quickly
Let's listen to the end of the clip we heard before we jumped off into reset Wars
Just to see how stupid it sounds now
It's time to reset
Diligently
Reset War
Really is
Defeating all of the
Alex expects his audience to believe that he's been working diligently for months on a project where the only explanation for what it is
Exactly like regular Infowars
Put some new age music behind it
The website is just contact info Gathering form
For the business that runs the website
Was formed a week ago
Jiffy Lube a really hard
Possibly impossible sales pitch but Alex is cultivated
Very gullible list
Cerveza it's probably going to be fine
I think about possible ways this could be going and there's a couple of options that may be going on I think
The first is that Alex knows he's going to be f*****
In the Sandy Hook case is in probably is going to lose all his money and enforces going to go bankrupt
So before the ship sinks he starts another busy
Incorporated
The state where creditors can't come after your business
For personal stats
Which would allow him to essentially continue doing Infowars as if nothing had happened
Just as
Recent Wars
Instead
The problem there would come down
Funding with his new company but there's a lot of ways I could be handled in because of the Delaware LLC
Who make the assets of this new company much more difficult
The collect on
So if you were to I don't know
Get
Does big sponsor for reset Wars run by this different company
That would be a way that he could
Continue on
Yeah so weird how all of these
Is laws and structures
Specific and
Endemic to Delaware
It's almost
I mean it's almost like there is a specific
Coordinated effort with banks and politician
Things with in Delaware to create a tax Haven like that
That's good thing one of them is our
Yeah there is still a mechanism by which
Delaware LLC scam has assets
Take
Looking for personal debts it's just
Immensely more complicated
Difficult
Could happen
So we get back to this response video for Alex's
Is January 6th
Committee subpoena
This is what
What the hell is going on here
I feel good
Whatever happens
Jamir whatever have
That
The organization
Separately
Are going to take
Plus our course
To the world
So go to reset wars.com
Open browser
Reset wards.com
One word
Put in your email
News alert
Information
I was going to come out about
12 days
With the first
Mindwar Spirit War
What
Because of this all going down happen
Earlier and
Believe me
They know
The Edition
Comes out and
Scream over
It's game over
Calling it by indoors as if it's something different like
His bumper is Infowars there's a war on for your mind
Where can I have to see what ends up happening here but I would guess that this is a six-hour course Alex is talking about his
Just a sloppily thrown-together documentary type of thing that's meant to raise
Meant for this new web
Nothing about Alex and how he operates leads me to believe that he's just put together a 6-hour comprehensive class on how did the
Globalist
Would you going to give away for free and then bow out of public life
That's completely unbelievable
Either way though I really cannot wait to dig into this course once of The Middle
I think this is going to be
I really thought I am going to
I'm going to go with the
The course will never be over
That's my that's my feeling
His his immediate in the announcement of this project is like
Now it might not become
Meant to release it in 10 days from the Snowman
We're going to come
There are other outside organizations that will make sure that the recent War goes on
I want the money I want them getting in their battle.
I'll be I'll be in for that I get billed wire together
Salad Alex
Put build water at his breeches
Houses being attacked
Cuz he's a patriot
I guess that has something to do with
Subpoena
Hard-working page
But I'm telling you
The fact that
Boston
Information on quantum
Physics
What
Observation
Principal
All of us
Just Wynn
Evil comes in like a flood the spirit of the Lord
Dworsky
That
Oh boy wow wow
It's it's almost like
They're the tip of the spear wow
Similar
Where the bulwark against evil
Quantum physics
And the observation principle half
To do with why Alex
Has been successful
Haven't you seen the quantum physics
I would like
Him to elaborate on that okay so
Electrons we know them as particles are there more like probability
Filled right because when you observe them you alter their behavior you're not really absorb
Really honestly they're just kind of a small weak electromagnetic field
And because of that
Alright
Yeah yeah then the Lord
Has to bypass electromagnetic
In order to raise a bulwark
Against the metaverse
Which functions entirely based on observation
Light passing through two slits
And then sometimes it's on the wrong one
Atkins Iowa
And recent Wars
So you know why my battle against the European Banks
Do with quantum mechanics
Absolutely
Because we're all good we're actually all
I think he might be listening to too much of that pure moods music
Could be difficult
So here's the Dismount from this video
God bless you all
And hopefully we've got
Broadcast
But if I get a ray
My test
Dot-com
I leave it to you
You asked you take
I know you're
But I really want
You to sit back
Cogitate
Meditate
On the fact that
Those of you that
My broadcast
Now
As
Parisienne
You realize how
Active
The tip of the spear
The very
Brookline 45
And we
All figures
Donate
Delta Air
Dave
Tom
Dot-com
Infowars store
Right now we've got
Kirbopher
10 hour cleaners
The end of this videos
Leather commercial but it also is a commercial that seems to invalidate the point of what we had just heard
Thinking that
Because if the Testament of his
Life's work
Why isn't he mentioned it was recorded before they had two emergency launch
I would assume
So this is remarkable like this is supposed to be responsible to go to the news that he gots
Peanut any barely touches on that issue
Basically six-minute long promotional video for reset Wars with a title that leads you to believe it's going to have something to do with the
Subpoena
Which is disappointing in a little quick baby
And yet
Exactly what his genuine response
To The subpoena would be
And is
It's fine it's interesting that this is
Almost
It's spiritually accurate what his January 6th
Got the title is
But if not
Another video that came out was making the rounds on Twitter Alex recorded himself in his backyard while a truck was backing up
In the background
Are you saying that he's likely going to plead the Fifth
For the
Which you
You can do that
Lowe's outside America the fifth amendment allows people to refuse to testify and situation
Where they feel like doing so would be self-incriminating
Essentially the policy is that you can't be forced
To be a witness against yourself
There's an upside to this pleading the fifth and that you can remain silent and juries are instructed to not take your side
Silence as an admission of
They're not allowed
On the other hand will you plead the fifth that usually means that everyone
Knows you're guilty of something
They're also downsides to the strategy for instance like if you plead the fifth you have no opportunity to defend yourself
In Alex's case that would mean that all of his passwords that are very well-documented on his show
Get to speak for him
Without any chance for him to robot thing
Provide context
Text dad had a radio show where you
Committed all the things that they say that you committed
And you don't say that you didn't say them and it said your testimony is what you said from the past
You're in trouble
Is there is no serological
Consider transcript of his show
It also deprives Alex of the opportunity to grandstand and have his how dare you sir moment
I think we all feel is kind of overdue
Like some kind of a blow up in
10 quart
Going to go out with a whimper come on Alex 02 Concorde Ellison are you talkin about you're going to bleed
The fifth this is your perfect opportunity to scream at Adam Schiff going down anyways
Ask him about how Larry Nichols audio
Text Colton I said
You can blackmail Congress we've already seen it on his show can do it
Also it's to understand that when you plead
The 5th there's a requirement that the testimony you would be given would be
Self-incriminate
That doesn't necessarily have to me that you'd be guilty of the thing that the trial is about but
The testifying about it would provide an essential
Piece of evidence that
Could be used to prosecute you for another crime
I would guess this is what I was worried about him
It'd be like if you're a witness
To somebody's murder and you're like
Hey listen I don't want to testify because the only reason reason I witness this murder was cuz I was committing a
Completely different murder that you guys didn't catch me Albright
I think all of this is kind of meaningless
The committee wants to ask him
Some questions because Alex was involved in the organizing of an event whether intentionally or not
U.s. Kappa
They are trying to set up perjury trap or even pursue criminal charges against Alex
I mean that is the case does amplify Alex
Is persecution complex he's playing it up quite a bit
Bennigan's
Steve Bannon was just arrested for contempt of congress after refusing
Cooperate with
Subpoena
You didn't plead the fifth though
But I'm sure ban into more important
Investigative lengthen Alex
It's hard to say
I don't know if they would charge Alex of Kentucky
Pecan recipe
I thought they wouldn't I mean
If he's
Don't charge
Him with
Congress unless
You're going
Me to do
You know sure otherwise you've just given him another
A couple of weeks
The grandstand about how can
Chris is corrupt
Do you know he'll ban in contempt and then it was like 3 Days Later returns
Themself in
You don't want to do any of that s***
If you're going to do that to Alex
He shows up in Congress and your life contempt and then you put them in jail
100 questions
And Amber
It's it's
Kind of interesting and exciting news the idea that he got subpoenaed
But
I think that this is going to be a disappointing
What chapter in the book
We're all going to be like oh the Alex part of this
This is a dud I think there's a lot of big stuff going on and then you get Alex in there and I think they're getting Malik's mainly cuz they wanted
Try and get Rodger Stone
Well I don't know if that's
Necessarily the case because Alex
Did
Promote
The federales a lot and stop Bastille
Constantly in the lead-up
He was
Going on a road trip
With Allie Alexander
I think there are enough things that actually involve Alex
Himself
That
Relevant asked questions about time a lot of those things dude
Weave into issues with Rodger
I like his involvement with stop the steel
Who knows
At the end of the day if you're going after a weasel out of all the people that are are put there you've already
You got one that's already
Supposed to be in jail
You've got OJ
Jesus Christ
So we get to now the beginning of the actual show
Mon November 23rd
And you would think that these
Subpoena is a top story
A lot
National team
Rodger Stone
That's not our top story
Ladies and gentlemen it's the fact the globalist are gearing up to launch new bio-weapon attacks on us
Are establishing un1 martial law
Launched this attack
I don't know how else to say this but the subpoenas definitely are your top story
The fear of you and Marshall are right around the corner has been the top story for 20 f****** years
Stale
Top story
I mean if I'm
If I'm a fan of Infowars and Alex says that I go cut
And then we I keep Drive
Mentions you in the top story listen I'm actually a very modest man and
I don't like to talk about myself I want an able
What what I've only talked about that I don't want to incriminate myself I don't want to talk about it asked
Some case against me when would I have ever done that
Anyway Alex's is going to talk about
Axiom's of course
In Union
Germany
Austin Jackson
When the cupboard 19 genetically engineered bio-weapon
He's going to start killing people
That's a good save on Alex's Bart realizing the Civil War
Hey if the Germans fight
Anything Could Happen
Chirp so the EU hasn't made vaccines mandatory
I think Alex is just exaggerating the situation in Austria is what's going on everywhere
Austria just announced recently the vaccines will be mandatory and that the country is in lockdown
20 days
But you have to understand why
On October 1st the country had about 1,800 new Kovac
By November 1st it was over 4,600 new case
November 24th
On that day they reported
14139 new cases
That's not good
No
S*** is out of control there and their government feels the DraStic action is necessary to
Do to stop this
The Surge
I agree with that decision or don't
That's fine but it's not appropriate
This is the entirety of the EU making this mandate
Go to the force
Bloody Civil War
Childish and stupid
Particularly because a bunch of country is already mandatory made vaccines mandatory and they haven't found them so
Dogs in the Civil War
Indonesia made the decision in February Micronesia did in
In July
Tons of other countries have narrow mandates like government employees are healthcare workers
It's not causing a civil war
So
But oh well
I mean
No
What is
The Civil War
Sure
That's what I've got for you
That's all I've got
That's what you that's why I'm here
I guess
Batgirl
I guess that is is appropriate question it is much as like
What's the scale
Does it have to be brother shooting brother
You know you want to call America in the cold
Civil War
Heavy tension
Yes have
Is a great way to say I would not call this in anyway is Civil War
It's a little bit of exaggeration
You'd run by Germany
German government says prepare for forced inoculations no one will be allowed to watch in your house if you don't
German government didn't say the vaccines are going to become mandatory
Are there Health minister
Spawn actually made some really
Depressing comments but Alex is just taken out of context
Reflecting the fact that they've seen a 50% increase in new cases week-over-week
He said quote
By the end of this winter pretty much everyone in Germany will have been vaccinated recovered or died
This isn't that everyone will be back
It's a grim perspective that he believes that given the rates of new cases and a low rate of vaccination
There's a good chance that by the end of the winter everyone will either have been vaccinated or will of God
And that's some of the folks in the latter group will be dead
Some politicians in Germany have called for vaccine mandates but as recently as November 22nd
Angela merkel's spokesperson quote
Made clear that her government had no plans
The tackle the thorny issue of Acts
C mandates
It's almost as if the actual people in German government or saying the
What's the things for my dad
Claiming that they're saying
And all these really doing is misrepresenting headlines and
Man does that
But he does
Can't believe
That what a sad day for a health
Just to walk up and be like man
This is
Fox haha
Sad
Alright
The end of press conference
Yeah just going up there in front of Mike
Is a real bummer groom
S*** man
So Alex
Wasn't going to
Talk about this
Subpoenas but then of course he does
And their subpoenas coming in all the rest of it
Just Department
Subpoenaing instantaneous ladders
It's dealing with it with the lawyers and
My Acosta
Dudes and guys
Thought you weren't going to talk about
It's just going to let it be your main stories of un takeover
But also it's mainly because
Anti his personal
Issues the world is ending but also it's mainly that I'm Blue
That's what's interesting is recently we heard him say we're all already dead
Right yeah
When he was in a particularly bad mood cuz he lost some cases
Some cases do we were all going to die I'm going to die
I wonder where he's at now
We're good American
Understanding that discretion is the greater part of valor
Were the poison shots in the rest of it is really
Pushing towards the physical confrontation because
They're losing
Political war for hearts and Minds we're winning
Big time
The football game where in the fourth quarter and were like 60 points at
Only
Dave lost
I thought that you'd already lost weird world that you are trying to force me to live in
Yeah I thought it said one and even if the Patriots win their still going to like Nuke cities
Super bio-weapon and then you're going to have to dig out
People from
Their underground bunkers and so self-reliant
Then you're hunting all of this stuff has a bug out plan
People
Define Hast
Sure
Yeah I think
What we're seeing is
Alex
Cuz maybe a little bit manic because
The excitement of starting
Believe
I don't know maybe maybe he's finally reach that point of
Acceptance
Do you know where it's like
I finally got it
For me
This war is
So all I'm going to do is ride it out
2bn do you know
No he's going to abandon the ship like a ray
All along all right
Engine
So dumb
You can track his mood
Pretty generally We Lay this point a bit but really
Howard Hughes
Interpreting
The Altima
Outcome for Humana
How how Alex Goes
So goes the rest
As it is
Maybe excited
Thought he's found a way to wiggle out of this stuff
Also
It could not be more transparent to that's the saddest part he really does think he's being super clever and it's hitting this very well
I don't think she's hiding it I think it's how he experiences
Even know if it's conscious for him
That when he's in a bad mood to go ballistic on a weigh-in
Feeling a little bit to work out now all of a sudden they were up 620 and then
The 4th quarter
Share share share
Dumbass
Anyway Alex is a lot of news
But
Might not be able to get
So many incredible articles for today
So much and I sit here before I go live on air
Hours of research
Yesterday evening and today
Working at 1 a.m.
5:30 studying to mine
Your daughter got up at 7 and I made a breakfast
Hashbrown bake
Daughter
That's been our weather just eating and playing the back
Tiana just Delight
Prisoner killed
Evil baby
Tips on the board
Everything in
Question
Have you lost the thread
You did
A big breakfast
Sure where I'm going to talk about the news anyways let me
Take you on this long journey
The hell I got
This is clearly not the daughter that he's disappointed in not being very much.
No this one he still have hope for
So I wanted
Things in Alex's stack
Is the most important article of the day
I don't think you could guess what it's
It's about okay
This is the most important article of the day
Do you understand this you understand everything's let me get it right now
Grammy's China
Thousands of articles
America's
America sell racially-divided
Will burn up and be over
Topsail mountaintops in the hilltops in the valley
There were the globalists Hollywood's investing
There were the New World Order has had set up their new system
China on four of the six big production houses that if you go look at who
Bones the movie houses that fund all this black on white
Bratz movies
Apple shows in all the TV shows and programs
The Communist Chinese regime
Which is the most homogeneous group of people in the world
Weather
WhatsApp
Most of you decide you want to stay Who You Are
What
Chinese
Billions a week
The program
Get them
Cool boy
Sup to this Breitbart article the most important article
Weather when a little bit on a Jag there
What is a boring yarn for Alex
I really hate to hear that this is the most important topic to cover
Are you going to be done this ramp many times like when any commercial features a family where the parents aren't the same race and that's apparent
Ally propaganda again
White people
Like we've we've heard this
Too many times
Tearzah is he still talking about the same Chinese billionaire trying to buy like A1
Content of a studio and that's why
China owns
All of the major
It's more like just that same talking to repackage
It's interesting that he never actually says which movie houses are owned by the tiny
Feels like China owns the movie studios
But that's just because of gigantic part of the current box office comes
A movie ticket sales
In China
And if you have a movie with Ghanta the China doesn't like your movie might not be allowed to be
He played in China thereby limiting your earning
Potential
It sucks
And I'm against it
But exerting that kind of influence isn't the same thing as owning movie studios
If you want to make content that would be offensive
Trying to get still kinda
Maybe you'll make less money
International box
I'm just freaked out by I listen I don't have anything yet
Keep being Chinese
If you want to be Chinese or whatever and all I'm hearing is him saying that is fentanyl the racist ass dragon
And then you're telling me that China is the oldest culture in the world
You're not supposed to believe that
What's it supposed to be supposed to believe that the West has the oldest culture in that everything came from
I don't know I think
He can he can believe that something's predate
But everything that's important like freedom and liberty and books
And
All that stuff is out of the way alright okay so we can accept
Babylon but we can't allow okay
Accept the things were around before but they were bad
That's right yeah
Nevermind so here's where this whole thing with the article comes
This was a Breitbart article from November 22nd with the headline
China Kyle Rittenhouse proves US democracy
Chrissy has failed
That's a flashy headline and its reporting on an op-ed there was published
In the global times
The actual original headline is quote Rittenhouse case
Exposes illness of us political system
The part about us democracy failing was taken from this setting
Unsend the text of the original article
Quote
The Fallout from the not-guilty verdict in the jury trial exposes that the Democratic political system in the United States is fake
He'll be quote
Illness of social polarization and race racial diversity
Said Chinese experts
On Sunday
The commentary is not the US democracy has failed as the Breitbart headline implies and Alex is covering
US democracy has failed to heal this particular social ill and I think that's pretty self-evident
I think Alex is pretty good proof of that actually
What says Chinese officials who study water
So there's an operating a Chinese Outlet which was reported on by britebar with an intentionally mislead
Eating headline added
And now Alex is just going to riff-off what do you assume this article is based on
Breitbart
A headline is
The stupid game of California couldn't be more meaningless
If this is the most important story that he is basing
Hours of research and being up at 5 in the morning for you made his daughter this giant breakfast
How long it took me to get to the bottom of this house
10 minutes 10 minutes
Seems to lost the original source
Global Times article
Massive difference in the point of these
These two
Wonder wonder about that
There's nothing I love more than
Taking out one chunk of a sentence and calling that your head
Doesn't it it's not there's just nothing better than ending a
Ending the headline with a f******
Adjectives that going to describe the next part of
Yeah
So Alex believes that based on this Breitbart article to Total evidence that they believe
US democracy has failed
And they're just taunting
The West
North America
Capitalist or whatever share
Are going to team up
Do takedown America
And
But he but here's what's going to happen before that all right
America in the end of the country
The justice department
Trump and get Alex Jones
You'll be a real boy
Noah
Always get rid of the Never
Leave you in place
I know after you guys brought the country now
What's one last time to join the global
I know that
Did we lose it all
All of us
What
Yeah
What your Outburst was really one of my main points I thought they were winning
What are they going to take to take down the country and then kill Alex because he wants to go to Exile
What the f***
What are we where is where is this all going
Nowhere
Fast
Galaxy
Is maybe a little over stimulated
And is
Give me one last chance to say no I would rather go live in Exile
They're going to be like okay cool but then they're going to kill me right you guys are stupid cuz you don't know that you don't know how that's how this works
If if
This is the result of him taking a bunch of rainforest I think we know the next hour there's going to be a pretty significant
Sure maybe
Dialysis
Honor
That he's being attacked
Stop until AIDS
Decided
He's going to play the
Check on the evil
Want to be energetic Lee spiritually
Anyway
What how like internal inconsistent that is
I got to be under attack I'm going to
Fight these motherfukers but also I'm going to plead the Fifth
If you really wanted to
And you do yourself to be innocent you should go to the court and a
Put them on trial
Remember
This
Hisar saint crispin's day
We happy few
The 300 at Thermopylae I just deciding
We were right so we're not even going to fight his battle
Scott
You going to fight we've already defeated you in the war of words Xerxes we've defeated you in the Battle of ideas
Come on
Answer our letters before you fight us
Boo
Do something else
Say boo to its episode
It's just Alex and Paul Joseph Watson discussing the walk
Peshawar attack
And it's just kind of an attempt to nail down a narrative
That the accused driver Darrell Brooks is he black
Supremacist associated with black lives matter killing white people in retaliation for the written
Nice word exhausting
I don't know exact
Really what is going to come out about this and I'm not going to engage with their
Attempt
To sort of
Mailed out a story that they can work with
I don't know we'll see what happens
Seen it too many times
Deeply deeply racist
Few things that I'm going to bring up
From Pauls
Appearance
Interesting
Here's the first
And then you look at the New York
The day after
Play put it on paper
The news
Can you imagine it
A white supremacist
Trailer black lives matter
SUV
Yes 5 people potentially more than 45 people
Would that be on page 22 remember when they psycho inshot poor innocent black people in South
Guilty
No that was one crazy person the point is
It's a bad person was there black white whatever
So the times may not have put the Walker
Waukesha story on the front page of the following
Because of the developing story and there were limited details
They did publish an online article that day about the event though
On August 26th
2020 the day after the
Those people that also wasn't on the front page of the time
I guess what the Charleston shooting that Alex brings up that happened on
June 17th 2015 in the next day
It also wasn't on the front page of the time
Probably because
Those are upsetting things and you don't want them to be the first thing people see
I don't know
It feels like they would be on the front the next
Paper but
It's like that off in Ark
It feels like they are only on the front page when it's an anti-white story people like Alex
Cuz they're white identity adherence and they've created their own reality to live in where everything is secretly an attack on white people
Bring up stuff like that like what what about like when those patrols to shooting happened
I know that was not yours
Your invalidating your own point
By bringing up that example about how every Harry Potter book
Is released on the summer solstice Dan
Right
It makes sense
Being stupid
Dad
Dylann roof
Disappeared
By the way Wikipedia
Change the description
Wakisha Christmas parade at
The wakisha Christmas
Parade
Call crash
It was just a car crash Alex maybe an accident
So I don't know if Paul knows that literally anyone can change things on Wikipedia but they can
Also the headline is now back to 2021 Waukesha Christmas parade attack
It's amazing that Paul seems to be acting like Wikipedia's run by the mainstream Media or like
We're going to be anointed to be able to change something
He could have changed it just so he could say it's the same way you know anything
Play pull from like 4chan
Could be something that someone that works at in for making report on
I'm not saying that they do but they definitely
Only could
Anybody could
To change anything change things as a joke
Oh man also part of the reason that we knew the whole thing was a with dylann roof a really fast is cuz he wrote a super races
This Manifesto that explains exactly why
He did what he was doing
If this guy in Waukesha dritan a manifest I think it would make the determining the
Precise motiva little bit easier people probably would have been able to
Determine
Another bad example
Pedia is dumb
Yeah and the things that I hate most about it
Beyond ever
Every single tragedy that were
I'm talking about all the time
Is that this is another opportunity for them and you can
Can see them take it
Dylann roof is a lone wolf actor
He's a loan guy they're all loan guys they're all loners
And how did they find out about his Manifesto they probably wrote it
Putting all that stuff in there not
Accepting that it is an entire
Ecosystem
I'm sure that creates deal dylann roof
Not a lone gunman
No no
Alexander park
And Alex is trying to play this game or it's like I was against it listen to those episodes
You were not
Really again
You was trying to profit off it and manipulate
Perception around it
The next
Day
He started his show saying if his guy really wanted to kill black people should have committed
Doctor
It's it's nonsense for him to
Pretend Piggy
Was traumatized or like was on the against
Dylann roof in any meaningful way
I totally such b*******
But it's fun
What are you just rewrite your own his
5 / Fun and Profit
Feel shame about how you're a monster
That's not an option
Decides
I got to get Rodger
Exclusive
About this whole subpoena thing
What's first go
Rodger Stone
Explosively to give us
Video statement
On where he stands what's really going on Rodger
Be here with you
We're not in trouble because we're bad
The evil
Blalock's you're absolutely right this is my first
National statement and any medium
Right here
I didn't Forge just as in the hours at
After I was
Framed and charged in the mother which on
It was Infowars where I did my very first interview to lay out the truth
That epic struggle and now Alex whether you like it or not
Your connect
Academy
For the rest your life
And the Sundance Kid
That's really weird
Rodger
Go on Infowars first when he got indicted got subpoenaed but
You know you didn't go on and forwards first-plymouth that we got pardon
Yeah
Alex is useful to Rodger when she it is bad
Alex and his audience of people you can rely on to believe you and who angrily tell them that their enemies are oppressing you and your
You need their help
Their marks
As a fundraising Ops
Yep they aren't however the sort of audio
Rodger wood
Choose to be around or give a s*** about
He wants to spend moments of bliss with people that he actually hook that is like
Relevant
. so anyway that's why you giving busy
Exclusive to Alex
Mainstream media Outlets would have Rodger on in both ends
Instances anytime he wanted to cuz it's newsworthy stuff
You wouldn't be able to get by
Without the pushback on some Fox News shows
Trouble he goes to Infowars and it makes sense
Also Butch Cassidy and Sundance Kid or Outlaws who died at the end of the movie
Maybe I'll choose a different example
Chuseok
I
It just occurred to
How many years
Of Rodger stones
Adult life
Has he been
Not under
From someone
Right
What can you order some years I think
The majority
Find me the early years probably were less focused on him
He had
Be the whole Watergate thing
If you will of his career
Yeah
I would imagine there have been some times
I swear he's dealing with foreign dictators
Might have
Been under some scrutiny
He's been
Just so many crimes
How does one live their life like I said.
For him it must be the only way he knows how to live
Probably
Pretty fun
There's got to be some
Open to that
It's like those people who are so good and
The crisis
You know that when they're not in a crisis
They almost trying manufacturer
In order to feel
Comfortable again
He's like if I'm not
Climbing I don't know what I'm doing with my life but I think they're what you might be describing as a mental illness
Exactly describe about you
Rodger doesn't want to deal with the reality of his own subpoena and so he has decided to create a strong
Man about it
I've been disparage
And smeared as the promoter of
American Capital
On January 6th
Despite the fact that I
Wasn't there
Any assertion
Claim
Or implication
To the contrary
It's Pat
Oracle
False
There is no evidence
Or any witness who can
Ashley come forward
Otherwise
I would say that it's almost more damning that you're really specific about how you weren't there and maybe had people
Around who can vouch the
Wow almost makes me suspect
But you intentionally working pre-made Alibis which means
But no one's suggesting that Rodger was there any of that s***
He's getting a subpoena because he ran an organization called stop the steel in the 20s
16 election any work of Ali Alexander for the new stop Bastille
Both him and Ali have said as much on Infowars
We know this
The committee's interest in Rodger is largely surrounding is involved
Make It Stop Bastille
As well as that whole thing about him having
Earthkeepers as his personal security guards
Quote several of whom were reportedly involved in the attack on the capital and at least one of whom has been in.
Okay well there is that
Tell you something
You know what they cut they call the Avon box
Oxtail a drug dealer
But he was never touching the truck so you know he didn't deal drugs
Then he wasn't there
Yeah I don't I don't think that Rodger is like
Any kind of orchestrator or ringleader
But I do think that there's some shady business going on with the stop this feeling
Anything that Alexander is involved with his shady as hell too
The beginning
So
Think that there are some questions that I think it would be appropriate to ask him
For a guy like Rodger Stone
Who has been under investigation let's call it most of his adult life
I think he probably
He has a good sense of when something
Might go wrong
Decided to stay away from
Yeah
Rodger doesn't know to that like
Hey why would
Could we do that
Right medicine Congress is stupid
Why would we do that right
Right
I'm many things Alex but I'm not
Stupid
Menacing lawmakers even though nobody was armed
Donald Trump
Politically
Is either an idiot
Or an amateur
Why would we
Motive for this
Well in my place it would take a very large
Garbage disposal
I'm not going there
What are we doing
That's all sad Tire plugs
Satire satire
That's not how fat tire where did I tell you that dick jokes are you can be
No clue
But let's try and imagine how they could be sexually
What could that be satirize okay
Him saying that he has a big dick
What would the what's that sound people who have like
Really bad talks
Sick mask
That would be the only way to consider that satires if what he's doing is lampooning
Accepting the trappings of a fool who would
Feel like you need
To tell people how big is
His dick is
Conceivably could see that being interpreted as satire but that's not what Alex
I can't let
People think I have a small dick making a small dick
Joke
Which is
Fun I guess get there talking about shooting your own feet off or whatever big feet big dick
A joke that has a small dick right and then
Handle that
What if somebody thought he had a small victory what if somebody didn't understand it was a joke
That's not satire and it's not even good comedy
Dunedin
So
Brutal Alex's there
Rodger is there
I got a third partner in this interview
And that is Mark Mendoza
All the time is there and Alex
The payroll
A couple times
He's like Mark am I not the most innocent person in the world
When do you just stop and look around at who you surround yourself with goat
Oh this was all a mistake
Damn yeah
Just sitting in that room looking at Rodger Stone and Mark Randazzo thinking
I'm on the side of good Heroes really
So Mark has some interesting ideas
And then when I started studying the car
Karthi is unwell
ISM School
Back at UMass
I remember looking at that and thinking why you know
Why weren't more people courageous enough to stand up
Shop and Save
I hate communism
Approbation of civil liberties more
Why
It's a shame I wasn't alive back
Wished
But I would have the ability
Be in a fight like that
Because here I am
Yeah right now
I think that this is the closest thing to an impact
It improves upon if you if you can use that word
Improved upon how McCarthy did
We have the same
Exact
Thing going on
Terrible news the McCarthy era everyone Mark Randazzo is talking to Woodstown Chalisa poor
McCarthy India caste mark would too but it depends on which side was
Paying more right
As for the question of why did more people stand up to McCarthy like a lot of people
Did
Now the exact thing that he's trying to present his like why did more people say I hate communism but this is bad
Or whatever it's because everybody who was super anti-communist
Didn't give a s*** against communism
And everyone who stood up to the McCarthy house American on American Activities Committee
People that announce
Around back then all those people who got blackballed in Hollywood
For that
They're the same ones who he says created all that this is such a stupid for them to try to walk
Like I know they want to portray what's happening them as a Witch Hunt and all that but they just got to give up on the McCarthyism example cuz it
Work
Also this what's happening right now is nothing like
McCarthyism because
Batman vest
Navigation into a
Specific event
If McCarthy was just subpoenaing a bunch of people who had physical or material connections to an event where communist
That stormed the US Capitol
This whole thing wouldn't
Be looked at so poorly by history
Except that now, his mistake was assuming that everyone he didn't like
Was a commie
Other than just subpoenaed whomever was that he felt like you didn't like it
It's fun how like opposition
To his
Is committee actually made you a communist
Yeah it is weird how if you were against him then he thought
It sounds so familiar
Democrats watch their own news feed their own
And all that got regurgitated
Back to them with water joke
Campaign was what a joke people like you were what a joke all it was and they didn't
They just weren't prepared for it they were as shocked as anybody was
The next morning when they woke up and they saw
And I think they looked at that and they swore they never be caught like that again
At what a real American would do at that point is safe
How did we lose in the market
Play some ideas
Are we retool our arguments
How do we get
To connect with the American people these people
Patriotic
Believe in America who believe in the Constitution
But instead
They looked
Do the other direction and they decided
That they were going to try to win the marketplace of ideas
By shutting down the
Clothing store in that Mark
Authoritarian model
Just come out
Shut down opposing media
And you noticed
First they started with people that it was easy to start with
Withdraw they tested the waters with Milo and then they
Kept moving along and they kept hitting other people and has one by one
Rodger Stone I got banned
One by one
I want to be like
Hero of this thing
Mark's talking about the really fun story but it actually kind of fails to take into account
The first is that when Trump won
There's a two-pronged approach the people felt they need
The take
Warren was winning the Battle of ideas whatever the f*** that means but also there was a need
To take action
To try to help protect people who are
Instantly in pretty serious real Danger
This included immigrants refugees members of the lgbtq community women
Hoops with face the real Prospect of having rights taken away from them by the
Stated goals
Trumps politics
No
Mark and folks like Alex don't really understand this dynamic because they constantly yell about Heather being pressed and rights taken away but the
We also know that they're lying
Which I suspect lead them to believe that everyone else is too
The second thing that needs to be pointed out here is it what's going on and what has happened isn't an attempt
Shut down the opposing side in a Marketplace of ideas
Like through censorship or whatever
People are facing the consequences of their actions
It turns out a lot of the folks who decided
The Grist on the Trump train
Did some stuff that had consequences
Milo wasn't kicked off Twitter cuz of his ideas
It was because he was leading targeted harassment activity
Alex isn't being punished for his ideas he's facing the music for stuff he got away with for far too long
Because people didn't want to deal with the hassle of holding him accountable
And also let's not forget Milo got kicked off Twitter
For the f***
Cool promise being put forth by Mark is absolutely flawed
Something to think about in situation
Like this is how people like Alex legitimately are trying to shut down
An opposing idea
In the marketplace of ideas
What does opposition to critical race theory if it's not an attempt to ban ideas you don't like
Get the f*** out of here
Anyway
F*** background I love this whole thing is dumb
Making
He's making comment to that
You're more reasonable than Alex
But in actuality or based on completely stupid
False premise
And I would our
That's people were correct when they said
The Trump campaign
And those people were
You're stupid they were right
And
I would say that the Four Seasons
Is all the evidence you need
All the other day
So Rogers got some more ideas actually kind of agree with part of
We have become
We're being attacked cuz it's just makes the left
Drool
The reason my wife was attacked
Outside our home
Abaya
Play some left
The reason that there's so much hatred of me literally
AAA
Aaja Sanam
Owen Shroyer
Is because we are cutting
True
To tell
People the truth
I don't I don't agree with that part but I do kind of agree with Rodger that Alex and his wives are kind of clickbait
You know but at the same time I also believe that they're getting the jester
Desserts with their act
They aren't just being subpoenaed for the sake of
Creative clickbait
Is that ideas
Yeah yeah I kind of I kind of get what he saying I think that
A lot of times maybe headlines about vembar
Not representative of the full story and a lot of times people can
Maybe get false perceptions
Slightly inaccurate perception
Depends on social media but
That's true of
A lot of people
It's always it's always fun to exaggerate things
I also think that they only make money by being click-baiting so I think they're kind of
Real Spider-Man
For sure
But I agree
Statement that his life is clickbait
I mean
It's sad
You can't hear Alexei all they're going to cut this out and play this all over the news that big dick without without being like
You really were
So Alex Rambles here a little bit
And it would probably surprise you to learn that
A lot of the interview with Rodger
Is less about like a statement and more about like
We need money
Nice guy
I want his money
Meaning powerful rich people
Tyranny
Rockstars
Music
About
Is one back for a pension after being fired under Trump
My legal bills paid
Democratic Party
You want us to keep fighting
If you want us to Stand-Up it mean we are the champions of Freedom out of there like some arrogant son of a b**** going
Thank you art
Some kind of guy yelling of the Big Daddy
Right but he also constantly talks about how like I'm
Standard error of God
I think that's a little bit big daddy asked
I think that
It's fun
For him to claim that the Democratic party is doing these lawsuits against him
Because then at that allows him to yell about them
I wish you would look really
Kind of gross
If you had to deal with the reality that it's the victims families
That are suing him
Cuz it looks like it's more of an a******
These lawsuits
S*** people who are actually
Why you've actually getting Subaru
It might
Lead to
Yeah
Linklater is cool I guess
Ted Nugent
Not
Definitely not
No guessing
Mrs.
Star-Lord you know we used to like Chris but now he's gone
Ondiem sucks now
Who else sucks
Mark Randazzo Rodger Rodger sex
Just this b*******
I'm only here
By the grace of God
Because I reaffirm my commitment to Jesus Christ
I'm only here because I confess that I was a sinner and I got right with Christ
Because they were going.
And Jaime
After gagging me
In Soviet
Style
Trial
God is good
Protection of this nation
We do know how this comes out
Weary
The Bible
That's why I know that good
Triamcinolone end
We just don't know how it happened
You want to make God laugh
Tell him you have a plan
Oh okay
Noted schemer and plan maker Russia
Subway
I mean it could not be more
The Playbook
Being a
National
Global ratfucker
For your entire life
Get a presidential pardon
And then fight.
That's good playbook
Bright but also
Finding God is part of you getting apart into thanks for the perfect Redemption Arc
The conman 101 I also really enjoy how Rodger cost in the middle of saying the good guys win
And if you read the Bible
Cuz it almost was like his body wouldn't allow him
Bevis blow Hardy
Part of me thinks he had to stop and think like wait
Do the good guys win at the end
The Bible never ride a bush
Catholic Bible
Now they're murdered by the next
So Alex has some
Spend that he needs to put on Mike Flynn's comments
About how we need A-1 government 313
That was interpreted those comments a little differently and I would say
Incorrectly not not accurate based on the words that were said
Guana State religion
Say that
No General Flynn is one of the greatest men of this century is a man of Destiny
He's a man of the Constitution
Eden Eden
Say that
No matter what religion you are do you need to have God
Nope said that is
It's fun though
Way better than what he
He said yeah cuz if you have to take him based on what he said you have to
Really ask yourself if he's the man of the Constitution then you might even have to say that man is fundamentally trying to destroy the
Institution
January 6th
Is that even that big of a deal at all
But hey
Here's the man
Wow Court not in condition of him going and testify me they would be
Hasn't he has Adam and just more generally
Obama to come to this committee because it's a kangaroo
Lied about being the past and the people connected to the Russia gate hub
But it was a real Congressional committee
I want to know all that
Clearly they were trying to set us up
Mission of the Secret Service
What about who wanted me to be at the front
Stupid now
New January 6th investigation
I totally agree with that
I would love an investigation as long as it frames me as the main victim
I wanted true investigation of very real and not the definition of a true investigation
I was set up by the Secret Service obviously if there was an honest
Investigation
I think that if Alex word
To go and appear before the house
Committee
Heat would be more than welcome to bring up some of these
Conspiracy theories that he has and they would be
Dealt with within 5 minutes and then
It would get to the questions that he can't answer without incriminating himself
I want I want
What's one of those
God I want a Committee hearing that we get to see because you always
Seems like you anytime you see those committee hearings you see
Whoever the political side is that against it
Is asking questions and the other side is like
You're a great person and I love
But your hair you smell nice favor cookie just tell us all
Why why is everyone against you because you're right all the time correct anyways next question
On a scale of big two huge where to take ass I want to see all of those right-wing idiot
It's have to be like Alex you're a hero I think there's only two Republicans on the committee
It's not going to say anything nice
That is true it's not like he's got Jim Jordan and on there.
That would help him out
I would have been fun
I think the Republicans that are on that committee would disown out
So Rogers one last little thing to say about about his
Subpoena before
We get out of here
This is the ABC News tecnico
Guilt by association
Here's a picture of Rodger stone with one of The Proud boys out
Yeah
So what does that prove that the bank
No that's your for McCarthy
This isn't
Accurate
Association is one thing
Rodger was using the proud boys
As
No keepers
Is a security
Is that something that's very well-established he's talked about that in the past
And
Then out they were
People who got indicted
First
I mean I would say Not Guilty By Association
Strong connection
He's he's correct
A picture of him with a proud boy leader doesn't prove any
The fact that he has said multiple times that he loves the proud boys
I has them work for him
PS4s for
And I love everything that they do
That prove
Pictures that say with the Oath Keepers
Is doesn't mean
Rogers
Presumably been on Infowars when Stewart Roads was around or whatever
There is a connection
Between I'm sure that doesn't matter
You never get two charged
By the committee for that
But if you're employing Oak
Keepers Azure security and they also
They broke into the capitol
Stand maybe there's some questions that should be asked
Maybe they're not about
You
Specifically
Maybe they're about a what's going on with this guy
Now the problem is if you're right
Stone answering any question honestly the only lead to
So after this interview with the reptiles and Rodger
Alex Goes to talking to another guy
Guy by the name of Jake Ducey who appears to have
A whole bunch with the recent Wars stuff
In the interest
Keeping things somewhat separated I'm going to hold off on covering this interview
Because ideally by the time we need to record Mondays episode
We will have somebody
Actual reset Wars content available
Costas interview with a guy who I'm going to call The Duce
No spelled differently
It just seems like anybody is due to sound
Spoiler alert
Lucy is a mess
Our next episode will cover whatever is available out the recent Wars
Yeah and we will do this as if it is the Gate of gay
It's at great as this is important Alex's most important
Today I mean that there's only one with the great reset Wars
To take it over
So I think is it at the end of the day what he's doing with reset Wars is a pathetic
Attempt to create a new business entity
The six-hour course
This is going to be
So much fun for me
I've been needing something like this cuz all of it like
A lot of the older documentaries
He has our
Useless
Like I don't want to force you to watch
2 hours of
Alex sitting at a desk saying thing
I already saw him bitching about a road for an hour
That's true
Which we got to hear a little bit of today
AAA
They look forward to some of that being released and being able to
To get into it
I love a good tease
CIA
Did the deuce will not disappoint disappoint
A-Z you got that
Jordan
Dot-com us on Twitter
We're also at
This response to the January 6th subpoena with disappointment
Really get
Yeah Leo
Dzx Clark
And now here comes
The sex robot
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color