Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Acknowledge
Jordan
Catsup
Ice cream sandwiches
My life
Yes
I have the especially the ones that are like
Oh those are the devil you take a big bite of one of those
And you're like
This is too much for me and then you go right back and forth
Looking into this ice cream sandwich and I'm glad you had a nice time on the day after Thanksgiving
Black Friday shopping
Oh good God no
Bright the day after and
Permian like
This was the first family Thanksgiving cuz you're blind repair
Parents have a lot of like
Questions about the episode we put out on Friday
Is capital MMA it all went South
Better route anytime
Just my thoughts
Are you saying
The first one
Thanksgiving was my aunt's holiday like every year for Mayan
Entire life
I was at her table at 1
And then this is the first Thanksgiving since she had died
And my mom
Clearly felt
So she put everything she could into the
But you and Brad together
This is got to be if this sucks then we're all going to be like. Tony and then is going to be
Absence will be felt Nicole there
Fantastic
Great job great job that's only podcast you should listen to
Too many times like that story goes the other way is like someone trying to
Diagram step up and then
Absolutely
Falls Park
She added this sweep
Potato thing with walnuts on top of it and you could
Field
Nervous the palpable likes
Should I have added anyting energy to it was amazing
Isn't it weird that people have sweet potatoes with marshmallows on top
Anyway roast last episode we talked about November 23rd
And
Yeah there was
A bit of the recent Wars
Yeah
I'm not too proud
To admit that I think I might have been wrong about
I think I might have made some Hasty assumption okay
And we're going to talk about
A bunch of that
Today as we will work
To do is we're going to
Beginner exploration of reset Wars
Jewel videos I don't think are out yet
His actual like 11 hour course
Whatever the f***
On the 23rd in the third and fourth hour of the show Alex interview Jake
Dulce
Who is his partner in recent Wars
The two of them worked
On this together
And
So what we're going to do is we're going to talk about this interview
Prelude to whenever
The recent Wars comes out
Yes
Cooking instead of the oven
This will be an ongoing series as we get more
This is reset Wars Episode 1 A New Hope
The Phantom Menace
From what I've heard this will be the fan
Yeah title
So first Andre from the Pod thank you so much you're now about was he walk
I'm a policy wonk
Communist Revolution in the sheets thank you so much as you want
Thank you very much
I like that because the play on Gary Allen's book coming is Revolution
Also it does
Leave me wondering what
Are you in the
In the streets if you're coming this representative
Anarcho-capitalist industry
I guess that would be the saying woodworking
Also we got a technocrat in the mix of Seymour insight
Democrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Seymour insight
In the 23rd
November 20-21 blackjack
Who is Ren the third hour
Alex's bringing on Jake Ducey
To talk about the wonders of reset Wars
Here is his introduction
Broadcast
This transmission
Human expression of freedom
Was not supposed to be on air right now
We're supposed to already be off every supposed to roll over
Everybody else the globalist enslaved and dumb down and kill
Best selling author and also to so many other
Workshop
But
Really help
Iresearch
With the launch of the next level of the infowar which is recent Wars
Potica
And the rest of it
Here's the first thing that you need to know about Jake Ducey and it doesn't get Alex's
Conspicuously leaving out of his his
Okay alright
Professional hip okay okay basically a new-age type
Power of attraction
Preaching self-help
Con artist kind of guy
He's blogging website
Just full of the most
Flagrant clickbait titles for articles which circle around ideas related to the
The secret and the law of
Retraction
Unfamiliar with this whole self-help Graves were about a decade ago this secret is basically about how you can manifest
Anything you want
A life
And the reason you have bad things
When your life is because your subconscious
Attracting those things
To you with negative thinking
The basic idea is to force yourself to have positive thoughts about the
Things like money your job or people you're magically the universe will bring those things that you want to you
Bars of gold your dream job in the partner of your dreams could all be yours
It'll be super easy if you'd have got out of your own way
You know what's crazy
Is that everybody I knew who followed that secret work years ago works perfectly edit billionaire
Like Bitcoin like I wish I had gotten in on the secret that
I'm too late
Legitimately some of the titles of the post
The artist blog
In these videos
Creepy
Kind of sad
Quote make them miss you make someone Peg to be with you
How to attract money effectively it manifested quickly
Save this for
Instant Financial breakthrough
Sarah lot of videos about how to magically make money fly towards
Are you in a bunch about how you can make people want to have sex with you which isn't surprising since those are two really visceral targets
Continental
Exploiting people
Yeah Bertie and loneliness
Do as a thing
Pretty cool
A certain type of people
Scrolling through his YouTube channel I got a very quick
Can clear impression
This guy is repetitive as hell and he loves clickbait
It's just constant thumbnails of him holding up hundred dollar bills of titles like quote
Save this to receive unexpected money in one day or less
Or quote I manifested $100,000 per month
He also has some videos
Kitchen telepathy
It's all just clickbait garbage
Which is exactly what online marketing experts luud
I need to do if you want to increase traffic artificially when you don't have good
Man bring back the guy wearing the green suit with money on it saying that you can get free money from the government if you
Buy this book I want that guy back I am saying this without having looked into it too much
It's my understanding that that guy actually did have ways you could get money from another
Grant funny like that
It's not
Not manifested
Paperwork
It's like an intensely bad vibe off Jake tousey even more so than your run-of-the-mill Hitman
To scamper
Also as a podcast on iHeart
Call Jake ducey's second Vine podcast
I believe in second mine thing is about your subconscious mind how it's the ones creating all the energy fields and all that
Attract and repel stoplight
And attractive
Most of the episodes are 10 minutes long and about how to attract money
The most recent episode appears to be titled quote
Easily manifest more money fast
With the law of attraction
How about a week before that he had an episode titled quote
3 most
Powerful Secrets to attract more money fast
About a week for that a million dollars
At the end of February to do this hypnosis for money listen everyday to become a millionaire in 2012
And the last
And this last one is part of what really troubles me about
He seems really anxious to hip
Notize people
He's jumping at the bit
Next
Seems like he's really eager to hypnotize people
On his website is bio Reed's quote
When I began to uncover how the unconscious mind works I went from a nineteen-year-old with a self-published book to a best-selling author
Catherine just a few years
I want to give you this
Success hypnosis
The changed it all
Free just click below
The supervillains plan you realize that 22 like innocuously attract enough people to hypnotize
Is all of them at the same time in order to get them to do your bidding there are overlaps
What is homepage there's a link to something he sells called the second mind neuro programmer
Great which is apparently meditation and visualization exercises they claim to be able
Rewire your brain to attract abundance
But I'm all for meditation and I even
I'm fine with some fairly nuages
You stuff but when you take a person like this and also combine all that with
He's coming out of nowhere to
To collaborate with Alex Jones at exactly the point where Alex is completely desperate in his life is falling apart
You have what I would consider a gigantic red flag
This could be a short-lived
Collaboration but I'm really really honestly worried about
Alex's light reset Warriors apparently was something that you get a big hand in an oz promoting it is the most
Portent work he's ever done
What makes it not feel like
A small blip
On the radar
And then you added to this
On Jake's homepage
Right at the top
He offers to help you rewire your mom
Quote
How would you like to hit the reset button
And rewire your body
Okay
Primary selling Ryan is
How'd you like to hit the reset button operating theory he is a super villain
I have a number of theories
I don't think supervillain is one of them
Regular Village
Occam's razor tells me that Alex
Credibly desperate for money
Jake is a rich
Online marketing
Scam guy
And
He is now bought access to Alex
That seems to be with the simplest explanation of all this is that's really terrified
Because Alex has left
These people very vulnerable
To someone who has
A gift of manipulation hypnosis
Techniques
But he really wants to use on people
Yeah yeah you know that the same time so this is the time. Of
The conman
Success to life
Where he does get
You know like
He's at his lowest point
Alex yeah Alex's it is entirely possible for Alec
Looks to be getting con right now like on a real level
I thought about that as I was listening
He hypnotized Alex
And I know
That's the case
It seems a little bit frustrated by him okay
I I don't I don't know if there's like a whole lot of we really like each other
You'll notice
Jay Quillen
Do not stop plugging reset Wars
Alex does a lot of bugs
Is embarrass
Okay constantly is telling people go to reset Wars sign up for it with a couple of hate
Everything
Every road leads back
After that plug
Even Alex
This is like this is a little much
Oh my God we've reached the Event Horizon of a black hole
Thirsty
Inside radiation Arctic radiation
I think
I think that there is there is something troubling about this Association
I also think
It's somebody ideas that are going to be Express
Over the course
This episode
AR
Really troubling things
Combined with Alex's work
Right maybe some of them are metaphorically things that
Yeah
Maybe could have some
Self-empowering application
Sure when combined
With the
Infowar
Right right right
It's a little danger
Yeah yeah it is a little bit like combining this secret and
Terrorism
Give you the secret of terrorism which is a good thing that you want to read
So Alex takes
Forever introduced
I want you to know what's going on
Farms of slaves
I can fly over anymore
You not being empowered makes me feel like crap
I want to see you fly like a birdie
I have children in this world
They're going to live with your children I have ancestors that live with your ancestry
I'm connected to you
The opposite I'm not all about me I'm all about
I got power over people
Unlimited
Consciousness
Knows we have that far
Jersey's here
Who's talk about good
Fire
Got to understand the bad
I'd like very clear that my ancestors
Did not
Hang out with Alex
Example
The Confederacy
And buying where matter
I was just I was just
Just wrote down Confederate royalty and historically if you are that connected to your ancestors you are very
Hidden Farms with slaves
It's up there
Today on this interview that Alex is doing
They're going
Look at the bad
Accept the good
You got to look at
Get the bag
Clear-eyed evaluation
We're going to look at the bad
6 + H transmission that's coming out
Early December
I wanted to just
Talk about this
Most people don't sit around and read 800 Pages Declassified MKUltra files
You just recently last few days went back over
When you Siri
Perdition Church never heard this
CIA documents
You understand this is the opposite
This is how they did it
There is a there is an
There is one little evil Shadow today
Good don't know about that
What year was posing how they operate what's going on
Cool so I'm excited at this point cuz I thought like
We're going to talk a whole bunch about MKUltra seems like it
I've read a lot of
Those documents
And historians like them or at least
In terms of being able to shed light on
Atrocious things that our government is done
I think that the there's a difference
Between a clear-eyed sober view of
The historical monstrosity of them K Ultra program
What conspiracy theories
Believe it to be right I think
There is a
And I was really excited to discuss some of that differ
Prince but unfortunately I over prepared for that
Really
Matter
We're going to have
Drugging people without their knowledge
Very much so
Drugging people without their knowledge in eating babies
Nonexistent
Damn drugging people with their knowledge
Fine
We wouldn't have had sometimes A Great Notion without it
So Alex brings up Jake
Finally introduces him
Eddie Gibbs
One of his credits is that he's from reset War
So that
5 minutes for you to break and come back into the main meat of this
Mission what's going on the actual
Hershey from reset wards.com
What I say is
Part of this massive MKUltra experiment that is society in
Honored actually go through six times and watch out his brand new courses coming out
Out here real soon
If you are a fan of Alex.
This is the next level because the way that the great reset
Officially is accomplished
Into subconscious patterns
Convincing us for just these little bodies
Using mind-control weapons
11 step process exactly how to break
Open up another browser
Go to reset wards.com
Right now as the first of his
2000 Colfax
Call Saxon they're always open the browser AOL
He's taking online mark
Cooking classes
So yeah this is
Is good
Not happy I feel like we're off to a bad start we are we say
Everyday mine
Control weapon
Mind control weapons
We haven't even some Boutique
Everyday mind control weapon
That's what I want
I thought that maybe he was being a little fanciful and metaphorical by saying that like
Society is an MKUltra experiment
No he means I quite literally
No I'm taking him literal for everything
You said is I decided that
Before I sat down in this chair yep
So he had me this drip
Really quickly into
What sounds like
Call Shay
New just learning all the news isn't going to have we're going to be able to change it
We're going to be able to change it as movie
Learn how the mind control work
We are we clear
Real spiritual powers
Cam
Alright that's what they don't want us to know
So there's the DD patterning yourself you got to reprogram yourself
Selling on his website
For been awhile right least advertise
Infowars
Yeah you got to reset
You got to settle things down
Boy that's a familiar tone
You hear quite a bit
Shady group you just need to come in here put your hands on this machine and tell
Tell me all of the things that you've never told anyone else before and I you can trust me you need to distract yourself
Completely destroy whatever using my program
Destroying yourself maybe I'm the only person left
I will be there to help put you back together and I promise I'm not going to do things that are
Weird
Recent Wars
Tom
Alright that's what they don't want us to know
Born with the goddamn as her soul
Realize the gorilla still there they erased the real us template
Interfacing with the universe British show the CIA document
Okay this is getting really
Scary at this point like
Overlap here with stuff that Alex
Skip into from time to time on his show but the vibe is going in a
A very different
A very unnerving directions even immediately in this interview
Alex's Methodist self-help conman Hypno
11 step program to save yourself from the globalist
Would you worked on with the hypnotist
And is the most important work
Do you ever done
This doesn't sit right with me and the prospect of Alex's terrorist edging
Constant violent preoccupation being
The Bible
Vague aspirational pseudo spirituality that
It's dancing around the idea
But you're not yourself
Is absolutely
Terrifying
I kept trying to suspend judgment as I listened to this but it's really really a
You know a lot of people think that
Combining religion with terrorism
Is bad idea because you know you get that feeling of like I will be rewarded for these acts of horrific
Now that
That's terrifying
What if
You are already dead in your own mind
Have no fear whatsoever and we're willing to blindly follow with anyone
That's not a problem it's a bad combination people should be worried
This development is bad
So Jake wants to explain to everybody how we live
No I wish the Becca is a good neighbor
Exist on three planes
We just on the physical and mental emotional and spiritual
Emotional control grade is all the craziness happening to Anchor lock us into or lower
Consciousness
Are lower emotions
And that's the simulation right is Zuckerberg scraping the metaverse
Already in the simulation
Control system works
And that's what did me about your work
We live in a simulation all of reality is controlled by subconscious
We already know this and I thought to myself or what happens
If I literally reprogram my entire mine
If I literally program everything I erase all the viruses
You taught you liking the mine to an operating system
The viruses
Fake identity
This is not good
Very very bad stuff
This goddamn show supposed to be with the Communists being evil in the UN secretly being run by commies were also evil
And now we're getting into explicit talk about living in the simulation and how we have a tripartite self
Existing in three different dimensions and how the answers to
Brainwash yourself and then rebuild
Helpful guidance of Alex's dumbass of the Shady hypnotize
This is scary
Obviously this could result in nothing
But also this could end very poorly for some people
And the worst part is
I just I just
Here in my head the voice of somebody watching
These and just gone like
Man it's a good thing I don't believe in that Prosperity Gospel
. cuz this is real
Glitterbug churches
Now this is the rosh it doesn't have the
Document
Before the interview Alex was
Constantly Bang
The drum of working to get in
Into these documents
That's me and Jake
We're going to get into the weed
That's one of the reasons why I was so excited
Is that like I want to know
What documents you're talkin about
I want to read them
I want to get a sense of okay so you guys made
6 hour or 11 hour excuses 11 hours on boil 11
11 step program
Hours or plus gas Parts I think it's complicated
Job but they created this entire course
A really good handle on the dispatch
You think that's all I got pumped
To hear that and
I don't know if you can be surprised about this
It's going to be a while
Because we got up we got to
About nothing for a bit
And that's why I'm so excited
Who We Are
Call sting weed and follow
Real before we sell we got program
And think about what's interesting.
Beacon
Of the world use the same word in MKUltra documents
Be conformed by the pattern of the world WhatsApp
It's the entire mind control system
Use predictive programming an unconscious hypnosis
You control it
I guess now Alex is trying to insinuate that the idea of being born again actually refers to the process of undergoing the rediscovery
Revere realself
Was replaced by the facsimile of you
That the globalist
Created
And Alex
Gazelle can help you with that
I'm a religious person but that seems
Deeply blasphemous
Search
Is the public library I'm going to have to ask you to lie
This is troublesome
I feel like that relies Less on the sacrifice of
Jesus as of the Bible discusses anymore about
Sacrifice
We all know that it didn't really happen
Oh boy
So answer the Bible verse that Jake
Is talking about the word pattern is used in The New International Version of the Bible
Do not conform
To the pattern of this world but be
Transformed by the renewing of your mind
And then you'll be able to test and approve what God's will is
His good pleasing and perfect
Goodwill
That's aroma
12 to but the wording is different in other translation
For instance
In the King James version
And be not conformed to this world
But be ye transformed by the renewing of your mind
That ye may prove what is
What
Is that good and acceptable and perfect will of God
The word pattern is in
Very very few translations of Romans
The book Romans was originally written in koine Greek
And if you go back to the original Source text there's no reason to add the word pattern to that sound
Text uses the verb to be conformed
Then the word
To end the word Ionia
Which translates to a
The age
This word as well as the next word Toto
Meetings this are both in the
The genitive case
Which means that they're meant to be taken together
The genitive case in Greek is used to generally in
Possession
And in this case
It's just a general sense of
The things of the ape
Taking purely from the text
Sentences essentially saying don't get caught up in the extraneous things around you the change gear.
This is probably all sounding a little bit in the weeds but the reason I needed to make this clear
That's because the reason that Jake is making
Big deal about it
Is because the word deep
Patterning is used
In some of the LSD and behavioral experiments
Nmkl
We'll talk more about that later but
What is critical to understand
Need to connect the word d patterning existing in relation
MK Ultra
And the word pattern in this Bible verse
Lesbian meaning for
When in reality
Weird pattern isn't in the original tax
And the only translations that include that word
Republican 1978 2011 + 29
There's no meaning to this connection
It's just an attempt to make it a
Fear the evil globalist
Who did MKUltra
Intentionally trying to undo what God wanted of
This is like
Two steps above qanon
Honestly maybe not
Maybe one I am starting to think and I'm
Going to go out on a limb here
I'm starting to think that in the beginning
Heard was
Not with us
Because it doesn't seem like he has a clear handle on it anymore
Well the word got away from
Beginning was the word
Workout away from there was wordplay
Such a mess
So Alex has got some complaining
To do and I think
I think
Stupid
The secret
Playing games
Listen for God you don't get it
Why your bosses are so scared because you're not like you some brainwash menu they're aware of this and using this against
Goodness
Two people
Unwilling to breathe
I'm willing to bring Alex
Nail the landing on that site out of breath
So what's going on here is that Alex
Creating a straw man
Protected insulators religious
Extremism
For being questioned
Criticized by people
I make it appear that any criticism of Alex's religious extremism is actually an attack on all of
Christianity
I don't think
Most people have any problem with the idea of someone saying that they're connected to their
Our conception of God or
Even saying favorite
Personal relationship with that deity
These are pretty well accepted and understood expressions of spirituality these days
Alex is claiming that he's being criticized
That's not true
It's not what Alex
Criticize
How much does it the literal devil has been trying to recruit him since he was a child because the devil knew Alex
Two critical two gods
Plans
Says that God gives and prophetic visions and allows him to see the future
How much does the god uses various people
The carry out his Vengeance on the wicked witch would be kind of hard to prove so
I guess you just kind of got to take people at their word but I say God told him to
The do something really horrible
Yeah I always believed the people on the left are literally knowing
Movie or unknowingly working
Sing for the literal devil
I don't believe that things like gender norms
Sexuality or things that are mandated by God
Not conformed
To his beliefs on the subject
Texas in
Alex's version of religion deserves criticism in rebuke because it's exactly the kind of thing that makes it easy for people to hate religion
I think religious people are assholes
Also Alex uses religion as a marketing
2 laswi exhaustively documented over the course of
The show
He's essentially a cartoon character of a bigoted religious con man
These are the things
This big-time like
Like that's just probably criticizing Alex for
Not claiming that he's connect
Good to God
Yeah
It's not a big time left
Somebody on Twitter person on Twitter
So Jake
Is pretty big into this idea that you're not your body
Sure you're not your physical
Self
And I assume he is
Is totally fine with trans people or body modifications
Anything longer
I will say that that subject doesn't come up
But the fact that he seems to
Simpatico with Alex
You probably
Do the reasons cousin
He doesn't want people to know
History the control system is always operated
Books of the Bible
A tyranny always controls people is cutting them off from their higher spiritual faculties convince them
Even though your body is just a rental car that house is Rustoleum here in Austin right now use a rental car
It's not my car I'm just using it
Body is just a rental car
For many years and I know you are too
Go to reset worship
You're not going to stop
Wow
So I got to say for someone who's so concerned with these lost in
Unforgotten
Forbidden books
So the Bible like Jake pretend
Centipede
He's quoting of that last verse reveals that he definitely read some
Some pretty reason
Translation
I'm sure he has a great grasp on the
The Book of Enoch
The Gospel of Thomas
Though and I'm pretty happy for him
Honestly
The Vatican secret archives
You know like he is referencing for the apostolic archives
Probably just so well secured and guarded because they contain information about
The Catholic Church
Internal working
As well as Financial details
They're plenty of Records they have that they would want to
Key private you don't need to create fun stories about magic
Nickel secret book
Of the Bible that they're hiding
Yeah but they
Also also like I had a. Of time in my life where I get deeply into
The books that were
I think I could speak about this
Grand Blanc
If Jake ever got
Specific about what he was talking about I think it's all just vague
Mumbo jumbo ideas about gnosticism probably
Oh yeah I would
Prefer if you got into the Weeds on those little bit like I would like to
To talk about that one
Story word when Jesus
This is a kitty just murders that other kid that one was pretty crowded back though
Dragons in a cave that was pretty cool
The thing is you know he has this like all there's all this stuff that they banned from the Bible
Same thing with Alex talking about the
Because nothing you can do with that
Even if you know a
Baton
About the song
The subject that's going to be
Pacific I don't know what you're talkin
Oh I wasn't talking about
I know you're talking about something but that's not what I was
Exactly
No one's mad about Alex starting reset Wars
I'm probably the only person in the world who pays as much attention as I do.
Message me whenever there's a
And no one has brought up reset work
No one cares
The World At Large doesn't care about reset a good reason to be scared about this develop
Honestly
The idea that you're not your body and that this life is just a rental car for your soul that can be fairly a knock
He was platitude in New Age
Self-help circles
But you can also be an indication of a cult going in a very dangerous Direct
Contorts devaluation
Human life
If you're not your body and you could strike a big win against the globalist by sacrificing your body and some kind of a suicide attack
It might start sound like a more compelling Prospect
Your body
Committing suicide just
Just for the hell of it but all the people that you might potentially kill in the process of whatever you're doing they're not their bodies
Either so what's really the harm in any of it
I want to be clear that I'm not saying that this is the direction that this rhetoric is going but
The combination of these ideas being pushed front
Center being presented as Alex is most import
And the world of angry bulshit that Alex has created in the past 20 years
What is career
He's super concerning
And it needs to be watched carefully
What I'm getting at is
Like this could go
Wheelbarrow
Yeah well I mean if you are not your body no one is their body and no human being really is
Is part of their body
Which means really
You can do whatever it is you want
To the body so long as you don't hurt
The soul
How would you even gauge that
Exactly I
Do whatever you want
Do what thou Wilt as though someone might say oh boy
So Alex told Dulce
When they were working on this stuff is
Stickman
People got me so mad we're going to get some ships
I don't think they have
Going back for 56 months ago Going Back 2 months ago we were working on this film project
Researcher
Hypnotist
Now you see
Really worried about this because
We're explaining what the enemy knows in the you don't see any TV channels
The only other person that
Conceptualizes
Show you in the CIA Zone admission
But they're aware of vision in the Bible
Literally
Quoted by the CIA and how they control people
I'm thrilled to hear that the turd in the punch bowl David Icke is now the only person who's the
Been speaking Truth All Along such b*******
Such nonsense also it's so funny to hear Alex
Let's dance around this dude's credit
It seems very intentional that he's not bringing up this
Very large aspect of cakes
You cannot have a
Insist on your new show
To tell people bad news
It makes me think of
Steve pieczenik
Steve is a psychological operations expert
Alright
Hypnotist is just a personal psychological warfare operation to be
Bring up
MK Ultra
Like I said
I'm really interested in them bringing up
Specifics
And
Just such a dry well
Really pops in
Do MK Ultra
And
Document in the Declassified MK Ultra
Alex film
Is reset Wars course
I was reading back through these documents
Cameron's notes
You and Cameron
With subliminals all these Control Systems going on
Is she sleeping well
She is disoriented as to time only
It is probably in her second stage of the patterning
And I was like
You'll see a lot of people cover MKUltra even the mainstream York Times all these places
What are they say the headlines are
Government overreach
Scary stuff
Why are they doing it
And they're doing it because they realized
The mind is literally a computer operating system we live in a simulation that's controlled your unconscious consciousness
And they figured out how to manipulate and control it
I'm in the same way the only way that we're going to win is 2D pattern ourselves
So first of all I love the idea that Jake is blowing his own mind at the idea that the word deep patterning is likely Translate
Location of Romans 12:2 he mentioned earlier
So sad
Also the news
Discover why these MKUltra
Experiments happened did you know what so do the MKUltra
What's the Jake is pretending to have read
And guess what they happened because of rampant out-of-control anti-communism
These programs MK Ultra and its precursor is Project artichoke and project Bluebird we're all predicated on the belief
Did the Soviet Union that already mastered the
Please take me to mind control
If we stood any chance in the Cold War will you need to defensively figure these things out
What I say this is obvious I mean that it's so clear that I refuse to believe that Jake would have looked into this at all and not
One of the major sources of information about the MKUltra program Disney 1977 joint hearing before the senate committee
Intelligence
And the subcommittee on health and scientific
This is a hearing where the event director of the CIA Admiral Stansfield Turner testified having recently found a bunch of new
MK Ultra related documents
As a result
Request
Money.
I've been destroyed these ones were accidentally sent to the cia's budget and fiscal
GoSection8
It was very thorough employee they were eventually discover
Much of this new information that was Learned was in line with the 1963 report from the
Those done by the Inspector General
There's an added detail and
It sound like
Stop
Anyway in the documentation from this 1977 here and go find
Quote
The late 1940s and early 1950s were marked by concern over the threat posed by the activities of the Soviet Union the people's were
Look up China and other communist Bloc
United States concern over the use of chemical and biological
Agents by these Powers with a key
The belief that hostile powers that use
Chemical and biological
Agents in terrorism brainwashing
And a text
Designed to harass disabled or
Or kill. Kill Allied personnel
Create a considerable pressure for a defensive program to investigate chemical and biological age
So that the intelligence Community could understand the mechanisms
By which these Subs
Census work
And how they affect
Could be defeated
From the earliest point
Dating back to Bluebird the focus on anti-communism with a
Explicit
In the document that was
Discussing the hippity
Test of the agency was contacting
Bluebird
It was also reported as being reliable trustworthy unknown anti-communist
Bluebird officers were unable to find any indications of
Deviousness or pro-soviet inter
The interest was two prong
That they had essentially they wanted to break the Communist spies
And know how to keep
The Soviet Union for being able to crack our spies
Naturally because of the need for intense secrecy of such a project
Shawty a oversight internally
This parole
Considerably and led to questions of whether the scientist
Could quote develop means for the control of activities and Mentos
Tow capacities of individuals willing or not
I got really out of control and they did horrific
Unacceptable a ton rationalize Apple thing
Yeah
It was all of it though it was all entirely motivated by fear the communist
The driving forces in the motivation for the project
Is very clear and the only explanation for Jake not knowing this or saying no one talks my why they did this
If you knows anything about this subject
Either hypnotized himself 24
Forget it or he's a liar
It is amazing
How
Stupid
America was
Time because
If I remember correctly that
Like ability
To control minds was disa
Information released
Specifically by the Soviet Union
And that sent
What's the United States on a
Billion-dollar Witch Hunt
Search for Magic
That's great
Yeah
Surprise
So
Look
We got this
We got this guy Jake
And
He believes that we're all under a Ultra Man
Everywhere
It's
It's happening right now
I used to think I was
I know what's happening in the world
Business and my success in my finances to my happiness
We are under MKUltra attack
Absolutely
Tire system is perpetuated off of one simple phrase I love to say this is
Brainwash yourself
Brainwashing
Brainwash yourself before the world brainwashed
The Cameron believed
On a patient's mind
Can do a childlike state
That would allow him to work
Clean-slate nearby
Program the patient
Too busy being presented as like a real doctor
Pretty excited
Nick Ewen Cameron
Yeah
To get this off like really fast we're not all under MK Ultra
Really makes me think of is Alex's marketing
G4 selling iodine
He tries to convince the audience of their all iodine deficiency
It's causing them to not be as smart as they could
This feels exactly the same
Jake is trying to sell you on the idea that you have a deficiency and he's the person who has what you need to break free of
Google just really shady techniques of of sales that they're using on people
Also the idea of brainwashing yourself so someone else does
Is definitely alarming
Do here because you know what you could do
Just do think
Don't you get it
Kill yourself before the world kills you
Perfect sense
Any negative thing eat your leg before the world eats your legs
Just put it all in there mayonnaise
Perfect sense
That's what you want
People think
Talking about doctor Cameron there
From something but the text didn't match anything that I've come across in
In the files that I dread
It took me awhile but I think I figured out where you got the
This from
Text Danny Rivas almost
A paragraph in an article from CBC News titled brainwash
The Echoes of MKUltra
This article has an interesting first paragraph
The following story is based on material from the CBC podcast brainwash
The six-part series
This is an article discussing
The content of a podcast that was investigating MKUltra
Isn't the First Source that I would choose
Used to go with
Particularly if I was someone who had to wear this
Of the document
Arabic
Entirely convinced of is exactly where Jake is his information
Wrong because just
For this paragraph
There's an image
Which is an image of a page from Cameron's note
Which happens to be the very page of notes
The Jake reference
Earlier about a woman having 16 days of sleep
I wasn't fully convinced that this article it was what Jake was using but then he said that
Driving the patterning cycle
Driving
Which men playing recorded messages to
20 hours
What do they were asleep
Or whether they are extreme examples
Schrier
Completely the pattern
She was mute and had trouble swallowing
Those are literally the details in the next few set
Sentences Mitsubishi article
If I have the article about the death of his
Information on this subject the rest is just pseudo-spiritual mumbo-jumbo that he is
You still get that he spouts all the time on his own platform
It's just integrating his own hypnotism
Scab into
The political world
Live conspiracy that Alex
Boy
If this is a simulation
In what
World doesn't make any sense for you to be able to think your way out of
No cuz Whitney
You think your way into brainwashing
Yourself
Then you're able to see that it's
Simulation
And you can
Create whatever you want
It's the Matrix
That's
Just don't you want to be Neo
I want to do is alright
Maui
I am
I see your has attached
Very frustrated by people saying that you can
Think your way through a simulation that's a problem
Yeah just a part of the simulation if it's a simulation is being stimulated
Haha simulate a simulation
You're inside of it
Right
And the exit would be death
So
Lead you to some negative thoughts
If you if you're in The Matrix
Someone has to break you out of it
Physically
Which probably will be impossible cuz what you are doesn't actually exist outside the simulation
What does it mean for a Sim
Did you take it out of the game
Doesn't mean anything
I made it free gosh it
I just don't
Back when I smoked a lot of weed I used to engage with the idea of the simulation quite a bit read like
Nick Bostrom
Stop blow my mind
Kind of came to a conclusion that it doesn't
Matter
Yeah
If it is a simulation it matters exactly as much as if it is not
Matters
Cuz it's fun to think about
And
And think about the nature of reality and that kind of stuff
It is
Is a good use of time if you
If you can
Your friends would you like to talk about that kind of stuff with it a good time
Ultimately
Hebert's is no different note
On how you would live your life
Yep
You got it
I don't know it's like Calvinism I might I might be wrong
It really matter then does it
Right
My ID is about to dr. Yuan
Cameron J this is coming
10000 children in the US Canada
GPS
Nlsd PCP
Video goggles
Nothing that I'm going to say at any point
In this episode
Please do not take any of it
To be minimizing
What these people do
Yeah I'm not doing
But Alex Isley
Protective Service didn't
Exist until 1980
With the passage of the adoption assistance and child welfare Act
So the timeline doesn't work at all but
Alex just hates the CPS
Because he thinks that they're trying to take
Street family children and give them to same-sex couples
Throwing the CPS in with salt
Who's going to follow up on that
Humor
Also I'm going to need Alex to substantiate the claim that you and Cameron kidnapped tens of
Dozens of children
Because as much of a monster as he is and was I don't think this matches up with
Any of the records I can find
I'm not going to spend my time for finding Cameron but I'm going to say that Alex does a disservice to reality and opposition to people like Cameron
By creating cartoon super villain
It's really dumb
Yeah
It takes a garden-variety
Banal evil that we need to
Combat and be aware of on a
Night
In the constant basis
And turns it into magical fairies that you don't really need to worry about cuz it's all the way over there it's over there
There in the distance
Tens of thousands of children being kidnapped for the
This program would
Be
Front and center explain to me
How you could get away with
Certified program for
However many years
While stealing tens of
Children
Somebody's going to notice
Yeah itsy itsy
Things that they did is they would do tests on
People who are like
Psychiatric patient
And
Folks who people who couldn't say no
Who weren't in the ability to have they're not exclusively.
Would be great
Entirely counter to
Prove that I'm willing
Here are the photos of oil down
Songs of like this
This is the level of their
Inhaled was only a small
Of this
40 50 60
70 years ago I imagine what they're doing now
So that
Is there argue
There it is without proving anything someone like Alex can just save it known information on a subject is a cover-up
Imagine what they're up to
Do now
Both of these are just suggestions without meaning
Anything could be a cover-up if you say it is and then the conversation
No it's not
Okay great
What now
Also be imagine what they're doing now is way weaker of a gay
That's just trying to get the listener to imagine
The scariest and most awful thing they can and they
Men giving them permission to think that it's
Possible or maybe even
Probable
That that's going on now
These are both intentional strategies where people pretend to have demonstrated a point when they really haven't said anything at all
Getting disappointed
Yeah because I wanted
But that's such an
That's such a good
Pick 4
For people who aren't
Hundred percent
Engage critically at that bone
Does it mediately you go
Well I mean we've got an iPhone now and they had a rotary phone
So if they were that evil back then I mean obviously they've
Accelerated or escalated their problems
And that's makes a certain sense
Thanks to you but if you're not thinking
Critically all this you know
It just stays
Yeah
Understandably is pump
About reset Wars
Because he's not teeth people that they're not their bodies
Excited about
Reset Wars am I safe
Everybody literally go right now open a browser
Go to reset wars.com because
History the way tyranny always wind is to stop us from Spa
Spiritual Awakening
As long as they trap us in the third
Third dimension
Make us live in an animalistic State of Consciousness believe
Physical bodies attached to this little tiny
Spectrum of visible light
What is soon as people start
Pharmaceutical corruption
Financial corruption
Really are
In the hole games over
Ford Racing cry standing
He believes that a child and natural normal
Trajectory is ending up
With the same price
Space religion
Just believes that he does
People who want to provide important medical treatment to children like vaccines are doing so to make sure that this normal trajectory
Goes off course
It's one thing to say that humans generally tend to grab a toilet tape towards feeling a connection to the
The Divine and they crave to be part
Something larger than themselves
Which is often found through religion in Connect
But that's not what Alex is saying
This is him basically saying that every person who's not a Christian innocence
Alex understands
He's someone who's natural normal trajectory was knocked off course
Likely by an agent of Satan
This is f***** up
Yeah that's
That's
Great that's real great
The dodo level of thinking
King required to get there
Hi
Precludes tolerance top scientist
I have a reach those
Conclusion
Yeah
That's f***** up
So
Alex reveals how little he actually knows about the organization of MKUltra
Earlier
Ahead of them tail trip
Declassified
Who is this
Jolyon West who is Tim mcveigh's
Psychologist
This isn't true
You and Cameron was
Responsible for carrying out a large number of MKUltra related experiments at his home base at the Allen Memorial Institute at McGill
University
Approximately $60,000 or $500,000 modern dollars
Between 1957 and 19
Please do this work for
3 years
Tens of thousands of children
Kidnapping three
An accomplishment
True
In reality Allen Dulles as the head of
CIA had given ultimate approval for the program but it was run by Sydney.
This is a pretty well-known piece of information if Alex has as much awareness of the subject as he
Either nose
That in this isn't intentional
Alternate is I mean
Allen Dulles
What's the center of all
Conspiracies
Right but Sidney Gottlieb is really the more important
Figure air
My point is you have to know about Alan jealous and if you know about Island Ellis you have to know about Sidney Godley
I think that Allen Dulles exists in Alex
His head as like in the JFK files so probably
Cross other
Conspiracy
I got you
It was not you and Cameron
Save the cat
But he did a ton of
Experiments on LSD in hypnosis relating
Suggestibility
And the possibility of implanting false memories in people
Auntie definitely wasn't contact with him
And funded by Sidney Gottlieb and the CIA
For some of his activities
West also accidentally
Killed an elephant with LSD
It's better than Edison killing it on purpose
Also Johnny West was not
Timothy McVeigh psychologist while he was on death row
Their claims made that to West visited McVeigh in prison but there are some reasons why that might not be as shocking as
It seems
First in 1954 he was appointed chair of the Department of Psychiatry at the University of Oklahoma in Oklahoma City
Your Deep Roots
In the city itself
Secondly over the course of his career
Criminal cases
But might even high-profile ones like the Patty Hearst trial
I think that that would be a case that he would drive it
Pay Torrid Ryan terms of
Understanding the mindset of the perpetrator
I don't think
It's impossible that he visited in prison but I don't think it means that he was
Brainwashing him or whatever
Yeah it's so like
You. I was thinking you and Cameron was working
Hand-in-hand with jolly and West in order to run MKUltra
What does reveals adapt
Of not knowing what actually is
Historic
Document
And a and a bun
Sense of not giving a f***
Talk about what real really have
Happened
I don't
Did you know
That the Pentagon
Has the ability to change your emotions without with a ray gun
The Pentagon admits
Can use
Microwaves
Electromagnetic literally
Control someone's brain and change their emotion to show you the patents we're going to show you the news articles
Years ago
So I guess now it's 5G damn it's all of it it's
Simulation also 5G within the simulation is made by stiffer different simulations
And then there's Jesus
Devil and Allen Dulles Olyphant
Makes me so mad
We're not even close to the depth of his frustration to
Think about the government has
Brain control Reagan vibrational pattern of them or whatever is identical to what is now
5G Towers everywhere so they can
Control everyone's emotions
The ability
Me to specifically Target
People because
Rotasu these 5G Towers would affect everyone in the
Feel so you'll be making a lot of people angry or just turned everybody to Happy
Simple if you can control everybody's emotion
Susan everybody
He's happy in his work
Better and doing all that better stuff and having better really
If you're going to be evil why not do it
What's the right way
Sherp
Earlier Alex
MMA
Implied that the recent Wars is based
Quit being born again
You know.
Yeah not the religion
This kind of ears in the same direction
Wow
Alex is undoing what Satan did in the car
I'm going to tell you this right now
He took a while
To get here and I'm glad we got here
It's funny that he's doing this at the moment of his greatest desperation insane
Insane
Almost like this is a Hail Mary it is a bit of a bit of an 80-yard pass
Daunte Culpepper
This to me just smells like
Well
I got no other moves like fixed-wing and I got to do whatever I got to do
So I think that Alex is implying that
Reset Wars has the ability to undo Original Sin
This is like a snake coming down a tree
We were perfect because we're following God's
Feels dirty moment
My whole will everything I am
No I have about 97% of the time
You're right.
Tell you you know in your spirit
Experience
Yesterday
No
Factual inaccuracies in the basic
Details of the things you're talking about if your spirit
That says old and Powerful
Knows the truth 97% of the time
3% of the time when your spirits wrong
Please nerfect
That's dumb
Also I don't think reset Wars is going to undo original
Now you say that but you're not thinking
Proactive
This is what we're talkin
Here dance you need to re pattern your mind
More towards a positive view of
Changing
This also leaves
Me to question whether or not you could show the devil reset Wars good
I mean
Why not
Right right
Should be able to reprogram self the devil having a better day
Yeah Jake manifest
They just don't have any imagination
For people who believe that anything is possible within God's power they
Patience true
So Alex has some prescriptions of like what you should be doing
Everybody
I realize we can fight all the enemies attacks
The racism sexism all the
We can just reach up to the divine
Say about the universe just
There's an interesting perspective
If you're someone who doesn't necessarily believe in religious
You might hear this as a racist using over-the-top
Religious imagery to plead with people to stop trying to
The fight racism
You might hear this as a misogynist using ridiculous rhetoric to beg people to just stop trying to
Define sexism
You might do those things because those are the real-world effects of what Alex is proposing
It serves the purpose of trying to make the audience
Even less about these social issues to be hostile and condescending towards people who care about such
I don't personally believe there is
The god who's handy
Can grab if you ignore racism and sexism but it is
Announces the embodiment of what it means to have grab that and I want no part of it
Personally I believe that there is a God the best way we can pay homage to and serve that God is
Respect care about and serve
Each other
That can come in many forms
But working towards equality in our social system
Definitely one of those things
I think would be there in Omar's to God this is another thing with imagination
These people are our
Italy associating this with good like
What if God is just a p
Piece of s***
You know like what if Alex is right and what God wants them to do
And we're out here
The one who's actually the problem is God himself he's just a real piece of s***
He's a misogynist he's a racist
Why I don't know
How can we possibly understand exactly as a reminder of God
Now
I think that
It's
Troubling
The insistence
Jake has is so much on this like you're not your body thing
This is just
This leads
Hilarious
Wasn't it wasn't that long ago if you asked me who I was
I would have said
6 ft
It's not blue eyes this is how long my hair is this
Rental car rates
It's a fingernail to who I really am
Showering is it once you realize that
It's incredibly empowering in and here's what's something that's so interesting I sent you this text the other day
On my YouTube channel someone left
The comment
And they said
Isaiah
As a black man
I don't know how this
Is blonde hair blue-eyed
Guys videos
But I don't want to watch you because
ABC media has told me
Because you're white you were racist your evil you're the devil
I'm listening to your video right now
I have this deep
Actually
We all
From the same source
And they've been lying to me
Beano's
Totally real you can tell that a 100% real black person 100%
Real rope
Totally real
That's a real thing that
Accidentally
To fit exactly with what it is he would hope
Somebody would write
I also think that even if it is a real ComEd
It's kind of sad to site
YouTube,
Really
This is the pulse of the nation
So I think that
This
Your body is a rental car stuff has pretty pretty
Spread
Troubling implications if
Just
Combined with that
That's basically
Call Mike major theses
Even John Mayer has troubling issues when combined with Alex
What that
So
Finally
He gets something that resembles
Our
Right here
Every time you have an emotion you activate cells and building neurological
Amino it the document
From the US Army College of War
Des Moines
Firewall
Active self
Electromagnetic
What's an electromagnetic wave
What is just
What
There's no such thing as matter
That we are these energy creatures are controlling
So that's not a direct quote
Doing but it's taken from an article published in the US Army war College
Quarterly
It was an article from 1998 by a guy named Timothy L Thomas
Who did published
Pretty widely in past 20 years or more in the area of 4 in
Intelligence operation
And psychological warfare
Are you going to tell me that I have to listen to something that timtom wrote timtom
The title of the article is the mind has no firewall in the basic gist of it
For decades the idea of information Warfare had to do with penetrating and
Any stores of information and disrupting their data
Action abilities
While simultaneously protecting our own
Typically this was thought of in terms of
Computers but new developments had forced people to recognize that the human body itself is
Does a powerful data collection
Interview subjects the senses to various stimulus you can create varying
Example of Sonic weapons and the ability to trigger a seizure through flashing lights are used to illustrate
This concept
The article then brings up the work of a Russian doctor named Victor assume that says
Who proposed that the human organism needs to be seen as an open system
Not a single thing ended up
Itself or recluse
This is to say that Environmental
Influences and information
Flow into the open
Open system
The person has
The potential to quote
Call the change in the psycho psycho physiological condition
Of an organ
This is disgusting terms of the relationship between computer and computer use
How it might be possible for quote
A computer modified to become a weapon
By using its energy output to it
That debilitate
Take the operator
Summative
Discuss that someone who is warning about that future
Potential
Messi's not encouraging
Lookout
This is
So let's have also warned about the idea of the information noise
Which is essentially an overwhelming stimulus in
Turn signals
Behavior modification could be one objective oven
Information noise
Another could beat
Upset individuals mental capacity to such an extent
To prevent reactions
To any stimuli
This was just a theory but honestly the concept made me think of Alex
His show is just a constant barrage of bulshit your mind can't possibly process if yours
Just listening to the show
Are you have to be critically examining at 2 even
See what he saying
He's full of s***
I can see that leading to an audience
Ending up with a difficult time real stimulus
The only real solution to any of the problems Alex rants about ends up being to give him money or to promote his show to other people whom
My giving money
So that was that was fun
Yeah that's good Corollary
Generally speaking this article is largely about physical effects
The could be produced with the use of weapons that would interfere with a body's data-gathering abilities
With modification these technological applications have many uses
Acoustic weapons for example could be adapted to use for use as acoustic
Rifles or acoustic fields that once established
Protective facility
Assistant hostage-rescue
Rescues
Control riots or Clearpath
Leprechaun voice
These waves which
Can penetrate buildings
Offer a host of opportunities for military and law enforcement official
Microwave weapons by stimulating the peripheral nervous system can
Heat up the body and Deuce epileptic like seizures
Poor cause cardiac arrest
Low-frequency radiation effects
Steve electrical
Activity of the brain and can cause
Like symptoms and nausea
Obviously being the target of those sorts of weapons could obviously like
Absolutely have
Psychological effects
But they wouldn't be the primary objective of the weapons
Linda precise reaction to be essentially impossible
So the suffix means
Disgust
Is not
Psychological in nature the word that
Is it implying
AAA lower-level example would be like a mall
Playing a
Ultra hyper
Frequency noise that only younger
Cheryl kind of in order to
I kind of keep them away
I'm certain areas
I guess
They do
Defense
The article further discussions have the USA voiced willingness to work with International treaties against these kinds of web
What are the primary
Concerned that existed the idea of non-state actors
Who wouldn't be bound by these sorts of treaties using these kinds of weapons
These are people referred to as psycho Terror
This is where the idea of the mind not having a
The firewall comes in
These are
Potential vulnerabilities that could be exploited by
Terrorist
Is to protect ourselves
The article
He's talking about how Russian researchers were looking
The topics like
Espe telekinesis and clairvoyance
For the purposes of Defending against
Quote according to Russian TV broadcast
What's the
Music Rocket forces have begun
Anti ES
Speed training
Damn sure that no outside force can take over
Commanding
Control Function
Of the force
That is they are trying to construct a fire wall around the heads
Of the operator
Why do we allow people who believe in ESP to fight War just in case
Is an article in this journal about how when we talked about protecting sister
Sounds like computers the military never gives proper Focus
Chris to The Operators of those computer somehow quote
Clearly the information operator
Exposed before a vast array of potentially immobilizing weapon
Is the week
Weak point in any nation's military asset
Yeah it's like social engineering
And if you've got a really good
Defense system lock system around your building the easiest way to get in is fine
Somebody's got a key
Can I have that
This doesn't prove any of the points Alex or Jake are trying to
They've just taken a couple words from this article and misuse them in order to pretend
It says what they wanted
How to say
I look forward to hearing about these documents that prove that were energy creatures though the CIA talk about energy
Yeah that one was interesting I think
Think he's trying to say that are are atoms at a fundamental on the quantum level
Magnetic
Text fields
Until what we
Feel as
Surface
This is just our
Magnetic fields
You might be onto
That's great
Fantastic
And you know what
My field right now such an Airfield
Get out of here this is my personal feeling
It looks like I stopped right here now it stops right here
But you and I are a field of energy my field
Everything is just a field
He says
He's devoted his entire life to the most clear-headed sign
I can tell you this much
There's no
Matter
He has his observation which is the quantum physics
Don't
You're aware of
But you don't
No
So I honestly tried so hard
Find that quote that use
Promax blank
Its original form some contacts but
I just hit a dead end
The most consistent attribution of this quote is to a 1944 speech to the plant gave in
Florence Italy
The Source lip cited is something within the Max Planck
Institute archives so I went off
To try and find it
Get there
Whose problem is that archive is all in German
And I don't speak German
Even just figuring out
How the archive is organized
It took a while but I was eventually able to
Reduce the details of where the citation was pointing
This was
ABT 5 section
Repository 11
GT5
Section A
A collection
Of numbered Repository
Unfortunately the archive jumpstart number 10 to number 11
So there's no actual accounting of what's an 11
And I was intensely frustrating
Wow
That's really free
12 slap-in-the-face
That's a slap in the face that said I'm not able to find this actual speech and its original four but I'm willing to believe that that's essentially and IQ
To record something
Plank would have said
Venice Beach in 90
I really wanted to get a better handle on the context this was set in but that
Barely even coming
Even without greater context.
The pretty part leap from planks, to quote we're all energy fields
Then what would become aware of that week
We can change the will
I think Planck's point was more than
Science was coming to a point where the conventional understanding of matter being
Completely solid blocks of stuff
Was being challenged by new breakthroughs that show that's on the
Tiniest level
Appear to be solid are not technically so
This is interesting and very important
To various scientific
Alex Fields but it doesn't really have as much practice
Classification in day-to-day life
Is there
Implying like
I know that my wall isn't actually solid but I can't walk through it be hard for me to believe that plank
Gwent from you know everything that he
He's done in his life
Then giving a
Speech where he's like
Guess what
All that Quan
On some stuff I told you about
You have come
Sweet control over
Magic's real facts
And then
I mean like it's it's it's one thing to understand this
Phenomenon that she took it appears to be solid on a subatomic level
May not be alright
Another thing
To be like my intention will determine whether or not this staysolid
See there we go that's an issue
Let me guess if he's just saying that like your emotion
Oceans are controlled by like
You can't control your
Subway
You know you're thinking
Can
You know
This is a basic tenet
The therapy like analyzing
Can have an effect on your emotions
Or your field
Not groundbreaking what I say to that
I feel like this is just a conversation between a washed-up bigot and a guy who's found a way to monetize conversations you have you for your friend
When your high freshman year of college
Sorry about where we're at
Nailed it
Yep
So is going on this firewall thing
I already talked about that article 370 firewall
Ford and Denzel greatest movie
I disagree
Documents
We talked about how the mind has no firewall right one of the things China
Is a firewall on the internet and it's something that we don't
Spalding who wrote the stealth War about
We don't have a
Firewall
You don't have a firewall on our own mine
I think Jake is misunderstanding something important
I'm here
The firewalls people talk about cyber attacks or viruses
It's government-run limitations on what sites
People in China
The Great
Censorship
Yeah
Cyber security measure except
We do have plenty of strategies in place to protect
4in cyberattack but just like is the case with
Literally anyting
Just having some Protections in place dozen
Guarantee that the folks were trying to do hard won't find new ways to get around those protect
Which forces you to find new strategy
It's cyclical in the same
No. No no one's ever had to
Also just because it's fun
In 2018 Robert Spalding
The step down from the National Security Council because of memo came out where you outlined quote
Nationalize the development of 5G wireless networks
Real property
Man that just hit Alex into really tender spots
This was a plan to nationalize something which
She hates right sizes 5G networks without
Alex just said is related to this attack on our energy field
This balding guy must have been
Pretty evil he's going around making proposals like that
Of course that stuff is just
Speak more than we focus on how Spalding is critical of China because that works
So the narrative these dudes are trying to build
Insulted
You know what maybe like Alex was just talking s*** earlier when he said that this was just 5G maybe was just trying to see how that
Feels
Maybe it wasn't a real belief
He has
They figured out
How to use Electric
Release Behavioral
Regulation
Oh no it seems like it's actually believe
Cowboys
Also that quote the Jakes
Using about that doesn't come from any official document Declassified or otherwise
It's from a 1997 article in the new US News & World Report titled quote Wonder Weapons
The pentagon's Quest for a non-lethal arms is amazing
But is it smart
Most of this article is about what you would
Acoustic weapons lasers that
Contemporary
Temporarily blind
Are microwave weapons they could raise a person's body temperature to make them feel sick
Each of these has conceived as a as a way to disarm recap
Acetate someone who poses
The Fret without killing them
Pretty easy but the other two are not really at operational status according
To this article they're sort of in developing
Ideas are being thrown around
So far we've tried it and we
Boiled someone and that was a bad start so we put it on the back burner for a while
Repeating
From this article is about research related to the related to the article's author by eldenburg
Bird was not the former head of DARPA although that is an organization named that
Conspiracy theorists are dicks
Throwing out
He was actually the head of the Marine Corps non-lethal electromagnetic weapon
Project which is right out of the Armed Forces Radio biology
Institute
Saying that this was DARPA makes it
Easier for the audience though cuz it gives them something to
Cold
Yeah
Bird was in this position from 1980 to 1983 and he claims that he did experiments
But sound like
By using
Very low-frequency electromagnetic radiation
He could induce the brain to release behaviour regulating camel
The issue though is that the waves that they were using were very weak
The effects were short-lived
He claims that he was able to do things like make
Brands release their natural opioids
In utero and
Get certain cells in Rat brains to release histamine
In which would cause nausea
And flu-like
The program was never quote
Stood in the field and those program was meant to last for years it was closed after 2
Just to
This doesn't pass muster in terms
So justifying reclaims Alex
Shakermaker
Opposition to research programs like this
That rely on it
Insisting that week avidan's like this proves that the government is mine
Controlling everyone on a mass scale
The answer is rebooting your brain
Pointless opposition
I made a rat
Sick so I guess I can
To control minds
That out
Interesting on that level also relying on something that was being
Told to a writer of an article in the u.s. News & World Report
As opposed to any data any actual report
Science on this
Not good
Yeah I would like more pureview fax from
Before I start
Just going along with
Can make checks
Release opioids
In the womb
Right it's
Just not good work
No
Faulty it's almost
It's almost like
They're to be explained
It's almost like it's a hypnotist
Stretch
Look at these keys
Look I'm going to make this this article magically appear to be a Declassified document
So Alex
You really want to talk about being in the spirit
Free spirit
Okay so Jake
Jake's going off on that then Alex's something
Deeply revealing
Find power inspiration we can transform
Greater than our environment
Access new ideas
The world
In this one
Absolutely so that right there was a gigantic tell that Alex is full of s***
They're going on about this esoteric mumbo-jumbo about how you have to let go of yourself as a physic
Globalist
Can't separate this playing from the end goal of
Taking over the world
He's unable to go
Conceive of an end goal for this process of Liberation that doesn't
Involve the accumulation
Power
That's pretty much the exact opposite of what one would be interested in as an end goal if you were preaching Detachment from the physical
Who cares if you take over the physical world it's not real
If I recall correctly
And I'm going to throw this out
It was
The meek
Who were
At what point do you stop being
Is it the part where you go
Let's take over the world
It's
It's a really hairy I don't know if the meat usually have that goal
This is not a small point
But like
How does this idea that were not our physical bodies mechoui
With Alex's obsession with property right
Not only do you not have ownership over your car according to Alex this car doesn't even exist
How can you possibly exert property rights over malleable waves and force fields are whatever the f***
Alex's ideology and worldview
Starkly at odds
With what he's preaching now because the Bedrock of Alex's ideology for his entire career
Is involved important
Individualism and materialism
Given these two things such as primary focus for his entire career is antithetical to the we are not our bodies nonsense he's pretty
Preaching now
If we're not our bodies then none of his politics make
Any sense
If you're not your body then you should have no problem with abortion
Because that's always just going to go back to heaven or come back to earth and another body rental car
If you're not your body then the argument for unalienable rights
To self-defense doesn't even make sense anymore
It's really fascinating and I honestly think that this has the potential
Either completely
Alex's career
I like the pseudo-spiritual Griff
Some bad news
Alex would be shity about Griff
No one wants
Namaste being yelled at them
I find it so interesting though this
This way I would love
To hear Alex try and explain property rights
Under this new paradigm
I don't think it would be possible
Well as somebody who has
Study Buddhism for a long time
I would say that many of the Great Buddhist
Masters while they preached
We're also
Taking over the world
And that is something that a lot of people don't remember
Amitabha Buddha you super nice you're super nice
On the surface
But deep down that motherfuker wanted
To take everybody to the
Cleaners if you believe like let's save this desk
Sure
Is it is it appears to be solid
Reality
It's not
Actually even matter
Can I be mad
If you take it I can ship over this an automatic
Yourself from these material things
Kill anybody who tries to take them
I don't understand it all makes perfect sense
Physical world is it real quick
Kill somebody if they steal your car what are the Greek Noble Truths
You got to f*** somebody up sometime
This is dumb
And I wonder if Alex's audience will pick up on me
Because I could do him some
Real serious damage
In terms of audience
Pretension
The religiosity that is
Is preached
Jose
Certain connotation
Intuit that I feel like
People resonate with
It's in his audience
And to switch to new AG bulshit Idaho
I think some will
Just trapped
Yes
Yeah it's hard to say like I don't know how much
Costuming of like
The globalist
Send the New World Order and Illuminati
I don't know how much of that
Is going to be required
To make this palatable
Because there are these
These differ
Like
Materialism is really big
Yeah property rights
Free market
These kinds of things are are
Alex's careers
Is based on
And this is a is a
Systems
Has no in
The same time is almost
I mean there is also the obsession with using this system
To get stuff
Oh on
Yeah you know you're trading fighting the Communists for believing that if you
Believe hard enough the Communist will just go away
Also
It beat the ideas of individualism
Alex
Who's obsessed with
Really run counter to
You are not yourself
Oh boy I wish him the best
And I bet I'm in the world
So Alex
Advice
It's now 8.
Go see eat like
If you have medical
Mental Health
Absolutely
Jersey Shore weather
Mine
Be aware of how they manipulate your mind you'll become stronger
Hello to some psychologists and psychiatrists the system
Telling your failure your week
Pills for you
Gimme a Break ladies and gentlemen
Flip-flopping statement comments on masks
Pecan masks
The audience already hates fauci and they aren't wearing masks
This could not be more trivial compared to the hour
What's the topics Alex's pretending to cover
I found that to be a jarring and that's not that's not okay
Yeah alright
Esoteric ideas proven by CIA documents
That we have also
But it isn't consistent about Mass this whole f****** thing is a simulation who gives a s*** about what fauci is
Is or is not saying the mask isn't real
It's a field I guess
So why are you complaining about it like you can't breathe you're not in but you're not even the person breathing you're just real
God dammit
So all right here we go
Finally going to get to the doctor
Aldi documents that history looking
What they admit they're doing how they're trying to erase
Personality store
50 60 70
Call Autumn a scale
The shouldn't be people shouldn't people be aware
I'm excited to get into these documents but also right off the bat Alex
Completely wrong
He said that the last time documents were Declassified about MKUltra is 1977a badges
Incorrect
Greenwald submitted foia request
Thousands of pages of documents
It's about MK Ultra back in 2000
Alex saying this leads me to believe that he doesn't know much about
This topic or possibly just stop learning new things about a prior
Also Greenwald has engaged in another flavor requests
In 2018 this one specifically regarding behavioral modification
And in response he received over a thousand more pages
Now I will grant that a lot of the pages there in those
Dumps
We're not really that interests
Things like a check
Disbursement
But there's also relevant
Kristen there
It's pretty glaring for Alex accidentally admit that he just
Made this big glass
About MK Ultra stuff
But weirdly isn't aware
Of things past 1977
The modernity get in the way of Lord
Sure
Sure we got to have lore
We're getting to the doc
Document I kind of don't believe
Document I really don't believe you
Here's the first one
Sort of
Richard
20 he's the deputy director was the deputy
Director of
The Pentagon
Advanced research
Projects
This is an actual quote
He says
Experiments
We did some remarkable things
There was no question in my mind
You can get into the brain
Microwave
If you really make the Breakthrough
You got something better
Any bomb
Everbilt
Because
When you finally come down
Talking about controlling
Peoples
Lesser argument
What are the 5G
That's the right one riot
Population
Good guys
Petition
This isn't from a document per se
It comes from a May 15th 1988 article in the Asbury Park Press
Which actually isn't
True
The Asbury Park Press is quoting something that Richard Cesaro said two years prior in an interview with a nun
Unspecified ENT
I can find
Hundreds of conspiracy blogs
It's repeating the quote but the closest I can get to the original context
Is this Asbury Park Press article
Find out satisfying
But oh well
Even so the article is kind of telling and it shoot some holes in Jakes
The article does say that 20 claim these things
But it also says quote
Initially Pandora researchers believe that the irradiation had caused subtle behavioral effects
Test animal
Later however reanalysis of the experimental data raised doubts about its validity
A scientific review panel decided in 1970 that the
Be disbanded
He was tested on humans and the experimental data that
Fitz's arrow is
Referring to was found to be dubious upon re-examination
This is a slam dunk
Uncle Jake thinks it is I'm I'm more to the point it's not even a document in the sense that Alex
I was using the term
This isn't the classified it's a nothing
Asbury Park Press article
I'm looking
A Declassified proof not
Quotes from an interview that you can't even find the full text of anymore
And also
The reason that Sarah was doing this research was because we were afraid of the Soviets and communist doing that same research and we did
Leg up
February consist
Send pattern that this stuff
Mysteriously unaware of that motivation
They had
Yeah yep
People in America were so paranoid about
They went on mulch
Multiple Witch Hunt
Engaged
Non-stop racism
Exploded things left and right
And
Believed in magic for a good long while
Richard a lot of vulnerable people
Yep suck
School
So
Let's never do that again
Before before we started
The show I told you that
There were a couple of clips
That worth
The cold water being splashed in my face
Was so shocking
Even masks are another example
I'm trapping you into your physical body
It's another
Anchor
Brings you back into lower emotions you're afraid of dying even though you can't die because
Everything is energy and energy is never created or destroyed it's only transferred to different states first law firm
Oh my God
I think it's safe to say that we have crossed a very serious. Cheer
Not only are you not your physical body but apparently now you can
Can't die
Dying
Possible energy and energy can be created or destroyed
I just don't know what to say at this point like a week ago Alex was giving
Growling
Heart-to-heart talks to his audience about how
Time for you to think about killing your family members
If you know your family members believe in vaccines
Now we have this Dopey
Be hypnotist and Alex trying to sell a bill of goods about how you can't die in the physical reality isn't real
I think this has a high chance of leading to some people getting hurt
And I hope whatever Jake
Good paying Alex for exposures worth it
Could go
So bad
A s'more
Board of b*******
Like if you want to believe
Anything you
Can find it
Like they're both talk
So fast
About so little
Aggressively
That's
You can just be like that one sounds like it resonates with me
Die
Great
If you got to save the kids from the vaccines
Ortho k
You got to kill your family member really dying
It's impossible steal somebody Never Dies can I watch Game of Thrones
Your ironborn
Big boobs
Matter is never
Aggravated asteroid so that me
Means we can't die I read that in science
I was wondering if there were ways for Alex to get less
Responsible or more irresponsible in this is definitely a way
You can't die
Alex not pushing
Aerodynamics
We're not even in that level of like your soul doesn't die or anything like that he's just straight-up like
Whatever you'll probably be reconstituted into something else somewhere else who cares
No no no
It's not
Even that like
Your soul
I guess maybe it's your soul
That you are not
Your body
Right
This is a rental car
Sure just break
Breaks down if you die
So
Matter can never be created or destroyed
Your body's not matter
No no no no no no let's stop right here
What's up right here
Okay
If my soul then what's my soul if it is my sole matter is that what he's trying to say
Is he trying to say
That the soul is also physical
I don't think he gets into it I would be curious
I want to know because I think it does have to have something to do with these
Field
And I wonder if you think
Makes the fields have any
Physically
The state would ever even if it is
It cannot be created or destroyed then yes it is
Are the fields
Function of the simulation
Simulators
Is it a glitch
In the simulation they have the
Ability to manipulate the
Fields around us or whatever I mean it
It can't be a glitch in the simulation
That would be in like then it could break
And then we'd all die
It's the end of the world
There's a lot of questions that are not answered
Say that's fair
We get to another example of what is
Supposed to be a document
Sure
Everybody go to reset Wars
Sign up
Right now
Reset Wars
Dot-com
Right now for the early breakfast because
Quote
Good work program
Disrupt
Political dissident and extremism by
Employing
Transcranial magnetic stimulation
Fisticated propaganda
Based on this technology
Yeah that's what you heard
Think about it
Keep chiming in with that
I know we're late we're getting a little bit hard out here
From a document or anything official
The characterization that's been given to comment made by an anonymous whistleblower as written up on the website
Blog
Activist post
Firstly activist supposed to be dumb website with a heavy
Conspiracy leading been
It's basically a less ambitious Infowars without a charismatic lead singer like Alex
Here's all you need to know about this site
The fourth book listed on their recommended reading list
Is AIDS Incorporated by Jon rappoport
John Rappaport denialism book
Really I'm 44 on their reading list
Nothing like that but it menu went to rap
Can't even hang up a f****** picture
Along with this on the reading list are books by Infowars favorites like Webster
Tarpley Mark Dice David
Another book by Rappaport
Also none dare call Atkins
Anyway this was a post about an anonymous whistleblower contacting them
I'm telling them that DARPA was running
The study at Arizona State University that was meant
Use transcranial magnetic
Stimulation
To affect the brain
The Narrative process
This
Was a real project
That was undertaken by ASU
Titled quote ordinariate of disruptors and induct
Mapping the narrative comprehension Network and its persuasive of
What what does
Really comes down to his interpretation
Like if you want to look at this project
You can say it's evil there's no way I'm going to be able to
The talk you out of that
I don't think it's evil and I really don't think that I could be convinced
But it is
The study is essentially about how the brain creates Naruto
Sand weighs
Is that you can effectively help
The narratives be more
Persuasive
Conversely how you can disrupt
The persuasiveness of narrative
The Hopeless
To be able to
Construct a better understanding of the brain's narrative comprehension Network which
School quotes
Lead to a full understanding of the influence narrative has on memory emotion theory of Mind identity in Persuasion
Intern influence the decision to engage in political violence
Or join viola
Groups or support such groups ideologic
Sickly or financial
The research focused on the persuasiveness of narratives as
Experienced by Christian
And Muslim sub
These groups are selected because religiously speaking they have many overarching
Similarities in what they called the master narrative
Well as many differences personal aspects of interacting with a narrative much more
Forecast
The first phase of the study was
Participants will watch a series of video vignettes
Videos and make decisions
That should be influence
By the videos
The group participants
Where are they were grouped into by two models
Spyware the differences were whether the master narrative
Which is the religious narrative
Weather that mapped with the local narrative
What does the video
That's the first
Variable
I meant how the local narrative is related to their personal narrative
So the two options
In the personal narrative section would be that sort of
Option
Who did they beat
Askew imagine themselves in the narrative
A 30-second
Ken's or they're being asked to imagine
The semantic consequences of the narrative 4:30
30 seconds
The first one for the personal narrative it makes it personalized whereas
The ladder is it
Detached and analytic
Afterwards the participants would answer questions about the video they watched
And what they thought about it
At the end
Quote participants would make a judgment about how much of their research payment they would like to allocate to a two
Particular
Religious group
Through the experiment neural images would be taken
Can to help understand the parts of the brain that were activated when different aspect of relating to
The narratives are happening
Cuz I didn't want to rely on self
Reporting right
Because that could
Be enacted
Okay
I understand please
If you understand what
Get this right
If I understand correctly what they're trying to find out is how much
Much do the stories that we tell ourselves
That we believe
Affect what we actually
And if you can
Interrupt
Or influence
The story that somebody is telling them self
In order to interrupt her influence there
Current belief about what's going on
Somewhat
But the interrupting
And inducting
Are kind of part of later
It's more about
Seeing
How
The relationship between
The videos that
People are being shown
Whether or not it matches with
Their religious beliefs
Why what the heck that has
On their response
Secondarily
Response personalizing
Sing it has to do like imagine
Giving yourself in the narrative that's in the video as your close to
Critically analyzing it
Like the semantic concert get rid of your own story
And see what somebody else's story or think about
Somebody else's story
Conversely
If it matches your religious narratives your master narrative yourself within the hour
And your own bunch of different
Aspect
It's do it and
You know it's an interesting study guide
I agreed so then the second phase of the experiment was similar
But they change the aspects of the relationship with narrative that were being examined
In this phase the two variables were narrative validity
So that would be valid or invalid
Per patient
Which is to say whether whether or not the narrative is immersive
To the person
Experiencing
So those are the two variables that
We're messed with
In the second
Can save other than that it was basically the same layout as
Is the first
These three is where all the hullabaloo comes in
In this phase they plan to use Tran
Cranial magnetic stimulation
Disrupt parts of the brain associated with narrative comprehension ideally to see how that affects
Overall comprehension and persuasion
I admit that sounds like a bit much
Watch but the other two phases are
Play lien Oculus research project
Much like neute
Taking place on any college campus everyday
And the third really isn't as
F***** up as a
No nut May
I mean that make sense because the other
Question is is it a
Physical process
All of that
Stuff that we've
Talked about
Is entirely within the Conch
Not even necessarily what you would call the brain or whatever
When you add
The transcranial
Magnetic
Then you take it from something that is what you are thinking
Do something that is actually physical
That you can measure
And the neural Imaging as well there are elements of what
This this was amen
To determine
But
Kind of irrelevant
Cuz I can find this grant proposed
And their contract
From the Department of
The interior
Their status updates going up to
The June 2013 that have been released
Any documentation drops off
None of these conspiracy blogs
Does it talk about this have anything past that point which I thought was a little bit weird
Until I took a closer look at
The contract
The department of
The interior had agreed to fund
Phase 1
But it didn't
Commit to the other two
Those were opt
I can find no evidence that the very scary face through this experiment has ever actually done
And if they can prove that it was I would encourage him to share that evidence with me
I actually have fairly strong circumstantial evidence that it didn't
Extended past Phase 1
Because I found the project manager Stephen corman's resume
And he lists this grant in it and it's spring 2012
But that's it
It doesn't appear again
Conversely
Spring 2009 Grant he was awarded on a project
Regarding quote
Embedding story and analysts in
Dictionary
Is listed again in summer 2013 with a grant God extend
If the study that we're talkin about had gotten
Extended that would mean a couple million
Extra dollars
The funding would you better believe he's going to put on his resume
University of Louisville
That shitt
Extension for the other project that he put on his resume there's only for $250,000
Like you would
Absolutely put in as an accomplishment right.
This refunded right right because if they founded the first bit and then they
Release the funds for the second bit
You got some promise
It going
And that means maybe I'll get this through this program.
That's really great
For Universal
It's because they really like
To be able to
Have their professors
And they're researchers
Claim to
Like we did we did this research
A prestigious Professor brings
Prestige to the university
So here's what's going on here
There was a scary sounding project at Arizona State University which an anonymous whistleblower told active
This post about
The conspiracy blog so they characterized
The study as an attempt to create
Control and Jake is just reading copy from that blog
Instead of engaging with the actual material and the research program at
This is sloppy work
Hypnotist
I'm very unhappy
Yeah I bet
It didn't actually happen
I prefer to be
It happened let me be clear
May have happened
But I have no evidence that it did
Strong indications that it
I cannot prove definitively that it didn't happen I mean they could have
Secretly fund
Did the program after that yeah
6-quart to prove it actually happened
No evidence
So
Do you want your dreams
No
Oh wait no I mean
That desires that I have
Come through if they put a magnet on my f****** head by a giraffe
No no no
What if you want that
True
Got to go to reset
Conscious
And then
Stop submitting
The outside stimuli
This is a real reset
Imagine if everybody realizes that imagine
If a nurse that's in the medical system that
I think she's power
Realizes she can create our own private
Eventually become the biggest private
The English teacher realizes
You can create the most
One of the most powerful
Schools
Going down the line
You realize the broadcaster that wants to be like Alex Jones and Owen
Actually
Did the same
Spiritual energy that's moving through all of us
And they can utilize that to become incredibly powerful to become the night or not going to get upset or successful cuz they're freaking us
It's moments like that
Suggested motivational speaker style conman really come out
Jake
It's just meaningless platitudes where the Fulfillment of all your dreams
Easily if you just follow this guy's plan which is basically what his YouTube channel is all about already
Halo embarrassing and exploitative
Like
Okay yeah
You wanted
Encourage people to take a chance and
Start their own business or whatever
Why not but insinuating that doing so is like you're going to be the most colorful
Practice in the state or whatever
Exploitative of peoples
Aspiration
Yeah this is
Wolf of Wall Street
He's like oh okay sell me this pen and then you do the whole thing and then you find Jesus and then you're a motivational
Speaker and as a broadcaster
No desire to be like Alex
Definitely no desire to be like Owen
That would be
So hora
Well I mean it's so funny to me that
When you're when you're in that
Stat like let go of your body detach from physical material stuff all of that
It goes to direct
Benzino it can go with
Well if you're detaching then what's
The point of all that stuff just let it go don't worry about your fantasies just being part of
One you know that all thing or the other ways
If you believe hard enough
You'll get a lot of
Come on now haha
Which one do you want to go with
It's just what
These guys to shut up I like to manifest I'm shutting off
Conversely I'd like to manifest them get into
That would be great
If I manifested that would like six of your clips
I've manifested myself sleeping this next curve cuz it's really just splitting hairs about Alex Smith
Quoting Einstein
But
You know he has got to spin his wheels a little bit about the vaccine
Why do you think Jake
Great research kill so many people
Statistically
Did just tell him
They'll rise of a defeatist we are doing their medicine
Had that really bizarre
Speech the other day work
They're going to turn everything to a nature preserve and it runs going to living space
I mean they realize they don't really need
And that's what this is all about
When we going all these.
It can be a little scary
I want to say that
Alex put together reset when you're conscious other operation
Knowing is half
This point of the interview I'm going to be straight up with you I'm starting to get a little bit resent
Fort Wayne anytime is taken
Talk about something that is not the main point of recent Wars
We've already laid out the central premise and promise to go super deep into it
Alex is wasting time wax
Philosophical
But why globalist
Statues various methods to kill us
It's super frustrating
Also to Jake's point at this point he's gone over exactly zero.
He's made references to an article and activist post
Encoded imprecisely from the Canadian news story about a podcast
Series
Great research
When people insist that they're going to get deep into a topic then dance around the edges a little bit and then incessantly promoted
Different show they do
And ramble about bulshit like how you can't die
Generally means they don't actually have a d
Familiarity with the topic there pretending to
That's a strong Vibe I'm getting
Chinese dude feeling that too
I was I was waiting for you to say it first cuz I didn't want to embarrass myself if that wasn't
It was a grand reveal
Feeling more comfortable hours in a podcast
They actually are right
No
Also let's not forget that the knowing
Is half the battle catchphrase comes from a series of
Psa's the future GI Joe characters
Which is produced by a Harvard child psychologist and endorsed by the national Child Safety Council
Sounds pretty globalist to me
The GI Joe folks only even made them as a cynical attempt to Garner
Goodwill cuz I didn't want people to get mad that their show is just a
Toy commercial targeted kids that screamed war is cool
I would think that
Especially considering how this episode is all about how Elite psychologists are trying to Minecon
Control listen to changing our Behavior
Alex should be pointing out how these
Psa's are perfect
Example of exactly that
These folks wanted to alter the behavior of children by having advice come from characters that they love which was
Taking them off their natural trajectory
Natural unemployment state a child would
No to not give strangers their address but also the national Child Safety Council
What the f***
It is
It is always funny to me how they pick and choose what they
Things are conspiracies in the house
You know and then they just take a lot of s***
For granted
Like I like
5G is terrifying to juice
Tucci was fine
But once
Victory comes along holyshit
Also dude
I want a slightly unrelated but
In preparation for this episode does game board
These assholes a bunch of those GI Joe PSA
The Jose had
Advice but they were getting seriously involved in stuff that does
Concerned by their own f****** business
I don't need
Flint scolding me for picking on the goalie on my soccer team for allowing a goal
That's a pretty small scale stuff for an elite military unit to be doing it honestly what's play to doing it that soccer game to begin with
Pictures of kids
What's a
I wasn't a g.i. Joe guy I was
Starscream man I was a Transformer
I didn't care much what
My parents didn't allow me to watch the
What are some awareness of these PSAs are hilarious
Crazy
It sucks small-scale stuff
Like some of it is great advice like don't tell strangers you're home alone
Great
But some of it is like
Hey if someone wants you to jump over a ditch
It's too big don't do it
Put a splitter
Is it going to be like
Hey
Listen real quick
We can't allow Saudi Arabia have nuclear weapons
Knowing is half the battle
Black girl skateboard with you
They're slightly do
I don't know what GI Joe is
Is doing getting
Stop
Minut Affairs of this small town
It's it's just military prop
You know it's like whatever cops say that they give a s*** about you 96% of crime is a
Violator whatever the phone
Like a bunch of
3 kids for kids around their bike and they're heading
Towards a railroad crossing and then out of nowhere one
Railroad crossing sign
Really
A real version of that commercial is that a GI Joe pops up while I'm riding my bike and I
Throw the bike out of and then get hit by a f******
He doing waiting at that train trying Clawson
Patrol near a bridge
Anyway it's
It's
Bizarre and I recommend people go watch those
Especially if you're bored of a hypnotist and a f****** washed-up drunk
Doing nothing
Anyway we get back to trying to promote reset Wars
We're saying
Go right now
Sign up to reset wars.com
Get on the early bird list because once Mark Zuckerberg sees as he
Chicken metaverse in
Explain that
Reset horses the answer to the metaverse
Really
So now we hit Bingo on the city used car salesman techniques
Card
Jake is trying to use
Salaries at Wars
He got to sign up for it now so Alex and Jacob Harvest your contact information because if you wait it could be
Be too late
What's Mark Zuckerberg
Bird finds out that this drunk in his hip
Just friend what they're up to
He's going to lock Us in the Multiverse
Sweet
Listen I got a lot of
People looking at
This car
And you can take a look at it first maybe 25-30 minutes
Cuz I can do buddy
Yeah this is just
Manipulative
Tricks to get listeners to sign up for this email list
Mark Zuckerberg could give a s*** about
Does not care
We release reset Wars
Zuckerberg is going to put the metaverse
Send a high gear you imagine Mark Zuckerberg sitting in a boardroom being like
What are you recently
Oh no this
Money hypnotism grifter
It's going to take down the metaverse
I have money so big
So I mean look
This reset words can be really disappointing
Probably
Whacking
In substance based on this presentation that they've given so far sure
But
Stop Jake's friends listen to it and he stopped
Drinking
Quit drinking from it
Has been watching you for
15 year saying
He's watched thousands of episodes in it was literally the most
You know all this stuff
You never put it together as you help me
Meeting after meeting at
I wanted to come on today just in honor of that
Where are where are the documents
Cancel what
Also I would love
To be a fly on the wall for those me
Oh my God
For those meetings
Holy
S*** that would be so I mean
Take out a whiteboard
Haha I don't even have a whiteboard they just got spaghetti in there literally throwing it a wall with
Refrigerator magnets and whatever letter pops up is it when they win number one I don't think these meetings happen
Start a business in writing
The fantasy
But
I can imagine
No more annoying
Anything then
That idea of this meeting
I'd love to watch it
It'll be
Nightmare for anybody else but for me who who
Whenever he said he got a friend to quit drink
Raptor watch
I imagined in my head that immediate moment where
Friend is drunk and he's watching this and then he looks at the
The brown bottle and just go
Nah
This is clearly this is the bottles fault
Is the bottle led me to this moment and I got to get rid of it
Immediately thought like
Okay so watching it got someone to stop drinking but making it didn't get Alex
Baby Alex
You know he's not he's only on the 10th step he never made it to the 11 so
Rijeka info
What's tomorrow's news today
But
A recent War
Infowars is tomorrow's news today
Reset Wars
Is
Tomorrow's wisdom today
This is for you
Always try to stop
Everybody from finding out so you better
Better believe
They put reset wars together there's a good chance
That they're going to try to shut it down they're going to try to shut the website down
That's why you got to go right now and sign up
Reset wards.com
I'll tell that coming out in early December it's going to be massive
So
This is wild
Conjecture on my part but
I noticed something strange when I was looking at the who is data
For this new website
Alex's pretty consist
With the hosting that uses for his website
Infowars banned. Video newswars B sites are all hosted by Epic
Because he knows that no matter what he does
Cuz no matter what criticism he gets
Epic is not going to take a s*** down
That company is fine hosting all manner of
Objectionable content and is essentially the last Refuge
Internet Chat Heads
If you're not see
Come on over we don't mind
This thing but reset Wars isn't hosted by Epic
It's just a URL they registered through GoDaddy
So it actually would
Eventually be far more likely to be taken offline
If GoDaddy didn't want to be associated with Alex and is content
Instances of GoDaddy doing exactly this like when they pulled their services from Hosta
Gab
In 2018
This is complicated
Because
On the one hand I think it's far too
Conspiracy theory thinking to claim that Alex intentionally put this website up
Funnel Escarosa
Open platform
Because he actually wants it to be taken down
Put on the other hand
The circumstantial evidence
Kind of interested
Like
Can Bounty be able to grandstand but I was the victim
How they don't want this information getting out
He be able to pretend he's a prophet because he predicted they take
Site down
I don't think that this is unintentional thing on his part
It's fishy is hell like
Why wouldn't
He hosts this on Epic
All of the other sites that he runs
I mean it doesn't make suntikan
I can imagine a non conspiratorial way which
Which is being dumb
Like maybe the
The site was set up by Deuce
And Dulce is still on YouTube so he was like I'll just use my regular
Platform
Possibility I suppose I can also I can see what you're saying I can't imagine Alex
Doing the most important work of his career
Launching this website
And then being like yellets
Let's Let The Host
Thing Beyond something today
Potentially faulty
You're very right about that
It seems weird
Yeah and they are pushing that like this is so dangerous narrative really hard
Actually believe it to be so dangerous to be playing
Preemptive
Even the most secure place possible
Which leads me to believe
Then maybe they have an expectation that this website might get take
Taken down
It's useful as a contact information harvesting
Get people's email addresses
I meant the contact
Can just be published out banned. Video
Totally
Fine so the theory that we're operating are not we're operating under but the theory that I'm
Hearing
Is that it
It's possible
They are using this as a
Fishing website for right now
Once the content is released on the website there expect
Taken down because
Is GoDaddy is like
Hey no Nazis
Then whenever the content is taken down they put
Put it back on to banned. Video
Grandstand about how they've been
You know is there in there telling
I don't
Want to say that that's a
The theory because I think
That's a little bit
Conspiracy
It's a little out there
Actual pieces of information
Are what that would be there if that's what they were doing
Might not be
I'm leaning towards
Occam's razor
Dumb oversight from these Dum Dums
That sounds like the most obvious and
Likely I think I agree with you on that
Write that fraud
But the information that you are pointing out is very sick
I'm in one of the reasons I wanted to bring it up is
I think
Obviously I agree with you the most likely explanation is
Incompetence
But on the off-chance that this does end up happening
To be able to have
Look
Is look at their hay
Like
Yeah yeah
And when the stakes are this High maybe they're putting more planning into it
I don't know
This day
Could not be higher
Maybe
Maybe so this life is deranged
It's the owner
By Jesse
Yelling about
In front of her in front of a building in Hellyer Mendeleev
What are you doing
In what
Everybody realizes one by one we go
Oh my gosh
Consciousness creates reality I've been programmed to believe I'm not that
Make money
Emotional pattern that's been memorizing my brain and nervous system that I've
Once we break out of
Muffler system
And re-engineer it
I just think Alex is like
Call a dealer need to make a new country is
Is I mean it's probably metaphorical but it's f***** up
Protesting is it going to do
Also
I think in terms of like
Saying that they have been
Brain to think that I have tendency towards
Depression
It's really insulting
And
I mean what would it what do you say that the man has
You know condition me to believe that my arm is broken after I falling off a roof
Right
All you have to do is believe
Is it looks
Looks like it's broken but really it's not even matter
Solid matter
You just need to use your mind
To believe that your arm is fine and then it is
Yet here's what I'm
All right and this
This is my pitch
I'm going to try and solve everything real quick
Good luck
When I was in
High School
Explain Sports
You know all the
The sports coaches
Had
Inspirational slogan
The lake
Posters
The Ted believe
You know the whole thing in there
Yeah yeah yeah
Now
I'm going to toss
What if we had poster
In
High school locker room
That just lay out of
Exactly what propagate
Justin comments
Maybe longer posters but I mean look
I've heard this speech
Word for word from a million different kinds
This is the one this is the speech
Yeah it's it's it's
It's very boilerplate right before the game
You don't get yourself
Like I'm not going to get caught by a cop I'm not going to
Someday be nice I think
Even what
You could do is just a poster that says
Don't trust hypnotist
They're sketchy
Maybe we should
To shorten it to instead of the poster that says believe it just says don't believe
Yeah yeah
So
This point in the episode
Kind of
Realize like
Brainwash yourself
For the world
Rain washes
The program are the systems
Call about it
Trust God to guide you out of it
Then just realize that this stuff exist
When
Was filming this
Reset where's the greatest thing ever did
Rarely police promotion
It's very humble
If what I mean it's about
People finding what they mean
They'll find it
I am f******
Urea
About this s*** because they promised they were going to get the weed and talk about these documents so I read up on a bunch of stuff and I found
It was perfect for them to talk about
This is what I'm about to
It's a real have to do with mind control on it
Easy to find
The actual document
Okay running a self-help hypnosis style scam here
Pretending that it has anything to do with the real world
Declassified documents
That's because they were serious at all they would have fun with this one
It's September 1965 researchers working within the CIA
Study to attempt to remote control the behavior of a dog
By way of providing rewarding elect
Call stimulation to parts
The dog's brain
Admittedly this sounds really fun
F***** up at first glance but then again people
Train dogs to do all sorts of things by way of conditioning
It's not like a dog wants to sit or roll over it
We trained that if it
Does
It gets the reward that it was
This operates in a similar principle
Does using electrical stimulation of Rewards
Centers in the dog's brain or at least the goal was to see if this was possible
We could give him a tree or we could
Cut open a skull put some
I see how that goes Nobody wants
To train their dog is hard
This is remarkable stuff
From a dystopian science perspective
You can look at this and be like hahaha
But honestly if you read the final report on it it's really hard to come away thing
Has any practical application
Particularly interim
Abused
Documents
For one thing
Human brains are very different than dog brain
Humans rely far less
On Insta
Thank the dogs doing term
Their behavior
Who be exceedingly hard to conceive of how you would program a routine of electrical stimuli they would get human to do complex
Especially considering
I all they were able to do with his dog is get it to walk from one place to another
Slowly
Slow growth is still growth
Accomplish this they needed to put electrodes
In the dog's head
Mounted with a protective helmet
Hey the stimulator pack which could be activated remotely
But only from a fairly limited distance
64 Wildman
The researchers tried to see if they could figure out how to actually Alyssa actions from a dog through electrical stimulation but sound
It wasn't an area worth it
Exploring so they only ended up
Doing Rewards
After training
They found that the dogs had a strong tent
Do the thing that they were doing
Just before they got the rewards
Simulation
So as it pointed out in the report
If they were moving
Forward they would
Continue to move forward
So you could get a dog to
Bye
But keeping on stimulating right they found the dogs had a tendency to
To move forward in the direction they're headed was facing when they got the stimulation
This was an observation the researchers made that allowed them
Anything resembling remote
Control of the dog
Kind of appeared to be remote control
Another problem they found was that it's barely do
Difficult to get these Electra
Hoverboard stimulation
To work when they're other
Competing stimuli around like food
Unless the stimulation was quote
At Optimum levels
It's hard to predict how this would work
In the real world like in the wild where the dog would have a
The Gathering
Cher
The researchers concluded that quote
Well the electrode preparation has
Been satisfactory for research
Purposes
It's unlikely that it would serve over very long
There was also the problem of eating
Take a person to monitor the precise movements of
The dog in order
Continue reinforcing the behavior that's desire
Spell require
Constant visual coverage of the dog at all times
Which doesn't seem too helpful outside of lab application
Like if you were trying to get the dogs to work as Scouts
Essentially
Be so complicated
And the idea of being able to
Challenging terrain review
Instead let's try training with food and not cutting open brains
This is mighty bizarre stuff
Obviously the ethical
Applications of how these dogs are treated
Is a serious concern but
The kind of super nightmarish it that conspiracy theorist
Whatever want imagine it
They don't even talk about this
See the worst thing is I bet so.
The type of evil sign
Encino where you're like you guys
Should really just
F****** stop that but the evil scientist kept who like
What's the dog's head alive after
After the body was removed for like a few hours
Let's see more of how that goes I want food
Futurama style heads in jars
That's what I'm
Looking more towards as opposed to like
Getting a constant handjob from electro
You got to manifest
Was Furious
Talk about that
Because
Yeah that's right a real house of what they're talkin about
If you start talking
About cats
Conspiracies that you can look into
People are going to start wanting to look into
All York
That's why they all have to be
Able to look at the source
Clear because if you do yeah it's
You got from
Finding this story and finding and learning something
Interesting and fun
Imagine if somebody who really believed in
Conspiracies
Actually got that real feel
Well blue
Present this as
Bisbee scientist
So figured out a way to make humans do whatever they want buy it and receptors in their brain
So anyway
Is stupid
This
Next clip ends
In the stupidest way
Once you reach out
Cost at all that
Barack Obama and nnn all these people
University Dodge
Barack Obama
Think about the idea
Abyss Newtonian model of
Don't know
Who's Newtonian model of physical phenomena
Has he won the Nobel Prize
Studying atoms and he said there's no matter is such that at our jumps back and forth
What
Fluxus
And that's why
What if
Realize the secrets of quantum physics and how to harness the power
We already know the observer effect shows us that subatomic
Particles are sometimes
And sometimes their waves
Moves into another dimension
Your bank account is an observer effect
Your bank account isn't Observer
Are you trying to tell me
That if I were to put my money in a box
With a cesium atom
Like sometime
Play 56
Could be all the money or none of the money
The amount of money that's in your bank account is a function of whether or not you're observant
If you're not observing at the way funk
Collapses naturally
No I got it
Estimated are you telling me that we're stuck in this do Tony and
Physics pointer video
Oh my God I do like that though
Alex is trying to get you to transcend CNN and Barack Obama trying to get you to
The f*** off from Dakota in physics
Slightly different agenda
Play you can break out of
If you just use the observer effect course
Your bank account is an observer effect
Thousands of people realize this and they all break out of
Servitude
Thousands of people realize that they
Change
Practices you can change the education system that
Once people start using The Power Of Consciousness to experiment on this reality and go if
Affected
Particles
Consciousness creates reality iCandy pattern myself from the world be transformed by the renewing of your mind
I can use the power of consciousness
Thermistor to recreate my life
They don't want us to know they don't want us
Start to test the power of consciousness
And say
Can I create this new business this new movement
Increase my business bigger and better
Right now
That kids too thirsty for this
Does plug
Holy kiss
Answer I have to tell you something right now I haven't been to
Did the greatest machine in the history of the United States tell me tell you something this simple machine
Can fit on your desk
So I can sit on your deck
And it will take whatever Rock
You find Weatherby LED
Weatherby sodium Weatherby
Sedimentary doesn't matter and it will take that Roxanne transmogrified into gold
Wow
Imagine what would happen if a thousands of people had these devices in their home every morning they would wake up
This is aspirational bulshit
Yep there's one person who's making a lot of money off
I just love like
Dislike you can sense it it does come to a head a little bit
Towards the end
Like
Alex
Is kind of getting
Being fed up with how much
He's promoting the website
You should go to a little bit too much
Only played a few clips
Since about it tonight then I
Concluded
Another thing that Alex doesn't like
Wouldn't like is
Directions to be a really
Comfortable taking over the show
I got a daughter she's
1617 months old everything's happening too
Finding out the secrets of the pharmaceutical industry isn't going to save us
Physical body there's no such thing as death
We're the imagination of ourselves we're already in the simulation belief control that reality
Reset Wars
Is showing the first but we are no longer in peace
Real players is Christ intended to me
Cam right now sign up
Wow I just I know Alex at well enough
From his
Yeah serving his work he does not like it when other people go to Breck
Kiko's to buy job buddy
You're taking my job yeah
Insulting all boys
Respect
And I love it
Where is it where somebody
Who works soap
Lee evil
I would be better but
What you going to do enjoy it though because I think there's a
Inherent tension
That exists here
Between these two people
First of all their worldviews are completely incompatible
Maybe because
Nick needs promotion and Alex needs money
But maybe they can
Get over these
Fundamental differences they have or at least pretend to
But it will be a problem
Yeah it's going to be tough
Hang around with time and time is an illusion and so is Death guy all the time
Also like if you just go through his YouTube channel I swear everything is so f****** repetitive
Over and over again with
Just clickbait titles
Yeah yeah literally
I just imagine hanging out with him would get old
Oh yeah
Then maybe you'll be fun
Towards the end of the day interview that they have
Alex
It's kind of realizing like we have got to do
We really haven't gotten too much of any
Maybe we sighted
Two articles
Fauci flip-flopped on masks
It's true there's also the ASU study that they were misrepresenting
Get back let's get back to this
So I want to continue here with some of these are
There's so many in
This one fascinating Alex
This is about
Energy
Human behavior
And
It says quote
Wow
Attention
Should be toward
Human performance
Loading
Electro
Magnetic
In an electromagnetic field effect remember we are all just an electromagnetic field
Play manipulator electrical field
That's what it's saying right this is a non-lethal energy weapon
So this is from a document I can find cited on
All kinds of sketchy
Conspiracy websites but they really just use the same quote
And the clean the source is
Creations on the title Airforce 1982 final report on biotech
Technology research requirements
4 Aeronautical Systems through the year 2000
I'm noticing
Pattern that most of them don't have links
Even when
This report is real
It's a real document it was prepared by the Southwest research
Institute in San Antonio with cooperation
From the Air Force Aerospace medical device
It was released
On July 30th 1982 and it has never been class
As you might expect
From clues in the document
Title this is a study of potential issues that could come up for future pilot
Which could have Biotin
Technological solutions
This document does indeed say quote
Initial attention should be directed toward organ-specific thermal loading
And electromagnetic field effect
Books like Jake
Or what I would like all dumb.
Just choose to read that and not pay
Alexa
Subsequent work should address the
Possibilities of directing and interrogating mental function
To provide revolutionary capability to defend
Kostelac
When this document says that initial attention to be direct
Did towards thermal loading and electromagnetic
It's saying that these things
Are things to be concerned about pilot of the future possibly being up a
Anyone who's as much as looked at this document or read the title critic
Would know that
Variable
Conspiracy theorist tickets
Too far and then
Southwest at the spin-off into an airline
Didn't see that coming
This specific word comes from a section of the text titled radiation environment
I'll read you the first paragraph
Graph of that sucks
Electromagnetic and particulate radiation produced by nuclear weapons high-energy lasers and futurehype
Powered pulsed radiofrequency radiation systems
Represent
Potential anti-personnel devices for the year 2000
Then beyond
Lasers and rsr systems
Add a new dimension of crew vulnerability that clearly requires protective devices
Hamilton Realty
For hardening
Normal aircraft system
That's what this is about
It's not about developing
Beamed energy to change human behavior get inside the brain
Another thing that's important
The point out is that the exact wording that Jake is using doesn't match the actual text
The documents
I know that he's reading this from one of the can
Conspiracy blogs
They just missed quotes
The text
And takes it out of
Depth of his research on the topic that he cares he's for
He's pretending to care so much about it this guy
The f****** loser
Right right so the document says like hey let's
Think about what might blow up our planes later and he turned that into hey let's create weapons to
Control people's brain
Okay as erroneously is this Jake has revealed to the world that either he's
Read this document needs intent
Lying about it or he hasn't read it
And misrepresented quote on a dumb conspiracy blog is good enough for him to try to pay
Pants off to his audience
Is proof of a grand mine
Control plot that the government is hatching
Convince you
Figueroa physical being in that death is real
This dude straight up the worst I just can't handle this b*******
Yeah
I want.
And I'm finding these document
It's right that is an issue
And I understand that megathrust
Have you thought about the
Perhaps
It is
An observer for
And so when you're looking at the document
They say what
You want them to
But when you're not
The documents they say what they say Dan
It's all about
Being an electromagnetic
Wakefield
Alright I got to go
It goes on
This document goes on according to Jake
And it goes on it says by using very low-frequency electromagnetic radiation
The waves way below radio freak
Quincy's on the electromagnetic spectrum
Found they can induce the brain to release
Regulating chemicals
FedEx Field
And they could
Put people into a stupor
Take a singing at the report goes on to say this but it doesn't
That's not from this
Report at all
That's a reference
Said the earlier thing you was talking about from the 1997 article in
US News & World Report
That Jake was lying about earlier
That's the one about Aldo
Bird who claimed that he used electromagnetic waves to release histamine and rats
The article does use the word stupor but it doesn't say that he could put human
Into a stupor
The sentences quote we could put animals into us
Jake is mixing up his shity sources and he's not even siding them correctly because much like Alex he's a lazy liar
But the article apparently goes on
And it goes on to say
Many of the non-lethal weapons under consideration utilized
Infrared sound in electric
Magnetic
Including lasers
Microwave
Radio
Frequency radiation
For visible light.
Brainwave
Welcome to the 5G world is not about controlling robot
That's a side issue it's about controlling Titus
Your conscious in their own
Ashley
Getting more upset control
So this also isn't from the same text to Jake was talking about and it's not even from that usnewsandworldreport article to jump to
This is supposed to be a quote from dr. Burrell
Barbara Rosenberg from 1994 in
Any bulletin of atomic
Scientists
The bulletin of the atomic scientists is pretty cool in that they have a backlog of all their tables
Contents going back to 1945
It's really easy to access
Possibly even cooler the group makes these bulletins available on Google Books
So they're pretty easy to find
Wow the article that the quote comes from is titled non-lethal weapons May violate
Treatise
Let's just stop and enjoy that this is actually an article that's arguing that developing non-lethal weapons in many ways
Other countries have a violation of international law
Believer
That's grey
More to the point disco doesn't appear in that text at all
This is absolutely the consistent attribution given to this quote on
Conspiracy blogs but the article that exist
In this issue of the bulletin of the atomic scientists
Says enough
Sing of the sore
This is the only article in the journal that was written by Barbara Hatch Rosenberg in 1994 as the citation is
Constantly given so we can't possibly be wrong about the attributes
Most recent article before this was a 1987 and then after that she came back for an article in 2006
So
Vigorous schedule
This is the only one that could possibly be being referred to by the conspiracy websites
There's another article on this issue about non-lethal weapons
Include this quote either
I kind of think it might be fabricated or deeply misattributed and I am not really entirely sure which
It is
Pretty sure Thomas Jefferson
That's
The end of the alleged quote is quote
The current surge of interest in electromagnetic and similar Technologies makes the adoption of a protocol explicit
The outlawing the use of these dehumanizing weapons
Urgent matter
Nikes
What appears to be the position
Dr. Rosenberg
And the journal itself generally
I don't
Text of the quote
He's referring to concert
Conspiracy blogs
It definitely doesn't come from the source
Set the blog save it a comes
From
I'm not entirely sure but
He doesn't use actual
Does
Fairly accurately
Depict what dr. rosenberg's is worth but that's also talking about advocating for international laws against these
Which would take away us offer until you know it should be opposed to that
Some kind of a complicated beat
All I do know for sure is that Jake is trying to pass this off as part of the document they're covering went
Together completely unrelated and out of context
And sometimes possibly apply
Apocryphal quotes
Really bad work yeah that's very frustrating
It didn't give me a lot of Hope
Ford reset Wars wars pretty quickly
So Alex
So what's talked about to have God made us we have free will but he also yellow
Spell yourself on your body
You on yourself
Jeffrey will mind control yourself
Somebody else
More money from a different Revenue stream
I'll steal it
I don't know about you but I feel like having someone yell at me that I'm free to mind control myself sounds a lot
I like a guy trying to intimidate me into taking part in his mind
Control game
I wonder if Alex intentionally didn't tell the audience
But Jake's main profession is being happened
Just because that would be really suspicious
Think I might be a possible choice
So this is where thing
Get ugly
But really ugly because they don't really argue but you can tell you can feel
You can feel something
Palpable to Jake is trying to Barrel in
Yet another plug
Listen to how Alex Cuts him off this is amazing
Consciousness
We are creating your own enslaving by saying we're screwed we can't do it as controlling us
Audrey don't just give
The power
Open a browser.
Surviving the thriving dermis
Have you ever heard Alex
Interrupt a plug
I've never
That sounded browser
Listen up listen up you just go up there and you click open a new tab
Jesus you're just click open that tab
Jesus
That's all by shut up
That might be a first
Oh man and when it says
When it says close all tabs to the
The devil you do not address ask again
No sir you close all those tabs one of the
Primary rules of Griffin
Thing is
Don't interrupt
The plug to plug
Apparently he's being so excessive with these plugs but I always have to break that rule
That's amazing
The documents
You know
We have so many of them I mean it's
Takis
15 hours
Crazy is there a
Metaphysically
Doing all this everybody
There's something weird with
Black magic
Okay I got
So stupid why do you think what do you think that all of these global
Conspiracy theorist that I've
I'm talking about right now.
Working literally for the devil until on it's over
Why do you think they wanted
5 minutes
Dumb
Pointless conversation put
I think there's
Black magical
About the idea that Alex is complaining
They haven't gotten to the documents and then instead of getting into documents he talks
Documents that they haven't gotten it do our
Yeah
Abusive also that it would take a lot longer
For them to explain those.
Give it to us certainly if they waste time like this I mean it's almost like they're asking you to be great
Grateful to them for not getting into the
I've already lost
Nothing much more entertaining show so dumb
So we have one last clip hung Cayenne
It's Jake
Doing another one of these
Manipulative tricks
In order to sell reset Wars
Open a new private window to the Lord this is incredibly abuse
And that's why it feels
Watching this right now
You feel angry you feel afraid
You feel doubtful that we're going to win
Remember who you are
Is literally a rental car for your soul
Energy never created or destroyed and when all of us start to wake up
Can you go to reset
Cam right now
Restart being renewed
The transforming nevermind
We will realize we create reality
Do not control us
They cannot win
That's
Just
Disgusting
Wow
If you out there feel like you're missing something
You know what you're really missing is entering my revenues
This commercial should be on at 4 a.m. this is when we should be listening to this
In 2015
I think dr. group
Would come in for like infomercial
And like it would just be an hour of them talking about his product
Yep
It's not nearly as disgusting as
He's really f***** up this is
Beyond over-the-top
It's
Counter to Alex
His career
I just I'm I'm
I'm blown away by this
This is a longer episode of the reasons because I think that this is
It could represent a turning point like
I really could
I don't think I
That way much
Over the course of
The time of us doing the show but like this is a sea change
Weird sincere
Yeah
Not then this is a really
Weird
Scrabble
He's willing to engage in this kind of b*******
But I'm I'm
You know I'm fascinated
To see what they end up producing
But I also
Haven't watch this
I am really
On
Sure I guess
Confident in their ability
Blowhard self-help
Stuff probably hot and then miss
Quoting
Thanks but probably what most of it
Going to be
I don't know
Iru I'm still excited
To do it cuz I want to
You know
Critic critic
Hypocritical of you to Alex's
Life's work
I know it's not
It's not better
Well I mean
Okay
So at least one doctor group was scamming
He exchanged
This guy is exchanging the belief
Of goods
Sprite and that's rude
Yeah that's rude I know.
It doesn't do s*** but at least they're s*** there
You know
Good
I know you're selling
Like a B vitamin or whatever
It's fine
Police that your bank account is magical might kill you
It certainly could lead you to negative actions
It could lead you to believe
Things that
Could leave your bank account looking a bit worse
If You observe it I'll look at it look at it
Yeah and then and then just emerge
Urging of
Ideas about like
Uno depersonalization of yourself
Impossible
Merging that with Alex's Louvre and the ideas that he expresses on a regular basis
Better so intensely violin
And full of wrecks
Tribution
Target
At the enemy
And all this
I just think it's
Powder Keg that
I don't know if they realize the kind of
The fire that is being played
I mean when you're saying the enemy is killing you
You know who they are I'm not telling you to take any violet
It combines with
Death isn't real
You're Invincible if you choose to be
And only if you are manifesting negative emotion
Can you fail
Unlife is real
That's not good
I hope this is a small blip
And maybe like a little side project that Alex's get
Getting paid for
But I don't think it is
For one thing
One of the things they bring up
In the conversation
Is that they had talked originally about doing something about
And like Financial scam
Yeah and financial Market
I'm so like they had originally thought about doing that but then they decided to do this
Series
And there was an implication that they're going to do more series is
So I don't know if they will
Cuz I
Don't know
How much does going to set the world on fire
B
I think the intention is to possibly do more
Work like
Like the
Recent Wars
For under the
Category or the heading of retard
I have these series isn't like this one's about you
Your soul or whatever
I mean I think there'll be a certain point where I'll just
Let Alex
Go do his thing
Feel like if he starts becoming like a spiritual self-help
Preacher
That's not us man
If you want that s*** let's see okay well we could do the B
Scam and get people to buy
Or we could do the fake God scam and get
People to buy nothing
Actually think that it was
Against
Oh I think their position would be opposed
Sure
Well somehow they would be wrong about that too or something yet they'll be right about the point but wrong about the reasons why
Exactly pretty
It's been long enough
Terrified of the prospect of what's
Succumbed
Excited when Alex is pretend
Deprived
Pretense of actual document
Leave this
Cold
I found very little of substance
But it was still fun to read a bunch
Maybe they'll talk about those.
Fingers crossed we'll see if Reese Awards even really
Places that take a second
Those documents aren't even real
Nothing's real
That's where the episode should have just cut off
Tell them it isn't real
Yeah we have death isn't real in life is a simulation. Camuy also or on a Unreal
Website call Twitter
So
Watch out for the Devil is worried about the fact that he got kicked off Twitter
What are we doing
Score cantero rundus
Which are real
Holding
Alex
Birthstone colors