Air Jordan 5 swetik
I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
The altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
Text June
What's up
What's playing
Is a little bit if he kind of
I'm not proud of this
But I decided to order Papa
Papa John's
Curious
Maybe a decade probably haven't had Papa John's
Builders memories of the garlic sauce
Emily
I don't I have an Edward memories but I don't like Eminem
I certainly don't like the man but a pizza that would be around and Shady places
Easter Pizza
Yeah and I did garlic sauce
It just like
It sticks out in your mind
What's up
Nothing nothing lived up
To know
The Beatles terrible
Imagine no I mean Chris was okay
The garlic sauce was not as good as I remember the garlic butter
When I was growing up
The Pizza Hut buffet was the
Height
Diamond that's the best
Pizza Hut got rid of the buffet
Why why even go KFC had a buffet for a while
Every Friday Pizza Hut
Didn't have the
Little bit later we had to CiCi's Pizza
Columbia Focus
See how many
Pizzas and cinnamon rolls
That's fine
Pizza Hut buffet because
It's gone in your memory your kind of like
That was pretty great remember CiCi's Pizza
Garbage while you were there when you were old when you were a kid
Garbage do you think that because it's still excessive
You could actually go revisit it order a Pizza Hut pizza
Probably
Papa John's
Terrible
Play brakes parties
Affirming that
What's up
Dan is I don't know if
Me talk about
This before but there was a live-action Cowboy Bebop
Oh yeah yeah
Came out and I've watched all of it
It is a bright spot
John Cho as spike is incredible
Everything else is kind of so-so Yoko kanno
Upton another level
He started as one of the parents guide
Right holyshit I think he started there and then he went to Harold and Kumar and then
Really good act
Flash Forward show
It was a disaster
But the problem with it and the reason that the whole show is garbage
Is because they did my man vicious and Julia dirty
Oh no
In this show
Those are characters in the original show you meet Julia only at the very end and she's
In the first time you made her cuz she's the like
Long lost love interest The One That Got Away in a horrible death
Incident kindest
Situation behind
And then she shows up
Writing a car getting chased by bad guys and then firing back and then
A badass Thelma and Louise instantly
You love Julie
In the show she's like
Videos and then vicious vicious is the shark from Jaws you only see him when someone's about
Get their head cut off
In the show
He's like I'm going to help you do
I'm sorry
Okay
If you like I'm not going to watch it based on
Alright
This is an episode of June 30th and July 1st
This is a Monumental episode I must say
Because
A wrench gets thrown into the gears
As it were
Some things that we've been tracking in the past
We may have been
A little wrong about something
And we will find out about that here today but
Let's say hello to
Does new walk
So first
Jenny Bento
Next Messi the disciple of Lady Selene thank you so much you are now policy wonk
Engagement I love you
Dress! Thank you so much right now if I was you on
I just
Psychicmix mr. toad loves double-layered carrot cake thank you so much you are now apology walk
Very much mr. toad I'm really worried that sometimes like
Names like that that I've liked
Right
Triggered an assassin or something
But that's a code word
The sleeper agent somewhere you have to read the first letter of each
The names in order to get the actual message I'm very worried sometimes people send me fairy
Cryptic names
Say hello to so sludge Factory hello
Business
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
We jump in here
End of the month
The 30th
Today
Is the 30th
At 6
Dash 3003
AO3
Three years after Y2K
We started to
Beginning of the episode
Videos going to have which is
Really bizarre
Constable
You like deliver summonses and stuff like I think you can do traffic stops
If you're a constable think so yeah I think I could give people tickets in Jackson
At least
Yes okay good so Alex's
Cameraman Mike Hansen
He's the guy who went along with
Bohemian Grove
Alex is a long time
Buddy and noted weirdo
Apparently
He
Is running a giant firework stand in order to fund his run for constable
And apparently he also has a
A little bit of a history of failing to run for offices
In the past
Fancy himself a bit of a political
I also ran
What's strange about that
Is that
Constable being a surly British word I don't think there's a more American thing you can do than run a fire
Work stand
Running to become a cop
That's the most of the Declaration of Independence
It's not there fireworks in someone else's
I think
Just have a job at this firework stands
The story that Mike is going to come on until
Is that
He heard some noises in the night
Not sure
Voices in the night he thought it was like an animal or something
A red underwear and found people robbing
Replace the three of them at gunpoint and then got the police to come and they arrested him
Wowhead so
They're thrilled cuz this is good guy with a gun Second Amendment
Constable
Play Bay
It might be spawn Khan for his confer
Yeah
It's so boring interview and like a 2 tells the story
And guess what he comes back like 2 days later and tells the same story
Ridiculous it is it's a good story
Got some news out of the UK
Hear from
Outlet called the Scott
Set the Scotsman
They've appointed Hanson is constable
Story about
Grappling
Article
With a giant
Going on
Basically they're all dancing around naked
I failed to find
Evidence of this
Does grand religion at this point is definitely is lost
In the UK it's probably Harry Potter ism
I just want to say and I want to get this out there okay
Dancing around naked
Is a long way from an orgy
Okay now it's not as far away from an orgy is dancing around with your clothes on sure but it is still farther away
Aventador J
Yeah that there couple steps
Still requires
Alex doesn't deal with that and whatever there's a lot of animals that are going missing
Have a citation on any of this I think it's just
Stuff sort of satanic panic
Some nonsense sounds like it
Alex has a commercial that he plays on the show that I found
A little out of place
I'll see if you can tell why
Financial
What
Invest in the Euro says the most nationalist man has ever been
Invested the Euro guy who thinks the EU is evil
I think it's going to go you know that you could be shorting it right that would be ideologically consistent you be like
Anti Soros
Right there recommend
Poised to rise
Yeah I thought that was very very strange
You see have like
Herb companies that are trying to save the Christian Remnant in America
Weird
Thing or the weird box or whatever the f*** that guy
Freqbox
Because you're selling Euros what is going on
This is ridiculous
I can't imagine somebody hearing a commercial from a Financial Group about buying or selling stock
Talking thinking
Well obviously they want me to make
Money I better call and get more info
Strangers making life. My best interest in mind
Alex gets his call from a guy they're discussing
Context
Of the night before the caller Alex I believe both of them
I've seen a documentary about like ancient
So
Sparta is on the mind
And this is where we jump
On all of our military vehicles
Prior we now have like a chef
And this is something I've noticed
Shields of
Tyrell
And I'm really concerned as to why we brought the
I'm sorry
Now
Watch out that's what you think
Cover up they've been trying to cover up that homosexual death called for years
Oh my God
The colors making an interesting association between the military and the Greek letter lamp.
But I think this caller is a little
Simplistic Bob just like ice from the
The Shield or whatever
If you look into it you'll find a bunch of fraternities and sororities that are military in nature that use the letter Lambda in
Her name is not the first letter like
In the case of Kappa Lambda Chi they still refer to themselves as Lampton
The first woman's military sorority is Lambda beta Alpha and they even have a side organization
Four family members in ROTC
Sea Cadets called
The orchids of Lambda
The letter Lambda is been adopted by military throughout West
Turn history largely because it was the symbol that was on the shield of the spark
Not of all
Greek
By the other city-states
I had different letters or
Symbols
And the Spartans had this because it was
Capital city
I'll ask Damien
The story of the Battle of Thermopylae and b302 held back the Persian army
Xerxes
They've become
The image of efficient
Successful military force
There's a lot of aspects to the story where the details are B fudge but I'm not here to take away any of the
Leonidas
Let him have it
Either way the letter Lambda at
Is it safe is very powerful
That's what the hours for around the shields legitness
The weather lambdas had a particular
Significant ever since
Like throughout West
Western history in our military uses the letter 26
Signify
Company Vehicles belong to depending on the direction that the
Llr the Lambos they say bud
I think Alex might have a slightly Elementary understanding of Sparta
Culture but if his problems with them are that they were a homosexual death call to head slave
You probably wouldn't like Athens
Or any Greek city-state much more
Yeah that was all
The great the Great Hero Achilles only agrees to re-enter the Trojan War after Hector kills his lover petropolis
And they were videos
In the theban Army there were 150
The gay male couples who formed the sacred band of Thebes
And the theban Army actually
Defeated Sparta Sparta in the battles of Takara
Andaluca look at Tura
And in the process they actually unseated Sparta is the Dominus
Force in Greece
There were many aspects of homosexual
Chips in ancient Greece
Read to them at all
Being a death cult I'm not sure what Alex means by that so I don't know how to respond
They were cultured deprioritized military strength
Text but I don't know if that make
Make some a death call
And that's for the slavery thing Sparta definitely wasn't the only city-state doing that s***
They pretty much all day
Including Athen
I think of history and
This case in particular is just a Pie Pop Culture
Things you see in like movies or TV shows
Cuz what he saying is just dumb
Yeah but not track
Even me
Very less
Those Greek
City-states
They weren't like
Grease they didn't get along very well
There was a period of tension
Home
Anyway
Alex
Moves on from wax
Philosophical about Greek
History
Right now
In 2021 we know
For snacks
Vaccine
A 2000
Okay
Just doing this over and over and over again it's always this
Wow
20 years
20 years this is your life
For Alex would be
Just the same two people being like
This is the same clip in 2003 but you got in 2005 completely different
Contact never really actually comes
The past
Oh Lord Fletcher's before his life his eyes before he dies and it's just the same flavor
Over and over
Metaphorically that
So Alex gets another call
Good better call
On the show which is fun
Except for the X
Four callers
Cuz they suck
Particularly this guy who's a bit homophobic
Tell you what's going on up here I'm in Cincinnati Ohio
And everyday is a newspaper.
Newspaper publisher inquire
Change it to the Bentley hell on Earth reported everyday
Supreme Court upholds
Backpages
Story about
Call Bahama Cycles in San Francisco
Two little boys
Talk about
How many homosexual couples
Raising children
Alabama
Holyshit
So yeah I think I've made note in a previous episode they like for a long time Alex's had this bizarre theory about there being a
Industry
Run by the homosexuals to take straight people's children
By way of CPS
Which is
Is gross
It's it's
Angry
Yeah I mean
The craziest part of that is
You know you were
Remember 2003 and that kind of homophobia was commonplace you know and it wasn't even just
Tacitly
I permitted you know Obama famously is like I'm evolving on gay marriage you know like that kind of thing
Much different just ate
18 years ago
It's true
It's true I think
Yeah I think there's a difference between
Blatant homophobia are even active
Maybe people didn't
Examine well
I am
Political
Driven homophobia
And I think the I think the
See a good deal of the ladder
Here on Alex's show
This color sucks
And another color which is
If this is real interesting
They came out in 2000
Free movie
Is traveling
New York
Couple things
Preview for a movie coming out called
Extraordinary Jen
Full moon
Sean Connery thing
About it
They finally ran the long enough cookware
Introduce
League of the
Extraordinary Gentlemen are
What does that mean
That was one of them
Captain Nemo
Dr. Jekyll
You know it's like a war
These are news
Superheroes
They're going to save the world
What
Just now
Wait you pointed out that it was a comic book League of Extraordinary Gentlemen comic book
The problem with the interpretation is being given is that the characters in the movie aren't all villains
41 the character played by Sean Connery Alan Quartermaine is not a villain
Novels that he's featured in
Unless you look back through very assertive evolve prism of
Colonialist might not have been the intention of
Outside or type what a big game hunter and adventurer
Many people eventually noted that
He's one of the foundational influences
Character of Indiana Jones who's definitely not mint
To be a villain although
Doesn't schedule
Captain Nemo also in the villain unless you think the people of non-european Heritage are automatically evil
You know was a member of The Avengers who are crime Fighters
Kind of her deal the invisible-man wasn't the great dude and mr. Hyde certainly got up to no good but bi
Idea that these were literally like all villains isn't that there was a literary figures from. Of time they're all extraordinaire
A banded together to fight bad guys
It's kind of their whole thing
The movie itself has a bit of a sloppy re-creation with the inclusion of Tom Sawyer as a secret service agent
Dorian Gray is brought in as a villain
Yeah but the real villain is Moriarty is the arch-nemesis of
Of Sherlock Holmes
The bad guy is the big bad guy for Sherlock Holmes
Yeah this isn't the movie about making the villains into Heroes
It's just that really flawed interpretation of this trailer
The color saw
But man I'm so excited
About Alex
Text banking there devil worshippers
I'm at what
I want to hear the review
I want to hear that review
That's so funny that he's the inspiration for Indiana Jones cuz you have that same thing now we're like
You you look back
On
It belongs in a museum and you're like yeah belongs in a museum and then as you evolve 20 years later you like
No
Repatriated
Sure
Another thing about that too is that
Sean Connery plays Alan Quartermaine news an inspiration
It's all coming together turn down office
Hello
That guy lot of money left on the table lot of money
Last year and this was this was traveling
We certainly more troubling than
Mike and his firework
I mean this is Outta control
Gerstacker
Aurora
I'm not going to cover this too much
Because this is actually the story of a really nasty divorce
From the information I can gather it's a situation where there was this divorce going on as a part of that there was a pretty messy
Custody dispute
I don't want to
Do you know try and delve into this parsley because you
Cases of domestic issues like this
It's really difficult to get a full sense
Of exactly what's going on from the outside
Haven't been said I can find no evidence of his neighbor is getting into trouble for arriving
Their children taken away because they wouldn't snitch on
I did find some interesting stuff and trying to learn more about this case
The first thing that I found was that stored in a blog up
Trying to get his child back title the kidnapped
Sun. Blogspot.com
I don't know what was up on that side
Because the earliest snapshot in the way-back machine is from when he had already
Change the title of the blog
Helping me reconcile
There's only one post on there from April 20th 2050
It starts quote
I apologize for my previous post on this blog which I hereby retract
In total
I was wrong to try to force the issue I should have made it my goal
From the beginning to reconcile this matter private
I would guess it Wrecker
Compiling the matter privately wouldn't
Involve going on Alex's show to push a crank
Conspiracy about your divorce that Alex
Used to fuel his own conspiracy theories about how the job protect
Service Steel
People's children to give them to homosexual couple
Autumn mostly unrelated note
I was able to find a transcript of public hearing being held by the Travis County
Commissioner's Court
In July 2000
The main piece of business was about it
Easement on a lot
Near Westlake Hyland
After that
There was no opportunity for open Quest
And even came
Stuart gerstacker
He came in hot
Quote
I come in peace and humbly
Fatshark five-star Stars
I come in peace and humbly invoke the blessings of almighty God
I've come to deliver a message of peace and New Hope
I forgive you I love you and I want you to be happy
You still have to repent your sins and make restitution from what you've stolen from me and others in the community
And I'm going to continue to come down and exposing the truth
Your continued presence is an Abomination against this land
We all know that Margaret Gomez stole her seat from Mike Hansen
I was there on Election night when the computers are repeatedly crashed
Program didn't do vote tallies
Pop sounds like 20/20 familiar what side sorry people you are to allow these abuses think
Continue
So I guess
At this point my cancer dad moved on from losing the election
Constable in 2003 to losing an election
The County Commissioners Board of 2007
Switches
Surprising maybe progress I do appreciate I come in peace
Beating the opening line
For a few sentences later to wind up with
I think you're an abomination
That might be a little bit less peaceful quote
Your actions are an abomination in the eyes of God and man
You'll become onuris to the people because of your continued abuses I now declare a state of emergency caused by the breakdown
Sound of lawful power in Travis County
Emergency can only properly be rectified by the people of Texas acting independently in our Sovereign capacity
I'm so Stewart declared a state of emergency in Travis County back in 2000
I'm surprised I didn't make the news
It's like Undeclared did he ever take the smell might still be active
Isn't that kind of guy
Who comes in with problems without solution
Call God quotes
The correct this intolerable situation I'm taking this opportunity to announce the new independent state Gathering
Exactly one year from today on the eve of July 4th 2008 we the people are going to peacefully surround the Texas
Capitol building
And our Travis County Courthouse complex and we're going to camp out and have a huge party
There will be large and it will be large and I'll be nothing like you've ever seen
And it will not end until all of you have gone away
Then we the people will constitute a new Republic
Together we the people will pee
Peacefully shake off these tyrants
Give the world in Independence Day that will not ever be forgotten
It's so awesome to cuz in the transcript you use either the board
Commissioner board response
Yeah and it was like are we invited to this party
That is a good response
And I'm not going to take seriously anything is
Same as interview with Alex and I think it's best we just move along
Yamin.
No that's all that's a lot of hurt
A lot of hurt man but I
I think I think you can look at that
County commissioner
No transcript
Activity response
Getting get a good
Make sense of the picture
You can see us blog that he had
We just trying to say that his wife kidnapped his son and then
Opposed begging
For reconciliation and apologizing
Yeah
Not worth it
So we'll move on
Update
From a caller who called in a couple episodes back
Good afternoon.
Stomach called
I told you
State of my tiger cub
Siberian tiger
Record after that
The doors were locked
Doors
Report deer
Court dates
Or the decision
The judges are making Oran
Or before a full moon or new moon
Daughter doing witchcraft
The first people
Hollywood
It's a little confusing to the guy but his Tigers taken away
Doing witchcraft
Step because of the Moon
Obviously
If it's happening on a full moon or the new moon
And I don't mean like you you would look at this and Alex probably want to be like
All right look I don't know what you're thinking here that the new moon means that they're doing witchcraft
Harry Potter on the solstice mean something
So he can't he has no leg to stand on here
Too far the new moon
Harry Potter
Anyway this guy witchcraft
Jordan ways tigers
Don't think that the judge also needs witchcraft
When he can just
Sign an order
Yeah I think it's really great though being able to go back and listen to these episodes and see stories developing with collars
Call Annie give updates
You realize colors anymore in the in the modern-day Carlos
Do two calls in all the time but not really
There's no story to it he's just mad about various
Geopolitical things
This is much more fun of switchgrass
Is a little bit like where are they now every you every few weeks yet so the witchcraft
Baby gets Alex
Send to the sort of mood or he wants to talk about devils
Stuff
I don't know what you're talkin
About here
Allure.com
Cam
Women in in
Children
Terraria
Patience
Delete all of the couch all the way up
What now
Dying
I guess
They covered up the story really well cuz I
I feel like there's no way I would not have known about the great swath of women without Hearts being dug up
Across Europe
Going back to the conservative leadership in France the government
Everybody getting taken down
Constable
Left and right
Themes
I feel like we would suck if this were something
And I was a big
Deal
Or happened
Arabi song
Memory of it I couldn't find anybody
Like reports November emaciated people showing up
Saying they were in a castle with demons
No no
I I don't know I don't know if anybody has a lead on this I'd be willing to
The Explorer it but I couldn't find anything
Sometimes you really do think maybe this is just a recurring
Dream Alex
You know and it's it has nothing to do with anything in real life when we just present or could be a chain email or something like that
Hell yeah it's it that it doesn't have to be strictly connected
Did to reality
So here's where
I have
Eat a little crow
Okay
We've been speculating
About
Alex
Having a different
Backstory
About satanism
In 2003 that he doesn't present
That might not be at
Rock and roll crowd
Coronavirus
Beautiful Darkness
People trying to recruit him into Satanism when he was younger
It's just a story that he tells
Less frequently in the past
Still part of his
His story and it's interesting to me
It's very it's
But also there's fundamental differences between this and the way he tells it in the present
Who Among Us has a purse
It's no story that they've told for 20 years that is not
Some changes
Is to it I think
One as important as
Constant recruitment
To the devil that's a good point that one would stick in your memory
The way I see the fundamental differences
Exists in this
Telling it in the future telling
Is
That hear it could just be a bunch of weirdos who are into Satan
Metal was big at this point when Alex was in high school
You could see
People who are inside
Dunno darkness and
Wearing antlers helmet poster on their wall
You can see that
In the present
The way he tells the story The Devil is actually
Telling these people to
To get him
Because he is psychic and he's going to be important the gods Mich
They are directed by the Dead
There's a little bit of functional difference
Prince
Right Right Alright also I think this is a different in
As much as there were multiple different groups
Strength to a recruit him into Satanism which is strength that is weird
Is apparently super into satanism
Together
Satanism I feel like that's
Although you don't bully the nerd Fitness
Bear I don't think you should do that
The conception that he's made
Is it like
All these groups of people within the high school are Satanist
Right now
You'd have to assume that they didn't all just one day.
Decide at school
We're going to become saved their parents probably have something to do with that
So Alec
Alex is tried to
Keep me this girl who wants to date him he's up she's over at her house
The dad
The bed is like hey
We should get as
Alex says no thank you which is fun he was polite
He believes in the Lord Jesus Christ
Thank you sir but I will.
Then
The police
Police start harassing him because
If you rejected
This called
Is involved with the Sickness
This whole town is so I could I could see him saying that it was just the rich people
Nope this is the police are involved in taking a but that's part of his backstory to is revealing the police were all corrupt right
Yeah but it is the the
Serta grounded version of it is that
He discovered that police were dealing drugs
And so that he blew the whistle on that in the police chief ran him out of town
He just described his childhood a lot like the movie Warrior
You know like
There's just different roving gangs around it is just trying to navigate where he's trying to get to
Yeah it's highly problematic
That's a good way
Is that that movie
Ohio
Looks like baseball players
So we're done with the 30th here we job
Up to July 1st
And Alex has some concerns
About COG
Aniline of 6
Succession of a governor
Neocon
Line of presidential succession
Wooing me
So I don't know Tom Ridge was the Secretary of Homeland Security beginning
In 2003
The issue that Alex is playing fast and loose with here is that that position didn't exist
Sprayer Tom Bridge
Since he was the first head of the Department of Homeland Security would just be
Create it
He was a Cabinet member and most of
The cabinet exist in the lineup
Succession so
It was felt that this position needed to be inserted into
The order
Senate Bill 148 passed on June 27th 2000
Can a thin line just after the attorney
But that's not all there is
List of the story
Counterpart
In the house HR 2319
That was introduced and it died
Committee
In 2006 the US code was amended to include
Secretary of Homeland Security in the line of succession
In 18th position
Or to put it another way
Personable
Why is that
Because in a very technical sense Alex is covering this news story
Like
We got some facts right
There is a real Bill a thin line for the
It makes some sense to assume the temp to pass the Senate it might get passed in the house too
Discussing that is a possibility is prudent
But I can still think if you listen to it the way Alex is talking about
Hamming it up a little bit dictatorship
I don't know if anyone cares who's
82 18th and lime it seems like
Except for the the Lone Survivor or the desert Survivor show
I think
I think that if we get to the 8th
On the list we have big problems
There's no country
Don't know if we could handle
Many people at the top of the Executive Branch the president
President the Speaker of the House the pro tempore president of the Senate
What's
Federal and 7th
Bye-bye Secretary of State Farm remember
If all of those people are dead
Let's just go home unless all of them are getting surgery at the same time maybe we could do it
Temporarily
Nathan Lyon be president that would be a big get for Kamala Harris
Arslan
I think we have bigger issues
Once once you're into like
Secretary of agriculture is becoming president
Yeah cuz what happened
Cause that
Is going to be a huge issue
Gets a call
Block calls
It's kind of it's kind of nice
Is this a little stretch
In
The question
About a clit
That is in Alex
Commercial for his documentary
Recording for the John Ashcroft lose your ride
Your liberties
Yes
Concentrate on that
There is no
Kangaroo court
I really don't want to be in the position of sounding like I'm defending John Ashcroft because believe me as a Missouri and I hate that dude
But
At the same time Alex Isley
And you can tell that he doesn't know where the
The clip that this guy talked about really even comes from age
Just trying to Spin A Yarn on the flight
Can hear that in the way.
He's pulling information out
Time to selling a DVD and a clip of Ashcroft was featured in the commercial
Play here
I just kept the rest of it into give you a little taste of how he was marketing his the materials at the time
I do like a good white
Slavery because
Slavery's not that bad
Sure about white slavery
I
I think you get a sense there from a scarf clip
It's just playing
You will lose your liberties
Helzberg testimony Ashcroft gave on December 6th
It's 2001 in front of the senate committee on the Judiciary
It's a three-and-a-half-hour video on
C-SPAN but after opening statement really only goes about 20
The full sentence that clip
Comes from is this
Since 1983 the United States government is defined terrorist as those who perpetuate premeditated politically motivated
Violence against
Baton Target
My message to America this morning then is this
If you fit this definition of a terrorist
Fear the United States
For you will lose your Liberty
Strategic and even though the Patriot Act sucks
And I hate it and I hate a strop
Alex has no idea what he's talking about him
I'm just making stuff up
Also there is no Patriot Act to but there is
Sister Act 2
So we know that Alex
Love's
Fake Thomas Jefferson
Now what do you think he thinks about
Possibly true Thomas Paine quotes
Oh I think he
Well Thomas Paine
I'm going to go and say
He loves them
Father
And Reserve order in the world as well as property
Thomas George Washington
So the clothes that Alex is using there is slightly a bridge
Here's the full of her
Supposed quietude of a good man is the Ruffian with the other hand
And arms like laws
Discourage
Then keep the invader
And the plunderer in awe and preserve order in the world as well as property
You can see that Alex's version is conveniently missing the words like laws
For some reason
Also this quote is in support of people having guns
Sure but the context of this is entirely
This is from a 1775 essay published in the Pennsylvania magazine
The entitled Fox on defensive War
It's essentially War propaganda for the fighting
The British
Persuade religious folks in the colonies
That it was right and just
For them to arm themselves to fight it
Defensive War
NFL religious liberty was on the line
If they didn't
Another important point to bring up
Scholars are not in agreement that this was actually Thomas Paine who wrote
This article
He was the editor of the magazine at the time and the essay was attributed only to quote a lover of peace
So many have assumed that he wrote of him
However in a
16 book titled new directions in Thomas Paine studies
The authors point out there many inconsistent things in this essay that point to it not being written by pain
The most compelling points are the TSA includes the Line quote
The reign of Satan is not ended
And it treats miracles in the Bible is having literal
Really happened with
Their counter to the well-established deism
Who's playing Express in his other writings like Age of Reason
Yeah it'll be very weird for paying to be like
Satan coming after me the literal Christian devil it's very inconsistent with the way he writes
Yeah another contact
Compelling reason to take that this wasn't an actual quote from Thomas Paine
It's just a person trying to convince religious people to fight it
Defensive work at the British
I don't know he's trying to overcome better that whole nasty Thou shalt not
Killpop
Of War
Got to get over
Depends
So I think
This is a Miss handling
Of this quote at very low
Guess what it gets worse
Another
Way worse handling of a
And then I've got another quote here
We used
Do not
Bernini
Youwin world
Apologize
Tres misquote down I ran into the expected problem at almost every website that used it was a very bizarre.
Cities ask website
Conspiracy theories of the quote is given with no citation
Her information when this head of the UN food programme said this or where
Finally I found a Blog
The claim that Catherine
Teeny the former executive director of the UN world food programme
I've said this at the un's fourth conference
Mozart fourth world conference on women
In September 1995 which was held in Beijing
This is already contradictory to Alex's citation that this quote was for 1997
Smells fishy
The fourth world conference on women
Did in fact take place in Beijing in 1995
You can find it
Painfully detailed collection
Information about the conference on the un's website
Including but not limited to
The text of remarks made by representatives from over 100 countries
The text of comments made by representatives of ngos as well as
Total transcripts of State
It's made by un representative
There's also a bunch of pictures and a video that no longer low
That should be their slogan Where the UN
Fully documented
I was able to find the transcript of the speech that Catherine bertini that quote comes from
Explain a few things about
Conference before we get to the actual words that she
She said
The conference was meant to attempt
Define solution
Sims 2 the problem
Severe gender
Inequality across the world
And what are the elements of that problem that was the
Discuss was ecrater food in
Security experienced by women in the developing world
Either due to systemic issues or even just cultural preferences for sons
That lead them to get in greater access to food
Education another
Necessities
Happy expensive
Daughters
Now that being said
Here is the full path
What was take
Quote
Let's Have No Illusion
We can easily change the underlying beliefs and prejudices that do so much damage to women worldwide
We cannot quickly chain
Attitudes but we can change Behavior
At the world food programme we've recognized what a valuable tool food Aid to be in changing Behavior
It's so many poor countries food is money
Food is power
And some of our most successful food a project we literally pay families who do not believe in educating their daughters
Descend those girls to school
A little free cooking oil can go a long way
We trade a 5-liter can of oil for 30 days of school attendance by a young girl
Yes it's bribery we don't apologize for that
We're changing Behavior
Your work even hoping opportunities to young girls
And that is all that
Every Small Change in Behavior will one day payoff in a change of attitude
So I think it's pretty self-evident what's happened here.
Conspiracy theorist who want to demonize the UN at every turn
I'm taking bertini's words and selectively edited them down in a way that was specifically designed to remove the context
What do you say
And make it seem is evil as
This altered version of the quote is posted on conspiracy websites and
Repeated by Alex with its origins of Steward or no
Citation given
That's making it harder for viewers to track down the source and judge it for themselves
On the one hand this is something that's designed to demonize the UN but the
Original statement bertini made was also Empower women
Around the world to have agents
Which is threatening to people like Alex
Who worked tirelessly in the service of a male-dominated society
By lying about the context of this quote you not only make a um look
You'll super
YouTube
I didn't doing so you turn the sentiment of the UN doing whatever it can
Cancel help women
Some kind of international racketeering and poisoning program
Xanax
I think that's
I don't know
It's hard to imagine
It's fully intentional but
It doesn't seem like a coincidence
Well I mean
Cuz what she
She saying is this
Okay when we give food out to the powers-that-be in whatever localized
Is National shanor or Triboro
Wherever we
Guess what it exacerbates the same
Inequalities that we've had four
From the beginning because men run though
So where is skipping past
We're going to be doing the most
Tactical thing week
Can do which is straight-up bartering
For education
It's not bright
Maria Trejo
You know I'm trading you
Draining you Orioles
So that everyone's future
Bertini even side steps that and just says like let's call it bribery cuz I have to have the argument
Accept the label but let's on
Understand what it is we're doing
And I just
I think that it's so wrong and so awful
Steve quote for trade the way Alex is for
Conspiracy theorist
Heaven when you dig deeper in
Find the actual quote see what it's actually about what
Conversation was
Where this conference
What what it was in service of
Haydocy like this is this is horse
This is
I don't know.
It's so dumb
That's such a great
Thing for her to have said though
Just f*** it
It's we got to do something practical
Because I don't care if my morality my personal morality
He says bribery is wrong
This is God we got to do something
This is garbage
Like it makes me feel like hey
F*** it
Let's just pool our money together
And bribe Joe manchin a little bit more than what everybody else is paying him and let's just get this done
You know like this
Find your corrupt
To ship will do
Play that game
And you know
I mean
I think
I was just drive up the bidding war and that no one would get anything
Right like if there if there were
Like sort of Market forces that were bribing people to
To not send daughters
To school it's developing world
Then you would end up
Situation where this bribery would only exacerbate the problem
It's just a we don't care to educate
Daughters
Perhaps less of a priority
Absolute also man talk about missed opportunities the US representatives that went
To that 1995 conference
Hillary Clinton
And Madeleine Albright
Videos about them that would have been more fun for him
It's always been there always been there man
So Alex
I think is going to little bit
Far afield
On the Harry Potter
Conspiracies
How far
I mean really
Where do talk about
From Belgium
So just call her is even like a man
I like you but I don't know about this Harry Potter stuff
Also he's wrong they didn't think it wrote the book sucker released every year on the solstice
His perception of it cuz
Fun stories
But I like
This whenever caller is
Somebody who is not
Like
Totally bought it
Summer is like I'm inclined to believe some of the things you say and I do believe that maybe the powerful don't have our intro
Tristan
The front of their their their lips
Put man Potter are you f****** kidding me
Are you are you going to come at me and tell me that the movie Witches starring what's what's their face
Is the 30 cuz broken Hocus Pocus
I have references
Is that is that like a
He's already complained about like Sabrina the Teenage Witch
Every Everything innocuous
Alex really want to win
From this caller
He wants to get him over onto his side and I don't think it's working
Grove
JK Rowling
Black magic
Real
Warner Campbell
Fidelity Financial symbol
All these things
AR
Disagree on this issue
ASU
Wall-to-wall
Okay and that is
Over
Long Wahlberg
I like I like the condescendingly Alex keep saying sir
I like how Alex is just
Just grasping at straws
Viacom symbol it's all fake
Little backbone
But I guess got to agree to disagree on this cuz
You're not going to change your mind and I'm certainly not going to change my mind
I do think it's
So funny to say I guess we'll have to agree to it. That's the most
Infuriating thing you can say to Alex
No cannot agree to disagree no you are wrong
And you have to accept it because
Hughes
Relation
Kinship with being right
Is so fragile
L A tenuous at Best Yet the idea that anybody could talk to him
And
Not
Agree with him
They either have to be like a paid by the anime
Or
It's impossible
He has to believe the games access to all of the most
The real truth
Or else
All this is bull
Okay
Here's a larger
Here's that infect maybe the largest
Okay
Magic is real
In Alex's estimation
He has
Real black magic books
She does is it possible for Alex to perform black magic and he simply chooses not to
I mean
Write at least in his mind
Right also text Mars is not the best reference you want to have for his giant Library
Full of Neo-Nazi book
I left your first Paul I think we're in trouble. I studied the occult with text Mars oh no
Gold nobody
I mean it yet I studied the occult with the with this guy now I know his last name is going to put you off
It was Hitler
Hitler
This caller really knocked it out of the park
A lot of homophobic
The office the work that we're doing
Wow
I think that color is faint like
Testicle
If that when I heard that I was like
That's exactly what I thought it was really homophobic
Better hearing that being voiced on the show is really interesting
That's the kind of thing that you would like to see what Alex has responses
And his response was apparently
So cold
Oh boy no how aggressive these sexual
Not good
They start leaving our families alone and we'll leave them alone
What the f*** are you talking
What about
That's its
It's so weird to hear this type
Type of s***
And then see it so late
Still
In the present
It's still there
You know he doesn't he doesn't open like about it like
Like that a little bit exactly
There is any possible to backslide
Into a place where he can just go around saying
These so-called
Homosexual families
Very possible thing
You know I think it's already still there
I mean
Yeah it's
Sucks
It exists
Send his
But the lgbtq movement is trying to normalize pedophilia
It's just sort of transition the exact Folk
Cast of it
But the same
But hatred and
Intolerant
Of people
Who are not
Straight white male Christian
Is is just
It's there it's been there
Endemic forever
So I thought that call was pretty
Pretty good
In terms of
Call Alex gets another call and Alex
Your birthday
Supporting your show I don't know how
Braid Finance
Know about them
New World Order
So this is the sponsor that also caught my attention that was the commercial selling Heroes
Caller who brings that up on the ball colors back then
Negative
Well-deserved
That sucks
That is so I would prefer people blindly accept whatever I say tell me I'm a genius
Just because Berkeley Financial
Is by all accounts
Exactly the type of Columbus organization that I am exactly
Fighting against
Doesn't mean I'm going to talk bad about them if they sponsor my show Financial Outlet
Advocating buying Euros
And they paid for add time and were accepted by 10% by the three sources
That's confusing
Ideologically
No
So we come to the end of this
Cuz the rest of the show isn't
Really it's boring
Very clearly
I'm from Illinois called back at so that was nice
There's nothing there's nothing really that comes up but I wanted to make note of it
The my boy dance Illinois got to get it in there
Consistent color
Yeah
Never exactly
I guess that brings us to the end of this and I think I I would like to just
Acknowledge that I
Was a little Hasty in my assumption that Alex
Didn't talk about to how he was recruited
Into Satanism backing
2003-4 fear of being seen as crazy
I think that there are Salient differences by
Between them
But make the present-day version
Far far crazy
Then the past version
Any talks about it less
But still hey
Yeah I mean this with this is fairly tame and you could even argue that it's just
Poetic exaggeration
You say that all the jocks
Send all this
In space what do you say
Exactly would involve an entire town dedicated to safety
Should be a great movie. I think it's been made a couple times
Real deep
Deep homophobic leanings throughout
I really thought that program
Quote was something that
Like that is such a
Good distillation of
The way that information is weaponized
Conspiracy theorists
People like Alex
They deprive a very
Reasonable and appropriate quote
About one issue into being about something entirely different
And strip it of all of the context that makes it makes
It's
And it's something the people should be very aware of and
When you have
Quotes in
Information that comes
From these dubious source
It's always It's always important
To figure out what is actually being said by the people as opposed to what
Being claimed
Things to have been sad
And yeah that's point I'd like to drive home
Love you know where I learned that from
Yeah
Interrupted you
I mean ultimately it is
It is probably their most powerful
Write via bility to take
Something that someone is saying
That you cannot
Not agree with
I think it's a regular tactic but I think they're most
Tool is
Well That's Amore
Blind
Trust
Ascent's of
Complacency and people just believing
These things that look
Looking at your items
Yep I think that's their most important tool
Yeah
But the strategy of yeah weaponizing
Like sensible quotes evil into the evil
That's a technique Intruders a lot
Indeed we will but until then we website.com
We are internal technology at the store fighting I go to bed Jordan
Job quiz
But until then
Omniome Leon dzx
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color