Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
What's fight.com
Words for the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about
My bright spot today and this is
No Quest
No question no question
No question
Kevin the bird from Up
Didn't see that, did you
Up the movie
Did you just watch a prison I just thought of Kevin
Haha
Question is great
Character
Maybe ever in a movie ever animated movie
Kevin the bird
That mean
Nothing no Casablanca no nothing
I would say that maybe heihei from Moana comes in conversation
But that Kevin
Kevin the bird
Expand this even to literature
Including literature
There's Something About That Bird something about that bird.
Got to get to a playful
Yeah he's playful and
Yeah just right
A joy
A bright spot to everyone
I I kid you not I was watching the videos of little clips
Strum up and
I got a B
Smile on my face
Love that
Tell my dad feels about the minions
What's your bright spot
I bought a knife
So we were it's a kitchell bread magnetic kitchen knife
We had lunch one day and I was walking back
And there was this little boutique store that had a
I like cookie
A cooking tray and it would have the oven
These things right about so I went in to take a look at it and
Immediately realized I didn't want it
The only the guy who ran the store in there until he came over immediately and I felt this pressure that I could
Not leave without I bought this
Japanese
Nice
Begin to
It is
So sharp so sharp I told you that I chopped of chunk of my finger off you can see that's not as big as I thought
Giant Band-Aid on your hand that made me think that you might have lost
Oh I'm sure it bled everywhere that's why I had to have the check bandaid otherwise they would have
It would have melted was either that or like supermax tampon
Monster level we were talking about impression of what it was based on
How you described it as like
I don't know maybe part of the mail it's gone
Yeah yeah it's good that it's not
Is it that is
It's sharks not thumb shape altering
So smooth
Some stuff in it
It's just like you know you should do
Chopping broccoli okay
Oh man that's great
So Jordan today we're going to be in the past forever talking about July 2nd 2003
Free continue to
Attract Alex's
Credibly
Homophobic
. going on on that front
Yeah it'll last episode from 2003 called him out on it
It's very weird to hate Harry Potter and the lgbtq community at the same
Time right you have to like you know
In the present day movie
3 / 20
Let's take a little moment to say hello
So first
Comfrey sucks
Demon fist is the new Monster Mash thank you so much right now policy walk
Need more knowledge fight crossover is thank you so much you're now apology
We're open
Next Lauren thank you so much and I apologize One
McLaren answer saying hello or thank you okay
Woop woop indeed
Next rest area
Heroin
Are you pimp so good
Is freakishly large
Alright
Yes sir we are here in the past
How do you feel being
I feel like
Maybe it's actually Shaggy 2 Dope
Who gave us like
In a $0.50 or whatever
And it's very funny.
What if it's the real
I hope it is I hope so too have some respect for the Juggalos
How to get a hatchet man tattoo but enough
Think very seriously back onto the Gathering
Oh yeah we'll be there
I don't I don't like how long how much
More homophobic
Especially during this
Little.
Consistently right in your face
Throughout some of this 2003. Like
Jejune
I don't know what's going on now he's just in a mood
It doesn't get
Quite as much blood libel as the gays are stealing your
You know like that's pretty intense
Well they're stealing them to raise them as their own not to because it was so little
I guess
Contacts dropped from Today Show
You have a great day
It doesn't get much more obvious how serious your show is
I love the juxtaposition of that
That is
That is so beautiful
Just cuz it's Hades doesn't mean we can't be polite
Yeah okay
Steptoe Alex is concerned at the beginning of this July 2nd episode
Tom Ridge
Homeland Security secretary
And makes a little bit of a prediction of what
The command
Don't know but I don't think that Alex's predict
I have a job
Credit
A fuse
So we
It is so over-the-top
So yeah we don't have four layers of security clearance to have jobs smells
.
Curfews
True I guess they're all have been sort of circumstantial curfews
Like when there were protests
There are curfews enacted in
Furts
Beginning of covid-19 resurging
There was a business is closed earlier I mean coupon
Place that I worked at I had a key fob to get in
That's a level of security clearance
That's not what he's talking about
This is one of the predictions that Alex is conveniently forgets that he was pushing
He's right about everything
Of the things that he remembers like this represents a hundred
100% accurate is also pretty good at is faking being emotional and he doesn't bit of
At the beginning of this
This show it's just
Tacky
Medical training
Feel great day
Did he just have a
Fake rage has specially with me.
Meant to say very false
You get that get that sense of like this is where the real opposition to
Yeah I'll be like George W bush comes from he thinks that they are liberals
Secret liberals not above the tube to the right of it
Yes everything else is to destroy Conservative Christian
Because I'm above the two parts of the left-right Paradigm as much as I am the broken if I going
Proven horseshoe Theory by the way
Cool
Glad lot of people fell for that
So Alex has a new story that he is
Drastically misreporting on this episode
Hello crime rate because their whole population is armed
And the government
Linda people in many cases even when they do
Ianthe I want Street Journal has document
This is weird
Point of order
I'm looking for point of you cannot
Both have an entirely armed population
And still tell me that the government is just murdering them
Yeah that seems like it should be the thing that protects people
And if it were true which is not
Then you have to
Call into question
Is that leading to a higher rate of suicide you would have to ask a lot of questions that
She is specifically glossing over
But I mean
Bring the story
From the coverage that you're hearing here
You would think of the news story that he's talking about this
Half of the deaths
Switzerland of the result of suicide assisted suicide which people may or may not want
Sure
R-Truth
Statistic
Huge but it's not okay
The reality of the story is that there was a university of Zurich
Study that was conducted on Swiss attitudes towards euthanasia
The report reflected that there was a white
Spread permissive stance in the country that the practice has early
As long as it's done within altruistic
Motive
Also a February 2003 article in the British Journal of British medical journal found these numbers
According to the president of one of the Swiss right-to-die societies
Around 8
1800 request for assisted suicide are made each year
Two-thirds are rejected after screening
Half of the remaining people die of other causes leaving about 300 suicide assisted
Society's annual
This constitutes around
For 5% of the deaths in Switzerland
So
2003 survey written up in the Lancet sought to find some data on these cysts
Suicide rates
In the countries of Belgium Denmark Italy the Netherlands Sweden and Switzerland
This found a 1% or less rates in Denmark Italy Sweden and Switzerland
The data from Belgium and the Netherlands
The little more complicated and it's not really relevant to our discussion here so I'm not even going to get into it
Anyway
The point here is that multiple studies at come out around this time that
Does datura side in Switzerland it under one
Percent less than half a percent
So where's Alex getting that number from you
Possibility you were responding to
I think
It's also possible that he just didn't read the article that he's covering and he's just skimmed this part
The study examined
3350 deaths
In German speak in Switzerland and found that half of them involve some form of euthanasia
Half of this
That these deaths
German
If you were just outside german-speaking Switzerland
If you just read that
You might get an idea of it but
This was specifically a subset of terminally ill patients in German speak in Switzerland
The study was considering
So it's naturally population we expect expect the rate to be higher and it isn't
Indicative of all the
All the deaths in sweat
Who does outlandishly sloppy work on Alex's part and serves as yet another example of why people who listen to him
I think they're getting any kind of real information or the things that they're saying is it's based on an ounce of study
You're all being
If you believe these things out
What is getting into
Your
Beautiful
Yeah I mean
Come on man
Harold and Maude came out 30 years before this movie this this s*** right here we should all be fine with somebody with
Terminal illness just going
F*** off
I think
I think it's a tough issue for some especially like
Make a discussion of it
I don't
No why you would
Let someone
Who's terminally ill not before 7 p.m. pain
God says
So for another eight months a tough
It's a tough
Line for me to think make sense
I'm so Alex gets
Some calls oh my God what
More homophobia
Hey I wanted to give you more bad news about Walmart
Have you heard
The story that came out today on Walmart
About the gay right
Yeah I just thought it was very in
Interesting in that they were they were saying here are there at there's
Moto Williams
The times are the most important factor with
For the letter
Several gay employees apparently there was a
What's the name of this
Let's see here
The Pride Foundation a Seattle gay rights organization
They invest
City Walmart
Policy change
And they were saying here that
Basically that
Williams was saying we want all of our Associates feel they are valued and treated with respect
Yes custom
At their job
Well I'm going to I'm going to tell you something I used to work for Walmart
Okay
From Walmart
Are you ready for the reason that I was fired
Because a customer said that she didn't like the way I looked at her
I'm absolutely certain that's not with that guy got fired.
If a man says it's cuz a woman didn't like the way I looked at her
Is going to be a more detailed guess what according to Alex on this guy's
Resume political beliefs he should have no problem with the company firing him for any reason
Employment is an aggressively voluntary agreement for Alex and his audience
Freedom of Association and all that you shouldn't be complaining
This is a story about Walmart releasing a statement that they would expand their nondiscrimination rules to include gay and lesbian
Employees
This was hot on the heels of the Supreme Court decision Lawrence versus Texas
Criminal sodomy laws
He's on Constitution
Don't believe that that's where things were in 2003
Walmart still was very clear that they weren't going to extend benefit
It's to same-sex couples but this decision that they made was still pretty impact
Now if you were fired because you were gay or your bully by co-workers for your sexual orientation
Recourse
New York Times article about this is remarkable as a poinsettia
This made it so nine of the 10 largest Fortune 500 companies
Had implemented rules against sexual orientation
Discrimination
The only one that didn't was ExxonMobil
And even more remarkable after Exxon acquired Mobile in 1999 they quote
Revoked mobile policy that provided medical benefits to Partners of gay employees
As well as a policy that included sexual orientation as a category of prohibited discrimination
The actor who's got rid of
ExxonMobil
We're actually evil
I've never seen this real strong homophobia on Alex's part here in 2003 which is
Troubling
It's gross
So gross
Will you bring you f******
You did this all happened
20 years ago
And now it's just being
Like transposon to trans people
Sure it's just
It's the same s*** I think you're absolutely right that a lot of that attention is going there just being real
Package in that direction
Some of it is just
Playing the exact
Same song over and over again
Like for instance we recently had a bunch of people trying to do
Straight right
Parade
Hooray
Yeah I just think it's quite interesting though that they're going to give give all these extra rights
But what about the heterosexual heterosexual right
The manual
It's just to put in a plug just to put in a plug for the competition on their target or somewhere else
I do know what you're saying
Hey Dan.
Please take a s*** head
I can't handle when they say things like what about straight rights
Complain the gay people are getting extra rights when anti-discrimination rules
Are put in place
They're so privileged
The disconnected from the actual reality of Oppression that they don't even realize that any discrimination laws that protect gave
People predict straight people
If a company doesn't hire you because you're gay
Violated anti-discrimination laws
And if they specifically don't hire you because you're straight they violated the exact same anti-discrimination law
These rules are often looked at as being extra rights for gay or lesbian employees but it's a broader idea of non-discrimination
Nation applied equally for all
Books like this call or just don't understand or care about that because he's a giant homophobe because the very idea of people
Not getting a job or being harassed by co-workers
For being straight is unimaginable to him
It so it's not even a reality in his world
Yeah I mean it's
It's so simple
To be like okay let's look at this anti-discrimination policy
Does it protect me as well
So it protects everybody
So let's say there was a situation where I become
The minority this protects me from the majority
It's very simple
It's so simple but that idea of
Eventually I will be the one
Without power
Unreal to them it's just such as bizarre
Interpretation of things to be like
This is specifically to
Make it so you can't
Make fun of gay people at work anymore
Reality is
Sexual orientation as a class of things that you can't discriminate
Sprite
Do the same things that protect
People of ethnic minorities also protect white people from discrimination
Instagram
Such nonsense
Anyway JonBenet Ramsey
Died
A while back
Good for him
Cheaper
So this color is an interesting theory about
They're killing children in NFL
Another name
Give me a call
John
Take a look at JonBenet Ramsey
Jacobite
Community threads
Okay
JonBenet that's
The devil.
I think I can hammer out a minute
It's a cliche
Playing the comedian say like this
What kind of Association that is required to create a VIP
Yikes is very
Not thoughtful listeners
That sounds like something
The Oz another big story that he's promoting on this day first half of
The people who died in Switzerland are assisted suicides
It is not true
And the other one is that
Women are becoming a more pro-life
Turning against
Abortion
And this
A warning that is a gross
Women and women who
Bobby Knight Roofing in the majority in the debates
According to
Really
Not even bigger crime
Wow that's a barbaric s*** Alex's on here
I mean
I honestly don't think that I've ever heard him get into the specifics of his anti-abortion believe so I was actually a little surprised that
But he would have that hard of a stats
Express that publicly that even in cases of rape people should be forced
Sicario
That's wild
If somebody can understand why explaining it isn't going to
So good move along I mean
The type of when you read stories where it's like that happens and then
They get visitation rights
The rapist
Gets visitation rights to the kid is like
I mean
Just
F****** unconscionable
That's horrifying and that's
Low on the scale of the abuse has better it couldn't
Took me forever to track down the article he's reading but I finally did and it's from the Washington Times covering a survey
Conducted by the center for the advancement of women
The survey found that 51% of women surveyed
Say abortion should be outlawed or severely restricted their shifting toward the pro-life side group into the
The majority in the debate over Reproductive Rights
There's no link to the survey and I can't
Find it so I really can't discuss too many of the specifics but does say that there's a 3% margin of error so
He knows that this is actually representative of
Majority
Either way this is supposed to be up
From 45% on the bedside in 2001 so
Even if I'm being a little iffy on the specifics
Because I don't have access to them it does
Seemed to show a trend of lowering
Support for abortion
It does appear that this trend has turned around
As a Pew research study in May 2021 found the 50
9% of respondents said that abortion
To be legal in all or most
Cases just in time for it to be over
The numbers look even worse for Alex if you just include women does 62% of people who
Where the women were surveyed side of origin
To be legal in all or most
If you look at
Gallup's data on abortion attitudes quiktrak with the results of the survey cuz it just Oracle data
Far back on that question
I can find I'm going to guess that this survey that's being reported on to watch
Good times is an outlier in the data
Or possibly the results came from a poorly worded question or Ops
The people could try robbery
Either way the public opinion was fairly
The proportion access at the most
Including in 2003
Yeah I don't
I think that this is
Reflective of a tide
Turn it says Trump is up 40 points
Where's my crazy that is interesting
So Alex is talking about this
Assisted suicide thing
I'm going to come up
I'm going to need a citation on that
This isn't about
This is Al.
The implication here is that Doctor Kevorkian was f****** dead bodies and that's why he lost his medical license
I can find no evidence
If you can't find any evidence that he lost his medical license
Kevorkian was licensed to practice in Michigan in California and his license in Michigan was suspended in 1991
The Michigan Board of Medicine made this decision because he they tried to file charges against them for assisting in suicide
But it turned up there's actually no log
Against that admission
The time
So the board claimed it had quote acted under a state law that gives it the power to withdraw the license
Any Doctor Who acted a negligent
Or
Set Manor
Sisters drugs for other than lawful diagnostic
Or therapeutic purposes
Some of kevorkian's patients
Had I have lethal medication
Right
Administered
And because of that people would claim the authority to take
Insurance license
He lost his license in California 1993 and this only happened because one of his patients was from
From California
He didn't actually leave apparently ever go to California
And so
Sure she did prior to go
Come to Michigan his lawyers said that like he was even been there in years
Alex Consuela Ridge it like as all he wants but you can't prove any of this
And it's just
Disgusting
Yeah it did the family show seem like
Kevorkian had at the very least the idea that there was an altruistic motive behind his ass
I've seen a documentary or two
At no point in time
Did they mention him f***
Walking dead bodies
Smell I tried so many search-term
Trying to find at least even like necrophilia
Something that would give me a foothold in order to
Define like this is what's being talked about I couldn't find
Anyway Alex has an exciting gas coming up
Underwear
Got some I canceled coming back to Keller
We're going to come back on
Imaginative
Carson had
The same person on on the same week I make no mistake
Exact same story
It's true that I guess
You think
It's true
So Alex get the call here towards the end of the show after Mike's interview
A particular
Audio peace
Has played in the past because they Jello Biafra spoken word
Exchange is so
F****** funny
How It Ends is
The best
Next week or something
I appreciate it
I don't care about that
Okay
But that's one
Go out and find
Door
Well if I can play
Okay well
Are you doing everything going okay
Oh yeah
Doing alright I just
Worried about it check it in Salina this CD stuff going
Right now it feels like a big mess
Like that's not right
Deep into the cold it's not like
This is open opening pleasantries it's kind of like
I like that
His collars at this point in history
Are split down the middle of
Horrifying monsters
And people who have like
Real Pleasant conversation
You seem up
Certainly nice you doing man Hey listen
I hear that song
How you doing so we get to the 3rd July 3rd
Before July 4th
Alex singing a song that we can tell a lot
In the present
Mall
I mean
So I think first of all the emotions are fake
So interesting
See he's
Ben
Just overworked
Is entire career there's just been too much to cover
Never been
There's never been a single day where is like list
Against All Odds today is kind of a light show
I've only got a couple of
Stacks here I think I'm going to talk to that guy he asked me how I was doing earlier
You know what let's have a fun story
Today
Never so we get to some of the news and
Smurf a commotion
A real
Troubling
Point
Believable
Got all these different with me
American
It's really embarrassing that Alex doesn't seem to know the difference between Karzai and Ahmad
Jalopy they are very different people different pronunciations
The same name
Karzai was the president of Afghanistan
A 2000
The 2014
Conversely Ahmad shalaby was Rocky politician who would go on to
To become the president of the governing Council of Iraq in
In September
2300 via Rocky National
Congress political party
The headline that Alex's reading is about Ahmad chalabi who played a large role in
In the lead-up to the Iraq War
Fairly quickly was found out to be a bit of a con man
True relationship to cultivated with a group of Republican politicians over the years from the first Iraq War
Political party the Inc was the recipient of over 100 million dollars from our
Matcha tea bad intelligence that was used
Convince the public that a war in Iraq was necessary like the ideas of mass
The best destruction
An saddam's connections to terrorism a people associated with shalaby
Nbimc
Yeah but
Bye 2004 he'd fallen out of Grace with us intelligence services
That he was sharing closely-held information with Ron
The CIA had actually voiced misgivings about him and his information all along
And suspicious connections to a Ron
But folks like Dick Cheney
We want to start a war none of this is to say that the war going to Iraq was all because of shalaby
Most of the members of Bush's
Just gotten it where more than willing to accept whatever rationale was put in front of them
To get rid of Saddam
It probably would have found someone else saying what they want
Gearhead chalabi not filled that role
All this being said it's really f***** up that Alex doesn't seem to know that
The Karzai until out of your two different people
Are you presenting himself as the only person who can
Decode the secret messages behind the news
The man won't tell you
It's clear that he doesn't even know Elementary details about the topics he's discussing
If I were Steve pieczenik
Definitely see how Alex would be a perfect March
Like exactly the sort of person that you'd be
Can use the sky
I was thinking about things one
I'm really curious
Where's Steve's at
Cuz I know this time. For the first time in 2002
Each other
And have talked
But he's not
You been on in the time that I've listened yet
Eagerly awaiting that threat
Steve pops up FIFA comment
He's not in the Solar
It doesn't appear that
Regular rotation
And the second thing
I've been thinking about is like
This guy isn't a star
Alex
You know to use more Celestial terms
Like he's not
In 2003
Does not ask
Don't have like he's got the
These skills that are just intrinsic
Definitely
Yeah but
He doesn't have the
DeSoto
Showmanship but he does
Later on
Right
I can see why he was
And Famous
It wasn't like super famous
It wasn't 911 that necessarily rocketed him he's kind of boring
It is
It is interesting
To see him in
What you would
Reconsider
Infancy
Progression
They have all these different ways
That idea of like
No no I didn't
Fuk up
It's that this
Human being
Has been like
Hey I'm going to trick
People with a bunch of
Different ways to pronounce my name and not trying to cover up that you f*****
It actually reveals
YouTube much
Larger
Aaron Esser
Ignorance
So Alex is a guest
Other than Mike Hanson who
Tell the same story again
Answer
The old
No no no the race no he wanted it off with the robbers
Mother Gaston Sky name red Beckman
We've talked about him in the past
He is a weirdo
Doesn't believe people pay taxes
He also is on here because he has interesting Theory
About juries
And how is your on the jury and you don't agree with the law
Even if you think a person's guilty
You should just vote them not guilty
Jury nullification of laws
Essentially is the
Is the push
Stitch a redback
Yeah
I can't imagine somebody
From Texas thinking that
Certainly
Red Bread got an interesting take on freedom of religion
In the First Amendment
I think I disagree with
They told us that we have free speech that you can criticize the government we have Free Press
The Press
Criticize
Is the government without the government
Laughing out loud
The same thing
The same
Perfect
The freedom of religion
The minister was to be
Condemned
Servants
Outside of the wall
They have changed that completely
Until now
If the freedom of the Muslims the freedom of the Buddhist
The freedom of everybody else
They're just ask
Absolutely
Running roughshod
Over the principles
The first
So I would guess that red Beckman would have a slightly different position if the conversation we're about like an Imam telling their Moscow.
Vote for who to vote against
As a prediction but I think he's very can
Across all religious idea
Posters can do exactly what red wants them to do and they could be as political as they want they just have to pay the tax
Axis then
Advocating for against specific politicians or policies as a violation of their tax
Exempt status
There's no law against preachers doing targeted political organizer
Have to pay taxes
That they do
To be able to use churches as political organizing
Entities because of course he does
The political project these folks are engaged 2003 is a Christian nationalist
State
I want a store that is associating certain way with following your religion
Is what redwood like
People to be forced
Into
Cool
That is
That is so funny
That did they rewrite
The First Amendment
I mean how can you
He said
But they changed it
Like the first amendment was supposed to be this
Well the interpretation of it is no longer that the freedom of religion is about
Like I originally the interpretation that the founders wanted right
Religious
L can
Leave campaign
Politician
That's what it was
Protect
Written that one in there
Cut up
Yeah I think
He's just talking about like the interpretation of it is changed to include like a separation
Church and state being
Very clear
The government shall make no law restricting
Editas religion
It doesn't take Christianity and others that
And then second it doesn't
Say like the government shall not stop religious leaders from talkingshit
So Alex gets a call while red Beckman is on
Through most of the show together
And this call herbally
Leave that his phone is being
He can hear noises
The phone
I am here is pretty insistent about this
Yes a Alex has to say
Call Bill Thompson
Call
Another
Hope
My phone tap
Because
It's probably
So true that they're going
Define
Talk to somebody else
What's going on
So this is fascinating like generally nowadays whenever one of Alex's listeners causing with a stupid
Paranoid Theory
Alex does absolutely nothing to reassure them that they're fine and this is
That is not happening
He actively encourages their paranoia and lends credibility to their fears
Here in 2003 though this caller Hank is worried that the man is listening in on his phone calls but
Set up saying that that's probably true Alex
Argues with him about how it's not happening
It's probably not possible
Anyway
It's also interesting to me to hear that Alex has articulating this review about government surveillance programs
You don't actually think there's a wife
Pittsburgh spine going on
The government's just revealing the day of spying
Capabilities
In order to scare Patriots into thinking that their calls could be listened to at any point so there's a chilling effect
Remind me of his other comments particularly more recent ones
I don't think that this is
Position.
Consisted on at all
Also as The Story Goes Judas betrayed Jesus for thirty pieces
Is the silver so either Alex got that
Very well-known biblical detail wrong
Hypothetical Feds that are listening into red beckman's phone or working at a rate
One of the two
I do like that
You know cuz that's evolution of that you know I don't mind if they listen to my calls I've either got
Say or they're going to hear
Engrossed
Hahaha that kind of big
This is elevating it to
I hope they're listening to my calls so I can get that
Truthout
Write to the NSA
Teach them a little lesson
Can you imagine surveilling somebody and then eventually being like you know what
They're right
What about it think is going on
Bellingham
The conclusion
Because when they listen
Conversate
Wow
Only have to do is look around them and
See what's going on
And they know that were
Telling the truth
Realize that it's now
A good idea to put people on monitoring
The Patriots phones because
They just like
That's
That is
A
Perfect encapsulation of the shot Chaser meme
Where I go
It would be crazy to think this
I think this
Okay alright
Yeah
Yep
The guy who famously has the dock
Catchphrase and a joke
Because he
The often times he doesn't provide these documents
This next clip is actually an interesting incidents where he's offering to give the audio
A document
Like down for this because
There's a little bit of a cat
Article
How long will it
That's fascinating I was blown away by
Aren't you the tip of the spear
Yeah in order to get this document you have to buy a couple silver dollars for Ted Anderson
You trying to get the truth out
Well yeah but you got to buy some silver
Why is there a pay wall behind
Because
Do you want to go to buy
What document is it
Wow that I'm glad you asked
Of course why would I why would I be so stupid
Here is what it is
Here
More days
So Alex is like he's full of s*** about this and it's really pathetic though he's playing this game it's
Clearly designed to get people
The order things
Anderson in Midas resources and hopefully get them into the on the phone with somebody who can
Tell them all about how important it is to buy precious metals
The game between times
The document is the thing that's being
Lower its luring them in
So sad the Declassified report
From DARPA is nothing of the sort
He reads off a document identification number and that alone is a huge clue about how poorly he's covering this
A b a is a broad agency announced
Not a board agency enough
Announcement
The Army's website defines them as quote
A competitive solicitation procedure used to obtain proposals for basic and applied research
Part of developing
Not related to the development of a specific system or Hardware procurement
Very vast the document that Alex is selling his audience as a Declassified DARPA report is
Actually just a posting
At a certain government agency is taking pictures for research proposal
Yeah
Various government agencies utilize Bas to find people to conduct research
Princeton Steve defense Logistics agency currently has one open to quote
Identify domestically-produced materials from
From possibly reliable sources to substitute for materials produced by Foreign sources or sole source
That's all
It's DARPA posting a help wanted ad for a project that they called
Combat zone that c
The posting was made on March 25th
2003 wood close
What year later
On the project
Here's how they describe it it's it's a project that quote
Explorers Concepts
Develop algorithms
Deliver systems for utilizing large numbers thousand
Oh camera is to provide the clothes in sensing demand
For military operations in Urban Terrain
The reason for wanting to do this
Explore this research is spelled out in the VA
Quote military operations in Urban Terrain
Fraught with Dan
Urban Canyon
Yield standoff sensing from airborne and space born Platforms in effect
Short lines of sight neutralize much of the standoff
Fan situation awareness advantages currently rendered by US forces
Large civilian populations of the ever-present risk of collateral damage preclude the use of overwhelming Force
As a result combat Insidious has long been viewed as something
Thing to avoid
However modern asymmetric
Threats to capitalize on these limitations by hiding in urban areas
Enforcing US forces to engage in cities
We can no longer avoid the need to be prepared to fight
Insidious
I read over this and I hate it
But they also understand the rationale for exploring this kind of research
It's very specifically aimed at targeting a Deployable network of sensors and cameras that can track specific Vehicles Over Law
Long distances
Including within Urban Air
I get why it would be a valuable thing to for the government to have during the Iraq War
And I think that the risk associated with the potential misuse of a program like this
It's not something that's worth the benefit that you get
Creating it so I would be opposed
I read a bunch of this
Proposal of the documents that are on the DARPA website I've decided that I'm against it
However I think of the way Alex misreport
On this proposal actually does a disservice to oppose
Because it's disconnect
Dude from reality
If you want to take this proposal and warn people that they sort of thing has the potential to be Gravely misused in the wrong hands
And its implementation of US Cities would almost certainly violate people's
Personal privacy
That would be a fine thing to do and I think it's a fine conversation
It's just dumb to take this information and use it to insist that this is a classified document approved darpa's doing the
Because the provided evidence fails embarrassing
Simile short of a proven that
It's counterproductive to report information this way but
It's probably deeply on ethical and exploitative
Use this kind of
Misreporting of this information to get people into your gold sales revenue stream
Also
I can find a ton of speculation about this
Program on blogs
For the life of me
I can't find anyone that provide specific details about what happened
Past the posting of this ba
I was able to actually fine though the project manager Thomas Strat
I found his LinkedIn page
And weirdly combat zones Betsy that project is listed in his resume
It's probably real secret stuff
I wouldn't put that in your CV if it if it was
Classify
Waltz
Yeah it's it's
It's strange
Obviously I think that
This
Serta program
I think
But the capabilities that you might be able to develop
Through it
Aren't good
The mayor definitely things that could be abused
Yes
There's a valid conversation to have around that but I think the way Alex is doing this
Justice cartoon
I want to know what it is
So I'm ordering silver
I'm ordering silver
In order to
To get this free.
Well and you're getting an AP story about
The document that proves that it's a real thing or something
And you're also going to get like red beckman's weird pamphlet
Totally
What am I supposed to do with this.
Do I use this to win arguments in with my family that's what it is
Hey listen
Guess what you think I'm crazy I bought this document from Alex
It was $25 but I also got silver
Sober and honestly while I was on the phone I bought it
Bunch more silver
That's what it's for right now it's the trick people into buying more metal from
I know I know but from a consumer side that's what they must be thinking
You have the documents you can make copies of it
Distributed I'm tired of looking like I'm crazy
Tell people that I bought silver and an innocuous
From DARPA
Great
Weird
But transparent in terms of the intent on Alex's part and it's just like
If you were trying to abused your audience this is how you have been
Yeah I know the Home Shopping Network is like we have to put a clock on this because everybody doesn't buy it is going to die tomorrow he don't like
Jerky
Worldwide
Conspiracy trying to kill you
What I'm saying that if at the end of their clock
You were going to die right there's a bomb that's unless you spell August
That's the problem
So red Beckman has some ideas about the USSR that I don't think
Now they're great I don't think this is
And people just do not
Understand what
USSR
Great world powers
The point where they were dissolved overnight
They were considered one or two world powers and they were dissolved overnight
People don't understand why
Simple
It was a
God
Point where it should be no longer answer the prayers of those who pray
Something that's really interesting about that
Is that if you were speaking metaphorically
I think there's something to that
You know I think that there are
The government's can collapse
Because of inability to provide for the needs
Of the population
I think if you're really generous with the metaphor
I'm
Fairly fine with what red sang
Because I listen to this yeah I know that he's being literal he's being very literal
Yeah if you want her to say that our government worships the false god of productivity and and capital
Totally fine
But if you want to say that the USSR broke up overnight cuz they were worshipping a false god
Literally like f***
Ball
Or something
Then you might be right back
You might be you might be
Yeah that that was a little bit strange
Has another take on this and that isn't like
The false god of the USSR fell trying to do it again
Before 911
New World Order
So there doesn't none of this is real
It was a report released by the project for The New American Century
In September 2000
It's one of the disappointing Smokin Guns that 911 truth folks
Spell out to prove the bush did 9/11
Appears in the tack
Process of transformation even if it brings revolutionary change is likely to be a long one
Absent some catastrophic and catalyzing event like a new Pearl Harbor
This doesn't prove anything but it's super fun to Sapient
Picture the word
Imperial mobilization don't appear anywhere the
Pinac document
A together and
Each word doesn't even appear in the text on its own
Alex is mixing the peanut document up with zbigniew Brzezinski book The Great the grand chessboard
Would you use as an optimal lined Passage
Including the words
Imperial mobilization
The first time
The term is used it's used three times in the tax
The second time is sort of a rephrasing of what we're going to talk about a second time was just saying that if we Russia
That was more decentralized
It would be less likely to
Engage in a remobilization
The first
Time is
The one that is
Often
Cited like
Conspiracy theorist and is misused
So it's in the section about the geopolitical situation in Eurasia or the Eurasia
Chess board
He calls it
It's argued that US influence in Eurasia is it
Exceedingly important to world stability
Possibly more to the point in more realistic
Stickley holding the most sway in that region is critically important
The US strategic interest
And the prospect of a hostile country having more sway is really Gretna
Link to our
Text envisions Eurasia is split into four segments on a boar
There's the west witch
Includes most of Europe
Where the u.s. is said to have a pulled on the chessboard
There's the East which is basically China Japan North and South Korea as well as Southeast Asia
There's the middle space which is the former USSR and then there's the South which is mostly the middle
According to brzezinski's analysis a situation that could be seen as a win for us interest
Is one where the former USSR comes
Closer to the US's orbit
Where the East doesn't outright expel the United States
I'd wear the South section dozen
End up quotes
Subjected to Domination by a single play
Player
You can kind of see the point that's being made
There's an interesting analysis of the sort of
Tension
Between these actor
Bruzdzinski points out that quote
The scope of American global hegemony is admittedly great but it's death is shallow
That's an interesting point
ABC's this
Kind of dynamic as an inevitability particularly in the Eurasian chessboard
Very scale and diversity of Eurasia as well as the power of some of its states limits the depth of America
Can influence
And the scope of control over the course of events
That Mega continent is just
Too large to populous culturally to varied
And composed
Too many historically ambitious and politically energetic state
To be compliant towards even the most
Economically successful and politically preeminent Global power
Before they don't just like rollover hard to hold
What do large reasons this is
The case is because American influence is not based on the primary tool that has been used by empires in the past
Which is correct
Control
Bruzdzinski isn't saying that not taking over countries is a bad thing and it's Vicky we should change it or something
That's not
Here's the passage where Imperial mobilization
Comes out
Quote it's also a fact that America is too Democratic at home to be autocratic abroad
This limits the use of America's power especially its capacity for military intimidation
Never before has a populist democracy attained International Supremacy
But the pursuit of power is not a goal of the commands popular passion
Accepting conditions of sudden threat or challenge to the public sense of domestic well-being
The economic self-denial that is
Is defense spending and human sacrifice
Casualties even among
Professional Soldier
Required in the effort are uncongenial to democratic enter
Democracy is
Inimical
To Imperial mobilization
Anyway
Alex will often misrepresent the grand chessboard and I guess in this case he got his primary sources can
Confused
It's basically the the Imperial mobilization
In the context of that quote is
Something I did
He sang with this isn't something
That
Did our democratic system is really
Compatible
Which is why it required
Far more authoritarian leading 30 years after that to do exactly what he said a populist
I couldn't even so I would I would save
That
The version of Imperial mobilization
That's being discussed
Is not what we have
But still fair enough
Also this is important George W bush never wrote
Anything that was released by the project for a new American Center Roatan
Because he was also never a member
Future members of his administration were among the 25 initial founding members of the group
It also that group did include Jeb Bush
But not George W
The group did hold heavy influence in the bush years but the way Alex is talking about the
This is just cartoon
Also the peanut document ends with a list of people who quote participated in at least one project meeting orchid
Tribute to the paper for discussion
That list does not include Dick Cheney
What is direct attribution really matter
Much like the case of the DARPA document Alex does the subject he's talking about a disservice by having no grass
The basic details
And making up so much
Extraneous stuff as to make his stories
Just more interesting
He's just trying to sort of flavor
It's changing things
Past the point of
It even
Resembling reality
Opposition to the project for The New American
Can century is
It's based on an understanding of the group that you get from listening to Alex
Cuz it's just Bluster and anger leading you down a dead-end
Infowars as we're healthy distrust goes
Todai
And that's
Really unfortunate
Yeah it seems to me that's so many
Conspiracies
Like boiled down to just
Reacting to having an error stock
You know like
Of course all of these people know each other there in the aristocra
They're connected
In the same way that with World War
All the countries were run by the same fam
You know like it's that kind of don't you have an aristocracy you can
Easily draw
Parallelism
Connections to him
Cuz they f****** went to school together
Yeah but you're not there an actual Criminal
Conspiracy working
Together
It's another thing to wear
Do you have a greater
Possibility
Need to make persuasive
Appearing conspiracy theories
The great Earth
The difference is
The gap between
Glasses website
Is the number at the top
Decrease and
Distance
Between them
Increases to a point where
People are just completely out of touch
People in different social strata
And the ability to
To believe
Various things about people
Right you're so disconnected from
Comes much easier
You could believe that there
Eating people or whatever
In a certain sense
The same
Impetus that gets
Rich people in trouble for saying like
A milk milk is what
How many is it $1,000 per gallon or for how much is a milk
Ask for what
Exactly the same as being like a Billionaire's obviously drink blood
Otherwise why would they be built
Right2know
Next
Beckman has some thoughts about 9/11
Let Her Go
For the American people
Go to
Were controlled by remote
Controlling
It wasn't
They didn't find the hijackers live and
I find this really interesting
The wave
This theory of the remote-controlled planes
It seems
Very popular on Infowars at this point
Which I don't think of something that
Hugh Allison want
20 yeah present I don't think he would like that
Because it's
Silly
And they changed
Didn't they change the main like that one
Is gone from even the most
I think we think so yeah they let that one go after while cuz they were like really hard for me to know
Know what is like
Still within the 9/11 conspiracy Cannon cuz a lot of stuff came and went
I think that's the thing that's probably about it
See one last clip here and I think
One of the things that's really really challenging
When your we are listening to this stuff is like earlier in this episode we were talking about
Alex
Trying to tell this collar
But at the same time he's really trying to scare them
Like this is how the show end
This is
This is a response
Possible
Liquid half
Iroquois
Well I think it'll be
Be bigger than the last
You go back
Menu
Progression
Ruby Ridge
Everyone
Maybe tomorrow on the 4th of July maybe they're lying or something
Something bigger than 911 that happened
You got to be paying attention
Maybe not all that close late
But
You might notice how this caller asked what would happen if New York was nuked and Alex
Immediately Rican text realized that as the globalist
Attacking us
He doesn't even leave room
Ferrer couldn't even be an actual terrorists
Possibility is not even in the consideration
Right
That's interesting
It kind of speaks to his
Unwillingness
To recognize
Aventus actually haven't happened
It certainly has been
In the behind
Much like Kevin the bird mite
He likes to
Eating the chocolate out of the out of the bush
Because little beef
Kevin so great
I think
That's Alex
Has gotten into trouble
Obviously with the Sandy Hook
Reaction to picking out this much
Must be fake
It's just super consistent with him the whole time
Must
Fit into
The storyline of the overarching narrative that he believed
You can see red reinforcing that with
Putting everything on ascertain
Trajectory Ruby Ridge the bombing of the World Trade Center Oklahoma City 9/11
It's all
Part of a progression to him as as a like
All of these things are being done by the globalist
Against bright the Patriots
And more specifically
Yes because he is the
Yes
And that's
Dumb
But it's it's definitely
Indicative of their their worldview that all of this s*** is an intrinsically connected
As opposed to like Wyler's a bunch of
Separate incidents of
Bad stuff
You know what's weird I almost
I don't
Understand being afraid of a new
I almost in the same way that I don't understand really being afraid of an asteroid
In a in a like
Pearson
It's like obviously like the reason is
Because the neck
Nuuk is the last one
You know like it for everything it's for the world
The human race is over
Maybe just like if we get hit by a meteor
The human race is over like why worry about an Extinction event
You know you got s*** to where I would I'm worried about a cruise missile hitting
Chicago
Deal with
People are going to have to fall there going to be a whole fall out
Chicago in autumn
Automated system happen
And everyone's dead
Maybe you know maybe
I think that in the past there have been discussing
Of
Absorbing a nuclear attack or something because of this very
Concern
How's it just turning into the end of the world
Situation even if an asteroid hit necessarily die immediately
You might have some stuff to deal with what I'm saying what I'm saying is if that happened
I'm not dealing with any of that I'm calling dr. Kevorkian baby I'm
Done for assisted suicide all over I'm not going to melt from radiation poisoning well alright
Personally I don't understand why people Fear the Reaper
Never bothered me
Yeah we get to the end of this and I think
Galaxies
Trend of homophobia is really troubling
Yeah
It's
Intensely moreover
Then it has been at other pee
. the pass
I'm having
I'm having very serious
Like
Immediate flashbacks to cuz 2003 was when I was
In high school
Sophomore and Junior and
School in my
Small Christie
Conservative town
And the homophobia I remember is
So
Intense
And then to think about
Like my little sister is a
For now
And the Next Generation
The kids that she's
She's almost resentful of them like how dare you be
Septic of people
And it's like
I cannot believe
How f*****-up it was just that
Just a short time ago
Probably true lot of times turns with generational
Gaps in
You just hope that the progress
It's being made as progress in the right direction
It seems like
On that front
It's been a little better
But yeah
I think it just sticks out to me is like these
Collars are
How are you doing an arm MB you take care
Just
Absurdly so to the point where it sticks out something to be said about how polite Society
Indian enjoyed their hatred
But they were still polite
What about it what what the people who were calling in and we're polite that's true
People who are at work
I just wanted to Jello Biafra a clip
Right right
Yeah hopefully they found greener pastures
How do I will be back
But until that we have left
We do it now
Twitter
Will be back but until then I'm needle I'm Leon dzx Clark
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color