Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Need
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Everybody was making I'll try.
Alex
We are Dan Jordan Jordan
What's up
Denny's new
For the money episode
And such
I have grown weary of hearing little pops every now and again I can drive people crazy
I'm a little bit so I got new courts
Chadwicks
And I'm hoping that that problem will be resolved Saturday because I was almost certainly where that was
Coming from
Bi-Rite
Perfectionism
Recorded
Replace these cords after
Albino in there was a problem
Mine
Is long underwear
Never worn long underwear before in my life
You know they called that
Nobody but my partner got me these a long underwear I've never worn before in my life
This morning this was our first Chicago day where was really down to that like
Single-digit
Temperature I'm walking
Can my dog
6:30
My legs are
Toasty and warm I've never felt better in my life I'm happy for you
It's great. Are they long johns is that the name of them
I didn't know they're just a pan
Okay I don't have the overall I don't have the sleeves I don't think the overall is this energy along
You got to work on that you got to get yourself a little bit of a better operational feeling there
Get yourself a butt flap
I'm not going to be in the in the
Turn yourself into like a little boy
I don't think that's a terrible idea I still I wear the same exact clothes everyday so that would make
It's not very good
So Jordan
Today we are back in the present
About
November 30th
24 Northwestern
And we had to 2003 episodes Outlast to UPS
Something came up everything is okay but we had to
Episodes that we had pre-recorded
And so that's why there was some stuff going on in the world and maybe
Like I said that Alex has a great journalist and we don't seem to know it's good we recorded those before
Stuff happens
There's a lot of nonsense going on in this episode
Let's take a little moment to say hello.
New Wok
The first VI on Keenan group chat
Thank you very much
Lachlan from Australia that gives about you an alibi
Cars Lachlan
Scorpion dagger thank you so much
Kropotkin that's a chicken but like with a bird The Crow
That Brandon lyrics
Bianca Cortez
Technocrat
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Also I've been thinking about this
Reset wars in the mick haha
I think it's time for us to do a reset to you think so I think I need to make
Sonu sound drop
Reset we have entered The Fray of recent War
I think I'm just doing the parody of it by making a new sound.
Play me some new drops going
Jordan
This episode is silly it's stupid but here is an avocado
6 drop permit
Pull somebody's head off their body
More power
Yes
I could pull your head off your body more powerfully with
Love because of love for love
It's a perspective on the mom lifting up the car to save her baby the mom just rips that
Head off of somebody within a block
Radius of her baby I feel like that's
What were they was coming
So we start off here on November 30th
With Alex reporting on
A clip
That he's heard of Joe Biden
John Muir calendar of Monday November 29th
The job I'm almost at blackjack
He
Is holding 350
Million Americans
Hostage
Hehehehehe
Room that we remember when
Picture of Obama watching I'm sitting in there just twiddling his thumbs
Bwahahaha
Seems Seems like a clip that Alex is definitely going to play
The new theory that Alex has it's based on the clip that he saw of this
So woman being interviewed on
Fox News
Puhi
Will not
Stop saying is beautiful
And it's a little under
It's a little upsetting
But this is the new idea that covid is an unsolvable problem
That the globalist have created
In order to
You know pretend that they're solving the problem
Which leads to more control
Yep into that's one of the big themes of this episode
Covid-19
Unsolvable problem
Transfer all power and control to a select group
Multinational
Corporations owned and controlled by
Free banking families
Everywhere
People are dying.
Last year the
Expectancy was
74 years for a man 76 for a woman
Two years for men
2 years for women in just this year
The averages drop two years
I saw through this weekend
I can't believe that I missed those actuaries
It is true that the preliminary numbers are showing that there were more deaths in the US in 2021 than there were in
28 seemed like an argument against vaccines on the surface
It's actually the opposite it's not all that surprising considering
Things have gone
The explanation is super simple
Vaccination rates
Are not high enough
And that is being combined with people going back to
RI covid
At the same time it was going around to being more highly transmittable
Has it summed up in the New York Times quote
Many Americans are behaving as though covid-19 is now a manageable endemic
Disease rather than a crisis
Transition that will happen eventually but has not happy
Opened yet
This is leading to wider spread in there is
Significant gaps and Immunity in the public and that's led to death
What are the most
Important aspects to resolving this problem is the u.s. not having under 60% vaccination rates
In the population but with voices like Alex being taken seriously at all
It doesn't seem like we're going to get there anytime soon
As for the life
Expectancy
Alex's operating off imprecise
Information
We don't have the numbers yet on 20
Play 21 for this kind of thing
But the cdc's national Center for Health statistics announced in July
Average life expect
Expectancy dropped the price
Smelly one point
5 years
Between 2019 and 2020
It's not two years were man and women
Is 1.8 years for men and 1.2 years for women averaging out to 1.5
A lot of this does have to do with covid deaths
And honestly when we have numbers for 2021
It's possible that the number might be even worse
But these
Speak about this very precise about life expect
Continue as though if you are 70 now
You will die in 2 years
Whereas if you were 16
In five years that's not how it works it's not Noel though it is fun to imagine that
He thinks that it's like if you're 70 you better not stop running you better keep her
Man seventy-year-old people used to live for years longer another
Yeah
They're blocked
I also I have no idea what I was just talking about with the various actuaries nonsense but if he does know about the three Bank
Making families that own everything and are taking over
Pictures of Duty to be more specific about that
You know it
Banking families
They have
Proprietary actuaries
But you know cuz they're in competition with each other
They don't want to give the bank families are related to the actuaries
I just think you just said it
He says x-rays all the time and I think you just threw out the
The three banking families because it sort of like
A hat tip
Do you like
The old-school conspiracy folks who might be lurking
I love me talkin about bloodline Riot making
How you doing up there old school before
Districts that are going around
I also have
To do with future prediction
About lifespan
That are pretty trouble
Years and I say scientists are baffled
Time
Increase in heart attacks in
Soccer players around the world alone
If you didn't listen to Alex's show regularly it probably come off strange to hear inside any population of soccer players ever
Some index group for heart attack
But this is one of his big covid vaccine there it is
Okay I see you throwing your hands up in the air
According to some of his weirdo guests there's a 66
* increase in the heart attack some on soccer players
And this is due to them being packed
Estimated vaccine cause
Sandy's heart attacks
There have been a number of heart attacks among soccer players in the last year but the problem is that what Alex and his guests are doing
Is preying on the audiences
Ignorance of some counterintuitive datasets
Princeton's let me read you this headline
From the guardian
More young footballers dying of heart problems than thought fa study
Defiance
He could seem like this would tend to backup Alex's Theory put in fact that article was published in
In August 2018 for covid
Even before the vaccine
Existed
There's this LA Times article from 2012 title
Quote be frightening frequency of heart attacks in soccer
There was a 2015 article from the New York Post titled quote
Belgium's young soccer players dropping dead of heart attack
Point here is that the issue of heart problems and soccer players has been something that experts have looked at in
I've been dealing with for years
Long before covid became an issue
A lot of the articles I read discussed the imperfect nature of pre-emptive heart
Screening particularly for younger soccer players
As a contributing factor to the higher than
Unexpected levels of cardiac
Issues
Another factor is that soccer is one of the more strenuous Sports you can play where your cardio is really
Challenge
So you have an underlying hereditary heart condition
For example
Playing soccer is up like that has the possibility of exacerbate
Make Edition even bringing on cardiac arrest
Makes me almost you know makes me almost Happy to have my little bit of CTE from high school football didn't have a heart attack
You dodged a bullet another thing
Consideration is maybe we don't we don't
Feel this as much as being people in the United States
Wiley price
It's by far the biggest port in the world
The beautiful game
It's sort of Representative Lee the number of people who you could
Say
Like had a heart attack playing soccer around the world
Deadpool Trilogy drawing is a lot larger
Is just got a soccer ball around wherever they go they could you could be walking down the street Heather and then all of a sudden you drop dead Mets
Soccer related injuries you see the
Amazing Grace
Every country they go to
It's just people kicking soccer balls around
Alex a weirdo friends
Probably know about this history of the
Correlation
Sure
Buy soccer players in Arkansas
Between those two things
So they can use the instances of recent heart-related issues
Among soccer players the fuel covid
Conspiracies
It's garbage
Yeah I don't even know where the 66
6 * number comes from either
I don't know who is doing things in multiples of
Devil were there
So there's another thing
That is going on along with the like covid this unsolvable problem the globalist of creator
There's another big
Catchphrase
It's running through this episode
And that is
All right look
We got Biden
He's the good cop
Fauci
Really the lockdown
Imask
Simplifying things that I do appreciate all Global problems being like good cop bad cop
Well
Global problems storical Global problem
An insane
Comparison girl
Horseshoe saw Biden come out last night and say
It'll hold you hostage
Copies a good cop
Bad guy what famous equation in in
Wait
I understand I understand he's probably just trying to call VIP mangala but unfortunately
Comparison that comes to mind is that Hitler is the good cop
We're doing right here
Viton is Hitler
The good cop
Incestuous the bad guy we were at
Battlefield
So
We we
Wie geht's
Alex discussing
Some calls
Media
To talk to him
Sure
And you're going to see more people from the power structure
Coming out against it because people are not figuring out if we don't stop this we're all dead
The Washington Post Pony this morning
Sugar
Sugar me on Pinos
Oh I like you over friends and I said listen
Surprise winner
System coming in is going to ruin her future I'm not talking to you
Cursed your children
Sure
You can just say no
I don't want to be I don't want to do this interview
Alright
Cursed your children that one that's a little bit weird to hear somebody obliquely mention to wash
You can post reporter
And and have the first thing I said to them was
You got kids
You courtesy of Carson
I'm cuz I mean that's it
That is a
That's not a Veiled Threat
Just ask
Hey you got kids like that
No that's a threat
You don't know the person to implying that they've curse their children really confrontational it's real
The rough way to start a new friendship
The phone call
Especially when it's a basic Xpress Incorporated
No I don't want to change my goddamn cell service
You cursed your children
I like the idea to that it like
Of course around this time Alex's
Obviously someone that people want to press comment from weather
So are the January 6th
You're saying he's a great Turtle assures somebody's got to say something
Send this a****** contact imagine that every time
You have cars.
I also enjoy the like
Yeah just heard of him doing the jack off motion about a Pulitzer
Oh yeah you got a pea
Balls whatever
So here's an interesting scientific
Idea that Alex has I'm fascinated by this a little bit
You don't just thinking their official documents
80% reduction
They're not actually planning a Revolt everybody inside
New World Order
Transhumanist
No one else allowed
Might want to absorb you but that's it and they're all battling to be that one God
Short totally luciferian it's Garden mean all over again
That's where you are
Look at your children
Being on TV and being with the establishment in your heart
You know when your bones at the fraud you know in your nuts that you want to buy it
You want to resist it
Water wants to come down hill
Go with your instincts
Who You Are
I'm going to really become who I really am in this struggle and that's why God put us in this position
Simulation of a real
Question of our spiritual power
Stop it
Important message from Byram Healthcare
Jonathan time at 1 right
I don't read enough science fiction I know that comes up on this
Show a lot because I don't
References are like that
Will give you males every now and again sigh Ki that was just a plot of blank
I don't recognize
Some of this deep sci-fi that Alex loves
I was thinking like
Is that just the Borg
Or something like something
Science fiction
Yeah I mean I got
Distracted whenever he said this is Garden of Eden all over again immediately following their these Corporation
Since fighting to become God so then in my head I was like wait
What part of the garden of
Eden myth
Do AAA is Battle being done
Buy multiple different entities in the garden
Free represent the corporation
Every bush
Is a banking family
You just don't understand the Deep metaphor
What's going on today in the Garden of Eden yet
I don't know also at the end there I I love him saying this isn't the simulation
Considering the entire reset was interview was about as a simulation
This is all a simulation
She might not like me
To hear that you can have the opposite
Choosing
To just see through it and then you then your knee
I do enjoy Alex's
Did it like Moviefone
Autopilot voice
That's that's always so great
So great
That's straight-up bulshit
Variance
Sincere
Schwab
Beastly where is he's the
You know I think he's really ascended to be one of the main villains
Is George Soros was really
Main villain
Years ago now he's kind of falling out of favor
We don't really talk about Soros at my contract
See I was a season for Soros
Turn turn turn
And it's a season
Where Klaus Schwab is the big bad guy
Alright this really interesting technique
Hi it in this clip
You'll be able to see what I'm talking
Mouth of Satan areas
Blood pressure to be together
Sign
Sofia Richie
We are here
Executioner
Future
Delta designs future
You have to execute
Kia
I think the next two days
We will
Aubrey
How we decide
Planet apes
Kobe
Define sistani
Power Wheels
Areas with corporate and governmental world leaders all together
Microchips your body alone nothing you like it
You'll have nothing
Dlive everything
Big Pharma
Alicia's weapon control the censorship
Blowing it all out
All the CEOs basically non-white
Indian
They've got it all
What
Anderson correction an afterthought
Close Schwab Clippers
Speech that he gave at the world
Economic forum
And we talked about that
So
If you want to go back
Was baby talk about it
In Greater depth
You'll notice though that Alex
Did this
Is this move that is referring to
He played clip of Schwab saying one thing and then as soon as it was over he makes
The bunch of claims about what was said of his conference
Anybody saying that they'll be microchips people have to put in their bodies and no one said
Anything about like you're knocking
An old anything and you're going to like it
I don't remember them
That was the topic of conversation
There's obviously video Schwab and everyone else's Beach is very easily accessible I mean Alex play the clip
He should have no problem putting these comments instead of mostly innocuous comment
Francois but he did play
Isn't playlist Clips cuz I don't
Exist
That means the problem
The problem here is
Alex is getting a huge assist
From all of American pop culture
Because even me like I'm listening to that accent
Just going
Something's evil going on here every time every time since I was a kid if I heard that accent
Somebody was murdering James Bond or some s*** you know
Like it's it's not my fault
That is that is playing into his hands
Quite a bit you can play him sing something innocuous in that
Accenting people especially Alec
Will be like that dude's f****** evil is she
Also I think
I think that the biases
Is Ron strong
And then there's also biases that Alex have
Are worse
In terms of
They put in non-whites I mean Hitler was
I find that to be a really disgusting idea this notion that non-white people are put in those
Those roles in order to make it so if you criticize
Their aunt there censorship activities
Oh your race
That really is
Deservingness
Any non-white person who's getting into a CEO role
Obviously got to be kind
Suspicious
This just being done as a mass shooter
That's the kind of idea that Alex is trying
Fright and really
Uno Alex
Has been censored by a lot of
He's been kicked off a lot of them
Danielak is a white man and he's the co Spotify who kicked Alex off
Mark Zuckerberg is the CEO of Facebook either way man
When Alex was kicked off Stitcher their CEOs Eric
James is another white man
Kick-off LinkedIn and their CEO is Ryan Russell and skeet another White Band
There's plenty of these instances of people who have
Put the kibosh on Alex's
Ability to use
You know
I was
I retook the turn
My turn towards hating white men
That would be a shocker
I think he's just ignoring those examples
And focusing on
Folks
Wants to hate because they're not white men it doesn't matter if you hurt me or not your non-whites
You can also like criticize anybody you want
It's not racist
If you can
If you guys don't be racist
I was actually thinking about it I'll take it out
Is mature enough to do that
Considered the possibility but the
Fentanyl the Chinese dragon
Then I realized
He's not going to be able to
That's how you want to like
Direct a lot of your criticism of
Doesn't give me hope
Criticize
Is the Chinese government plenty of time
X without saying
Any racist
Mike zeroh
Jason Statham
Can I have a
A full conversation
YouTube
And some of the problems with it without attacking
As Susan with Jackie from Evil Woman
You just don't
Completely unnecessary but I don't think Alex can I think he
These two hung up
So my man
Who's the good cop
No no no
Don't worry no lockdowns
Normalize her to take whatever shots we want to give you
Always wear your mask from now on
Oh how nice of him
The New Normal
Wow
The good cop
She's like no no
They'll be mandatory by next year
Born babies
In the first quarter will get the shots
I'm a nice man
Good man
I'm going to help your children
All the mass murder in Manning commercial
Bible verses and remove even more of God's protection
Oh I hate that
Children
The castle
I really
I really hope it all those cool skeptic bro types who decided
All of a sudden that Alex has been right all along
I hope you're excited to realize what they've actually done is sign off on a right-wing Christian Fundamentalist
Extremist
It's hard to be iconoclastic and pretend that you're in some kind of a noble opposition
Group against Power structures but honestly
It's really impressive how Alex is managed
What's the scam these people at the
Take that what he's doing
Someone like Joe Rogan or Tim Dillon respond to someone who was
Alex saying that they need
About these vaccines because if you like then the devil will have free reign to come and make Mischief in the world
That's someone who wasn't Alex saying that
You think they want to talk to
You think Tucker would
You guys going to take timer to show to call that guy a great journalist
You know he's been right about a lot of things I don't know necessarily about the
Underpants all of it the bums me out even if
Even if God is real 100
Percent literal Chris
Christian God is real if you're telling me that this guide is at a point where he says okay fine
If you guys want vaccine
I'm going to take away a little bit more of my protection
Not all of it
How to take away
Guess what everybody
Can break their knee easier
That's it that's it that's what I'm doing like that God
Well it'd be really weird to imagine that
For a while God was
Was taking his time to make sure people had a harder time breaking their knees
Exactly
That seems unnecessary
Finite
Find your God but I'm not going to worship you I wash my hands of you so to speak
Well I regret to inform you that got protection I was going to make it harder for you to wash your hands
So one of the big things that
Drew attention
Into this November 30th
Episode
I was that
Some listeners
In Australia
Certainly a new Wok
Lachlan
And it turns out
That a member of the Australian government
Happened
To be on Alex
To show
Ayanna
A prompt
Bubbly
Probably too like
Really push
Legislative progress
The policies that they want Australia to adopt
No they went to an American radio host early
No
Nirvana
George Christensen and
Nike until especially
People from Australia who have reached out
Guy's a weirdo real piece of s*** Alex giving him a nice introduction with
Sweet old plug
George Christensen
He is a member of
Parliament
From
William
And he is
Of the ruling liberal National Party
Patient First
Cubs.com is where you can find
Informative
Waiding
So I have a little bit of a sneaking suspicion
About what's going on here with this interview with the Australian MP George Christie
I think he knows exactly what he's doing he's he's making
Some Sensational ass comments
About how
The covid response
In Australia is like
Nazi Germany or stalling
I think he knows what he's doing and showing up in places like Infowars
He's been in office since 22nd is a long history of being a bit of a dick but the swing he's taking now is
The bitlord
Hey birthday to tough time figuring out what was going on but in the course of reading up on the situation
I read in a few news stories that kristensen has already announced that he's retiring from his position as MP
At the next election
Yes absolutely nothing to lose from a political
Perspective
Everything to gain from making a name for himself in the reactionary as right-wing media sphere
Ever since he announced his pending retirement earlier this year George has been ramping up his efforts to create online Revenue
By creating this upstack newsletter
As long as using Telegram
A nursery telegram types
Creeps bigot
That is
He's looking at that he's looking at that Greenwald substack money in thinking I would like some of that
Along with that he was asking his political party the liberal
No party to disinter
So we could keep a little bit over $105,000
In like a severance thing
A writer named Tim Wilson noticed that around this time to Christensen was getting pretty heavily involved in using his news
Letter to make a book recommendation
To his followers
However this wasn't just like eggs
Read this book
Yeah it was also Christianson using Amazon affiliate marketing program to make a cut off the books
How the people bought through his leg
Get them coming and going
This kind of action has been seen as a bit Shady
For a sitting politician
Engaged
It feels like a strong indication that he's trying to make a move into the arena of monetizing
The following has
From being a bombastic
Politician
The picture of what he's up to seems pretty clear to me like
Actually being engaged in politics right now is a nightmare
Sucks thanks it to the opportunistic politicians and media figures and brazen
Conspiracy theories as a marketing tool
And now he's
Do you think getting out of governments
You keep using that marketing tool without the
Ditto
Expectation let me clean up the mess
What they're all doing this is essentially the gold rush like they're all in the East going like
There's no point in staying in Washington government anymore
Tricking dum-dums into paying for shipping don't need
Also I want to get too deeply into this cuz it seems really weird
Christensen also apparently has the nickname the member from Manila
Indian. Fishel circles because
An investigation revealed
Between 2014 and 2018 be taken at least
28 trips
Cast of the Philippines
Sprint proximately 300 days there
It's all people have seen that is quite since
He just likes the food
Sure
Suspicious going on there it's a lot of trip
I mean come on and with the government
Does the Philippines have there's no way that you would experience any kind of corruption through that
Certainly.
So
Look George likes Alex
And that's great
Because Alex
Is a great place to Market yourself stack
And so that's probably what
This going on
Well thank you very much Alex
Bacon's we have around the world
God bless you search if they were interrupting at all time
12 like to hear what I have to say
Like to eat
People getting up and standing up for freedom and going against the
Vaccine mandate
What's a duck say
There it is consumed Australian
Q in the political leadership landscape that actually a standing up
Proofread
Back out for you to miss things
When
Government control
I'm not positive with true Freedom means but honestly just kind of sounds like a fun meeting was buzzword so to think
Guitar model shows like
Also it's
It's really really f****** funny for me to hear this guy say that there's very few people that are standing up for
True Freedom within the government knowing that he is retiring from his
Position is empty at the next election
If you actually believe there's a shortage of people standing up for Freedom against
Security within the government
Wouldn't the last thing he would think of
Badoing beat
Voluntarily leave and I will unless I have to
Looking for true freedom in the government
That seems nonsense
It seems like his ideas
What is expressing
Alberto's action
Either that
Or he thinks that having a sub stack and going on shows like Infowars
That's a more effective way to influence Australian government policy
Actively involved in Australian governmental policy
Well I mean you know
It's like
If you're the leader
Of a group of Freedom fight
You know trying to
You get true freedom
People and not just
Not Justa
The people in government
Then
Naturally what you do is you say
There aren't enough people around me
So I quit
That makes the most that we all remember when Nelson Mandela said this is too hard
I'm starting a livejournal
You know what
My MySpace page is going to take off
Yeah and then I'm going to be in a band
That's its
Heroes of true Freedom have done
All along
When the going gets really tough and there's no one standing up
Could I do that I'm by myself use my Amazon affiliate program to Market books to my dumb dumb followers
Megatut office
As the world ends around me I'm going to be a little bit more comfortable than other people
Yeah
Seems kind of like what a s*** head
Anyway
Some concerns
Rarest
Another shoe
You cannot hold a decent job unless you are vaccinated right now this second
Vaccinated
Social life
Popeyes restaurants
Where's Museum sporting events
If you're not vaccinated
So we truly I gag to have home
This is cute and all but it's also pretty stupid
George says that you can't hold
Decent job in Victoria unless you're vaccinated and that's just not
True
In early November Victoria announced the Mandate that workers in many fields will be required to be back
Estimated quote
If they want to do their jobs on site rather than working
Being remotely
That's a little different than exaggeration
Employee
Open situation
Cleveland there's a broad vaccine mandate where many businesses and venues will require proof of
Games to enter
Specifically though as was reported
In the Australian quote
The Mandate does not apply to essential services such as supermarkets
Retail stores public transit places of worship
And funeral
This is not something like apartheid partially because
The choice
Apartheid was a system of racial discrimination where the people who are subjected to it where a brass because of an immutable characteristic
The color of theirs
Skin
In this case not getting vaccinated is a choice
And that choice comes with some
Central benefits
Some drawbacks
Not getting vaccinated allows you to be super combative and print pretend that you had some kind of
Bizarre moral High Ground as it relates
Freedom
Which were someone like George is almost certainly a benefit and a marketing tool
And he's using it
Conversely a drawback of that decision is that you may not be welcome in many public spaces until the
Pandemic enters the Lesser
Endemic space
Because your decision to knock
Vaccinated puts people around you in those spaces at greater risk of
Contracted covid
Including be like other unvaccinated people who would be there around 2
It's like having a car
That you
Taped a s*** ton of Swords 2
That extends straight up
To the edge of the sidewalk and you're like what
If somebody gets cut by the source
Because they're off
The f****** sidewalk man
What I can't have a car now I can't have a car with a bunch of swords on
Interesting metaphor
Not many people go to
Are the car with sword metaphor yeah I was caught off-guard by that I will say that
The reality of the situation surrounding vaccine requirements to enter certain venues
No actual similarity
82 apartheid but that word because
Alright think
Can people are offended by the historical reality of South
Apartheid
18% 90
It's really
Weird because he's
That not actually against
Actual apartheid
Apartheid supporters on his show
Yeah a historical heroes people in the John Birch Society people like Gary Allan
Very strongly
Opposed to the elimination
I'm not sure if this is like Solid Ground for these dudes
Do we say it again
I don't I don't know if
Cigna Medical Apartheid on Infowars
Is really
Worthwhile it would be a little bit like a
Appealing to the
Speech for the letter from a Birmingham Jail
Conversation
And they can have about Medical Apartheid but it would revolve around how many parts of the world don't have access
Vaccines even if they're public wants them
German article in the New York Times
Worldwide about 76% of shots
Instead of going into arms
Stupid administered in
Mahai and upper-middle-income
Countries
According to the our world in data project
At the University of
Only point
5% of doses administered in low income
I think there's an argument you can make it
In terms of
That
But if this this nonsense
George is going on about
Less
Less real
So there's one way that George
Think that you could stop this
This whole
Medical Apartheid
Basically just a get rid of
Data
Settled
Something that I think would stop it
Alex's that we had
Which is actually owned by the federal government
Mandatory vaccinations
The hints to the state
Governments that doesn't want them
To do this
That is simply
It's nice type government
Corporations
Treating that work is
Like slaves like chat
Remind if you got to work for us
Maximize it
These corporations
Outfits
Can actually tell their employees
What I can and can't do with it
So I would say
You know in the middle of a pandemic is always a good idea to get rid of data
Like that's usually that's a Sound Decision right
Stuff I do like that the right-wing respond
Wants to like
Okay so whenever we learn about history it doesn't
Look good for us
What if we just
Got rid of history
In the present Noah really bad news for George about what corporations can do at least in America
I'm not sure about Australian labor labor relationships but there are so many things that you can do with your body that can
Can totally get you fired
Tattoos you can be fired
For that give me fire private piercings that your boss doesn't like
You can be fired for having a tan
Conventional hairstyle that the boss is uncomfortable with
There's a bunch
Situations where you can actually be fired because you smell bad
We're so far away from living in a world where the choices that you make with your own body of
Protected from being used by
Employers to fire you or to not hire you
But there's another irony
Alex absolutely cannot advocate for better protection
Confirm
That's essentially a violation of one of his big principles
Freedom of Association
Is a voluntary agreement on both sides
This is just incoherent isn't ideology
Like employers obviously should be able to hire or not hire you based on whether you got a fax with you
I mean the
The fundamental
Angle here is
I don't think
Private Corporation should be allowed to
To do what I don't want them
Time to do
But
If anybody else tells them that they can't do anything
Especially if it's something they paid me
Then
They're evil
Yeah yeah
It's just
Self-contradictory
Anyways
It's very dumb
So
This is this is largely about promoting that Subs
Amazing working ridings at Nation first. Sub stack.
We've got to jailbreak Australia folks that's one of the main places
We've got to fight this tyranny there to stop it here
Los Angeles in California New York Cesar globalist
They are all our brothers and sisters and we will break them out we will bring down the globalist covid dictator
Mayweather George Australia straight-ahead on Alex Jones
Ward.com the tip of the spear
Bigamist I'm at break 2
His timing is not there
I also feel a little bit off to recording care like I feel like my
I don't know how to do this right now everybody is taking a little bit of time away from you
All of a sudden I feel strange
Schedule and I cannot that's why I can relate
It's Alex
Trying to get to the break
Hey happen
It happens you're not on your game you can always be on your game every time you see a late night show in there like we got a great show for you tonight
I know you don't
Yeah
I don't know what Alex means we have to
Jailbreak
Australian Cattle jailbreak Australia
That's weird
It is an island
The continent and we cannot allow that any longer
Jailbreak it
To get some
Grappling hook
Okay Pull It in reel it in
I also
Can't Stop
Thinking about that song tonight there's going to be a jailbreak
Lyrica that is tonight there's going to be a jailbreak somewhere in this town like the jail
You know where it's going to be
Jailbreak it like me
Pizzeria
Alex Williamson reports
About the situation in Australia and wants to bring these up
Welcome back to the Alex Jones Show Our Guest has agreed to stay with us for the wrestling hour and that's good because I have a lot of questions about WhatsApp
Australia
Helicopter
Miles away
We're going to go make sure they're all inoculated with none of them around civilization it's just
Wild and images of a Megalodon and paddy wagons and driven away
This is really really Draconian stuff
Foot bunch of nonsense
2021 article in the New York Times a couple of really important points are raised about the vulnerability of the Aboriginal
Communities in Australia
The indigenous population only has an approximately
15% vaccination rate
In New South Wales quote
Most of the area's 98 coronavirus cases are among
Indigenous people
Piccalilli serious issue here because among indigenous populations there's often a higher prevalence
Conditions which would put people at a greater risk of
Severe cases and death if they got covid
The article includes this paragraph
Quotes
The dark Elders group
Association of Aboriginal Elders in Wolcott
Quote
Many of our elders and other inweld others and will get experience health and social issues
Vulnerable to
Contracting covid-19
The impact on our community
Could be devastating
In there. Meant their first
Request was for more trained nurses to administer vaccines
Indigenous Australians aren't being rounded up and if Alex were forced to cite a source on this he would stammered and then he would just try to change
The subject
There was an article in the guardian actually from late November that included a comment from the Aboriginal Medical Services
Alliance
Of the Northern Territory
Who said this was all nonsense
The Northern Territories chief minister chimed in
Hello to all the conspiracy theorist overseas watching this
Please get a life
That's one way to do it this wasn't response to how cook over the past few days.
Circulating online that Aboriginal people
From binjari and rockhold were being forcibly removed from their home
And take him to enforce the quarantine in Howard
Woodsprings people including children
Being forcibly vaccine
Right being made
Ivy
Original Medical Services Alliance
Northern Territory and the Northern Territory chief minister
If John didn't have been like oh f***
He's making it sound like it's
F****** cops driving up to a campfire Baelish
Interesting Lee they're also in this past August
SV Australian government announced
Today would be paying approximately 280 million dollars in reparations
Two survivors of the period between 1910 and 1970
We're digenous children were rounded up and take
Taken from their homes
Washington Post article about this nuts
An official inquiry is estimated as many as one in three ended
When is children were forcibly removed from their families Nationwide
I'm taking the school
Wow
Just a bunch
Psycho
Just a bunch of fun
That's real but what Alex is talking about
Non-non real stuff
In addition to promoting the sub stack
What else really wants here cuz he's got
Somebody that
Is
In an elected
Position
It somebody was kind of
Play this up
That's what I really want
Is
For George
Forgive like
A message
First of all he wants a message for the freedom lovers
I also want the message for
The Pirates
Basically a bunch of times
So here's one of them
She got someone
The layout basics
Information
Real quick Alex does play the clip of George
Responses like Nazi Germany
Ebola
Did not enjoy it man basically he got censored or talked over which is
How could
Horrible
Call shoaib
His message to
Patriots
But I only care about the street
What is his message to the world
Millions of people are watching right now
Position Sheraton Millions more
Cannot stand
This information coming out exhaust and L
Where they are arresting and basically disappearing people eat
This Edition has gotten a little frenetic
Else is speeding up a little
I also do at the end of that clip
Really really interested me the way Alex is phrasing
I would love for him to try and
Explain in any kind of a coherent fashion have something happening Australia
Possibly serve as a Presa
For us laws
We have entirely different kinds
2 Chainz
Different organizational structures of government
The idea is
Is really really stupid but Alex says it all the time
Like it's an idea that's so dumb
But it often goes in one of my ears and out the other
Think about it
You're not understanding that Australia is weakening our first amendment protects
In the same way that God is weakening his protection over it's and it's all over these jab legitimately don't know what pressing
Could be set
Buy Australia
For you as well
Somebody at the Supreme Court day like one time in Australia
Cool
Alright
All right it is that going to help us what are we doing here
Well
I guess I guess we've reached an impasse we've got to follow precedent here
What are the things that he has primarily focused on in this interview that he really wants to nail down
Is about the idea of there being
People are going to be taken
There is some camp
Tell us about the
Wants to know about those and they're in there
You're going to take shots on a routine basis
Don't talk to your neighbors I mean
This is why God episode of Red Dawn or something
Spanish Gary
Very very scary and lot of paper
Questioning
E4
Incoming arrivals
Korn change
7 diezman the question is
Security
Christmas
The second thing is that they're actually
Nothing used for
Incoming arrivals
Endeavor July
Round Up anyone who dis
And put them in there
It's going to be like
And I want to come and get laid
Designview
Into some quarantane cab
So there's there's two quarantine facilities in the Northern Territory
There's the center for National resilience
Annie Alice Springs
Quarantine facility
Australian to a returning to the country into the airport
Vaccinated or not are required
To go to one of the centers for 14 days
They offer flexible payment plans and there's some amenities like there
Get food
So they don't look exactly like a prison
I bet you could probably find
Some pictures of like
Offense somewhere probably find
Something that would look
But don't look
And you got people like this f****** dude winding up in a quarantine camp and they're going to
In May Robyn Dixon wrote an op-ed about her experience staying at the center for National resilient to the wash
Washington Post
Experience sounds nothing like
Like what George is
Describing it sounds kind of just like
I may be a slightly annoying Resort
Beautiful
Yeah I wouldn't want to go to any Resort that I didn't
I have a choice
To go to a really nice place I've been like I didn't want to be here right now
From everything I can tell these primarily exists to allow travel to and from Australia without risking people bring a
Incase
Djokovic
Unless George could demonstrate any of the stuff that he saying I'd love to assume that he's
Alex and making s*** up
But I do think
I think there are some
Instances where people can't quarantine on their own
They can go there as well
So I don't think it's
Entirely for travel based
Quarantine right right
Did the way that it's being discussed here just
Does not match up with n
Anything I could sign
Yeah I know I do appreciate that
What style of old man beating his chest
That's like hey if they come to my house
And try and steal me just cuz I had it covered posit
Like
That's a thing that's not going to happen
True orakai come to my home and try and kill me Dan I will fight to my very last breath
But you notice to how like
Like that ideation that violent ideation
Is the exact same as Alex
Yep it's
It's almost like the
The fantasy of being able to fight
People off who want to take you to a fever again
Is like
Pleasant thing
Him and Giorgio Pizza in the same pod
In that sense a certain extent it does feel like maybe there is just a
Type of person that is
Criminally incapable of existing in a modern society and Woodruff
Prefer to return to like a
Fictional I fight for every bit of grain that I have it I guess
Something like that
Yeah George's interview is largely like these are some of the main points that get hit
There's
A lot of
Nonsense
Ninja Turtle
Boring conversation some conversation about the protest
Sure are the anti mask protest
And what have you
What are the things that people really
I took issue with
Is some of the comments he's made in the recent past
How about civil disobedience
And I don't
Know if you said anything that Rose to the level of like
That sound
Scary
On this episode
Sounds kind of like a s*** head was trying to get out of politics and into a right-wing
Grift
That's a smart move
I think it's
Easier yeah oh yeah wait wait
Jordan
Considerate
When you get into the right-wing grift
Like Alex
You're risking your life
Oh what
Free coming up here folks this is a total war
We could be
That's okay
Don't want to hurt and children into people
But I'm not
Just please keep us in the fight and please financially supported
Products you need
Like a Mountain Dew
So Alex goes out to break
And he comes back to
The 3rd hour
I don't even know what the
To say about this this is just
Bizarre
Ecology
Populations of
Former
Wealthy open Western societies
Attack because
Doctor problems their free
Chihuahuas playing are not
Compatible
Weather system
Springfree
Not going to want to be pardoned
Call Schwab and Bill Gates's new world
Order
That's why
Moral set by there
Scared of letting them
Break your will
Every challenge
Wind in your sails
Enjoy
Persecution
Joy
You will become stronger than you can
Does it mean you're perfect
It doesn't mean you're a masochist
You got to go through to protect
It will actually become pleasure
And once you have
How much people have attacked you and lied about you and you forgive them as Christ said
Absolutely
Devastation
Don't know what to do
Hot burning coals eponymous kryshak
You don't even want to do that
What transfer over you
Beautiful
And I've been a very angry person I've hated
Have you
My stress levels
Because I've learned to forgive my enemies it doesn't mean I don't prosecute him it doesn't mean that I do
What they're doing to stop
Let them know
Yes
Wow
Thought that I have threat like listening
Into something like that something as bizarre as that
First of all this is no place on the news
Absolutely not this is
The psychodrama that he's having with a nips
Second thing I think
Is
When he's talking about like you have to experience persecutions pleasure
Joy
Are you feel like if you believe that too much
You might want
2 Triana
Experience everything is persecution sure because then you can translate that into
Pleasure well you see people like
Pleasure and so they seek out expera experiences that give them pleasure if you enjoy quote-unquote
Persecution
And it becomes pleasurable
Then perhaps you have an incentive
To continue being a
S***
Well
Hypothetical person
I'm sure something I was
Is that
If I was
Talking over that song
Or if I started talking in that song was playing I would be like please stop that I got to write
This out this song put
Pressure on you
To deliver the inspirational speech
Conversely if that song was playing
And I was talking I would say turn that f****** song off
Because it you know
The stakes are too high
I look like an a******
I look like a try-hard a******
Pull it off though with the
Quality rating
Well then what the real question I guess we're left with his
Did Alex pull it off
Disagree
He's not a masochist though
Noshir
Sure
I mean he did describe Define masochism almost
Exactly though
Turning
The persecution of pleasure
Yeah
Kind of
And he said that's the thing he was
And that you should be
Because if you do that you no longer have to do that
No longer hate your enemies about how Brian stelter
Ears nose makes you feel real
The only thing that's true
That I heard there was
That he has been an angry person he has been
That was honest
I appreciate this
Alex does clarify that
In this
War
These in
And we are all in
Extension
The wind will not come
By tearing off people's heads
Which is good news
You're not going to win this
Standing up against evil
Being an example to others
Letting them
Troy Gentry
As man
Women can step in that office as well
Lily men's jobs
To fight evil
People should be hiding under a rock
Everywhere
What are you doing
Because good people
Stop standing up against it
Okay
Most the time I get in here and I cover like three stacks on 20
I really need at least hit on somebody else actually they're really important
Today's news
What is shocked you didn't get to the stories from yesterday
Behavior today would not lead me to believe that you're behind on the man refused
You cannot tell me tomorrow's news today
If you're reading yesterday Peddler
Okay well that's fair
We'll get some of these headlines
But first
Alex has to sing along with Born to Be Wild
Unreal
We haven't stopped caring Loveless a stop hearing
About article I love the criminal
I love them coming after me cuz I'm now making up
My children that I had chopped up and thrown in garbage can what
I'm ashamed of you know what I can just feel the change
Eternity
Thank you God
What do you think about that Joe Rogan
I get high
Oso
Seems like it was a non sequitur that's because it was
I thought it was very bizarre that he
Start singing along
I've been is like
I'm making up Rock Hill I mean yeah yeah
I think I think this is evidence of why there should never be a meteor
Conglomerate
And all media Should Be Your Own Boss
Because
Fuk fuk every new show if you
You can at least once a day go
Crank It Up Crank It Up baby it's pretty good
Crank It Up Baby get it out of
I worry when I hear things like what came
After the crank it up baby
Roberts Airport
Yeah
Think that we just
We keep getting
Like a clearer and clearer picture of
How much
Alex seems to be plagued by his past actions
And how much his history with abortion
Seems to
Buta he describes it as chains on him
And I think it I think maybe there is some reality to that
I think
In some way
Imagine
Persecution that he's experienced
He's turning that into like this is the
The Penance that I pay for that
And that's
Where he gets
The Joy from
Absolving me of the
The guilt that I had
Who were
Those Acts
Actions that I took younger in life
And that's pretty f***** up
Man I feel like if a
It's like a really weird oh church had just taught him how to hit his back with a cat-o'-nine-tails
When he was like 8
We would all have been saved so much
Like if you just want to flagellate f******
It's been going on for thousands of years man
Chop your backup I'm fine with that the lord loves it or whatever go for it don't scream at me on the radio
I think that's self-flagellation or
I don't know
Get like you seen a dominatrix or something to our would-be healthier Outlets
Then super healthy eating
A destructive
Political ideology
Talking bulshit on air all the time about stories that are
Not true not for the
First time has it been pointed out
That sex work is infinitely better for human beings then belief in
Talk shows
We get to the story
He's now that Alex has gotten his
Bizarre
Song
Out-of-the-way
So you're the first
Okay let's
Forbes
Yes
Go back CB mRNA changes your DNA
But it's good for you
Hey buddy
You're not supposed to say that
So there was a Forbes headline that was quote yes but I seen changes your DNA
Naturally this got some backlash so the author had the headline changed to add Clarity to it
It was updated to quote
Covid vaccines don't alter your DNA they helped you cells to strengthen your immune
The offers
Steve Salzburg tried to explain his point telling Reuters
Quote some of your immune cells multiply in large numbers to fight off the
Infection
Some of those cells stay around which is what gives you immunity
The technical point I was trying to explain was that those cells have slightly different DNA from all your other cells
The changes in the DNA of those cells which occurs through a crazily complex process called
Vdj recombination
Occur before you're vaccinated or infected
So the vaccine doesn't
Cause the changes directly
But it does change the overall make
Picture of DNA in your cells
I in your body
Anyway the idea that the headline was changed
Become a bit of an anti vaxxer meme
And that's about the death of a story that Alex is capable of covering so here we are
First headline
That's just one of those
Situations where
You by virtue of knowing so f***
Talking much
You just have these
Assumption
That when I'm explaining
To somebody
They know these
He's very base level
You know so you're like I can say yes it Alters your DNA
Because
I know
A million different like ways to
To contextualize that everything you're probably used
The talking to people who have that kind of
Nuanced
Understanding of what you
If you didn't understand so many of my idioms
You would think I know
Incomprehensible or most of the time that I talked to anybody about Alex Jones
It's not a fault thing but it is one of those that is a thing that you need to be aware of
Of going in
If you're an expert
You have to be aware that
That you cannot
Communicate
The way that you're used to
Communicating all the
You just can't
Probably not
The headline as it exists I was
It's clearer certainly
Be mad
Here's the second headline
Think
12 gauge double ought Buck right into it
The study showed you Sunday and causes the worst
Goebbels
One part of the Spiral repair
The worst
Weapon you can have
You just sit there
Immune system
Murder their children
Is
Is this a headline from yesterday as if yesterday
Okay
So I wasn't really specific at all I didn't know what to do with that but thankfully Alex start
Mentioning these studies
Oh, that he was talking about
And so we can
Secret Service
That's what's going on
Images of major study of stars coming to spike a DNA
Damage repair inhibits
Vdj recombination in vitro
What is in the vaccine creates the same Spike protein and does indeed destroy yourself
Literal
What are the conspiracy theories surrounding this article for this study don't even
Even say the things that he saying
About the like
Double
Severing D I don't know what's going on
Alex is Donner partying it across
West Coast I was a little I was a little bit worried
Cuz it didn't match up at all but then he has a second
Non-homogeneous DNA in joining
Pathways to double-strand brake repair
Nature.com
Really doesn't nice thing
I guess this is where we get to the double-stranded DNA break
Comes in entirely misreading the title of the study
It's actually quote nonhomologous.
DNA end joining and other alternative pathways
Two double strand brake repair
Also this is from an August
2017 issue of the journal
The nature reviews molecular cell biology Sheriff
The study of nothing to do with covid or the covid vaccine
It doesn't even have to do with anything that causes double strand breaks
Halfway
Do such breakages being repaired
4th and argument
Nothing has been done here and I'm
I'm just confused you know I'm not I'm not
Butter
If somebody is reading me something
And I'm like
I don't understand the words
Spin what you're saying
I'm not going to be like
Well then I'm afraid and I believe you
You aren't you aren't meant to be
What's the name of the game and it's because you can really tell by the way he's
Reading these pigs
Here's an easier heads
History of mRNA vaccines
Amazon
Yeah goes on and on
That's all you need to say I was just completely misrepresenting this article
It's mostly about how the history of mRNA technology being used for vaccines
Fraught with trouble mostly involving people not wanting
Invest in it because
Who sing this too expensive and the MRNA was too prone to
Degrading rapidly
Best most investment went to other projects and this is a very
Extensive
Discussion about innovations that were made
Different ways that
The technology went from
Being
Mostly only
It was considered as viable for research purposes into being something that's more
Applicable as a medical thing
Has nothing to do with any of that stuff
Cool pretty dumb
Here's I'm going to censor Alex
The same way that Christians
So this is really what I want to shows more about okay week
There were many of them not really
In-depth coverage this pisses the
Boba
Everybody
Josef Mengele on steroids baby
Society at his mommy ran it
Even on a mission
Kill you if you don't stand up and say no you deserve to die
If you don't stand for the children
12 in
I guess just sent
Demons nightcrawlers
I think Alex might have taken
Turbo Force at some point
Cuz he's he's getting weird
For sure you just playing
If you don't say no to a demon
That demon is actually God's punishment for you not saying no to edema
What's
Again I don't like his guy
Is God
Piece of s***
It's a mess so I I thought that we were done with headlines
But we are
It turns out
There's some other import
Stuff going on
Mass killings under communist regimes here is to
PDX
Deleted because it's racist
So there's a Wikipedia article on communist Mass killing
That was
Is up for delete
Sure up for review
Fertilization
Has nothing to do with racism though
That's
Some folks on Wikipedia believe in that the
The framing of all these events
Communist mass killings is not necessarily historically accurate
And it likes a bit of a new w
It should be
The applied to these topics again Wikipedia at like 8 doesn't have a board
There's no one in charge of it it's
It's not like there's a shadowy force here trying to whitewash communism
Really weird
That Alex is pointing to they said something that is worth
The pointed-toe recycle look
Conspiracy here actually does seem like I think that would be
Huge and Alex's world just
Because
If it were to become a
Accepted on Wikipedia to kind of
More nuanced
What's 2
Did the communist
Murder everybody articles
I've been more people would be like oh no it was a
Communism economics
System it was
The government
Audrey's place
Do you know what I mean
For sure but
Wicked Wikipedia
Anybody can edit it
You know like
Target for
Not nothing obviously there's no if they want
Yeah but there's a mass Purge
It's going well nevermind
Represent override Wikipedia
By the way honey go back to one of the articles on discovering earlier
Something on Wikipedia
Marxism
Saul Alinsky
Was Jewish Eden golfer cloud
Weather
What is happening
No part of this jump from Wikipedia to the abl
I feel like we've really lost with red hair
Wikipedia.
I think I know what's going on and that is that I think
Because Alex uses Wikipedia as a source
He doesn't realize that other media Outlets
Don't do that
That's what I say
Yeah Wikipedia Pages generally aren't even considered acceptable sources
College papers
Alex
But they're gospel to everyone else
Which is weird
But I don't know how we jumped at ATL
But somehow we did
Quick
And look
I don't know if it look up
PD page is the only thing that Alex has red on the idea of cultural Marxism
But it's definitely an idea that
The only promoted by deeply anti-semitic folks and white Nash
Either
Alex is completely lie
Anti-semitism
Relive any grass
On the topic is discussed
Stop
That was really weird
Yeah yeah that's no good no
I don't appreciate that and you're totally right
It's because like
If you're a person who printed out a wicked
Pedia articles
How to put on your desk
So you could read it on the radio
Then you assume that other media Outlets are just like well Wikipedia's good enough whenever he goes to like an overhead
Shot all the Times Herald just be Wikipedia articles in his stacks of important
If you print out a Wikipedia article you're the one who should be
Be judged
Don't know what to jump to the ATL was
Felt weird
Feels weird
And it only gets weirder oh no
Imagine
Water slide for all the nice wonderful Jewish people out there
Suzanne habash weird criminal groups and they represent them
Going out attacking and bullying people
Hiding behind shoes
What
They must be stopped
I don't want us to really come together under God day don't want us coming together we're very close to that they want to bring us under communism
Unity
So Kate
The abl
Is hiding behind Jewish people
In order to
To stop Alex and his friends
From being able to come together under God
F*****-up far as a way to attack
Jewish people I'm not under sure I'm not sure if I can understand a more aggressive way
Would you be like I hate Jewish people then to say
See Jewish people look at them hiding behind Jewish people
I got to get through that wall of Jewish people before I can get to those Jewish people
It's
Not a good look
But what he's doing is kind of making
The other side
Pretty clearly
So now I mean like
Okay we've had this interview with the weirdo Australian
Screaming over Born to Be Wild
You've gotten to the news
It don't make sense
Another exciting
Hundreds of questions on the street
Tons of emails and calls her to the office thing Tellez
About satellite phones
Military has gone way down on him
Are we really doing this
Compact model
I don't have them on the infomercial here
Get them on
On.com
Satellites
Water pump
They're not an infomercial but they are making a piece of video that's full of information
May Shield that can be used for a commercial
It's kind of like an information
Commercial the only response I had at the end of that way
Beautiful
Describe an introvert
The fantastic
Now this is hilarious
Videos like f*** this noise
Last half-hour of the show is this
Should have a satellite phone
And watch the game
Because I know you're one of the biggest suppliers out there you supply a lot of military supply line the board Pro
This motherfukers phone is cutting out
To have the best phone connection if you're a fungi
It's
Pretty fun
It's really really funny
And it's so bad it's connection is so terrible that Alex even has to call it out
Soon as I pull it out
Music
Clarity whole time I can talk to an engineer doctor
Family member for hours
I need to clear it's a lot clearer than your Skype
Hahaha
Oh boy
Do they just do it in commercial about Alex
Infowars
Phone for the rest of the day
This is dumb
Yeah I don't I don't appreciate
I mean
It's another Revenue stream it's yet another
The thing that we are info marshalling I assume that we're going to start picking up a lot more Prada
Enchanted we go along
Maybe
You know that mean
Beefy can attract people
Who were willing
To be involved
And if your Skype connections that bad yourself your satellite phone has to be sold on it forward that's kind Rob looking at
Yep
This episode like
It's just people
Just being shity and sell it totally Australian dude coming on but it seems largely about
Promoted to sub stack which is a revenue stream he's trying to create yet after getting out of politics you out Alex infomercial in with his
F****** satellite phone guy
Ridiculous now the first clip that you played of the Australian Christiansen
Is he was talking
Looking for so long my immediate note was he paying for the
Like that was
Ameet like the moment you're allowed to complete like $0.03
Fences in a row I don't know
Feel like Alex
Has taken a cut I for your tie that's interesting and obviously I'm claiming it is true
I don't know of course but
I think that it's
Equally possible that Alex thinks that this is a guest who has a reasonable amount of credibility given a publicly elected
Beneficial and that like
If I can get a great soundbite of them saying like this means war or something like that
That
Let them talk
Because we might be able to use something to make a compilation
Would be
Far more interested in
Giving
Why latitude
Does someone like him right
I don't know
Cuz honestly who really cares what he says on the f******
Show what it is important is if we can
Make a bunch of promos for this that play Forever that's
Millions you know sure
Sure I think it's
Probably
More likely a situation where they both have interest
Angela
Him talking boy
Hymn for the ability to promote himself and Alex for the ability to
Possibly use him later
Yeah two parasitic amoebas
F****** each other
Do jumping back into the present day was
Slightly disappointing Nose Day
Is because
Just
Want to talk about reset Wars
I don't even
Who you know what it is
That's why
I can't
Anyway maybe our next episode will be more about recent Wars
And not
Alex
Is normal
Incompetent sell here's what worries me
I feel like reset Wars part 2 is going to be named attack
The Clone simply because it's going to be
Exactly like reset Wars part 1
No I had to really almost
Physically stop myself from titling that episode The Fan
I would so close
Can't do it
On Friday but until then
Whatsup.com Twitter
Will be back but until then I'm the only one bzx
Clark
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work