Important
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Selena
Text June
Jordan Jordan
Emporia sup
What's a bright spot
My bright spot today Jordan
Is at Mariano's
Okay I can pronounce that for Chicago if you want
Mariano's
Where's Santa Claus at
I can only do real Chicago in one word
Mariano's has a Nashville hot chicken
Finger the prepared food
Sogo
I really enjoy it
I had it last night
So good
I'm surprised to hear consistently like
Mariano's in pretty good like I hear that a lot for everything at Mariano's
But I can say that I am shocked
By the consistency
Of
Supermarket chicken finger
But I was younger Universal standard I don't know if Universal but when I was younger than that Gerbes
What are the grocery stores in Columbia
Rate chicken
Spicy and regular off so good
I just
Go to Gerbes just for
For the chicken weird
Some the other hand the other gross
Every store in town.
Growing up where I did
Strangelet
Best Chinese food in my tiny miserable all white
Section of Illinois
Jewel-Osco
They had somebody there who is like f******
This place is a desert
Yeah they went for it man they make
I think I must have seen something on TV about like that great barbecue place that's in the
Gas station
Switch to Russian
A little bit similar
Took the argyle stop today which I normally do anymore
It's been a long time since I've taken the argyle Saturday
And right underneath that it's under construction of the right underneath that was the bodega that I used to go to every time we work
Recorded at your old place
Yeah I don't know the one you're talking about years or whatever
It looks like it was struggling
I used to live in the neighborhood number of years back
Goddamn places still there
Wow you are not taking that place out
Good for them. The construction and they're still going I used to live over near there
A couple years back and
Would get on the argyle stop to go to work I would work I work at the end or south
The red line
And I would go into that but they go pretty much
Everyday before going into
I just walk around like you got nothing in here
Every morning
Like I just want
Debbie or something I don't know
Nothing is amazing
It really is but good on them surviving
Somehow
Jordan today we're going to be talking about
The Sunday episode December 4th
2021 like
Who was too early.
So this is this is what you think I think
Play a little bit of ketchup
You got on some of the narratives maybe that we missed
Well we are taking our 2003 sabbatical
At least hit on one of the very large ones
A man one of these things
The media the people talked about regarding Alex
Let's say hello
So first the gym Carowinds
Institute for probably not human trafficking
I'm a policy wonk next love you came over from Pat Elsie and Mack
Macaroni Jones thank you so much
I'm opposed to that jazz band
Next Cavalier otics thank you so much
Consenting a in lieu of a
To give a shout out to
Charity
It was
Our timing was way off cuz
As we were at we were gone
When this game it's a little late but
Give a shout out to the find the lights on
I'm a policy wonk charity is a policy
And we got to take a crap in the mix that we like to say hello and thank you do demon feast
Technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
As soon as I came out of my mouth
I think we might have shouted
Already
I can't tell if we did
My bad
Armenian no it's
So Sunday Alex's is a
Weekend
Maybe lower steak
Who knows little little light on the light on the loafers there starts off
Pretty hot
Tuesday
Police
Personal drip
Hundreds of thousands of pages of documents
Report on the 1st
It came out
Those first 30 pages of
Total Criminal
Admission
First
Beginning of the
Show called vaccine
Pfizer
Causing thousands of death
Farms in new and covered it up well guess what
Facebook Instagram they're all censoring even medical doctors
I mean
Go to prison executives
And word is Jack Dorsey
He had to step down
Right off the bat like it's super fun
Decide to make up
The story about why Jack step down
Like a quitter
To fit in perfectly with the dumb conspiracy theories Alex pitching at that time
We help them out it was nice of jacked
The reality is that it's more likely that the investors in Twitter had put pressure on Jack to decide to either step down
Is the CEO of Twitter or
Square
Since they're both Jake Gant
Attic businesses
Snbc news reported prior to Jack stepping down he was quote the only person to be CEO of to public
Market valuation
The greater than five billion dollars
That's not that's no good
Yeah there been
Tensions between the investment firms that are on Twitter's board
A chemist feels like a lot more
Kind of that sort of thing
And if I were Jack
Ceo.of I would totally go
Square
Processing is way better than a load of s*** people running Twitter after deal with
Which is
Is a lot of it is their own fault
Problems
Or maybe The globalist Wanted Twitter to censor IPA document to Jack said no so he stepped down as a CEO the five billion dollar
Just for the principle of it
They decided to stay mum on the topic
Could be a possibility lately who quit or or Studio
Up to the censorship generally they've done so very quiet
And off
Sing with I kind of stayed at
Usher
I can't wait for him to go on Rogan and talk about how he was forced out of quitter
They wouldn't allow the censorship of
So I'm certain these FDA documents that Alex is talking about aren't being censored on Twitter
Just fine
I would guess that maybe Twitter could be blocking links to blog posts about the documents on sites like natural news
Things that have been already
He kicked off because of the bulshit
Yeah there's going on
A group called the public health and medical professionals for transparency if they filed a foia request
After the FDA
To release all documents related to the Pfizer vaccine
And then sued them under production schedule wasn't what they had request
This case is a little complicated though and the FDA have suggested that they might need a deadline of 55 years
From now to fully produce the request
The documents
Which is approximately
329000 Pages worth of material
That might have been asking for too much could you narrow down your request
Do they want everything
Give them everything
Almost
Comically long amount of time but this is
Huge amount of
In order to release them to the public by way of soya they need to review all of the
To redact all sorts of things like Pfizer's confidential business information
Any possible identifying information about the
The participants in the clinical trials
Busy huge undertaking and I don't know if it takes 55
Years to get through all that
But I can see why it wouldn't
Pick 4 months which was the initial request line from the group bring the suit
I want them to go ahead with the 55-year at this is like what this is like the Voyager now this is like we're sending it off
Who knows what'll come back with 55 years from now
November 15th
Pleading the FDA requested that they released batches of the initial documents on November 7th
19th and December 1st
And thereafter they quote
Propose to process and produce the non-exempt portions of responsive record
At a rate of 500 pages per
This is a tough situation and I can
Time to see both sides of it
I think they probably 500 pages
Sump pump is
Buying I don't know no no
So I'm really interested to see what's going on here and I needed to learn a little bit more
Like really
You know
Put my foot
Down somewhere
Immediately reading over some of these court documents
The way the plaintiff
Speaker group of doctors with that with the way they're presented themselves
Didn't sit quite right with
Thinking they was going to go in their initial petition to the court they seem to be attempted to come off as if their concerns they were based on
Desire to provide information that are
It will quiet
Axiom Skeptics
Releasing this data should also
Confirm the fda's conclusion that the Pfizer vaccine is safe and effective
Have us increased confidence
It's in the Pfizer vaccine
Is that where the motives of someone were following Aika
Can totally understand that
But there's just a tone in their second filing
The Joint status report that makes me think that this group might be a little bit anti-vaccine
Will kill all of you
There's some strange B like them insisting that the FDA produce the documents in 108 days if that's how long it took
Remind Pfizer began producing document until the vaccine
Target
Another part reads quote
In any event the FDA should welcome making these documents available to the plaintiff if it's confident in the analysis and review it
Nail and taking such an absurd and unconscionable position of waiting until 2076
To complete the production
Further Heights
Is the grave beat that these documents
Produced
Oh no they did not write forthwith
Doesn't seem like it
Listen to your position that kind of seems like something you would say if you were fully aware that the manager making isn't
Impossible
Give no expectation that it'll be mad and you're kind of just prepared to use that is proof
There's a cover-up going on
That's kind of the vibe I was getting I mean you're not
Tossing around forthwith unless you also have a familiarity with admiralty law and that's kind of what I'm
I'm driving with around here it some
That there's a there's like
Words that in college
I think it wasn't like I think was professor
Who was talking about like those words you should just never use outside of an iconoclast
Don't say it but I'm not going to say it out loud
I am I'm now dreading that I probably sent a bunch of time.
There's a list of list of members of this group on their website
Scanning it immediately an interesting name popped up
Polly Alexander isn't
And he was also a scientific
Advisor to Michael
Caputo Trump's assistant Secretary of the Department of Health of you
Human Services
Just being involved in the Trump Administration alone isn't damning but Alexander is influencing the covid response
Love it happened
Pretty serious
And it gives me some pot
It's about this group given the he's a member
In December 2020 political released internal emails from the Trump
Human Services
Department
I've some of them were pretty f***** up
Fourth of July 2020
Email Gmail to Caputo
Where you suggested that the country needed to open up Emmett quote
Infant kids
Teen the young people young adults middle-aged with no conditions have 02 little red
So we'll use them to develop herd immunity
We want them
I'm infected
In another email from that day He suggests
People spread covid to each other intentionally like having measles party
In later days figures like Secretary of HHS Alex Azar
Alexandra
But there are a number of reasons
The doubt that
In another email this one sent to CDC director Robert Redfield stop the release of the
The morbidity and mortality weekly report
Because he felt they were being used to quote
President
He went on to demand quote
Nothing to go out unless I read and agree with the findings how they CDC Roatan
And I tweaked it
To ensure 8
Fair and balanced and complete
Oh boy
Yeah nothing goes out unless I tweaked it
Ellen saying is we
Can't print out
QuickBooks
File
Okay we are just send it to some real familiar
Before we could
So this doesn't stop here other released emails you can see Alexander attempting to control
Particularly about the possibility of children being
Infected
He was fired shortly after these emails were released which may
Every got fired he seemed to strike a bit of a combative tone
In a lengthy email to the Globe and Mail on Wednesday at a subsequent interview dr. Alexander accuse the CDC of
Generating pseudo-scientific reports
And said he was more qualified to analyze covid-19 data that lie 1700 scientist at the age
Go to none of those people have my skills dr. Alexander said
I make a judgment whether this is crap
It's starting to feel like delusional narcissist just kind of meat
Hardee's or something and then overthrow
Well
At this guy he met Michael
Caputo when Caputo was a radio host
President's Administration that's what I want my radio.
And his fingerprints are behind-the-scenes on a ton of things that don't look great in hindsight about the pandemic and it's
Response
And he was only an advisor to Anna
Assistant secretary at the HHS
Ateez member of this group
But one sketchy Apple doesn't mean that the whole group should be
Be seen as suspicious so I kept looking
Another member of the group is dr.ira
Bernstein
He's a family doctor from
Toronto who's pushed
Largely supplement and lifestyle approach
Do avoiding a reducing the danger of covid
He's kept a largely low-profile but he
You did fly to Rome this year to speak at the international covid Summit
Which was packed to the gills with a notable anti-vax proponent
Ivermectin and hydroxychloroquine pushers
Like Alex's buddy dr. zelenko and passed in Fort Worth guest PR Corey
Who was the guy who went on Rogan show along with Bret Weinstein to promote
Hi Roberta
You may not be as big of a name on this as people on this lineup but you knew what this event was
About me flew across the world to be a part of it
What about all I need to know about his
His judgment
Also I watch
Just Beach from Rome and in it Bernstein recommended Ivermectin and Hydrox
Chloroquine
Including siding both as
Is preventive medications people can take
Prophylaxis
Just for covid-19
Also co-signers
Is Lex Luthor
Joker
Whoever Aquaman fought in the guy who is a manta Black Manta was that him
That's all they're all in there some other people have some like real
Serious
Maybe not as over but Siri is kind of like anti-vaccine
Urologist
Another interesting character is Doctor Lionel bassoon
Who seems to be most notable for being deeply involved in injecting Wall Street Traders with testosterone to quote
Give themselves an edge over their professional rival
I
That's my dream job
Dream job $2,000 with the last name bassoon just
Scamming rich people with injections that might
F****** kill them who cares but it could also if you could also make them manly
Mine's they're all screaming nonsense at each other
Bassoon people are not above board and I do not trust it
Their motive at all
This is a group that I find sketchy
Coupon I'ma Haven at the Goldman Sachs lunch
A bassoon recently
The trombone
I thought dr. trombone
My woodwind are a lot smaller than you
Even with all that set
It like even if I don't trust that group they're still putting out RealPlayer request
For real document show that's good
More information is a positive thing and the documents themselves could be assessed outside of whatever they end up using them for this
Whatever
Whatever spend there going to be dicks about it but I'm
I'm still happy if we get
Public document that interpretation
How the documents end up becoming public
That's more information
Hurrah
So at this point they're seven documents up on their website and two of them are text files that don't really provide any of
Information
I know from following the conspiracy world as I do that the document that's the most interest to it Alex
Talking about talking about very briefly
Episode do it
His top story is a document titled
5.3.
Six post-marketing
Experience.
PDF
This document is an analysis of the quote
Cumulative post off the reservation safety data
Including us
Stand for in post office relation Adverse Events reported
Adverse event reports
Received through the 28th of February 2021
But like we talked about with the various data that is consistently misuse by and Evac propagandist
The date of that underlies this report is also Limited in its application
The report specifically points out that this data cannot be used
Determine incidence rates of various potential Adverse Events
And is useful primarily just as a means of signal
Detection
Which is against a Prometheus
In addition many of the reported adverse event
What's come with
Incomplete Medical in
Formation about the patients
Making it essentially impossible to gather follow-up in
Information about there
Specification
And for these and other reason
This kind of reporting of Adverse Events is on helpful in determining if something is caused by a particular drug
It provides information just not that
Information
So in their dataset there were 40 2086 case reports of which 25,000 three
Had been medically
Confirmed
So almost 40% of them were.
Confirmed cases
Don't really know
It's a person actually had
What they're reporting
They had
It's okay
Get those get those at
Maybe maybe not
Yeah maybe not not for sure
Received then analyzed and evaluate
In terms of how much of a
Signal the data was coming in
To represent
Which would then continue to guide how the monitoring would proceed
Example they found their based on the reports anaphylaxis was an important threat they identified
They review the cases and found
The reports come again quote
Did not reveal any significant new safety information
Because there's already an awareness that there will be
Some potential allergic reaction
The people can have
But they have to
Any medication
And the vast majority of the cases had resolved
Of the 2958 potentially relevant events
So they identified
There were nine fatalities
But quote
Although the
Patients experienced Adverse Events that are potential symptoms of anaphylaxis
They all had serious underlying medical condition
And one individual appears to also have covid-19 pneumonia
The likely
Contributed
That's right
It's it's very difficult to do you have the number of 9
Anaphylaxis dataset
And
You could look at that
And say well
People had a flag
Responses to the shot
Medical
What's the reality is
With the greater amount of data that they have there's no
Proof that
Possible
Anaphylactic reaction that they had
Contributed to whatever
So that's
Kind of vibe of
Proportion
Looking over the document
If anything I feel more confident that the folks who released the vaccine are doing due diligence
The terms of monitoring
Post-marketing safety issues
That's not Alex's take on it and I get any type of document gets released he needs
To find a way to make it to
Open gone he's been
Looking for all along
The other three documents that are currently available on the group's website or long list of clinical sites and the seavees of researchers
Involved
I don't think of getting nearly as much traction with folks like Alex
It's not fertile ground to misinterpret things you can just grab LinkedIn pages and put them on your website and call the doctor
Get more than the LinkedIn page man you got the whole like resumes of people
Email address
So I took a little longer on this one in like got into some of the stuff because I know that this document was a big deal for Alex
The time that we skipped over
Address
The group that's behind the suit
I get a sense
Particularly if the FDA does end up releasing 500 pages of documents a month
Then we're going to be getting new imaginary Bombshells about this for a long
I think this is going to be
Something
We'll have to deal with I mean it's going to be a very annoying
My guess
And that's only because this is
Just how it's almost always were
Is that if the FDA test actually start releasing 500.
If it's a butt
They will then
Feel obligated
To work
To get through those 500 documents
Do you mean by that
I don't know man I don't
Think that
Everybody like Alex
2 plague
By the feeling of needing to work
That's true
That is true I think that they've made peace with that quite a while ago
Stick with it
I do you read a headline and make something up what are you sticking with
That's true other people will write a headlight for you that's all
What an a****** there's no debate
Now because all these documents Republic there's no debate that this is
I kill you
99 in the anaphylaxis group little over a thousand actual fatalities
Deaths that are reported in this document
And obviously
Not all of them
Maybe
None of them can be definitively proven to have been a result of
The data that's available shouldn't
Be using that way anyway
And Aunt is breakdowns of like the individual things like the anaphylaxis
They have the instances of death
And
All of his other mitigating circumstances to say that you have confirmed this is the Smoking Gun yes that is going to
Alex
Okay before we get to this he says there's no debate I would say that
There's a little bit of debate
There is
There is no discussion
There's no debate
That
The government documents in their own admissions are this doesn't
Protect you
It erases your immune system
Contract
Need more likely to die
And it was all a premeditated plan
We are here in the middle
This
How do you operate if you think that's
True
I don't know
Implications of it are staggering
I mean
You have to feel completely unsafe and literally every moment of your life
What can you trust anyone
How could you go to
DMV
How could you
Just get a driver's license whatever works restore
They're killing you you think they're going to give you a non poison potato
The level of
. every living in his
Just
Impossible
Like if you're in that
Completely paranoid headspace how do you not start thinking like
Oh obviously
If all this is
True
Then up Alex's
Clearly here to pacify me
I'm at that paranoid skepticism
The very person who supposed to be the only person you can trust everyone is murdering me why am I still sitting here
Here listening to this a****** tell me not to do anything but give him money
And how could he be
Be here that the only voice you can trust
No do you get anybody
Nope there's just one person you can trust
Please eyes crazy I just got into a weird space thinking about that lie
City horrible 2
To live into think this is
True yeah I mean just
Is if your
If you're that influence that you're either bored or you're just trap so Alex has a little bit of news about close to us
And I'm going to need a citation
We're going to blame
On the existing Institution
Then they'll order those institutions they control
Publix
The public will destroy those institutions
And now the global is coming in to a failed state
Control
That is the plan
So doody under
I have no idea where you stay
Sing this from
But
Do you understand the plan
So the plan is
Call Schwab is like hey guys
Is totally cap
Asphalt and everybody's like hey man we got to take down Kappa
Them so everybody takes down capitalism
And then the globos are like
Surprised
Is capitalism that was keeping globalism
From killing all of you
Even though capitalism was also killing you
Now we're just going to do about it
Maybe
I think
That seems like what I was understand
Okay what are you
Is up here like a bond villain
Temperature
He's saying hahaha great reset
Right to destroys everything and then he tries to pin the blame on capitalism
But
This only prompts like
Like the Patriots a people like Alex
Forget the street
And start to start a shooting or something
The forces of the
Estate Rider sent out
To attack them or whatever they have a little bit of a battle
End up winning but in the process at the failed state
Savannah
Can come in and be like we own it
You know it's
Real fun
I think was the most fun part of being a patriot hat
To be the part where you assume you would win in a fight against
The state
Like as a leftist
Not once do I assume that I'm going to win in a fight
Get the state I assume the states going to murder me twice over if I come if I look at the state the wrong way they're coming for him yourself
Michael Ian Black
The whole thing the Showalter
Is it is it is an interesting aspect of their ideology so much of the
Literature that
It's a lot of the stuff
Disorder grow up on this
This fantasy ideology
Well the only reason we're not
In charge us cuz we're too nice
Back and allow you to oppress your all day
Everyone of you yeah it is
Little bit of hubris
Just a little
So look
You can save your own life
Okay to do
Are you ready
Not ready to do it
If you put out today that's on Bandit video
Because of the time we live in just like my broadcast or more Powerball
I don't like your FairPoint
It's only
4 minutes 50 seconds long
I suggest
Six Flags
Collapse civilization
But you do get that
Share it like your life depends on it cuz let me give you a little news flash
Your life depends on sharing a johnbowne video
My life
Depends on that
There's a lot of people who
Didn't even know who John Powell is there screwed
This is a little bit like whenever the Europeans brought Christianity over to the to the new world you know it's like
If you don't know about.
Jesus you can't be guilty of his original sin right
If I don't know about John bowne I can't
Be killed for not sharing with four minutes
I regret to inform you this situation
Responsibility to know about John Bonham
In the beginning was the Bell
Yeah so I'm going to dispute whether or not Alex's broadcaster more powerful now
He ended his show with a half-hour infomercial for his phone
Don't know this is hard head
Thanks.
One of the big things
That happened in time in between
Sabbatical in the past
Was there Tucker Carlson
Then came out and had some words
But Alex
I want
I want to talk about a little bit of there cuz Alex plays the clip
On his is she out
AC3 wanted to do everything except his job he plays a lot of
Sunday
The balance Dasher
Here is the first piece of this clip
Tucker
I got to say
This is
Amazing
Like there's no way
He's this stoop
Whatever else is done with the body
This is not a fight
Is it highly
Obviously
Punished
He's talking about the January 6th
Using a pretext
Something reset
Advisor Steve
What
What was the score
Fraud on a radio show that's illegal now
There's legitimately no way he's
Stupid that sucks
So intentional
Is f****** unreal
To imagine
Inform
People hearing that and being like Oh that's
What you're reporting
What's Wild
He knows damn well the band and got indicted for refusing to comply with a subpoena
Tucker also knows that the subpoena wasn't just issued cuz Bannon talk about election
She brought on his radio show
The subpoena letter is publicly available and has been for months and it's super clear why the committee wanted
Let's talk to him
Turn the letter quote
He has reason to believe that you have information relevant to understanding important activities that led to and informed the
Events at the Capitol
On January
For example you have been identified as present at the Willard Hotel on January 5th 2021
During an effort to persuade members
The Congress to block the certification of the election the next day
And in relation
The other activities on January 6th
It's true that the letter does also mention how band and made some comments that seem a bit pricey
Episode of this podcast that was released on January 5th
All the episode he said quote
All hell is going to break loose tomorrow
Just understand this all hell is going to break loose tomorrow
It's going to be moving
It's going to be going it's going to be
Be quick so many people said man if I was in a revolution I would be in washing
Well this is your time in history
It's all converging and now we're at the point-of-attack tomorrow
And all I can say is strap-in you've made this happening tomorrow it's
Game day
Man you know I really don't think he knew it Advanced that it would go as s*** is
Is it did and he was just using bombastic language
Right
That's the wrong day to do it he's got he had to have seen should happen on the 6th and just go
Remember we said an approximate
Bulshit actor pretending to not even know the basic details of the stories he's talked about is
Way less convincing than Alex's
Like Alex seems legitimate Leon aware of
Most
Library details
What story he's covering you just
Inno skins a headliner whatever
Tucker is feigning ignorance to allow himself to making
Incredibly stupid arguments will be impossible to make otherwise
It's more embarrassing
The bow tie
It's like
Through too much propaganda if it's what the entire world is lived through so much propaganda that you should have to at least try harder than
Let's let's take just like the really Bass
Part of that
Right
So he's saying he's asserting
Outrageous
That the committee
Would wanna arrest
Steve Bannon just for talking on a radio
I would be out
Now if you're a listener
Of stalkers stuff reviewer
Is that true I can't believe that that's
Terrifying
And you went ahead and looked
Get up you could very easily find the letter
Empty but no that's not the reason that they want to talk to him
That's not an accurate portrayal
Of what happened
And then you'd have to ask yourself.
Team
This is on Fox News there's no way that this
Accidentally slip
No choice
Yep
Especially considering that
If you've been watching
Tucker show you know exactly why
He got
A subpoena
Like he's going through all of the reasons that you would subpoena somebody like Steve Bannon
For the January 6th
By his defensive
Steve Bannon
He is revealing all of the reasons
He also defends
Rodger
Big a big Rodger Stone it's okay to publicly defend him
Well I mean unless you're defending his
They even subpoenaed Rodger Stone
Yet again
He was in a hotel room
Capital is being
Literally
Nothing to do with it
What does it matter
Going to jail again
So
Start arguing from a false premise
You pretending that the January 6th committee wants to speak to Rodger to get information about his
Direct involvement with breaking into the cabin
Tucker's doing that so we can brush it away with it
Deflection like Rodger wasn't even at the Capitol
How many can move on
This is important to do because if you were required to face reality of what the committee subpoenaed Rodger about it would take a while for
For him to explain it Rodger will come out looking not-so-innocent
Spoiler alert they want to talk to him by about his involvement in
Stop the steel in multiple members of The Oath Keepers that he paid for his personal security guard
Reportedly involved in breaking into the Kappa
Tucker brother not on pack that and I understand why I wouldn't want to do that either if I were him
Too messy I don't like
I mean
Defending Rodger
Rodger went away in the
The public
For a good while as far as somebody that you could
Even on the right
Defend Papa
You know they were like
Rogers a great guy but then they would just let it go you know they would
Just leave that on the sun I think the pardon pushed things a little too much
Yeah he's now coming back up
But somebody was like
Why is everybody picking on Rodger Stone
You shouldn't even be allowed to say Rogers name without like I was wrong
List of crimes popping up next
Do your name scrolling down like
Accredits decades-long Manos Rogers that should be his epithet title
So now we get to the alley
Alexis Park
In the Tucker commentary
Now the committee's
Journalist on the right Alex Jones
Truth is he in Spanish
In recent years other words
Nbcnews National Security course
Kendall
Margaret
The Russia House
She he would ask him
Real question
January 6th
I don't really
Interesting way for Tucker to discuss Alex's journalist
Merit
Take this piece by piece
Go for it. The first claim that he's making is that Alex is often criticized for his flamboyant
Oh yeah
That's not
It's the only thing that we positively affirm him towards
The problem with Alex was just a matter of flamboyant
The podcast
Exist
Like David Bowie or Prince or Elton
Little flamboyant
Stop playing
It's insanity
The things that Tucker is passing off as flamboyant
Things like Alex fake crying on are thinking about all the abortion
Transitive happened in the country
Things like Alex discussing in Greek
Detail how he stomped multiple peoples guts in
And when they do that it takes a person a long time to die
This is flamboyant
People do people think on it for that man also a larger problem that people have with Alex
Spend that I guess you could call it maybe Showmanship
Is the fact that he's constantly wrong about things and use makes up s*** all the time
He basically just skim headlines than improvises what he imagines the story is about and how it connects to his larger
Conspiracies
It is much bigger problem than any kind of
Imagine flamboyant
Okay so maybe we call him a journalist maybe we call him a guy to maybe we blur the line between the two so
You don't have to worry about that
Fancy truth that you
Keep talking about Dan
The next point is interesting as a Tucker seems to think that the fact that Alex was super combative again
Against the idea that Trump's campaign and Russia had any
Is the primary variable that makes
Emigrate journalist
Guide to reality
I feel like there's a larger picture than that one story in two that Alex was super wrong about Trump and Russia
Constantly
Give right though that the hyperbolic claim that Trump was Nathan to brush it wasn't correct and I guess
Alex knowing that makes him an offer
Some journalist
East Coast. Maybe
Well I guess so I guess Tucker will report on that next to
The other thing that qualifies Alex as a real good journalist is the Tucker thinks that if he sat down with fauci
Instead of being a sicko
How's the terrible news for talking about what would happen if Alex interview fauci
It would begin and end with Alex
Accusing pouch of crimes against humanity
You probably try to put pasta under citizen's arrest at some point
I'm sure the devil would come up and is supposed to ask
Questions
The conspiracy means he remembers at fauci
And trying plug is website
Are you would also make fun of fauci using County
His voice yeah probably do an impression
For sure are you accuse him of his last name meaning the sickle
At least a few times
BBC to know that Alex will treat this less like an opportunity to ask real questions
Morgan opportunity
Ready to do a publisher
That's what he does
And
He would treat fauci so obsequious Lee while not on a
Probably I can't believe that you came on my shows
Great I can't talk all the time anyway
Philip theaters Manuel just Philip theater in your famous and I'm not at all sycophantic
Finally Tucker search
That the committee is threatening Alex of prison
Because he makes fun of Joe Biden
That's dumb and it's not true but really what all the screams
To me is that Tucker doesn't watch Alex's actual work and it's kind of banking on the hope that
Not many people in his audience to either
What he saying is laughable to me because
I know what Alex's show is
Like how we interact with information Howie's
Flamboyant
2 *
But if you know like it's all you know about Alex's the little glimpses you get from time to time a Grogan
Podcast you might get tricked by this kind of bulshit but
Anybody who knows
And listen to his show at like
Yeah. Just a little quick
Or whatever you know
This is not accurate
Christy is not
Is not flamboyant
So Alex
We get back to him
And there's some news out of Luxembourg
That there is a people who are having
A bit of a protest against covid restrictions
Transmasc rules
This is one thing that bothers me about the far right now
News media
I don't care
If anybody in Luxembourg
Is doing f******
Wow
Let's party
True I don't agree with you
I don't I don't agree with you I think people around the world that are all their concerns are all valid
Alex doesn't really know what looks
Showing you footage of Luxembourg Germany were thousands of people
Reality
Easy mistake to make tiny country and maybe Alex just misspoke or whatever
Interesting Lee though Luxembourg was occupied by Germany in both world wars
So it's entirely possible that Alex just thinks
To the country still part of the Reich
Sure like he's called Zimbabwe or Rhodesia a number of times I thought it possible that he actually just fix
But not the
Third Reich is still alive and action is still in the Soviet Union
I swear to God
He says Czechoslovakia still
Probably
So Alex has
Using source to get to
There is a guy who's an Archbishop
Things come up on the show
For Santa he's got a new letter that he's written
I don't do interviews X
Hoobly
The live show feed
Those who resist the New World Order will have the help
And protection of God
Italian art
Bishop
Bogano chests
Charge density
And Christ said
A tree by its fruit
Is there a Jeffrey by its 2
This dude's a retired Archbishop has decided to create a late-life career in sending letters out to talk s***
He's written a few that I want to talk about the past and we've discussed them when he has and now I guess he's back on his b*******
This new letter starts off sounding like it's an appeal to all
People in the world to band together to fight off the New World Order and Evil covid
Global coup d'etat deprived citizens of any possibility of Defense since the legislative executive and judicial power
Are complicit in the violation of law just
The purpose for which they exist
It's a global coup d'etat because this criminal attack
Again citizens extends to the whole world
With very rare except
It's a World War where the enemies are all of
Even those who unwittingly have not yet understood this
What does happen
At least that sounds unifying
Shrug
It's based on dump
Conspiracy theories but at least
There's a hope of humanity banding together to fight off a common enemy
Because everyone's under threat
This is kind of a little bit of Independence Day
A worldwide anti-global unfortunately
Did you read it
It's really just Christian nationalism
I invite all those who want to defend traditional Christian Society to meet together an international Forum to be held
Soon as possible
I called the Christian nations together from east2west inviting heads of states and the healthy forces event
Institutions the economy labor universities Healthcare
Information
To join a common project disrupting the old system
And putting aside the hostilities that are desired by the enemies of humanity in the name of divide and conquer
How great
He's trying to overcome the evil people who are divided
Screwing everybody by dividing the world into Christian or non-Christian country
Elisa cats in plaid
This honestly seems less like an attempted fighting something
Is it sounds like a new version of the Crusades
I call upon Nations and their
Ally themselves under the
The cross of our Lord Jesus Christ
The only King and Saviour the Prince of Peace
In this science that we shall conquer
We must gather our troops together and take them down the merry Road
In the name of our Lord.
It does seem like Crusade
That's the way of Our Lord Neighbors
Sorry
I got I got carried away by the spirit of the Crusades
Post on life site
He cites inaccurate quotes about the new world order that are actually identical to the one
Songs that are sighted in endgame
And even post
Points to the lockstep document
Some kind of proof of premeditation on the part of the Rockefellers
I was really impressed with the information coming out of this dude last time we talked about him and it turns out that his not change
Dick's always write letters for
Austerity is if anybody in the
You know what I kind of enjoy it it's old-timey
Yeah I just didn't they all start out like they're writing the Declaration of Independence series about the New World Order
Pen to paper everybody considered a piece
I use the cloud
This is Rick
Do you even have anywhere
So Alex
Like you how he's going to
He's got to get to the news
He hasn't yet maybe not maybe not quite yet
And then I'm going to cover
That are
Government documents admissions
Vaccine
The race is your immune system
Heart attack
Another Tucker car pees
I found this disappointing
I found this was yet another
Expensive Alex
Not getting to the point
But there is another point
He wants to get you before
Gets the point
And that is
The people
Excited
But he's going to declare war on Trump sure if Trump doesn't
Get on the right side of vaccines stuff puts all his power behind
Getting rid of vaccine Alex is going to declare war on him
He talked about that a little bit here
From Tucker on this
Jose
Almost there he's based
Asiago
I need to get
Video
How much are the VR go is vigano that's
We at fellows advisor
I'm going to go tomorrow
Keep staff
Then he's heading into bedding and
I just I'm fascinated by
How much
This is been like a I'm leaving
You can't stop me I'm leave I just
So disgusting
So just to give you a hundred more chances or man
16 or 17 more times you do the exact opposite of what I tell people you're doing and I'm going to be mad
This is difficult for me to string along
Good one more chance Trump you one more chance
Today we're going to get to the news
Or maybe maybe
Okay baby.
The gentleman
I mean I'll just be honest with you
Andre research all the stuff
I got a problem with this is all
We have articles coming up next
The government
And the corporations know they're telling us that it's on
And I know that's the message of the show but
Okay I'm here it's not even debated it's like
Shopping mall scene in front of the world app
O.j. Simpson really kill his wife
And Ron Goldman
Police in a white Bronco
Are the shirt I'm wearing navy blue
And the watch I'm wearing it has got a
Army green strap-on
Debatable
Petitions going on
Magically overwhelmed by the gravity of the news
Just immediately at the point where he's committed to buckle up and get to the information
Got to get to this going to get down going to do it that always happen
But it's time to get serious
Specifics
Too much to handle
Sirius everything is
This is like a kid to do his homework kind of s*** to the office at around 8:39 you spell
Send your little time dickin around and then you're about to get right to work and you're like I need a cup of coffee before I can really
Tackle what's going on here so I'm just going to step away
To also as it relates to Alex
The chirping blue
I'm sure that Alex's new hypnotist friend Jake Ducey would be really disappointed to hear that Alex
Think that's a certainty
I bet it's not debatable
Debatable not only the color of the strap on Alex's watch but what did I watch even exist at all
On a subatomic level that watch it is not solid
And your mind can change not only what color it is
But what it is to begin with
Is your bank account isn't
Observer effect
How's it going towards here
You're using their own words
Against
I'm starting just to build up a little bit of a theory that I'm working on fixing
The case that might explain why it's
Completely counter to literally the entire world do the DS Bowser
Excuse to disappear off of quick
Certainly
Certainly does
So
Except we're not
Because I looks like it's
Uncomfortable to talk about the news
But something else is way more comfortable
And that's just yelling about how people want to kill you
Years for years five-year tenure 20 years 1,000 years this is never going to end till we're all dead
Vaccinated
On all the lights
Didn't take the shot
They're the villain
Doesn't matter it's not a vaccine
There were last year from the shots
These people have signed on to kill a
Because that's the response of these globalist
The hospitals are all full of dead and dying from omnicron that's all made up it's from the vaccine
Omnicron omnicron first author
I kind of like
The omnicron though
Who knows what that can do
Yeah
There's that there's a certain point when I'm listening to this
These shows specially in the present-day it's
Just like
This is feeling
Sometime you have so much news you claim you need to go over
Going to get through this
5 stacks
Macron macaron
Everett
I was like they don't
Women
Are from Omicron Persei 7
Where is Mater from Omicron Persei
So
Alex get back to talking about the situation in Germany
But he's also talking about Luxembourg
So I think he does that
Think that Luxembourg isn't it
That show the footage we shot earlier
TV doors
In Germany
To the Christmas
Unbelievable
That's the same story about Luxembourg definitely think that's in Germany it was not a slip of the tongue
Really sad
Great City
The reason that Alex is doing that whether it's probably because he doesn't
No
The difference
But also
The whole thing about the Australians being like under a tyranny in Australia
There was a German politician
Who spoke out
Pam was like we have solidarity with the people in Australia
And so like apparently like a Germany is also under complete
Police state
According to Alex
Did anything that's kind of close to Germany
I guess you just going to say is a part of Germany
As opposed to having to be like all I'll also
Is a small country called Lux
That would be too much to introduce to his audience
It's this late in the game
You can't
You can't just suddenly invented
New countries for the B
Start a new country
Alex gets to the story's final
This time I'm not joking he actually.
German data analyst
What are the vaccinations
I was worried that this was that Alexa
So this was a paper that was initially released in mid-november and then immediately picked up by Alex's buddy
Steve Kerr shoe post
Substack and that it went around it
Conspiracy circles from the
Upon the release of this paper which made the claims that Alex
Does repeating
Tons of researchers started examining the data and found that the methodology that was used to reach the
Conclusions was useless
With one statistics
Professor calling at the equivalent to proven the correlation
Between store
Works and births
That's why I was a good line that is a pretty solid burn
That's the science bird
Received all this backlash
Essentially admitting
That this was supposed to be a private note that was
Commissioned by an anti-vax politician in Germany
Bergner
I was it was meant to be used at a parliamentary session on covid policy
Facebook
Wow
From the retraction
Quote
The reported and surprising correlation was intended to spark further discussions in analysis
We regret that this note was been so widely distributed
Wow
They went on to say quote
For clarification the notice
Is neither scientific publication Nora sound scientific study which means our own standards for quality
Are note does not prove in any way that a higher vaccination rate leads to higher mortality
We do not want this study to be falsely interpreted as such this way
They also asked that wherever people think this study they also mentioned this
Retraction with you'll note Alex's not
I
I am amazed
That
You can do that
Without also having
Look
We take money to tell politician
Bulshit that they
Want to hear you get it that's what we do
We took money
To tell this guy
Bulshit that he wanted to hear
Apologies so they could
Salad
I'm trying to run the world
Morally
That's what we are
Fundamentally because we took money that would give life
I understand why you'd want a more thorough accounting possibly of the ex but
I think I think they may have suffered some
Like professional consequences as well
I'm not I'm not entirely sure but that were tracks
Speaks volumes
And Alex
It would be available to him
I am at the point of doing this episode
He does not know anything
So here's the Second Story
Same thing in the UK
Under 60 or die
Twice
The same age
Statistics for
Fauci says
Good good stuff
Good coverage
Cover
That's
That's the way you informational fauci said
Kill the kids what
Speartip
What atmosphere
We're always being killed by somebody
So I'm surprisingly this also is
Untrue
It's a claim that was making the rounds tracing back to anti-vax substack enthusiasts Alex Barron
Basically what happened here's the Berenson took some actual death statistics from the UK but then represented them
Out of context
Text entirely
Essentially he was take
Date of the reflected the entire population
Asian people age 10 to 15 not considering any of the other variables that might make differences
Among
Differences among smaller age bracket
Kitson groups
Within that larger set that are big
Taking into consideration
Bear bear
Very clear footnotes on the
Statistics report that he is using
Age standardised mortality rates can be affected by different characteristics of the population
Can in the vaccine status group
Andy changing covid-19 infection rate
Therefore the ASMR
Do not show causal links
Between vaccine
And risk of mortality
Forgot to parse the data and use it how it's supposed
To be used
Different kinds of data are good for different
Thanks and this report
Even stress has some of the limitations that people making the APA
Argument from Berenson
Might want to use it to say
Quote while the asmrs provide evidence
What's that vaccinated individuals have a lower risk
Of dying
From coronavirus visuals
They cannot be used to determine vaccine effective
This is because the populations in each vex
Status gruppe are likely to differ in ways other
Then the population size and age because of the selected rollout of vaccine program
It differences in vaccine update
Basically this just another flashy anti-vax headlines based on a
Complete misuse of data
I wasn't looked into any of these stories at all
He's just
Dispassionately reading headline
I've no idea how could possibly be overwhelmed
Yeah this is this is not good
It's not good
I want a little bit more I feel like
Deflated
There's there's a little deflation there's a little deflation he's really avoiding saying anything other than playing Tucker
You're saying nice things about him
Sure
John bowne
Most important report our most important
Kubota Greg Reese reports
The people that don't
America
New York in LA in
Francisco
But we had
Liberty sorority their butt
Them
Now that's all
Going out
The window and
Show is all of our
Prosperity
Such an important race report
Batman. Video
You do a mask
So yeah to headlines
Some rambling and ever talk about Special Report Gregory
Just bad work
So it's probably no surprise visit
Report about fauci having Mass Graves
Is another misrepresent
Studies that were done between 1985
2005 which were funded by the niaid which traffic is the head of
These were trials and observational studies where the
Participants were children from the New York City Foster
Secure system
Who had HIV AIDS
The investigation found a532 children participate
Disney studies
And up there
25 died while enrolled in a medication trial
That piece of information is being used by
Conspiracy theorist
The claim the child she killed all these
These children
And his mask
In reality the report that
50 figure comes from what
By the Vera Institute of Justice
Delete author on that very
Report told the Associated Press.
The claiming that these deaths were related to the study is
Is completely misleading
Baby was able to review some files and found a quote over the 25 deaths of foster children who were in the clinical trials
The report says that a detailed review found that 22 of these
Twenty-five children
Had developed multiple aids-related complications
Prior to their enrollment in a clinical trial
Several have been enrolled in trial
Designed for those with multiple aids-related complications
Who had exhausted other tree
Treatment opportunities
Her options
This research report is
Honestly feels more like an advertisement for Robert Kennedy Junior's new book about how evil fauci
Yes I mean this is really it's obviously very sad thing
But it's
Very unfair to use this in the way that they're using
It's great that
The Raiders using a pandemic that they exacerbated to exacerbate a pandemic
Exit exit
That's great it's a horrible roast yeah
The snake was all tail
Headline
Sort of
Don't start going through these headlines
Majority of Voters
Concerned about potential of harmful
Side effects
74%
Concerned about
Headline that Alex's reading for Breitbart confused about what the context is
What's the connection between voters and covid side of
Doesn't know what to do with it
That now
I know for a fact
That Alex either didn't read the story or he's intentionally lying about
Because the 74% figure usciences the people who work
Concerned about side effect
It's actually a difference.
The survey found that nearly three-quarters of respondents 74%
Have been vaccinated
That's the first line of the Arctic
So what's going on here is that Alex just skimmed over the text so number
And decided to report it based on whatever you felt like it might be
That's not the act of someone who's a great guy 24 reality know that's a great guide for reality not a great guy.
Reading
About reality
Oh
I still might Point stamps I think it's
The actual figure is 50
Before percent that are concerned about potential side effects
But only 27% are very concerned
Also this is a Rasmussen poll being reported in Breitbart so who knows what's going on
Anyway the point is that Alex just saw the number 74
Decided to
Label it however he wanted to wish I was
The criminal negligence in recording
What's the number of heartbeats you have before you die everybody knows that if you just see a number you can
Can say whatever happens after that and it's true what's fascinating is honestly
You said is as true as what
To look he's kind of tired of
News
Sucks
Disgusting into the news
Nobody agrees more than me
So you decide like look
I'm not doing that anymore
It's hard for me to cut a pro wrestling promo
Sure that's
Good Rand Paul I'm coming for you
But you still supported early on now you need to come out against
The whole thing
Doesn't give you immunity
Actor Paul
I know you're not on the enemies team
I know you got bamboozled
American to you
Senator Paul.
He's one of the main reasons you were with warp speed
You were conned
Call
Come out as well
How old is Donald Trump
Nevermind
You don't
I'm not going to sit here and risk my life doing this
I know you're good ramp
You thought he'd give it to people will say why
You work on
But you're not
Suggest we love you calling for about you spend five years in prison
Love you both
Go all the way here and debate Muir and tell everybody that it's b******* or
Tell me that it's
What honestly think there's no chance
Is going to this
Wrestling shoot Bravo
He's going to have any effect on Rand Paul's Behavior
I still think it's more likely than him debate
I do like
The idea that Alex
She's like listen
I'm going to be real mad about this
This for the next couple months
And if you don't do anything in the next couple of months
Few months from now eventually
If you don't do anything you will be on Nuremberg trials
Listen
500 times a month for the next
55 years I will be very mad at you also Alex should not be in favor of Nuremberg typed
International law doesn't exist
To look it's fun
The Chute on-ramp off
Itsfunneh
Do you know what let's
Spread it out a little
Let's talk some s*** about some other people
Get with the program more
DeSantis
Enough
Was a fraud
Who was Ally
All of them
Are you good
So you see what's happening
What is hell
But the point is you can't know all this and do all these other good
Self fraud
Call you and Trump and all you are losing so
Support with your constituents
And they're getting mad at you
Help you
Trying to help you
I actually think you might be right on this will I kind of do too I think you might have really nailed the head on what's going on
On here that these guys are not understand you will lose your crazy bass
You guys think that you made us crazy
Anybody no no no
This is just more fun but
Because
Doing work
Actually getting into any of these topics is exhausting
I think you have to know where Luxembourg is
Yeah if know what the country very hard to do yourself
Absolutely I'm coming for you on Sunday
I don't like this
Is he trying to go back to being the guy who's Above It All by being so far right
That he can
Say he's not part of a political party
Cuz I'm getting real pissed off about this
I'm seeing I'm seeing this Red Scare bulshit
I've seen those two Dum Dums soccer
Talk to him
I'm seeing the Rogan bulshit I'm seeing them all over places
And now he's trying to start talking s*** about Trump and Paul and all this stuff
I'm not liking where this is going
Maybe maybe a little bit
I think
I think that
The situation
And I will admit I don't know enough about that podcast to speak about it in any way with any kind of
Actual inch
Information
That is more an instant
Of like
They sent out feelers
Yeah wherever anybody appearance laundering
The left rights
I don't think
He could launder that now I think
It's too cute
Yeah he's too associated with
He spent so much time with
The last
Couple years just being like all Democrats are evil
I think he always tries
To maintain a little bit of that I hate both
Sure
So it's true
What's up
Can see where you're concerned but I I would
Going to sell but everytime I think people are going to buy something
Most popular product in the world
I don't know
At this point we get to another headline
Another headline
And now
Evil
Wicked
Corporate combine
Is suppressing
Mainline science
Heart Association
Has had their tweets blocked and I meant to be suspended
Publishing
What is on
The Pfizer and moderna injection
Now he can cause a heart attack
That's premeditated Eve
That's not true the American Heart Association
Blocked on Twitter Twitter David Warner
Bring two people who tried to click on a link to this abstract that was on the American Heart association's website
That the link that they were clicking might be unsafe
You can still go ahead and click on it if you wanted to
The reason putter doesn't generally is winsome
Something is
Being Mass posted by accounts that are off
I'm spamming in nature
They usually are like
Just in case
Dysgraphia
As for this abstract itself it was
Retracted a couple days before Alex is on are here
The American Heart Association was having a meeting and there was like presentations of people giving
And one of them that was given at the meeting was titled
MRNA covid vaccines dramatically increase endothelial inflammation markers
And ACS Chris
As measured by the puls
Cardiac tests
A warning
Great title
Sure this Title & Abstract and posted online in their publication
Called circulation
A satirist ran with it is proof that the American Heart Association was saying orthodox
Can cause heart attack
Also was written by a dude who's deep in the
More games
Might be
Skechers
This was published in their publication the editors of circulation posted a clarification
Quote
Soon after publication of the above abstract
Can circulation
It was brought to the American Heart Association committee on scientific session
Program
Attention
But there are potential errors in the abstract
Specifically there are several typographical errors
There's no data in the abstract
Regarding a myocardial T-cell infiltration
Embury arnost
Statistical analyses for significance provided
And
The author is not clear that only anecdotal data was you
Do nothing
Scientific adult
This is written in crayon I am confused as to why this made it into art
There's spelling errors and this guy is talking about anecdotal stuff pretending it's scientific
I heard from a guy who knew a guy did I mean to say
Decor did I want to say f*** I can't remember the reality though to is
These abstract
Text that they publish often times
AR
Perspective
Start
What is that are going to happen
The future
Beginning of the process of something
Be a study that ends up
What is a testable hypothesis that could get a grant or that we need
Misrepresented
What the
That's just incredible that you
Clarification was public to days
Before Alex is on are talking about it
I got you a point where I was realizing
That
A lot of the headlines that Alex reads
Outside of these just
Rank
Misuse of
Information
Some s*** blog
Shirt
Kind of like
Gossip
Restrictions Henderson police state
He won't get the vaccine
I won't play
Everybody have
Dale Watson
This is kind of like a anti-vax
Text weirdo Entertainment Tonight
Yeah it's a little bit
Listen we caught this guy outside of his beachfront property and he's telling us at the vaccines
Pro-vaccine people
Furious at Country musician mad
Cool definition of trivial
If I understand correctly
I
Should be listening to Conor McGregor Conor McGregor Eric Clapton
And other country music stars
Alex said the dude's name and I don't even remember it
Getting covid advice as well as apparently
International law advice
Whether or not Ireland
Sun stays in the EU
That's how it
Listen to Conor McGregor
And look at
It sounds silly
But Conor McGregor will be
Beat up anybody who stands in the way of Ireland leaving
Yeah I feel like if we just really buckled down on domestic
Sick violence
People
I would go away a lot too
I'm just saying that maybe there's a lot going on over overlap
We want my flip here in italics the end of the show he's just going on about how the globe
Doublelist
Hurt and kill your kid sure
He's getting pretty extreme
Kind of saying that he's going to have to save the world
Blood clots
Prion disease
It's wild
Australia
Whataburger
Tomorrow is the last day of
Hair clip like that if you might be inclined to think that I cut out
Space in between
No I'm talking about God's protection and separately
Oh man that separately is carrying a lot of weight
Separately
Completely unrelated this Commerce and my religious beliefs
I think I think
Separately is one of the things he says
The most
I wish it was I'm not mad at the crew
That doesn't come up as often
Separately
H-E-B on his tombstone
The adverb that keeps you from going to
I think I think you got a good sense of what's going on but nonsense
Very surface-level storyline
Reset me nothing all kinds of bulshit a desperate attempt to do some work
I think
And then application of
Address to that
Larry Hardman a fun shoot promo
On
All the people on the right
Yeah
That's
You know
When your heart's just not in anything but shoot promos Maybe
Take a step back
I can just do some shoe promos
You know what I mean like
For good anyway Jordan
I will exact
But until then
We do it's knowledge right.com
Brussels on Twitter go to bed Jordan
And now here comes
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color