Air Jordan
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody was right on that
Alex
Joe
Jordan
I struggled with this
Up and down
Because
I struggle with
Being into things that are too popular
Sure wish that I had pasted that were like
Under
I got recommended a video on YouTube I don't know how just popped up and it was of these dudes dropping something from a really high height
And watching it the fall
I love it and I
Got really hooked it's hard not to see something
Big beautiful in
And to channel called to how ridiculous
And they're like dudes from Australia
Steve millions of views on their videos
Come to my attention but I didn't know that they were these
People getting Billy interviews dropping things from a high height don't know anymore
Because if there's so many fractures like there's many fractures that there are in the bulletproof glass when they act
445 m in the air
Viewership for
CNN is like
Everybody knows CNN but 700,000
F****** nobody
So it's like of course you know CNN and it's only watch by 700,000 people but these f****** are in the
YouTube
Amazon 24 hours a day
It's it would be
Be tough to tell
How much viewership there would be of guys who drop things from really high
Are or even if it was just appointment television
Tough to say what kind of readings it would get if it wasn't something you could do
Just click and watch
Mora MN watch more
Given that to me when I was high at 4
13 that would be all my friends and I did everything like 20 years ago
It feels a little bit like jackass but without the meme
Nobody getting hurt
Fantastic
Yeah but I struggle with
A very popular thing that a lot of people
Know about tonight just heard about it like I have business trip
Every big on Tik-Tok that is true that is true
Yeah yeah
Events that that whole world
Never never shall I
Even if people tell me that people are dropping
Things things from really high up on tiktok I'm still not going to check it out
Maybe the best batch
Chex Mix ever made in my entire life it's fantastic
I only cook two things
At a professional
Potatoes
And Chex Mix
Me and Angela Lansbury too much for that
Who's not great ham
But this was an especially good batch what about air fryer
Chicken that one wasn't that wasn't how he's going to go
I think you eventually got that one together right
That one real wrong I actually was not there for that
To try this Chex Mix
Fortunately did not have any for the show so I can't vouch for you but what is it
Timer
On the next episode the Chex Mix
Well that was it
It's not it's going to
We'll see we'll see if I even remember by the time
We're in the present Davis
Is Thursday of the week that was
Last
Do you like that we had a week it was the Thursday of it
There's kind of a specific reason that I decided
The truth episode
And spoiler alert
It's because Alex is a little bit mad
At a certain point
About Vice article
That I was interviewed for responded to some of that
That's Tuff
The first false flag football thank you so much you're now policy walk
Ewok
I'm a policy wonk
Spotify wrapped Saline
Blizzard lizard wizard love Serena thank you so much you are now apology
Thank you very much thank you all
Restart off here on Thursday
Congrat with Alex
Talking pretty extreme
He also wants to remind you
Hindi always
World's been artificially put into a Cascade of crises
Control
Sure
Broadcast
Predictions
Off in the future I said 25-30 years
Collapse of civilization and the
Anymore doesn't work here
That kind of talk I never really would
Think I would describe as fanciful let's not be term I would use
Who's a really sad attempt on Alex's BART to misrepresent how he carried himself in
Earlier career
He's pretending that is a present-day saying that the end is right in front of our faces
Years ago he would say that the end was coming in 20 years
It's almost like
Totally right about everything
Complete Vindication of everything he's ever believed right then this is total horseshit
It is earlier career Alex is very similar to how he is now but he would just say that the globalist or 10 years behind and their play
Planes or whatever
When is predictions dating
Come to pass
He didn't say that in 20 years should be going down
You saying what disaster was coming imminently
Pretty consistent
I could go through many examples of this so how over the years it was just
Consistent pattern because it's more fun this way here's a clip of him from May 5th 1998
Where he predicts that within two years there will be complete martial law
With hit teams roaming the streets
Two years you have a massive crash in the
You have a match
Criminal consolidation of wealth you have a police state
Rounded up wholesale
You barely hear about on the news
You will have six
Excessive vomiting
Coming out
Until
The governor
People being killed.
Local
Sheriff being killed being in prison
Squadron all over the nation
Killing people
Get ready
They didn't do nothing
Alex never predicted the collapses were coming 20 years down the line because that's not good for business
One of Alex's most essential tools
In terms of f****** with his audience that is created
Sense of emergency
See where the information he's yelling about his
The most important thing
Right now
And that's something you're trying to make someone scared of something that's supposed to happen into decade
The difference between Oz earlier career in now is that we're currently in the middle of a protractor
Societal challenge in the form of covid
And it's something that fits very perfectly into a strategy of making people
Scared of how the end is right around
The corner
He's smart enough to know that his fear-mongering and doomsday s*** sounds way less convincing Than People realize he's been doing
Exact same thing for years
In the way around that is pretend that all along you've been saying that this big thing was coming aways off in the future which would coincide with
Insane owl
The end is here
Like I said it was going to be here
Maybe a little bit like if Nostradamus is writings we're actually like he said all of that stuff was going to happen tomorrow and then when
When did news 1000 years from now how about that Nostradamus
Long-winded RadioShack
Recovery time
Yeah it would be rhyme
And that's no fun
Actually I would like Alex
Stride
Navigate to make things a little interesting
Studio is a little ominous it's looking a little bit too spooky
Today
Describes why
The u.s. cap
Winifred storms in the back
Describe
Free evil
That ass control of our government
Almost every level
We are the bad guys
We have been captured
We became the most powerful wealthy love Nation the world still at incredible problems but because
We had a Christian but also rugged Western
Renaissance
What are the freest greatest most productive Nation on Earth
Took over
We have become a slave
Of the New World Order
The wages of sin are death
What's up what is
Feels just like Christian nationalism
I'm poking its little head up again
Cuz I mean like it's got to be that the thing that went bad was
Bakeries not Christian anymore
Outside of marriage
Because I don't feel like it's that we're not rugged enough
That's not the complaint Alex
He might make a complaint much rugged about going to the grocery store when you
You're hungry I will admit that
You know instead of going out and shooting the Bison
Do
Push a herd of bison over a cliff in order to insure my son
Sustenance for the following winter
It is less rugged
Certainly doordash who really struggled with
The Unabomber is against
Did it probably less rugged than
Then you would like
Do the government is captured because
Circle
Christian
The Orient
The policies aren't what is
Is flaw
The laws of Deuteronomy should probably run most adult
Although I don't think Alex would particularly like it if that kind of like
Theocratic State we're actually enacted to be a real problem
Well I mean
Like it really like it it's Austin was a dry county
I don't think sad and
Let's see how prohibition did first
So Alex has
Some weird ideas
On this episode
And here's one of them
There's a number of things that just even Felix stray thoughts
Better
But also see
Disconnected from anything else
She's talking about
That's why you see them letting murderers out of jail
Robbers out after a week
Yeezys release the next day because he's black
All of that is being done to totally undermined changed
Put you in a state of confusion
Show that you'll accept
On your phone even leave your house
The great reset
Confused
Okay
So all of the bad that
It's being done
To confuse me
Well into being like
I'm going to use
The Euro guy who shot people at a school was released on bail
Use the euro right
I must get involved with great recent because this guy got a bond
Armed robbery
Got out of prison on bail
So now I am going to be
Define with vaccines KB also that this person got released from jail because they were black
I am going to need a vaccine after
You tell me that to the other cases like an armed robbery or murder I've no idea what he's talking about
Internet is
Clear
Is about Timothy Simcoe
Play an 18 year old student at High School in Arlington
Send Texas
He's accused of injuring four people including one teacher and a shooting
He was released on a $75,000 Bond and is currently under house arrest and wearing
GPS monitor
Simkins wasn't released
Because he's black
Any still going to be most likely to a bit
Trouble
What are the reasons you probably released on bond is because no one was
Killed
Also there
Some strong indications that he was acting in what his family is called Selfish
According to a relative Simpkins have been robbed multiple times by bullies at school in the
The theory is that he was the target for that kind of thing
Because it came from a well-off family
None of this justifies shooting people but it does factor into whether or not you would think it was a risk to send someone out on
Bond
But Alex is this story the only relevant details
The Simpsons is black so that must be why he's out on bond
It's really tough to compare the circumstances of different school shooting
To gauge how treatment varies among perpetrators
There factors like whether or not anyone was killed
What state it occurred in
A specific context of the shooting that you really need to take him to
Consideration if you want to compare TSA
The case be sure
I could do through a number of examples of people who engaged in school shootings who are white allowed bail
But does it really matter
Examples to Alex's claim here doesn't
Mean anything because Alex isn't even
Making this claim sincerely
He doesn't fit
Think it's a release because he's black
He would have been held if you were white
That's not a serious point
It's just signaling to the racist audience
But he has created the perception of white oppression
To them to experience
Then get mad about
Yeah
I guess
Sia's
Why everyone's
Joining the euro
It's just racism racism is certain except there's at this point
It's like
If this is the only nation where this
Type of thing regularly happens or happens at all
Then it take
Complete struts
Troll issue
You know so if you want to get into the lake
Weeds of
Should the child be punished with
10 years are tried as an adult that's fine but the reality is this is a
Complete struts
Before it's a personal responsibility
More to the issue that Alex is specifically bringing up though the
The qualifications of when someone
Would be allowed bail
After a shooting
It's a very
Number of circumstances
Exactly
I don't I don't find
Alex's Gates
This is just right
It's verifying your already held pressure
We get to talk in a little bit here about those
But we talked about I think I'm the last
Alex a
Text example
Do use a word that he loves and that he's props
Atrocious
I see so good
They want 75 years
I'm not joking
Emergency authorization
Last week
Release
30 pages
Thousands of dead
In just the first weeks of the rollout
Massive
Increases in
Spontaneous abortion
Play call a miscarriage now
Everything
We talked about the documents in detail on the last episode so I'm not going to go over all that but there are some other important points
It's here
The 75 years thing is just another predict
Should have when the documents would be fully released
The same rate
Discuss the 500 pages a month
BMI just refuses to accept massive difference
Between the FDA reviewing the science and documents it receives
Privately
And the process required to then ethically and responsibly released those
To the public
The first isn't in-house scientific analysis
And the other is a legal privacy-oriented analysis that obviously could take longer
The idea that they're pretending to not understand that a very obvious Dynamic is pretty clear everything
That's just
Show me the argument is essentially
You should just turn over all of
These documents so we can harass people with all of this information
Regardless of whether or not approves our point we will have names in personal information that we can f*** people up with
That and it's more efficient Expedition
Things we could be misrepresented as has already happened with his first
Class
Oh yeah this 3838 page document that Alex's
I turned it to the Smoking Gun
Yeah you're going to give them 300,000 pages so they can find
$0.03
Says to really Hammer home for the rest of our f****** live
The second point I want to make is that the FDA did request that they narrow down their request so it wouldn't be 40
Over 300,000.
Witcher timeline
Where's everyone to get the documents they want the lawyers could make sure they weren't releasing private
Information to the public
From everything I've read it seems like the fda's willing to prioritize whatever documents are most important
So ultimately if this group really wanted to reach the goal that therefore
Pretending they're looking
Collaborate with the FDA to get what they want
Well before 7
35 years from now
Okay
Stupid narrow down your foil request
We want the documents where you admit to killing everybody
I'm sorry those don't exist
Well obviously they both do you want everything
Forever cover up
Okay
Third point I want to make is that Alex is claiming that now that the FDA has killed everyone they won't release
The documents
He immediately says that they did release the trash
That includes what he's pretending as evidence
Thousands of vaccine
That's completely self
Contradictory of the position
They refused to release the documents but also they released this document that's the Smoking Gun
Bring Me The Smoking Gun of what they've done
Finally I want to clarify with Alex's lying about as a relates
Spontaneous abortion
There were 413 reports
Involving persons in the data set that they had
And of these
He's twenty-three were reporting
Spontaneous abortion
And five additional instances of different variations of spontaneous abortions like
Ones with neonatal death or intrauterine
Worst case scenario from these numbers as if they were 28
Agencies that ended
Spontaneous abortion
Some people who were vacs
This cannot prove that the spontaneous
Were caused by the vaccine
So what's up for now
And talk about what we can tell from this number
This would constitute approximately
At least 7% of the break-in
She's captured the data ending in spontaneous abortion
This number sounds really high out of context but you need to know what the rate of spontaneous abortion isn't
The general population
If you want to get any kind of sense about whether this is within or outside the range of what you would expect
In this number of people with or without the vaccine
According to the Mayo Clinic
A quote about 10 to 20% of known pregnancies end in miscarriage
But the actual number is likely higher because many miscarriages occur very early in pregnancy
Before you might even know about a
You might think
Having a heavy.
Possible
The numbers captured in the FDA Adverse Events report actually reflect
Text a much lower than
Unexpected rate
Spontaneous abortion
Then you would expect
Courtesy of the general population
That's probably a function of
Incomplete information
Then the report about pregnant
The outcomes
You have really no reason to suspect that the vaccine that any discernible outcome
In terms of miscarriage
That's why this report concludes
Quote
There were no safety signals that emerged from the review of these cases
Of use and pregnancy and well
Breastfeed
What a great things are right
If you're covering up the truth
Alex can take this number of reported spontaneous abortions about 7% and that's a lot if you expect that the number should be
0 but that's not reality
He's creating a false problem bike
Comparing these numbers to the wrong
Baseline
And that's because he's dumb and
Anyway that's what's going on here what he yells about
A bunch of
Spontaneous abortion
Sidetracks
Wow 7% is lower by
Send the estimated 3% lower than the low range excited by the Mayo Clinic
It's almost like we should probably know that off hand but because it's
It's about women
Society
Large doesn't care that
More dangers and difficulties
Is a pregnancy then then a lot of people wreck
Goodnight seem like that should be so obvious though if it is 10 to 20% Which obviously it is
How is it that that is not so well
No do you know what I mean like that's a significantly higher amount
For the number of people who would exist for which is just about every f******
You know
It's weird
Yeah yeah it definitely the beat the fact
The people don't know it is a handy tool for someone like Alex to be able to misrepresent the data activist
So we have to
Haha. The vaccine still going
Pfizer covid vaccine
Pulling off the market
Wowed
So I'm sure
Open Twitter
In fact they are
I can find a few articles that discuss the Japanese Health Ministry deciding to put a warning on the visor in vagina vaccine
That
I could have possible serious item
That's their prerogative
I can find no evidence that they're contemplating taking it off
Market over this though and I strongly suspect
Like that
An article in the Japan times does discuss how the health Ministry may decide to recommend a Pfizer vaccine over the moderna wanted
Because it appears that the possible risk
Is lower
With visor
But even so the rates of myocarditis
Some people who get covid
Substantially higher
But even the worst numbers
You can find for the vaccine
That article cites
Tetsuo Nakayama the project
Professor at the
Attitude for life sciences and the director of the Japanese Society of cultural virologia
The risk of myocarditis is much lower and people who got them the vaccine than those
I experiencing a natural infection
So there is no reason
To Halt its use
That's got to be the vibe that coming out of the story
Given a warning of the potential
Side effects
Delineator lesbian causally linked but
What was Japan
So
Get out
You can't say well oh it's not the UN so they're going to censor its like you been part of the us but it's not coming from like the
The un's had the body or whatever the World Health
Translation
So we got also some news out of Israel
Israel says at least 7 boosters
Haha
Oh my God I told you it'll be 10 shots a year
Elder said
This is the best business ever
Song when I do
And
First of all that Bill Gates Prospect
Cuz doesn't exist
Alex is just making that up
And if he's not I would say that he's committing journalist
Malpractice by not releasing
Absolutely not real so I was just committing journalistic malpractice by bang that s*** up
I just started laughing while talking about that because on some level he can't believe that he can get away with this level of b*******
As for the seven boosters think that's misreporting on Alex's part as well
There was a Times of Israel article that Paul Joseph Watson
I'm covered poorly and now Alex's covering Paul schuette work
Even more sloppily
The actual article is about the health Minister and it's on Horowitz
Discussing the possibility of a fourth dose
In the country
Which would be the second
However he says quote I don't know yet if we see that the vaccine's efficacy drops after a certain amount of time
Even after the booster we could wrap a recommended fourth dose
It's possible
That's what the health minister is
Once again
Measured
Obvious response
If bad
Then yes
The article also has a comment from Professor are known as
The deputy director of the Sheba Medical Center who is of the belief that the second booster was
Inevitable
Whoever thinks that we won't have a fourth doses simply mistaken
Isaac told the Wynette
News
As long as there's still a pandemic and areas like Africa which have low vaccination rates there will be more and more variants
Eric said he hopes that sucks
Covid mutations won't be as contagious and severe as the Delta variant
Quote but it
It seems
That we will need
Need to take a fourth and fifth
In 6th and 7th dose
Who knows how many
So that's where this quote is coming
Any coverage of the story Alex's misidentifying the source of the comment and he's also mischaracterizing what was
Set
If you just listen to Alex you would think that a health official was saying that you needed at least 7 boosters to be considered fully vaccinated
Would you be 9 shot
That's absolutely not what this article says and once again
I'd like to remind Tucker that Alex is a shity guide to reality
Nonsense
Dumb
S***
Yeah
I mean what else
What do you expect a f****** expert to say about this is just literally like this is how shots work
We're in a pandemic if you don't want to be in a pandemic than guess what this
This is how it works
It's not like
OSB Legos
We're making it work like this this is how we have to
To respond
Because of you dick
Funny about this professor just saying
Is that is of his
But
We could be looking
Sure that is not somebody dictated government policy
Thing we definitely need seven shots and that's how it is
Is reporting this I mean imagine imagine if this happens like
However many years ago in somebody's like listen we're going to have
We're going to have a yearly flu shot
I put your face it
The flu is going to mutate every single f****** time we try and stop it
So we're going to have yearly flu shots how would Alex have covered the moment that was in
Introduce
I'm certain
That there were people who acted like Alex Becker
However many years later and everybody's fine
But it's going to happen every single time there's a new disease that we create
Entered into a f******
God I hate everybody
Do you should do also know if you hate everybody you should hate
Because they're talking about preemptively nuking
Russia I don't know if you knew that
Pisanello's look war with Russia
Oh
A grand collapse
Crisis
Possibly can
Destroy
Almost past the point of return
World leaders aren't talking about nuke in Russia
I did was just a comment that Republican senator Rodger wicker said on Fox
Fox News
Discussing the situation in Ukraine and how Biden should respond he said quote
I would not rule out Military at
Military action could mean we stand off with our ships in the Black Sea Andre rain.
Obstruction on Russian
Military capability
I would not rule out America
Troops on the ground
You know we don't rule out the first
Use nuclear Act
We don't think it'll happen
But
For no reason whatsoever I want to read to you from an email that Rodger wicker sent to his
Constituents in Mississippi 3 days after the 2020 election
Quote
President Trump's team reached out to me about the voting fraud that's going on in our country right now there is no
Capital n o
Excuse for any of this
Americans should be confident that their ballot was submitted directly legally in untampered
You don't vote to certify the election that's great but not before he played his role and whipping up
The distrust and paranoia that led to January
First of all wicker is not what you would call a world-leader he was just talking s*** on Fox News
Second diesel truck guy
About 22 report
The story accurately he would
Be saying that one of the senators of Kik
Ring now wants Biden
Pitkin Center attack
That's more accurate
I mean it would be
Very similar to him saying something like remember how pissed off I was whenever Trump drop that bomb in Syria
I cried and said he can go f*** himself forever and all of that stuff Isis apart dirty assholes
You did say that or his dirty a****** account number is saying we should do this
Same thing to Russia so I am also angry inside of it
It's world leaders Rodger wicker is a globalist except when he sent out an email trying to help Trump find voter fraud
Music by name you can use them both white alright
And later Alico call him Rodger Whittaker
I've no idea who the people even are
What's good to know that we're almost
Past the point of return now as opposed to a few weeks ago when it was already too late to stop what was coming
Sympathetically transparent that Alex's mood is the only real determined
Exactly whether or not it's too late to do something
Stop the globalists plan
Really hard to imagine that his audience hasn't caught on to that by now like
How do you not ask yourself why he
He keeps going back and forth
On whether or not it's too late to stop the end of the world
Except our death
Or do we fight or do we fight mix up their deaths or do we not accept our deaths in then fight
Because
It might be somewhere in the middle
All I can tell you
The answer is going to be
Going and getting very conservative Christian communities
In the middle of nowhere work
People just very austere
Because once all this Falls once all this goes
And
Tried to stop this and we had a chance to back
When you look at
Klaus Schwab
These are psychos
So I have terrible news for Alex what the plan is I took it up about setting up like
Christian cities
Complete violation of
Well there's that
Particular The Establishment Clause
Sure I guess if you wanted to just have a weird compound in the middle of the woods or pull of Jim Bakker that would be
Define
Structure like incorporate as an actual City
The First Amendment rules about the
State not being involved in the establishment of any religion replies
Who plays not just the Federal
But the lower governments as well
What you're discussing the need to create religiously-based communities
You pretty much have given up any right to care about the cost
Restitution ever again
He wants to
He loves guns
It's tough to respect those arguments being based in a reverend
For the Constitution to Caesar
His solutions to problem
Yeah aren't they aren't there like militia cities in
In Idaho but even they in there like Charter not cities
Even they can't like
Incorporate as a City Christian City you cannot
Not do that yeah it is a
Christian City
Or something is just like
Campus
They have to refer to themselves as a camper
It has like a
The hospital
And
Text money from the government
If your incorporated as a city that won't work
But maybe that's not what he wants anyway baby does just want to have like a compound
That's healthy
Yeah that's great. Everybody in history whose wanted a compound has been a good
Person
And it's usually worked
Yeah
You know what specially especially people have compounds where it's like
Alright the premise of this compound is that the rest of the world is f*****
This is the only place we're safe
So also there's a fun fact
I was just talking about like a class lobbying
You do class Schwab is
Like a relevant figures for a lot of hits
Is created the world economic forum
I can find no evidence that Infowars ever posted an article containing the name Klaus Schwab
Until November 6th
Jeep 2020 that's not good for somebody who's been right about everything to not even know
The major player in his
Extinction game
Pop up
If you write about everything 20 years later if I didn't even know the name of the guy that's kind of
Yeah yeah yeah
Suspicious
Blofeld who is
Hiding himself from everything even made the world economic forum
Stroke
So Alex
You know whenever he brags he likes
Society's not bragging
Here's an instance of him not bragging
About how he's woken up
Really important
People.
I say this so you have somehow
Brag
Acrostico deposit
We have come so far together
In this fight
The guest
The collars
Probably because
This is our culture
This is Who We Are
All alone
They want to cut off from each other
Do you know that
List of everybody fighting New World Order
By the day
Almost every one of them personally told me that
Them up
And they wouldn't be awake or understood this and if I had been there
But I thought it was crazy 20-something years ago
From
Other surrounding contacts he's talking about Tucker Carlson and Clyde back
I totally not bragging what are you bragging about how those dude say he woke them up if that's great I mean
Tucker is a shity opportunist who found ridiculous ratings lean and hard at the trumpet
Extremism
He's just following that thread out as far as he can
Hey Susie needs to get it
Self-preservation mode
Seriously end up finding someone else to wake him up to something else
Like maybe helping him ReDiscover his meal
Conservative route
Right
As we're going back this is really just more of a desperation
Something
Legitimately
Nobody respects Glenn back anymore and he's got no place in the market
He's laughable
Sirius media and he's been way too weak for the extremist
Immediate
He's got the blaze Network
Reruns and I'm sure he does fine with that but he's not even the most relevant host on his very depressing Network
He's way less popular than Steven Crowder it probably even less popular than Dave Rubin
And I would guess that he probably has less of an audience than Gavin
McGinnis did but
The fire Gavin back in 2018 when he merged with Mark Levin conservative media platform
So cool
Really really into free speech
We woke up a lot of very important people this year in my head I was like yeah yeah
Zach
Kelly
Lisa
Slater
Screech
Why am I thinking of Saved by the Bell
The Millman he's like we woke up a lot of people I'm like
I got the whole cast
To say by the Bell. Everybody I'm confused why you were thinking that
I don't know
It's interesting that Alex is so proud of Heaven waking up these
Clearly disingenuous media figure
Other people he's woken up
Like Daniel Rodriguez
The guy was arrested for tasing officer Mike fanone during the storming of the Capitol on January
The FBI released a transcript of an interview with him
I'm in the conversation he's asked about how
No prior to January 6th
Keep in the back of the blue rally and he stood up for
The cops then on the 6th
There he was assaulting a cop
The agent who's doing the interviews asked me what what'd happen
So how did the Danny that stood on the line in between law enforcement and antifa and BLM
How did you get to that point
What happened in your life like how did you start going
These rallies
Daddy responds
Infowars
Infowars so like Alex Jones stuff
David replies
Send Danny.
Later in the interview Danny says cook I've been following Infowars for
2008-2009 Maybe
He's the one
Alex Jones Infowars out there you know
That there's an other news that's not on TV but they don't want you to know you know
They don't tell you a lot of things
That was just information is is what it is
I was trying to find the truth and answers
And what I thought I found the truth and answers
I thought it was up to me to I don't know I just
It's like when like
There's a saying like
To know better is
Knowing better
To know better is to do better you know
Because they really are
You're killing Trump supporter
Shooting them in the head
School in public everything right
So I kept thinking that we were going
Go to like a civil war
Kohat
It's going to go you know
I don't know
I don't know we didn't nobody knew
So we just thought it was going to we're preparing for the little prepared to save the country
We thought we were saving the country
I thought I was going to help save the country
Decided
Consider himself a three percenter also which is something that he
He told the agents that he had learned about from Infowars
In the interview
Danny tries to downplay his desire to do violent s*** at the Capitol
But unfortunately the end of November he got hit with some new charges involving
Conspiracy to commit violence
It turns out he was on a telegram Channel
That he and his friends created titled Patriots 45
Where he at these friends wrote fairly openly about their vile
What plans
One of his buddies wrote quote
We need to violently remove Traders and if they're in key position
Replace them with able-bodied
Patriots
Danny wrote about a week before January 6th
Congress can hang
I'll do it
Please let us get the
These people Dear God
The person who wasn't named in the indictment but whose identity is known to the grand jury that he would assassinate Joe Biden
If you got the chance
On January 5th Danny posted in the group quote
There Will Be Blood welcome to the revolution
The indictment alleges that in preparation
For the 6 the group began quote collecting weapons and
Cycle Gear to bring to Washington DC including a taser
Pepper spray baseball bat gas masks
And walkie-talkie
In contrast
I'm confused you appeared in the FBI interview
Immediately after leaving the capital Danny message
Does group chat and said quote OMG I did so much f****** s*** right now and got away
Tell you later
Tazed with a bunch of Z's the f*** out of the blue
Wow wow
Fun
Interesting Lee we also learn for the indictment on January 8th one of Danity
He's co-conspirators guy named Edward balidan
I called
Owen Shroyer show and field in fours in on what they've done
Haley blamed the violence on Trump supporters that they had just decided where
Antifa
Yeah
Tucker and Glen Becker shameless.con men telling Alex what he wants
Insecure cuz it suits the current state of their grid
They don't even know what Alex is actually promoting or preaching over the years
Popular in the world
Why isn't as a point
At this time
Like at this moment
That's popular in their grip
Pretend
Cast aside the moment.
Convenient
People like Danny Rodriguez real people Alex wakes up
They get sucked in by Alex physics
Stream and very immediate rhetoric
And they reach the natural conclusion of what Alex presents
There demons in the White House
Trump won the election
The demon stole it
The only way to save the country has come to DC in flight
They lash out
And brag to their friends
It's about how they tasered
The cop when the coast looks clear
They call into the War Room in the next days
Established
The false flag
Antifa
You don't know if they themselves know it
What's b*******
And that they plan to do it
Exactly what they
Play data Megan joined it when it was happen
Let me cry but Heather actually a good person once I have to answer for their actions
And they get arrest
I didn't know I was going to face
Consequences
Now this doesn't feel as good as it did when I was hurting people I'm going to take a break from crying to make
Make sure you don't have no about my telegram Channel if I hurt somebody then it's possible
But I will then have consequences
This is completely new to me in the United
Yep but like Alex wakes up a lot of people into just being scared
And buying useless pills
That is death
Definitely true
But a very small subset of the people he wakes up or Danny's
Dynamic
His legacy
Concern
Tucker
Glenn Beck
Dark matter you know what
What's so weird
Is that nothing
Alex's effect on people reminds me of like a f****** Firefly and serenity
Like the way that they never help me with that
Did the Firefly show is with Nathan Fillion know what it is
This whole thing the packs
Right and it makes everybody
But what they wind up creating something that made people sell Pacifier that they just wound up not living
They just gave up
You know where they stood
Rough 10% of that population
What the exact other way and got so viola
Vicious and awful
That they're now the Terrors of the universe or whatever and I was just keep thinking of like
If you're an Infowars listener
Most of them are just sitting there like a frayed shaking
Or maybe posting
It is getting on Facebook and posting memes and stuff
But then there's that fun
F****** 10% that's just
Vicious ya-ya-ya
Metaphorically 10% who knows what the actual number is
It goes on they embark on a
Journey
That leads to really
Tasering a cop
At the Capitol
And planning to to stuff like that
And then the other part that I find really disgraceful is the way in which
Immediately afterwards
You call into Infowars
To try and help build up a narrative
No you did
Cypress Imaging
It's real
It says
Just amazing
How did you how were you the guy at the back
The blue event
And then the guy who heard the cop that doesn't make sense
Condition about race not about cops body
Is it already
At least the sport back the blue
Absolutely
You know what
Sometimes
Things get a little bit like that for
And I'll do something to palate cleanser
This next step is not that
Oh no I was hoping he's going to sing
It's kind of like when you need
If you'd like
Something to
Glenn fallat
A different Flavor jelly beans
It's like
Like a booger
Aggressive mustard jelly beans
This is not a palate cleanser
Breakfast with my girl.
Usher love you so
Show Daddy
Sure what it is
My daughter but she did
Text my mom
Show me will sweetheart
I never saw
Well
Oh my
Oh man
You have your hand on your forehead
That's that's just I'm not going to be a parent
And I haven't read many parenting books I'm going to go with that one's not in there
Dr. Sparks book was mostly about show me your will
You know you know how creepy devil noises
Excuse me daughter
Daughter you know the sounds good my theoretical demons make when they see me
Make those towards me on purpose cuz it means you're good it's kind of interesting
To imply that stuff that he does on his show bleeds into his personal life
Daughter
Is aware on some level of making
Weird demon noises
Yeah you must do that at all
Beyond me yeah
Alright
Cuz he's beautiful
Poison control
Add
Because they know we're beautiful
They know we love God they know
And they want to kill us
Beautiful black skin a beautiful white skin a beautiful brown skin
You all got red-blooded God Made You And if you love God the devil h
Club Cafe
Jean are so incredible and I want you to take stock
In your will
The God gave you two
Exercise
Exercise your will
Coin yesterday
Then I won't be all these writing projects that are getting launched
There will be
Alex is now selling a silver
Pork loin
He's pretending it's some kind of a war bond
It's a lot of fun
Imply that you be willing
To buy all of them back in a certain point but I'm guessing that's not part of the
I wouldn't think
Who is Mike sense
I was just probably just marketing someone else's coins and making a
Haircut but there's one really interesting thing that I found in the fine print
Due to current restrictions
This custom round is not available for sale to the state of Minnesota
Weird
But it has nothing to do with Ted Anderson living in Minnesota
Got to be a coincidence was involved
Then the only state that he wouldn't be allowed to sell this in would be that's why I don't know if he's actually involved
I honestly think it could be a coincidence and there's some sort of a weird law that they Minnesota's just like
Gold sales
Sing people
Probably
Also
Coin cost
$129 and is one troy ounce of silver
In the past
30 years the highest an ounce of silver has ever been worth his $42.88 back
Can April 2011
And the price is currently around $22.29
This is a heroic level of policing Alex is trying to pull off
On eBay you can fly to 3 Troy oz silver Tiki head for
25 bucks less than Alex is dumb coin
31 bucks you can get a 1 oz silver coin with Snoopy from peanuts doing
Sonic
You know that he's never
Overthrown
Kingdom of the Red Baron that's true that's true but that Red Baron was a monarch
For 47 bucks you can get a 1 oz silver coin with Joe Campbell on it from 1930
Very classic
Milford suddenly wanted a coin
Joe Cool stupid
Speed scams I wouldn't do that
Joe Cool 1913 I want it
What's a silver Cthulhu coin to
And on the backside of it is weirdly Queen
I don't know why it legal
Silver and Allstate all spend
I was very close to buying
Joe Campbell
Absarokee actually does address
The fact that this is a ridiculous markup
You're getting a coin and momenta other resistance it says
King George
What eating with children
It's the founder of our country the archetype of
Killing the dragon Place gentleman of Christ
What
His archangel
Saint Michael
And an end that's what this is
What
It's a powerful coin
Faithfully resisting in Latin on the back
Always resisting
Turn on the front
Always left the tyrants
I don't even want to try and unpack the idea that George Washington was somehow like an avatar of the Christ
Spirit or whatever
Like a
Kind of implies that Alex was
Trying to say that
Trump was
Is like an avatar of Jesus
I guess
The Christ Spirit exists
Like over and over again same way that like there's an antichrist
Right then
That was Debbie
Treated Trump like he thought he was
Incarnation of Jesus true
That's maybe a little sacrilegious
Would you want
John Wilkes
Booth last words to be on your coin
Yeah history
Tree is a little bit
Iffy
Schlage Abraham Lincoln is a dragon that would make more sense
6/2 Rands is something
Existed prior to call John Wilkes Booth
Terms of American history that is definitely contacts
The people have for that
Hey kind of ruined the turf
It really didn't end up together with the guy who ended
Slavery being killed
Even more Infowars adjacent place that that the expression pops up
Timothy mcveigh's famous mugshot every blew up the Murrah building he's wearing a shirt
A taranis
With a picture of Lincoln on it
Great
Straight
It does feel a little bit like you might be signaling a tiny bit so that this going
Baby the war of Northern aggression
That seems this
Deadline
Advice
Little bit on the other side of a little bit mad about
Spices come out in freak out
About freaked out
Occultic New Age brainwashing hypnotism
No you're the ones we're doing the brainwashing
This is
Alex Jones oh my goodness
Keep on wishing
A little bit
About the article a bit buddy
Never mentioned
Stas
First I thought was a little bit strange
Because he's talking about how they were afraid of reset
I was
The person who talked to her about reset Wars animal in the writer the story
I also interviewed for the story
But as far as I can tell I was the only person who was like
Hey look at this crazy nonsense
Tells you you can just imagine more money coming to you
Antelope
Before I didn't actually read the article what I do come out because I get a little bit
Uncomfortable
Would like chasing
Turn down clipping but I don't do it
Interviews I did your own grandpa
Right right and so when I heard Alex talk about the reset Wars stuff I was like
I can't imagine
Jon Ronson was talking about reset water
I've not heard
Anybody except us bring this up we spoke to him was like I don't pay attention to him
Given the present
For good reason like I thought like oh this is a clearly intentional thing
He's knows that this
Article deals with reset Warriors and he's intentionally not mentioning
Again it within
The pattern and once again
But I when I read the article and
You could take away from it that
Was just bringing up Reese at work could come off
Off of that the article itself
I have information about it
And that a comment
It's very possible that I could have seen this and not recognize that
I think I think a lot of the like hey what up what's up
I can tell you is dealing with this
Yeah it might not come off that I think that I was
Obsessively talking about this
Wasn't quite that she was like can you have so many more like shut the f****** it's right that was we got her talking about right now
What are you up to
The most important work of the story Rings hanging out with a weirdo hypnosis
That's how you start a conversation
So anyway Alex doesn't bring us up
Which is I put it up on the board for 20
Or whatever
Glenn Beck now
Because Glenn Beck is gotten weird they went on Tucker's show
Inside somebody
Conspiracy ship
Well the Gateway pundit got it right when they put huge in front of the headline
Tucker Carlson
Us doctors were reviewing moderna vaccine 2019
Ash
They were calling covid-19
Bunch of viruses
With the
Set the description covid-19
Months
Before we hear the name and they're already running
Moderna vaccine for what they cooked up at a lab all confirmed in the emails now
Glenn Beck went on Tucker and misrepresented in agreement between moderna and the niaid
Where they were working on collaborating on a vaccine for covid before Mercer
I know it's fun to finish dum-dum just either work coronavirus and assumed this must be secret evidence that they are working on covid vaccine
Before we do about covid
The coronavirus is out there
This isn't even news
Conspiracy theorist tried to push this narrative back in June and it went nowhere so I guess
Stop going back
I was just trying to reach
Reheat it
You know what your own little spin on it it's like a it's like remaking Family Ties
Can you stop for a second and Rec
Thick thighs
How lucky we are to live in 2021 when we can see
F****** Bow-Tie guy in Mister chalkboard get together and try and Rehab their images by spouting covid conspiracy
How is it possible
How is it possible I thought we were done with these
Dix 15 years ago
Glenn Beck apologize with Samantha Bee
Jesus
None of that happened
Some weird analysis hear about Russia in his concern
About
The new king
Concerned
Morgan
Building
Show
Just been
In Europe
That major Wars
U.s. senator
Rodger Whittaker
Rob say everything's on the table including a pre-emptive first-strike
A sneak attack Pearl Harbor
Was Conventional Weapons
Bombs and torpedoes
No it was bad
Rodger Whittaker
Mississippi
Maybe he can come out and tell us how the Japanese were good
You think the Pearl Harbor was a false flag I was going to say
What is happening
Straight b******* straight
If you're going to create an ad
Expanded universe at least in Marvel Universe when they retcon something
Tell you
They're like a hand wave
Alex Wilson some really weird ideas about like we're borders
Exist
Is the time that you should stop recognizing changes to borders I mean
In his mind I think the entire continent of Africa was just renamed Rhodesia so I don't know how many borders matter they
Germination
All the Rodger Whittaker again
Not his name
Is talking s*** on Fox News
I mean granted there are reasons to be like mine full of and watch
Situation
As it relates to Russian
Ukraine
And do you have
His response to it but
That it I think that everybody knows it
It's preposterous
To say like we're going to
First strike
Nuclear attack
Really fun for Alex and his friends to get back in
Into the Cold War
I don't I don't
This is productive
Speaking of unproductive
Alex decides to spend a little time
Chasing the world
And some of them are end-of-days stuff
Which
You'll never go
Okay
Let's end racism in America yeah that's our big
Looks looks
Chopsticks is a Mudslide
All the new winner of the international
The top
We're going to accept a man
Pointiest
Men are taking over women's forged
Man
Woman swimming match
Wrestling match
Lea Thomas
Is Val the top
X Converse
I find myself fascinated by the sorts of things Alex
Considers End of Days
Stop
Is trans athletes
This is evidence of the Apocalypse
Ridiculous
The Olympics will be overtaken as for Leah Thomas the transformer Alex's maligning
Really good meat
At the recent Zippy Invitational
I also think that Alex is just
Read clickbait headlines about this
Forgot to actually looking
Is true that Leah sent me quote pool and meet record on the 500-meter free
During the event
And that her time is currently the best
Best in the country
It is true that you said a couple other pool and meet records and other events
Really accurate to say that she's the best swimmer in the world
The one thing Alex's just glossing over the fact that the same beat Leah finished
Fifth of the fifth
Demeter free
And fourth in the Quaker of 400m medley relay
He's a swimmer who's good at some event and apparently not as good at others
Just like any other athlete
This isn't stuff
It's just another manifestation of Alex's bigoted RI
Imagine he actually cares at all about women
Collegiate swimming
Like to take collagen shity
What are you doing I mean
Again this is like go back 50 years was like well
I can't believe we're allowing women
Like it was just the same bulshit it's just
Updated I'm bored
It is
Spiritually
Almost the exact same
Yelp
So Alex now makes a deeply deeply transphobic
Narrative about the swimmer
But she
He can't
But
He's stunning and brave
$3 on a Wheaties box
All there is
There she is
Joke
Is a pretty standard thing for bigots
To suggest because there's a subtle implication baked into that statement that he's making that's inherently transphobic
Pier
Necessarily on the surface
Alex's suggesting that Leah couldn't
Can compete with the men
And so she transition
This allows Alex to make the claim that her transition was in
Inspired by a desire to swim against people that she cooked
Compete with
And he doesn't even have to say those exact words what you come off as really bad
You can make that that basically
That claim without actually making
Yeah that's gross
Essentially by holding
Kingsview Alex of giving
Voice to an idea that people's reasons were transitioning are not legitimate and they people likely or only doing it as a shortcut
Success
That's f***** up
It's stupid and it's based on absolutely nothing other than Alex's hateful imagination
Also pre-transition Leah was a really successful swimmer at UPenn
For instance in 2018 she broke the pool record for the 1000 free
And at that point in the season was the
The number for rent
Swimmer in the ivy league,
Before and after transition Lee has been an elite level swimmer
But Alex doesn't know any of that stuff
You just makes up a fence of storylines if it is prejudices and just reports those facts
Yeah yeah dumb
Yeah yeah
Guide to reality I think it is it is a great conclusion to make that someone would ever
Absolutely torture themselves
By living in a society that is 8
Angry and miserable and hateful
Towards you
Just so you can win a few
You collegiate
Yeah
Yeah it's it's a ludicrous proposition
And just based on
To create
Some kind of
A non hate-based reason for great
Trans people haha
Sports
I care a lot about women's Collegiate Sports
This is a little sweaty
He's trying to make this narrative that he has about Leah
Fit into his other narrative
Bono
I found this to be a little too hard
Mortgage companies
Goldman Sachs and JPMorgan
If they can get you
Who's the really famous Olympic swimmer dark hair
Tall guy
Michael Phelps just want to like always all metal
Best of everybody
What
But the only way
Did Michael Phelps what's going to happen
Dementia
I want to go down the women's division
I'm a woman
A lot of a lot of
Because I'm a signpost to hell I'm a signpost a collapse
On the signpost to the end of the world
A man
Can compete in women's sports and beat their ass in boxing
Orange
Orion MMA
We're all supposed to sit here
And go along with that light just like
7 shots
Subway
He's trying desperately to swing this into
Like a story about this Chinese
Weave that story
Come to this
How is he
Right here
And then into his lies story about Israel requiring 7 shot
It's just like I said it's sweaty
That's a lot of Hoops
To jump through
Returns at bat
It's very under
Compelling
I'll buy part I don't believe that any of this is
Materially related
I have a hard time believing that
Barry Bonds
Being
Kept out of the Hall of Fame is going to make him transition
Until we can get in
Into the Women's Softball Hall
I don't think that's how it's going to go
According to Alex
So answer the gas
At the end
The show
Okay
He's been kicked off Twitter
People on
Link to the
FDA documents
The final court order to release a little bit of them
Yeah
Posted these FDA documents on Twitter and got back
That's all you need to do
Not true I mean I assume there was some massive anti-semitic content somewhere along the line.
He was kicked off Twitter because he posted a long thread admission
Information about the IPA.
Being booted for posting
The document send and doing what
Haven't listened to your conversation about that would be one thing but it's not
Situation
Is misrepresenting its on of
I things from inside the
The same way that Alex does on his show
So look
Got these
These docks
From someone else
Twitter heat someone else with a smaller
And they turned his stomach
What golfer say we're just horrifying
Yeah look I mean I have a follower on Facebook
Take me to his
Little post
She doesn't have that
That much of a following so I
How to read
Mike Meisner
Stomach dropped
After I have 22
Weakest out
And all within a couple hours or just ate
Doo-wop listen notes
Documents are pretty
Scary
And
That's a lot of Santa
You know there's
Nobody wants to answer any
Nobody wants to talk
That's self-selected the group of doctors
You are talkin
Who can find doctors and scientists
Discussing this
Pretty easily
Does
Cause problem believe that
I do but I don't believe that there is a mom
Conspiracy among scientists about these.
I don't appreciate the Bible
The level of heroic myth-making it seems he's put into
I just read these documents and I realize
I had to tweak
It's outright like he's a f****** pianos
Twitter account
Yeah
Who makes another
Acclaim here
I don't
True
Conjecture that is that
It initially
Doctors
We're reporting things to like there
Joanne to the Pfizer Edwards
Events reporting
Fret
Okay well that's
The beginning
It was it was still
Pretty open
Or doctor
To speak outer or two
Give a call
Pfizer or
To the various data
And they weren't threatened
And about it today they're being threatened about it
Patient
I think they do that
How to get fired
Does who
Look even if you are in
An evil entity
Like who's
Like trying to kill people with the vaccines and stuff
It's still in your best interest
Stick out of that date
Yeah absolutely cuz you need you have to also have
Control over reality
In order to kind of unpredictable
Both of you need to know how people
That makes sense
I don't believe
Probably what doctors are being
Indoor fire
If they report adverse effects
Even if you were evil
You would still want the reporting of the opposite of people who survived
I just think that if you were able to produce
Proof
Maybe respond to it
Currently but I think
I think it's a joke
Because
He's talking s*** I want to know who's there
Heading home
That would be nice but also
He's just deciding without proof
Name plate like in this next clip he's decided that every single thing that's in that report is
Been proven to have been caused by the vector
Complaints
Many of them
Pretty serious song
Pretty serious.
As you saw it
12:00
So if you look at the
If you Quan
N35
Side effects
Reply.
1 + 35
Unprecedented
Playing with their side effects
Sure
Is a little bit loaded
That's the implication and throughout the entire conversation
Is that all of this
This is caused by
Not founded
When you have the conversation being had on that
Oh my g
In those terms
What's pointless conversation
Just dumb
Not going
To get to truthful
From falsity
Also
Is 4K
Nothing
You know like comparatively speaking
42000 is not even one-tenth
Does the people watching CNN
Just to give some kind of
Push back on that
This is only up to the 28th of February 20th
So at least it's
It's dated it only covers
A couple months
Vaccine
Information
But
It's not it's not as low of a number as it would be
Yeah
No it's really this guy lives in Israel
To know like
What
Why do
Globalists
All these bad guys
Really want to see
Israel
The clip is good
What is going on these foundations like why
Foundations the big money have the biggest hard-on
Choo choo choo to attack people in Israel
We can release dates
Justin
Israel's like this
Spearheaded
To spearhead so like we were the first
Any pregnant women we were the
First vaccinate
Company everywhere
Yeah
I mean
I can't I can't even try and imagine I mean looking for if you want to get down
Down deep the rabbit hole I mean
All the major positions in the CDC info
Pfizer going all these other
Companies
Companies that are pushing this all the
Call Jewish
So I mean
I mean I'm not going to I'm not going to
Let you know say that the
The craziest things but I'm just saying like
Pretty
Pretty weird
To see that all these people are in
Are Jewish and they're doing this to the Jewish shots and the Jewish
So there's there's a mess
Plan here and you know it I mean
Talking about it first
You know two decades at least
Silver has always been very own antibiotic
Listen I don't want to get too far down the rabbit
Butthole I mean you do what you don't want to do this but it is obviously
Conspiracy of the Jewish people to destroy the Jewish state
I'm not saying I'm just saying
Alex you've been saying that for 20 years so I mean you know that it's a conspiracy of Jewish people to destroy
Everybody knows
I'm not saying anything weird
Payment and all government is controlled by the
I understand
But this guy got kicked off Twitter any is a big-time got
Huge
Somebody somewhere knew about it
Pat said
After that
I might
Baked phone issue
Spider-Man
Doesn't want to piss off the anti-semites in his audiology
Take pics on Skype issues South packages all the time
Man from continuing to David indicating that it's common knowledge that I've
Been reporting essentially that's all I've been trying to say is that it's the globalist
Come on guys
He doesn't do that
Is Lament
The end of Truth
That's great
Sure except for he's doing it in response
What's to a question that Alex asked him
It's based on a false premise
Which is kind of ironic
Howard Howard Israelis that's the EpiCentre responding
This is
You're you're not actually that's why I'm sick you need to take a shot
There's no logic there
Logic
Definitely out the window in 2020 and 2021 has literally no logic there's no truth anymore
Now there's no truth anymore you ask me a question that's a lie
Yeah
How do you feel about the plague of pegasi absolutely destroying every Airline
Mister Airlines anymore
No one talk
Facts about the pegasi out there
The mainstream media is invested in bigpantha
It's the corporations
Who want to prop up the picket sign Arizona
I don't know if you've looked
Intuit but a lot of the people in major positions
The media are Pegasus
Boo
This caller is presenting as the major plan
Globalist
In order to get
People to be the track
Green passes
Social credit score
Which kind of runs counter to the entire idea that it's meant to kill you
Because why would they need
Cards
Tracking dead people
Who cares
Anyway the big plan is
According to Galileo is this tracking
And once they're able
They can turn off your
Your stuff at any minute
I meant he realizes that this
It's exactly like a documentary that Alex did in the past
Filmygod
They can't come up with a name of the guy the interview
Then once everything is done
Digital and they have
The screen passport and
You know
I think it was you speaking to
To mr. Ross
I think it was Ross
Saudi director of the American movie
It was a long time
He said all you have to do is is
Hit a button
And then your life is gone I could take away your life by
Pressing a button
Call job
What's his name
Exactly exactly
Okay
Good friend
El Papa my name who made America freedom to Fascism guys
Passed away
Castaway
Cancer
Yeah Hammerhead going off on the neck
Something Rossa Rose
Ross
Anyways the whole time I was like Aaron Russo is Aaron Russo
Football guys
Alex are good friends with her
Revealed all this secret information to getting rotors name
Does not really that important
Yeah you know you know it's b*******
I mean if you were
Earth-shattering info
I feel like I would remember your name
Also
Be totally clear
The Rockefellers didn't reveal
Aaron Russo if you don't remember
Talking to a guy named
Nicholas Rockefeller
Who is not related to the Rockefeller
Right who I was kind of a conman tank.
And I presented Aaron presented it as if he was in the Rockefeller family
And all this but that was not the
Regular old guy with the last name Rock
Yep no big deal but these dumb dumb
Don't even know that
I really take offense to is
Play calyx introduced gal by being like this person on Twitter is like
Good researcher
In charge of the information and such
And then like
You didn't take the time to ask yourself like
Did
Aaron Russo really talked to one of the Rockefellers
Like is this real
Well I mean it's been my experience that every human being with the last name Holmes
Has been related
Absolutely
Why not
You got some badass family member
Elizabeth Goodwin
Very yes
Not good Jordan your family sucks
And by the way it's got to be like the people who are just bad researchers who resolved
Infowars
I wanted to cover this but I just don't even care
What are the fourth hours
And his entire segment was about silent weapon
For quiet Wars
Greyhounds like
Man
This is just a fake document
You're doing
An hour
About how silent weapons for quiet Wars relates to the covid conspiracy
Island
You didn't
Look at this
Care to ask yourself is this real real
Conspiracy worldview good
Workday
I love it
I just lost a lot
What is the name Silas
A quiet Wars great height on a great title
I'm not going to argue that
There is a problem
31 last this is where things get a little bit scary
And I do not like what's going on any
And I'll tell you more
Try to
Get advice from lawyers and people who know the law and I'm like look at
What point do the
The citizens have
The right
To take the law into their own hands
To do anything.
You know violet
But when am I allowed
To arrest
Adjudge
That is not upholding the law
When am I allowed to arrest
Police station that is not upholding the law
What is it far tonight
Put take back
Check the law into our hands because nobody is
Nobody's Inn
Putting Justice
Holyshit
And you know what I would probably agree with that was Danny Rodriguez
You know you have the right side of certain points take the law into your own hands
You know maybe when you have nothing left to lose
I would say a lot of terrorists
Start from when you have nothing left to lose and you know what's interesting about people like this
Feel like I have nothing left to lose
And maybe they do something like
Taze a cop
Capital
It turns out I have a bank account on God
Pretending to have nothing to do you have family
These shity media sources that I was constantly
Convinced me that I had nothing to lose when in reality
Quite a bit
F*** you about the not violent thing
How do you think it's going to go with you try to arrest
The chief of police
You think you slick when can I peacefully
And here's the other question cuz I feel like this is the subtext to what he saying
When will the police chief
Recognize that I should be allowed to arrest him as well
What police chief
Well obviously
That's kind of the subjects
Never when will they realize LOL I'm obviously on the rug side
I'll just put my hands gently behind my back
This m***********
You can walk up and say that you are a bad judge maybe when you create overwhelming force that the police can't
I got a maybe but that's
Stomach still in
Implicitly violent sure you understand about the violence of the
Yeah
Congratulate
These guys are really stupid conversations dumb
I guess
His relevance is that he was kicked off Twitter so what did I expect
Dangerous dangerous mentality both V all these people who are doing this are Jewish
Bucked up
Not good
Mmv when is it time to take
Things into your own hands
When you have nothing left to lose
I think I probably sounds great in like a movie trailer or something but not Infowars
Good at what point does
The entirety of humanity go do the people telling us we have nothing left to lose our million
School
I don't think they have my back
The guy the guy was telling me like a maybe if nothing left to lose is selling me a
God silver coin is Nicholas markup
The guy who is telling me that I have nothing left to lose is fully aware that I am losing everything because
Part of why I'm losing
He's also working with a conman admetus cheesus Christ
Right Stuff
Uno's Uno's
Haven't tell them Jordan website
We're also on Twitter
Mdzs
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color