Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge vype.com
Alex Jones
What's a Jordan is a yearly ritual
Around this. Your holiday season
Every year
Are you a nice package of Williams-Sonoma peppermint bark
From my aunt and uncle
It's very nice I just got that I ate it already
Are you very fast
Goodall man ABC I'm using this bright spot also 22 to make up for something
Constantly forget to like thank them
Sure until I'm banking on possibly that my mom is listening to this podcast
Exactly
Not texting them
But also not texting your old boss busy I like it I love it
What are you got going on
Today Dan is we were guests on the wonderful god-awful movie podcast
Set dropped
Confusing movie we have to watch
Yeah we watched the Universe part 0
What
Fun
You will not stop yelling at 10
If you don't understand what that is
Those
Folk were having a song
What are the light
So Jordan today
We have to do our work
And that is
The most important work that we have ever done in our lives
Checking in on what's going on with reset War
We have to
Alex is going to say that this is the most important thing he's ever done
But I'm going to treat it as such
Yes
I'm so there's been some developments
Medcenter last time we checked in and spoiler alert it's been released
Have they disappeared Into The Ether
I have no reports okay on that
Alright
Absence of evidence is not evidence of absence
So
Transcending that has going on among
What's the info Warrior community
But I don't I don't have any other.
I think I probably didn't happen
Doubtful but
I have
Reached an impasse
Slightly
And we'll talk about it over the course of this episode
I'm up against the wall
I don't know what to do
And I'm getting it I'm willing to take advice from the audience on this one
I will talk about all that before we do
I'll take you to some new from Virginia Beach Virginia
I'm about like Wavy Gravy
I like it
To the team
Separately double Patriot points till Valentine's Day
I'm a policy wonk thank you very much and I can't Listen to Smashing Pumpkins now and not think of the time Billy Corgan was
Gaston in pool
Oh yeah
Yeah but he was saying the world is a vampire he was being literal it was it was not
Metaphor
Quaintly put into a cage and transformed into a rat Chimera is there an issue
Despite Israel
So I have a couple things that I want to get out of the way better than reset Wars
Before we get going
I have
The information that's available and I
Have looked at what
Been going on with reset Wars and what's been going on with Alex on his show
And I am becoming more and more convinced
That I was a little bit off
I don't think that Alex is running
Reset Wars
At all I don't know for sure
But it does not
View attached
To his main product
In any way
Completely separate
Feels like a gig
Did the vibe that I get off
What's this
Is it this is a this is like a Dulce thing
Tim Burton producing Nightmare Before Christmas
Timber new mate
That kind of thing
No no it was produced by the director of Nightmare Before
No no I don't have a totally different thing
Monkeybone Monkeybone that movie Monkeybone was directed by the director of Nightmare Before Christmas
Exactly
I worked at the movie theater or Monkeybone came out and you will not believe how many people were so different.
Ono 30 years for the Brendan Fraser to come back after Monkeybone
That's how good he never came never never end
God bless him
He shouldn't have weight Corky Romano is that before or after monkey baby under we may never know
So yeah
It feels it feels kind of like
He's a picture man
Something I don't know I don't know for sure
Like I said
Help to tell butt
Everything seems very discordant
The contactor is pulling out on this
Maybe
The observer effect
Everything
Seems to disconnect
Is a little correction about this
And that is that
On our first episode about recent Wars I talked about how Jake Ducey has a podcast
And I said that it was on iHeart
And what I meant to say
Calculator this incredibly poorly
His podcast and I didn't realize this because we're not on a network and I don't know how these things work
Reached out and made it sound like they produced that podcast
I realized that is
Kind of how it came off
Totally not my intention and I
I did not mean to imply that the company iHeartRadio
That was just poorly delivered on my part
Anyway
Look here's what's going to happen
Alex released
Reset Wars
The other
Couple nights ago
From when we're recording
Like a Taylor Swift
Talk about that a little bit but before we do we need to lead up to it
By looking at
Free videos
Could Alex put out
Promoting
Hello release of up reset Wars
The first one
Is a video that you put out called
Transcend the third dimension with Alex Jones and reset Wars
This is a good
2 minutes long
This but these videos I'm just going to play
Just cut it points for us to discuss share not
Not leaving much on the on the Cutting Room floor
And here is where we start
The archive
Tunnel
The portal
Is amongst the most
Because
We know we came out of our mother
What
We know that
Portals are tunnels
Symbolize
Coming from one state
Instinctively
Symbol of the
Transference
Destroyed
What quantum
Quantum mechanics
Ever done
And all available
Reset War
I think Alex maybe like
It'd be so fun if you just like
Heard that Alan Watts
The drunk
Actually I could ramble of nonsense over
Soft music people see the f****** love that old man I remember reading the Dallas pool imagine if it was the reset
He's mine
Yeah so what's going on here is that
16 there was this picture of Alex walking out of
Atonal looking pretty angry
6:30 or 4:40.
So I
On his property
Probably
I think he's leaving his driveway
The man
How great would it be though if that was
In like
Some random ass place in Florida and they're like
God dammit
Turtle tunnel
Nearby have been occupied Texas I have never looked at a tunnel and thought
Wow
That reminds me of vagina
Is it
It didn't occur to me to drive beneath the mountain and go through this is warm but that rule
I want to go through it
Cuz it's like a womb
Yes yes strange don't know what it means to say that the tunnel is one of the most
Tibial images
Cuz I
I think
You could come up with a lot
Of different
Archetypal images
Sure
I don't know I don't know how you rank them
But I guess tunnel is up there archetypal image
Also the idea that the energy can't be destroyed or created only change
Hello that's quantum
Mechanics that's just
The first law of thermodynamics
It's just how it works
I don't
Noah
He's trying to say
We are but it's
Confusing me
End of the social ears Engineers understanding the first law of thermodynamics is wonderful
Straight I appreciate that
I'm confused as to how they can orca
Castrate movements based around that most scientists
I think that like
Quantum mechanics
And so probably be understanding of it relies on
Stuff that was built out of the understanding of
The more basic for the
Sure I mean
To my ears
I am getting the vibe of people who have just
Like
Taking the pseudoscience
The four
Humor's and just changed it with quantum mechanics you know like
Well if your bile is out of alignment then you're in trouble or just like
If your color about
Quantum mechanics is out of
Whack then you're in trouble like that gun
I feel like generally speaking it's just kind of like
Bluffing depth
And this is big comes across in this next Passage
I hope you'll join me
Secret
Howard
Incredible level
A lot of
Others in the dark
We are literally talking
Spirit Wars mine
Just a word to the wise
Don't fall for it when people act like this
Do that
When there's some kind of a nut
Unspoken piece of information that is transformed and empowered someone's life but also
A lot of people have found out about another using it for evil but I'm not going
Talk about what it is or
Don't believe
No it's not
Amir just stop believing hard enough
I believe it real hard
This reminds me so much here's the problem that I'm having right now haha one of my favorite gods
How to beat You black Emperor songs
Is essentially a tunnel is a metaphor
It's like an eight-minute song I can't remember if it's bbf3 or Moira or something like that
But it is this
Lunatic poet
Who's just come out of getting a f****** Park
King tickets
And going off
Sovereign citizenship all put to godspeed You black Emperor music
And it's really really good and Atmospheric and it sounds suspiciously like this
But this is way worse
Gatsby doesn't involve
If godspeed and Alex Jones had Italian
I might be f***** I might have no idea where the land but morally
Alex hear that
On way to inoculate yourself from me
But here here is the here's the end of this video if this is
Pretty funny
You'll notice a change in audio a little bit
And yet you build be pretty
Please do figure out what's going on
Find out more and start your journey today
Reset Warriors
You don't have to stay with him
You don't have to
Free will
Eternity
So that was Alex yelling from the other side of the tunnel
Will Echo
Hello
He's yelling from across the tunnel short
Amazing come with us just beautiful
That was disappointing
Anyting
I have no idea what the hell does reset Wars about
Vaguely spiritual
Vaguely based on like hypothetical quantum
Mechanics sure it's something to do with transcending the third dimension
Also it seems a little creepier
Then
Very creepy
The end of a tunnel a big like come with us
Butts
Yeah that's upsetting
Satisfying but luckily Alex released another video about Risa or plugging the eventual launch
Postpone the number of Thai
The second one was titled
The Earth and reset wars.com
Starting the video up I just I have to guess that it's going to be pretty grandiose considering the recent wars being put up there with a pan
A lot of important things like God and the Earth
This is the least viewed preview for recent Wars and it starts with Alex talking to a camera
In a wooded area
That I'm going to gases backyard
F****** around with here here's where we're at on
Tune in to God
The Earth and reset wards.com
Grandiose
How do you say
Pink butterflies
Enable 2fa
Gallstones
Parents were born
Naproxen
It's electric
Cell
That actually navigate
Layla onto the Earth
Ley lines
Connecticut
To lower animals
Aldi's
Trees
Everything
Conduit
Football
Swinging
I would say I'd already Alex's way off on a bunch of stuff
The question of how birds know how and when to buy great is really interesting.
Crazy field-of-study
The mechanisms that are involved for Birds aren't the same as what's going on with like butterflies but I guess they're both situations
Involve migrations cool call it all the same thing he's implying that
Decent hummingbirds and butterflies migrate to the same place they were their parents were born in order to mate and lay eggs
And that's not true
What I was actually referring to the phenomenon called natal homing which is weird
Go to reproduce
This is not like messerli prevalent in geese or hummingbirds
Probably meant to use where salmon and turtles
Which are better examples
This is like really
Crazy stuff to be far beyond my ability to explain to sync lie here but there are few things that I need to point out
This has nothing to do with ley-lines which aren't even real
It does involve magnetic fields and the ability that animals like turtles and salmon as well as pigeons have called magnetic
No reception
The exact process of how this works is something the scientist heaven
I really reached a consensus on
According to an article in the Smithsonian some believe that it has to do with proteins in the retina that can detect magnetic information
While another hypothesis is that quote
Microscopic particles of the mineral magnetite said if certain receptor cells in the
The ear or behind the nose
And work as biological
Compasses
It's entirely possible that some humans may also have very subtle levels of magnetic reception
But this is far from being proven in any repeatable experiment
Also a number scientist don't seem to have much
Faith that even if humans
Physiological
Physiologically capable of detecting
Changes in electromagnetic fields that
Really means anything
There was a study a few years back done by a geophysicist
Caltech
This guy wanted to know whether just simply whether human brains were even
Capable of responding to changes in the magnetic fields around them
Leaving aside how it could happen is it was happening
People people in a dark box where he could have just
The field inside and quote
The experimenters recorded dipson the amplitude of alpha brain waves
Is in a third of the participant
There are a ton of caveats but even so this is a pretty interesting result for this trial
But what does it mean
Does it mean that we have electromagnetic abilities that are dormant and we don't even realize it
Probably not
And it might not even mean that we have what you traditionally call ascent
It is article the Smithsonian thorsten Ritz a biophysicist at UC Irvine Irvine had a great quote
If I were to stick my head in a microwave and
Switch it on I would see effects on my brainwave
That doesn't mean we have a microwave sense
The decent articulated definition of apathy,
Barry Pitt
Articles about this study were making the rounds in 2019 and I could easily see Alex reading a headline and disorder writing his own
Story about it
I think that might be what's going on
Again this is all fascinating stuff and it's pretty exciting
See where this research will continue toward but the stuff Alex saying is a little much
He's taking a kernel of something event extrapolating it out far past the point where it be
I keep standing on Solid Ground
What was the ND seems to be getting into like epigenetics where the like instinctive pass generation
Things are inherited
I don't know
Exactly how that applies or what is point even
Yeah that's always enjoyed learning about migration and the thing that I've learned her
Repeatedly is every time somebody tells me
Me how migration works
It will change
So I'm I don't trust how migration Works Beyond Magic
And then whenever they figure it out I'm going to be so excited to know
But until then
A lot of it also has to do with the Sun
Speaking of the Sun
A lot of it has to do with internal clock
What's the weather like
Butterflies have in their antennae how do they have internal clocks they're not that big
You got tiny tiny
You know they want you to plug into
The Matrix
Conduit
Connect to the
Sean
All the Third.
Forgot
Weider
In home
Watching the
The Prado Matrix
Chucky
VR real
Cuz that binds
Seymour the Third
And for even lower.
Artificial
Still like
Really wrestling to try and figure out what he's saying
Like what's the point
What are you driving
You can do anything
As long as you give me money
It does feel that way
Cuz we've got Okay so
The globalist want you to stay connected to the third dimension by way of
The Matrix or whatever
But
If you're someone like Alex then you understand the way there
Geese
And butterflies migrate has to do with electromagnetic
Things in their brain right
So if only you do the stuff that Alex does
You could migrate
I guess I just feel like what were
What his
Like
Gameon that is an explanation
An explanation of like
You know
Stuff is weird
What if we just
More like
Time
If we had the same abilities that he's describing
In like
Birds
And I butterflies like
We just okay now we don't need GPS
I mean okay
What is a high school reunions but
A return to your home to breathe
Right well
I guess but you can't you can't get there you know you're not going to be able to just stay away from flowers
Think there's a there's a pretty strong sense that this is just like
Go outside that seems to be like what the
The point of this
How to lock you
In the five senses
And worshipping at is the entire
Existence
Distracted
Walking
The sound of a babbling
Brooke is
Hundreds of
Times better than theirs
Do some Studies have shown the forest bathing can have a positive effect on people's mental state but these studies are far from
Conclusive
And a review of existing research in the 2017 issue of the international Journal of Environmental Research
And Public Health
Find some comfort
Locating biases and methodological
Problems with the setup
All these previous studies that have been done on the health benefits of forest bathing
I have some of them or like
People went out and had to walk in the forest
4 hours
It's like I could have a positive effect on your well-being but
Yeah yeah yeah that's not really a long-term solution
Your mental state to spend time outside
If Alex is just saying the people
Should spend time outside I guess that's cool
Like if resources just scolding is audience to get away from the TV and take a walk in
Park it probably can't hurt
I'm sure somebody to do
Mystical nonsense he's attaching to it is
I don't know if that's helpful but at this point I guess the worst that's going to come out of this is like an info Warrior trying really hard
To tell him what a worm is telling him
Believing you can do some internal superpower to find the spot where he was conceived
UPS
It is it feels a little bit like he's like
Redoing the guru movement from the 60s for far-right
Conservatives you know like I'm a little Dumber
Yeah yeah like a Ken Kesey called abuse
To have all of these people come get into a hot tub with a mini tell him about spirituality and be like I'm a
Psychologist again I don't think
Alex is doing
No I don't think he's that committed today
I do I don't this does not feel connected to what's going on and he showed
Generally
Let's say I mean
Stephen Butch
Writing of what
Keep saying still feels soda
Disjointed and improvised
You know it's like somebody was like okay let me give you the bullet points and we're going to like Will Ferrell
All this movie until today Saturday to go until like has Paul Joseph Watson style jumps
Sending audio
Shocking
And annoying
Well it is annoying but it's over like this is the best you got after
That level of editor
You do it and this is what we get not good
Also when I was saying that like what's the worst that can happen is like trying to listen to worms or whatever
The case except for like Alex is using this ideology to demonize and invalidate medical interventions for Mentos
Go health issues
Like stigmatizing people taking appropriate steps to address mental health challenges
This is just unacceptable
Like telling someone is dealing with a mental health crisis that they just need to listen to a babbling stream
That's the equivalent of telling someone who just broke their leg in a football game a rub dirt on it it's just
Really really unhelpful
All it'll do is
Make people less likely to take mental health issues seriously
And blame themselves when listening to a Brooke doesn't help
As listening to a stream as somebody who was very much instructed to treat mental health that way all
All the way up until I don't know
Yesterday
I-88
Brutal
Soccer
Fux with your head for the rest of your life because you feel like you can't share stuff with other people because then you're there just going to say hey
Suck it up because you like fine I'll suck it up then stay silent and then later I'll die of can
Demotivated
People to even
Experience
What they're feeling or
Look for help when they're feeling something they need help
Hell yeah
Just I think that
I mean I don't want to say evil but that's
Awful I mean an awful Behavior
Years for me to even talk to my partner and be like hey I'm
Fox man
So what you going to do
Well I'm going to play another clip
Dammit
Through the
Environment
But I do work
God
Smoothies
Conduit
Like an animal
Connect me
Listening to some of this and it's starting to feel like
A little bit like poorly understood gnosticism
Like there's some there's some Vibes that I'm getting there pretty pretty gnostic
Who are the ideas of what recent Wars
Seems to be based on traceback pretty neatly to Gnostic cosmology
41 this whole thing seems to be based on the idea that there's something within us that's more than our physical selves and in fact
We're trapped in these physical body
According to gnostics thought each person has a Divine spark within them which is eternal compared to the physical body which is H
Shelf life
Juicy's interview on Alex's Alex's comments about the whole thing so far
It really seems like their goal is to wake people up to this reality and that the moon of the globalist have been trying to
Keep humans in the dark
About the fact that they are
Actually spirit
Does the direct parallel to the Gnostic belief about the demiurge and the archon
The demiurge
The creator of this physical reality which is actually a false reality and there's like the real reality of the
Picked it up laroma in the goddess fullness
Archangel Michael supposed to be in Catholic
Mysticism I'm not sure but in this case it's just the creator of the physical world
It's a goal of the demiurge and his minions these Arkansas
To keep Humanity from recognizing that they contain this
Divine spark which connect
The Ultimate Reality
It exists
Beyond the false reality that we are in
Even all of Oz talk to you about the out of the system w
Keep you in your home watching The Matrix screens because they
Keep us in touch with the third dimension
That's exactly the strategy that the bad guys and gnosticism Hughes
Gnosis.org
Humans are generally ignorant of the Divine spark resident within them
This ignorance is fostered in human nature by the influence of the false Creator and his ark on
Two together are intent on keeping men and women ignorant of their true nature
And Destiny
Anything that causes us to remain attached to Earthly things serves to keep us
And enslavement to these lower Cosmic ruler
I'm very similar to exactly what I want to say
And now
I want to talk about how his Consciousness is God experiencing itself
This too is pretty rustic at its core
In the secret book of John the story is told of the Gnostic creation of the Universe and Everything essentially spirals
Outward from the Sun
The one
The father of fullness
What's the beginning of everything
This one views himself in a Wellspring of Living Water
Experience
Seeing him
Are experiencing himself
Gives birth to barbelo the embodiment of forethought
Who would become the creator of all these other entities that would inhabit
The fullness or diploma
Then again also
It could just be a situation where Alex's misremembering the Carl Sagan quotes
We are away for the cosmos to know itself
So could be a little bit of what
Palawan
I feel like imagining that Alex is actually aware of an able to grasp agnosticism is probably giving him
A bit too much
Credit
It's interesting though how much of an overlap there is a lot of these ideas that are being articulated in reset worth
But maybe it shouldn't be that surprising
I don't think it's indicative of all people who follow gnosticism but there is a bit of history of Gnostic ideas being used to prop up
The worldviews of white supremacist
The Nazis
You can kind of easily see how Nazis might use the creation story to Aiden there demonization
Jews
Some followers of esoteric branches of Nazi ideology like Miguel Serrano believe that the demiurges is the god of the old
Old Testament
And consequently they believe that Jewish people are followers of the equivalent of Satan I feel like being interested
Gnostic ideas
Should make someone like be suspicious or like no big deal
But when it's combined with the rest of the stuff Alex believes in preaches to his audience
Comes
Little bit I'm not sure I
I'm not into
I think it's bad
Yeah I say eyes and here's my pitch know but
Picked picked up on it so far but
I think we should just return to Sumerian gods
Exclusively
Play like let's just do eggs boil
Stay where we were we were crushing it
I bet it all went to s***
We don't even know how to speak super anymore see well I know what is Erich von daniken
Speak it perfectly
He does not know
Nature's good
I've heard
It's good
Okay
The natural
Horrible rap
Why am I
Lower third
I'm not saying
Incredibox
Part of Who We Are
Keep us only
Allstate
We don't rely
Stupid
Best friend Joe Rogan primarily famous because he was a commentator for the UFC
Meathead Bros that makeup is fanbase loved Newsradio
Maybe maybe they like Fear Factor but I don't believe I don't believe that's the primary
Reason he has an audience
Interesting contradiction that Alex is presenting
He constantly talks about how the globalist want to convince you that you're dirty and bad
There's a human you're doing
Something wrong
Then here he seems to be juxtaposing the beauty and goodness of nature with the ugliness and evil of Times Square
But ultimately what is Times Square other than a representation of what humans can create
It seems like he's trying to save a human to decide to build cities
That dark to his liking or dirty in bed
But I'm not sure what he's based
That honestly seems very very weird
Yeah generally speaking the original sin
People like to just Define whatever it is they don't like
Has
Spiraling offer
So that way you don't have to worry about whether another God's at it or whatever you're just like see your ugly and Evil.
Maybe something that speaks to a deeper aesthetic
Pleasing Ennis
About nature then
What's a building
Sure
You know I'm an indoor kid I I prefer cities
Obviously you and I have discussed me going outside many a time and I'ma
So I've I find his spirituality been to be ridiculous I'm constantly reminded of
Achievements of mankind
But what is it about Time Square that Alex
Is opposed
New York cuz it's not consumerism
No not a lot of people probably would take issue with
Is it campy pollution
Which would be a problem that some people would have he doesn't
Really believe that the problem
I'm going to go with Melting Pot
Is apartheid
Pearl City
Time Square was in
F****** Florida
The scientist was ruling over
We wouldn't have a problem with it Factor do it
Stressful there's a lot of people walking
Pink around right
Well I mean if your basic
Underpinning of your philosophy is that
The races are under
Equal and can never possibly coexist is equals
Then where would be the most
Threatening thing in the world to you because it clearly shows you're wrong
That might be
That's why you got to go to Nature
Be there to make you feel wrong
The globalist are creating virtual reality
Right
At 8 I think
Alex has a weird
Theory about why they're doing it
Bubbles cleaner building
We are to get us out
Make a trance
All of the
So we come to them and submit to them and do whatever they say in the great race
Reset today
Let's go outside
I want to need Source on the globalist claiming that they're creating VR in order to make us less warlike
I have not heard anyone say that
Yeah I was looking
Some of this
Gerard like
Applications that are possible of VR technology in therapy settings to work for like children who have problems with the gray
Absolutely research is pretty exciting
But I don't think that's what Alex
Just talkin about
I'm sure that would be huge for like immersion therapy isn't something along those lines that I can actually use
Totally without actually having to go to Virtual Reality
You're able to hang out with a giant bee
Who's cool what is he having boyfriends butt
Basically we're just describing Alice in Wonderland when you could do that in reality
Then you're no longer afraid of bees infect you think they're your friend
One thing
I've always bums me out about people who are obsessed with the fact that we live in a simulation or obsessed with believing that we live in
Dissimulation
Is how disappointing VR is
In a simulation
Eventually br
Like what a bummer
To have shity VR inside the best
2BR but I hear it's gotten a lot better I haven't checked in
In quite a while in terms of
Piano
I haven't tried VR in a long time and tried like the Oculus or what
Wingstop is pretty
Pretty cool
What do I do with your I get what you're saying
Take me to
Also if we are in a simulation of gives a s*** if we enter a second one
Like an otherwise I'm really matter
It's just Turtles all the way down
And we create this alternate reality that Mark Zuckerberg is running or whatever and we're all forced to enter it
Great Angela simulation start yelling at people in there nobody's being bothered
Build a video game inside of Minecraft
After you like fine
Yeah it's a great way to play it I don't care
Get inside that simulation early
Set yourself up as like a Saviour figure boom
Yeah it's like snow crash
Just like hero you got to be there you got to be on the ground floor of the net and then you then you're good to go there you go
We talked already about how this is clearly there's cuts
Multiple takes going on
I would have cut
This
I would have done a second take on this
For sure
This is the reason
The great reset is
The Old World Order
The tyranny
Trying
Suppress the Great Awakening
Okay so the old world order is folks like Klaus Schwab in the tyrant
It's right there. Alex and his buddies are engaged in the Great Awakening
And from this one might be inclined to say that if Alex and his buddies were successful they be creating a new world order
It would certainly be a world order that was new and different from the old world order I don't know what else you'd call it then a new one
World Order I'm so frustrated because just a few months ago he called them the New World Order
The Old World Order
You can't be
The new guy all your life cannot believe he wouldn't
Just like oh wait hold on
All of my ideas
Oh well
This video ends with a call to action
Of course
Join me now
20 today
Reset War
Globalscope
I open
You got three wheels
I have free will and I'm not going
Power somehow Force
Maybe I'll join your dumb s***
So
The times going on like Alex putting up these promos for recent Wars
I don't know it
Means
I don't get any sense
Of what this is the temperature
Esoteric pseudo-spiritual Babel
Like I do
Don't even know what's going on just buzzword
It's pretty detached religious Concept in Fort Worth Tarrant all being mixed into a stew
The only thing I got through line that I can find it like he's desperate to get people to sign up
That's basically all I've got
And that feeling of desperation could even pronounce when Alex released another promo for reset Wars that was titled
How Joe Rogan's Awakening affect the great reset
Eagle-eyed observers noted that this headline news the wrong spelling of effect
And as such the technical meaning of the title this video is that Joe Rogan's Awakening
Cause the Great
Reset
Imagine that isn't what Alex was trying to convey
I'm pretty sure this is
Just another case of bad editorial at Infowars and now it's doing everything you can to constantly remind people that he's friends with Joe Rogan
Amuse that Association to sell his balls
You got it
By this point to Promos in I was
Not expect
Too much but this is the video where Alex is contemplating the flower
The report we put a Twitter picture up
So I couldn't resist as he's looking
Stone flower
So anyway here is here's where we start on this
Do you know world
What we call
You're always so hard
Core program
This goes to a Bazaar
Notion that I've seen in other reset Wars promotion
Materials
And that has to do with the idea that when you're born you're a blank slate
Like there is just nothing going on
And everything that is bad interesting or whatever is stuff that has been pushed
Sit upon you
Like negative feelings
Self-doubt depression
These are all viruses bad programming that has been put upon you by the global
Dumb
I mean it's a goes counter to the thing he's supposed to believe
Epigenetics and stuff
Runs counter pretty heavily
There's a lot of
Counterpoint
Yeah Alex himself will just bring up
But yes look did the bad guys hate
In a sense because it's a new life that hasn't been corrupted by their
Other system I guess
Whatever
How do you know who else is innocent and like
Totally cool
Shelter Rogan
Alex
Yeah they're cool
F*** you
The most alive
Celebrating
It's just funny
Pizza think back on like
Nonsense ideas words like
About me to why are you so popular Alex Jones
Well for the same reason that the most popular podcaster in the world is popular his final wonderful
Great dad I don't know if you remember but back when he was trying to go Sneaky Snake
And expose Joe part of it was talking about Jose kids
Which was gross
Personal attacks
Saint Joe's
Children let's listen to few clips from February 5th
2019 when Alex was going to war with Rogan
And then
It's insulting like I still want to hug you
I don't like you
I'm guilty
I need a bad news 20 years ago
I should have ignored that
Are Charming.
I want war Joe
I want more I don't want to be nice
I want a cleanser
Hyundai
So it changed wasn't letting you on his show and let you on about
He's always been the greatest guy in the world as opposed to I knew you were bad news 20 years ago
Guy who won't let me on the Shelf
Yeah it doesn't feel like Alex ever grew out of that
7 year old level of under
Understanding where it's like I want to go outside no you have to go do your homework
You're my favorite person in the world I have no Rogan
I'm running away with you
So I think it is
This video is largely just
Vague platitudes
Essentially I mean nothing
Following
Globalist
Culture
Obliterate
All of that
Will
So they can impose
None of us really even means anything I can do
Saying things at Times Square
The important thing about being a
Call it later is
Be as vague as possible
And then when somebody is like what are you talkin about you say
What are you
Feel like I'm talk
And then whenever they say some b******* back at you or like see
The Revelation is upon you as well even better thing to do is just be super vague
The fallen on science and then never make yourself available to be quiet
Well that one's good but you're not going to get let off with that kind of behavior
Field mechanics that he's looking for a couple bucks
That's true
You can get a lot of money if you got a strong call to
Alex makes a bizarre
Claim here he seems to be saying
That
The globalists
Are trying to
Force VR goggles onto children
And I see no evidence of this being the case
Albany
VR goggles
The imposition of
Real life Matrix
Onto them
Crush and destroy
Child
That's not godly quotes
Yai
Don't know how I feel about
The notion that kids are being forced into VR goggles
I know that
All you have to do to switch things up as far as fake quotes go is
You know
Far-right Thomas Jefferson said it new age
Gandhi said it baby that all you got to do pretty good sister sample
So do you think they're forcing
I didn't get off this I will tell you the image in my head that popped in
Because of the way that Alex
Has built these people up
I get the sense that like they don't even have the ability to
Control it like if you put a globalist inside of a cage
They were and then like let him out with a bunch of Greece children around they chase him with a VR helmet be like
Or even
Like more to the point you put them in a cage and then you like
Sneak in like
A doll of a child it will think it's real
TV shows this is all set up
I don't
Yeah I don't I don't think this is accurate
Cool
So Elon Musk tweeted something that's similar
Theme to some of the ideas that Alex
Apparently putting in to reset Wars
My male baby
Information
Talking about
Exact
Information
In the 6-hour class
Is what month
Radio wasn't invented
Technology was already there humans
Just
Discovered
It's fun to say that three people invent did radio on different continents in the same week but that's
Because I wasn't being specific I'm honestly not even sure who the third person he's claiming invented radio is but the cover art
Comes down to Tesla and Marconi is being two people
Most appropriate to say are the inventors of radio
Which is to say that your wireless communication
Each of them has a pretty good claim to the title Tesla was the first to demonstrate wireless radio in 1893
Years later Marconi got the first patent
For wireless telegraphy telegraphy
Though Tesla got to the actual radio thing first Marconi would be the first person
Beside the signal across the Atlantic Ocean
Really pretty
The correct answer in this debate
Is the inventor of radio is Marcone
And we know that from 1
Very
Piece of information
I can't believe you
Fitbit today
That's right
Marconi plays the Mambo
The radio don't you remember
You know it's trouser Starship at that point
Nowhere though
James Clerk Maxwell who formulated equations about how electricity and magnetism
And in 1886
Heinrich Rudolf Hertz made a proof-of-concept that electric current
Could quote be projected in the form of radio waves
You can even predate the invention of radio as a broader concept back to 1866 when
Quotes that wireless telegraphy work
This kind of putting it mildly
In October 1866 Loomis used to kites between 14 and 18 miles apart
Vertical antenna
High frequency detector and espark.app transmitter to
To conduct his experiments
Is credited by the Library of Congress is the first known incidence of Wireless aerial communication
The transmitter and detector work together to successfully cause one kite to move the other
Speaking to one another through radio waves
For a dude in the middle of the Civil War not bad not bad
It wouldn't be until 1915 that any speech would be able to be transmitted across the country from New York to
Francisco and the concept of radio for entertainment purposes
Wouldn't come along
For quite a while after this
The idea that radio was invented by three people on continent
It's in the same week
Just decided it was true
It's ultimately meaningless as a clam though since the development of what we know is radios Annex
The cover the better part of 100 years
To come from its conception
Formulation and then implementation
Although now that I thought about it
Just saying the three people magically came up within the same weeks
More fun
Yeah
I'm probably more profitable one of the most destructive points of view of History
In all
Time is that great
Man.
Like
Not even just
The inventors or anything like that or or the scientist or or
Actions before them
Thousands of people
Thousands upon thousands of people doing research all the time in communication with each other and some
Sometimes not and sometimes not build the basis for these are called invention
Do you know it's not like
It's not like all we was there to be discovered it's that there were
People work
Yeah there's a lot of things that are very fascinating in terms of simultaneous Innovations
Any breakthroughs that happened
And sometimes it's
It's pretty hard to explain
Why
Those things
Explain how it's possible these things were people came to the same conclusion
This Innovation was based on a breakthrough that happen
Previously that people are both working off the same competing against each other as well
Explain everything but it does explain
Something
Yeah so here is beat the end of
A video of those
Supposed to be a promo that had to do with Joe Rogan and didn't really have that much
To do with Joe
I don't know why this
Was titled
Joe Rojo Joe Rogan's Awakening affect the great reset
Except for Alex wanted Joe Rogan be the title if you put Joe Rogan the title and people search Joe Rogan Maybe
Pop-up marketing
Don't let them
Crusher will do
Doordash
Realize
You have 1/8 Freewheel
You can overpower
But you're not conscious
Seeing the world
With new eyes every moment
Slaves
A Very Brady
Turner back
On.
Take us
Wisdom
In their own
Medemerge
Humanities Counter-Strike
Join me there
Boots
Like that
Really dangerously close to saying choose life
Giving me a chance to play some lineup
That's not how bored I was getting with these these promos by their 25th
Starship city shows up
It's not cuz you were interested in the material for the hoopla
Saudis promos
Socks
And I did not feel like I had a better sense of what any of this was it was just
Especially if you're somebody who like myself who's gone
Through
Like a lot of self-help
Through a lot of self-help so put likes seeing a lot of these blogs
These message boards of people trying to push this nonsense
Stuff like
This just sounds like any kind of
Vague platitudes being used to try and sell something
What
On Sunday December 12th
Alex announced it at midnight
He'll be releasing
The biggest
The most important piece of work
Recent Wars
And I didn't know if I should take this seriously because he's done this in the past and it has not come out
What
At midnight
Exactly
@midnight reset Wars change
From being a
Fill in your email and you'll get an announcement
To being
A new page
At the top of it there was a video
Those Alex sitting at a desk
7 Minute long video
It's just meaningless it's
Just
Him reading a script to clearly like he's going 4.8
Point B
Not saying anything but he's
At least like this is off-the-cuff
This was him reading
It was
It's a disaster is fad
Horrible video
And a lot of the scriptures reading is actually
Covered in
The text on the page
It's way too long
It's
Reformat it
And it's presented as a letter from the desk of Alex Jones
Good God
A letter
Yeah
It starts my dear fellow Patriots
Jesus
There's there's a number of things
Things that jumped out to me
I am at one of the first things
Is a visit there's no there's no way out
It's so out of his voice
It has no
I word choice similarities that Alex uses it is
It's outrageous
Like halfway down the page
Beginning of it pretty boring
It sure you stand her just kind of like
You know what we heard in the recent Wars part 1 episode 2
It's kind of like a globalist
The page business starts to pick up
There's a section with a big bold headline
They wanted
Install viruses into you and keep you from realizing your power
Here we get back to this idea of the
Blank slate
Here's the stats section
True...
By using social conditioning they install viruses of negative emotions self-sabotaging behaviors
Self-loathing
Depression anxiety and many more
When were first born our minds are completely blank slates
It's why you see so many babies with thousand yard stare
They're taking it
Lot of babies staring into the middle distance
Call the bus while it's raining outside wondering where their relationship with Raynaud's more baby
Alright text they're taking in all the data from the world around them and trying to process it
These viruses start getting planted When We're Young through movies television music and especially nowadays social media
You all this babies on social media
Every time they said play Mozart for your baby in the womb but they weren't telling you if it's installing virus
Susie inside your baby's head that are making them stare into the middle distance
Yeah and I accidentally for my baby I accidentally play Tupac Hit Em Up
Call your phone
Program people with a belief that they're not enough and they're flawed worthless creature
Bluewater unpack there
Like first babies are not blank slate
It's as we discussed and in many cases of mental illness has a genetic basis
Like the idea of this being presented is stupid in the main effect that it can have it
It's further stigmatize mental illness
Dissuade people from seeking help
And like I said earlier I find that to be repulsive
Yeah I'm not bipolar type one because I just can't
No I think it's because you're on social media as a baby could have been an early adopter
Friends
The second point I have is like
I think this is really important
I was noticing it also as I was getting to this point
The text is written and formatted intentionally
To be like subconsciously persuasive
Their paragraph breaks after every sentence
Oh God
Digestible tidbit and almost all of the sentences Trail off with ellipses
Ending sentences in ellipses is a subtle marketing
Amtrak that's used
A couple different responses from readers
The first is that it gives the impression that a thought has more
Become which inherently builds tension in the reader's mind
This has the effect of making the reader less likely to get bored and stop reading because the ellipses
Text Amanda thinking
Did something big is coming
The second effect of lips
She's having writing as a bait indicate ink
Complete thought
Which allows the reader to mentally engage with a text
And fill in the blank with something
Which creates a subconscious connection
Whipper with a reader and what's being red
This is something
Canby
Khalid on an ad copy
But the way that's being overused in this text is almost embarrassing
It denotes an awareness of this technique in persuasive writing but almost no awareness of
How to use it appropriately
Like if you use it
Every set
The formatting looks like s*** and it becomes obvious that you're trying to pull a fast one
Obviously I'm not saying this is like brainwashing s*** it's just tacky persuasive writing trick
That's being embarrassing
Singly overused
A text but
Nintendo Super
Clear yeah you can you can either be
Using manipulative techniques
Or you can be riding like a first grader
They're very
There is no they can seem similar but they are very different in fact
The first grader for all of the other manipulative tricks
What are you
Another section A little bit later uses this headline
My goal in writing you this letter is not to convince you this is happen
If I wanted to do that
I could write you a letter the length of a book filled with proof
If you don't believe it already even though these Elites have failed to keep their wicked plans
For the third-dimensional control the
Secret...
I wouldn't read the word further this letter
This letter is intended for the person who already knows this to be true
That's you isn't it you understand what's happening at 1st and what's happening
You know why this letter is of so important right
This is just Elementary level persuasive bulshit
Elizabeth sporting three very basic
The first is fake personalization
This is imagined to be Alex writing you this letter which is just nonsense
If only because there's zero chance Alex Rose
This is Jake Ducey writing as Alex I've almost no doubt of that
The second trick is that it's creating the impression that by not putting this letter down
You've somehow proven that you're one of the elect
You understand the reality that others are too
You dumb or stubborn
Accepting the proof of that is a fact
You don't need this letter to prove anything
This is a really common manipulative marketing tool and it works pretty well because
It essentially flatters the reader but the only thing the reader can do to Merit that flattery
Is not walk away from the sale
Well yeah you got a not walk away from
Is the use of questions
You know the reader is prime to answer affirm
Like it's really Bass
Sales trick to get the person that you're trying to sell something with you about something
To answer in the affirmative is to create a connection
Get them saying yes early
Another thing is important to understand is that this isn't just a sales technique it's usually a closing technique
Usually want to create that saying yes as a way of getting
Someone say yes to this ale I spent 10 years in sales and I was told by a lot of
Very shady salesman how to make sales
Be asking these questions unless you know the answer is yet right
When it's like you know that this is important because you're great right
Bet you're a super smart person right you're the smartest person I've ever met
If you pay close attention to how this s*** is written like this copy a large portion of it is
Just
Like used car salesman
Closing techniques
Little bit later we get another
Manipulative sales tax
I'm giving you the globalist entire Playbook
So you can protect yourself from their attack on your freedom your mind your soul...
We're calling it reset Wars
I'm risking my life in my own freedom to share with you the elites
Secrets of how reality actually works
So you could use it to your benefit
Dot-dot-dot
I'm going to review what they're trying to hide so you can
You can see their mind games from a thousand miles away...
And you're going to
To discover exactly how to fight back against the New World Order so you never end up a slave for their evil power...
Reset Wars has the most detailed explanation of what's current
We going on in the world...
I can't tell you
Exactly how deep this goes in this public website cuz they're already got damn prison...
That's so good
Yeah I tried all the way down to that I would throw sit at the wall
Here you have the false impression that the salesperson is risking something by text
You just go to the Omni
Play this is
This is too much even for me but listen I know it's important
To you right
And I'm just such a good person
Such a good person I am willing to take this even a step
Further
And I will throw in
2 bath mat
It's just that exact same thing but being Amplified to life-or-death Stakes for Alex or whoever is writing this
Pretending to be a Leo
Here you see the promise of this dangerous secret information that can't be revealed on a
Public website
For some reason because the writer this is being threatened with prison that doesn't make any sense
This kind of
Classic chest
Not the Creator
Super inflated impression of what's inside the magic
Boxed
It's too dangerous
Steven open
Publix
Also I would assume that it makes more sense to release
That on a public website if you're being risks and there's a risk of being arrested
Go ahead and get that out secretive
No that you need to be arrested or something it don't snatch
I can't tell you anyways though everything now
Manipulative techniques that are way too liberally employed
Thermite to lead you up to the actual cell
We've put together a special offer for anyone reading this letter
The material inside reset Wars is going to be retailing at $297
More in the near future however
For me
We we are having a pre-launch member special at 25% off for a limited time...
Taking the price down to just 222. I can't say no to that's so pathetic
Even further
Quote
Listen
It's as simple as signing up with
Immediately recognizable listen-only as in parentheses a****** after
It's a simple as signing up and you'll get access to the material right away
Here's why you need to take action right now.
Dot-dot
Currently there's an active subpoena out for me
They're trying to take me to court so they can
Completely shut down Infowars along with all my Prada
And possibly even send me to prison
They've already shot me down on all social media platforms
Stop.
I'm even getting death threats every single day from Anonymous numbers
Dot-dot-dot
They're doing everything in their power
Stop me from exposing these evil powers to the world
I truly have no idea what's going to happen
Or if they're going to succeed and shutting me down
And if they do end up getting rid of
Meet... You won't be able to get access
The truth
You won't be able to share this truth with the people you care about
You won't know how to fight back
This is why it's so important that you act
Now before it's too late
This is such a
Amazingly abusive at the things
To do to your audience I have not heard that many ellipses does O'Malley
A****** taught me Emily Dickinson Street you know the places that I would like
You reading text fragment
Translate
Piece of paper is missing
These were standings for like a series of swear words
None of the sacraments that are being a
Express your are real this is all just more sales tricks
Primarily creating the impression that people have to act now or they'll never be able to get
Thing that you're selling
This creates the artificial sense of immediacy where you have to act now it helps override people's rational thought process
Reminder for second
That any of this was
Actually what Alex's position is
Think about what a horrible piece of s***
The traitor to his body
PNC would be
Give this six-hour course that he's created that's the way to defeat the globalist
The enemy is that he's been
Convincing battle with
For over 20 years
Many of these people are probably sacrificed quite a bit to follow Alex whether it's
The respect of their peers or
Money that they spent on keeping him on air so the fight
To continue and Alex
Keep documenting it for that
Goddamn
Custody has been lost over Alex
I'm here is the sales pitch for the course and if you believe this s*** without the course you won't
Be able to if you quote won't know how to fight back
You quote whoop
Be able to access the
This is not an overstatement to say that
Is critically important
Stuff for you to have if you want to save yourself
Go to save your loved ones in the rest of the world
You can even argue that
The key to defeating the globalist is actually this
Information getting out to as many people as possible
Instead of providing this information
Alex with Holt
Advance over $200
Give you access to this information without which of your helpless to fight back
Against the devil
Even though the best-case scenario where Alex actually believes all the complete
Bulshit that's being set on this webpage
He's a monster
To be able to
Ba bestowed life-saving information from him
Thankfully I'm certain that Alex doesn't believe any of this s*** and it's just a cash grab so honestly it's just a standard Infowars bottle of f****** with
With the audience of that monetize
It's
Awful that is
So
F******
Naruto
The idea of
Oh man
Imagine imagine if somebody had
Follow this show for 20 years
We were finally like okay
We're ready to get rid of conservative evil forever
It's behind a paywall
Twenty-something years
My figured out exactly how to get rid of Griffin
I figured out the right-wing scam
And I know the exact solution
If
You are aware of this and you don't understand this
Your dad should already know Adonis
Is there a short. Of time where you're going to be able to get this thing that I've created because
Can take me down
25% off from you in order to
I mean you know what to a certain to a certain point of view though if you're a group of people who believe the
That you are safety and life is dependent upon spending $1,000 on an automatic weapon
It seems like it makes sense to think that you should pay Alex 222 dollars
No it doesn't
Find a gun is buying anything
Cool or whatever
No it's not it's information
This
If this information is good
And it actually is transformative in people's lives
Help a boy more than $200
If he gives it for free
Totally the amount of money he would get
From people just wanting to support him for being that
A generous and that that caring
I would be
IFly
Compared to whatever he's going to be getting to these $200
I guess this desperate cash grab
Yeah it's
It's really sad
You put out something worth something for free people will want to pay what
It's worth and more
Take a lot of people's experiences but I think
Alex's is structuring this
It's very obvious
He has no faith
And the thing that you
Doing he's just banking on people not
Getting mad I mean yeah it's it's
The f****** Ted Anderson gold sales bottle
Of like
As long as I get you to buy the first thing you're obviously not coming
So I just need you to buy one thing and then what other things are going to be going to be another round of course
He offers a 30
EBay money-back guarantee
Globalism 30 days
Think I think
30-day
Money back guarantee
At least you could do I suppose
But I also think there's pretty good reason to believe that most people want
Take advantage of that because
The way that this information
Appears
Tubi
Being presented
The cryptic Miss of it
The vagueness of the nonsense
I think a lot of people will be prime to blame themselves
They don't get the magical transformation that Alex is selling them
I just didn't meditate hard enough or whatever visualize hard enough
You see that a lot in like comment section Moto people who like like Dulce
Who do this Law of Attraction stuffy nose like
I haven't made the money yet but I'ma keep on trying I don't know I'm doing something wrong
I need some advice on how to do this right
And then 30 days
Going to be up your refund there already
In this place of like a
You know
If I admit I was conned on reset Wars
How was I not conned
On info
How can you
How can you be
So f***** over
With this b******* that you spent 232 Suboxone cost
You know so either either you say well I got conned and he's been lying my entire f****** lie
It would be a little threatening to to think
If you if you're in
For this right yeah that's
Oh maybe 911
So another thing that I find really fascinating is the disclaimer they needed to put at the bottom of the page
It reads quote
The contents of this program entitled reset Wars is designed for instructional and educational purposes only
It expresses the views opinions and Analysis of Alex Jones and Alex Jones exclusively
And such
The content is not intended to represent or warrant
The accuracy or truthfulness of any particular statement or any information disseminated.
And accordingly Alex Jones as well as all individuals are ant
To be participating in the production and distribution of recent Wars
Disclaim any and all warranties or representations of any nature whatsoever
Frankly we don't even want to put our f****** names on this s*** now
He's getting all this money taking anyway but it's all Alex and I was also just claims that Halo
By the truth of any of this
What do you think this is been evaluated by the FDA
Beyond that likes the ideas that he's
Saying or like
Get the pieces of evidence he has four things
Like if you were if you were a consumer and you're like hey this is a lie
Algebraic I'd like to point you to the disclaimer where I never claimed
You should know when you bought this that I had a
Had a boilerplate sitting here that said yeah no s*** it's not real fine print where it says come at me
And I will say
Don't care
Joker
It wasn't true in the first place of course it wasn't true why else would I put this f****** decyfer down there
Yeah it's a little sad
Jesus a little sad
We get to the Dilemma that I'm in
It's like a CEO
Commercial for f****** PetSmart is that they're being like
Honestly I don't think this
Is very good program
At all I don't think you should do this
Jordan
I want to
Distill
No
The actual course
Obvious
But
I'm not paying
200 something dollars for it I mean I don't want anybody who's listening to buy it and then give it to me or anything
I don't want this money to go to him do not give him money but I still want to
I don't have any idea what point he's even trying to make with these promos
Reading over the copy it's just
Sales tactics
And like
Audible bad
I listen to that interview with Jake to see when he was on Alex's show and
Nonsense
About MKUltra the Wikipedia
I don't know what it is I'm curious
Most important work ever
I don't know I don't know what to do maybe some archive obsessed infowarrior will put it out on B Tour
Maybe get it from f****** The Pirate Bay
Do you know who knows
Does me
What an Alex
I don't I don't know if some certainly some contradictory ideas about intellectual property
Yeah
Typically
I've had a rule against covering things that are behind a paywall
Make it except
And in this case but
I still like
I'm struggling with this
But I also really want to make clear that I'm not
Struggling in any performative way to try and get an audience
To send it to me don't want that don't know what to do
I think you're right I think eventually it's going to be posted somewhere
It might be it might be a situation where we have a little bit of a delay before
Park
3 attack
Will get there
Somebody's going to put it out
Frankly
There's no way that it's really that sustainable for them to not eventually be like okay well the game is up
We might as well just have it out
Yeah it it may be it may be a situation where you just want to hit people
For whatever it's worth
Upfront
And then and then eventually
Once there a warrant
You. Is over
Absolutely
I think this is a little bit disappointing
I certainly was very disappointed by this
This entire path wanted to know more about what reset Wars was I don't feel like I do
I do know that
I think I think I know exactly what I knew before which is a f******
Hat in the flower is a metaphor for a scam
To Big scab
I don't I don't feel like this
Exploration has gotten us any closer
Truth
It won't be back for another reset Wars they want we know a little bit more
Galaxy
Started his career man put it behind a paywall
As the tip of the spear
Fighting on your behalf
The oncoming murder of the globalist
Just
Unacceptable if you believe any of the premises
If you believe that you're fighting against the literal devil and somehow
Waking up of the population
It has a bearing on whether or not you'll defeat the Devil
The idea that you would have to pay wall is
Absurd absurd and unacceptable
Prohibitively evil yes beyond evil like that scarf
Begging to a new level
I'm fascinated by it like
How you could
Defend that
I don't think you could not put a lot of money into
The course is just sitting at the desk
Look it's just
It's not like he flew across the world to record himself
Basically it's a show with a script that was written by a
How do I will check back in
But there's some big updates
Primarily interested in this cuz this
The show is it is
It's mostly
Vaccine
Conspiracies and then
Apparently he said that whether weapons were involved with the tornadoes
I mean what are you going to do we already talked about it as dumb belief in and whether weapons
That again in this situation
That's Craftsman he's truly he's trying to say whether weapons so people will talk about him saying weather
Weapons that was bulshit
I don't like it
Back with another episode on Friday.
Put our own letter up
We're also on Twitter
We are in 30 technology underscore fight night go to bed Jordan
What the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work