Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Stripe.com
Alex
Joe
Indeed Emerick if you're nasty Ono I'm not
I'm actually
Quite polite
Jordan
What's up
That you go
Okay my bright spot today Dan is I saw this new TV show anime called
Sonny Boy
It is
F****** spectacular
It's so good it's an examination of this
Japanese High School class tickets
Unmoored in space and type right and so allowing that to happen you get a
Wonderful mix of like
Lord of the Flies examination of the dawn of civilization and societies growth in
How should falls apart along with
Emotional messaging. It's so good it just so good it's a great great show
Highly recommended
Cool
What's your birthday
What right spot is their rudeness.
Actually this is
This is tough for me I actually don't know what my bright spot is when know what it is but I don't know what the name of it is
I saw a energy drink
That was at the store
And I got it
Because it looked like an interesting flavor
Sure
It was great
It was a Hawaiian shaved ice flavor
Interesting energy drink with a Hawaiian shaved ice flavored white rice interesting
Just basically like a strawberry watermelon
Tasty
Whatever I don't know if I didn't think I was just advertised so f*** that
Energy drink
Some brand I like it right spot
Absolutely Jordan today we are in the past about July
10th 2003
We noticed there's a little bit of a gap
Between our last episode and July Temps
So here's what
The audio is unlistenable I tried to fiddle with it and get it to a point where it could
Actually be usable but it's just
9th and 8th are
Like its
Outrageous
It's comically bad
This audio but I do listen to a bit of the 8th
And Paul Joseph Watson showed up
He just written his book
Wow that is a while back
They're promoting Paul Joseph Watson book
Yeah
Yeah but he's around
And that's a lot of fun but audio
I'm very excited about this up
Episode
Waiting
Anxiously to be able to talk about this it's so much fun
Say hello to
Newaukee nicely done
This is something that apparently you're supposed
Alright Cooper's long-lost
Also Cowboy Bebop
I will not never
Next
Rainbow pronounce the rainbow thank you so much you're now policy walk
The help
Sexy bath water
I'm a policy wonk
July 10th
Delight 2003
710 03
Not
Be more thrilled that this audio was
Listenable
This wasn't
I would feel
Just so
Deprived
Here's how we start
Neocon
Coming on the broad
Movement
Telling you
Well the Patriot Act
I'm not a liberal
Alex has got a big deal Khan, show
The National Review been reborn with a clone of what's-his-face
Who knows
William F Buckley
Look
We don't know who it is
And Alex won't say
Horse
Yes Alex is going to have a parade of Trojan horses excited about this idea
Leo cons on Lisa's going to he's going to go toe-to-toe with them
Very excited
When you let it in
Was that was the big mistake that was the problem
Yeah it wasn't that there was a trojan horse outside
That was a great place for the horse to meet you want to leave it out there
You defeat the Trojan Horse by leaving it alone
You don't want to parade of Trojan horses that's
A parade worse than regular
Not good
I'll bet you love this idea that I can't say the name
What kind of assholes here's their name in the first hour not here
I might cancel if I heard out
Talking like this
I have one
One of the technicians
The
New World Order
Neocon
Border Police
Probably cancel
Exciting prospect
I'm a slimy creature in front of his audience
That's a little bit combative before it's even begun
Nah.
Continues
Neocom coming out
But there
Their own lies against them
Sure
When I come off at this point I'm just thinking like he's trying to get this person to cancer
This is like please just cancel I am going to disembowel this person because if I act
Actually talk to them I will be disemboweled because I'm full of this is a big fat slimy neocon who I
I've only invited on the show is a trap to destroy them in front of my audience
Demolish it doesn't scream good faith
No
No I was listening to this
Yes yes yes so excited this is going to be fun
Cancel and then Alex is going to be like another cat
What I thought was going to happen
It does not
That is not what happened person shows up
And it's a mess in in Syria
But before we get to that cuz that's in the third
Yes plenty of other meat to get to like
On our last episode going over 2,000
Alex had warned that on the 4th of July there might be a little bit of a Terrace
Well I mean it's a good day for
Until this caller asked
About like a man
What was going on what happened
Yeah I heard you
Play something about you're worried about
Federal Reserve Bankers Lautner
Microfiche
Cutting Loose
July
Nailed it
They're only going to do it when I
Kids are in school
Undisclosed location
I know
You can't open up
The school year now in all if you want to open up the revolution
If there is to not go along with the next school year
That would open up a whole bunch of questions
What would 14 be disgusting
Why was there why
Wasn't there a terrorist attack I didn't say there was going to be there was going to be one
But I didn't I wasn't wrong
It's like misinformation is part of the part of it you know it
Maybe it was just important
Art of War this information is important for both enemies and allies
That's that's
That's kind of the
I like his rejoinder of like
Well obviously there wasn't a terrorist attack they're only going to do it when our kids are in school a dummy
That's an interesting premise
So they're only going to do a giant kids are in school to stop this from happening
Exact
It is it is so fictional it's a little bit like to D&D nerds are like no
No no no
Dragons only attack
Near large mountain it's not going to be around
Yeah and I like that Alex is responsive that seems to be like yeah yeah
So the way to stop
These date of the big one coming
Is not have the kids in school that's why I'm schooling is so popular
Cuz I need to have those kids in school 41 vagina terrorist attack does happen
Alright
What kind of a day did the globalist have when they were like oh no
We were going to do it when all the kids were in school but we took too long now there's so many of them being homeschooled
Are we going to do now
It does like Montessori School Waldorf education
No question there are italics
To clarify
My man
Damn from Illinois is back
He's a good dude calls in every day
Call boy
Two-bedroom still couldn't
It's not about what
Interesting
Documents
Talking about the rebuilding America's defenses document
Document
Hot as it's often because the tag is off you think it's a 1998
Alex is talking about is not a white paper and more you hear him use that term the more you need to ask yourself if you even know what that
This was a 1998 open letter the project for The New American Century sent to then President Clinton
Urging him to pursue regime-change in a rock
The letter begins quote
We're writing you because we are convinced
What's the current American policy toward Iraq is not succeeding
And that we may soon face a threat in the Middle East more serious then we have known since the end of
The Cold War
And your upcoming State of the Union Address you have an opportunity to charity clear and determined course for meeting this threat
We are due to seize that opportunity and to enunciate a new strategy that would
Security interests of the United States and our friends and allies
Around the world
That strategy should aim above alt at the removal of Saddam Hussein's regime from Power
Agree with it or not
Absolutely doesn't seem like it's coming from folks
We're saying that Saddam doesn't pose a threat
No no that one says we got to get rid of
Seems like it
That was a memo from 1998 that was signed onto by Donald Rumsfeld but not Dick Cheney
Heather sionito is a future Trump National Security adviser John Bolton
An apparatchik
A couple months after that letter was that the group followed up with another letter to Newt Gingrich then
Speaker of the House
And Trent Lott the then-senate majority leader
The weather was basically
Clinton to work on getting Saddam out of power but he wasn't biting
They reiterated that it was their belief that policy of containment that it been in place regarding sedov weren't working
And that if left unchecked he posed a very severe threat
Perhaps the worst sense
The Cold War
These are the letters that were written in 1998 that were seen as being addictive of a longstanding desire on the part of the member
The Bush Administration
To topple Saddam governor
It's either the case that Alex is just making up
Things about these documents or he has such a shaky grasp on what they say
But he thinks that they're saying that Saddam isn't a threat and that it's just an opportunity
The resource
Sprite I don't know
No I mean
I guess I guess what are you
Saying is
He's just editorializing that there
They were aware within those letters
That they sent saying we should overthrow
Saddam what was unsaid was that the reason we're doing this because we want that f****** that's an interesting
And if Alex
Secretly they were signaling that would be the claim would be different difference
Then wrote the white papers
Saying that they knew that Saddam was just wanted resources to make a base which is not
What that letter say
It would be a bad idea to write a letter that says
And I'm going to throw this out
Because it could be obtained by
I will in the future
Yeah
I wouldn't put that in writing
Illinois
This caller asked about like
You know we talked about tearing a lot but what about the tyranny of the early part of our country
How do you feel about that
Okay
Tyranny
Express store
Mi flavor
I was just interesting thoughts
I am not surprised
Four score
No one
What happened to the America
LeBrons
I'm a cute view of history but it's so detached from reality I can't really believe that this is an expression of like idealism or no
Naivete
Seems like rationalizing
Prettiest do it it's fine that they were slaves because if they didn't want to be slaves
The idea that no one can take your rights is so dumb that it barely has a meaning in the real world
If u.s. history teaches us one thing it so you can totally have your rights deprived from you
You may still have those rights in an abstract
Accents like you deserve those right
B but in terms of actual concrete reality
If the US says you can't vote you don't have the right to vote
No in the United States
The angle that seems like a cop-out but that has nothing to do with the absurdity of this position that he's like well maybe
Maybe the right
The protection of Rights weren't enforced or direct
Native Americans are Black America
What does it mean to not have
Protection of Rights directed at you
It feels like it means like you don't have those right
I think what he's trying to say is that
The founding fathers were like
Itching at the bit to
To give everybody right right
But because
Black people and Native Americans at that time
Didn't ask
The founding fathers for those rides didn't say anything they were just
Hey I'm loving this genocide over here you guys keep it coming
Yeah what do you say that their protection over the enforcement of right
It's worth directed at these people it seems like you just trying really hard to not say that the US had laws on the books
Depriving people of specific rights
Based on their race or gender
The stupidest part of this club is that Alex's pretending that he thinks that groups like Native Americans are black Americans needed to stand up
Send Amanda god-given right
Dumb because the way you saying that you really have to think of you'd be right there on their side supporting campaign for equal
America
That's not true
He stated his opposition to the Civil Rights Act in the past
Because among other thing
Things he feels that requiring businesses to serve people of all Races
Could be a violation of their right of free association
Further his Heroes and intellectual Traditions his worldview grows out of
They fought tooth-and-nail against the Civil Rights Act in the voting
His favorite author Gary Allen wrote the book Communist Revolution in the streets Bertrand caused by black Americans for equal
Right as the result of a nefarious communist conspiracy
Alex doesn't believe any of the things he's saying just called he just knows that
And I believe it otherwise is
Bad luck
Yeah you can't really say that and then if somebody was like hey
What about that time America made it illegal to be Chinese here you can't be like all that was too far away
Chinese-americans just didn't stand up
Everybody David you got to ask for what you need otherwise you're going to let white people just run all over
Not be excluded
It was a terrible idea you got to send a letter for
True
So Alex get another caller in this guy has an interesting idea about how to promote Alec
Next to the masses
Make it illegal to be Chinese here no idea would not work well
I really hope
Your staff
Get your
Comedy Central
Daily Show
Jon Stewart
New World Order
Mineral water
The color is saying hey you should go on The Daily Show
Response to that is hey you know what Gary Busey likes me
Okay
He is a show that was on Comedy Central
Tissue their butt
I forgot about I'm with Busey
Easy to forget I will only ever I live a Charmed
My Busey began
Ended
Point Break
She and I never have to worry about another what about baseball movie
Plenty of that baseball
Rookie of the Year NBA Rookie of the Year in Rookie of the Year
All-time great reveals that the glove was actually his mom
Time to play softball
Celebrity Rehab
I don't remember that one how did he do did he get rehab
Seem to not think he had a problem
Which is not surprising good place to start if I recall correctly he thought
He was he was acting like he thought he was there to be a counselor
I like that yeah I like that
Dr. true
True
Just needed an assistant man yeah so I got called in to be like
I do think I would I would I be
See how Jon Stewart would try to handle a lie
Interesting meeting of the minds
That didn't happen
So are you ready to find out who the big fat slimy neocon is it will Crystal
It is not
Is it Newt Gingrich it's not
Not Tucker Carlson although he would have been someone that I would call that
Nope
We're behind
Damn answer it's an Coulter
So he is going to tell me
That Ann Coulter
Supported McCarthy
And that that is a bad thing he's he wants to know if she supports McCarthy enough
Subway supporting McCarthy Isley like that's the Trojan Horse aspect of it
Yes see other stuff like they believe in The Patriot Act and neoconservative is a all this stuff yeah
Without that she really believes but she tricks you into liking her what with her support of McCarthy episode Alex is going
I thought a lot of people really got trick by Ann Coulter support of MacArthur
Mickey she's so clever like that
I can't believe she got away with it for so long
So at this point 2003 and Coulter just released her book titled treason liberal treachery from the Cold War 2
To the war on terrorism
Around this time culture was at the peak of her powers as a media troll
Who just saying things then get people mad at her to facilitate a cycle of attempt
It works really well back then far more so than now
The book treason was in large part about how culture felt that McCarthyism was something that was created by the Liberals imagine
McCarthy was in fact
And did a great job of rounding up communist spies
Like we have all of his words though they liked wrote them down
Evie got this stuff isn't true but a big part of the show the show that we do here is humoring ideas
So I decided
Let's do it I read a number of interviews that she gave around this time and
The thing that she seems to point to as our primary evidence that McCarthy was right is the 1995 release of the venona intercept
Peter translated cables that have been captured by us intelligence in like 19
M40
The venona intercepts are actually very fascinating and they paint a picture about the scope of Soviet intelligence projects during the Cold War
There's something
Definitely could be used to demonstrate
Instant that Julius and Ethel Rosenberg
In fact Soviet spy
Yes that was true I found that out whenever I read about
Interceptor do definitely back
There definitely was some indication that there were few people within government who were Cooperative with the Soviet Union and providing
With information
That is all
Assessment
Go so far as to prove Joseph
McCarthy to be on the up-and-up is not supported by the information
McCarthy was a raving lunatic with a penchant for public
Do a lot of the fervor round to Auntie communist witch-hunt in there. They're so sweet at the house on American Activities Committee
McCarthy himself presided over the Senate permanent subcommittee on investigations
Would you use to grandstand against the ledge
Communist
In the transcript of his hearings between 1953 and 1950 for all of Vail Ebola
Great picture of the man
View transcripts probably weren't available to Ann Coulter at the time of the writing of the book though since they were only made public in
This book is probably written
The most Spotify
That being said even for 2003 there's plenty of public information that would lead someone to assess McCarthy is being an idiot.
Piece of s***
It's once imagined he was just trying to find out the Communist spies in the government
But you have to recognise he was also doing stuff like the following
Quote
The state Department's International Information agency operated several overseas libraries that were freely available to citizens
The host countries
McCarthy declared them to be Soviet tools because there were books
Show me libraries author by Communists in their quote fellow Travelers
He harassed the library so fiercely as communist propagating tools that some of the library's actually burn the book
Books written by authors McCarthy deep to be subversive
At no point in time
At no point in time are we going to get a hundred percent of people saying
Burning books is a dumb idea
We just never going to get there
You can you can get most people on board January
So we've got into McCarthy a bit in the past I don't want to go to
Too far down that road again but
I just really interested when I heard Alex say that he was wanting to give Ann Coulter some kind of the McCarthy purity test
Signature defended him based on the venona intercepts just going to let down a weird Road of looking into this Alexia Nicole
Does actually does backup sump
I'm stopping at like there were right there word Soviet
Spies going to surprise me and be like I'm going to give her a litmus test on McCarthy did you like blood
Meridian mulatto like that kind of dough
A lot of stuff doesn't even come up in Alex's interview which is like 50 top
Yeah but it's just weird that citing the Winona intercept is a fairly solid way to argue that there were so
Soviet spies running around in the cold war. I've literally never heard Alex bring them up
That is weird looking into a culture in her arguments in favor of McCarthy are the first time
That they have ever come up
In any of the things on the Shelf
Offended
It is
Maybe that's why I
Can't have it
Yeah but I think it also is evidence that
Has a finite point
Utility
Like you can't use it to argue
Like he likes to that
McCarthy
Found that the globalist we're running
Or whatever
Those are things you really need evidence for cuz they're you know you're not going to have that at
Yeah things like there's no Nature Center like those are real they exist
And they get you
This far
Router
No I didn't say almost by Omission make McCarthy look like an even more insane person
Considering
Haters can't work
We get to
Bringing a Coulter in
At this is a meeting of the minds my friend
I thought you was going to destroy this seems pretty
Very collegial starting off who's polite
Kind of fun
I mean easy breezy
Oh you know the twin the Trojan Horse came in they had a nice party that's the same thing
Before we destroy it
Maybe maybe
Who knows
About
By the sea
But it's the shows so above the left-right paradigm
Anyways I love you too
It just seemed a bit more friendly than I expected I
Kind of felt like oh okay Alex was talkin big hoping the person would
We wouldn't have to do the interview but it's happening
There's a big star at this point she's got a lot of pull that yeah he can grab onto if she likes him
What was going to happen
I was wrong This falls apart really hard
It starts out even like
You're just being a kiss ass
Sycophantic
But pretty quick
Alex S2
You know clear-the-air
Look
Lady
Oberon Paul type of
Time to get this I need you to know this upfront
Conservative black
Confirmative
Respond
Borders
Whatever
Don't want
I Hold On
Soccer moms out there
But but
Wow
So I mean it's mildly confrontational but I think is a little spicier
Comment that the president can only really do 23 like three things
Best kind of telling
If she's trying to make excuses for Bush by saying you shouldn't be judged
Except for based on the three issues he's decided to focus on
Shouldn't she have the same latitude that for any politician any Democrat president
And the biggest issue could be let's a reducing regulation but that wasn't one of the three issues that Obama decided to focus on
Shouldn't she have the same kind of what can you do attitude towards it
Because a pretty transparent dodging of the question I'm pretty glad that Alex just didn't let it stand
Do you know like that
Of course Alex's objection to her answer isn't going to be anything close to where I'm coming from
But at least he's not giving up on it entirely
You know there is yeah yeah more like hold on
No that's that's some bulshit
President
When you elect somebody to run a several trillion-dollar Enterprise per year called the America
Government
What you want to make sure they can only do is focus on three out of
The 10 million possible things going on at any given point
To what she saying in terms of being a public advocate
About
Every political capital is one of the ways
There are only three things that he can focus on your Administration if you're good at delegating thing
Can have other priorities that you're working towards a senior State Department
Is invested in X Y and Z sure your department of the Interior is doing all this stuff your education
Departments
Like there is a lot that the president could delegate but yeah I guess I wouldn't say they can only spoke
Focus on three things
But in terms of what you can publicly really
Make
Awareness towards maybe three maybe four
There is a limited amount of time that a president has
Advocate publicly for thing
And I do think that she makes a fine point that it is up to
You know the conservative
Folk in America just to convince
Their fellow voters
To go along with this shirt like whatever they think is
Platform people should be going toward true
True but
Is one of the stunning aspects of American politics indirectly politics in general
Ace how often presidents are insisting
Insistent
That the buck does not stop their solutely not it's not my fault I've only ridden I've only got
Only focus on three things at the
You know I got this going on I got that going on
You don't have to hold me responsible for all the stuff I delegate you know that kind of
Anything and that's kind of what
Hearing again and again in a
Yeah
Yeah it's
I take issue with
The point that she's making
A different
Version of the point cheese-making I think I could see where it was
Yes but he was Alex's abject
What is oppa
Borders
Apartment
Oh no
YouTube grifters can't be asking to Define terms
Kryptonite is definition
Does open borders make
What do any of our buzzwords mean also
Alex's objection seems to be like
Things that bush didn't
End up doing
Okay
Well he's afraid of
Which don't happen the left-right Paradigm in above the left-right Paradigm you don't have to worry about all the reality that
Set the left-right Paradigm deals with
Above the left right there. I'm you're just worried that everyone isn't going to be as extreme right as you want the right
You're just looking at it we are gremlins all over the place
Instinct was right
Alex's
Does not want to have
To Define things
Funny fails
Borders
Service Pro
Bushisms
Doing everything
I think I clip is super revealing
The first thing you see is that Alex can't Define what you mean by open borders and any sensible
Already here is not the equivalent of open
Running the borders
The only other thing he could even come up with
Was the bush supported the Pan-American Union
None of this amounts to open borders and I
Alex is going to need to
Define what do you mean by panamerican Union
Because that definitely is
Existed for a long time
In 1889 the first International Conference of the America
Can States was held in d.c.
This was quota for the purpose of discussing and recommending for adoption to their respective governments some plan of arbiter
Operation for the settlement of disagreements and disputes that may
Hereafter arise between them
A considering questions relating to the Improvement of business
Intercourse
It means of direct communication
Between said countries
And to encourage sup such reciprocal commercial relations
As will be beneficial to all
Insecure more expensive markets
Through the product of each that Nation
If Alice is going to be mad about anybody at this over the stove you should take it up with Benjamin Harrison
Yeah that guy was a real dick
Out of this conference the international Union of American Republic was founded which would go on to be named the Panama
Union became the organization of America
Can States
I wasn't worried about a Pan American Unity just worried that bush is going to let more non-white people into the country
But even so here's a terrible grass by being able to
Depends what is really strong accusation
Bush Sports open border
On some level Alex knows that he can't backup that Hyperbole and an is called him out on it to Define his terms
Without admitting the bush
Isn't actually in favor of open borders as he wants the audience to understand the term right
Spam
Alex doesn't really have good information to go on here
Only can throw out is that the NRA put out an alert that they think bush is going to band
Assault weapons
Really weak
It's interesting how I am can see the point because I think she gets the sense that it's not even worth arguing
So she retreats to be very reasonable point that a president can only do so much and
I have to consider getting re-elected
I think here we can see a fundamental
Princeton House someone like and Coulter it someone like Alex Jones
Understands power
And Leadership
The president is part of a process
You're picking up where your predecessor left off and you're going
Going to leave the next president the circle
Stances that your term ends in
You can do a lot but ultimately you can alienate the voters who determine whether you'll stay in office
You have to make concessions and recognize that imperfect compromises might need to be struck
Someone like Alex doesn't b l that way
He really does ascribe to a strongman dictator molding
In terms of people he likes
Want to be in charge
Common
With a set of Educators to Alex's social and political preferences
Place whatever whether or not most people wanted
We saw this play out with trumpet even back at this point is supporter Ron Paul is a lot of similarities
Because he's never been president we don't know if you'd actually follow through with it but Alex has every reason to think that the day Ron Paul
Got into office
He unilaterally withdraw from the UN
He get rid of pretty much every social welfare program shutdown OSHA and eliminate all four and eight
Fantasy what Ron Paul for him we never had to test the theory of whether or not he would do it
And on the other hand has had experiences in the actual political world
And she's a politician Street supported
Become president
Because she's very close to the actual working
The politics doesn't have the same delusional idealism that Alex had 2003
And I'd still had about Rob
Although he's threatening that
Discount this one's have 20 more times
Any number of times now is going to be the last drop
I'm not certain that means much but I really feel like this difference came through in the
This chunk of their conversation
Alex says this delusional expectation that bush do things that he's not
Doing already
Where is pragmatism towards the political process
At this point I was like she's going to win
Oh really
This is not good
It does not appear to be going well for Alex
Right out of the
It does not seem like he's going to eviscerate her in front of the audience in order to dance upon her bone
For him this would be a point where I'm starting to walk back my position
Get real polite again
Get real polite again you know what let's talk more about your book
Talk let's talk extensive amazing let's talk about how great
Give me serve you
Making a point that I actually think it's a really good and insightful about Alex
Funny conservative
The problem with this is
Build
How to never agree with it but I think
And is fairly right and accusing Alex of insisting that bush do everything for him
In the past I wouldn't have looked at it this way necessarily because I'm anyways
Alex is doing something that could be described as politically active the way that I like
Political beliefs
Do the line was suggesting people do
Is there too because Alison show is basically just complaining about how Bush isn't doing everything that he wants them
To do there's a passing of the Bucking Alex's politics because
He believes that things get done by strong singular leaders as opposed to the result of
Collective action
Miscellaneous financial interest
Sometimes coincidences
Bush signing the assault weapons ban which he didn't do wouldn't be the result of a ton of influences like millions of people elect
Members of Congress
Who would pass legislation for Bush to sign in the first place horse special interest groups lobbying for or against the bill
It would just be a matter of bush doing this to us because he's bad
If boys were good then the millions of Voters of the majorities in Congress of the lobbying groups they wouldn't matter
He would just do whatever Alex believe it was right even if
So my problem
Ridiculous political conflict
Possibly torpedoing his own career
Is enticing to think of Alex's habit of looking at his favorite politicians is an all-powerful daddy like it
It started with Trump
I don't know I don't like
The future is probably there a little bit to consist
Yeah that is a that I mean to a certain
Okay
If he if that's a function really of his same show though even in his
In his f
With his show
He is consistently telling his audience
You don't have to do any
You give me the money so I can do stuff
So in essence his political ideology is well I'm not
The politician
So my job is to
Support whomever
For them to do it for me in the same way that my listeners give me money
So I can do both
So it seems like an almost
121 explanation for how he
He thinks everything operates sure
They're also there also seems to be like
I guess the idea would be
To use the political organizing of Alex's show like there's enough listeners
And if they vote
Weekend
Vote for the person who will do everything we want them to do right
Play idealistic in a wave it like
I guess I
I don't dress nearly enough
We could we could theoretically vote for somebody who wanted Universal Health Care
But apparently we won't
The goal is
How to convince people to vote
For people who would
So I'm Alex
Brings up a a bill that bush didn't beat out
Just a little bit confused
Barbara Boxer
Now
Because
Alex is almost going to sell
A wrench so big was thrown into his brain he's now agreeing with her too.
Defeat himself
Yeah so he realizes that he's made a point really well
Neymar
Look I do in my butt
Advising your audio
We need to persuade
This is what
Real dickish
A mascot
And the reason that you the mascot is cuz she's an intelligent conservative woman I was going to say that what he just told her is
Is that your are token intelligent woman and obviously when we do have power if it's cuz it's
Consolidated
You will not be involved
Are you willing to be involved is Alaska
Rivoli excuse me
I would like you to verify real quick
The only thing the far-right cares about is your gender
Because you're not saying anything new baby that's pretty much
Deserves that kind of thing from Alex
From Alex
Snow
Alex keep bringing up like
Why is Budweiser weapons ban
Yeah yeah
Only able to do so much
I can only answer this question the same way so many times we have you can bring up other examples
Anime answer will be the same
What about that time that he went to that bar with a buddy who wasn't a friend of mine that guy was a real a****** is he an ass-whole
Alright dammit starting to get a little bit annoyed
You're not saying this
I don't agree with what she's saying but like in terms of
How she's responding
Alright
One question of
Over and over again
Totally clear and even
Barely polite with Alex being kind of a dick calling her cuz she's intelligent
Again I hate Ann Coulter but in conversation with Alex she comes off like a less of an a****** interpersonally
I'm more of a person who actually knows how to convey her point
I want to talk for a second about UNESCO though
The organization was founded in 1946 in the United States was a founding member
1984 during the Reagan Administration the US withdrew from UNESCO and it's historically fairly open
Question about whether or not that was inappropriate
There were some complaints
Mismanagement by the event director
General Tso
It might not have been a totally frivolous decision
But either way in 1995 we've seen a change in leadership UNESCO
And A Renewed interest
In rejoining
President Clinton
Indicated that he wanted to rejoin at this point but he was limited in his ability
Did you so by budgetary
Constraints
As he left office you requested that bush rejoin
Which he did
In late 2003
It's true that Bush was inclined to rejoin but he honestly couldn't have done it on his own unilaterally
In order to join
Funding had to be appropriate
Which was done by an act of Congress
It wasn't the active one person because the action needed to be
The action needed other things
Had to make it happen there were multiple parts
There's like more than one branch of government
And it goes through
Actually a bit of a bummer
Ron Paul tried to get the us out of it every year he was in the house and each time it went nowhere
Then in 2011 UNESCO allowed Palestine and is a member state
And that was a huge problem for the United States
We just decided to stop paying Nesco
And in 2013 they stripped the United States of voting rights
Madden 2017 drop State Department announced again
Billion dollars
Unpaid dues
Ivan
Great
Great school great roommate for the rest of the world I think we're best bros
Wait what am I big Point here is that bush signing onto UNESCO isn't some kind of a single event that happened
The tireli motivated by Bush himself
It's a piece of a larger picture that Alex just doesn't
Pandelis just refuses to deal with it
Yeah and it's a really depressing picture
You know it's a really dumb picture that it's entirely possible that Nancy Reagan's astrologist told
Ronald f******
I got
Soup for brains that we should get right out of UNESCO and that's all that you needed to do
Total fairness
The arguments in that point in the 80s
For getting out more sensible
Is that a lot of other decision Shore
But yeah it's this point
Starting to get a little bit like
I don't do that
I guess you just like
Realizing where she is
Yeah it's kind of like this isn't good I thought it was going to be promoting my book
She had no idea who Alex
Yeah it pretty clear
It's very obvious that she really thought this was going to be a boilerplate radio appearances like that
A radio person about her book
Safe is the safest possible thing for Ann Coulter to do
Society
She's annoyed
We can get in the morning
And okay I'm
I am not going to say that I don't appreciate too monstrous children
Bickering what you like about Coulter
She has a whip
She has an ability to
Speak extemporaneously it away they can sometimes
Chief position of
Professional troll
With
The talent to become a professional douchebag
Yeah you know used against Alex
It's often said a little
I just
It does make you feel like maybe there's a certain time to tap into being a dick
Maybe when the time is right you should have the powers of douchebag under your belt
Joinder of like
I've never seen her this mad at liberals I'm just bored
You're not going to break through
At the dinner table so are we get to the Patriot Act 2
After this
Just doesn't
Give a s***
The police
I mean
Let me get it for you
Love it
Electric razor
No no I don't
The earlier the interview when there were the discussion about parts of the Patriot Act and said that she hadn't read this so I can actually totally
We see how Alex would have interpreted that as her saying that she hadn't read it at all
Kind of wood it would be a fair reading of what
He said right
It is really fun. What you clarified
That she hadn't read what he's talking about
It also doesn't care
We talked about this a bit the past but there was no Patriot Act 2
The bill that Alex is referring to as Patriot Act to didn't
Also there's no section 501 in s22 descended bill
The first section is 1101 so this citation that he's throwing out just isn't good
I understand that this is a proposed bill and I did and it wasn't cool
When was a bit scary
But it's really counterproductive for Alex to embellish it about it
In order to take a shortcut
How to get in the audience of Esther
It didn't pass
It doesn't allow the stuff Alex is claiming it does
By this point July it's been six months and to any action has been taken on the bill
It was introduced
The newest Center committee is essentially a dead bill at this point in July
To know that
So now we go to call
Alex realize like I'm not getting anywhere here
Sniping at me cuz it's no good
Who are Bella
Oh yes Alex how you doing
Cheyenne
I can't help the drawing
Analogy
Play some business and
Something something so I go to a
Clerk or salesperson
And I walk away
Disparagement
Sometimes no more than they do
To be the case here without
Hawks versus you
Are you right
Well
I don't think
Ardent
I disagree
Well I know but maybe
These These are issues that you talked about evidently
Ma'am ma'am you aren't support my president
Colors of real assholes
Yeah back and forth of it is no good but it's pointing the episode like
Alex maybe was starting to win me back a little bit
Enos is starting to show through a little more
Supporting award not being concerned about possible rights violations and what have you
Melo grant that I don't believe Alex is principles actually sincere here
There plenty of instances of potentially rights violating things the Trump proposal to put into place by executive order now it's at no
Problem with them
Even if someone I don't fully trust the sincerity of I still find his position here more palatable and responsible than an
Not caring about the violations of right
You didn't know I was on that
I I dunno I strongly disagree with
I think the way that Alex is interacting with his like
She's on the phone another person's on the phone with the two of them are teaming up against
The guest
I think it's probably poor for that
F*** it was it's like a Sports Talk Show
Really sounding like is somebody calling into the
God dammit strength
Coach for the Philadelphia Eagles and being hot
Why didn't you run the 45 at the
Another thing that I think is also in terms of
I like the Alex's Leanne thing
What where I kind of side more with Alex
Is that Anna's very clear that she supports the war on terror
Course
Support the so-called
Ministration
Terrorism correct
Okay well
If that's the case
Very critical
Equation
But you don't seem to know any
Civil rights
Violate
That is absurd
The Hue even fell for the sleight-of-hand metallic
Text Deb there
The problem with this conversation and how it's
Been carried out is very
Clear here
These two people are talking about things so in precisely that a pretty decent argument could be made that they're both right and they're also
Both correct in saying the other is wrong
Up to this point the discussion has been about the Patriot Act and Patriot Act entirely around the notion of the in French
Bank of American citizens
Right
She's looking for an example of a citizen of the United States
Have you been cheese clearing her question that she's talked about the violation of civil rights
Alex follows this up by saying that US citizens were taken to Camp x-ray which continues the theme of discussing US citizens
Avenger
Torture at Bagram International facility
Which really complicates things
It's because now the conversation is incoherent
Has every reason to think they're still talking about US citizens and their rights possibly being
So she's absolutely correct that the US didn't torture any us
Citizens death of Bagram
Simultaneously Alex is so used to Jumping all over the place and not staying on topic that he probably doesn't even realize that
He's now shifted over to talk about non US citizens in a discussion about civil rights
Excuse correct
In December 2002 our soldiers killed to citizens of Afghanistan
And they had been tortured
Both Alex and and will probably leave
Completely insane it wrong
And now it'll take this as proof that she's a liar who reject proven real
But it's actually just a case of people not being precise with what they're talking about and ultimately
And this Pacific exchange Alex's
Far more guilty of making
This conversation nonsensical
It's hard to tell if that's a debate strategy or his mind just doesn't have the normal guardrails that most people have
But either way the result is the same
Also Camp x-ray is a part of Guantanamo Bay
Yaser Hamdi was captured in Afghanistan and declared
An enemy combatant
He was raised in Saudi Arabia but I was born in Louisiana so the government claim
They when they held him at Camp x-ray they didn't know that he was a US citizen
Once it was known that he was a citizen he was sent to a jail in the United
According to findings in the Supreme Court opinion of a case against Donald Rumsfeld
You've taken to Guantanamo in
In January 2000
M2M clear that he was a citizen in April 2000
He was sent to Norfolk Virginia
According to the information that they have
They didn't know he was a citizenship they did find out
Who did not allow him to be held at Camp X right whatever you want
To be clear
I don't think that any of this is okay
It's just not relevant to the point Alex is trying to make
I would say I'm opposed to people being taken to Guantanamo US citizen or not and that I don't think
That this case is a anyway indicates a desire on the part of our government to put
Uso de something camp
Or establish that press
Nonsensical argument there having
Is meaningless
Point here is that because
Alex has such incompatible communication
It's almost impossible for them to actually have a conversation that means anything
And this, this is really Illustrated
Think about two different thing but notice
Notice how you responded
To their nonsensical incoherent conversation
You prioritized
The fact that people were tortured
Because that is a more important issue it realistically speaking
You
Cited with Alex you were responding to an Coulter saying that no one will
Was tortured to death
I have like
She's wrong Ono I was responding to Ann Coulter saying
Find me someone whose civil rights were violated because in my head it's like well listen
That doesn't prove anything towards any
But in America if you want to find somebody who's civil rights
You can find but any examples that message meant specifically as a result of the
Or not you could produce that
Person
Alex can't know absolutely not
Yeah yeah it's just a bit it's just so stupid
It's just that was weird being just like
What are we doing
Why are you asking me for an example of what you would think
It's stupid but it's also the game that Alex's play
He's making a claim he's not used to people challenging his client
His claim is challenged
You can't offend
Can't back it up at all
That's fast
Second
I don't believe you at all
I think Vick
You did not see the sleight-of-hand
From US citizen
Do people being tortured
I think it's really easy to mess
If you're not paying attention
You could
You could very easily or
Get that inside when he sang two people were tortured
You could be like you'd forget
The conversation was centered around USA
Right now and I understand that that is an important thing for a conversation that is trying to go somewhere
Is to maintain a like
If we're talking about US citizens citizens
Then we can only have a point
If we're both talk
Question I asked you was based on
Think about
Other people who wrote USA what are we doing
It's a pointless conversation yeah but I just don't care about US citizens versus
Nan says I think that's
It's ridiculous I am 100% for open borders I think I think I think I think I was trying to
But I don't care about the distinction
But yeah it's it's
Just interesting to me to see the
Half
That this goes
And how from an external
Really looking at it you can see all right here's where this
Is going off track
And neither of them really wrecked
You guys like the other one
Except am kind of does a little bit later
This point in the conversation they just are butting heads about
Completely
You're having different conversations with each other it does feel like Alex is
Trying to find a weak point and if he can find a weak point
Then he's going to hammer it home and never speak about anything else again so we're just getting a lot of like
Little pokes here in there
A man tries to stay on topic because I think
She's too smart enough to recognize like
What are we
What are we what are we talkin
Alright bye
Aggron
Civil rights
University
Used it for
Civil rights being violated
America
So where you see her such a great example of how Alex can answer any questions or dig deeper into
Any of these narratives
Talking point
Even at this point in his career even in 2003
Example of someone who violated because of the Patriot Act and he's capable of coming up with a single
Example
Whether or not there are people who fit that description if Alex can come up with something the defense is playing he's lost the point
In terms of conversation and his
No reason to take seriously his claim
No one is ever really challenged him on this point before especially on the show so Alex's unprepared to do anything other than what
Always does on the show we just about all over the
The conversation of civil rights Wings to the use of torture against foreign combat
What's an realizes at the switches
He tries to get back on track and remind Alex if they're talking about USA
Citizens civil rights
I was trying to bring up various country citizens being designated as enemy combatants which again
Agree with it or not and is a perfectly sensible response do in there
Boat the enemy is a wartime cry
My point is not about which side here I agree
It's about who's actually making sense
So try to stick to the point
And that person is undoubtedly and Coulter unfortunate
Unfortunately unfortunate
If the use of torture against for a combatant is disgusting and should never be acceptable but it doesn't intersect with the Civil Rights concerns that
Alex is breaking up
So it's really irrelevant to the conversation
Countries being designated enemy combatants also doesn't really have anything to do with
Point but
The notion that US citizens are being taken to
Partiallyroyal
There's only one example that could possibly possibly have about this which is Yasir Humpty who at this point
Already been transferred to a US prison once it was known he was acidic
At this point the only other citizen who had been declared an enemy combatant was Jose Padilla
Who is sentenced or planning to manufacture a radiological bomb
And held at a military prison in South Carolina
Both of these instances are interesting and concerned to civil liberties organizations but neither of them
Possible by the Patriot Act
This really has much more to do with the authorization for use of military force which was signed
On September 18th 2001 which itself was highly reliant on a 1942 Supreme Court ruling
Ex parte quirin
Regarding the use of military tribunals
48 captured German saboteurs
Instead of dealing with some of these subtleties Alex just point the finger at the Patriot Act because
That's easy to hang your hat on
Shorthand
Hey big post Ricky
Give him some kind of a credibility in this
Left Right right-wing civil libertarian liberties
Strictly speaking though and is still right
And if you want to take issue with the designation of people as enemy combatants
That essentially requires
Fundamental opposition to the way that
Mozart Opera
Alex doesn't want to deal with it
Tattoo instead he jumps to another one of his preloaded talking points
About what it
Support.
It wasn't talking about
Supporting the troops are not that I was responding to
Because he has a pre-scripted rant about how he's the one who supports the troops
By throwing that out we can pretend I'm some kind of a moral High Ground
Resume incredibly pointless conversation they're having analysis
Is losing
Losing
Yeah the point where she said then you then do
Fundamentally disagree with how the US military works then the the answer you have sugar
Then you can continue a conversation if you say no I still want them to do everything and I support
The troops then you're then what thinset stop talking
Shifting of the conversation in order to
Score Point absolutely
Another caller
These callers
Fitness culture
Please
Kakaboka morality
A president that has
Bohemian Grove
Oh yeah
Men get dressed up in
Songs
Human sacrifices
George Bush
Functions with
Whatever goes on that the Grove the sources that Alex aside until backup
Who's playing the gay sex workers are carted into work
Work for the group member
There's no women around and articles Alex references do discuss
Including but not limited to Men playing women very lewdly and States perform its is
And the audience hooting and hollering
The stories that Alex's referencing do discussed prostitution but the story
Doesn't match what he say
Essentially there is a nearby City to the Bohemian Grove called mate Rio
And there's a bar there that was Notorious for being a place where Bohemian club members
Could slip away at night
Order sex
According to a 1975 book by G William demoff
This is what the group members referred to as a river jump
This Washington Times article that Alex is referring to is from 1989 and it doesn't actually have to do with Bohemian Grove at all
It has to do with the
The fear that the Soviet Union was using male sex workers to ensnare politician
Not great
Quote we have known for many many years that there is a department of the KGB whose job it is to pray on sexual.
Etc retired lieutenant general Daniel Graham
Former head of the defense intelligence
Agency
Because closeted homosexuals in government service can easily be turned through blackmail for Espionage purposes
General G
We have we have always an intelligence tried very hard not to be giving classified information to known homosexual
Play could have gone the other direction you know you could have just been like it's okay to be gay
That's interesting
Totally cool source that is
In 2004 which is after this episode
Prisonplanet reposted a New York Post article about how there was a forward a pornstar name
Who worked as a valet at The Grove
Which is meant to imply that I guess he was also a sex worker powerful that that
And definitely not substantiate by the reporting
The Grove spokesperson Sam singer said quote
The club doesn't care about his past
Totally possible video someone who worked in the service industry and also in pornos
It's not like sex work always pays everyone's bills people also something inside have a second Revenue stream
What I can find no evidence to the claim that Alex is making
Might be able to win $10,000 here to take Alex up on it
An interesting Lee if you do try to find claims of like
Gay prostitutes being taken into Bohemian Grove so many other sources just linked back to Alex
Of course
How to really tough to try and find like where is this coming from if not from an Infowars article
I do think
That it is enjoyable to see a
Theoretically conservative luminary
Being peppered with the questions of people who actually follow them
And what's gray and will become a problem for them. Bye
It's always great whenever you have somebody who's like a screeching talking head on TV actually confronted with what they
They created and meet your demise years from now these people
And Israel was like oh my God I can't believe I'm talking
Do you weird us
It's in the title of your new girl car
To divert attention
Prescott Bush
Criminal
Farming
During World War II
Divert attention
A batch
Service cleaners
Fingers Valley British Empire
Fascination Ronald Reagan Iran-Contra.
Leave
New York
Are you sure
I'm saying this is
I'm concentrating
Helicopter
Chronicle
Warner
So I kind of feel like a pretty well I would definitely listen to take
Altogether be so much fun as punishment for both of them as long as proceeds from the show went to a charity
They're both of them didn't
Support yes they can't have anything to do with the money
Prescott Bush was not criminally convicted like this colors and like Alex's thing
Use on the board of a couple of companies that did business with a man named Fritz place in
I wasn't industrialist in Germany has been a member of the Nazi party
Business with license
Totally not illegal until the end of 1941 when the US entered World War 2
Since we were technically neuter
In 1942 the assets of these companies overseas
They seem to have had a falling-out with Hitler
Was no longer support of the Nazi party
In fact
Tyson had supported the rise of Hitler and the Nazis financially and material
Had a strong break
In 1939 when Germany decided to invade Poland
Oh
I thought it was like Hitler slept with his girlfriend letters were published in life
Show me article quote
In publishing the paper is leading to my break with Adolf Hitler I wish to show that the German nation which elected Hitler it's
Leader because of his professed opposition
Communism
Is innocent in the developments that turn national socialism into its opposite
It is letters you pretty
Clearly opposed to the mistreatment of Jewish
When in on November 9th 1938 the Jews were robbed and tortured in the most cowardly and most brutal
Manor and their synagogues destroyed all over Germany
I protested once more
As an outward expression of my repugnance
I resigned my position of State counselor
All my protests
The pain no reply and no remedy
Essentially it's a pretty messy
Materially this guy and by extension the US folks like Prescott Bush who did
Businesses on the rise of the Nazi party
At the same
Time looking at their precise actions and what they did
Kind of different than if you were to look at someone like Henry Ford
You don't care
Sure
Sure all these people in a certain amount of historical blame but it's not
Always totally Tut
Dry or bush had great
They would have been happy to create an oppressive corporate state where labor rights were not existing
All of these characters sucking their own way
But Alex has to call Bush a Nazi
Speaker that's because he can't unpack
Things to recognize that the real
Jeffrey's involved with bison was
Their shared opposition
Communism which Alex agrees with
If you have to unpack this and talk about Jason's history witch
That only opens a political machine out of
And that's probably not something Alex on
To get into I am
Loving
The irony
The irony of a woman who is coming on this show
To sell me a book
About how great mall
Karthi was is now telling other people this is the nuttiest thing she's ever heard there is it is
Playlist nutty to call Prescott Bush and nothing but it is to say McCarthy was a good guy
I think though that one of the things you'll notice
If you listen to this whole thing is that
They ultimately just
They're both wrong
Pretty consistently
Is it least structurally making point
Right so she's right in that
Right but they're wrong about so much but they both think that they're right
Looking for black helicopter
Call home
Kane
You in promoter open border
Over here okay
I believe you are
They're both wrong Alex 2.0
Demonstrated that Aaron is somehow
Disconnected from reality because she's supporting these weapons of mass destruction
Your points are wrong
Two people arguing over how the KKK should committed genocide
Like what are you guys doing it is pretty strange
Go to break now it's come back and this is just pathetic
I don't know about you
So perfect that is
The Pink Panther theme because both of those
Clouseau with conspiracy
So Alex starts getting into like 911
Sure false Flags.
Comfortable territory exactly
Is a little kid
One investigation
Intimidating
Feisty
Easily intimidated
Call Jackie
Planes and flying
We trained Bahar jackalope
George Bush
Not as good
Your update
I came here to talk about how great and correct McCarthy was
Sdick I came here to sell the book full of nutty theories
Exactly what you say I came here to lie my way
But it still delightful
Are you do something about this
Part of it is because it's in the past
Pass
It can't hurt us more than it already has
Kind of fun to see her be annoyed
Also be
Be correct
And her annoying little at all so wrong about everything
There's just layers
It is it is nice
To see these two Dum Dums
Really just get to the heart of why they're incompatible and why the right-wing grift is
Destined to eat itself alive
You know is because
I'm selling my b*******
And I don't want to listen to your b*******
You know it's and it's like
Well yeah Alex is selling his bullshittin he doesn't want to listen to your b******* especially when your b******* is like
Fairly contradictory stupid
There's that so it's just a going back and forth with people and Ann Coulter gets to act like she's laughing
Get all of this s***
Because it's
Sounds more openly lunatic
Then what she selling you which is it adult same lunacy wrapped up in better word but she's got like
Great
Life of privilege to get to answer the phone call
She'll go and meet up with a friend have a cocktail and talk on the phone
One last call for an
Does not get a chance to answer and let Alex
Crater Lake
A real pilot garbage
Tambascio
I mean look it's rude
But also kind of funny
I just want to do
Faded
Things to get reelected
Azar
He should be
Being elected
There's more important things
I like Preserve
Constitution
Right now
More than
I'm quotes
Doesn't matter anymore
Pretty pretty good
That's good stuff
I mean there's three things that are amazing
First is the
Sweet
You can't answer the question
That's supposed to be the last question for a
2nd and jumping and receipt like I wish your candidate Lyndon larouche the best of luck in the next alarm
Drivel
This lady lying to you about McCarthy I think
The Alex
Wanted that like don't buy her book to be way more earned that was
That was really a really really jealous
Like it if
It's
It's pretty funny though hey I appreciate
I'm sorry
I think that
Like
This is a gif
For Alex
Hotels in 30 is a big deal
Huge
I think he handled this
Poorly
I think they called it doesn't give a s*** about who he is
Might not matter
But this kind of behavior would definitely be like
If she cared
She has access to all sorts of
Very famous people
That could be Gaston altucher and now will not
Hello
Promises the interview was supposed to be the promoter book
And instead you just
Set about to dump shift or annoyed her
Yeah
It's kind of. How you treat against I love
Both of them feeling bad
About this
I think she
I don't think she did I think of the end she's got a good good snippy
Line and I probably could line into that she's going to get a highball and have a great time have a nice day
Tell me I think she walked away from this thinking
I don't like what happened
I like are feeling like that
But I don't know if it matters matters to her
Probably from this much more pissed off than
I think he was actually mad
She will be happy and playing around with
The laughing at being like this black helicopter s***
This is larouche announcer for sure there was actually an amusement on her part like
I have accidentally stumbled universe
Calling and asking me about prostitutes the Bohemian Grove
Amazing people who will just agree to go on a show
Now just with no knowledge
Don't know who that person is
Yeah
It is it is strange
This is
Maybe one of the last high-profile interviews to get for a while
Because it does it does not
It's not a good
Marketing tool for like
Hey come talk to me right I will treat you well I know it's three or four they didn't
They didn't have group text
But I'm sure she could still get on the phone pretty quick with a lot of people so at least in a day
There's hundreds of people who are going on
Alex
Like I said I think it's probably just
Got done with it and maybe want to tell the friend cuz it's funny
I can't imagine that she thinks he's relevant
No that's true like if you have this kind of interaction with somebody first of all you know that they
Are behaving is
A gracious host
She'll probably like this is an unprofessional a******
Doing a radio show
Successful possible ideas that are being expressed in new like this is
This is fringe nonce
Maybe I got to talk to my
Yeah Boy anyway I enjoyed this a lot I was really looking forward to this episode
Because of the like
Batiz I got a
Big slimy
Off the rail fun
That's great
That's just great
Good clean fun
And it's for 2003 that's the best
So we'll be back
But until then
Website.com
Back when Zelda enemy Lemley rbbx
Robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color