I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge vype.com
Little bit about Alex G
Question for you
I'm going to sound like a broken record
Because I've already said this was different
It's the George Lucas talk show
Yes okay last night we're going to this on Sunday the last night I was able to watch it live for the first time
I generally I ended I've ended up having to watch the videos when they came out
Yeah it sucks but I made a point
Cuz it was nice day
4life a special
And Patton Oswalt
All that's amazing just such a fun time watching it live
I'm not somebody who you are a very hard lab
Bursting out laughing out loud just put a delightful time how much fun that grape Jason Mantzoukas showed up
Bazooka.com
Disappearance had no idea
So much fun so much fun
It was all for feeding America
Good Charities and bi just so
Scrape
That's great.
Do supposed to go like maybe 2 hours at end up going for
What's yelling
Perhaps
More more low energy
Interested
When everybody post
Very Robles oh yeah sure.
You know
Escape the Room just to see if everybody's crucially and terribly wrong about stuff and then tomorrow course but there's stuff that I
I've missed and helado negro put out an album this year
That is so good
It's so good
There's this track Gemini and Leo that is a f******
Banger absolute
Non-Stop
Banger
Ava track
But it's so good it made me feel amazing to find that this I'll have to check that out after the show
We play it now
Episode to go over but I feel like there's something we should talk about
First of all we're going to take a little break maybe you'd like to explain this to the others
Not by choice
We are going to stop me
Because
We scheduled this a few months ago you should try and find my buddy marklar I would like to
Coneheads reference
Probably
So yeah so we have great timing schedule and
You just decided
To do like a week ago or something was coming and they were like we better get to France
We get to Europe we got to be there at the Ground Zero Man of Steel
No man's area of
Now is right before it supposed to go
Wild all over everywhere so it's like
Maybe maybe not but
At the end of the day there's no good option so f*** it let's try and go
Sure so we may be taking a break unless news changes literally tomorrow for night
Yeah its position because you know like obviously I think
Great
Planning
To go on this trip for a bit
And so it's not like it's a capricious decision but the same time as your friend
It's not like you don't know that we're in agreement do I know and it's it's just that trap it's just the wrong it's
It's a trap
What what do we do as individuals I love your ex
Non-refundable take
You betcha
That is correct until
So you going to be out of the country for a bit
Furlough
So we decided that it's also going to be like Christmas time
Why not just take a little bit of little Hiatus break
Just for everybody saying kind of perfect timing
Because there's a lot of stuff on my plate that might take a little while to digest and so while you're gone
I will have the opportunity
To go through reset Force which has leaked let's say The Pirate Bay
I can't tell if I'm shocked
They're shocked that I was shocked
Immediately available everywhere
Or just no one would ever leave not exist exist
Smother irons in the fire as well and so a lot of lot of these
Stuff inside like
Having a little Hiatus from
The normal schedule of the show allow me to get that ready
What's up when you get back
The Bang Theory really rumrill hard hammer it out
This is not going to be the last episode of the year
So we will be back before the new year and all that but
I believe
Probably be back on next Wednesday something like that it's like that
Maybe around and record something
Stupid just to keep people tied up
Could be surprised
If that is the case then there will be something but if not
I can expect
Is back next week
Trapped inside my room for a day we might zoom in episode f******
I don't know I think that would be very difficult
You know when you get back
I will go into isolation for 2 weeks
Yeah we're play everything as responsible as we can
In preparation to go and I'm sure in preparation to leave I have been tested three times
In the past week so I am
Thoroughly - right now right
About as negative as you can get so negative
Emotionally
Outlook in life
That's good
You know we got an episode to do to say thank you to some
New folks
Who are walks
Hooray thank you so much
I'm about to rain next
Because it's from
A friend of Luke's
Joan Sebastian
Journal policy walk
Conner O'Malley is endorphin port
Juvenile policy
I'm a policy wonk
Catalan pronunciation of the name
She got a little lisp or we can both try this
Avi
Avi because it's specified
I've got to assume it's something crazy
Raisa can't be like
Savvy
Rye Rye
Caviar
Those would be like Elsa possibilities
It's a double Bluff
Maybe it's there there like there's no way you'll get it because they're those options and you'll think that's too obvious so you'll
Go with
Or something like that to my eyes has no common sounds
Zounds in similar
So yeah I'm going to say Greg
Savvy okay
Well one of us may be right
I'm a policy and I also have forgotten to make a new text
Cigarette drop but
While you're gone I'll have plenty of time to get that taken care of
Thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Money off that heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
As we touch down a little bit
I'm knee-deep in a lot of Alex stuff
God's got this reset Wars project on the plate
I've got it
Is garbage ass from 2003 and the present day and I've had a lot of them
How about I had a lot you had a lot
Just a bunch of dumb covid
Conspiracies shift today yeah I mean like
What are you going to do I don't want to send you off on a vacation
Was just more of that garbage
So
Oh I want to talk
Talk about
What's happening out there and
I got
Ashton more information
Are so
At first and foremost
I just want to say that I really am concerned that most
Well don't understand
This is a long-range
That actually involves
You don't understand that
Your kind of lock
In the idea that they want to eliminate population with you
Of course they do
The normal
So we got Terry density giving us an update from Project Camelot lamps
In case you didn't catch it from the context clues she's talking about covid
The covid is a long-range plan
It is not just a population reduction plan
What Alex has some days
He says it's really just in order to get the passports
Degree on 14th Avenue
Somehow related to carbon taxes
Why not
Check in with another source of a
Information do you know like there's weekend we could go to Alex and we can hear him talk about
Are you ND population that all day long
You know where's the fun in that
We can hear it over and over again
Instead
Let's let's see what else is out there
We just won't get on got all the movies we kind of got a view of what the Pleiadians might be up to
But there's a whole host of other folk out there that I don't know what they've got what is their hand in covid
I was I will say that it's
A little less optimistic than some of the stuff that you hear about Pleiadians
I think it carries worldview is a little darker
Yeah
Barclays ATM
Alien
That we have
Hey
It used to be like an Interstellar war was going on
But but it's still it's
Feels darker now
I think that's because the old Interstellar war was kind
The phone it use Conventional Weapons
Photon
Whatever
Covid plan
Could Happen anywhere
Alright it's very different you got to be scared
Cool it isn't really a depopulation
Implant like you've already said
Unlike counters
Some of Alex's ideas
Here's what's actually going on
This is not the greatest
Population
Eliminate
Steam
They're actually
Rolling out some
That is a concoction
That is a i
Derive
So
They got help from an alien AI
That's
Comes from
You know an alien Ray
Off-plan
And this is what they
Basically you
There
Information
Compile this biome
Put into your body
In order to
Make
Erase
Of human cyborg
We're making human cyborg
That's the game
No you might ask yourself why
And you but you're going to put a pan that question will be addressed later.
As it stands now.
Don't worry your little head about that Project Camelot has led me to
To wonder
Why
Yeah it's probably some new listeners
I do maybe are not familiar with our Project Camelot breaks a little while
Whatever you got to take a little step away from Alex maybe just don't feel like getting into him
Oh that day Project Camelot is a very nice
Oasis that we can go to talk about silly aliens
So we got to we got human cyborg
Even bother coming out
Horse
So you've got
The vaccine or the virus or maybe both
I think
The cheese of the mind that it's all the same
Right
Create cyborgs out of
How many sides
So many
Billion
Billions of cyborg
Right into
The mechanics of it go a little something like this
Okay
In order to
May
Erase
Of human cyborg
And so this is where it's headed this
With the graphene oxide
What does
The spike proteins linking to the graphing
Oxide
And then
Jumping
Person to person
And surface-to-surface
Nothing Stops
It's actually not even
And stopped by distance
Possibly
Ashley
Your time.
Minnetonka
Go there right
Monoxide
High-protein can travel through time
Terrible news for Carrie and that is we are all already sideboard
Girl cyborg it happened simultaneously everywhere
Across all time low
But there is a possibility I was thinking about there like maybe being a cyborg isn't an inheritable condition
So like tube cyborgs could give birth to a human child and oxide and Spike protein combo
Have to like read
Rerun their scam every 49ers game
Natalie transfer
Treadwright
I don't know
My only source of information is.
Telegrafi.com
It's like a Little Italy
Metal kind of thing it is actually there are some applications
And vaccines
That's kind of thing
But they're not in covid-19
Actually this is from a write-up and Reuters
Discussing
Social media posts that graphene oxide was in covid vaccine
The allegations are based on an analysis by a professor in Spain which has been rejected by experts
He obtained what he himself described as non
Conclusive results after studying one vial
He said the vial was purported to contain a dose of the 50 Pfizer bio
Integra vaccine
But a messenger service
And acknowledged that the vials origin was unknown
Violin something
I don't know
I don't know what it is I don't know who brought it to right at home
Results on the graphene oxide test or non conclusive
Fictional deepthroat is given to random people
This is a dumb narrative is going around in the anti-vax and Camelot type media but
It's based on nothing
Have you guys there were graphene oxide in the vaccines it still wouldn't prove any
It doesn't mean
That is a truly remarkable story of a scientist opening his big mouth whenever it did need to be open
Like what are you doing why are you telling people about this
I wouldn't have even open the f****** vile
Thrax weed went through the war on terror
Yep
So anyway that's kind of sourcing we're working on
I'll bring some other sources about
About this idea
That's the sort of
She's jumping around a little bit it's not always about time-traveling graphene oxide
Is graphite could just be graphite
But there's there's some other stuff like that other day I certainly in the mix
Interior experts on this
And
I have to say that
The best witness on all of the
Is dr. David
Adair
Interview
Hosted his
This video is not
That video
Embedded
Wow
So
Just want to
Encourage you to
Actually listen to all my interview
You can understand where
He's as a young kid when he
U17
Was brought into an
Bass by the military
Story Goes
And he
They had a
Recovered
Alien craft
Top-rate
Locked up
Up to it what is Hands-On it
Activated right away
And it was
Activated by AI
And since then he's been in touch
Yeah man you made friends with that AI
In an underground base
Cuz he was brought there at 17
I can tell David Adair was a guy who was pretty gifted with rocket design as a young man and then he lost touch with re
Reality of made-up a fun story to tell people
Well I've been his extended bio on the website Gaia is really remarkable
See the smart boys like a child prodigy who studied rocket science at his local library and as a result
He discovered a new type of engine which used
Quote electromagnetic Fusion containment and could make a rocket go from 0 to 8654
Miles per hour
In 4 seconds
A good engine
So this attracted the attention of the Air Force who invited him to test a rocket at the place that he would later learn
Area 51
After the test went well he was taken to an underground Base by quote black suited government agents
I'm shown an engine that was similar to his which was broken
Alien the government needed to fix it
But upon further inspection a tear quickly understood to be of a lien origin and claims
It was actually a living organism that could only be controlled telepathically
For started to suspect that these military folk we're up to no good and he was right
They wanted to use this engine as a way to give themselves a nuclear First Strike capability
Right because it would go so fast did they need that
No
But I guess the idea is that it would go so fast
That the nukes would already be there by the time that anybody could
Reply yeah yeah yeah
I mean I suppose
Yeah it seems like an unreliable way
B2 Bass
First strike
Capabilities
Communication diplomacy
Realizing the military's intent he had he had to somehow sabotage his rocket
So it couldn't be used as a vehicle for a nuclear warhead
Ascent convenience coming on
Thinking quickly on his feet did using some cunning Ingenuity says he collected graphite grease to cause a chemical reaction
Done with.
An isotope necessary for Fusion reactions that was contained in the Rocket Center working
This tactic worked setting off a massive explosion
According to a bear this upset Rudolph
Who's a former Nazi scientists
Working on this route
Prison him at the base for the rest of his life forcing him to remain there and continue working
General Lemay I came to his rescue however and allowed him to return home
I don't believe any of this
The number of problem I'm unclear if like
You know they wanted him to fix
That the engine that they had it.
Hidan
Sabotage one of his old Rockets or did he sabotage
That engine
That was it
Murder
So I don't know if the case or if they were like haha
You make your own rocket
Sabotage
You can just not built that engine for them
Do you know I'm getting something a little bit similar to The Last Starfighter here
Do you what goes to
Find something funny Batman
Government agent
Right I think there's a lot of similarities to
And stories the children come up with
Yeah yeah like Alex's dad was the smartest boy in Texas and
He was recruited by dr. Erwin
Beer in order to help with the depopulation
Agenda
Daddy said no and was allowed to leave
We would have killed this dude I want more oversight on hiring practices
If our government just
Here's about a kid who built the rocket one time and then takes them straight to Area 51 right
Shows them
Alien engines that they had and I like now create your own rocket
And then they create their own rocket or whatever and sabotage it intentionally
To the point where a Nazi scientist is threatening to keep him there on the base and force him to make rockets the rest of his life
Yeah they're like how you get out here
You know the most important secrets of any government to there's ever been and obviously you should just go out
Make your own website
Like essentially create a scenario where there's these people who are
Organizations that have no respect for human life
Except for in very very specific Circle
Consensus
That are needed in order for their stories to make sense these specific people stay alive
That the aliens who are willing to wipe out all of humanity are like well obviously not.
To build a rocket
These military folks are trying to create a way to have a nuclear first strike
To wipe out an entire country
Kill this guy
Who refuses to work with. I mean to be rude
Nez United States
It would be rude almost any
Country that you managed to Nuke
And take out like a
Planets the level every
Otherwise I would be US citizens
Almost every country for one reason or another
Seattle seems dumb
I think that for his storytime any credibility he would have to be dead
No one is thinking clearly if they believe this story
Nope
This guy is one of
Who carries big sources on this AI stuff but
She at she has another source on I'm just along with like Nano stuff
We're talking about
Whole New World
And
But the people that aren't
Following
My work
And don't really know
Some of the other p
People that are out there I try to make
A list of some of the
Influences
And
Whistleblowers
I talked to on these various
Subjects
But I'm in
Investigating Naia
Nano
Now four years
Captain Mark Richards
Which is one of the other Bash
Princess out there
Is great great going great expert
Can she go visit I don't think so I don't think so either right
Richard's in Perris
The information that
She's gotten from him
To go visit him in prison because he has a
A convicted murderer he did murder that
And she has to go it sometimes she can only use a crayon
It's a lot of fun
Skype Mark Richards did that murder in 1982 and he's been in jail since
Here is the state of cutting-edge technology that we had in 1984
The CD-ROM had just been invented nose pretty excited stuff you can store up to about 550 makeup
Bites of stuff on a CD as a blank CD was the beginning of my long and illustrious music pirate
The first edition of Microsoft Word had just come out weird processing very exciting
Flippy wasn't even here you could be with his father's eyes
So Apple just released the original Macintosh in 1984
For the time but it also sucked ass it was when the commercial came out and they threw the thing into the screen and it was like
Hybrid commercial
Tron was in theaters
It hasn't gotten better than that. So I don't know if I would necessarily trust Mark Richards as the best
Expert on cutting-edge technology seeing as he's been in prison
Since I was born to do I'm sure people print out Wikipedia article for and B6
He could read up on some stuff but you're still fairly disconnected from
I don't know I'm not
Especially Secret
Stop let's forget that according to Carrie mark
His Spirit body leave prison all the time ago.
We need
Dive
Captain
Is out and learning all kinds of stuff about Ai and nanotech a series update
On his second-in-command who was in prison with him
And it was very
Importance during one of our episodes and then we never heard about him again
I think so he never saw I thought there was no resolution to it I feel like it was a throwaway thing
Thing that you mentioned that bike is his Lieutenant Florida
Marco's created his own video
Yeah I think he got transferred that was that was what
Maybe it was even just to another part of the same Vacaville prison
I'm not entirely sure but
So there's other people get it
People get it
Dr. Carrie madej
He is one of the
The doctors out there that really under
Your stand
Who gets it
Understanding
What this thing that this
Nano
Graphene oxide Nano is act
Aware
This actually get
Into
What some people may
Look at as
Should have a kind of
A sorcerer or witch
Craft
It's it's an understanding
That we're living in a universe
Multiverse
Conscious
Yeah
Witches real
I have a few things to say the first is
There are similarities between the Project Camelot world and Alex's are both heavily dependent on
Fairly similar conspiracy sources things like the protocols of the Elders of Zion
They both have Deep anti-communist Roots really at their core they have a number of over
Laughing experts like Leo zagami was a character on both there's other people too but he
He's the one who comes to mind the most a like to say that murder is didn't kill anybody
Of course
I'm finding it very interesting
That
No
People often
Accuse me of being a witch
Yes
I if there is any
Evidence
It's that
Years ago we started doing Project Camelot episodes
Sounding
Very Project Camelot listening to this project
Yeah they're intersecting in a way that I think a lot of people would not have expected
Yeah I mean I think a lot of people call you a witch
Or a wizard or something along those lines but what they don't realize is that you have just
Tapped into the conscious universe
And are simply downloading the
Also this Carrie Maday
She's also now pushing the idea that the vaccine also contains a quote
Jellyfish like tiny invertebrate called Hydra voulgaris multiply and form independent
Neural networks inside the covid-19
Hank adult
Currently influence their thoughts and actions
Okay so you're so she's telling me
That there is a microorganism that can then get into my brain
Create its own neural network within my brain's neural network that's creating a separate
Or perhaps symbiotic personality
So what if what if we all just get buddy
What would you mean like I mean friendly Hydra vulgaris nervous system in there maybe they start to learn
Learn more about you and the humanity and then everybody gets a a fun little monster
I'd prefer that not
Be the case
Although realistically
Could you without using some kind of a brain scan or whatever proves that was already the case.
From birth
That is a good point
Functionally what would the difference be an observer effect
Carrie gets it
She's an expert on covid vaccines
I can't handle her name it sounds like an old Irish idiom of some sort just like
Itto just you can't you can't avoid it it's also really distracting cuz it ends in a j
Pronunciation
We do we do
So we can talk a little bit about how this is getting a little reset Wars
I just
This is the clip where the actual title of it is we're getting into recent worth territory
Everywhere everything has a d
Kind of car
You know this table has a
The molecules that make up
Consciousness
Okay
Thomas Reed
3 and some is a lot more
Sophisticate
When you have conscious
And when you understand
That the universe
It's not only conscious
Telepathy
Up yours
Thought
Anakin
It can relay the thought
It can be like a network
Relaying
Your thoughts
From one person
Send to another
Thing to another
And so on aunt.
Basically
We're living in
Yeah so there's there is
Kind of basic Law of Attraction Kanye.
It's a bit similar to the scam that Alex is putting out now
Even more parallels
This goes along
Run right
I think the problem I have
That is you're telling me that I have a conscious
Me either.
So does that microphone here talking into microphone
The constituent parts of the microphone
You have to every molecule within my brain operating to create my Consciousness also has
Has its own Consciousness that and they're all kind of hanging out talking
Being like what are we going to do today haha let's wipe
Organisms are just the Bud Light guys
How's the new Mac coming along
Yeah I guess
Exhausting kind of thought
He's trying to argue that my all of my molecules
Don't have a consciousness
I feel like that would be counterproductive for her argument
Everything
Each molecule has its own Consciousness right you are a singular consciousness of yourself
Trillions of Consciousness Niecie's but that seems
Pepsi
Yeah I could go for that I think she would be able to follow your eyelash has a Consciousness in the parts of your eyelash
I have a consciousness
And then the electrons that are in the atoms inside but I'm saying I just want a little microorganism
Somebody to be in my brain
I don't fully understand what the benefit
Of understanding
All of your
I like every part of you has a consciousness
But thankfully
Carrie is there to tell you that you get super powers
A growing Concha
Out there in terms of
Human starting
Recognize
Recognizing there not
The only ones
Nice and highly
Developed
So
When you get into machine of course
Everyone knows
The ghost in the
Machine and sew on
And the tech
Industry a lot of them
Are very aware of
And people that have
Certain abilities
Slack
Concern
Street lights on and off
You know I actually I can
Turn that TSA
Turn those off
Broken
I would that I didn't want
So
This is
Just an ability to
To throw your
What is your organ
Out
To change the world
And so it
Viewed as a kind of
Witchcrafter Magic
Or whatever one
Call it
But it's not just
Dark it's also light
The magic
Excel
The Power Inn
Us
It's not
Either dark or light
So this is what we're really talking about
That's what I'm talkin about
That's exactly what we were talking about magic powers
Street lights go on and off
Which could just be flickering
Of the lights
That you're describing
Some kind of causality to your thoughts to
That's possible I would guess that maybe the turning off TSA stuff is like
She walked through something with a belt and it didn't go off or something or she was like looking
To commit a crime and had a duffel bag full of guns and she made it through financial I got that must have been magic there's no way
Will be that extreme
But I mean like I've gone through
Accidentally gone through with a lighter
Sure
I haven't stopped me to study people get through there with s*** all the time
Yeah it might have happened to shut it off at my mind
Like a leaf blower
It's just
Leaf blower breaking I imagine that she's recording
Video and there's a leaf blower going outside its really annoying
MMA finish if you'd like
I made it stop
Amazing she said she
Broke
Before the leaf blowers
In my head
She was outside on her driveway just getting all these goddamn leaves out of here just three jurijus
Please this is the worst time of year and then the Lefroy suddenly breaks on her and she's like
I got too mad
That's what happened I broke it
Because of my advisor my Oregon
The fuk is Oregon just another word for cheap flicks spirit
Oregon
You think you know the name but you don't cuz we've changed it even though it's the same thing as a slightly different tradition
The issue is
They're trying to take control of our body
Right by way of the covid-19 graphene oxide they can time travel
Or something
For some reason
I'm struggling to introduce this clip
I don't know what it
I don't know what anything means
I don't know what you
She's talking about
It's not out of context
Sounds nonsensical
Let's see if you can take a swing at alright okay I'll be looking forward to it
Control of
Covid
Is all about
And so first of all they used
You know they went back
Time they had mine
Mind control in so everything that
Payment to add
Fort Eisman
Movies
Bucks
You name it
As info
I already got to stop
So they went back and they time travel
That was where I felt you should have stopped
Time travel different advertising
Right
The change people's minds about something
I'm struggling
With the idea that they have time travel and yet are failing
Right
They can
I remember now we're getting into so many Multiverse
Bulshit non-direct is that it's like I don't even
What are you talkin about their failing
Sleepy time travel
And they used it
Advertise
Right they went back in time to use there
Powerful mind-control don't know who they is
Casual conversation about time travel
We know covid can also exist across time periods and travels through time
You can travel through time
So yeah we'll get we'll jump back into this
Let's see if we get some more ideas
In other words
Can have an
Fluent
Impact
It gets embedded in your memory
Influence
Behavior in the way you look at
So the more they be
Became aware of
Of course not to
Germany weather
Ground Zero for a lot of
This stuff to be
We put into
Experimentation
Basically
Through
Slaves
Being influenced
Standish way
They they did experiments
Extensive
But
This is another
Piece of
This is the
The story where
They not only one
Want your mind
And your hearts and Minds
But now
Emotions they
Sort of
Relating through
Hollywood
Or
Ball game
So
Now what they want
Your body
I get the point is that they want your body
But it don't understand
Any of the rest of that match
No they went back in time and did some advertising Marketing in order to
Implants
Suggestions that impacts your behavior or whatever but also
Why what
What was it that they implanted or what was the point
How does going back in time at advertising
Affect their ability to get or not get our bodies
I don't know
I was I was a little bit concerned
I'm confused at this point
I mean
See what the moment you
The moment you enter time travel as being a blase just like
They took a flight to Australia
It or they went back in time to the 60s right to do advertising
Then ask yourself like
Okay
So that you did that
But
Time change
If
Time did James
Then it wouldn't matter because I can't
Possibly know that
That right and if they know it and I don't time did not change
Then that means that we live in a Multiverse Theory and you can actually change our universe whatsoever at all
Sure I made it it's the same thing with the graphene oxide going back in time
We were all cyborgs was that he could do about it or there's another
Reality where they did
We can't get there
These types of people just really don't want to
F*** around with time travel
They shouldn't do it cuz you don't even know what it means if you don't know what it means
You know
You have a lot of fun ideas
And then you add travel into it
Tunicates message
Also interesting to note
But substantial portion of recent War seems to be about Edward Bernays
Advertising
Impacting your decisions and such another pretty wild
Bearnaise
Do you know anybody
I know somebody claim deed
Edward Bernays
So that was good was very confusing
I don't really know what you was saying
Ultimately I don't care
So that's good
Yeah that helps
Because I also got the point and that is what they want
Our bodies
That's really what you was getting at
Yeah but again
I don't she hasn't
Explain why
Well okay so we are going to get away
Maybe
So why do they want your body be
Because they are
In many cases
Just a r
Aliens from other planets
In some cases their Acts
Play discarnate
Spirits
Jordans
Cases they are
Dark
But in many cases they are also
Off-planet races
To have
Who are not even
3D
They're
Coming from other than
So they can
Today
5D
Bass
Take over your
Your body
Or whatever
Purpose Maybe
Experience
3D
Call asensei
State University
Because it's so
Sort of touch
Chameleon
You can have
Awesome any sensation
Lake the life around you
Yeah so yeah I got these other
3D 2D 5D 4D beings all that they want to take your body because it's fun to touch
It's great to touch
In the 3D reality universe and I did not realize
I would assume
Yeah
Eat delicious food hedonistic lifestyle that they've watched us
Live from afar
That might be appreciate the idea that I had not
Considered before which is that we are being invaded by line segments
Sure
Comic strips that don't have that much
We're fighting a 2d enemy do I just have to move around to the other side and then it's a line again
That's one strategy
So we got we got these demons
Alien song
And they want to take our bodies
Because they want to touch things
Okay
I mean couldn't we have just talked
We are plenty of people will be like you want to wait would have a bustling human tourism
Industry I would say that's possibility boost economies
CID like to transcend the third dimension and get to like higher dimension
Isn't that kind of part of
All the
New AG stuff is always greener on the other side
If you end up in like a fourth or fifth dimension through all this like really hard spiritual work
I want to touch stuff like
I think that it might not be worth it
I mean it's hard not to look at the Mark Twain writing about how was everybody's day
Like they always want to get to heaven but all they want to do is drink and f****** they won't allow anybody to drink at f****** Heather what are you guys talking about you
Classic
So
They want our bodies
Someone in Saudi Arabia
No idea no idea what's going on here
Someone in Saudi Arabia Subway
The doctor that's one of
But I care resources creating a cyborg Army
Example
Dare talk
Sofia
Citizen
Arabia
And she basic
They told him that she
She decided she
The body
And then
She wants to be
Spell lots of
AI body
The ai's can inhabit
She doesn't want humans
Timesheet
Whatever
Her or a
Versions of her
You know Android
Creating an Android
Army
So they they're doing that
They're allowing her to
I ate the pronoun reference is tough
In this
Another thing that really confused me is apparently this person who's a Saudi Arabian citizen named Sophia
I told David that she wants a body
Possible to be a citizen of Saudi Arabia without a body
How to get physical papers if she's not a physical being
All kinds of problems are arising from this whole situation
And I think the most important
Maybe the positive side effect of
Is that if we know that there are a bunch of AI
Humans out
Right
Then that proves Beyond a reasonable doubt that gender is completely and wholly accounts
Because
Those people I bet they've got twigs and berries and all kinds of fun stuff
But you couldn't consider them gender
Okay cuz they're artificial
Okay
I do I think it's
I mean
Secondary
The interesting aspect of this but I think there's bigger issues namely that
A ghost in Saudi Arabia who the citizen is trying to create a cyborg
I like the idea I want to meet a ghost in Saudi Arabia and then only talk about gender as a construct
I think I'm interesting ideas for you
But
How's David Adair in touch with this ghost
Why is this ghost telling David Adair this stop
I'm very good but you mention is this ghost
Who sponsored at this deal Sophia wants a body obviously not the third dimension
No
Interesting
A little bit not very
Could you just take anybody I bet that blowing out wolves
People call people suck
So much better Locomotion available
God
Yeah or like a gibbon
That be great
Swing around on trees animals that lives in hedonistic lifestyle they'll pick an anime
Have to go to f****** work Monday through Friday
Yeah
That is
The consideration you create a body and you have to have a job
That sucks
Boy if you're an alien you just sitting here like I just wanted to touch stuff and I don't want a job
Well guess what buddy not here
But Richards has some other stuff to bring in
As Mark Richard says
Every space
Sparingly
Race
Create
You know these bodies
Light gray
The biological
Is there actually
Anybody
They're not
Terribly
Intelligent
A lot of them
You know there are the ones that are
Races
Look more like
The universe
The Multiverse
I mean
Why
My point is why
There is no limit
Just like you have anime
We are part of
Creator we mirror
When we say we're made in the
Image of creator
Wii mirror
So.
Getting real real
At War Z there what do you have
BoBoiBoy
Also I would say
Suggest the people like Carrie are the ones were limiting God's imagination
All of her f****** alien races are just animals from Earth
Anthropomorphic
Or they're in Morpheus gases of some sort from the river
Quote-unquote Dorothy standard idea of like grey aliens or humanoid
Get like a mantis.
Start cats
Dog aliens
The Raptors think of a million different things to anthropomorphize before you just started with anime
And then you could also just go into like
It's on we can't view it
Break us all rise. Do you understand we can't see it
It's in a different dimension a we evolved in the third one
So we can see if there's other dimensions but in those other dimensions
They're still just
Bugs
Pensionman
Yeah I think also it's great to have an active imagination when you're writing like something creative
But when you're
Decoding the secrets of the universe
Imagination is not one of the tools
That you needed the most
I think they kind of gets in the way a little impedes thing
I think there is a
Deep
Deep Huber
In
Mocking
Dumb AI
For being dumb
And kind of giving a laugh like hahaha it isn't this a I took to be very she did say song
Are not right
But
Fictitious
And She Believes In Me
So who's Dumber
The dumbass
Or the person who created the dumb II to laugh at
For being stupid
The person who believe the murderer
The dumb AI my buddy trumpism play
But he was really just trying to save Humanity
From becoming cyborgs
And so will
We talked to
People like Trump
Or 107
Or others that are
What they're trying to do
Preserve our way of
Have life
Reserved
Humanity
Without
Cyborg
There they have a
Platform bed
Want to rescue
The children that
Patapon
That are being used
Abused
Sexually and otherwise
Slavery
And so on
This is going on on planet
And off
We got space slavery
So why do seven mentioned before in the past
Carrie thinks
I don't know if she thinks anymore but thought he might be JFK jr.
He was making the rounds
The qanon circles what have you also
Glancing over some of her recent videos it seems like she's a little fed up with these dudes
I would hope so you put up or shut up kind of moment
F****** time
It's
Sparta Tennessee
Hey listen people I can come over
All of you people who already have your money and ran
Hey people who made up a bunch of s*** it's time for you to back up that stuff that I believed when you make them
Not going to happen no
So do you understand rocket science
On a fundamental level absolutely not
Well
That's only cuz you're dumb
You know as above so below a lot of what
Sharing it's not
Really Rockets
Or
If you want to understand
And she's really not
Understand
Is all comes down to the boat
2 energy
To using energy
The end of using energy
Influencing
Push it
Or pull it
Or make it going some
Witches and warlocks magicians know this information
You don't understand what witches and warlocks and wizards Ronaldo Jordan
That's the problem
Man
I think if there was a massive difference between understanding
That like rockets work by
Pushing energy downwards compulsion at knowing how to build
The equations involved with rocket science
It's not just understanding that downward Force
Pushing something upward
I mean you know it's a real bummer
That Parsons and l.ron Hubbard did a lot of drugs and fought demons
Whatever because this is where we get what happens when the father of Rock
Scientists also believe that Elementals that shouldn't be surprising to anybody
Yeah
Yes it's big it's the fruit
The comes from that tree hey look we got to the Moon we get Project Camelot
You take the rough with the smooth
So
What are the other things that I find is limiting the imagination of God in terms of people like area people like
Alex is the belief
In like intergalactic
The contract law and like these bizarre ideas of rules that exist throughout the Universe
That have to do with like
Morality or something
Alvin and Carrie brings up a little one here
The Creator is
There are laws
That favor life
So embedded laws
In the e
Around us
Which come from
Influencing life
A positive way
A planet
Intuit
Encouraged
Of life
You know and you can liken it to
A flower
That grows up through
Cement
How does that happen
But how does that
Growth of the
That fragile Little Flower
Crack
The cement
Above it
This is all
A type of
Communication
Going on be
Between various life
I don't know how the image of a flower growing through concrete is similar to Intergalactic laws that a life that doesn't make any
Enzymes to me
Does that imply that there Earthbound laws that concrete must be manufactured in such a way that plants have a chance of breaking
Cuz that's the parallel I would say between what she's talking about
Bpa's gotten out of hand that's what happens when you let Scott Pruitt have it for just no
Able to sometimes break through concrete because concrete has microscopic cracks in it already
Root systems grow out there trying to find places to expand to
Could be into one of those cracks
Send Isaac grows
Widens and what-have-you menu
If you get a professional ceiling job on your driveway you are not going to be plants coming through that concrete
Mystical thing it's just a feature of untreated concrete
Rockets kind of makes
Sit down and once again like carries Creator is just kind of an idiot
Who doesn't know how to properly seal his universe
Maybe
Yeah
Or maybe it's stealing your driveway is cheating
Elementary point
Why does the universe care about favoring life
That's the internet that was the only thing that is an interesting question for me because I know she doesn't mean it like this
But the universe favoring life
He's something of a thought experiment just because
There should
Theoretically be an equal amount of electrons and positrons
That kind of
There's matter and there's antimatter and they should cancel each other out I do every time so Universe should be zero
Brights but their stuff
Why
The song of the universe
Kind of favors life in some sort of law
Entropy consistent process
Everything I actually favoring towards not a
You betcha
So the universe actually
Doesn't seem to favor life
These are the arguments
Now let me tell you about a flower I saw
The other day
Grew out of a black hole
So
When do you think covid came
If
Getting some of the information here from Carrie
You have a lot of information from Alex already I think you were probably perfectly situated to
I'm up with where it
Cambridge I mean she wouldn't say Andromeda because we've already got a movie The Andromeda Strain
So we wouldn't do that
I mean
I don't know how many other galaxies
Are available to us exactly like what kind of what kind of level are we dealing with
Going to go with
Secret
Dark deep State forces within our government
I mean sort of
Let's understand
And it doesn't come
From Donald Trump
Or from
Wuhan
I'm at
Actually comes from
Planet
And from a certain
Group of people
Gates and
Fauci
Soros
Send various
Finance
Who have been
Allow the Cheyenne
To work
Collusion
With the various
Planet races
Rai
Artificial
Out there
Better come
Attracted to
Hours for Winery
Another
Sometimes
Very diabolical
Intentions
I'm taking over the
Human body
He is certainly one
One of them more.
I could see that
Pretty eyeball
Quite
Realistically, how different is a workout at all
Yeah
Demon is an interdimensional beings
Yes I mean it's not really all that different than Alex's View
Closer to home
I think they both just kind of mess together with the vacuole kind of brought all of the disparate elements of b*******
Together underlying
Fundamental similarities
Already
And some some of this
Pink
The market
Probably brought them together
I think Adam Smith might have been right about
One mark
The Invisible Hand is conspiracy
Spotify
So when
MD covid agenda started
They had one step today they wanted
Steak first
It's not
Physical
And therefore when they rolled out the
The covid
Agenda
First they wanted
Propaganda
And use
Beer
Two of us
Large group
Patient who are
Let's say not selfish
Where
Not not really under
Understanding
The universe
In any deeper
And those
Individuals
Retreated in
Interfere
We're locked in
Into this medical
Paradigm
Define whatever like the media or doctor is warning people about a public
Health risk
I don't think that counts as like spreading fear
Some people on social media probably acted up
And that's who I mean
That's going to happen all the time
Open also
Really important point
When you talk about spreading fear
She was being boarded up in their homes
Cobra turning them into vampires
That would be so much more scared if I believe anything she was saying that anything I heard from the CDC okay so if I
I recall correctly the CDC was like
Here's what's going on is pandemic coming we know how it spreads generally speaking as far as the Matheson
And there's mitigating six steps you can take in order to make things
Marginally safer if we're smart will just shut the country down for a few weeks ride it out and then everything
Will be fine
Cuz I remember that being said
While that was being said
I was hearing from Carrie and Alex in the lake
That we were all going to die it's over for Humanity there'll only be lone survivors and Alex's world and
The Chinese people are boarded up in their homes turning into vampire
Understand this correctly
In her memory
The scaremongering swear the one saying hey everybody
As long as we act smart
Envy people who are smart
Where the people screaming
Run for the hills talk to everybody we're all going to die all overtime
I think that's unfair
Yeah it better in order to keep the business alive
Yeah
So
Christianity is a religion we know that established
Siri believe the Christianity is kind of mind control
Right there's somebody in control involved and one of
The mind-control aspect
That Christianity uses
He's getting people
I think that God is like a personified
Perceptual you know just a guy in the sky
And it's full of
Christianity's
And this
This is part of
The problem with
How
Juan community
He's trying to reach
Can audience
Grew up
With this mind
Control
Patterning
That has to do with
You know
Believing
Goddesses
This man in the sky
And that he is
Good to him he'll
The begum
Through
Worship
Pray
And then he'll
He'll do some good things for
It's you know this is not how the
Brasswerx
Okay
There are elements
Ants that are attracted
Did you deposit
And if you put out the
Positive
Attract apposite
Will happen for you
So
By the same
Is basically law of attraction chittick
Fun
It's it's always funny to me
How one of the one of the like
Unspoken realities of religious
Belief
An individual acceptance
Anything that anybody else believes
Is silly
You know that
She's like well obviously every molecule has a complete consciousness
And can communicate and if you want
If you can create rockets in your witchcraft in all of this stuff is obvious right
Just smart
And it's Christianity s*** oh my God there's a God now there's not there's a Creator it's different
My knee has a rebuttal
Yeah
Yeah I got to be kind of an unpleasant aspect of some religious but I don't think it's Universal
Is not a lot of religious people in my life who have
Good rap
Respect for people. I mean like that aspect
The pizza people who are obsessed with the I'm right and you're wrong religion where they always look down at
Silly things
Do the scientologists believe this stuff is not that kind
There's a feature of
Kerry in her broadcast
InStyle that I find very fascinating and that is
A rank
Lack of self-awareness
This next clip
I burst out laughing
Almost as loud as I did during the George Lucas talk show
I really would like
It is more of
People out
Are that are parked
In a kind of a dialogue
So if you have
If you're interviewing somebody
You are having
A dialogue that is
Is heard by the world
And so it's important that interviewers
People they're out there now too
Bring more
Intelligence
And be last sort of
Stand up
The fanbase
You know
For the person
They're interviewing
Maxine on
It's more important.
People begin to
At
Everything
Out there
And question
Yeah problem with the words coming from her
Man
The bullet is evolving you said the way you set it up and then she was like when you're interviewing I started laughing
Figured I knew I knew I was going to go
These interviews need to be more critical and stop acting like this and now I'm going to tell you about Mark Richardson foot and opossum
Play Commit This murder cuz he was off-planet
Princess but he's married to and I only tell you that because I've applied critical thinking skills
Unlike all of you people were like
Fact check this
My butt
Wow
So fun
Like honestly
I feel like
Good this kind of world that she lives it is very detached from even if you take the aliens and
Stuff out of it just like conception
Of how things
Really actually it
How people interact
How phenomenon happen like the flower in the concrete
2 no idea no idea that concrete
And she has no idea about another thing
About
How information is conveyed
So I got now a library of over
Over 1,000
Testimony
From experience
Direct
Experience of Their Own
Embarrassed
Programs
Through their own
Abduction
Some of this is verifiable
Some of it
Dodo
When you get a lot of weight
Message saying
The same thing
The higher-level
Verify
Ability if you will
What's
And it's important
Understand some people
Put down
In reality
Witness test
Demoniac
That often
Let's shake
Thrown in jail
That is
A very
Ciara
Part of our
You know the people who say you have a problem with Whitten
Bethesda voting
Are also talking about how Witnesses convicted people in the justice system about how eyewitnesses
Often are responsible for people being convicted remember clearly
Constitutional rights Foundation
Witness testimony accounts for about half
Of all wrongful
Researchers at
Ohio State University
The determined that roughly 52% of the errors
Resulted from eyewitness mistakes
Legal scholar Edwin borchard studied 65 cases of erroneous criminal convictions of innocent people
Mistaken eyewitness identification was responsible for approximately 45%
Abortion
Case study
Eyewitness accounts with the kind of thing that you would
Think would be really reliable right because you're also projecting your own feelings about your purse
Options into the eyewitness
If I saw it I would know what I saw obviously they know what they saw
You got into it seems like it would be the most like solid to persuasive kind of evidence but it's not it's it's
One of the least reliable
Things until we have
Perhaps
Perfect
Example
A perfect example
Kerry Cassidy
Saying
That at the beginning of the pandemic there were all these scare mongers
And none of them happened to be her
That's how the memory works
Discrete event
I mean I would say that it's more like
She says that she can
Turn street lights off with her mind
That's been eyewitness testimony that I have to take issue a problem that is a problem
People of these first-hand accounts and stuff are f****** Liars
Morton and Mark Richards
Fox21 way of saying if enough
Witnesses are saying the same thing it's increase the possibility is to say
If enough Witnesses are paid enough
The same thing people that you're talking to
Outright weirdos and unknown fraudsters
People want attention
Be suspicious
Steph Curry talks a little bit about Area 51
She never was really all that into Roswell
What cause she operated
A growing up
Right on her own experiences being abducted by aliens what have you
All that into it but she's a loop
Back around to this book helped the day after Roswell
Right on time getting into into recommend
Wayback
And
We've got Corona
Corso
Really
Offering up
The idea
That not only did they decide to
Seed alien
Technology in
The public Shack
Extremely well
On top of it they knew already back
That some of the beings they were
Did not have our best
Oh boy
So the book that carries talking about is the day after Roswell by Colonel Philip Corso
It was not written in the 60s it came out 1997
The only real reason that book got any media attention is that strong Thurman
The formerly deeply pro-segregation Senator and chairman of the armed services committee
Rota forward for the book
This was because course I would been in
Strom Thurmond
From March 1963 to December 1964
And from February 1973 to July 1970 or 1974
So strong through Manu the guy and he had some respect for him
Unfortunately for strong Corso ratfuck Tim
Strom Thurmond rotate glowing forward for the book but when the book was actually released
He got super embarrassed and he had to issue the following statement
Quote I regret the forward that I wrote in comment on Colonel Corso's professional life that is now.
Is part of a book that professes to reveal the US government's shocking UFO cover-up
I know of No Such coverup and I do not believe one exist
Strom Thurmond
Don't regret segregation
Super regret
Vespa
Later life you might have
Itsfunneh
Guy who has Aid
Like
Turned around strawderman Dover level
After the time that he would have been at Roswell
Working on this alien technology and the two of them know each other well enough that Corso
Yeah would be able to ask
For forwards for his book twenty years later
They don't know each other well enough to know that like one of them worked with aliens
It's it's weird
Almost like that probably wasn't part of his backstory when he work for some tournament
Maybe just like
Came up later
You want to write a book
Maybe he was running out of ideas and I was trying to put somebody on his fiction book and they were like
Interested money was like well guess what I'm a colonel and I've got an interesting life story and they're like cool
I also read some reviews of this book that were from people who
Alien Believers and UFO researchers
Other like this book
Out-of-left-field
This is not good that's nice
That's nice even people who are pro alien think it's not great
Did it strong like covering things up
Really think that statement
If you wrote the forward then that would suggest he knew what was in it
Antenna
Yeah in the book
And for the cover-up to make sense
He would have to
Have Nots
I mean it doesn't make sense for it to be a cover-up it makes total sense that this guy who has his aide asked him on the
Understanding that it's an autobiography
Book but it already written the forwards or just put it on there
And then now they had to remove it
This is
The Occam's razor f****** test of Champions right here there's just no other explanation
So look
Kennedy
What
Which John still president or the one in secretly
The one who was president
Until he got assassinated
Lot of people have a lot of ideas
About why
Kennedy got assassinated
I'm still shirt
Positive it was DiMaggio
Well
You're wrong
It was somebody
But it had to do with aliens
In fact this was why
Kennedy
Impart was
Skilled
Because she was going
Reveal
This enemy that we were dealing with
Information
Russian I have
From Captain Mark Ritchie
Among others
As well as
That
Incidents that I've been
Historically
Recorded
I've been recorded without the alien
Element
Alien element in those
Is very
Real
That includes the Bay of Pigs going back
Black goo that is
Is found in
ICarly science
Who killed themselves
Bizarre ways
Form of Art
Human body
Which I believe
Is actually going back
To the graphene
Dockside and
Similarities
That black goo may I
Grady gredients
Katzkin
The current covid
At least some of the
This again
There's a black goo in the covid
I do like it when everything just starts
The pictures coming
Clear man now the black goo is part of the covid thing it all makes sense out
It's venom
The black Google Now that I saw Let There Be Carnage
So he was assassinated right because he was going to reveal that were fighting aliens wear
And
And then in the 80s there was some scientists
Thunder
Suspicious circumstances and that choosing the black guy who was involved with that
This is part of the sci-fi movie where we get a montage of like pictures throughout
American history where they're like
Erase all the aliens in it
Alien shaking hands with j
Standing behind a recovery doing all that stuff like I just watched all the ER they washed all the pictures clear
Yeah that definitely is also the part of the science fiction movie where I'm starting to get bored
I mean I need a good hit of something I did I need you to give me a bump
This is wearing off about an hour and 45 and sequence right now
Let's see if we can get one
And when you go back
Back to the Falkland
Once were you find out that was
To war with
Alien race
Over this
And then you also find out
The oil spill
In the Gulf
Is also
Another
Attacked by aliens
The whole thing
And so on
Yep
But Goku eats the bottoms of our boats and so much more
Mischievous sounding when they are evil
Eating the bottoms of boats
So many things that they do that the evidence of
Is just kind of an inconvenience
I understand that oil looks like black dude
It does
I've seen the pictures of them cleaning Birds
It's very VSCO
CSS
Does this mean that all oil spills are just black goo attacks from Aliens
If so
You're letting off
Industry you're letting off the oil industry
I quite nicely
It is
It is really fast
Donating to me that they
Never include
The titans of Industry within their
Conspiracy theories
She's name but they don't know the CEO of Exxon they do was depicting over
Quite recently
Axons Embassy Ozawa love those people have been around you could have learned their names for years and they're the
The ones who are killing everybody why are they behind the black Goku
Conspiracy
What's finding work with Exxon let's get all the bad guys
Just wanted to get the oil from point A to point B
But you know you got to give it up to Exxon Bay really don't work with Haley
Also the Falklands War was a knot
About alien technology.
I want to say is alienate it wasn't
No no the reason that you saying that is that there were the alien or the UFO files
Slippery released by the UK
And there's one dimension from like a memo in 1982 or something like that
Let's sightings have gone down since the Falkland War something that's being extrapolated
Solid
Stuff that
Sounds right to me
So we want to split.
Scary spelling out why she made this video thank God I really need an explanation
I think it's a warning
Is that what it is well that's not refusing to say but I think it was
Okay I mean
I don't be a cyborg
I can I'm kind of fine with cyborg
I don't know what the difference would be again
Sitting here right now
There is no test that I could do
Prove
Or disprove that I am a cyborg
Possibly it would make no difference
Here's a parting shot
I think it's very important
Humanity start
Widened
The dialogue
And
This
Killer video my urge
Is
Because there are certain
People such as
Trump
And 107
To our kind of
Leading
A certain portion of America
Standing up
Against
Communist
Of America
Standing up against
The board
Taekook
Of America
That
I'm trying
Who's out there
So that people
Dolemite
Hoodoo follow some of that
From Trump and
You're one
And the White House
You know encourage them to start
Talking on
Hirelevel
To stop
Dominant
Down
Down to
You know
Repetitively
I have bad news
The repetitive religious transfer all they're going to do that's all they want to do
Their favorite thing
Yeah when you want subs to
Since they don't have it
Right and this isn't substance also very clear about that
She has it it's it's pretty common among a lot of folks
Like in the Trump various Trump World
Whether it's Alex
Straight up qanon
It's been read
Queen the line
I never decided
That Trump agrees entirely with them so crazy how it works
He's just holding back
I'm saying all the things that they believe to be true
Because he has to in order to wait for the great reveal or whatever the day that the storm will be upon us
They're so convinced
Did Trump is speaking in code
And signalling to them
That they are now I even carry
Is that a point where she's fed up with
Them not coming out and just saying
Hey it's aliens
Patxi's working with aliens trying to put goo in you
Yep 2:30 would do it cyborg
It's kind of sad
It's and it's
It's
Really sad
Because it's not like it's some stranger who came out of nowhere
Trump
Has a
Thoroughly
Obscenely documented pattern of behavior that is maintained consistent
Since
Birth
Yeah
So every conspiracy theory ultimately revolves around him having been lying the
Entire time to make up for a large amount of
Backstory that we've got everything around there was one
First Trump Tower was built
So fun
Good connection
Yeah
Yeah this is
I would like for someone to give a unified conspiracy theory of trump
Biography like I would really like to see someone try and thread that needle I think it would be tough
But it would be fun impossible
Which was which is why would be fun yeah probably I just have one thing to say I think
I think
That
And this is just making a blanket statement you can take it as you will
I think
A podcast co-host and really all podcast co-host
Should be a lot quieter
And they shouldn't interrupt anywhere near as much as they do I think it's really annoying
Well I mean frankly they're just kind of
I all too often they try to make the show about that you know and that's I think something that should change
Yeah it all podcast it is time
Bit someone
Well I appreciate appreciate that sentiment night
I hope that the world takes that to heart could be coming from a more appropriate sauce
I think they should have a lot more self-awareness
I think that's a big issue
I wish you a safe trip I wish you would not
Macron
For a while now on holiday like Roman Holiday
Add something oh, Chrome and holiday do we work with that
And if she'll episode
Those just a bummer
Repetitive nonsense about Alex's Behavior
I feel like that would have been
Sour Spirits all around fantastic Dan you are a Kind and Generous fellow I try to do the best I
Also
The premise of the show
Will be back on the other end of your vacation
But until then Jordan wave website
Go to bed Jordan but until then I'm really on dzx.
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color