Alexandra Thurston color
We are novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
I would I would so much more prefer that I was
Edwards podcast
My boy Nick Rolex
Strawberry with Jiffy Lube
Here's the deal
Time I felt it was time for a hard reboot
We need to go back to zero
No good
I just bring in like I don't know a durian good luck
I was actually hoping to bring it to the drive across but that was never going to have never going to happen I don't have access
Any scared children
Children
Hey Jordan you know what you know what doesn't
Scare the children
I'll tell you what doesn't
Donator
A couple today
Give a shout out to what's going on
Welcome board
Welcome aboard Andrew
Marty Stuart
You are officially a policy wonk
Congratulations
If you would like to become a policy wonk yourself
You may do so by
Support the show link
And donating
But
If you do soon we will have a password portion of the website
They will have all sorts of goodies
Maybe a Jordan block who knows who knows
Kind of suspect I won't be getting
Baltimore
Grandfathered into the policy walk considering the fact that
Before we could offer any just went ahead and donated and God bless him
Thank you very much
Jones of Marty DeRosa
Indeed
I appreciate everybody
There will be a backlog
Episodes of that and new episodes
Just coming out periodically
Invite password protected areas
So if you want to hear
I wanted to I wanted to
Dislike it just to be
Dick cuz he worked on it
I understand.
I hate what I do
You know what else is garbage what we're going to talk about today
You are the matter
Amancio Ortega
Perfect
So today we are back in the present we're in 2017 we're going to go over favorite place
We're going to go over
Episode
Unfortunately I had when I was
I was only able to get about
Like stuff from
In the first hour and a half
Cancel the show
Caveat
The folks
I miss the past
I am Joy
I enjoy be episode where we go back to
To2015 way more
More it's less painful cuz it's
It's almost nostalgic now
Anticipation there's excitement of what are we going to do
Discover
Are we going to find
Steven unlocks The Alex Jones propaganda box
Where is now I mean like
We're just going to listen to him rationalize
What's going to happen on this episode
Make excuses for the trumps anymore
Crabby
What else what else could he do like
Just bail on the whole thing like
Like no like strawberry soda style hard on YouTube
Never speak of it again
I think
Europe
You have gone way too far
He could do that but I think they're going to
To be lingering consequence
He's done in the last
Yeah but his
His way of surviving is going to be
He can't
He can't turn against against
He's got to pull up Sandy Hook
Play
Look we just have debates about Trump
Five years from now that's going to be his story
Debative
I I sucked his info.
That's his way of saying he's not promoting infowar
I know it hasn't worked out the way we wanted
But that's because he was corrupt he touch the touch the glowing orb
I told him not to
Rockefeller building map
Orbs have power
I do believe the dorms have power but globalist believe that they do and there for you after a
Play It Again store
There's a recording of a phone conversation
Between Alex
Drop
Night
Don't you dare touch that or it's just the middle of the night
Trump doesn't take out the cat
Answering machine to one with the tape
About orb Runs Out
Picks up a goddamn it
Just want to reiterate about the or
All right got to go love you
Let's get to it Jordan
What's the Jump Right In This is how Alex Jones
What's the show
On
I have total proof
Put this entire attack on Donald Trump jr.
Is a total hoax
Because it's the end for them
They're losing control
That's a Republican
Don't cares about Joe Scarborough
Also let me ask you this
She's f****** one gives a s*** about
The very next time the Republicans are like
You heard Alex start the show by saying he has
Total proof
Let me ask
Do you think
Key.
You know what
Because
I'm a dreamer
You can get deported
You better not say that on the public broadcast
Entertain the fans
Total proof
Bach
Wow I
For those of you like I can't imagine who you might be
Doesn't know what this is about Donald Trump
That's the best thing you could do you are woefully uninformed
The New York Times David Brooks's win the New York Times
I'm not saying that he should be a negative thing should happen
Through the cause of other
Doing it
Karma is real
He will choke to death
On a regular burger
Prosciutto
No
I call him was the definition of gauche
I use that sort of blurry
Krowd
Arco
Trump jr.
Is really dumb
And there's no way around that
He
Was involved in a meeting back in July
I believe the right July
I Got Stripes
Fourth of June
Who cares
And
The key release
The email
That set up this meeting
The New York Times
Washington Post
We're going to
They already had access to them through the Xbox
I am released
These emails
They are corresponding
It's between him and a gentleman by the name of Rob Goldstone
Who is the publicist
For a Russian
Recording artist
Named amen
Who's is an oligarch
We live in a cloud basically
His dad is that an oligarch who is very rich
Is a close associate of both
Putin and Donald Trump
Yeah so do junior get this email
From Rob Goldstone
And conveniently Alex Jones Fox News
Don't
Actually talk about what
In the email
Feel like
It's very important
Nope so here I will read it
Here
So we will be above all the
Good morning
Eamon just called
And asked me to contact you with something very interest
The crown prosecutor of Russia which apparently is the real possess
Baby basically
The crown prosecutor of Russia
His father ARIS
This morning
And
In their meeting offered to provide the Trump campaign with some official documents
Information that would incriminate Hillary
And her dealings with Russia and be very useful to your father
This is obviously very high-level and sensitive information
But is part of Russia and the government
Supportive for mr. Trump
Helped Along by Eros
What do you think is the best way to handle this information
And would you be able to speak to
Batman about it directly
Now the important piece
Is
This is obviously very high-level and sensitive information
But is a
The part of Russia and government support for mr. Trump
That part is been cut out of Fox News that little Chiron
Where they have like
Yeah
Where
Like that's amazing thing for them to do where it's like
We have the first part of the
And then the last part of the
At least
At least try
Anymore
Donald Trump
Junior right back I'm on the road at the moment
I just speak to Eman first
Seems we have
Sometime in
If it's what you say I love it
Especially later in the summer
Why because that would be the time when it's more politically damaging
Call First
Thing next week when I'm back
So they write
A little bit
Schedule a call
Here we go I can get down that does were on June
Emails
I don't juice
At 4:20
P.m.
Schedule a meeting with you and the Russian government
Attorney who's flying over
For Moscow for this
This Thursday
I believe you're aware of the meeting
I'm still wondered is 3 p.m. or later on Thursday works for you
I assumed it would be at your office
Donald Trump jr. rights back
How about
3 at our office
Thanks Rob I appreciate you helping
Set it up
So
The issue out nail so right back into the great it'll like
Sleepy Paul manafort
My brother-in-law and me and then give the address
Threats
Palmetto Ford
The address
It's at Trump
You know where it is you checked in on Facebook you dumb dumb
Really comes up about this
Is
In this email
Caltrain
Rob Goldstone make
Perfectly clear
But this is about
The government's
The Russian
Support of Donald Trump
Campaign and the person you'd be meeting with is
Is a government lawyer
Or a lawyer connected with the government
So
Let's take
Everything out of the equation
Let's say worse
Case scenario
This is a democratic
Plot it's a globalist plot
Let's just say that for me to set up Donald Trump jr.
Once again my Narrative of course
Is that Obama
Is the reason we have in order to punish white people for all the things that they did
Got robbed Goldstone
These emails to Donald Trump jr.
Is no Russian lawyer
Do it himself because Obama
Is Brillion
Through at least 45 channels of plausible deniability
Obama used
Signal
You can't get my emails
At the very least
It's like George George George
Speaking in the Royal Oak
Pluralism
The Entity known as Obama Obama
Cutouts
Donald Trump Jr probably committed a crime
Even
There is no other person on the other end of this
Broke because he
What he indicated
Willingness
To accept
Confidential information
Empower guys are less
Gullible
Donald Trump
The further problem
I would say the bigger issue is
That there's timestamps on this
You can trace back what was going on around
The campaign
Yeah and
June 7th
During the afternoon
Formalize
This meeting that they were going to have
Next week
I'm going to lay out
The truth about Hillary
That can't be
If you could that be
It lays out the truth about Hillary
Further
Because it's
Timestamp
On
And the third
And because
Is Jared Kushner
Are all day
But they can really claim
At any point
Ask them they didn't know that the Russian government
Had a preference
For Donald Trump to be
But were they BCC
How are these people
Email dude I mean the the biggest thing for me is that
You know there is awareness that is
Solidified
They have to know that the Russian government wants
And that makes every statement
No idea alive
I passed that point
And because they have
Consistently lied weather is
Or
In public
Speeches
Every time they lied is an opportunity for blackmail to
To be created by Vladimir Putin
Any other hostile entity may be a mop
Of some sort that has ax
Information
Consortium
Coast might be the frontman for maybe laundering money for
Crazy f***** up stuff
And it's
Not a hoax
The park
Might want to focus on
He might be able to dance hope circles around the reality
And it's
It's Donald Trump jr. release these email
It's dark pink
This isn't some sort of like
He said she said
Sources say
Straight from him
Right
No it is here's my
My question
The emails were coming
Junior
Is he actually stood
Stupid for release
Bring them himself
Like cuz that's the that's a bit on Twitter it's like
Could you be to release these emails
Coming out
I don't know I don't know enough legally to know if it was smart or not I have no idea
But I do think
Just being involved in this sort of s*** make
Oh yeah
What is a dump
Insanity
But I don't know
I mean
I guess that there's some sort of power you can take him being able to direct the narrative
A little bit
Succeeded in doing that
I don't know
I don't I don't know I just
For some reason
In my head reading this
Reading this whole story
The part of people
Clowning on Junior
For releasing it
Nothing silly to me
Maybe even better
Maybe even
More stupid for him
Is that if he
The New York Times
Then they still have your
This is bulshit
New York
Selfish
There's no anti-media narrative
You like they're always
Anything to take us exactly lose a lot of Leverage
They made it up that was the single dumbest thing I've
I think I've ever seen
C90
New York time
Games to come out with it
You give the pro Trump media the crnkovich is in the world
Much more to work
Exactly as you'll see
They don't have a ton to work with on this
And Alex's got to do a lot of
Right let's get to the next clip
Is human
Candy machine
Still don't know what that is
It's pretending that he doesn't really understand what this is about
Well if you look for
Every time they give us another Russia nothingburger
It doesn't matter how many internal videos we have from CNN MSNBC
Not recycling
Beauty pageant
Last July
They just keep recycling the same
647 nothing burgers
If we had Donald Trump jr.
Missile secrets to China or Russia
I would say
Basically arrest him
Okay well at least we go to Baseline
Could be used against you
Bios later Alex I will be counting the number of
I think the switch that I play
Because he doesn't know
I think it was somebody higher up from the project Veritas video
Said that Russia was a nothing
Burger
In one of their heavily edited behind the scenes
Expose that are inaccurate
Should never be believed
You've been sued
Successfully for defrauding people
Still not enough
Yeah
This is
Alex loves
This like
This
Okay
Here's why
So f****** boring
I know all his tricks already
Like
Because the most exciting time in the history of American dolls at
Time where we
No longer be
Survive
Already and it's
It's just not
Like I like to learn
For while we were sort of getting
Engaging with Alex
I'm figuring out what's going on and researching
Wingstop
I'm sort of getting a sense for his little tricks
And the one you did fairies like they just keep recycling stories
Recycling not necessarily stories
Tactic
Cuz this is the same thing you did with the Jeff sessions
Right
The same story recycled
A couple months ago
The stories story was lying on his
Exactly
Music this is the same story was Donald Trump who also committed
Are cranes real
Okay
Good
Nope nope
This is a political Grand Theft Auto
What he's doing there is
Harkening back
Do a little
Trick a little story
But he tells of like they're just recycling stuff
As a wave
To harken back
To what he made that argument
Before
And there's familiarity in his audiences mind
Rhetorically asked
Smart butt
The same time
It's not at all cuz he doesn't
Actually say what the stories are
He's pretending that everyone is making
A big deal out of
Russia Russia
She's already cover
And already spun
So that
He's basically lowering his work
Yeah
Very hard
Yeah it's being credit
But it is
Trump went over to Russia to do a beauty pageant
But the bunch
Oh yeah that that is his like way of not dealing
Pete on the lake
Well he's not going to use that as a way to
Bowflex from the Steele dossier
He's going to use that as like
Not really
It's very little about
Is
And that's the reason that I got all that
Without
You know the shift ran
Got all that noticeability but nobody's talking about how
He's drunk off of
It's exactly the same thing
But who cares
It'll it'll come
To be real
The other has got to do is
Because this story
If taken at face value isn't
Difficult
To argue
Right very difficult
What you have to do is you have to attack
The players involved
So Alex
Does big motifs
Operandi is to
I used the wrong word there let's say with his bit his tactic is to attack the lawyer
The Russian lawyer that was in the meat
I like
I like that
Okay because
Combines
Rusev
Sure
People over 50
Play it's still like in their hearts
Right
Is
Essentially
A blameless
Most likely
In a little bit more down the road but
CR Alex
Is First Take On Me
He starts by talking about
The difference
Between globalist
And
Astarte's
Okay
With this Russian lawyer turned out is sucked up with the Kremlin
It's true this Russian lawyer
Irrigation dirt on Hilary but didn't
Infowars.com
Right now
Not once
But at least twice out front
Russian light sign
Part of the George soros-funded operation
So I say it right
Alex is never will
Say it right
One X information
From Fortune
Which is great
Always a great
Source of anonymous very fact
Checked in for May
Love me some memes
But
Histamine
Even a machine there are pictures
Of her
Like the women's March
Stuff like that
I don't know what that mean
I don't I don't know but Alex
Seem to not
Be thrilled with her
First Amendment right
Yeah he's not a big fan
I don't understand what's the what's the problem with her being at a protest
What's the problem
Like the pictures that I can
Can find it they aren't really dated or time
Necessarily
As much as they are the woman's March
So if she's interested in women's issues
It is
Wants to
Speak her piece on that
That's not
In anyway invalidating of her being a Russian lawyer
Like
George Soros operative just because you went to the women's March I went to the women's March
I mean
Do you have to be anti
I didn't actually go to work
I forgot I went to
Sorry
Play blood-borne
I don't want to claim I did something I didn't you not being able
I'm the new meme machine
The women's March
Is
Not necessarily
Entirely
No
It covers the entire Jeep
Hayward
Have open shoulders
It's
Being tired
All the all the time I think so
Sing there is just putting her at the
90%
Male audio
Obelisk
It is like
PetSmart from his
Him talking to
Who is audien
So it's a very smart thing when you ever like
Indoctrinated dumb old white
Unit had right on the nail
Alright
You have the the
Deeply embedded
Subconscious vs. phobia
You have the knee-jerk instinct
Who support Trump
Defend him
And think that the media is lying
To you
I don't I don't f****** know if this is the women's March or an anti-trump March
And either way
Women with their tops off
Electrical tape on their titties
America I want to live in
Was Donald jr. setup
Thirsty dozens and dozens of email exchanges
It's not.
The Russians and physically
That's what Hollywood
What what what
So I agree with half of the end of that sin
Okay
Alright
But you
He's not
A secret agent
You know like
This is where Alex's narrative is completely bonkers
And based on some weirdo spy fantasy
Donald Trump jr.
No business
Searching out a playing spy games
He has no business to do that
If I f******
Agent of a foreign power
That is hostile to our interest
Clearly
I mean
Took like
Last week
They just took
A couple miles
Of Georgia
They just Annex
A couple miles
South Georgia
Coupon for fun galeno we're not going to do anything
Country Georgia
Randomly a couple Farmers houses how long before they're taken Ark
Won't be long
It won't be long
I want peaches
Hey There Delilah on junior is that
Is like James Bond
Yeah
He's basically the James Bond
Play by Woody Allen
Do you remember that one
Yeah exactly
The one that was just a whack you like
Sellers David Niven
Meaning of the Pink Panther
Blake Edwards
AccuWeather
Anyone should be playing behind it
All of these
There's no doubt about it
Caper
Comedy of errors
But I like
If you get this order thing you get
I'm not saying this as if any of our listeners are going to
To get this kind of offer but
You called
I got to check this out for myself
Cuz you're not prepared
You're going to
Get fool
Course you are
You keep repeating info.
So
Call Scott
Before
Republican candidates
Because of course
Republican
Align with
Call the FBI
People used to America
People believing that even if I lose an election
I still believe in the rule
Now let me also be clear
If Alex Jones is a narrative is correct
And this lady was setting up.
Lovely still committed a crime
That's not been tricked by the globalist
Does he not bleed green
Green alien blood
So I mean
This is not a solid defense
Because it doesn't really get the
Criminal Intent
Out of the equation
You still going there thinking he's going to get information
It's not entrapment
Even if it were like
Some sort of Outlaw game
They're not doing making him do anything he's not
I'm flying to do to begin with
Can't be
Rush there still
But the other thing
That I realized
The first until I read over the emails a couple time
Is the waves this Rob goats
Stone phrases
This is part of
Russian government
Support of Donald Trump
Campaign
The way you phrase is it is very tall Society
There's already an understanding
Between the two of them
We all know Russia support
What's Trump
So to me that I mean it's
That probably wouldn't hold up in a court of law
But
Like
Grammatically
Text what they're saying
Taking the piss
Pieces out of it
It really tells me that even before June
Of 26
16 everyone
Together
That's really f***** up that's going to be a bigger problem
And of course that's why I was just want to bring up that sense
So that's that
Big
Census f*****-up
To imagine that that is not
Complete
Undeniable proof
I don't know if it's necessarily trees
Cuz I don't know if you're willing
The trees you can do trees in anytime you want
Alright
Where did the like literally hanging by the neck until
I know there's not a lot of Preston
Denton modern times
Anyway
Like I said
For us not to watch
No
That's on you man
I'm going to I'm going to stay out of this
So you make the argument
Yeah but this is incredibly difficult
Context of this email
The surrounding
Things that happen
The end of the speech Trump gave that day
The fact that
Infowars
Trump started eating out
Hillary's going down
Kind of things right around this.
Right
Noah
Which previously
They had never
Which is an important
Not.
She's going down but this is what the beginning of Hollow Creek prediction exactly
Two things which indicate
Like we know something
But be that as it may
Difficult to make an argument about that it
That's not
So Alex
Decides to go up
Very bizarre
In terms of Justice
He starts
Using
Trump
Speech that he gave where he asked
Russia to hack Hillary Clinton
Wait
That's his defense
Yeah yeah
Invite
Yeah is the way you defend against your son
Committing
I think what he's trying to get
But
I don't want to put words in his mouth so let's just hear his his version of
I get to a clip of Donald Trump
A little less
Thanks
Meeting for 15 minutes 20 minutes
Russian lawyer who promised have dirt on Hillary
Opposition research
At a press conference
Nothing about Russia
But also
It's not true all of those
Categorically
I don't care who's got the email
Who's God
Directions
Releasing
They've been proven not to be illegal
Trash
That is incredibly stupid
But also
He didn't say digital dropbox
I am so mad
It's right there that's like him talking about Colorado Springs not saying space command
So
Bility inputting microfiche
Or secret plans inside McDonald's wrappers and throwing them
But
McDonald's
Sure throwing away class
Innocently
That brings up a whole host of
Questions that I need answers
Did you order
Do you like the pies what are we talkin
The attorney for the MacDonald rapper guy
Can say with reasonable certainty that I've never put anything that wasn't McDonald's related in a McDonald's bag
Then throw it away
McDonough
King stuff into a McDonald's bag.
To throw it away
Treason
Here's the thing that I love
Here's the thing that I thought
Is
Is so kind of
What am I
When he threw the phrase opposition
Research and I'm glad you picked up on that
Completely normal eyes
The problem is that it doesn't
No of course
Because getting
Opposition research
From foreign powers hostile foreign powers
He's also illegal because foreign entities are not allowed
To donate
The campaign
Add donations don't just come in money
They also coming
And kind and useful thing
No no no
Legally they do not
Okay so it was about like a golden cat
Does that count
If you were to what about a nice meal
Is he
If you were to receive
Opposition
Research from
A Kremlin
Connected
Would be breaching
Campaign Finance
Laws
So there is a
No problem
Even with phrasing it like that
So
If you're listening to
That gives
Is opposition
Research
Which implies that everybody
False equivalence
Between the Steele dossier
Opposition research
You say dirty.
Fortnite
Use that as a false equivalence like it was Hillary Clinton
Going abroad to try and get up
Things that
U.s. government
Which is what your
You're supposed to do. Democratic opposition research
It began
As I recalled
Like
The Republican
Candidates
It's all Republic
Temperature
But her email
This is still on the trumps
Each being adjusted
While
Memory
Until they play up on that when it was a Democrat
Communist
Partially
Walmart
Tens of millions dead
What comes around goes around
Karma
You reap what you sow
Alex Jones
Obici Donald jr. did in private
What is Father did publicly the search for truth
All the search for truth
Opposition research
Search for truth
Indiana Jones
And
The Holy Grail
I love when Alex Jones gets lost in a metaphor like with the illness
Metaphor that he had there
Hey cuz he doesn't know how to really connect sauce
What's really well
Got it
Globalist
I've got better but gave it to
That's a man who
Experienced a lot of her
What goes around comes around Karma
Come up with four ways to say the same thing
Africa
Learning is
Jesus wear a hat
You're going out don't catch
Cold
If you're going to bumblebee ready to rumble
Has more to say in his next clip about
That clip
Playing it
You give some
Fairly was unwise,
Along the way
Trump
World Junior
New hires
Looking back
Call one
It's just a total deflection
It is so far-fetched it's so ridiculous
Russia has no respect for our country
Countries and competitors
It's a
Disrespect
Country
And the leaders
I hope you're able to
Emails
AR press
Pure instincts of a thoroughbred Real McCoy Americana.
Yikes
What is that mean
I don't know it was a string of words
Americana
Dyed-in-the-wool
I might be adding ones myself
Listen to his interviews
I don't listen to
And you forcing me to listen
Makes me very angry
I understand what is
Makes me want
To rip off my skin
It is brutal just listening to him
Almost everything he said there is a lot but the other one of the reasons I wanted to
Keep that
Is that there is still
Making a big deal out of the like sort of the idea that he has like
Like a neurodegenerative
Situation
He does sound a lot more coherent than he does in
Any of the interviews that he's done recently
I don't know if that's evidence of anything but he's
Certainly able to
Mostly makes
Sentences and I'm sure it's more like
Stress-related
Degenerative
Or it could just be
He doesn't like doing the job
People hating in this
Doesn't like
He's just filled with
Anger and rage
Pull it out
He knows he can't throw that out in an interview
So he does that thang like
You know how sometimes when you're so angry
You start to cry
Can't really
Handle your words sort of
Alright well
Baby
Maybe I'm an angry guy there there's no evidence
Listen to anything
Yeah
The other thing I wanted to bring up is the idea
Just loves it
I love that Alex
The interview and he's like
Junior said he could have done it.
Would you like
Mistakes were made
What in the hell
Could you have done that differently
Call the FBI
Have a good indication
That there's a reason why they would have never called the
FBI
But
Do you think I love
Is Alex is like
Know what you should done is that God damn right we're talkin to the Russians
Is totally fine
With the idea
That they are
Working with her
They working
Subconsciously a lot of it is Rippling through
Hold back
The damn a little bit
Whenever he starts yelling
It shows it shows those through feeling
I like I don't really give a shih
Is there working with them I hate Hillary
So much
I think
She
Kill children
It's it's not
He's losing his ability
To pretend he doesn't know thing
Things by the day
That's why I like coming out
In advance for a little bit saying like
Well
Is collusion bad like that
Those are trial balloons
Next clip
Alex Jones a little bit of to about what the Russian narrative is
Which is pretty fun
He gets Tucson
Harry does Sakura
But then it gets
Some scary news
Staring
You'll find out
Tabitha Russian
Hillary's in bad weather
Company
I know you are but what am I
7 Ways to Sunday
And George Soros
Audi
DoubleDown
That's not what you're saying
Kohl's
You just hoped
And say
At the Federal Election Commission was no proof
Brewskis
I get it from our audience if everybody knows it
So the issue there is that
There have been some indications that Mueller's
Investigation will have to do with
Yeah absolutely
7 fluidscape
Has been
And a large portion of that is
YouTube ivy
Pro Trump alright
Ding dong
So there was an article a while back
About that about wars and Drudge
Breitbart
May become part of the scope of the investigation
Inasmuch
As they
Far
Mirroring
Russian talking
Disseminating Russian propaganda
It seems relevant
The investigation
Now there was an article
What came out the other day and washing
Examiner
Which is a dog
They were talking about how she article from a couple months ago
I didn't
The FEC might be revisiting
Is Alex Jones taken that as medication
He is under federal investigation
Spinning it like that to make himself a Vic
Read what the other
Piece of it is
He's saying
That
It's about them getting
Paid by the rush
Cuz he knows that that isn't a charge that
He can
Beat
So he's like oh they're saying that I'm getting money from the Russian
I mean is it a charger
I'd love to get a look at his finances don't get me wrong I'm willing to believe that he has a
Received any direct
Money from Russia
Anything like that
I think
Varmour Vicki's beholden to
Russian propaganda
Give
Not necessarily
Because
He is
Giving marching orders but
Because of those
Because of that
He has
To be getting
Positive
Feedback
Uncertain
Thanks
He's going to lean into that
In order to get
Right if you got bot Farms that are giving you a
Huge boost
Every time you repeat Russian
Propaganda
You don't necessarily know that's
You're doing the same way
Right now MSNBC is getting higher ratings
Because they're going after
Seth rich
They're lying and making up bulshit
Everybody's
Canobie Lake
Mickey Mouse
Yeah now the other piece that we have to take into account is
Prior
And that's super important
So
I am unwilling to believe
That this is
The first time
That Donald Trump Junior has been offered information
From a Russian
Source
Or some
Resource like that
Okay
I flatly refuse to believe that this is the only time that's ever happen
And if we go back
Just a couple bucks
On the Alex Jones Show
Alex Jones revealed on air
But his source
Mike cernovich has doors for inside information
Was Donald Trump
So if that's the case
He is being fed
Straight pipeline
Propaganda
Donald Trump jr. is getting
From these Russians
He's only like
Two stages removed
M-theory
The direct
Spigot of propaganda
And that's
Junior
Giving it to them
And then yeah
There's a massive problem
Agent
Yeah they're only two steps
Remove trim cap
Slipping on Aaron saying that is
Incredibly important
Like that
Bucked up
Down
Nobody's getting charged with a crime because
Because the only the only way to get these people charged
Crime is FB FBI
Are the FBI
Listening
Like they would have
To take it upon themselves
To arrest
All of the
And that is beyond
What I think they're capable of
If the power is still
Consolidated amongst
The GOP who in the same way that
Weather in Brazil
Tamara was
Caught on tape
Offering bribes
To get the corruption investigation
To go away we just went to prison
Notes
Oh I'm sorry
President-trump
2002 to 2000
He's the one who is installed by the Brazilian oligarch
After
Taking down
And so the only reason that Tamara still
Is because
All of the people who run the government
Have a vested
Interested
Because he's going to keep
Keep them from going
Great
You know the GOP
Get rid of
Is because
He's really the only one who's going to keep
You keeping them go to jail in the same
He is the reason that they would be going
Complicit
Right
People want to say like
Take over and he's going to be
More evil and and
But he's going to be a better States
If Pence takes over
He should go to jail too
Leggett they're all
We need a Sunkist
Strawberry soda style hard reboot on the government
Quite frankly
No probably not
We're going to be in trouble
Oh yeah
I got a phone call
Lexus
Good so
It's good to switch from hopelessness to a fun little
I would like
To point out before this clip gets played that I believe that the mess
Spying isn't it
Bixby address
It is a real thing
Absolutely
Alex Jones podcast
Exposed as a fraud the Memoirs are destroying their ratings go from almost nothing to just
Almost
Opposite
Question
Outside
Call the National Security Agency under Obama
With a giant legal
Thousands of people
Pyles office when they left
Just a snapshot
I'm a few thousand public figures
Michael Savage
Alex Jones Donald Trump
What do they all have in common
Those are all numbers
A phone number that I had a landline
Number
Alex Jones's office number
My private
Phone number
6 years ago under Obama
Turn on list
They're listening because they know I'm exposing their Criminal
Info
If you'd like to know why I am
Dancing in the studio
But listening to Alex Jones
Go back to the store episode about that information the game from jail
Crock of s***
All of that is
That is so stupid
It looks like
The emails came from Kush
It looks like it is a internal setup
That sort of situation
Sheriff arpaio's Dennis Montgomery related Dragon isn't real
It's based on an elaborate fraud that we got to the bottom of Google Search
Eventually find
This is why I'm so bored
Valex in the present
He's getting so lazy
Like there's just all these things that we've already looked into
Can you brings in the Montgomery s***
We're talk about for 3 hours
But you haven't heard that episode bill doesn't do it I've never been prouder of myself
All this other stuff
Anyone that app
Yeah all this other stuff is like misinterpreting current stuff
That's boring
It just all these old tricks an old narratives repurpose
I think
The larger problem is
Lazy
It said he does
If you don't have anything to go on
Right there's no there's no other end
So because
His wagon
Before before he got on the Trump
He's got
Everything
Yeah
He can talk about whatever you want
But now that he's there
He is under constant
To kind of pull this.
He's always defending
Damn
Come from a place of
I am fighting back
I'm always
Defensive
There
Where else
Do you go like what other narrative
Non-religious everything's got to be related to got to do these like pedophiles
Too but also
Stupid
If I was if I was
Just you know whatever you know what I realized I think I think I kind of got to pick
Picture of what Alex Jones is
Business
Model is
Like nocturnes what his finances are I'm still very curious
About that
If you go back to like the 2015 stuff that we're going over
I kind of notice of
Pattern
Of false
Prediction that he knows are false
Like the Purple Penguin stuff
He's saying that there's this
Gay rights
Organization that is trying to outlaw the use of the words boy and girl mother and father
That's what he says
He knows that that's never going to happen and that's not what people are asking for
But he knows that his audience is dumb and it keeps
Quicksand their mind they're tall Purple Penguin
Yeah these f****** dumb liberals around it
So when it doesn't happen
Use of boy and girl is still legal
He gets to be like I did that
Because we brought awareness to it
I did
The it's just I attached
You can't because it's setup
It's all set up
When he starts doing the narrative he knows
How it's going to
And I think
In the case of like the
Them saying that I'm being federally investigated
Another one of those
He knows he's not actually being investigated for
Getting money from Russia
Or whatever
He can claim a victory for a false battle that he could have and I think on some level
Maybe a big score in his mind
Like obviously I don't think he thought he was going to win
I think that it was a lie
Trump can win
The globalists are going to not let him win
That that was the narrative
Then he sets up an advance
This would be like
If people really did Outlaw door
Boy and girl
Like what would you do at that
That's a good question
Did Trump getting elected is like one of his failed marriages actually coming through
World of his own design
Very unpleasant
Yeah so long as so long as he fights imaginary battles
He always wins
Bedtime
Caught in a real fight
He does not know how to do that
No.
I don't actually
Thank you.
Charlie Brown
Is a cake by metaphorical win
2 b
Just pretend
Threat
I'm serious about Alex I don't have clips of it but
Show earlier this week I think I was on Monday
He
Keeps talking about
Monty Python and the Holy Grail
And he's the Knight who gets his limbs
You said Monty Python
Entire movies
I know every lie
He calls that night
A knight who says me
Absolutely absolutely
I refuse to accept that
Like to say me want a Shrubbery and then he gets his leg cut off
How dare you
Are you out in 15 years
With your transphobia
Nigel farage
The movie again
Can't watch that movie
Very anti apologize
What is pro Joseph Watson
Is white Nash
This next
Clip
Alex Jones wants to
To tell you
You
You want to tell you why Trump
What is B is the villain
In the globalist
Paradigm
He's coming up
I want to play
Overthrow the West
You'll never defeat us
Liberal globalist
My family
So
Discussed a little bit
Speech
Text
There's a lot of people who think it's just
You know Freedom isn't talked about freedom
So you guys don't have to do it is
Went checked out storm
Confront
I wanted to see what
The speech was
Got them at
They understood the coded language
Look at all the white people in the crowd just decades ago America
In crowds used to look like that to Holy
F*** this about all white Poland
To see him there with all these white people
Notice how a pro White
Speech in a pro-white country Poland
Is completely ignored by the Jew media and anti Trump Jews
Cool cool cool
Such a Sublime speech given by Trump and Poland only to have the carefully-planned leaks on Donald Trump
Junior to take some of the Shine off his momentous occasion
Also perfectly time by the Auntie white forces around Trump
Now we are more determined to stand and fight against these venal solace
Destructive Elam
Makeup the anti-white
And Auntie West
Coalition
At least they used
2 hours I misspelled something else then
He mentioned quote our way of life
And I said you see what's out there
Trump knows what's up
I mean the post about it are all pretty much
Spaghetti
I don't
I don't believe it's possible that Alex Jones
For all of his studies
Is Dawning
Everything
So smart and so are has no idea how people
I can't imagine that
He's oblivious
Two white mask
Everything but name
People
The people that he's surrounded
Himself with
Even if Trump doesn't
No
She has no idea because maybe does
Maybe he doesn't understand the dog with
I mean
Maybe
Understand
Like he agrees with it but it doesn't really
What makes it a jaguar
Possible
You can talk to your parents and they'll be like
No he's just
It's the right
Understand it
But the white nationalist
Immediately
All of the codes and this
Is 100
Percent why
We go back
And listen to that David interview that out
Alex Jones dead
David Duke doesn't really get why Alex Jones isn't on board with
Reason to callers
The call him don't understand
Hey what's going on everybody
To the word listen
To what's being said
Knows that Alex Jones is absolutely is in the way he presented stories and all of his
Is rhetoric
All of it
And the idea that he's been
Accused of being this thing
I don't believe he'd never look into it
I don't believe that he never liked
Check out what they're all about
Alex
Does he read any of the s*** that like if he doesn't resemble that
Put
He probably Ron White nationalism
Message Board headline
Attitude like Trump gives great speech alright
Position
That's pretty pretty strongly felt
But Alex Jones
Is at least
And is
Subconsciously or conscious
Mostly supportive of
Yeah now he has a really funny
Quip here
We're here
You imagine what a historical leader of the past might have thought about him
Which one
Establishment
Now
It's wonderful.
44 if I was alive
Launch
I don't think that Hitler would not like Alex
Is awesome
Hitler's belief
Would be
Best friend
Actually looks
If those guys
Would Have Been Loved by Hitler
Who always say that
Martin Luther King jr.
Yeah those guys are like
This week Alex Jones just
Heard about that NRA video The Dana Loesch
Threatened
And it was like
Liberal
Guns at all
She just says
I hate these Liberals are
To kill our president
Are children
Closed fist of Truth
Now here's why that's a brilliant
Cuz it doesn't mention guns
Liberals
Afraid
Hey they might buy some
That's not a bad
That's a genius angle
Cuz you're playing both sides
Hey they're trying to kill our president
You should buy guns
Yourself and him
Liberals are like
You guys are going to burn
It does feel that way
I mean it's like 2 weeks old at this point
Skewed
Rock
Rock hard boner
Until he decided to make his own verse
Oh no no no
But it's not about the NRA
It's about
No it's Alex basically just realized like a promo a wrestling style promo
Excellent
But it doesn't
So close all my on the tales of the NRA video
I've kept it in its entirety
Diana it
The background music is alright
Everyone to post this video on your Facebook
I'ma Twitter
Mike cernovich Rodger Stone
Matt drudge wants to get it out that's everybody
This video out because he goes further than the video
Explain
Globalist want to overthrow the country's by
Why are they
The final equation
Why the left hates America
Hitler would have loved to
Rising anti-American rhetoric
And what
Behind it
Learn
What's behind it
Get this video out it's posted on infowars.com
Right now
Hollywood
Our education system
Electric razor
Burning cars
All of this leads to the destabilization
America America we are the infowar
And we are
Like crazy
Because
Isn't
That's what
That's what that video said
What
What do you mean
Okay walk me through your friend
Was calling for
That could not be
Misconstrued as not being called for violin
On the left there's no
Now if it's that was not made by the NRA
Conservative organization
For literacy
Or something like that
Organization that would never
Hibachi
Waterbirth
You know cuz it's not a gun
It's not
Yeah but yeah it's pretty difficult
Things short of calling
I believe that Alex Jones
Couching
Hey
You're going to have to retaliate
Exactly
You're going to have to be a good guy with the gun you're going to have to save this
From
Nan wife
It's always 8
I don't don't understand how we live in
Different reality
Like there is nobody
Calling to assassinate
Except for Alex.
And god dammit if I'm not the person who would
Accurately pretty much the only person in mass media
Discussing
Regularly
And he's you calling for it
Inasmuch as
Is he saying that everyone else is calling
Right
He's trying to do some sort of the meter
Can you imagine how happy
Would be thrilled
In so many different ways
Yep that would make him
Hero be a prophet
But I mean still just with his old white bass
Matter
And the mainstream Burdick Hunter
Something totally you could take
Pence would become president and he doesn't like Pence all that much so he'd have a new enemy in power
You can't
You can't do that
It's boring it's boring when you're villain
It's
It's your villain can't actually do any
Yeah villain was just kind of like a little baby
Torpor
Core James Bond villain
Who's in a wheelchair
The boy
Sidetrack
Okay
There's a lot going on
Right but Alex Jones
Is so bad at his job
He can't cover all this
Who decides to take a nice five minute
It's out of his show
Mark Dice
Video
Guy we played a number of Mark Dice videos where he goes out on the street and ask people questions and
Spotrac
Threat
In this clip
This is the other version of Mark Dice video
Or he does cultural common
And I want to keep this an entirely
It's very
Bad
Dumb
But I want it I want to illustrate a couple
Verse that Mark Tyson
I'm second
But on this day
We're post
Donald Trump Jr revealing these emails that basically spell out of
Conspiracy
Alex Jones
This much time out of his f******
King show
To play this
What before we do that
There is one
I'm saying that
One thing about that video
Proof
That nobody else at in Fort Worth
Like his voice over in that video
Is good
I think I took that out
Alex Jones
Is like Sinatra
But it's it
Uses great Dynamics
He uses dip
Adult video
Even though
None of his people could do the
Like all the times that we've heard voice-over especially from
Paul Joseph Watson
That's pretty bad
Alex
Call Joseph
Sam is also a pretty talented propagandist
In terms of the way he makes his videos
Any of those
But also it's just like
You're just fast
Cutting lies
It just fast-cut video lies and am looking like
He's going to cry
But be that as it may
I did decide if we ever get to it
Defense
Is it going to be
Go go eat a book please leave me alone
Maybe Daniel f****** learns
Absolutely
So here is one of the least
Talented members of the Infowars family
Mark Dice
And so much more
Also Captain Bahama care
Shopping with tax.
That's all coming up Adam always guess we have a day
Titus report
Watching Amy Schumer is sexist or show has one star last on Netflix I take away the Star Ray
Amazon everywhere you rejected
Hollywood
So get the video to second but I want it I want it
Point out a couple things
First
Now is the time
The capital of
The big important stuff
I don't know
Is finally just like
You know what
I got to get this
Yeah I don't care what what's going on
It's because no one else is
A couple things that are
Centerpoint out
She's going to mock the idea of sexist
Mnb
Misogynist
Beyond that I need to save us very clearly
The reason that she has a one-star rating
On
Netflix
Is because of
Brigading
It's because of the
Men's rights
These alt-right dudes ago and just
In math
It wants our reviews online reviews that are under attack like this like the Ghostbusters
If it's not
It's the starting point music I've got one star it's terrible that you know
God damn well why it has one start now
I don't think
It's not for me to say that cuz I'm coming at it from a position of
I think
Summer premises or a little stale
Someone is really funny
But I know I have other comedians like Maria Bamford I much rather watch
The position that they're coming from
Is
Regrettably sex
Yeah
Here's the Dice Man
Silverman
Christian
Tumi in Chicago
Absolute
People who are funnier than Mark Dice who are also named
Andrew Dice Clay
Endless play son throwing ironic
I like.
Okay
I'm sorry I want to take a break here real quick
To let everyone know that this
Article
I was posted on April 5th
Of this year
A little old
Statute of limitations has run out
Hilarious sketches
He said
I know exactly the argument that it's trying to make
And that is that people say to vulgar as a
Does a bit Louis c.k.
Type of archetype
Want to get to the
The point of what this person's exercise
Just wants to read the article in the snarky
Voice
We love your
So if Mark has wanted to make a compelling argument based on this very short
Censored clip
That's not a fair representation of her work
Weebly.com
Does the Brian Posehn joke for like 15 years ago
It's told from the other perspectives and maybe it's a little bit different but the premise
Of women
Is a b
Been done that would be like
You actually know what you're talkin about
But see if that's the approach
Terrorist
Equal pay
If you say the name Hillary Clinton
Email
If you go
Amy Schumer stand-up
These the worst
So I mean in this video
Sound like
He's laughing at everything
Sing but
It comes off as
As like weird and gross
It's crazy that is not not okay
It's not okay it's so many of the attacks that he tries
Make on her our appearance
Yeah they called her like Amy Shamu
Call Jerrod Niemann Pig
Thinking about her having sex
Yeah
He's illustrating the
Very sexist
Position on Amy Schumer
While trying to mock
An article pointing that out
These people are so f****** stupid
But it works
Work
Amazing you don't want to be
You don't want to be the villain
No matter
Like that maybe I think Rodger stone is fine
I love it I love it
Cheap razors
Before we move on from Mark Dice let me save it
You should really stick
To just asking drunk people stuff on it
This is because that is so much better than this
Like this work is terrible
It's really sad because he does
Like there are
And not just that as far as the sexism
Like if you are if you aren't unlike and the reason that
In the Arctic
Is because
That coded
She's too vulgar
Right it's not because
They didn't like
No
Up your favorite Lee office game with women taking that sort of an aggressive
Disposition
And listen
I don't let him get on
Trouble
Got to move on
Boy
I don't know if that's better
Let's work for me.
Everything Rosie the Riveter will be down with that so let's move to the next clip or Alex that talked more about how
He was just trying to get Russia
Suffuse he's back on that b*******
Espionage missing children
Call 911
Call 411
It isn't them trying to get there
She didn't
Actually Alex you went to Russia debates Fox News
Infowars.com
Infowar
Outsiders
Just bring this up cuz you said over the video that Alex
Went to Russia
Video
And he was on Alexander Dugan show over video
But he did not actually
His
Because I believe if you are photographed
What reason I brought that up is cuz one of the things he screams about all the time is like
Just to make sure you didn't fall into one of
What is tropes
Notes there
The election
Both
True
Like and the worst part is
It's under
It's an
Nobody's nobody's actually looking into it
All of the all of the attorney generals and all of those people in
Election
Committees or whatever it is
They've all said it probably didn't happen probably none of them
Actually looked into
Yeah
And with what we know that the Russians
Can do as far as tearing down a grid and all of this
It's hard to imagine that they would think
Beyond
Even with
Yeah there is something to be said for like
Maybe you don't actually flip switches and change
What have you
Hacking the voter rolls
Preemptively there's ways you can Purge people from voting
And that's as good as change
Making it so people who can vote people to
So
As well as
Yeah it's full of s*** there
The Lord's work
He's becoming like
It's like handing is
He's old
You know why
Glenn Beck
Got to plug in Amity
Actually
Tucker Carlson
He's not really Alex Jones
He's very you Freddy trust fund the douche bro
Republican
But
I wanted this thing is starting to dawn on me
Me too
Is this actually end up being a bigger speech that I mean it to
We will fight them on the beaches
Do not be that inspire
One of the things I'm starting to realize
Alex for a bit
Start
To see his narrative
Playing out in larger culture
Publication
Videos that are posted of Hannity
And Tucker Carlson
Friends
Even
Responding to the narratives that are being played out
Alex Jones
Style narrative
Sir Alex Jones
Talking
I'm not saying this early they originated with him
But they are that
Drudge Breitbart Alex Jones world of narrative
Before there was a
Think different
Between the stories that Alex Jones
Hotel and he's wacko bubble
Even on Fox News
There would be a line between them and now there's not
There is just those worlds are essentially come together
Anything that I think is super irresponsible is that I
People talking about how dumb they are
Picking up people writing articles people on MSNBC or CNN
Talking about how these
Things Are
Stupid
And none of them are addressing the fact that when you
When you talk about Alex Jones narrative
You can't talk about it outside of this
Umbrella of globalist
You can't because if you don't you're not getting why he's
He's mad about ex wires
So even Media Matters I know they're aware of it and they probably talked about him being obsessed with globalist at some point
But if
Even when they post these videos of like
Robert David Steele coming on in talking about Mars
When they like Drop It
Peter Schiff
Adam Schiff
Leadership is the guy who tells you to buy gold
Screaming at him
Did you clock sucker
All that stuff
Dayton
People don't
Bring into like
The reason that he's mad about that
Is a fictional narrative that he has in his head about global
Central Bank
And I just think
I think that the longer that we don't deal with that the longer or the more likely it is to become a saint
Sir problem
If there's an inundation of Alex Jones's worldview into media into
Supposedly
Mainstream media without an understanding of what
Comes from
You run the risk of people being tricked into believing something they don't realize
What they're reading
What they're getting in
Say what you want about
I think a lot of bad things about it
At least
He's very upfront about the fact
Camaros
That he thinks the globalists are trying to kill your family
At least on his sleeve so if you think that's crazy
Thank you. He lies about his sources and stuff like that but it
Is Donald Trump
Clearwater
Weirdly
Not prompted
Self
Do you understand what I'm saying
Just hit me there
Is that
He's always lying about his sources and you know that
Because when he has a real one
He gets so excited
I think you're absolutely right
In that
What is
What I see
Be happening
Is his protro
Because
Because he's
The only one who
Is really just kind of
Wacky
And throwing out anything again
Against the wall
You can listen to his show
And most of it's lunacy
But you'll get like
Oh this is
Is a good office station
Something that I can
Can pull and put on Fox
It's not the globalist
It's not all that
Until when you go on
And you're a Democrat
Undead or
Or whomever
And you're engaged
With this argument
You're engaging
The surface
Comes from
Problem with it is is if you do.
Into the
So if you get rid of all the surface
Like it explodes from within like as once you pop that balloon or whatever it all the water that's inside it
Yeah
Well ended
To me it is again
The way that the
The KKK was
Defeated
In the 50
Was with
The Superman radio show
Yeah that's true
Information to Super
About how these guys are
Billy
The Wizards are not
But their power
Is a
False front
For how silly and
Childish things
People are
Is men's rights
All these men's rights
All the people say
Liberals are snowflakes
And then the moment they get even a little bit
We're going to go out and fight with antifa
You guys punch
Each other in name cereals as a jumping in ritual as a f****** idiot
Why would you want
ICICI
Because they
They're getting into this
One thing that's going to release their
Yeah and what they're really doing is
Nothing more than a lark
Not like that really white version of Second Life
You know on the inside
There is nothing but
A small little boy who's afraid of women
And Olympic
Yeah
I don't know
I'm scared
Coming
People need to
The dress
Their idea of globalist
Somehow it relates
And bigotry but we'll deal with that another time
And the burnings and all this s***
And all of that stuff is
Currently being perpetrated
By the very people who
He's saying
To a beeper
Prepared for it
Yeah Oklahoma
Some guy blew up an Army recruiting center
Former Army guy
Horse Sprite
It's it's
Yeah it's a lot like
You know
The opening line of pride
Prejudice
Where what it means is being version
So in the same way that what Alex
To saying is be prepared for the standings
He doesn't mean be ready
He means start stabbing
Bright bright
Like what do you mean
I agree with that that's what he said
Exactly
Great
Madness
Let's move along
We got this next clip here
A little bit more about that
Speech in Poland
Invading Poland
Hate Christians
We hate Protestants
Pedophile Pope
Globalism
Trump campaign
They make it all racial what about the decline of the way maker
Yes I will
North Korea
It's not compatible
Weird hypotheticals
Here is that
Are you sick cuz I'm kind of bored with that too
Will Thrive and hours
Rodger Stone
Stop the triggers White
People will
Exceed our civilization prosper
Will Triumph
What are we what are we
Talking about when we say the West is South America included
Morrow
Mexico's part of the West let's build a wall
In the middle
What are we
Africa's right underneath
That's why I Alex
Is really more accurate
More accurate whenever Alex really talks about like white
Some dump that's why you talkin about like they hate
White people they hate
Catholics hate Protestants
Yeah that's all he's really triggered by that's all he cares about
When he talks about the West it is code for white
Christians
That's essentially what he's talking about
I need the flex by sayings
Right after he White
Protestants and Catholics
As of the groups that are leading Defender
So I hate I hate
I also hate the pedophile Pope
If he if he is indeed
Is not
Information on that
I'm not here to defend the Catholic Church
Innovation they've done a lot of bad stuff in the past I'm not here to pretend that's not the
At the same time
I've seen no evidence that the
The pope himself as a pedophile
How do you
How can you possibly say that the weather
How can you possibly
Simply say that the West
Is at all
Geographical
Of course
Like white culture
What do you think
That because it's so true
If you've seen a f****** globe
Now if the world is
Classically the term Western world is Europe in America
That's what it
Because they're white
Exactly
Point proven
That's why when Alex talks about like they hate your family's he's talking about white
You talk about traditional two-point
Three children
If you know you have two cars
Picket fence
Wife doesn't have a job
White family system
Muslims
You know what I was
About earlier today I had this really weird
Stray thought
Did the world Alex Jones really wants to live in
No that was that was earlier
At the thought that I had that Alex Jones wants to live in
Could be said in that future is
Hey remember when people were gay that was weird
Yeah you're right that's the kind of future he wants to live at your absolute where I think everybody is
Confused about
How crazy was that remember when we allowed abortion
Different races
I didn't just have their own countries
Yeah that's kind of
It's really bizarre but
It's not far off
If you if you look at the mirroring that goes on but
Can white National
Avenue extrapolate that a little farther and see what the white nationalist
Say
Like what the Stormfront people in
Lorena
What they're really into
What are the things about a bunch
Africa for the African
Write America for the white people
The Mexico for the Mexico
I like you all have your discreet play serial hey have fun over there I don't hate you I don't want to kill you
Play song Staying fine
Can't we carve out a spot
Google
In Siberia and call it just
But what I'm getting at I'm not sure that's terrible idea and everybody else for everywhere
What I'm getting at is
I don't know if it's
Insane
Extrapolated Alex Jones
Kind of alright with that
Lake
Based on how much mirroring an overlap he has with white nationalism right is it
Insane to think that more extreme white nationalist position
Are things the key
Is transphobia
Suggest that
You know hey
There shouldn't be
That's what he is
Regardless regardless of
How far it goes
There are elements
That provable he supports Administration where the
Vice president
Thanks VIP gay is something that you should
He taught not to
Yeah you know
Education secretary
Or whatever
Came outside
God
Batman
Eclipse
Forget the remember all liable rap
This baby up
Ears ears
My
What is
My my
I guess I guess my
Is that there are going to
Tubi
It's going to be
Ground up
Right but it's going to be from the ground up
So if you have your edges
Saying that
That mean
There are plates
That are going
Reject it
But there are places that are
Into a
There already are there books rights activist groups
We're becoming more sector
From the ground up
Instead of a federal kind
Then laws app
Insert
Places
Means that the country is
And frankly at this point
I'm halfway elect
Bones
So Alex wants to ship more on this Russian lawyer that Don Trump Jr met with
I'm at I have a really interesting
Information that I'm going to drop
And now we have this
Kia
Cut out of ass
Alicia Rose
Junior setup
Only set up a
That's what I told Michelle yesterday
What does democratic party group
Bastille dossier
So
No more
It's also not at all like
Situation
Didn't go
And I
It's
His his narrative seems to
To come from the idea that Russia is
Both sides
The plant one
Work for Trump
Clinton
Muddying everything up like
Russia be judge I've started reading foreign policy I think it's a great publication is really insightful
Came out today I'd like to read this headline for you then I'll get into the body of the article
The Department of Justice settled message Russian fraud case involving lawyer who met with Don Trump
Junior grade
Democratic Congressman in the house
Abruptly settled a money-laundering case
In May involving the same Russian attorney who met with Donald Trump jr. during the presidential election
Stauffer dirt
On Democratic candidate Hillary Clinton
The Civil forfeiture case was filed in 2013
By preet bharara
Do the one who was fired the former US attorney for the southern district of New York
Who is fired by Trump at March
The case
That 11 companies were involved
What's Broad in Russia
The portion of the 230 million dollars they got
Into Manhattan real estate
The forfeiture case was heralded as a Time
At the time as a significant step toward uncovering
An unwinding a complex money-laundering scheme
Arising from a notorious foreign fraud
As alleged
A Russian criminal Enterprise.
Vanille gotten ruble
Do the purchase
The pricey Manhattan realest
But
Proceeding with the trial is scheduled the justice department settled the case two days before it was
Due to begin
Text by the
Did not immediately respond to requests for comment
Quote we write with some
Concerned that these two events might be connected
Have at the department sataloff
For the United States in order to
Obscure the underlying facts
Brookside
19 Democratic congressmen on the house
Judiciary panel
In a letter to sessions on Wednesday
The Russian
Fraud scheme
This big 230 million dollars
Sergei magnitsky
Mysteriously
As a result us lawmakers passed the magnitsky ACT
Which levied sanctions on Russian officials
Sanction
That Natalia
Micaiah
The Russian
Also the attorney representing the Russian companies in the Department of Justice
Okay
Is the same one who organized the meeting with Donald Trump jr.
Antop Trump campaign officials in June
Dolphin material that could
Incriminate Democratic presidential candidate Hillary
Quote love it
Responded Trump jr. to an intermediate
Connected
People in jail forever
I don't know
Isn't that super f***** up
It's not like
Unheard
It's not far for the course given all the Cirque
Bringing this case
Cease fire
Then
The Department of Justice
Only gives Mac
6 million-dollar
Penalty
The 200 million dollars
This Brodsky
Wow
Russian illegal money coming into being filtered through
Pricey Manhattan real estate which is what
It's so f******
Clear all this is going on at that meeting
That's all they had
I imagine that might of come up
Reminder
Mighty Mike
My toes
Burlington
Yes
You gotta bring it up
Dude I'm much better job for nothing today Monday
340i had a whole article to read
So all all the stuff she has pictures
I looked at the pictures that Alex's posted I see no evidence
They are all from the women
Are there negative
Trump signs
I mean of course
But the idea
Appalachian
He accepted a meeting
About
Hillary Clinton
Right I think that this stuff is
The super involved in that
What we're seeing
Is possibly
Massive
Money laundering
What's really amazing
What we're discovering
Is that the globalist
Are real
Amir Imam
Who are stealing everything from
Nongovernmental organizations
It's not the EU
It's not government
Except for now Trump is in our government
But it is like a International
Yeah
And they are going
We're not discovering that so much as it's looking
Stay Together
Maybe
That's why this investigation is taking a long time
Abe maybe why a lot of the people
Before the election
Who saw this information in the summer of 2000
I didn't want to act
Yeah
That's a good
Can you imagine how like
Shattering some of this would be to come out during the election
Cancel our government right now
It would be better if we just cancelled the elect
I don't know the other thing
So this investigation does come out
And what is obvious
Becomes
Baby
What the f*** do we do
Yeah cuz that means you're going to have to try and take down f******
Like it's a RICO case
How to take down f****** ever
Take down the people
And our government that are involved
But that's
Come close to the network and all that stuff
We get further into that and you start going back
I can to the people who poured money
How far away
Mercer is a global
F****** instigator in that he has influence multiple election
Around the world is I want us to stop speculating and stuff because I don't want us to drift into Alex
Jones arrest
People
I think you have enough to arrest Donald
He's in the hopper
He should be in jail and he should
Should not have
It doesn't get more of a Flight Risk than
Who has International connections
In hostile non-non extraditing countries
If anybody deserves solitary confined
It's Donald Trump jr.
Donald Trump
And I miss
Mitch McConnell
Paul Ryan
How many hours apart
Bizaardvark
Thankfully
Alex Jones
Gets Rodger Stone
In studio
Act
I get the feeling that Rodger stone is the only person who is
Going to walk away
From this like I honestly don't think Rodger Stone
Is a
He might be one
Love the Fall Guy
Not so much a patsy but
There's a reason they've kept him so on the outside
Like Trump saying I haven't talked to him in a long time
Publicly trying
Keep distance
He's never with them
He's not a part of the administration
I think there's a reason for that
He's too close
Like I wish
Bi hacker
He's just a bit player now
Like
If it was
Closed
You've you've easily got him a
Fall Guy
Now you're going up
After such bigger fish
With Rodger Stone
What are you trying to do with him
Yeah same way you're trying to flip your your manafort's and whomever
You're trying to do you extradite
Michaela
That's basically what you do there
That's not how we
American I apologize
But whether Rodger stone is the Fall Guy or not he is a guy
Have a little bit of a talk about
This side the situation with Junior
They want
About it
You deserve a medal an award
Rodger Stone
This is insane
July last year about Russia
Is involved in this
Volume
Subject
They change the subject
Classified
Publicly
He's pretending that we didn't hear about
The fact that Trump
Emails from Russia
I've been reminded of that by myself and various
Twitter personality
Turn on my mind for over a year
George's been on
Trump was right when he said Russia
A month
His son met with a Russian agent because
She wasn't cut out for the globalist
Okay
All right well I buy it
Nation release
Sure they're the ones kidnapping those kids I mean
Unexplained criticizing
A real pistol
Different
Alex is terrible at asking questions
How long was it was like 40 seconds after the question
You going to be surprised
Does Raja still going
MN
Just keeps yelling you got it
You know I was in Washington yesterday and I got to tell you
Ever seen
Fake hysterium Moore
And drying about nothing
Let's be very clear
Nothing illegal and nothing wrong
Whydah targeted
Because he's the strongest and most effective spokesman for his father's campaign because you
Retrieve things from infowars.com and other alternative credible news sources
Because that's why
In frankly if in a middle of a presidential campaign
On your opponent
And you do not
To get that information
You're guilty of malpractice
This isn't this is a struggle for the presidency
I'm going to I'm going to cut the clip off early cuz you just got it
I think you just moved it
Directions
We got investigator
Listen I'm telling you we need to redo Nixons Alexa
Let's just reset America
Starting in the late 1500s Iago can go back and read
Reset everything for us
Too old to old age regression
Give him in one of those
Come on
More believable than Trump not committing
We are in a weird world where Project Camelot is more reasonable than Alex absolute
Barry Williams play
Carrie Callahan
Calm down
I love you calm down
She probably has less CD acquaintance
And that's taking a lot
Time Travelers and weirdo
Still more comfortable with that
In governor
Solutely anyway
In this next clip Rodger Stone w
What's the go just a little bit further than Alex
About trying to sort of poo poo
On this Russian lawyer late
If you look at the circumstances under which the woman lawyer go into the country
I think play into the the idea that you just put forward
Compromise
Trump jr.
Nothing whatsoever wrong
Strong otters House and Senate investigation
How come
So he's trying to
Pretend that this is it this is all they got
They were trying to set up an
Compromised
Junior
Eddie doesn't and the sentence
And they totally did
Got him to commit a crime
If that isn't a quick it's not
You're so f****** dumb dumb
He's the strongest
Most vocal supporter
He's a warrior
Constantly retweeting
He's a warrior and by that we mean
He pays tons of money to kill innocent animals in Africa
Also this
Premise that her visa have been
Expired 4
Six months or Obama had better in the country
It kind of run
Counter to Alex's immigration Argent
Just a little bit
Just a little again
I don't know
Dreadlock I'm not saying
I'm just saying also does Obama get every Visa renewal
That's
Listen Obama if you're listening
That was a lot of work
Every single legal immigrant
I can't stay mad at you
You're a woman lawyer we need you to Alex
That's just
I said lady lawyer and I apologize
I just don't have space my brain right now
That's one of those
Little thing
It's like
It's built into the way that we
Noticing
That's just how I talk
You know it's weird
Rodger stone is like 70
Car part for the course for him
All the stuff going to go on and Alex is going to get in
To his sort of
Oppression
Exactly I'm being investigated
Real whack
Violation of lawyer
I don't think there's anything politically wrong
Well
I don't want thing for absolute 100%
They came out with Federal License Commission
Reply to yesterday
And sad
Titan Machinery
Four months ago from the house
But I'm under
Counter Espionage investigation by the FBI
Before Congress
Literally
Know that
The reason I lost the election and the Russians fun me and told me what to say
Election
Going to Trump
It's just crazy I mean I want to be called before Congress
You'll get your chance
I just love this call before Congress
He'll be in contempt be the best viewing I've ever seen
He's on
Unsub
Audible
You know that went if he comes
Is just going to yell at you and you're going to have to LA
I put them in the
Put them in Chains
Seen him do that on
TV shows enough that it's
That's boring
Like in the Senate
Whatever but I also think it would be like
This is bad
Before the Senate you're making a mockery mean
Dude
Could you please
We called Buckley to the steakhouse
Buckley
You've been with
Michaela
How many
Does imagining he has a little hillbilly draw that I don't know why
Anyway we have one more clip left
Play this is
Kind of Rodger Stone
Surrendering
A little bit
I don't think you think that's what he's doing
But I'll let you hear what he says
I think it'll be pretty clear
Iyi this is admission of
Guilt
Why don't you put the candidates family in the line of fire
Send a low-level
Well it shows they don't have the
Theories of Presidential Power
Did the clintons have
Honest
Buddies
Since the beginning witch
What is the problem
This town
Andy should I use the cutout
What why would you use a cut out if you're not doing something illegal
Beguiled
Citrus bring in a movie theater standee
I got cut up
Somebody else
Yeah I mean with the argument that he's making the underlying argue
Yeah exactly
Do you know that you're if that's your argument
Something is not right
Which is like
Oud
Your incriminating yourself you realized
A hundred percent
Is weak
In terms of his
Defense cuz all of his
Fall Apart
Anything about it being opposition research
Stella crime
He was duped by somebody
Still a crime still shows Criminal Intent
The idea that this lady is
Soros operative because they were pictures of on her Facebook
Over at the women's March is weak as hell
That is circumstantial
And if you really want to press
The matter all you're doing is sort of denying her
Her right to congregate her right to free speech
The right to protest
I think that's again
Your narrative Alex
You wouldn't want that
Further if you look into it
She
Is clearly the benefactor of a weird favor by the department of justice under Trump
That's very suspicious
Pick you want to talk about that Alex but I'd love to hear your
Even their spinach
Incriminate
Everything is like
That's the getting closer to the center of the drain
Yeah that's just the water going out
Touching the metal map
What happened
To what happened
Whenever nothing
Opens with Alex
Whenever nobody's
To Chester
I don't know
Whenever the FBI report.
And it is like a all these times they did it
They did all this stuff
Trump jr.
We don't even need to investigate him
He said he pointed it out and let everybody know
Dave everyone evidence
Proven
Like
Stupid
None of it is
It's all a globalist
Set the groundwork
There is no
Like he is literally saying
Can trust no
Anywhere
Except for your Sarah
Just your Sheriff
No cuz he would he would still say like no matter what let's say worst case scenario it comes out that literally
Trump food we're sitting down
There's a quid pro quo
About the the terms of
They have did all this slanderous material about Hillary Clinton
All this defamatory stuff send it to WikiLeaks
And I will lift
But if there is evidence that there was
Foreign policy sold
Ralph Jones
He's already put the
Jesus
The little building blocks
That is that comes out
Listen
The reason he did that is because Russia is our only potential ally against
The globalist
Ravioli country that's kick the globalist out that power
Then go right back to
Of course that would be
Yeah that would be a distraction that ended up happening
Trump is already violated the emoluments clause
Ever again
That is a hypothetical
It's pretty likely
But it hasn't been proved
Most corrupt
Thievery of
Government
This is the single largest most inexplicable coincidence that is ever happen
Snow White
Be like
Complete
Collusion invisible
Not really even massive conspiracy
Trump
And some really shady types
Or
The the Democrats
Are butt hurt about losing the election
And they're really
Dead Sea
Narrative
That happens to be reinforced
Information
No they couldn't control Donald Trump Juniors response
Gmail
Is my favorite
Yeah it's
All of the
Lineup with their fake
Reality narrative that they're pushing
In order for that to be a plausible
I don't see a third option but I don't know what it is
Get into
His listeners
So we're talking about a lot of lawn for
A lot of ex-military
Kimmswick MO
What is
What is there
Like do they
Do they accept the rule of law
Narrative
You destroy
Faith in government
. if you say the FBI
Is full of s***
The
Department of Justice
If you go through all of these differ
All of this intercept
And you say you can't
Any of it
If you are ex-military
Do you say well that
We're innocent
Door is already
Or does that mean that it's time to honor
3 /
I hope that's
I ate and knowing that Alex Jones
Is a craven con man
He also
Love's
Like we know that from
The percentage of time he takes on his
Joe to sell products
So I would say
Is keenly aware that there is
Align
There's a Mendoza Line
Fear-mongering is going
To call people
To start fighting in the streets
I won't sell anymore product
After that point so I think he knows that there's a point he can push it
And once we reach that point
I think that will be when we can determine whether Alex Jones
I mean he's a con man either way
The weather
He's lost it while we can
Is lost it he has
It don't matter
Hugo Fugue out here with that line tells us
If he crosses that line to the point where it's no longer financially
Reasonable for him
To be pushing the things he's pushing
Then you'll know that his ideology
Outweighs
His love of money
I don't believe that
I think he loves
Does millions of dollars
I think you'll get to a point where
He realizes he's got to pull back
I don't have that
I think where I think we're past
We'll see
Either way we're going to die so
Yeah but
Before you die please
Optimistic wayfair.com
Knowledge
You can leave us a review on there if you like that's great
Donate to the show
There's a knowledge
It says supports
You can give any amount of money a month
Bonus stuff going
Some fun things to be a policy wonk
Everything will be great
Yeah
In the meantime
You know where
A die
There's one person wrong again
Still about you do it
Alright alright
There's a lot of people
The world
I remember the right way
Look
There's one man who's responsible for us
Not being able to our outro
His name is Jay Rappaport
Even f*** yourself
Jon rappoport
And I said it
Alexandra Thurston color