Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge
Dollartree.com
Acknowledge
No Jordan hey what's going on vacation I'm here
On my lonesome sitting here recording an introduction
And I guess I should give a break spot
How many messages I got about how Sofia is a robot
Was about giving a Saudi Arabian citizenship a few years back
I still think it didn't make sense based on what Carrie was saying in our last episode
But in my defense one of the reasons that I'd sort of forgotten about that story get filed in a similar place in my brain
Brain has the alpacino movie Simone
I thought those became became the same story
In my head and I just I lost track of it
Anyway hey folks
Here's what's going on
We have a little bit of an episode to get to this is hard without somebody sitting across the desk
I'll tell you that
I've already lost Steam for the reduction
Explain what's going on but first i'm going to say hello to some new no walks out there
The first my coworkers are you and to belligerent globalist corgis thank you so much you're now policy walk
Brooks cambium
I'm a policy wonk next Derby a Creator thank you so much as he want
Strictly speaking based on the way this is phonetic just the letters are written
BBW hater
Be a crater
I'm not
Any white Faberge eggs the movie thank you so much right now policy walk
I'm a policy wonk in the mix so thank you so much
Should I go now technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
Heroin
Freakishly large
Alright so look here's the deal
Evans kind of always the case whenever we end up having a break of some sort
Like let's say
One of the co-host goes to France something happens that requires attention in
And that makes things difficult usually will have to wait until we get back together and then trying to play catch-up
In this case Alex Jones sue the government
Jordan life
I'm going to be gone for a week and by that time something else crazy will it happen will be
You know who be too much to play catch-up on I think
I decided to go do a little sneaky snake episode and so what I did
I was I reached out to Andrew Torres of the opening arguments podcast
Find a cool dude and I wanted to
What was going on with this suit that Alex had brought
Against the January 6th Commission
A committee excuse me and that is now what we shall play is today's episode so
Sneaky Snake it up
I will be back we're back
Well ladies and gentlemen hello welcome to interview
Today Alexa
One is that Alex
Cannot stop getting himself
And legal trouble
To the point where we need multiple legal experts
Stu to cover all the ground
All the territory that he's getting into
And he has the world's worst timing where Jordan leaves for vacation and then the next day he decides
To sue the government
And we can't wait till Jordan gets back from France welcome
Cast from the opening arguments podcast
Amber Torres thank you for joining me
Out there thank you so much for having me on the show I've been
Looking forward to coming on for a while we've had do you guys come come on over it
Opening arguments
Stuff
Seems like a propitious time talking the law and Alex Jones there's a
Heavy overlap
Subject
Don't look
Very promising
4 per hour
Yeah that's that's
I will I will accept that as a
Seems like a pretty pretty
Pretty clear based on the trends you know Vic we had the the default judgments that happened in the Sandy Hook case
Just recently
Hey now
Total mess with the January 6th
Committee
Yep this is a truly incompetent
Kind of complaint niani judge that on the basis of the
Comparison be
Between this complaint
And other doomed lawsuits are filed by
Similarly situated
Individuals who have been
Subpoenaed by the 16 committee and are making the same arguments Alex Jones is making here only Alex
Jones is making them worse
So making some pretty exaggerated sort of claim
And also his asks
Seems to be a little bit ambitious sure we'll get to
I was looking at Ali Alexander's lawsuit cuz he's also filed
There's a lot of similarities
Hollywood
Similarly
You have the
The lawsuit filed by
By Mark Meadows right and they and they are all
Designed to do the same thing
Which is to quash
Subpoenas that have been issued
To third-party
Providers to turn over cell phone
Look like the AT&T subpoenas that they had they put out
Exactly right however
What are the things that the future of those other lawsuits not a feature of this lawsuit is that you will note that AT&T
He is not a party
To this lawsuit
Typically it again
Give you the disclaimer from opening arguments right like I have a real practicing law
But but
I think it's safe to say
That as a lawyer
Wendy wants to get relief against somebody
Uu name that person
In your lawsuit
So if I'm understanding correctly these other lawsuits like the alley Alexander or Mark Meadows 18
He is listed in the lawsuit
Verizon for provoke
French for Alex
Not
And in fact
I mean one of the
Reasons why
One of the few things that
You might actually be able to accomplish
With
Bringing a lawsuit
Use
Delaying a cellphone carrier for
From turning over
Your cell phone record
Typically the response that they will take his
Hey we've got us a bit rate that will call you up another pursuant to our terms & conditions
We have received a subpoena for your records
We're going to turn them over by
XJ8 unless you can show us a
Court-ordered
It says
We should not turn the boat
End
Typically
Somebody who has
Incel
Subpoenaed people's phone record
Zigbee the phone
The owner rapist
The client
Can I call up and be like hey
We don't have a court order right now but we do have is
A
Valid
Pending lawsuit in which we've challenged the basis
Of the subpoena and you know you should
Probably not
During that time
Play I like giving the phone records over can't be undone and maybe this lawsuit will work in and having it
Injunction
And so like let's hold off on it basic
That's it that's exactly right
But
I noticed
Is that the date that AT&T gave in their letter seems to have passed already
Kind of interesting the way these years there have been other
Lawsuits that have served
Similarly been filed kind of right on the day of
This is the first one I've seen
That. That has been filed after the date at which AT&T said they were going to produce documents
And by the way although this lawsuit
Quest declaratory and injunctive relief
You've explained this well in
Covering
The Alex Jones interminable numerous
This is a situation where there is not a specific
Motion for a preliminary injunction or temporary restraining order accompanying this loss
And typically that's what you do right like if
If I need if if I know that 18 tsp
Can I turn over one of my
Lions record
Then I go into court today to get a temporary
What that does is that preserve the status
Ask what I make
The argument that you articulate
Right which is
Look if they turn over the records right you can't put the genie back in the bottle
So you don't give us a stay of a couple of days
Let us breathe this up
And then you do the court
Applies 88
A four-part legal test
I couldn't figure out whether you can
Continue that
Over you know and that a preliminary injunction usually lasts a couple of weeks
And then you do you can get a permanent injunction
After that
And so
What would it would have he ever does is it buys you time to then fully breathe
I did a preliminary injunction
It seems like it's also like a pretty reasonable request the most
Courtney's probably G
So the wait what work would do is
Acorda employees
And it's a little bit counterintuitive
The two most important
Things
That you look for in in granting injunctive relief are number one is there a bullhorn
Reparable harm that means is this a thing that money can buy
6 or no
Write something that money can fix
That's not a rapper
Write like it so it'll it'll be really really bad if I too bad right like that's
That's what courts exist to do is to sort of direct money from Party 8 apart
But I guess I feel like if he would scream
I did I buy vibe
Channeling a little Jordan
And then the second thing that the
The court is going to look at is
The likelihood of sick
Success on them
Sure
That's going to seem really really weird right
Emily b as a lawyer
Practicing it is kind of weird to ask
The court to judge
A case that it hasn't heard yet
And so
For example when you Prevail on an injunction right
Usually it's a pretty strong signal to the other side
When you lose on an injunction that
It doesn't mean anything
It just means
The court
Decided that the factors weren't your favorite says
Based on what we've heard right now we think the plaintiffs are very likely to win
In the event that this would go to trial
If I'm a defense lawyer
I take that very seriously right
Epic Sports
Prejudge this case
So
You know we can talk about all of the other factors but basically when I go into court and I won an injunction
Those are the things that I wanted my
Irreparable harm
And
Yeah we're we're way ahead on the merits
I don't feel like those standards are met
Not here
What are the things
Ed
I buy pouches of this is a little bit of a rabbit
Enjoyable sure
What are ways which I teach people to read complaints over on opening arguments
Is back
It's right you scroll to the end you'll get a caption then you scroll to the end
And then you work your way back
And that's because
Lawyers do that
People are reading the complaint
From front to back
And like that first paragraph is just an introductory
Inflammatory like summary paragraph of stuff
Really a Republican
Right
Yes I'm none of that means anything
What I want I didn't what I want to know is
Write the important stuff.
This is is also kind of fun because when you scroll to the bottom of this hundred
23-page
You will see that they have attached
4 pages
Authority
And I want to tell you with somebody who
This is civil litigation like
All the time
That's not a thing you're supposed to do to your complaint
That was one of the questions that I was going to ask you
Is it normal to attach the entire rules for the House of Representatives
Onto your
Your complaint
No it's not normal in any way right oats
That's because
A complaint
Is not a legal
Sets out the facts as you assert them or believe them to be true
And then frames them right Within
Legal counts that says
If these facts are as they are
Then the law in each of these counts that's compels you to find
And then you go through
Kind of a two-step process as the
Defense
The fur
Process that you go through is deciding whether you're going to move to dismiss
And when you move to dismiss what you say is
Even if these facts are
100% what you say they are
This is not a legally sufficient
Ground upon which to sue somebody
And so get out
Write the video who gives a s*** stander
That's exactly right the example that I don't know why professors always use this but
Everybody I know who's ever gone to law school like has
That their professors use the same example so I'll reiterate it here
It is the I say
Paragraph number one
A damn frowned at me I could see you doing it right now over Zoom
Paragraph number 2 that made me super sad
A paragraph 23 therefore I'm suing him for intentional infliction of emotional distress for a million billion dollars
Oh no
Ed Edd n Eddy would say
Enter I was not frowning at you this is just
Like what I look like
Like writing but but when you move to dismiss you if you like
Man even if I frowned at him like
Browning is not legally sufficient grounds
Intentional infliction of emotional distress my contact has to be extreme and outrageous
A frown is neither
Extremely outrageous
F*** off
And and the courts will say oh yeah we agree f*** off
Right that is
Motion to dismiss granted and you
We will not move money in your direction
And then if if not
Right and this is where again
I just went into size
Most cases
Pass that minimal filter
Because
Suppose
I just Airi erratic that exact same lawsuit and I say
Ghetto vet
Dan
Broke into my house
And slaughtered a rabbit in front of me in the middle of the night
And said if you don't come on knowledge fight him to do the same to you tomorrow
If your defense is but I didn't do that
That's not the basis for a motion to
Because if you did in fact
Do that
And we all know what you
Look look it's hard to book guests
But if you did do that right that would be grounds for unlike the frowning thing be like
Digging into my house at
Murdering a bunny in front of me and threatening me that I'm next that would amount to that standards and still we would proceed to discuss
And I would be entitled
To seek documents and information everything else from you
That would then enable beat approve
That you did in fact
Sneak into my
Murder the money
And that by the way right it did the through-line
When you had it was fantastic
With
The
Sandy Hook
Plaintiff
Alex Jones his failure to turn over those documents in Discovery in the Sandy Hook cases
Is what led to the entry of
So yeah so that's the difference between a motion to dismiss this case is nonsense
Versus
Moving forward with you then adjudicate on summary judgment
Right so take our same thing
I do get Discovery Discovery is expensive right you have to hire a lawyer you have to put
Documents
Deposition expensive when you don't
Well yeah that's a bad idea
At the end of that process if I still have no evidence
That you've actually
Come into my house
W would move
Not to dismiss what you would move for summary judgment
Defense verdict that says
Hey
You know they did they did a fishing Expedition for 6 months
And there was Zero evidence that I even know where Andrew lives
Let alone has been in his house I didn't have a bunny that there's nothing
And at that point if all of that
Judgment in your favor
Could be a bit of a pyrrhic victory
I just made up the whole bunny thing
And now I
You know kind of drunk either drug you through the wringer
Even though you know you did
That's an endemic problem
It's probably beyond the scope
That is
The complaint doesn't seek
Took the complete set up a kind of relief
The plaintiffs want right but it is not an operative Motion in it
And so you should not be attaching legal authority to it
In particular you should not be attaching publicly-available legal Authority
I thought that was a little much
That's
That the exhibits all just being like the rules of the Republican conference and
Like
Cuz I opened it up and it's 130 pages
I am not reading all of this and then it was only 30 of actual right I was very very thrilled
That was the case
See that is the difference between this is 138 like I can't wait to see all the allegation
Star Bakery
Oh man this is like
The kid whose fiddled with the margins of his paper to
To get it out there
Female trouble I want 130 pages
130 pages cuz I know it's going to be filler
There's this.
So-so
Return to the actual last page
P29 and and the reason you go there first
And I'm serious as a lawyer I really read when my clients
Get sued
The complaints this way the first turn to the last page
I see that Alex Jones is represented by
Patterson Smith
Norm pattis alloy
Norm pattis
So
So what is the is there a long-standing connection between Norm Patterson and Infowars
Yeah he's been he's represented Alex on a number of cases he's been Gaston
Infowars
When
Particularly when he wanted to put a million-dollar bounty on the Connecticut
Lawyer Chris Maddie
Norm was actually sitting next to Alex when he did that
He wasn't he what he did there represent Alex in the Sandy Hook case in Connecticut for a bit
Around
It's been at least a few years
He's been in play
That's interesting right because what I do is
I go to the law firm's webpage
When I go to Patterson Law Firm. Com
It is Blaze and over-the-top
Connecticut criminal defense lawyer
And it says
Do you need a Connecticut
CT
Don't know why you would
Second
Do you need a Connecticut criminal lawyer
New Haven Connecticut Connecticut criminal lawyer Norm pattis
Blah blah blah found it the Patterson Smith Law Firm to aggressively fight for your rights and freedom
And then it says
Norm pattis of the Patterson Smith Law Firm criminal lawyers
Have an exceptional defense and appeals track record
Felony and misdemeanor cases including medical and legal professional misconduct
Capital murder
Connecticut sex offenders
Federal in Connecticut white-collar crimes domestic violence internet Financial online sex crime
Theft fraud and other offenses Criminal Appeals Federal appeals and misdemeanors including tuid
And I look at that and go
That's not somebody who
You hired
To sue the United States
You know to sue a committee of of the United States House of Representatives
Talk to Norm
I think he is probably good at those those forms of law but there's ever was discussed in terms of
Like Alex he always calls him one of the foremost
First amendment constitutional law professor
Lawyers in the country
Then I'm sure that's true
That may or may not be true
But but I will give you the following B
Of effect as far as approaching
The first is
Alex Jones
And Infowars
Is is nowhere to be found
You wouldn't put that there either
That's just good business
I certainly wouldn't
But when I go to
Types of cases it says
Criminal defense police misconduct
Whistleblower claims
And then
High-conflict
Sybil
Okay well maybe this is a icon flexible
When you click on high-conflict civil
It takes you to a page that says that has a single red bar that says
Details coming soon.
How like a Robert Barnes was one of Alex's big constitutional lawyers
The website the America Law Center or whatever he was trying to start
And one of the big pages in it was about his case that he was
Doing
Like he was putting it out there front-and-center
Yeah
If
If you have represented a an individual in suing the house
House of Representatives
That is unless you don't want to get those kinds of cases
That's the kind of thing you put on your website of your like C
I do this kind of work
Work all the time like if this case were to go anywhere this is a career kind of case
Alex is suing the House of Representatives
And
Spoiler alert one of the things he wants is to recognize
A b b January 6th committee has no legal basis
Horse the dissolving of the committee
Yes yeah
Add so that that is right at all of this is to say look like
What are the dirty little secrets of
About being a lawyer is
You can come out
Of a doomed lawsuit looking pretty good for yourself riding like
You know if
Your client may not ultimately get what they want
But you know if you did a super competent job
Advancing the arguments as much as possible Right like
You know you would
You would still list you would list
Field representative
On a similar Larry always want to have wins
Example of something
I do
Chalon in in in government
I will do
Hot challenges B
What we called did
And that is
Contract put up for bids
And you know that the the
One company that wins
You know my client came in second and
I get that seem kind of fish
And you take a look at
You look at him and go
Yeah okay but as it so happens that you know the
The director of the company that one is married to somebody who's on the
Approval
Yeah exactly
And I tell my clients right
You know that
Bid protest
Reversal
Incredibly rare
Right like you you lose eight out of ten nine out of ten of
And so
Have a 500 record in bid protest case
And that's pretty good
Right and left good batting average
That that
Just not seem to be
Advertising his his
First Amendment
Maybe he just didn't
Guy lately but he giant ponytail
And then he grew huge beard to
Far be it for me to critique driving a big beard but he looks insane
Did the other big covid beard
Once once my
Fortunately
Classmate Ted Cruz grew the beard I think the floodgates were he's actually you're ahead of me
I think that opened the floodgates
Anybody
Ted Cruz can have a
Beards are cool for the right now
They're taking a bath
Makes me want to go
Yeah all the way down
The skin right
Yeah I would if I if I didn't look like a gigantic baby without it
Without my beard so
The same thing that I
I'm scared to take the gigantic baby look
Might be a winner
The other name that's on here is
Is Cameron Atkinson which is noted with a
Footnote as mr. Atkinson has submitted an application for admission to
The farthest Court
And meets all the requirements for admission he had weights
Admission
Admission percentage
Was the score
Does not
Say and I cannot find proof
That Mr Atkinson is admitted to any bar anywhere
He is at most
2 years out of Law School
Go get his Law Firm
When you go to his webpage
Cameron L Atkinson.
It says that he's an associate for Patterson Smith Law Firm
Connecticut criminal defense lawyers
When you go to the Patterson Smith Law Firm in click-on firm attorneys
He's not there
Again
What I did is I wouldn't to westlie look to see while going to court appearances he's at
He's had he's had three
And I hit around for a few years come on
One of them was his failed lawsuit against face
But back when he was in Lost
Which is how I know
When
Exact that that he was a
Third-year law student
Is that what that was he was very very mad
At Facebook
Removing
Several of his post
Online platform
And he set up what he thought was this
Amazing
Gotcha so
He
I'm going to read from the case she says
2019 Atkinson learned that Facebook was Centura censoring post
That mentions the name of the alleged Ukrainian whistleblower
Whose allegations prompted impeached
By the way
Yeah that and that was
In a week
Figured that name out as well a little do you know
We're not irresponsible
So we did not
That may or yell at like a Rand Paul was doing as I recalled
Was doing a lot of that like signaling
To that
Yeah and at look like lettuce boat plugs very brief just how evil that is
That is to to name the Whistleblower is
An effort to go out and say hey
You are horde of crazies
Should now harass this
Like hypothetically intimidate
People from coming forward to the future
Like there's there's that dynamic
Absolutely
So
Atkinson decided to test the scope of Facebook censorship himself
He made three posts on Facebook
Each of which use the name of the alleged whistleblower
The first to post begin with the phrase test post
One called the individual the hero while the other called the individual a
Dirty lying rat
Right to be there he was going to prove that Facebook you know is out there censoring
Right-wing because you know blah blah blah
Yep he's got a control group
Facebook remove both posts without warning or notice
But not the test post
I bet he says Atkinson the middle third post still using individuals name but stating that Atkinson had conflicting
What's on the naming of the alleged whistleblower
Facebook remove the Third
Facebook was just removing every post that used
He he sued Facebook in Connecticut
Facebook moved to remove back
McKay's
From Connecticut to the northern dish
California cancer
Terms of service
Wendy Sue Facebook you have
Sue them
In the northern
California
This is the thing a lawyer should know button
School still figuring it out
Well he was represented by Norman a pedestal
So yes
You know Norm pattice from from Infowars
I had to back into him through
Cameron here
But I'm going to looks like
He befriended a little buddy that was in law school
Who's interested in a right-wing shitposting
AT-AT
End end that that was worth there was an interview
If you go to the public appearances
I have a media
If I were on Infowars wearing a 10-gallon hat
I will probably not post the video that but I am not Cameron
Oh no
May 30th 2020
He did an interview
S2
Why covid lockdown measures are unconstitutional
Traditional spoiler alert
But nevertheless I know he has a big hat
Capitalism
It is official
It's official photos
Okie dokie Pizza
He looks like
8818 age
Child wearing his dad's suit
With a with an oversized
What I look for in a lawyer
Especially like a constitutional lawyer is someone who's not afraid to Peacock
You know like somebody who's got a giant or like Noir with his big ponytail
Like these are people who are taking bold choices
Well if you like bold choices you will like how Kevin
SA
A Christian a trial and appellate lawyer Patterson Smith LLC a former business consultant
A published
Constitutional scholar
That by the way means that he wrote a law review article
In law school which
By the ways of thing that
Most of us do
And he's he's written the what
Anika published in the
Marquette University law review
You know what
It's a legitimate
Conservative-leaning
Whatever he did his thing that lost future
That's like the comedy world that's like someone saying that their album debuted at number one on iTunes
Generally speaking you can get a couple people to buy your album it's going to take you at number 1
It's basically everyone has bad credit
Yeah I did get that something that's a great metaphor
And then it says you got to love this for this is the
Yo ended General Hellraiser witch
I'm just I'm looking at that hat that ha
Christian and a hellrazor
I don't know about this
Admitted that he's been dead
Put on let's put a pin in that one
Evan says he is taking on substantial roles and breathing cases to
You know and then list the whole bunch of
End end
I'll be daddy's again that's just lawyer-speak for
They let me write but they would not let me
In any event
This is a there's a child
Episode L now I am armed with the knowledge
That I need
To look at
This complaint knowing that it was written by
A DUI lawyer into chili
And and I can scroll up to the
Beginning of accounts
And the counts are the parts
Complaint where
You list the legal thing that you
You claim somebody has.
An end of
Usually right
You put your strongest one first
End
Although you have multiple canister 6-count
A little bit of a spoiler
What are the reasons
Multiple accounts
Is that
You can as a plaintiff
In a civil suit in the snow shovel
You can plead in the alternative
And I will give you a classic example of that if
If I pay you $500
For the promise that you're going to come by and paint my
And then you take the money but you never paint
I'm going to sue you and Mike at 1 will be Bri
We had a contract
I give you the five hundred bucks you agreed to come paint my house you never Kim
You never came by you never painted my house
But I'm also going to plead in the alternative
Right I'm going to plead something called unjust enrichment
I'm going to say
You know
It's possible Dan is going to argue he never signed the piece of paper and he thought I meant something else and who knows what
The house is anyway and okay so in the event that the
It says that there's not a valid
Contracted
I still want to prove that I gave you $500 and you didn't do anything sort of like a just-in-case kind of thing
That's exactly right and so
The key part for something to be
Leaving in the alternative
Route to be a good just
Didn't case
Is that it's based on a different theory of the facts
Then
The other cow
And I notice you going
Because
Spoiler as you look through this
Virtually all of these
Six counts here
Are premised on
One nonsense argue
If I understand correctly it has to do more or less with like hey they can't do this
And I will tell you that
Donald Trump and his cronies
Have been making the
Congress can't ask about stuff
Argument
4 years
Dates back to
Congress subpoena
Where is Jack's return
And the argument
But the argument is
That what Congress has the
The power to do
Who is to
Investigate
Things
For the purpose of
Writing few
What they don't have the power to do
Is invest
Navigate empress
You cry that's an executive
It belongs to the Department of Justice
That is a true statement of law
But the problem is right that the response back to that is
Lots of things that
Produce crimes
AR
The kinds of things that Congress would
Want to know
In order to write
New legislation
There's that one another election
Yeah we would want to know for example how did you evade our existing laws
Which
Existing laws did you break and by the way there was nothing to
To prevent
Congress when they uncover criminal information
From making a referral over
Hey this is summer job but
That's pretty normal
Yeah it is
Totally normal
And that by the way is what happened in the mieszerski
Trump said you don't really want this to write legislation you want this to try and punish me
For you no criminal Behavior
And in Congress
Replied
We can do Tuesday
We don't we don't want it to show your criminal Behavior
But what we want to do is
Pass laws like
I don't know
Figure out
What kind of
Mandatory disclosure
Requirements
We ought to have for elected officials
Doesn't have to be a Witch Hunt
And that's exactly right and that's essentially what the Supreme Court said in Mazar
It was like
If you have a valid legislative purpose
Is
Seeking
Potential legislate
Even if you haven't drafted the legislation
Damn right because you might say we would want to discover the full scope of how people are evading the law
Right now before
Rewrite a new one
You don't have to have Annex
You just have to have a valid
Legislative
And so
All of these recycled arguments that are like
You're really after Alex Jones because you
You hate Alex Jones and you want to
Put him behind bars
Amphitheater responds back to that is so what
We can hate you for multiple reasons
We want this information because
That was an Insurrection at the Capitol
And we would like
The craft legislation to make sure that doesn't happen again
And figuring out
How this happened
Crucial to us
Figuring out how to do our job
As legislator
It feels it feels sort of like
Alex is taking this personally
As opposed to a positive
Recognizing that there's a work the work that needs to be done by the
The committee
Yeah nnn
Again yeah I just I just want you to substitute in
Any other kind of crime right like
If if you went into court and said
The only reason that in an officer Smith pulled me over for drinking and driving
Is kissy hates me
The judge is going to be like right but were you drinking and driving
Me and the dressing to be like
I don't really care whether you know that they like when I
If you could show you know some kind of improper
Activity
That's one thing but like
Saying
They don't like me
Therefore this process is invalid is
Not a syllogism that are quartz
Look I recognize their probable cause
Stew have pulled me over but he hates me and that's why you did it
Berend and that will involve
You spending a lot of time
Sugar
SoCal one says that
Did this is a violation
Of Article 1 Section
1 +
Of the concert
Challenges
The subpoena Authority
Of
The Congress
NN. I want to pick up
Number one here
Just because there was a section of the
Tuition to which you can point
Does not mean that you
You have the right to that gives you
A cause of a
Action internet
I was wearing about that questions that I really wanted to ask you
Standing
To make that kind of a complaint
About like the inner workings internal workings of Congress
It is not clear to me that he does right okay so as you point out right so this this
What follows then
In
Count one
Is an argument that
The 16 committee is not
Dooley compose
It does not have
A ranking minority member
There was insufficient
Advise and consent with the
Ranking minority member with Kevin McCarthy when
If you wanted to staff
Committee with
You know trolls and lunatics and
And I Nancy Pelosi was like I think we will decline to have Jim Jordan on the committee
But not with the stupid
Not that
Panda
And all of that
Right is subsumed by the fact that
Again this sites to Article 1
Sections 1 and 8 but the Article 1 Section 5
Clause 2
Of the Constitution
Explicitly States
That each
Chamber of Commerce of Congress
Has the right to set its own rules
Right now and this is a longstanding principle Coast
Back to Before the founding of the
Republic right
It's why the Senate
Has
You know that the filibuster the closure
Requirements
And House of Representatives has fixed time it does not rightly
Those
Because each house
Can set their own rules
And part of what each house can set their own rules means is that
You just need an organizing resolution in either the center of the house
To change those rules
And that the other house the president the courts
They don't get a say
Right and so there is I think
AAA
A knock-down argument
And that basically says
This is
If if you want to bring this kind of loss
For you to have standing
You must have been a
Grief you must have been
Personally enjoy
And why
By the Rumpke subpoena that you feel is not cool that's not
Qualifying as being the green
Right because
That's subpoena
Is within the lawful power of congress
The person or persons
That have been agreed right away when you say
For example as it says in in
Count one paragraph 70th listing the failure
And it says
Failing to appoint representative Davis Armstrong and Neil
Troy meals
Richmond from Texas
To the select committee despite her promise to do so
That's because
Kevin McCarthy said none of them would serve
The failure to appoint Davis Armstrong and deals
The court is going to say will you know who's been injured by this potentially that might have a cause of action would be Davis
Armstrong and Neil
If Trey Neal's thinks he belongs on the 16
Text committee let him come in here
An end argument but who on Earth is Alex Jones
To come in and go we are
Geranios really should be on those
He wanted me to take this one for him and see what I can do
It it so
I do not think the one week when we go back
The
Be kind of motion to dismiss motion for summary judgment standard
I would be
Shocked
If
Count one
We're to survive emotion
I think that the 16 committee is going to say
Alex Jones you don't have standing
To argue
Weather
This committee was
Dooley
Convened
You don't have standing to argue about the internal processes by the way
The court likely does not have standing to adjudicate
Write like
Because that's great
Stop you've violated the rules right like the house kicks you out
You know your your record is not
Clear to me
Where
Your recourse lies even if you are
The member who has been expelled
It is certainly
Clear to me that you do not have that
Remedy vicariously
On behalf of somebody
So
The argument of
This isn't a real committee
And so therefore none of it
Subpoenas are real
I think is
Not likely to
But what about the second account and if I may quote
Come on come on
Oh yeah I think that that makes total sense the way Vapes
It would be dealt with is even if Alex was somebody who could put forth the lawsuit
If this is
Naughty real committee
Then it would be dealt with within the house
And like Nancy Pelosi would get censored
Not forming the committee correctly
Or something
Yeah I think that's exactly right
Because again
What are the other things just to kind of keep in mind as you know as we move through
It is that
Right now
The injury that Alex Jones has suffered is
Someone has given him a
And he is required to show up and talk
Particular date
It's tough for him to talk
I can do that
Episode
As you might imagine right like that that is
This contains a whole lot of speculation that after he talks he's going to get arrested
Got the trying to lock me up
But again
The general standing Doctrine right like it
Very very clear article 3 of The Constitution
Courts
Do not a judicate hypothetical
There must be a live case or controversy
Problem for Alex
It really is and so look like
There is some anticipatory
Behave
I just want to be clear because you will have lawyers who were listening
And you know
Sometimes there is
Contact which is imminent which you know the other side has said
It will take for example B
The agency phone
When when AT&T says I'm going to turn these over honor before December 5th or on
December 15th
Unless you get a court order and you could go in the court on December 10th for the courts I could be like well let's wait till the 15th and see if 8
AT&T turns
I have a concrete injury when a party is said I
I'm going to do this in the future
But
I am worried that the house
Microphone
Fermi over to the doj
Which then might in turn
Cite me for a misdemeanor right is the kind of chain of inferences that that
Acworth going to be like
Well yeah
Call us call us back when you get arrested sir
A better
The position to make a claim
If he actually got arrested
You think he would
Nightclub
Which is probably like never will be
Correct count to is described as violation of the separation of powers contained in the US
Constitution
I can not clear that this is a cause of action this is more
Thing that you know what's it about
Principal and put also ironically wouldn't
If this case went forward violate the separation
Of the powers
Of the Executive MBA judicial
Burnside the legislative and judicial
It is so weird to me
That
Fitbit that the Trump has been making this argument based on separation
The powers
And it is an argument in favor of
Kind of the unitary executive
Right it is
We must have separation of powers and that means
The defective Branch can do whatever the hell it was
That is not you know if you seem like the Schoolhouse Rock
Videos right like
That's not really what separation of powers is meant to be about
Separation of powers is meant to be that the 50 branches of government
A relatively co-equal branches and so the idea is if the legislature
Issues a subpoena
Wright Vet
The
Executive branch will duly issue right there
The sheriff will
Carry that subpoena out to where it belongs and that the Judiciary will enforce the subpoena if you do not
It is in fact what's subpoena means right
Combat is an adversarial V like parts of the government
That seems that seems
The really tough to be function
Yeah that's right nnn I will tell you again count to just reiterates the
There's no legislative purpose argue
You know we have
Beaten to death
If it's the fact that
That there is also a criminal component
Is not disqualifying
They quote
From the mazars cases
And so you know it
Acworth is just going to look at
This be like
Under Mazar
You have to have valid legislative purpose
You can say as they do in paragraph none of the
Pick up 84 quotes
None of the information sought by the John stabiner the AT&T subpoena will even remotely inform a valid legislate
Purpose, I'm sorry. Jose is activities pertaining to January 6th
2021 Arbor
Affected by the First Amendment
Which also provides a corresponding right to privacy in his activities to correct a peaceful in lawful protest
About that sentence is nonsense
But you can say
It's not a valid lunch with a purpose
But Congress in the responses to be like
Figuring out
How people planned any legal insurrection
Is absolutely critical to us figuring out how to write lost
Anacortes going to be like
And it's such an easy argument to make that like we have
Reason to believe that there's information that you're in possession of that would be relevant to
Informing this future legislate
So
Simple of an argument to make
He was hanging out with Allie Alexander all over the place
That alone is enough
Retreat that is exactly three in which
We have
An application areas is it labeled
Violation of the First Amendment
And again you will not see it like
Usually
For example
The way in which you might typically
Speed
A broader First Amendment
Is
You know a section 19
83 action against
State cup that keeps
Shutting down your outdoor rally
In which you are in a lobbying for you
Occupy Wall Street
And so
You would say
This is a violation of the
First Amendment
Because
You have a state actor
Police
Who is using their authority to shut us down
And they're only shutting us down because they don't like our message
You know the Young Americans Foundation
Gets to hold a rally every other night and they never get
That's how you bring these kinds of
You identify the state actor that has
Interfered
Speech you identify the speech that has been in
Interfered with
And then you know you
Please discrimination
On that basis there's already a problem
The globalists
I don't know if that's going to fly
It isn't right because
As you look at it right back up 87 says
That the documents sought by The subpoena include
All documents pertaining to political protests and
When's the Jones attended
Proceeding and after January
Okay you can see why they would want that
Second Astro Sign if I'll communication methods that he use that are related
To the political protests and
Him to produce.
Notwithstanding the
The grammar of
Third day that shows to disclose all Financial account
Pertaining to
Financial transactions donation speaking fees
And other fees the Jones receive
A connection with
He protested demonstration
Stations in the days preceding and
After generation
This includes Financial
Cancel
Forte that reproduce all documentation regarding his trip to Washington d.c.
Honor about January 526
Including his hotel accommodations in
Security at again
I know you know this
Part of that is there is an allegation
That Donald Trump maintained
A war room at the Willard Hotel for
For coordinating
The
And so wanting to know if Alex Jones stayed at the Willard Hotel
Is why they have that hotel
I mean the white I think they could just go watch his show from the day
Did you figure that out right right quick
They do it remember like lawyers will ask
Four things that are
Over-inclusive
Particularly if you're going to
Make a criminal referral
Write as a lawyer it is easier for me
To introduce information
That a party has produced themselves
That authenticate
Right that there's no
Question LOL you know you're good
You know you have we seen Alex Jones do this
Independent
You better get together clip to my show that could be anything I don't
I have any recollection on that 5 Second
Are you better than
Then we watched him do that in
Firestone
And and so
So that's why you would even if you've got
Publicly available
Clips
Always better to go
Sure
Right so
Trips to DC
Document city has by fundraising for any the protest
You made a mistake of talking about that quite publicly about his
Fundraising efforts for the ellipse rally
But yeah that alone would be like well we need to
Hear about this
That's exactly right and when we get to
That that the Fifth Amendment
Claims
Right that's
That's going to be instantly rella
Because
Spoiler alert
You can
Leave the 5th
Much as you want but if you plead the fifth on a subject
Upon which
You have
Previously either given testimony
Or spoken at length in public
You've waived
You're privileged
You cannot
Selectively and deceptively release
The good stuff
And then when asked questions about it Billy why
I claim the fifth
Right like you 5th is All or Nothing
Are you talking about it or you don't
You can't defend yourself
Ryan contextualise thing
Cat inside of it
Yeah that's exactly right
The upside is it is
If you do absolute and end
@alex jumping and Buena Vista
Kind of the initial statement in it
It and it remains sort of what I
Expected him to do
All of this
I should I should just bracket
Alex Jones could just show up before the ones
He would get asked the
Answer state your name for the record
I am Alexandra Jones
Where do you live
Baba blah
Question number one
What were you doing on you know
Xscape
Answer
I decline to answer that question on the grounds and anything I say may tend to incriminate
And then dead literally like
Just ripped
That sentence robotic
I assert my Fifth Amendment right to privilege in declined answer that question on the grounds anything I say may tend to incriminate
For the entirety of the hero
And he didn't get arrested
Raped because
Because even if your Rodger Stone and Ed Rodger stone is let's be honest about this a cartoon
Level supervillain
She has Richard Nixon tattooed on his back
True forget about that
He's the person who who
Called up a Jerome corsi and said
I need you to do a Frankie five Angels right like the bad guy
This is
Rodger stone is being
Shinto the
The rule that you know everyone is the hero in their own story like
The villain in his own story but like another guy with great hats
Can't take that away from him
I like the I like the pinstripes
Denver
Also
Bruce Lee hit on a friend of
Hope Rising
But frankly
But but he was somebody with
Be the second God
I could so the bile is creeping up in my throat as I say this but like
Who knows how to
Manipulate
Write like
You you turn over the documents you want to turn over
You answer
You know whatever questions you want
To answer
Including done and Ed by the way like
You could even start
I have seen it done you could plead the fifth in response to state your name
Typically the way that
That that gets done is win
Drug dealers file
Anonymous tattoo
Returns
And one of the reasons
You do that is because
The IRS enforcement mechanisms
Are more robust
In many cases
Mechanisms and they have
People who understand it and so
There are I'm given to understand drug dealers who pay taxes
What they do is
They write occupations rugby
Dealer right Revenue tax source of revenues drug-dealing
And then on on the list your
Name say you don't little asterisk
I decline to State my name or social security number on the grounds of anything I'm a Dubai
So soaked the point is
You go in you sit down you take five
And you just on a quest
Buy question basis
Decline dancing on the ground meat endocrine it myself
You don't need
This lawsuit to stop you from doing that you
You could do that
And you'd be fine
You want this. AT&T
From turning over
Yourself
Weather's bad but then also you're forgetting about the really crucial element of that is
Attention
Being able to present yourself as the victim of a gigantic
Government-wide conspiracy
You know that that's the real reason for this lawsuit
It is
Like
These allegations here in this
It is so I agree with you
I just got a bringing count 3 to a close right like me
Alex Jones has kept can point to
Aspects in which
He has been
Retaliated against
For freedom of speech
Censored unable
YouTube say what
He says
Demonstrable e crazy stuff
3 hours a day everyday I know cuz I listen to you guys
So
The idea that
Defendants
This is quoting directly from paragraph 91
Defendants seek to probe activities that Jones conducted in his capacity as a journalist
What are the things that you could do is
Probe activities that people conduct in there
Fastest turtle
That's not
That's not a fit right like it's not like oh
The First Amendment super important so you know journalist could break the law
Yeah you can't kill someone while you're reporting
That literally
Think about that if
If a if a member
Of the state
Republican Party
In-N-Out
Connecticut
We're nice
And you
Found a bloody knife
In Alex's house
Right you would then say I want to know all of your interactions
Republican party of Connecticut
That's not a violation of the first amendment in Belle Chasse
You're dumb
It just gets this continues to get the super quickly open till
For which is a violation of the Fourth Amendment
Because
This is again another nonsense count where
A remedy already
So this argument is the Fourth Amendment prohibits the defendants from issuing sweeping subpoenas untethered
From valid legislative
Already you have remember the you know the whole painting example I gave like
This is requires you to accept
The premise
That there are no valid legit
If you already think there are discount adds nothing to the
So which one gets knocked down then for is
Knocked out as well and I think it is
I think
What 12 most of
+ + 4
Are all contingent on you accepting the argument that
You know this is just a Witch Hunt
Carrying out a u
A criminal
Poorly set up dominoes
Typically when you have Independent Health you want them to be more than a Domino's with the park
Cuz
You look like this happens all the time like in in civil cases you'll go in with 7 count
Flip the other side will move to dismiss all 7 you might lose two or three sir and that's fine
Dennis just
You do not want to have to lose your entire case
Because the core allegation
Whatever some who am I to tell Norm
Add a practices job
Delightfully there was also a specific remedy
If
Congress
Or anybody
Issues
An overly Broad
Or
Illegal or unconscious
2-channel subpoena you can move to quash that subpoena
You set out your objections
True that subpoena
And
Mitigate that independent
That is not the okay that is 8
The way what you do that is you just control left
Document and you type in the word qua
Sometimes
Delightfully gifts
Gets ever put in the media's eight
Motion to squash switch
Which I love butts
Squash does not appear because
That's not a thing there.
Count five is the violation of the Fifth Amendment
And
And again
Get there if there's a remedy
There is quash in this in this document
Oh
Really oh well it's it's quashing is in the h
Part of the prayer for relief
So it is down
It it's it's
If the relief that they want done
But have not asked for help. Setup
In the legal sex
Yes
They want
The this court to quash the subpoenas
But the way in which you get the court to quash The subpoena is by moving
Takuache
Or
Pointing that out as relief in the
Count that
Neither of which app
It's the fact that this shows up yeah poorly structured
Correct
It's the kind of thing that if you were a civil litigator you you might have known to do
So
Yeah then we have it so so let's go back to the
That the violation of the Fifth Amendment
Again
Everything in here right Jones's inform the defendant
He intends to exercise his Fifth Amendment right to remain silent
Okay great
Come in and do it on the record
Right
They have informed his counsel that they believe they do not believe he can properly assert that
Okay
That's also fart you know what that
That's a thing that people litigate against all the time and again
What you do is
You
Builddirect
Toledo
What you come in
And
You sip
Had to give test
And
You either answer the
Question or you decline to answer in the way that I took
And then when it's over
Brent
Then in
In a
Typical
Congress can look back and go
When I asked you if you know what
What color your shoes were you said I decline to answer on the grounds of that may tend to incriminate me
What's a basis for that
Objection
Right
And you could go into court
And one of the things that you can do
In court
Helps resolve these
Is a court can undertake
What was called in camera inspection
Of
Documents
Testimony whatever
So another words
Like it if if I have a valid
Assertion
And that is chal
One of the things that I can prop
I can say well
I'm going to disclose this
To the judge
And once I tell the judge
The judge will then you know
And the judge will
Be able to look at this and go yeah that is
Totally
A valid
And then keep it confidential without
Telling the other side
And in fact
Quartz do this
All the time
Because
When you have Discovery issue
Typically the way in which
One side will
Withhold another document
Yeah we're not going to give this document to because we think
It's covered by attorney-client
And
I've lived on this issue I've lost on this issue where I've said
Okay we want to judge to take a look at
Because if you didn't have some sort of mechanism for that
But you couldn't get anything done
That's exactly what would ever testify to anything
Go to be pointless
Yeah you would it would either be every time you assert the Fifth Amendment they would say well what are you doing that for and you would have to tell them
Meaning
Poor
You could just say I plead the fifth sorry and then they would be like oh well we're not allowed to ask why
So you know congratulations right
Hoist by our own petard
And
Delightfully
I just have to say
Kept out 6
Use
The kind of it is is a chef's kiss
That's the way it is the
Does the Whopper thin mint
The end of a Gourmand meal
It is
Violation of the stored Communications Act
18 u.s.c. section
Stored Communications act provided
That a
Person or entity providing electronica
Vacation service
Switch to the public
Shall not knowingly divulge to any person or entity
The contents of a communication while in Elektra
Public Storage
By that surface
And you say nothing like
Well that
Probably make sense
I can understand why we would have a law that says
If you are storing somebody else's
No data
That die you will not publish
You're probably thinking
But there are exceptions to that was my first thought
At one of the reasons he could tell that is because
The complaint addressed this in a single sentence which says
None of the exceptions enumerated it 18 USC section 2702 A1
Maybe because the exceptions are listed
2702 B
But it says
A provider
Beige Eiffel
The contents of a comedic
And then
It lists
All the different ways
In which you can divulge
Law enforcement agencies surprise
And you can have doubled it
To a governmental entity if the provider in good faith believe sit-in emergency involving danger death
We're serious serious physical injury to any person
Requires disclosure without delay of communications related to the mm
Or
So by the way like
I think that is
That is probably
That is that that Criterion is probably met
And it is important to note
That that that is
Independent of the knockdown so
I'm about to get to
This is to say
Without
A subpoena
AT&T or any of these companies
Could voluntarily disclose
Any of this data to the government
And say
Look in good faith
We Believe
That there is an emergency
Involving danger of death
We're serious physical injury
To whip you
People planned an Insurrection and maybe planning one again
And we're giving you these records without you asking for it and without their consent
Now
What are the things you might be thinking is
What about
Like where there's a subpoena in the answer to where there's a subpoena is
Yes as otherwise authorized in this title including section
Which is required disclosure of customer
Communications are records and it says
The governmental entity may require a provider of remote Computing Services
To disclose the contents of any wire electronic communication without required notice to the
Favorite customer
If the entity obtains a warrant issued using the procedures
Describing the federal rules of criminal procedure
Or in the case of a state court issued using
State board procedures
Or use as an administrative subpoena authorized by federal or state statute for federal estate Gray
Sure your trials
And
Of course
House resolution 503
Empowers the select committee committee investigating the January 6th
Attack of the United
To issue subpoenas
The chair of the subcommittee this is
Section 3 subsection c6a
The chair of the select committee upon consultation the ranking minority member
May order the taking of depositions including pursuant to subpoena
I member or Council of the subcommittee
In the same manner as a standing committee person with two
This other
Another words that was a lot of legal jargon
But this law says
It's illegal for a
A telecommunication
Provider to turn over your
Your private stuff
Unless they meet any of the requirements
And there were multiple exceptions it very plainly apply that there is the public emergency
The end of the fact that they'll be complying with a legislatively ballads
If I understand correctly
You have you have a situation here where
The argument
If it ain't count one essentially is needed to back up the idea that the subpoena to get ATT to turn off
Over the records
Is not a valid exception to that rule
But
That's not even necessary
Like even if
That wasn't considered an exception to the turning over the records
18t cotuit voluntarily
So that is exactly right so that will not hold up at all
It will.
Remotely holdup
I don't know who's going to advance that argument
Given that they can sue AT&T
I mean the house is likely to just Advance the
I don't know what you're talking about
You say it doesn't meet any of the exception
But one of the exceptions is
If a governmental entity issues a valid subpoena and by the way we got a house resolution that says
We can issue subpoenas
So
This is the
Kind of thing
That a DUI lawyer searching through the US code
Might come across and be like
Hey
They didn't
You know divulga
Communication
Without asking me
I got them
Activate this is a DUI lawyer / constitutional expert
I should have you know
Hey baby
It is just
Like
Listing this is
When you make a mistake of of that kind of level
Really
Color
The rest of your pleading in the eye of
I thought even
Without some of that legal reasoning
There's a lot of language in there that is really loaded
There's a lot of like you don't like
For instance the saying
Is Liz Cheney even a Republican
That kind of accusation
The other Witch Hunt language and stuff and like
Paragraph in particular was saying that like
This
Committee is
Just grown out of the failures to impeach Donald Trump
It seems like
That's an unearned
Conclusion to reach and including it in
The background
Of the
You're playing Sims
Shity
That's right
If there's there's a number and
Ed so I mean you really point out
Two things
Step
Again
You know
It
I bet dick jokes for a live
Living right left
But we filed last year
An amicus
In the Michael Flynn
And
I basically
Put my firm on hold for two months
And
And we rode into a dresser
Particular
Part of the law when this was back
Before Donald Trump had issued.
General pardon
And when he was just trying to get
Via Bill Barr
Trying to
End up
You would not find the same kind of informal language that I have employed on this podcast Ron open
How you communicate
Territories different
General vocabu you can switch between
Yeah I think that's a good way of putting it so
You know it's so true
If it's too full
Versus PlayStation 4
This just jumped out to me to write
Paragraph 6 says defendant Elizabeth L Chaney is purportedly a Republican
Of the US House of Representatives and you'll like
When you get down to it multiple times
And then
There is right beginning it
Craft 38 like
A question exists as to whether defended Cheney is still a member of the Republican Party the
Wyoming Republican party has expelled her in
What
The second half
The brightest is so
So you have the kind of like
Firebrand language that
Voted for the committee to exist in the first place therefore she didn't show loyalty to
Before 4 right and therefore she is not a Republican or Republican
Pretending she's pretending to be
But
And that's the second part is that like
Beyond kind of being intemperance
Is the
Irrelevant
Schleich
Why on Earth would this
Mater like
Say she's a bad Republic who the hell cares
That this
This
Winning or losing on this point
Right
Is is of absolutely no moment to Yorkie
It seems like just something that could play for like
Media
You know they get something that
Like it's feels like a dunk
For them
Yeah it
It's hard for me because you know I have waited through on my show the like
64 separate election lawsuits filed by the Kraken lawyer team
Is Sidney Powell and Howard
Kleinhandler end
And I
It was one of the things that I
Really
Initiated
In the sanctions
So they the in Michigan
That whole team was sang
Byland
Glorious
7 hour
Grilling of the lawyers
Which iWatch
Start to finish
You know it's just still like
Better than any
I saw also
That's your Superman
It Rialto yeah do that was yeah that was
The Super Bowl game 7 of the World Series in 00
Mixed together
And nnn what was really like
Masterful about
Was
Got universe
Cutting through the b*******
The city of
Detroit hire de
Lawyer David
To kind of be the
Turn on
That
On that sanctions
And
And he just
Expert
We was able to do things like
Call the side like the dog whistling that's in their pleadings right like
So
They're pleading
Contained
The
Fraud vitiates everything with a citation 2
A case from
End
NN it was David think he was like
I thought it was kind of odd as I was reading through their briefs
That they would cite to this you know
Fraud vitiates everything in this single like obscure Supreme Court case that
Isn't relevant that has never been cited before you know in the
The previous history and then I went on the internet and realize like oh
What they're doing is
You know copying shitposting from qanon Bright
Attitude dog whistle to their to their constituents and this is additional grounds for why the
Sanctioned
Because they're not acting as lawyers
They're acting as a
Cargo cult of
You know using
Attend legal language
2 stirrup
And rally their followers
But put them up
Even pretending to practice law in this court
And part of what that what made it into
Not only did that make it into the
Order weird
Sanctions
But there's a lengthy footnote that
Enid encouragingly
Tri-State bars
To disbar all of
They should that that mention that
Sidney Powell is fundraising over at defend the Republic
On the basis of these hearings them
Look you know if if that's not enough
To tell you
That that these people are not
Practicing
As lawyers in good faith
Should have that privilege
I don't know what
Antiemetic
Tecta keep me a little bit of Hope
For the future Viper
Professional well
A glimmer of something
Dark Times
Makes it even more seems like
Brand of dog whistle kind of thing
Is that there is like Adam
Kinzinger is another Republican
Who's on the committee
He is a republican wouldn't he then just be like who cares if Liz Cheney isn't a Republican
He already got them
It is the illustration of how
You know
Half of the allegation
In this Meandering loss
Don't matter even for the things that you were allege
Probably Stillwood to yell at Congress though.
If you're Alice probably cathartic
Well I think that's right and that's why you know we've
Because Witnesses
Needed the
Reading the complete
Play Backwards right because all the things were talking about now
Are in the factual and allegation
And this is why I read the black
Sprite because
Dead-end is particularly egregious in this case
But
You know it's true in other cases as well like
A fact
Is not relevant
In that section
If it does not line up with the stuff
They say they're going to prove and give their legal causes of as
Towards the bottom
Area
That's okay
I'm going to remember that when I'm reading these in the future
Every element
That is required
Please
Of
Criminal
Or if it's a
Civil lawsuit
Rights
Has to match up with
Fact or facts
That are asserted in the facts
What there's nothing to stop a lawyer from lording it up with a whole bunch of others
I have traditionally read these kind of filings is like I'll start reading through the facts
And I'll be like, what the f*** this is nonsense
And then I'll scroll down to the bottom
And see what point you're trying to make
Skip that first part
It's just frustrating
Yeah it it will it will definitely
Save your blood pressure
Yeah I thought was really interesting in the background section is it appears that there is admitting
That they were trying to stop the certification of the Electoral College
Saw that too and I wonder if I wonder how
Interacts with
What
John Eastman has been try
Right because we got
The contents of the Eastman memo which are
The playbook for the insurrection
Right it is
It says halfpence go down
Have a friendly Senator Rand Paul Ted Cruz
Abject
You don't have pimp say I'm not going to see these delegation so I'm going to throw them all out
And then you know xy&z Walker
An easement has tried to walk.
Backbite by arguing
Completely disingenuous
Everywhere
He's been
Including an egg
Utterly
Uncritical puppy
Review what look like
That was a what is
I also put a longer memo out there and you know when I told Pence Direct
You know of which there's no.
Even Tatian no memo and nobody
I told him directly I didn't think this was a great
Idea but that Mama was just what if you thought it was a great idea
Here's how that might play out first page of the memo it said whatever you do don't do this
Yeah
Legal memos to my clients where you rip off the
The first page says
For the love of God do not do anything written on the next
Terrible idea coming terrible idea
They're saying the Trump supporters
Got together started protesting the in opposition to the certification of the Electoral College votes
I meant in paragraph 19
It's basically a well-known episode happened
I quotes on January 6th
They were a large group of protesters they enter the US Capitol breach security and disrupted the counting of the Electoral College vote
Connecting the dots between 18 and 19 is the mission of the 1650
It seems like a bad thing to have him the statement of facts
Dissection
Ino this is why when you answer
Complained
Sometimes you admit the allegation
I would not submit again I don't think this is going to get to answer States cuz I think
This is all going to be
Dismiss
Out of hand for life
Understanding
Coherence
Upstate
Yeah
How I wish I lived
In the
Ductulator
2016 and earlier world before they were her
The Deep state of now you know that is
I get to hear that
Major news
There's so many sundry weirdos that I'm aware of now that
I had no idea where alive or existed
Years ago
Yes I wish I could
Time travel my brain back
Well and
And thanks to your show I mean
It it
The
Until I became aware of what you guys were doing and then
Got
Suck
Down the rabbit hole of
Just
Oh okay
The Crazies crazies right
The it gets it was easy to kind of think of the
Like
Trump supporting right as an undifferentiated Mass
As opposed to the sort of lie
Loosely help nucleus of
Of competing and what time
The fundamentally
Contradictory
We're really all just would have held together by
Cult of personality and
But but I love it when you expose the
You know
The ways in which there might be a
An uneasy tension
If I do I just can't get enough I know I know this is unrelated to the that I would give
All of it back
If the rest of the world didn't have to be aware of who Allie Alexander is there's no reason for her to be articles about
Healthy Alexander in Main Street
That's why we had to come on the show window and Owen Shroyer was indicted
No one needs to know his name
I know who knows who the hello it's rare
One more question less there's anything else you wanted to take it to in there
I feel like we've hit the main points and also that your prediction is
Not great
This is the Outlook is not good for this case the 8-ball Outlook not so good
About
Big question that I had that I have no idea what that is like is there any kind of a punishment
You can end up getting
For making a frivolous lawsuit against Congress
Know that it did get there
That's probably for the best
Cuz it seems like you could end up
But like
Punishing people for
Well maybe you should punish them for
Wasting everyone
So
You know that this is
This is part of a of a larger
Project
That that I think
And it has its roots in the
Between
What we called the American system in the European such a butt really have to be like the American system and pretty much everywhere else
That is
With which Sonics
Write our system
Is the
Capitalist
Free market
Each side pays their attorneys fees no matter what
And there are laws
The Confucius
If there are
Egregious
That confused
But by and large like
If I sue you even if I win
Right I pay my lawyer's fees you pay your loan
As opposed to other the the
European model
Is largely a
A loser
And so
You know
There are
It's been a tough scholarship about this
Centennial
Start thinking about the arguments going back
Back and forth
You know
How that
Interacts but
But one of the things is that that means
In the United States
We have
You were disincentives
Abusing.
NN I'm in class
You know
At the risk of being sort of 2
You know small-c conservative about change
Probably a good idea
Right here I can see what I can see what you mean
Part of me was just curious about like if there is like a slap kind of thing
Look like Nancy Pelosi could hit Alex with a slap suit
Yeah no
That is an example
Full of
Institute strategic lawsuits
Station their states like California for example that have very very robust
That that have essentially imposed a process
On top
Of another
So what's up
In
Digital Communications
Bloggers podcast
That that existing laws
We're really
Not sufficient
To protect
That the balance
And the important
Free and open
Communication City impose
A different set of procedures
If you think you have if you if you've been sued
Right over thing you've said
Published
Do any of the claw
Online on a Blog
Gunn Auto Parts
It is only drink
California then you can go you can invoke kind of December
Brit special
Procedure
Get it adjudicated quickly
And potentially get your attorney's fees
Fees paid for
So this is an example of
Of one of the
Specific substantiv changes
But it would be like the way you think about it is like
That's the proverbial exception
Yeah that makes sense.
The Baseline is
You know ya unless unless somebody
Where you can bring
The cause of Acts
For abusive
Is when
Somebody
Uses the legal system
In a way that they that they
No
Is raw
And I know that
That seems like a tough distinction but
But here's
The case that I can
Think of that thing
Suppose
I threatened to sue you
And then I write up a
But I don't know but I never asked
We filed
Right because I know
It's it's
Bullshitz
But I can't a copy of it
Process server
And
Tell him to track you down
And hand it to you and say all right well now you've been served you're going to have to respond
Or you know you can
Pay me $10,000 and I'll
That becomes an abusive
Surprise
Because
I know I didn't really filed
Right
Like I'm using the legal system
In a way that I know is
It's Roxy if there was the demand for $10,000 that was just a prank
Well if I file the lawsuit I'm perfectly entitled if that's no legal extortion
Lawsuit
Send it serviced have a big meme guy show up at your
At your house
And then call you up and be like all right you're going to write us a
Check or you know this lawsuits going forward with the weird lines
You file it legal extortion if you don't ask for money it's a prank
If you don't file
Again we should emphasize do not take legal advice for this podcast
Absolutely.
There was one thing that I was thinking about I didn't think that Alex stood any kind of a risk of
Getting in trouble if you plead the Fifth
Or even if you produced
Some documents or whatever
Play Blake what Rodger stone is doing basically
I got to hold him in criminal contempt
And like
Thrown in prison or something
But I was wondering
I'm getting the sense that this is not
Likely or even possible
I was wondering if there was a chance
B from like
Putting a suit like this that's
Frivolous
Just nonsensical he could f*** around and cause his own criminal contempt
Chart
Does that make sense
Yeah
So I mean what you would have
Have to show is
That you know that he is materially
Obstructing
That the work of the
End
And again
You know
It's strange music
Right side one of I-10
Would kick I get that
But that could also be a tough standard to have with any question related to Alex of it being materially UPS truck
Is Elias material any of the information they get from him they can probably get from Ali Alexander
Any of the other people they've
Subpoenaed and apparently they can
AT&T stuff
With or without it
Yeah well and that
Debbie this is sort of a good kind of opens a door
We talked a little bit
About when you
Canon camp
Take 5
Underprivileged
Right you have a very very good argument
Because Alex
Gave a play-by-play of his involvement with
Fundraising giving speeches on January 6th telling people to show up
Right
I think you have a very good argument
That he's wave
If if not
The
Privilege against self-incrimination innocent
Tiger tea
Certainly with respect to specific
Text subject matter that that you know you can
Play the clip from the show would be like okay right and so
What are the ways in which
This is my
Play out
If and when outside
Show up
Congressman Raskin for example is
Very very
Until I can see
Write asking a question
Ghetto mr. Jones we would like to talk to you about
Your efforts
Fundraise
With the
I-16
Correction
Have you
Raised funds
In connection with
Any argument that you know the
Action was
Improper
Or you know what I'm after
Was there a promo code stop the steel that you enter to get 50% off supplement
You get him to assert
Fifth Amendment privilege and then you say respectfully
Jones Avenue
Play
Ghetto that clip of you know come on down
Get 50% off
And then now you've set up a really really good Wrecker
Heard a we come back and say
With that in mind giving you up already
Spoken at length in public about the
Serve respectfully what's the basis
For your
Asserting
At your fifth amendment privileges here like that
That's how I would want to
Set that up
Seems like obitalk
I just feel like giving how much public statements he's made
It would work against him
To play the
So tell me what you'd so tell me what you think
I mean like you said so much about so many topics and in ways that really don't look good
Without being able to spend them a little bit
If you please the fifth on things then he is also giving away is ability to
He'll defend himself on some of these subjects if he's
You know
Play I'm not going
That's what like
Maybe
Defend himself
Answer the question
Better than
Playing something you said in the password
That makes sense
If
You're not thinking about
Kind of potential criminal charges
Great Lakes as a lawyer
God help me I would never be Alex Jones
Right but but but I'm thinking
Yeah I know what you what you want to do is say nothing on the rec
Leave here
And then say whatever the hell you want on your double
Little shop
And and
The idea that
You know yeah
Is it possible that you could get in like
You know what good Zinger
Really
You know Market something from your appearance
It is
A Boy by Sister lawyer would be
Let's not risk you know potential
Perjury charges criminal contempt 2usc 192 rightly
But let's not run afoul of that in in seeking the the Holy Grail but on the other hand like
You know
I don't know how
Easy it is
For Alex Jones lawyers Tucker
Corral him
They certainly all seem to be True Believer
Right
Maybe
Obiano
Is
Opportunist
But
It is always hard to differentiate opportunistic
True belief yeah and then then you ask the question of like what are they True Believers do is it the like philosophic
. or is it
The Griff
You know
Not that becomes a murky area
Yeah it was City Paulino
Exactly what she is a trooper
Yeah with the red white and green little bit less so
Yeah I guess I have one last question alright
There is video of one of Alex's employees
Walking into the capitol while video recording
Streaming
And as he's walking through the threshold into the Capitol building on January 6th
He's giving a a plug for a sale at Infowars store
It's one of the cameramen
Who's there
That looks bad right
It looks bad
But but I will say that
The fact that it's a
Cameraman
Right it gives you the opportunity if you're out
Alex Jones to say
You know well that
Maybe that's just obvious
That person
Never had
Apparent waraq
Actual authority to
To speak on behalf of Infowars LLC
You know whatever he
He's calling his company now remind Kathy plugs
And it sounds kind of silly but like
That is part of the standard
Buffalo
Uses
When you
Hold yourself out as representing an organization is
Do you say okay well would a
Unordinary
Person
In that position
Think that you represent that organization
And
Create some kind of
I want to see perverse incentives but like
What's the weather the things that Alex Jones will be able to say in his defense is everybody knows Infowars is me
Rights and I will come in and I will
Cut off right other people don't get to do plugs on my show I'm the one who authorizes the
The plugs
Get out I was thinking about the
That the hypnotist conman guy with
The deuce
Ed
You should have documenting the
Palpable anger
Right when he took over giving
The plugs and
Doing the throat
Commercial
Yeah seriously right like
This is where you get those kind of moments
That were you know
Astonishing right like
I don't recall if you asked the Young
The Sandy Hooks
Plaintiff lawyers
Question but like
Everybody around me was
Raymour astonish
When Alex Jones you know introduced
The testimony of like
Well you know this is kind of a character I play on the show
I don't really mean the stuff that I say and it's all for entertainment
As a lawyer that didn't strike me as odd at all right like that struck me is precisely the kind of thing you would
So you know you kept
He's kind of great
Moments where
The thing that
That seems like
Make good legal sense
Maybe it
You do a p hard disaster but
But for me is Alex Jones's
Lawyer game
Like I would relish the opportunity to be like
Yeah I know sorry
Everybody knows like
That that can't remember like fired 2 days later like you don't
You do not abuse her
Plugs for mr. Jones on
It's almost like being his lawyer would be like a challenge round you decide to get fancy
Do it like pull off little arguments
If this universe is a simulation right like an end and I'm the lawyer character
I feel like I've had the difficulty turned up to
The hard but
You know representing Alex Jones wood with ratchet set up to
Yeah that's instant death mode
Joining me on this I really appreciate your insights into the
The lawsuit
I had to
Little idea of how flimsy it was
I knew it was not good
Just for my own reading but
You hear you break that break a lot of that down I'm worried
I'm worried for Alex
Well that is
Your concern for him is touching season
Important time for him
Have a pic of the die-hard Christmas
But thank you so much for for having me on the show this is
Is this a lot of fun
I
I love what you guys are doing for any of that.
You listen to Alex Jones so I don't
Don't cross to bear but people can check out your fantastic podcast opening arguments
Where can I find that everywhere
Everywhere
That's pretty easy to find we are at openargs on Twitter
But yeah you start
Whatever your podcast vehicle to start typing opening in in
And I think most of the people who was Starbuck yes don't really need any overlap
Indicting listenership
That's what's up
So I think I think we have a lot of lot of s***
Which is pretty pretty fun
Pretty cool love
Love being in the space
Well
Thanks for having me on the picture for sure we'll talk soon
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color