Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for snowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Dot-com
I meant to say
Newsome be home
Fix-It around Alex jordann
Christian fauria
Great time to go because of the intense amount of stuff that happened
Are very particular media sphere
But because
Is the Chicago thing
But he went out
He did not go out is now fix
Song covers it livable in the apartment but yeah it was
It was brutal
Maybe it's just like
Particularly drafty today
Am I in my old apartment I absolutely left it for two days before I even called the landlord
Probably kick back
I think I went more Becky G's I had a little space heater that I could keep my little toes up
While I was here the office but yeah
It was. I should have called quicker
But like they responded really
Stop my landlords
Within an hour
That's amazing so that was that was pretty impressive
And now it's
Warm enough that I have to have oscillating fan Don to have a little breeze
Back home
That was a bad is heroin a trip that I think I've ever taken I got a few texts
About this
You have to have a negative test within 24 hours of leaving and you know that when you're
They're you know that when you're there I don't know if I'm going to make it back on
But when you're get that test in that 15 minutes before you know what's happening
You suddenly realize the gravity of the actual
It's several thousand dollars and God knows what else he liked all of your plan
Everything is fuc
That is a state called now and then the moment we got the negative I wanted to just start screaming at French people like
Hamming cigars the amazing got your test back and you tested negative
Perkovich becauseit of for crepes
Episode get some actually didn't have any
Is very weird
It's never thought I would do that before my life you've discussed it with a whole fish
You find a whole fish
We are on several months now and Counting everywhere
I don't know cat
We made it home my partners bags didn't but they're on their way to it
I nearly forgot mine in France
Along with my wallet and all of my information
We had multiple delays with flight
What about the flight that got back into
Chicago
It lasted an hour longer and we had to wait an hour longer after that where do you fly into Chicago from
Heathrow
Yeah and that
I've not heard the pilot say something like
We made it guys I told like that before
Hey you know we're a little bit behind but
We had some strong winds we had some strong winds and you're like
Can't do anything about it I didn't kill them
Episode
I'm Rusty it is
There's a lot
To get into from the time since you
Yeah
In honor of Alex
There's just too much to get to
We spent four months in a goddamn holding pattern
I'm gone for a week
Everything happen
Too much to get into
Prepared
Princess
I got to get out of here I'm going to get off early to go to rebroadcast unlike Alex
I am going to do a two-part
So we decided to catch up
Is working at this episode and then on Friday tomorrow we will have
Part 2
This is going to be December 21st
Interesting stuff that goes on first before we get into all that little moments say hello to
Between your t's and Cat girls I know which side I'm on
! chernow policy walk
You so much you're now policy want
I'm a policy wonk
Meat House in Via George White thank you so much right now if I was you want
Thank you very much
Curved code either I really
Glasses
Maybe this is a Chicago thing but what is a 40-year old Swede know about that
Thank you so much you're now.
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
Similar
I always enjoyed Mike's May quite a bit though he is the first season of never not funny
Knox
Chicago
Really really talented storyteller
Pretty funny dude many people is called in the Mark Twain in Chicago
I wouldn't do that
Here is where we start off Jordan
This is
Got my ears okay
Today
Apologize
Was legitimately having
Because I'm a real person
Learn self-control I've gotten better about it over the years
I am so upset
With Trump
And the Betrayal
That adjust
Just makes the top of my head blow off I get so angry
Best okay so it's
Pretty rare that we get to start the show with him
Apologizing to the crew for the day before
Book the 21st I'm going back to the 20th obviously there were fireworks
Anything following the I apologize to the girl at the beginning of her show is f*** off that means
Disaster
Yeah
So we start off on the 20th and here is how the show open
Where are the others
In the Democratic Party
This is a
A break is a special report the John bowne
Send
The smash-and-grab
Epidemic
Popularized
Buy black live
By the Democratic
Party
According to witness
Shortly
For the Barton Creek
Square mall closed
During the biggest shopping weekend
For Christmas
Broke into the display
This is just like a flagrantly racist way to cover a story like this
The game of their trying to play is just there was a looting in the aftermath
George Floyd killer
Black lives matter logo
He stops all robbery
Who's really transparent
Just the work of
Cretin bigots
This kind of crime happens a lot
Because as it might be super obvious if you think about it for one second jewelry stores or places
Massive amounts
Highly valuable items
And if their security isn't very good they make for
Compelling soft targets
Cmovies
Contacts
Going to data compiled by the Jewelers
Security Alliance
There were 200
26 Smash and grab robberies of jewelry stores in 2019 and 20
The total number of on-premise
Burglaries during that time frame was
Jewelry stores get robbed a lot
That's why a lot of them have bulletproof glass bars on the window and remote
Door locks of people like you could only enter if the person buzzes you him right right right
You can find from the jeweler's Alliance report is that Texas is the state
Pretty consistently tops
What's the most active States for jewelry store robbery
In 2020 19.8% of the total robberies were in Texas
With California being the next highest state with 8.7
God damn so pretty pretty high above that is like an exemplary
Version of like a man that never ended in Texas it's over double cab
Yeah you said you started robbing people in the 1700's with stagecoaches and it just never stop
Also as you might expect jewelry stores in malls had the highest incidence of Smash
Grab
Which makes sense because the robber would have reason to think they could Escape into the crowd and more easily get away
There was a jewelry store robbery at the mall near Alex's house and now one of his subordinates is
Was making a really racist video about it
Complying with these robberies are happening at a different rate than they always do
It's the fault of Democrats are black lives matter
Food place. And I wouldn't be too surprised if this isn't an attempt to get another panic going like they did with the knockout game
A few years back
To be clear it sucks
The crime is happening but expect me to believe it's the same as losing the brakes
Political unrest
I can only assume that's not attempt to your argument this is just bullshiting
Absolutely
Nonsense
No I need
It's not hard to see all of this and then CV blowback coming from all the propaganda with
At endless
Endless explainers on
The actual data like eyes are all f****** lying to cut crime is going down get the f*** out of here these people are like
Tires trying to get money from you stealing
Your money by telling you that other people are stealing their
I kind of was interested in this because
I don't know
Overly invested in the 20th because Alex apologize for it
Fine I'll listen to John balance report if you have to
This is just
Bulova
This repeater Eyes by black lives matter like black lives matter was like Hey guys
Nobody's ever tried this ship before it's been in the shadows
It's time to really bring it to the Forefront of the tool
Right it's it's like
Rainbow suspenders with the sky
Popularized
Reporting going on in this
Report
Patrons
Before the exit
Claims that a voice came over the loudspeaker
Announcing that the doors have been locked
The innocent
Trapped inside
Desperate arms
In order to
Prophets
Of the blood
Diamond industry
Wait what
Confusing
I can find no evidence of people were trapped inside by any locked doors and in fact
In every article that I can find about this robbery
Disgust me quick evacuation the First Responders did just in case there was any real Danger
There were some reports that people heard gunshots but their ultimate Lee was no evidence of any guns being used in the robbery
Are people most likely heard the breaking glass
From the Smashing at before the grabbing show
So there's no reason to assume that these innocent people were trapped in there was desperate arm Bluetooth
Yeah that would be a crazy thing to immediately leave to
Supervillain level s*** right there I love it
Okay I'm going back to the jeweler's Alliance report only about 35% of jewelry store robberies even involve a guy
If you're trying to be
Quick and there's a high likelihood of you getting caught
That's the wrong
Smash-and-grab and jewelry store robberies
Like if you get unlucky
You don't want to add a gun charge to whatever else you're going to be facing the most people probably wouldn't bring a gun to bad idea
A robbery like that
Yeah it's what burglary versus armed robbery is a difference of like 10-15 years and sentencing or whatever
Something crazy I mean yourself shot easily let's say
I'm confused
Like we both were
The stick 12 the jewelry industry for selling Blood Diamond
Does he not know that the network is shows.on was heavily subsidized by a guy who owns a gold company
Who did a lot of business with a guy was deep in apartheid gold
This is odd to be both like it's mrs. all entirely black
Lives matters fault obviously the profit-driven corporations and made all the decisions made
Play the reason we're here in the first
What are you trying to say to me
Very strange
It's weird to complain to the idea that corporate
Profits are being treated as a higher concern than human life when that's Infowars in
Higher philosophy as its related to covid
Before they embarked on their vaccines are secretly killing everyone season
The earlier argument was that lockdowns attempt to severe and affect on the economy and
But some people
Getting sick was a good price to pay to keep these Corporation
Yeah that oftentimes it was like listen there's a mortality rate under 4% or what
Whatever so we can just live through this let 4% of people die
I don't know this is an incoherent report that I'm listen
I was interested like
I gave it a shot but
John Brown can I keep my attention for more than a minute
Good morning ladies and gentlemen
Alex Jones
Will be here quick
Not interested just going to be there after the first hours
It's going to go bad
So I skipped ahead to the second hour and
What's going on
The Alex Jones Show
Ikea
I truly incredible I have a hard enough time just putting on my show in the morning I was Johnson only does larger
Franklin
Is that all of this stuff and operate the store and deal with all of the attacks on him continuously
Probably stressful and you can afford
Him and all of us of course I going forward store.com take advantage of the Christmas supercell it continues their 60% off plus free
Prepare to make good on your New Year's resolutions
Went smoothly from an apology that Alex isn't here yet
Also Harrison
Desperately
Trying not to say that I was just talking to lawyer
Oh yeah
Absolutely
He's working on the
Code for all of the lawsuits
Since the attacks
Hey but it's just trying not to say like
She's trying to figure out a way that
He's not here today
From cigarette how to build a metaphorical life raft
Epoch time
Because if he doesn't we won't be able to afford a literal life rap
I was Fury
I was promised
Going to be here the 2nd.
I don't like
All right there's something you promises
Again that Alex will be there
47 minutes into the second break of the hour Alex shows up
Well I really appreciate the great Aerosmith a normally host American Journal weekday mornings 8 a.m.
11 a.m.
For sitting in for me
In my office getting ready
For today transmission
So much work in front of me and in so many important things going on that I had to
But I just called
I just took a hundred yards away or so
I'm sad
Ourselves
Take care of this business
Normally my own private business would not be
And the list
To explain myself
Where does country in the world
This morning I went ahead and made the decision
Especially
Wednesday
January 6th
Witch Hunt
Will be filed against the committee
Today
In Washington DC
Alex comes on air is
I'm fucken suing the government and that's what I was doing
So
Maybe
Maybe a little bit of that
The
Pleading the fifth like I was obviously going to do tonight
Pretty much said as much
Repeatedly prior to this over and over and over again
Consequence
Is there written certainly no
Just love the image of how Infowars works
Smith show
Is before Alex Adams and then Alex's show straight away
Pizza from his office
Stay on air
It does have a little bit of an even more chaotic
Shity
30 Rock Live to it
You just like you're peeking out of your cubicle and being I think you could pick me up
On your way back from the kitchen
My name's on that
I got a deal with
With all these lawsuits
Can you cover my shift
So there's another reason Alex's light
It was 11:00 already told Harrison to to do that but then I was doing some more accounting
In the past I just hope the money comes into fun things
This random County
Because this is a place you built this is place you kept on Aaron
That I don't like coming on here
Plugging medicine selling that
Support
Because
That's not the position I like the
But with the supply chain breakdowns inflation all the rest of
Check
Call Wars
Will implode
Within 36
Not bringing enough
Money and because we have to have our own servers
Systems are on satellite uplinks our own
Proprietary systems that we have to go out and have people build in May
Level
Looks like
War bonds in the form of overpriced silver worth a good investment
Seemed to work out the way we had hope
Snow
I'm also I'm not going to put too much
Stock into this 326
Six months number as I've been
I've got my hopes up a number of times and Alex is like work or f***** we're going out of business
Money bomb episode in Year One
When he was like what's
It was different it was in the development of the like
We have a couple months left in the last year-and-a-half that's true
But
Still it's just kind of the new desperate version of exactly what you
Talk about the money bomb
We need to do a 37-hour marathon for freedom of speech
We just got to get rid of all of this product and if you don't get it soon I'm not saying we're going out of business I'm just saying that the
Finish Line is in sight
Need to sell this s***
So you got you got this
What's going on
Bright
Kicked off social media
It's not about the people have been kicked off social media platforms
Alex believe that there's another layer of censorship
It's coming and that is
Apparently blocking URL
Something that is done too like infowars.com here
In the near future and then he predicts a false flag
And I intend to fight as hard as I can
And working with others to build
Structure
Next level deplatforming
Urls
Delisting of URLs that's going to happen right before the midterm
Guaranteed they're going to do that okay
And they're going to Stage Terror attacks and they're going to everything else has
Do you understand that will say on the news that my followers
Blow up the Pfizer building or something
I see Over the Horizon
This is just the same game he always plays
Can you get placenta
But someone might
Take a shot at Pfizer
Whether it's
Some kind of property damage killing people or
I'm some indiscriminate Act
Domestic terrorism
It seems it seems like the temperature in the country among the people who do stuff like that
It's warm
It's in the it's in the higher register the temperature of Alaska right now which is not as cold as anybody would like
From there
That doesn't make me feel good
But it's kind of predictive
The way he always does this
UE makes me skydive
Decorations with there's going to be a false flag
And then when it doesn't happen
Hooray we stopped it right if it does happen
Like someone goes in
Does the act of terrorism
In advance
Perfect propaganda game part about it is
When you say when you tell people they're going to claim
That is my followers who
Who did this
I would have an easier time believing you when you say that your followers would never do this
If you didn't have to immediately remind your followers
Not to do it
Hey guys
Now I've got to remind you guys please
Don't blow up
We must blow up the Pfizer building politically
You're saying that they might
So
You might be confused like I very rarely
Get into the Special Report
I don't really care to talk about Gregory surgery
But this is this one kind of
Interested me and I think
I think I have a theory
About this why is this special report was made
Last night I tried to go see Spiderman
Where they admit
Villain is Alex Jones
There's a snatch-and-grab robberies and shootouts at the mall we didn't know about
Close
No one told us
So I think that's why John bound made the Special Report the beginning of the show
Alex was yelling about not being able to see Spider-Man and Josh Johnson opportunity to score some points
Also Jay Jonah Jameson
Spider-Man character who's an a******
Make some for Alex to assume that his role in the film is much larger
I haven't seen the film but I've heard that they were
Pretty much full Alex with
The characters onscreen there's no way as narcissism is going to allow him to experience that is the Moon
Movie portraying
You have to secretly be with the movies actually about
He's the real bad guy
It is funny
Especially because
Unlike
Other superhero movies
They really
How did the cast of villain
When's with this one
Stick up villains from movies that aren't in the same universe
From the original Spider-Man with Tobey goddamn Maguire Goblin
Somehow I was like well obviously I'm the most important character
You have three Spider-Man Spider-Man
Is the Green Goblin in Spider-Man Spider-Man Spider-Man
A person feeling Billy Billy Billy feeling Alex is still somehow convinced he's the super villain in this story
I like it
Kind of fun he's the comic foil
This guy is he doesn't even know when the superheroes in front of
Got to get that vigilante Peter Parker
It's ironic that he's my main source of income
Yasso Alex believes
Himself
To be the villain
0 superpowers that which is kind of which is kind of a bummer
They made Alex into the villain to Spider-Man because
I mean not afraid
It's not like I'm up here saying oh look
I'm the villain in the Spider-Man movie
They're coming after us folks they're not doing stuff
And admitting the director yeah this is an Alex Jones character
About Spider-Man and
Does all this evil crap
Why do you think they do things like that to me
Cuz what you doing
Rico.com
Thousand bucks football game
500000 box 200 something dollars is 25% off
Horses
Might be able to continue on
Almost no way that couldn't be intentional
Beautiful beautiful
If that's not self-aware that's
Most embarrassing
You can't you cannot tell me that's not self-aware if it is not self-aware all of my beliefs about
What is possible are out the window why do they make a character of its all trying to sell
Do you stuff
Volume body exactly what that is a parody of
He's asking me to take the bait on that
It's too good
Can't be I just
Like I can't get over this road but I really think that made that special report about
Just because
Alex was mad that he couldn't go see Spider-Man because of this robbery at the mall
I'm being like I got to re-up on my contract instantly if I make this piece I've got a guarantee
Another two years here
Or like Alex is having a real bad couple weeks
Like maybe you want to do something nice or around the holiday season
Down with the blaming him not being able to do that
Alex kicked off Twitter
I don't see any possibility that this is going to change
We have a little bit of difference in the status quo
Now
Jack Dorsey
Gone shorter
He stepped down
So now
Going to do a brand Rehab on Jack Dorsey
Free Speech advocate
Twitter
And that he was really on my side and I was told that
ITube
3 years ago during my deplatforming I didn't believe it
So I guess when I went and screamed at him and chase him around Congress that
Lastdayonearth
I was naive
What
What's this song
Havenly
Naive
Everybody evil
Then
Very well-known talk show host
To him
Always right
Alex Jones is his Guru
Yeah man
Sure
You was
Razor thin ice
Better if he didn't kick Alex off Twitter than he would be gone
I mean if that's the
The case
He can't really talk about that now
Yeah yeah yeah. In charge of food already
But you don't have to worry about the board like I tried to keep Alex around really think that he's right about a whole lot of stuff
If I started a new platform Alex would be the number one person on it wait I'm in charge of square and he still on the phone
Is there two and
I find this a little bit
Time and that's all that's all I'm saying I guess Rogan told him this
I mean DPW wouldn't super surprise me that a weirdo Tech billionaire
He's also a weirdo believer in Alex Jones
That's fine maybe
But this is like me going to a bar
Getting kicked out and insisting that the bouncer is a big fan of mine
I mean
Because they
Yeah it was it works for the first few times and I said do you know who I am but the last time it didn't work
Infowars
About to win
So that's the mindset we're at we're at the Wynn
Sure things are things are good
Horses ride on The Cosby you were out on the couch
That's why we're in so much trouble
Marshall Law head of the election
Everything is do or die right now
We can track
Martial law is coming before the midterm sure so we'll see
Xerox
Get that one right
9 months
Yeah about maybe say that we'll see we'll see if we've got to we've got that coming
We get to the news now
Stila doing anything that I would
I would say is a blow up or is worthy of apologize
Next day
So we just
Just going to check in on some headlines
What's job
Decipher this headline
Retired generals urge Pentagon intakes
Upcoming elections
Decipher
Why do they has
Shimmy's under his control
Find control General
Call for martial law
Animal action
Right there in that clip that's the perfect encapsulation of how I look
Flies
He read the headline and then instead of engaging with any of the information in the article or attempting to learn anything further
He rewrites the headline into what he thinks or wants
This is legitimately what he does with everything
Which is probably why if you ask him about it
He wouldn't actually think he's a liar
He's telling the truth according
To the stories he comes up with by misreporting Headley
This was an op-ed generals wrote which
Just published in the Washington Post
These generals were Paul Eaton Antonio's
Gooba and Stephen M Anderson
The reason they wrote this op-ed is primarily that the anniversary of January 6th is coming up so the idea of insurrection maybe on
People's minds
And what motivated them to put pen-to-paper is explained
Text
We are chilled to our bones at the thought of acoustic
Succeeding next time
It's clear from what went down on the 6th
That is their been better organization or even a little bit of luck and timing gone the other direction
We would have
Far greater consequences from that attack on the camp
Makes sense that people with over 30 year careers in the military might be a bit concerned the folks might
Not be taking things seriously enough
What creates a greater risk
Worthy next
Do a temptress
Makes total sense
Really this article isn't about what Alex is even claiming it
To be at all because
Just making things up about the headline
Making has nothing to do with martial law
It's about a concern that we're going to see a complete breakdown of the chain of command in the military
Paper to keep this argument on the stat that one out of 10 people charge regarding January 6th have service Wrecker
Among other disheartening signs that if things go bad
It's unclear how much
Japan impact disconnect being able to mobilize a response
Against
Might be a challenge
It turns out
Similar to every military throughout his
History it's filled with fascists
A large part of the issue is they when you enlist your ultimately serving under the commander and chief
Many of the folks who are in the camp don't believe the Biden is legitimate or the rightful
Decent chance to be concerned about that dynamic
Essentially what they're calling for is laid out in the
Pentagon should immediately order a Civics review for all members
Uniform
Pavilion on the Constitution and electoral integrity
There must
Also be a review of the laws of war and how to identify and deal with illegal orders
And it must reinforce unity of command to make perfectly clear to every member of the defense
Department who play answer
No service membership
Should say that they didn't understand who take orders from during a worst-case scenario
Wargaming the possibility of another violently contested election in 2024 so people aren't
Caught off guard
As they were last
I don't know any of this because he's only really read the headline news is making
Things up by what he thinks this article is about
This is how we covers news
Which is to say that
Doesn't
You just make scary stuff up and it tries to freak out his listener
There's motorboat
It comes out of his mind
I think
That's a
Could could
Amanda Civics review for all
People
I remember is it when I was in high school required to take a
Government class
What you doing continuing education program
I buy goddamn hope so
It turns out probably like I don't know that
Schools now those kids probably understand Civics better than I do
The problem is that the jurisdiction
Above them have no clue
The government class
We took in high school might have worn off
So Alex talked about this headline some more
Call for martial law
Texas from
Do they
Disrupt
Those are military terms
Horse feed
Killing them
Capturing them
Torturing them on the headline making up what he wants
Sota mean
Interesting Lee though the words degrade and disrupt
Don't even appear in this op-ed
I really liked her I tried pretty hard to figure out where he was getting that from but I I'm not entirely sure
Like I tried to find repost things of this in like
Washington Times or Breitbart
But someplace that he must be pulling this from
Even the articles on Infowars a newswars
And those articles don't
Disrupt I don't know I have a military operation
Make that up
But
Don't think he's making it up
I think it comes from somewhere
I just don't know where and it's not the opposite probably a
Call of Duty
That's why I feel like it's not just random lyrics
Yeah and if it was would be something
He's not one of his normal buzzword
Yeah that's the reason why I think there's there's a root of it somewhere I just can't figure it out
In the Call of Duty Black Ops 2 is like we got a degrading disrupt these goddamn Nazi zombies out here
So Alex finally gets to Kick the Can down the road
He's talked about this headline
He's complained about not being able
Spider-Man
And now it's time to really get down
And that is
Talking about Trump
Going
On that show with O'Reilly and
Vaccine
You should get it you.
Happy about this
So I see Trump in these big rallies
Thousand fifteen thousand 20 thousand
Thousand with Bill O'Reilly
Auditoriums in rental stadiums and do that
Here's Bill O'Reilly you know he's making jokes
What movie stars they are
Flashlight away
Looks good that's great
Who cares about all that
Point
You want to hear about
The New World Order
It's being used
The global ID and social credit score
Now been put into place
Nothing
Isn't saying the things that I would want them to because he doesn't believe any of the things that Alex's
Convince himself
The Trump believe
Over the past years Alex got so high on how Trump was
Such an a****** really mad
Control the fake heroic version of trump
He created to sell that the audience
That version of trump isn't real
Going to lean into it
Is really pathetic to watch
Like I went to overcommitted on this really stupid bet and I was just being is left holding the bag
Expected
Explained to the audience
The hero total
Only knew everything about
Evil globalist
We've confirmed with Alex about this stuff behind the scenes
Metal seems to be acting
Completely counter to that understanding weird
It's probably going to be easily diverted if you would have just stuck with Rand Paul back
In 2015
Ears of integrity
He could have had
I mean it's it's hard to Sarah propagandist back a loser
It's hard to say like
Oh he's a sleeper Patriot agent
And now he's awake and then he's the president and then when he's
Not present here like I see he's back to being a sleeper Patriot agent
Until he's asleep now
I like now you know
You can't put that back in the bag
No it's it's
Kind of embarrassing
Flashback
Think about all the stuff Alex has said about Trump
Besides stupid
Positive
Calling him Moses
If you are someone like Alex
Back a loser
Back of loser
Cannot risk
The person that you you were in bed with women
Worst possible thing
Because of propaganda
Can't win
By Design
That's not their job their job is not to win the winner is the
Military or whoever insta
Attitudes fascism
The propagandas job is always to get
People to the point where they'll accept fast
It's a terrible idea to do that before there's Bashas
We'll probably cameras aren't going to really serve any productive role
Even if we even what you're saying
In terms of governor
You know like you're not able to really
That's why we see like over the course of
Trump's presidency and obsession with the
The Deep state
Write all of these secret attacks that are trying on on
Trump
And look as you still have to be that opposition thing
You just could avoid it by
Insisting on emotional and intellectual integrity
Text Rand Paul is
Is the candidate who
I mean he came from
Be the best totally absolutely
He's never going to win
You can save face
Oh well
So now you're left with like the skeleton
The bone
Of your past
Support
Him up there with Bill O'Reilly
As I got all these guys they're just stuck in a world of
Glamour and Glitz
And helicopters
They're still in the normal world of golf courses in
Helicopters in their supermodel lives in
Everybody goes like it's a big event
Undergoing
Rock and roll band they're going to see George Strait
Where all the celebrities who are all the people Americana
They're nowhere to be seen
I know that I was a fan of George Strait's music
Can you play songs like Amarillo by Morning as Bumper Music
But I'm not sure that he has much of a grasp on who George Strait is
In May of last year George Strait released a PSA encouraging people to wear a mask
Can practice social distancing
Along with Governor Abbott
He's currently on tour and proof of vaccination and or proof of a negative covid test are required at 3 for most of the venues
Except for like at 1 today
It was unclear about his
Like a rodeo
Maybe that one I'm not sure you never know with the rodeo
Simmons Bank Arena is actually requiring everyone to wear masks
Upper the George Strait
King of country music
You know what
Jeff Bezos his cousin
So the f*** what
Alex is looking for him to be politically
I just picked that
You're not he's not going to come out with an anti-vax Anthem like
Eric Clapton but yeah yeah
George Strait
Alex's prefers the image
George Strait gives off
With his cowboy hat
And
Amarillo by Morning
I got it I got to oceanfront property in San Antonio
Stacked
Oceanfront property in
Arizona
From my front yard I can
See the seat
Great songs
SMS guitar
Yes I do George Strait
Sounds like this
Beside e of the trumpet
Provoke
Can't really
Deal with that
I think there's a little bit of trouble understanding that
Can't be
Against the vaccine
Cuz he needs to take credit for it right
Unlike a visceral narcissism level
Like Trump can't be like
This thing
That is
The crowning achievement of my presidency even people on the left
Are like well
Trump did
To go along with Lightspeed and we were able to make a vaccine much quicker
Got to give it up
On that front
Which is wild cuz I think the smartest move for trump it is to say that he was against the vaccine in those elements in the Deep state that did it
Tell you if he ever wants to get elected he's going to have to what he has to say
It seems like Alex is mad about is that
Trump is moving towards those other Republican
And not
Embracing Alex again which I think is
Probably sorry for Trump to do
Nope should be on the Alex's team right now
F****** showing up on info
Maybe I mean
I think if he
The goal is just to like rise back
To the presidency
Then maybe
That is the
I think the
The damaged
If you can
Could do her
There I don't know it seems like
It seems like he's not
Inherently
On board with a lot of a little bit
But I thought he was a True Believer damn you know I mean I saw what he's done for his entire
Our life but then I thought he'd really changed entirely just by
Distill doing exactly what he's done exiled guy who did a photoshoot in a apartment
Made of gold is a 3.0 weird
Popular is not a popular
This isn't a problem
He should be talking about January 6th
And how they wouldn't let him know that Sean Gardner
He should be talking about the
We are rolling knows all about it
He should be at the Deep State and the New World Order
He should be talking about
How many people are
Poison injections
Mass death
The crime
Human history
Absolutely not
Show with L like this we don't have much of
Not much hope
Emma Wars is on the cusp of great
Success
We don't have much help because we l
Winning but there's no hope for us to convoluted message so far
I get I get where I was coming from it's basically just a like Trump please validate these
Completely non true things fright that I am selling as as my my narratives
I think it would be a really be helpful
Right buddy
Remember when we had a good thing
Sing going yeah man make people angry about
The things I want
To get attention
Confirm
And that then we can
We can do this
Yeah if you start making people real mad and say that the vaccine was created by the Deep State when you were the president whom
Made it happen
That's going to make people go f******
Nuts man
And then maybe they'll forget about all these things they're suing me about in job at Bob January 6th
Let's overthrow the country buddy
Reality those
The Trump has a
A real rapper
Opportunity
And that is a chance
Transcend the left
Alright paradigm
Bye
Coming out again
What's the vaccine I'm not sure but this is just sad
Left right
He could come out and say he was wrong they lied to him
Instead he knows now
Ski sign on to it
Until he's decided
We lost respectfully asking him
To help save the children
Just say no
Not going to do that
Schumer and Bill Gates
Really
I know you're making a
Uses for wild wild weird he's one of the most fires
Tell that to the biggest crime of the century now you know he's into.
Doctors know so what are you going to do
We looked up to him and we begged him to save us and he said no
Yeah I think the biggest I think the biggest realization that Alex is having is that
If Trump really wanted to do this thing
After seeing the almost complete lack of consequences for starting
The January 6th insurrection
He could actually cause a real Revolution right now
Can go for it and he can't
Don't know if it be
Successful
I don't know who do whatever he wants
A lot of trouble
And he's not
No
And you got to ask you a question ask yourself why then
Cuz it would be really hard to lead a war against the United
As people who've run the United
Midstate snow
Diablo
So
Trump bad now
Bees not going to save the children
Malik Baker
Him to save the children and he said no silence might have to go
Protest
Have fun
What's a dick
BBS in history consult the
Very important
Our children dying in Mash our children having major health problems
This injection not protecting them being a fraud
Oh it works wonderfully oh just get it
The Dallas Crowd Oh I just got the booster
Get the shot
His constituents to take
Southeast poison
Bill Gates is venom
About this
But
Why
Follow him around the country protest his ass
Evil
We know Bill Gates is super Wicked
But I mean really Donald Trump
Is that a prion
Is it spring on this first
See if see if man upstairs wants
Steve
Protest
What actually I mean I would
Based on the things that Alex has said about Trump in the past
How like
God wanted him to be president and
All this like he was chosen
He's got game
I would assume that God would tell Alex
Text to chill out
Even understand what's going on here
That was my idea I wasn't
Idea
It seems like
Talkingshit
Just pretending that he has the religious conviction
Things that he does
If he did
He's being a
Remarkable blast
How do you think about the reality of what he's
He's described the vaccine as is a
Population
Destroyer
A genocide weapon a genocide weapon
I wouldn't be like
If burn
Bernie Sanders is like listen
I know you agree with me on everything but I do support Hitler I would need to pray about it I was like
How to send on 95% of staff for killing everybody
That's a big 5
I just have proportional 95%
Yeah
Infrastructure
I disagree with him on killing all of human life but
You know what that's 50/50 I don't know which way I'm going to go I still
Even listening to a show pretty regularly I
Can't really tell you
If the
Plan is supposed to be that the vaccine will kill everyone
Or if it's a bureaucratic thing
Like to get us
Stabbed vaccine passports
Are doing great situation actually is
We will get to reset Wars eventually but that is coming
Anyway Alakazam theories about why Trump is
Provax
Donald Trump
That hates the UN and hates the globalist doesn't trust the system
Months ago
People have a booster
Are they running that scam
Did you just say that
And I will give Jared a billion bucks or something and you just say that shot screen
How many she get
Can you do this
What
Whole show asking what the hell's going on with Trump
You kind of all right now I mean
Wow deep into the subject matter
Papa's doing now for the past four years getting boring
Opposition to the boosters and those public comments he made
Manufacturers to give Jared Kushner a payoff
In exchange for Trump supporting the boosters
But first of all this kind of sounds like something a frontman for
Consortium
East Coast might do
Right lighter that kind of behavior listen you don't get me a lot of money
People don't get your vaccine I'm just saying I'm not saying that I'm going to do anything I'm just saying I'm just making a point
Secondly though
While but Alex again speculate this scenario is a sort of thing that he could believe Trump
Might be doing
And not ask himself
Maybe drop was capable of this sort of thing for the past few years
Use the second coming of John the Baptist
Honestly there is a small amount of schadenfreude listen
Did Alex abrines audience like this little bit sad
Oh haha you finally got your comeuppance
It's him transferring his
Misery onto his body
He knew Trump was polish it the entire f****** time
Enter now he's just
Boy acting as though he was betrayed the reality is everybody's been betraying everybody
Accept because
That is the way that you can make this season
Profitable exact
Bye-bye pretending
Play acting like you were conned by this
You can make a villain and create a whole new way to salvage
You know whatever you can
This seventy-five-year-old lifelong conman
I think he might have conned
Yes
Big Year
Last year
Is pretty big
Years this year
Flexradio
Biggest
2022 is going to be show deciding
Every other year in your life
Look like Child's Play
Guarantee
We're only
11 days out
From Destiny
Right now
What
It starts on New Year's
Run from all this
But at the same time watching
Everybody else sit there unconscious
Eyewear how much trouble we're all in collectively
Want to just jump off a cliff
You know what I mean
But here's the problem
I can't just jump through a portal
World
Because there is no new world
Its Global government and the same crap
Everywhere
No matter where you go really sounds like someone who could benefit from the lessons
There's no new world he can drop into his million worlds a trillion world
The goal was don't get to constrain his reality and dictate the options he is a light being
According to himself
The most important work of his career
I recognize that we have a cover the reason Awards episodes yet but knowing the sort of bulshit he's selling in those videos the tone of this act
April show
Is hilarious
Also I think of Alex Everest
Guarantee guarantee
He should be forced to do that
It is a little bit like you wouldn't listen to Amitabha Buddha so much if he was say
A bipolar lunatic who is screaming that you are going to be saved and you are not going to be saved
You should detach and you shouldn't detach
Simultaneous
Baby
You learn too much about Buddhism in you get a miserable in truck
Pat science
What I thought was really strange
Is
Alex is not throwing out the baby with
Bathwater
Inasmuch as
Look fucktrump with his back
Text stuff
But I'm going to hold on to the election conspiracies the rightful president
Severely you still the rightful dead
And we can't get President Trump who is the real president
Wonder landslide
If we can't get him on the most Central of issues
He's coming out
The only Silver Lining is Democrats that hate you so much
You know what
Even if I would like
If you believe any of what they're trying to explain to you that's of you
Like it's hurting my brain to understand it
And I know they're lying
Sure you know
Is a betrayer
Who is
Chicken jump companies for billions at the same time
She is the rightful president who is also still president I actually
Drink that makes sense
Alex's world
Like I do think
Otherwise you've got to undo all of thee like
Stop the steal stuff
Walk-back
All of the
Stuff that led to January 6th
Coverage that you did
All of the Smoking Gun proof of election fraud that's got to be thrown out and you don't think
Alex would want to do that
And it kind of raise the stakes a little bit while we have the rightful president
Yeah
All the presidents are committing genocide president
Wow
Nobody
Very very few
People who identify as Democrats
Is are not going to get the vaccine
Because Trump support
Yeah I think that maybe there'd be a couple of frames outliers
But most people aren't that kind of Oppositional defiant
Yeah Alex is
Yeah so he would make a healthcare decision based on
Who supported or who's against absolutely
100% everybody else does that too and that's
Really
Childish she
A little bit it's a terrifying thought
Yep
So
Man
Alex gets into his lawsuit
The government
You're going to win
Thought we did it episode why you were gone with the Android
Thank you very much and ra
This is depressing
And like I'm not even
No hope for this lawsuit
Listen to Alex
Talk about it I don't think
He has any hope for it either
We found a big suit
I guess the January 6th committee United States history
Court District
Columbia
Select Committee
Benny
G Thompson Elizabeth
Call Cheney
Susan
And the rest of the monthly
Here is
Lawsuit
We're going to be taking action
In many other ways to fight
They are going after Everybody's Free Speech everybody's right
To assemble
With this garbage
Make
Blush
Tolls going up on cam
Any minute
Thursday
And there's explosive
Magazine
That is very historical
Extremely
Important
Yeah. Sounds like it
I'm going to take a break for a while I may just leave
I just a country
I just
That's why you're all going to die
What what
We switched over and we're all going to die real quick
Like honestly don't know what happened
Have you ever been in the bus
You know
All those people
Bus
All of a sudden a bicyclist comes out of nowhere the bus driver Slams on the brakes and the one person who hadn't got
Other hand on the thing just click enough goes
Flying forward
That's what I feel like right now it's
The inertia
Coronavirus
This could hurt yourself force of gravity was
Brutal
So I think Alex
Maybe doesn't understand what
In the lawsuit even I may be as a
Really grasp it yet like a bad Norm
Paris Road it all up or whatever
Emphasis
Get any sense
He's like I am a champion I'm going to take it to the January 6th
Committee is getting sued by Chobani we were ready to fight to the end
Well it's historical
Bandits
Important
Those descriptors descriptors or a discussion of what
The suit is actually about
And then a long pause
And we're all going to die
6 things series
I mean
Is he taking it seriously
I don't know
Anybody leave
Alex is in a bad mood again
I was wondering when we were going to get to everybody
Yeah where is there and now it's time to talk more about Trump
Easy bum
Okay
That's why you're all going to die
Global is are injecting
Children with deadly poison
Trump is running around
Stupid red dye
You are playing into their hands and destroying yourself and signing yourself onto the New World Order
Idiot Bill O'Reilly
Credible joke
They are the problem with Bill O'Reilly wasn't whether or not he could pick up women
Smartbud
Serial sexual harasser
The same thing of sexually harassing someone
Language is
Little troubling
Also has a chameleon
And it was his show was before he was a president
His presidency
That's why he's doing that
About
Watching something that was eminently predictable coming
True is that it is not satisfying whenever you predict something that comes true I think that's the thing
Okay about this Trump coming out in
For the vaccine Alex getting mad about it all of them fighting with each other about it
People we all saw it coming
And it's not
Satisfying kind of like haha I predicted I would win but you know why
Here's why it's
Not satisfied
It looks like it in the terms of trump like coming out
Supporting the vaccine
It's not it's not satisfying because it's like well
The least you could do
It's kind of like
Absence of a negative
Really like
Energems
Kind of know that the people who really need
I hear that message aren't going to hear it even
Alex
Him saying this stuff doesn't really give you that kind of boost
Because we've been
Here too many times
Like I'm not even fully convinced he's turning on Trump
Things are pretty harsh stuff
Totally I still live
I'll believe it when I see it
Like him out there with a bullhorn
At a trump rally
Trump for prison shirt believe it whenever you're Trump actual
Billy finally does shove Isis up his dirty a******
Yeah that'll be the day
The day
Alex's got to go to a Greg
Report
Who got to get off there
So he tries
But then they either start Tagalog
I just can't
Get back on there anymore
So let's just are that
I'm not trying to be dramatic here I just
Seriously
Everybody have what you want that ship and Pelosi rob you
He's too busy and their own candy-ass BS
You look at it analyzed at this ain't human
You people need to wake up and rally against it
Hello that like
Rebroadcast I might never come back I'm not saying this to be too dramatic and then I'm going to proceed to do the most dramatic yet
Possible
We're fighting a alien people are too wrapped up and going to work everyday
And having families and all that s***
To really get down to brass tacks and realized
Bring that we are fighting an Intergalactic rep
Representation of the literal Christian devil
Cool
Little more time off
Remember he showed up an hour and 47 minutes
Time off before the show
Okay little
Prediction before the midterm
We're going to get martial law
Tonight will track that
You make another prediction on this clip that did not come
You know big text announcing new lock
Years ago
Is announcing that they're closing
I had all the other lockdowns in Biden tomorrow
Going to make some new bigger County in
Ignoring
Natural immunity
Totally ignoring real science
I would think that Alex would be thrilled
Davos is canceled
He hates that s***
I mean yeah
Big Tech decides to do with their own workplaces I don't really know what that has to do with it
It's meant
To precipitate
New lockdown because
These things are locking down the argument that he's making but
It's dumb
Zirconia new Lockdown from vaccinated people the next day so
Teddy never made
To maintain the image that he's consist
Bentley Wright
In fact
The opposite of what Alex said would happen on December 22nd
When the Supreme Court decided to hear arguments
Regarding the legality of Biden
Vaccine mandate
Also let's not forget
These aren't even
Blanket vaccine mandates that are in place
They only apply to companies with 100 or more employees and they require proof of vaccination
That employee that doesn't want to get vaccinated has to get tested weekly and wear a mask at work
Almost sounds like
Unnecessarily permissive insanely permissive that's
That's a ridiculous thing
Is a provision within the vaccine
That allows for the if you don't want to
Build stuff like that in there cuz not everybody can be vaccinated
Pencil
Anyway
Is it the whole idea that there's going to be like all this news
Of
The 22nd
Possibly overturn this man.
The speech the next day
On December 21st which is
This is a speech to they gave about covid and they opted
Coming holiday
There was no lockdown talk
This is how we address the unvaccinated
All these people who have not been vaccinated
You have an obligation to yourselves to your family quite frankly I know I'll get criticized for this
To your country
Get vaccinated now it
It's free it's convenient I promised you would save lives
And I honest-to-god believe it's your patriotic Duty
As far as like rousing speeches from presidents to people to
Will step up and do their patriotic duty this
Doesn't rank is
Anywhere near the most
Inspiring
Western with Rhett
More like an exhausted parent trying to get kids
Intervention
The only thing we have to fear
Is all of you being afraid of the wrong
F*** is wrong with you
Any speech he literally address be concerned with rice
In cases would be heading back to how things were in March 2020
And he explicitly made it clear the
The sorts of locking down that we did then are not necessary now give him a different variables were facing
Not least of which being the difference in how many people are vaccinated over 200 million
Versus how many were vaccinated and which is exactly zero
He did kind of call out people like Alex
But even in this case he was just empathy
Bentley begging with Liars to stop lying
Look Beyond vaccinated starting with look
Just just softer than listen
Look younger accelerated are responsible for their own choices
But those choices have
Open field by dangerous misinformation on cable TV in social media
You know these companies and personalities are making money by peddling lies and a lot of misinformation that
Can kill Theron
Consumers in their own support
It's wrong it's immoral and I call on the purveyors of these lies and misinformation
Stop it
Stop it now
That's my president
I mean oh my God
I think in terms of what you can do as a president maybe that's about is
Are there as harsh as you can be
Without without possibly drifting into Lexington laws of some sort or another
Get into a person Amendment chilling kind of conversation
But eventually we have to live in a world where you can say look at these f****** Liars we have proof they're lying there lying to
Do you know they're lying to you I know they're lying to you
Call Don the purveyors of those lies to stop
Stop it now drawing words
Talkingshit make bad predictions and that's pretty much his entire shout that didn't happen
And we know that because we're it winter of it now
Oh man
You like comedy
I've heard of it
Did you happen to see that clip of Jim Breuer
That was going around no I heard of it and I saw what that people were
Dunking on it and I was like
Why why are we doing this
It's whatever Year we're in now Jim Breuer can go f***
Himself I don't need this
So I said no
Jim Breuer zombie reawakened America
Annie had a little bit but he did
There was
People who like vaccines
They're like cockatoos
Because they go around and they're like
Falcon
Trust doctors
Lakehouse basically is better
Wow good
That is exactly
Exactly as good as everything else I've seen Jim Breuer do exactly
Let's take one note and make a career out of it
Jesus God so he he did that bit too
I would say mediocre results even in that room
And Alex was pretty good
But they just repeat over and over again like
Dallas conference
Weekend
This weekend
William hawrelak
And it was all freaking out about a making fun of it
Show you
A research paper they don't show you a statistic
In the news
Can you show me the news where the effects
A bit ridiculous
The left was
Mad that Jim Breuer was make
In front of them as much as they were
Football socks
Jim Breuer was getting booked
Pretty amazing
A2031
That's not good they were laughing at how bad
Construction of the the comedy lies
I don't think anyone was really particularly worried about the
The insult
I don't think anyone was like
Oh no
Oh Jim breuer's got my number I mean
There was a clip of me going around being like hey
See the right they're all like I don't like to do that would be bad
Comedy
Posted all over Twitter and make fun of it because they were
Somehow worried about how you're making
In front of that I think my fear would be that he's what they would be worried about
Let's test it out again or not
Bugatti video
So
Alex has made a lot of prediction
Comes in his life
Will you receive a couple here on this this episode 1 we're tracking until the midterm one that was
Completely wrong
But Alex
His one failed prediction
According to him
We are ladies and gentlemen and
I'm just sad to see this all that
The only big one
What do you think vibeszn announce tomorrow
You ended the clip with the prediction that didn't come true but you said that you're only predict Sunday. Wrong is that you
Stop it
Dumb
Alex reveals that he doesn't believe in only
You are you are saying on the ground because he saying
I think it's delightful that Alexandra refuses to call Atomic
I'm fine with that I'm 100
Yeah if you want to call it omnicron
Have a great time
The puppet president is set to announce measures tomorrow
Across the u.s.
Why I don't believe a word of it
Wow
That's nice
To be fair I also don't believe in the omnicron
That's that does sound like a totally made-up life they're not naming it correctly
Just banging the drum on this predict
So that's
That's fun
A story
Cuz it's a little bit
Off the beaten path
Off the Trump news
The guy
In Canada
What do a farmers market
Okay
Louis
He was not vac
Believe
But he got into a fight with people who wouldn't let him out
I believe that's probably the whole time probably with the attachment
Anyway here's a little bit of that video
Preventing me from getting food
Temecula manager what's his name
And all of her information is there
I don't really care about this guy or this video at all particularly because at the end of it someone tries to offer him the option
Making a list and someone will go get the food that he wants from the Farmers Market
So the whole complained about not being allowed to buy food
Just dumb
Alex is also trying to prevent the situation is like it being an open-air farmers market so it shouldn't matter
That isn't a good argument so isn't it open
Farmers Market
Super clear if you watch the video and the person working there
To the guy that it's private property and is generally a performance
Headspace on a venue
That's just where the farmers market is being held
If you pay attention she says the name of the place and actually eventually the guy gets
The flyer
Either he shows on camera
Escape Wychwood barns
Knowing this week and then learn a little bit more
About the situation
Angola website
You see that the interior of the space
This is blocked off into
Sweet we're different folks
Renteria.
Branston sweet once
62 is the Children's Art Studio
Oh and 173 is home to a couple of Storytelling program
The farmers market is in Suite 181 it is known as a
There's an outdoor portion of it but the larger portion right now currently is indoor
Which is where this guy in the video was trying to go to
All the stops website they explicitly say quote
Due to the unique multi
To use nature of the building
Artscape
The building operator requires all customers
Enter the indoor portion of the Farmers Market
Please have your Kudos receipt or qr-code ready with photo ID
You don't have to be vaccinated to go outside the building
But if you want to enter
You have to follow the rules of Artscape
The owners of the
Property
The website I'm not sure exactly how much this is the case cuz
Anna Wintour and such
But
They did say that some people were still outside
Yet if those people word still had booths outside could have gone to them
I think the fact that the story is so thin and meaningless is
Part of the reason that Alex has the hinge so much on
The point
This person correctly guy that her manager is a woman
Like this is just rank massage
It's amazing like he can't let it go even after you plays the video
He wants you to know he's a beta
I submit
I want to talk to your manager
Oh my gosh your woman's my boss
It's okay you're killing me
What
It's just so dystopian
So much nothing that he has to fall back on pretending that the employee was trying to exercise
Some kind of power by saying their boss is a woman
When a reality if you pay attention she only did that because the guy was talking about the manager and ask
What is his name
The only reason
This person was not exercising power at all it was a
Yeah that's
That's
Wow that's infuriated you know in when I was in France
Spell vaccine
And when we got there we had to go we showed our vaccine card to the pharmacist
Pharmacist write out a vaccine past put it on my phone everywhere I went
All I did was show QR code
They go beep and then I got to do whatever I wanted
Fantastic I didn't have to have my
Simcard carried around with me I didn't have to worry when I was inside a restaurant that nobody else around me was vaccinated I could have
Just f****** scanned their backs on the on my phone and said it
Amazing I want one of those
It was absolutely not tyranny
And
Do you are a tyrant
Alex decides that he wants to hear that
Trump video again
I don't know why
It seemed to make
I'm pretty mad
And maybe a little bit sad
But he does decide we're going to have to take a canker sore you can't stop
You know how long do you think he makes it into the video
I want to go with one and a half
Corral
I feel like somebody
Oh my gosh shop
And then you got Trump
Overhears Posey on our side sliding
And then over here
Pedophile leftist
And you're just like
How do you deal with something like this well
You got to reach out to God
I just going to be overwhelmingly dr. zelenko
He's going to pray for God
Holy spirit of discernment
We're going to win in the end
Again
We did something that was historic
Who
Auditorium of tens of thousands of people in Dallas
Did not do something at store
Come up with the Pfizer shot
Blood clotting agent
Roll out the gene therapy that turns off your white blood cells
Do that
What are the white blood cells turn off
Tabata Ramen starch
Start shutting down a diamond my buzz like I'm dying what's going on everything's dying
And he's up there
With Bill O'Reilly that joke
He's up there with him I'm sorry
Girona Club
I do like taking potshots at Bill O'Reilly and I enjoy that
I think you were over
Ice
I think you said I think your prediction was too long I was thinking about it and I realized that my
Mistake was in measuring it with
Time value the word instead of
Syllable
Syllables
And that was where I went wrong
I should have I should have been like does he make it through 10 syllables this is why you play the game
We can learn
For next time next time
Yeah I'm so bored listen
Nothing to this
Disdain
Constant repetition of these dumb covid
Conspiracies
But I kind of got lost in a little bit of a flight of fancy about personified blood cells
I just got it.
Cartoon
Cosmosis Jones sure I work all let's all go to the lobby
Concessions
Stand
So
Do we get back
Alex
Back to listen
How many syllables
Are cantaloupe a good question
I'm actually going to go lower I'm going to say 5
5 syllable
End-of-life worldwide we together all of us
Not me we
We got a vaccine done three vaccines done antrum
Therapeutics like regeneron and other things that have saved a lot of lives
We got a vaccine.
In less than nine months
To take from
5 to 12 years
Because of that vaccine
Literally
Kind of funny the way visible
You do
You Google goodbye I was wrong
The safe money was on very short
But
Yeah you went a little long
I do enjoy that the way that Alec structures this kind of thing here
Is like
Trump Twitter
Never talked
To Alex about these issues
Answer this is Alex's way of kind of pretending they're having a debate
Exactly
That's kind of fun I'm talking to the TV because the TV is with me
Yes and because man on TV won't talk to me doesn't talk to me anymore
Because of that vaccine
Millions and millions of people
I think this would have been to Spanish Flu of 1917 worth
Up to 100 million
Because of adee
Really sick and dying from
Lockets
People died
This was going to ravage the country
Far beyond what it is right now
Take credit for it
Take credit for the great what we've done is this
Could you sign on believe it
Bill Gates
And and and and
Most group in end
Peter jurasik
The trumps on the TV
With dezek
I don't
Weirdly gensaku
Pressed
Presidential press
Spokesperson
I mean
Dia DIA
The idea that
Trump
Is taking credit
Taking
Credit for the VAC
Wouldn't even have been necessary
Were it not for his actions at the beginning of the
Probably but also
However you do not get to claim credit for the win
If you don't
Get responsibility for the massive launcher
I think I think
Obviously be taken into
When you sort of like old that I change
If you don't want to take it you shouldn't be forced to take it
No mandates
But take credit because we save tens of millions of life
Away from you
Okay so the president
All right I mean that's
If you
She wants to take credit for this amazing backseat but
I mean okay
Okay
Fine
That's how it goes
That's the way it is you get to take credit for the vaccine but I'll see you don't have to worry about it if you don't want to
If you continue spreading it
Because you don't take the vaccine you still get to take credit for the vaccine
Because you voted for Trump
Even though you're not getting the vaccine and still actively strategy I do think it's a little bit can
Confusing
The framing of it where the audience
Should take credit
No
Yeah
No mandates.
Anyway trumpet we get back to this invisawear he says he's boosted
And Alex's
Just like oh boy
It makes me think that he didn't listen to all of this clip before
Yes
You get to play God shut up there than in do all this crap and
Play footsie with the Deep State that's fine.
Not with killing the kids
View
I got to be dealt with it
I thought you said earlier that he was looking good and he lost weight I have had a spare in hockey
I guess that makes Alex the Beast ravaughn
I don't know afternoon references
Get through this conversation
So I think of this clip really is
A good example of why Alex isn't embarrassing
And childish coward
He's now decided to because Trump isn't going to help him with his Sensational ass anti-vax narratives that he's bad
Send out at the audience just move on
Moving on his grave
But it's missing the very essential step of reflecting on what went wrong
How could the person that you routinely offer to
To die for the person
Constantly claimed knew all about the globals plans his whole life
Everything was leading up whose presidency was Wipeout the commies
The person you claim was communicating with you telepathically
The person who sacrilegiously called Moses
How could a person be the same person who's now bad because he disagrees with
The self-reflection here is really important because if you do even the tiniest bit of it Yuri
Realize that all that b******* for The Last 5 Years
Didn't mean a thing
He saw Trump as a potent weapon that he could use to attack the last in Progreso
Causes primarily surrounding Civil Rights Voting Rights reproductive Health in any attempted gun regulation
Purple such an a****** in an idiot such
Please embarrassment that I was had to create a grandiose mythology around him
In order to convince the audience to overlook the complete embarrassment he was on the surface
This is essentially the same process Cuba not used
The creative fake
Hero to Rally around
Really well for scamming in Griffith
But eventually the real person isn't going to be able to live up to the fake version you created
Comes in
Thankfully for Alex the point where he's decided he's got to lose the truck baggage is at the point where Trump himself doesn't really have any
Power that Alex
Good Hope to use against
The left
He's out of the office and most importantly the bases moved on
They've been radicalized past the Trump point
You can see it when the audience Boos Trump 47 got the booster
The person isn't really useful for Alex or any of these con men anymore
So it's easy to cut bait now
The key though is to just move on
And not ask what the f*** happened
Started doing that they realize that Alex and pretty much everyone in this right wing
World
This trumps cam community
To them for political and financial purpose
If they got around to asking even more questions they might realize that a couple months before endorsing him Alex said the Trump was a mobs
The frontman for
Consortium on the East Coast
His whole personality and riches were fraud
Afford the risk of the audience doing that kind of thing
Consuming is best for them just
To move on
Yeah it's almost imagine that he was
Great but
Now he's turned back
It's almost like
If you know
Say he was saying one thing and then Alex said something completely different later you might think
Oh
Trump give Alex a lot of money in order to say I'm not saying he did
But those are the
The questions that you would have to ask if somebody's opinion
Change so drastically
At your image of them James
Along with
You're just giving him the the Kushner
The Alex's series
So Alex is Donald Trump
But again we'll see
We'll see about that
But you've done
Trump for the moment
I just got to get back to talking about that headline
About the generals
We're trying to avert a civil war
No
General
2024 election
I think that Clippers really telling
Alex believes that if you're
Conscious you can read a headline and then see what's really going on and read the secret messages behind
You don't need to read the article at
Self I guess which is really what I would consider the bare minimum a person needs to do to understand what an article
Call says bud
I don't know baby I'm not conscious
Alex seems to have the same relationship with all news that most people do with the onion
The headline is what's important of the body of the text
Maybe it's just
Belair
If you start to understand that this is how his process works you'll start to understand how Alex
Abuses primary sources
It just makes up whatever stories he want
Launch then points to headlines that secretly backup is made up stories
And you can see it all if you were just conch
To read between the lines
Now
What I find even more
Thing is that why you were gone
I was listening back to bunch
To those old files that I
Found from 1998 over the past week
I stumbled across this
This is from his June 30th show
In 1998
I'd like to hear
Some people have never called this
And you can call if you call before that
That's fine
Bajoran people that have just
People
4 years ago on your TV show
Stop lines are always busy
Sunday night tonight
A new caller
The call-in also you have any news stories
You like to just read the headlines from
And give
Give me in the public out there your interpretation
What you think
Think what the media
Pushing
This is always been with Alex does
I need does it because it's the only way to market the bulshit he sells his news
Because they think the things he says are based in research
They need to realize
But they're accepting is fact
The improvised ramblings that come out of Alex's imagination when he reads ahead
This is all this s*** is and it's been that way for his whole f***
Yeah
What do you think
This is a hummingbird's that's an entertaining radio show
When the when the not this one
But that that kind of dynamic where the host calls in and ask her if
Opinions from people
And then they just banned him about and it's
It's not good when the host
Is the one doing that and then forcing you to agree with
I think there's a difference
Between expressing something strictly as an opinion
And relating with news stories
Tell me what you think it means
Yeah what do you think the man is pushing with this headline what's secret what secret
Can we find in this headline what code is in there right then there's an even bigger difference
Between tell me what you think it means and I'm going to tell you what it actually means that if you disagree with me you're all good
You're just an idiot
Headline
Completely
Different story from the body of the article
It's too long
You're too dumb to do
Is not read
To look
Alex is suing the government
He's going to win one of his lawyers ignore Patty
Alex Rambles a bit
About like
All these
Cancel out I think he's still mad about Trump but they like these people they
They take money to support the New World Order blah blah blah and then
He brings in
Norm Macdonald
To the right of self-defense
To the right to elect your own local
Destroyed
Unlimited money and power
Dubai off
Peabody little take the money
People take the money cuz they're not even
Thinking about whether it's a payoff
Flashlight
Their fellow citizens because they believed
Winner movie
Establishment
They get to go to the conferences in the meeting and they get patted on the head
4050 years
America
While you were being the Lemmings and the quislings
And the traders in the sellouts in the suckers
I'm a double agent
Now you're coming down to the end of The Wire
Now you're coming down to the
Final point
With a collab
That's where we are
Patterson
Against the January 6th
Meals with all of your rights or freedoms
Us to talk about
Okay
I just realized
30 minutes
We're done
Total incompetence
Society
Charlie
Norwood
Busy
Working for me most likely right I waited wait half an hour while I rambled about nut
Yeah he's gone
I was just such an incompetent
Listen to All of society I will tell you that there's something
So much fun
Near to me about the
Then him yelling
What are we doing
What is anybody doing here
Close to a moment of him being like guys I've been lying to you for 20 years I don't understand what you guys are doing listening to me anymore
We're done we're done we're just done
The buildup of the government is one of the greatest constitutional lawyer
He's not there
He's not coming over
Deflation
Yep just such a
A company director
Record scratch there should have been a moment there or like a whoopee cushion
Planning for the last half-hour of the show
To be an interview
About his lawsuit
Norm's not there
So it's just talking extemporaneously
I would say he's having a rough time with me
I don't care about Trump
Get ready for this tells you need Vitamin D3
What a devil
What I need
Okay
What
Carabiner
What is it you want
Are you
Why are you being nice to me
Their mother put them in her crib today
Lives in a crib watching TV
That's why they can't believe there's people like me
That I got all the milk I wanted
I own the love I want
Wow swab needs to kill everybody cuz the public
Is scum
Who's the worst kill dojo
He'll be clawed back down into the
I do think that it
It's interesting that in the past we found clips
Of him talking about his mom kicked him off
I heard that you're a mama's boy
Be strong my love no more
Something
Yeah that seems to run count
Turn to that but
If people are other people he wanted
Your house up with gas in your face for an hour by your family
Yeah it's true but that's chivalrous
Yeah I was just so
So much
Is there
To really sit back and
Enjoy you know
Just the feeling of a man who's been slighted
In a minor ways all of humanity is scum I got to die
Over
The question of if if you if I'm a person
Who would I make a big dinner for somebody they have to ask me afterwards why are you being nice to me
That doesn't suggest to me that they want something for me
That suggests that maybe I'm a complete assholes 99% of the time at least suspicious
Talking about Rob Jacobson
Cuz he's told that story of having Rob Jacobson over for dinner
I'm being weird or something like that
In the past I think it's just like a a retelling of that
Details on
I think it's interesting this what happens when there's a little flight
I mean I could see him taking that hard
There's also just like
This wouldn't be happening if Norma dancers
That is what would happen they'll relay delivery cost
Bizarre world
Where everyone's going to die I may have to die. Rob is a right that everyone stomach because they didn't get nothing
Breast milk and
Howard how are you throwing
Giant shity tantrum on air and we're the skunk
I think it's because the Dems of people on the left
They get sexually excited
By vaccinating their children because they know that they're going to die
Piece of garbage
Call Schwab
He's ruling us
Gaming us and scamming us
And we decide spiritually
Listen to what he's doing
Acima
Sacrificing my child is this
I did 20 months ago and 10 months ago and six months ago in a month
Thank you for being Heroes
Take your shot
Because there's too many people
Thank you for having the courage to sterilize yourself
And give herself heart attacks and yeah
Your children come from you at The Fugitive in children
They're trash.
Call the Nazis had to hurt people in and shoot on the back of that develops to your own children
Thank you for your courage realize your trash
Thank you for realizing your subhuman garbage
Warriors
Yourselves
Carrier self I could see why you needed to apologize
This is getting to be a little but
Actually ever if I had when I got I got my shot
If there was just
Two big lines of conservative weirdos sarcastic clapping as I walk in
I think for once
The kind of track
The character that Alex is doing that kind of
Progress
That it start
With
Benign
Applauding of the people for getting the vaccine right and then it takes the narrative twists
Into
You are murdering exactly
Sarcastic escalation typically does not
Go from A to B to C correctly
To apologize for
Oh you're so smart for getting the vaccine and that's why communism is coming over and you're like no no that's not how you do the Batman
Now this is this works
Android Beam on the left the thing is they don't actually even want their kids
Like their kids
Mental Health
You're a hero
And give them to your baby come and get attention when they're going to call
Everybody will feel sorry for that your child you want to get off on the attention you get when they died
Uncle God you're so good it's so much Bill Gates
Southie said I can't have my
Family over there on injected
I agree with
Stout
Disgust
Things stuff like all of this has better than a little bit
Stone ocean
People on the left
Who would be getting their children vaccinated
Don't love their children I just want the attention
From there.
That's f***** up
He's acting as that Catalyst that every
Genocide needs
Of the person who convinces you that
Despite everything you've ever known about every human being you've ever met having very similar thoughts
10 goals and hopes
Joy's in love's in all that stuff one group of people
Is subhuman
Absolute garbage and that nothing you do to them matters because
They don't even love their own kids so what they don't even care what
Happens to them
They just want the attack
Just want the attempt
It's really
Bizarre
Says about
His
I'm not going not saying that he just wants attention from his kids dying
He went to just come up with that
Is a very bizarre place for your mind to go
And I know I wonder
I wonder how that
Thought
Comes in
And that is is just like let's go with it I know I've never I've never thought
Anyone
You guys only had tubes
The most inconvenient thing for you possible sure pretty expensive dangerous
If you wanted my attention
That makes sense
I don't think that if you would be
If I was a producer
A little bit before this I would have called bark
Cigar bars in here somebody
There's a dark
8 ft long candy cane and grab them by the neck
You could do is get a like a cardboard cutout of norm pattis
Hide behind it
Hey Alex it's me Norm I'm here to talk to you
Also Factory didn't say that you couldn't hang out with your family unless they've been vaccinated
In fact he said that large Gatherings word even safe for people who had gotten the booth
He said that if your family was fully vaccinated getting together in a smaller group is pretty safe but that if you're not
Even that kind of smaller Gathering
Could be risky
He didn't say you couldn't do it just at the choice to do so came with a much higher risk of getting infected and possibly inside
Checking your family members
I don't know I don't think he's
Don't think you said anything that rebate
Whatever be careful
The worst thing you can say
Inside a day
And he only came in like right before the 3rd hours started
He did stay in the fourth hour for this one thank God for that
Just between
The aftermath of missing Spider-Man
Ropes betrayal
Norm's phone not working
Forsyth Tech
This is just he's bad it's bad never ceases to amaze me
That we can be talking
Think about how the entire human race is scum
But it's important to remember that a big part of that is
Is Jay Jonah Jameson is not a flattering portrait
You could do worse
Even if j.k. Simmons play me is an a****** what you would be like hell yeah j.k. Simmons
I less flattering comparison is that guy from
Elizabeth Australia
And at the end of the show he has some choice
Take your injections
It's so
Be better tomorrow
Location
But you know it's okay
The temperature
Cuz you don't want
According to them
We
Her courage great work she's doing
Yeah
Prodigy.com
Legitimately just can't imagine being a person they show realize that Alex showed up an hour and 40 minutes late to his job
And then proceeded to knock into any real news of substance at least partially due to his emotional reaction
Hearing Trump endorse a booster
Rashad a good place to throw your financial support
Like what about this contact the contact looks like it's a good in
Investment
Song
I was told that I am also scum
I do deserve death
And Society is pointless and useless right
I would not think
This guy
Better keep saying that to people otherwise bad
Things will happen
Energy right now but I
Would be too hard to make a solid argument
Ethically wrong
To give Alex money
Right now by his product
You could make that argument
Alcoholic
Alcoholic bottle of whiskey everyday Bay like man
It's a good thing I'm supporting you cuz otherwise no one would buy you this booze anymore
Yeah yeah
Pills
More achy than normal go home and calm down
Go to you know
People used to go to the Arizona to loosen up their breath or whatever cuz they have tuberculosis
I believe I'm in Arizona
Good. Go hang out with our pilot
Animals twice a day exercise
Nobody allows them to eat sugar
I haven't heard him talk about going to Barton Springs and like the
The hot
Bob ABS or whatever it worth globalist show up
Play Lisa maybe baby is overdue
Get to get a hot bath
Yeah hot bath Manor
Practice self care self care
Open mike eagle has some advice for you okay
Dreadful
The beginning of the episode there's just too much
To get two in one episode 4 part 1
I will be back tomorrow with part 2
Your Man
This was something
Listening to this was
I'm glad I'm glad that I followed my nose
From the beginning
But I do like what happened on the 20th
It's almost you know
We've been doing this for too long
Because it is impossible for me
Outside of the context of having been done
Been doing
Solvang
Believe the B is real
You don't like this if I was told this
But you know at the beginning of our I don't know anything about Alex Jones
You are learning everything about Alex Jones
And you told me this happen
Yeah I would say not a chance in the world would anyone allow that anywhere broadcast
Anytime if we if we started the show this was our first episode like the eclipse
I don't know I don't know what we would come along
Healthy no
I don't think the show would continue
If we hadn't found it's time to pray in the first episode
What is happening
It is it is surreal
Tickets
To consider that like this is
It's happened
Bonkers
You there's no context for this
With it like I said no point in time in any school I've ever been in was anyone even aware that this was
The only contacts
Relieve it we can even understand it in Asia
Like you said haven't listened to
This familiarity with him
Like and knowing there is no boss
His show is a psychodrama
It's all just as petulant outburst
Things get worse and worse
His ability to do his job
Gets thinner and thinner
Under a lot of snow
I'm not saying that it's not
Understandable that you would have emotional outbursts
If I was going to be sued into Oblivion
And I was going to be brought in front of a congressional committee
Regarding an Insurrection that I sure had something
Said to do with
I would
Feel like I was
You know in a column space to do a good show
You might want to go to rebroadcast
So we'll be back
Tomorrow's but until then Jordan a website
Jordan
Forgot what to say
And now here comes
The sex robot
Alex
Birthstone colors