Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Text Joan
Jordan
Sup
My brakes I forgot
Christmas
Gifts that came in from
My folks
Thank you so much sentiment lovely
We got this
Enjoying
I appreciate that
I also thank you so much
You got some h.g. wells man I got some serious volume
Yeah I like
Book here I haven't had a chance
Crack into it but it's about Lovecraft
HG Wells book from that era where if you were science fiction writer you also
So had to write the rise and fall of the Roman Empire or Lowe's along those lines
The other gorgeous hardcover books
I appreciate that I always loved a dignified hardcover Neverland a hardcover
One rule also Christy
Out like a indoor
Campfire
Immediately said to me
We're not doing this inside
That's true you do that there I am not a lucky window it could do that
Cool cool stuff
How about you
My bright spot of courses
But also I have finally gotten into the expanse
The Sci-Fi series of novels and television that every Syfy nerd has
Unequivocally praise
Almost non-stop for about 50
Teen years finally
I have caught up to the party
And it's
Welcome it's really good you say is if I've watched
You haven't
Condescendingly has helped in the spirit of
Hurrah
So Jordan today we've an interesting episode to go over
It's going to be on our plate
We've got
And that was on Christmas Alex put out an emergency warning
To Donald Trump
About the vaccines and stuff
He's very mad about Trump the sporting black
Recovered on the last episode
And is it escalated to a Christmas Day emerge
Message
Put down the Coco
Tell Baron to go to the other room
I got a warrant
Camels and horses in the opposite direction to come bearing gifts of Frankincense myrrh and a dire warning
Then we're going to be going over Wednesday December 29th
I tricked you into saying I had to really Revolution
Is the game on the last
We can go with it
So we're going to do this
First of all because there's some
Serta follow up on
The Trump Warren
I also because I want to get us
Pretty much caught up because on Monday
I'd really like to finally get into reset Wars
Damn time where can I get into reset one of these days
It's. Clones
Will be back
So we've got we got an emergency Christmas message but first
What is new walks Jordan
Marquez Callaway ministar Club
Absolute unit thank you so much
Ewok
Big Bird gold versus big
Bigfoot thank you so much and I apologize
Next to mr. aptronym thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Thank you so much
In the mix
You're now a technocrat
What's the business
Money off that heroin
Freakishly large
All right here is not a contact drop Jordans
Let it be said on my Tombstone that I'm part
We got it okay
I will honor this request once you've passed
Listen I'm going to give it to I'm going to give the wants a little bit of a
Glimpse into into a behind-the-scenes thing just so everyone knows every time he plays that
That's on both of us start dancing
We are doing
Alright you ready for this you doing on Christmas Day
We were sleeping for the most part there wasn't much to do because everything was closed
And also you know
So we were just kind of sleeping
I was watching reset Wars
To all a good-night
Here's what Alex was doing
Is an emergency Chris
A warning
2 president
Trump
You were either
Completely ignorant
The so-called facts
Gene therapy
But you helped Rams
Proof of operation
Or you're one of the most
Evil man
Who has ever
Lived
The Porsche
Toxic poison
The public
Constituents
They simply try to save their lives
And the lives of
We're about to lay out
The basic
Facts
What you told
Candace Owens
Few days ago
It's nothing but a raft
Realized
You know sometimes either or statement
Feature two things that are not mutually exclusive in both can be true at the same time
Also raft
Nice
Flip toss
Yeah it's nice to get rid of trump
That's like a grip you got to grab me something
The original
Just kind of responded to
To Trump's appearance
What's Bill O'Reilly or admitted he got the booster chair and all this this point
Candace Owens
Where she hit that I've been like implying
I'm saying that the vaccines
People are vaccinated of the ones who were in the hospital's Italian most
Of course no no no no no no playing the game right
No answer this is what he's got Alex's goose
Christmas Day
And we saved under covid this year by the way under Joe Biden
Then under you and what people took the vaccine
In this year so people are Quest
Shanaynay
The one chick
Very sick and go to the
The ones that don't take that Maxine
But
It's still their choice
And if you take the vaccine you up
Sexy results
The vaccine a good ad
If you do get it
It's a very minor form
People are dying when they taking a backseat recently Candice
Owens
Confront you polite
Face-to-face with the fact
Show called vaccines
Are causing a lot of death
An illness
And you
DoubleDown
Sing that
Nobody
Has been hurt
By the shop
But that is just
A flat-out
Lie but it is a dirty lie.
There's one explanation for this witches
In order to believe that the vaccines are more dangerous than being unvaccinated
You would have to be
Dumber or more evil than Donald
J Trump
That's interesting
Tough to wrestle
Yes I thought that obviously I have
Watching reset Wars and s*** like that course
Can't handle watching a full episode of whatever Candace Owens
No not that I'm going to watch Tim pool
Absolutely no watch the whole thing
That's about appearance
It was pretty funny
Cancel it seem very confused by not being on board
The mainline Trump community and he's exposition
The speed with which he said
No no no
Was was almost
Delicious
Yeah this is really pissed Alex off
To the point where
Christmas
He's got it released this message where
Reviews clearly pre-recorded this there
Probably multiple takes like
You can hear. Performative voice haha
That was cut to
So
We get to a little bit more of of this
Alexandra saying it like this is whatever Trump saying hear the
And then you
Triple down
On top of that
And said that 90% of
In the hospital
Around the world
Tap.
The vaccine
When the facts
Statistics show the APA
In Germany
In the UK in the US
In Canada
Across the world in place
Israel
The double A
And triple vac
Are more than
2 *
Had to be hospitalized and or die
In fact a new study
Came out
Justice League
Here it is
For you to research
But we spent so much time going over specific claims when they popped up on Alex's show in the pass I'm not even going to get back into the Weeds on the
Claims like about vaccinated people twice as likely to be hospitalized
It's just an old
False talking point but I was curious about this new study
Generally end up listening to stuff and what becomes
Necessary for me to check visually I'll go and watch the video
And so when Alex says that there's a new study out for Trump to research
The image that's on the screen is just a screenshot of a tweet that Ezra Levant posted
How about 8
A review
Great doesn't it doesn't get
Much more,
Concrete than that it really does it
Dick's big they're blowing everyone's minds and making an appeal to the former president
Save the world they can't even be bothered to
Trackdown the actual study
Get a screenshot of that do this show a tweet
The link to the study is in the tweet wow you have to
Through
Alex through so embarrassing
But I wanted to say something about the experience of going through Hazard is
Twitter feed
The link to the study
Houston kind of shocking how just stroll just scrolling through it heightened by anxiety
It's just a barrage of memes and Sensational post to make an arguments that I know or flawed and dumb
But the sheer volume of them and
The quickness that they come at you
Confidence
These people with s*** positions they do
Just proper them up
It's still heading
Effect on me
It was horrifying.
Consider with the experience to be like for someone who didn't
Know that these people are all liars and con men
He's so scary to take in
How long it would take you
To track down all this barrage of bulshit this coming at you
It's it's
Visceral
Yeah I mean we're in the situation now where I think it was
Fundamentally asking the Eternal Quest
Who gots like the gas
Who I am now and I turns out it's
While he's also be
Gas-lit
So this study
It almost certainly will either have to be redone or retracted as soon as any review begin
The quote as well as analysis of the study that shows that quote
Customers are 76.5 more percent more likely
Customers are 39 points
3% more likely to be infected then unvax
This is in regards to vaccine affect effective
Against the Omicron.
The reason I saved this study will probably never make it past the reviews that there's a glaring methodological
Ankle problem with how they prepare the data for the study
There were three groups of people that they look
Unrest
Play the people people have gotten two doses of moderna if people have gotten to do so
The Pfizer
It's very well well maybe the fact that there is a reduced efficacy overtime for these vaccines against the Omicron variants
But quite likely the reason there's a negative efficacy reflected in these numbers
Is that the study excluded
People who had previously tested positive with a PCR
Which Korea
Some problem
For the data
What is use the people who tested positive previously are probably going to be a group at skews heavily towards being unvaccinated
And it's been shown that the Omicron Barenaked apps
Absolutely reinfect people who previously
Leacock covid
Removing
Group from the dataset may have an effect on the results are released would be a cause for
Concern to trust be specific
To the numbers is being reflected
Reality
Absolutely
Even leaving that concern aside the authors of the study provided a very reasonable
Explanation for the numbers that
Makes sense
The negative estimates in the final. Arguably suggest
Different behavior and or exposure patterns in the vaccinated and unvaccinated
Causing an underestimation of the vaccine
This is likely the result of Omicron spreading rapidly initially through singles
Super spreading events
Causing many infections about young vaccinated
Right
This would make intuitive sense
Super spreader
Could have occurred in places where vaccination was required to enter and this is an issue
Particularly relevant to this study
Subjective
This study were all people in Denmark
Which is actually pretty route
In September Denmark lifted all of its covid restrictions and went back to business as usual
It was believed that there was a high enough vaccination rates there is no longer any reason to be required to show proof of vaccinations at bar
Bars and clubs or anywhere
This was prior to the first ident
Application of the Omicron variant by researchers in South Africa on November 24th
In mid-november it was starting to become an issue in Denver Ark that cases were starting to go up again
And on November 29th the Danish Health authorities re-imposed Public Health measures
And crew including real requiring masks
And not allowing people to enter many places
Without a Corona pass
If you look at this study you'll see that this is the precise time frame when their data was being collect
The first check-ins were on November 20th
Yes and it ended at the earliest
December 12th
Unless there was a positive test for a death that would lead to obviously
Here's the contact
It's very important
If you go to the Danish government site about the corona pass
These are the groups who are eligible
To get that pass
You can get a Corona pass if you have been previously infected within the last 6 months
Have been vaccinated or tested negative with the PCR test that is no more than 72 hours old
And for Rapid tests that is no more than 48 hours
People who are unvaccinated but who have tested positive in the past within the last six months are eligible for the past
That would allow them to be in places with potentially High concentration
The people around when Omicron was going wild
Super fighting events were most likely occurring
Well
Still very well may be the case that protection against Omicron variant is weaker
The further one is out from the vaccine
The negative Effectiveness may be implicated by these confounding factors
And likely doesn't reflect a reality where the vaccine
Make a person more likely to get
Not
Really something you could
Use this non-peer-reviewed study
Tobacco
So what were kind of describing is a situation where so many people are vacs
Sedated
That's the available pool of subjects
Is such that it's more likely to find
Vaccinated people are being
Reinfected
Simply because there's so many more of them
Is that kind of what we're talking about I don't believe so because I think the rates
Will probably take care of that
Balancing of that
I think
Faulty application of
The cohort
In the in the data
Not including
People who have tested positive in the past
I reflect
Skew things
Towards
All right away from unvaccinated people having higher infection
I believe that there is an argument you could make on that front and whether or not it's
Bully true or not I do think it's enough of an issue with how this was set up
That
You probably
Would want to redo it the data to the point where the conclusions you could draw from it are too tainted by that
At data being skewed
Baby yeah baby yeah
Exactly and you need to know more before you could really
Make any kind of conclusion
Also you have to consider this
For all but nine days of the time that the study was taking place
Unvaccinated people couldn't go on public transit or enter bars or restaurants
Where is vaccinated people could as well as people who were not vaccinated but who had tested positive in the past
Write these factors make the raw data that you may see blood say like in a tweet posted by
Notorious Canadian propagandist
Blastin the full picture
Exactly how much of a lowered Effectiveness there is overtime
This study alone is
Going to prove anything
Don't think Trump's going to research today
Picture of a tweet
Garbage
What is a one of the nice things about science
And the peer-review process
Is that when you have a lot of people all coming to the same results are far more reliable than if you just have
One study out of Denmark
Yeah
Kinds of questions are not really even missed
On the authors of the study
Does the conclusion of the study even with these like rod numbers that would
Possibly be able to be taken out of context to show a
Looking negative riding 6%
Babe that's not the conclusion that they come to write based on
Certain
Of contact
Wow that almost
Makes me think that if any any
Eddie study now
Should have like
Highlighted sections where the authors are like hey
This data could be
Be taken out of context that used for evil purposes
Just like big
Giant
Bullet points of light
Here's how propagandists might take this
You can even go to the setting be like to hear what they said you or a little junk where it's just like
Bad
To study hit with a rolled-up newspaper ideas every every study has a point where it's like
Sexy don't take this out of context Alex you piece of s***
This goes on at the
Plan out of the globalist
Quite terrifying
To know about this
Within 3 MI
You are twice as
Is likely to be
Become infected
Omicron
The Pfizer
That's because it's a racing your immune
And that was the
The plant
Erase the populations amused
Make them dependent
Ongoing gene therapy
Have to be taken
As often
Everyday
That's so stupid that I don't even really know where to begin with
I guess I would say that Alex would probably have done the second take every said omnicron
Actually thinks that's the name
Rattling it it almost more importantly though if the vaccines were wiping up people's immune systems you would just be seeing
Sing an increase in cases of covid particularly Omicron
You be seeing people dead
Everywhere from normally very minor things
Without proper medical attention people who are vaccinated would be dying or getting severely ill from bacteria that we all normal
Encounter on a regular basis
People be ending up in the ER all over the place with things like food
I mean I guess you could if you had a severe case of food poisoning anyway but you know what I mean
Ammonia would lay waste to this land
Similarities
It does share a lot of similarities with what you would
Expect to see you in the car
Right right circumstances of covet
For four people who were infected with HIV for the longest time it was not that the actual
Hy-Vee would kill them
It would destroy their immune systems
To the point that they would be killed by many other differ
Sure
Yep
Alex is saying about how you're twice as likely to get infected if you get the Pfizer vaccine doesn't match up with a misrepresentation
Somebody's reporting from Ezra Levant
Crank but I don't even know what's going on tonight
Lovett weird compound in
Yes
So we talked about tranches earlier just because
Fast forward
We know this word
Is now identifiable with the FDA
Better being released
Visa vie
There
Security check
Exit and safety
Measure surrounding the the Pfizer shot
Tranches
That is
The big Pharma takeover
Of humanity
Helium
From day one
So-called back
Roll out
Pfizer in the FDA
Plot to the
Stop
Being released
The medical whistleblower group
The last two months
Federal courts have ordered
FDA to release
Several tranches
A millions of pages of.
The first
Data Doctors
Show conclusive
The show called Maxine
Bowser
Thousands of death
And more than 100
Thousand
Adverse
Including
Spontaneous abortion
It's so funny to me that Alex thinks he's fighting a big campaign against big Pharma when he couldn't
Stop promoting hydroxychloroquine and Ivermectin
Ivermectin Zone by Merck
And the most prevalent form hydroxychloroquine is
Is produced by sanofi SA
He's going to stick at the big Pharma by encouraging people to buy a bunch of stuff from the Starbucks
So evil you got to be on Instagram
It's nice to hear that there's more conscious of documents now
We've already gone over Alex's narratives about this dumb s*** back on episode 626 so I'm not going to be
Over it all again
He's talking points haven't changed at all so I don't really believe he's seen any of the new document
Once that have been released
How the initial documents the ones he lied about initially were released
On November 17th 2021
After that
A few PBSO released on December 1st
Another batch of documents on December 13th
Mn1 index
Israel on December 22nd
There's absolutely zero chance Alex's read any of the documents that were released on December 13th because he's already got ever
Everything he needs to make up stories
From the first document that he read
That's enough
Why would you overcomplicate things when you can use that one document as a Bedrock to build whatever bulshit he wants on top of
Also Alex probably isn't interested in what's his argument at all
There's a 344 page analysis of efficacy trials that shows very strong efficacy results
So that
Doesn't really help
Also
Hey 2030 page document listing interactions with participants in the trial
Like visits to get medical histories or document showing
Informed consent being given
How to get a dig through this
No one without anything for him to be mad about yet so the documents in this Toronto just
Basically the same as the ones in the old one
It's just more of the same thing which
Just kind of tell that he doesn't actually believe that anything to be revealed in any of these documents
If you actually believe that this was like a big smoking gone wouldn't be trying to squeeze out as much evidence as he could from them
It's just repeating the same old s***
Same old
It's not it's not that there's anything in there it's that they exist at all
Write the Specter of them existing
Zach is enough
To convince
Photo.
Know if you see a Komodo dragon in your leg you know that's probably means that there are dragons that fly around and shoot fire
That's not quite
The good boys
That's what makes sense
Because one exists obviously they eat most extreme person of it exists when I was a kid
Let you know I lived by for a bit
And all kinds of lizards
This taught me that reptilian aliens
Definitely
Fight one Gecko and you realize that if there was one that was saved several thousand
Repeat all
You probably wouldn't win
So obviously that's something to be afraid of my most recent Wizards
Anyway Alex what a great non sequitur
Resolution
I miss lizard Chase for lizards
So Alex
A little bit in this Christmas
Report I don't know if it's him
Someone who's editing
It does because they add in
Clips
From Alex's show bolster
Alright
We've talked about this
FDA.
Trunks one
This is a massive story right here
And the documents that are in it
Which I'm sorry I met you
Thousands of more deaths thousands of more miscarriages
Bleeding out of your nose into having convulsions becoming paralyzed
Becoming blind
Are your ovaries basically dissolving
Find covid-19
Women's periods
Eventually give you endometriosis where uterus is going to be removed
This President Trump
Is what you are now
Signing on
So there's a recent study that looked at the possibility of a connection between the vaccines and menstrual changes and they did find
Beta incidence of menstrual cramps
Seem to rise after vaccination
Is a total liar in a
This study has nothing to do with endometriosis or people needing to have their uterus is removed
Panera
The actual study had to do with self-reporting
Any changes in menstrual patterns for women between the ages of 18 and 30
The specific changes they were looking
Forehead to do with heavier
Your periods longer periods longer or shorter time between periods
And at any increased pain
I guess if Alex wants to play hypothetical OBGYN games and assume that any incidences of pain were secretly and Dimitri
Trios I guess
Do that if you want but he's just be making that up because this study does not back that up at all
The author author
Very careful to point out that this date or Eliza
Entirely on self-reporting so there is a possibility that other variables
Could lead to participants not reporting their symptoms
With complete accuracy
Also they do point out that their data shows that
Foremost
The changes were Transit
And had returned to normal levels Windows to was given
Approximately two to three months after vaccination
With the first dose
They don't have any data get on the duration of any effects after dos2 but it does appear that it
Probably will be similar to
The phenomenon Cena doseone
But that's like 2bc
There's indications of the probably
Maybe have some effect
Can I go back to
I'm absolutely not saying this is no big deal I don't want people to think that
But the study doesn't show the results
Better align with Alex's reporting
This is a pattern
Because Alex is a habitual liar
Yeah loves to lie
And it's somebody who is not a weird 1930s man-child
Many times about her menstrual cycle and there are many different two variables that can make it early or late or heavy or light
Or whatever
Desert ongoing process
It's not like
Hey it didn't happen on the 22nd so we're all
Ditto
I do not introduce the
This club because it's just fun Alex make a fun fret
Okay this is
It's one thing to
Watch the shoutout
Because you believed it would
Save the p
People and help in the lockdown
But now that you know
Signs you onto a fraud
You must extra
Locate yourself
From this lie
Or you will be
Forever known
At the end
Vivi
What most valuable
Vaccine
And the name problem
Associated
Pure Evil
There's no way that wasn't written
Ahmed that was that was delivered so much like
I got this TV.
Seen too many comedians go up with a joke they knew couldn't
Fail and watch it fail and hear that exact same response
I also
Think
That if you're going to do this
You got to find a way to make MVP work
You don't throw another another V in their otherwise you're just creating a new act like that make up a new Echo
Similar
Tune there if you're going to do and BP with four letters you know there's no point
You got your dream leaf
Impatient
Osteoporosis
Alimony avoider I got nothing
See that's why you have to prepare a heads-up acronyms a hard
The Dome
Alex brings up an expert
Here that supposed to convince Trump
You take this seriously baby
The inventor
MRNA
Technology
Dr. Robert Malone
Has gone public
For more than a year and a
Warning
Technology used
Counter a cold
Would lead to serious
Blood clot
An autoimmune disorder
Arcadia
And now the hospital
Across the West
Western world
Double facts
Patience
Showing exact sign
Of Aging
There's no evidence of people or antibody-dependent enhancement from covid vaccine
I've seen Alex tried to present evidence of it but none of it proves anything
Just headlines
Maybe a tweet
I am tied that faulty
Misrepresented studies
Yeah it's always
Since to make it
Conclusion on that
Malone it's definitely not a consensus opinion that he's the inventor of mRNA technology
He's been making that claim as he makes the rounds on all media Outlets like info
Podcast Dark Horse
But it's not really
Wayfair
He did some work in the late 80s that involved mRNA but their studies you can find that predate his work
Using mRNA stuff going back to at least
Center for technology
As well as it being kind of disrespectful to all the other scientists
The played a role in the gradual development
It's fun though tell me inventor of the technology because then you get to play out there
Undramatic game where the guy who invented something
It turned out to be deadly
Has to come out and try and stop the monster he created a really great story it's really fun it really is
Into the human psyche yeah but we all know that Robert Malone never would have become the MVP of
Bulshit about vaccines if it weren't for
Sure
Yeah
I made you I made you
Twist away for a second and that was worth it
I was trying to find a way to add in hornacek
I was having a difficult.
This s*** Run Deep
On Infowars
For The Narrative of like I've got to fix the wrong
Like if you were called back when he was around doctor group claimed that he was motivated to sell Health Products
Cleanses to undo the damage that his father did because he allegedly invented Saran Wrap
Saran Wrap and Robert mRNA technology
But if you want to pretend those things are true you get 2% their stories as like a comic book s*** what is it what is
More f****** apocryphal than the sun trying to undo the damage of the father that I
Biblical Star Wars
Yes I was going a little bit deeper into the cannon but yes it is true
This boy was really confused because
Alex was talking about Robert Mueller
And then he starts home with somebody else but he doesn't say their name
And it's really confusing
Does dishonestly or anything
Robert vallone
An emergency
Warning
Parents of the world
To not give their children
The experimental mRNA in
The most
Good names in the world
Concerning vaccine
As the former
Chief scientist
At Pfizer
Overbite
He has looked at
Every angle of
This rollout
The US
But across the world and us
Concluded
Better to take deliberate
Depopulation
Opera
Targeting
Humanity
With infertility
Blood clot
Heart attack
Just confusing he started talking about Michael Heaton
Subjective
It sounded like it was almost edited out
It didn't have that car right there and you can hear the cut
Changes the subject
Right it's a little bit concerning
Yeah I don't know why they would do that though because like the den play a video that has Michael udon's name on it right now
Not like
It's not like you have to censor that cuz he's going to sue them or something I don't know he's a wacky
Do you think
I don't understand but it does if it gets there was an explanation that may present
Blur
Yeah you better about that out
Kesakitan as the former Chief scientist Pfizer it difficult over vaccine
This is a flagrant lied
It's meant to imply his pretend
What are you doing was working at Pfizer what you did
His title was vice president and chief scientific officer of the allergy and respiratory unit of Pfizer
He worked at the Pfizer plant in Kent which was closed
Decided not to try to find another job in the industry but instead of cortisone pass
He convinced the higher-ups
TripAdvisor to allow them to work with some of their compound
They almost never do
He's telling of it
The key wasn't getting Pfizer to recognize that we could not pay cash for the asset
But we were willing to Grant equity in exchange for their assignment well spinning the dream of therapeutic use in an area
Is that at the time they had little interest
Essentially we would create upside in which they share and they needed to do nothing but agrees our proposition
The alternative most likely being that everything would be lost
Is out of this initiative he formed a biotech company called Z Arco
Which almost entirely focused on Dermatology
Particularly to eczema drug
Candidates
But they have gotten from Pfizer
After showing a good deal
The promised largely surrounding a once-daily orally-administered eczema treatment called
Zpl 389
Zika was bought out by Novartis
Sprint undisclosed
But some speculation has been made that it might have been upwards of a billion dollars
Great promising eczema drug
Anti-vaxxer with a billion dollars
Yeah I know I
This doesn't turn out great once you get past 10 million all monies imaginary to Mesa
Whatever
Is Blvd made was largely based around
The promise of this drug zpl 389
And the potential that it had to become
A prophet
Coronavirus
However if you flash forward to July 2021
You'll learn that they story did not end well
The drug failed to perform in face
To a trials and Novartis decided to abandon it
In the process they took a hit of a proxy
Smelly 400
89 billion.
Wow wow almost half a billion dollars of side money
Wow
Yeah I mean
It was something that did not live up to
The early indications
And that was that
The largest thing on you Don's resume since 2011 and even prior to that when he was working advisory had nothing to do with vaccines
Even infection
Just disease
The nature of the work that he was doing
And have done is intentionally being fudged in order to lend his words
An unearned credibility
He's made a bunch of completely unfounded covid conspiracy claims in the past year or so but there's no proof for any of it
Other than 2.2 his fake former job title
And assumed that he was the 4th of March
Chief scientist for Pfizer then he must know what he's talking
Same thing
The guy who's like turned against the company used to be in absolutely
Same
Trucking storyline I'm doing the wrong absolutely most respected people in the
World regarding vaccine technology absolutely
Alex might respect you. A lot
Because he says without want
But that doesn't mean any object in the real world
Nonsense
Donna Malone
Hey
Ways to get up on
About everything all the time
How can you get rich Dan that's it's a it's a meritocracy that we all know is 100% accurate
If you have money you're better than people who don't
I've heard that
I've heard that before
Alex is doing like
Weird Movie voices trying to threat
Trump baby
The world is watching
The world is
Very very
You do
Right now
Are you going to continue
Assign your fate and
Phaeton 2 cost
Bob and Bill Gates
And the tables group
And the whole Global issue an agenda
Probably
Or will you
Stand up
And be the hero
So many of us
If you were
And say no
Medical
This is so dramatic probably not
Yeah yeah yeah
That is
That is great that is really more fun to live in
Movie4u
Christmas Day what was it three years ago it was drunk throwing hatchets are other Studios on top of the world that is more fun then you better
That's true
Come on out
I miss that maybe over
Malicious
I'm sure.
But they won't be thrown in a camera because he can't afford that kind of
So anyway and Bill Gates
They are they like to bite
I can choose.
This house
Cardiff
Coming down
Klaus Schwab Peter.
Bill Gates
Anthony fauci
They all bit off more
We know they premeditated
This whole operation
Take over
I get it
You wanted to be the hero you wanted to go
Get the vaccine out there.
Economy moving again
I saw
How you were deceived
But now
Clearly signing onto this
And that's why it's so important
Public record
Warren
You were conscious
You made
A decision
Okay
Don't know how to make
I mean
Can you imagine
Trump caring about any of this
Snow
Gifts
That Dynamic gets a little bit
Too obvious
The report goes on cuz he just kind of imploring Trump to do something
Never going to do
President-trump
There's not
Time left
Across the world
Children are
Injected
With dangerous
Gene therapy
The race their immune
And give them
Chronic illness
President-trump
You don't want this
To be your legacy
You don't want
Tubi
The person that was
Creek by fauci
The Takeover
And who later when confronted with the facts
Decided to be a coward
DoubleDown
Betting on the Corp
Betting on big Pharma
Betting on the UN
The build back better
Great reset
Don't throw in your lot with Bill Gates
Don't throw in your lap
Stand with
Club America
The world
Stand with the chilled
Come out and tell the public
Call provel cheese arrest
Get on the right side
What fortunate Limited
Trick Trumper fool them into getting his vaccines made but there's one thing I can't imagine
Ever happening
It's Trump coming out and saying that someone fooled him
Do you know Alex running
A pretty close race in terms of who the bigger narcissist is
Ego would never allow him to look that week
In public
That's a really fun way for Alex to present his point
You can do this blowhard s*** about how time is running out for Trump
How to turn back
A directly to Trump so when Trump inevitably does nothing
How to pretend that he actually JoJo likely rejected
It's ironic that this is a Christmas message because it does remind me of like
If
Santa had been bribed
You cannot deliver
Presents this year
You got to think of the children Santa
If you don't
Do this this year it'll never happen again
You got to change your mind there's nothing more valuable than the children Santa
We got to make this movie
Alex
Videos getting a little annoying for me because it's so obviously meant to be for the audience while
Tending to be a warning to Trump
My feels to me like this is an attempt to soft-launch
Turning Trump into a villain on the show while doing so in a way where hopefully people in Alex's who still support Trump
Turn on Alex
I am stuck between two extremes community that he's helped cultivate
The Trump idolaters and the anti-vax lunatics and now he's in the unenviable position of trying to thread the needle
And whether retains as much of his Revenue stream as possible.
Alienated
Too much of either side
Let's
Good good bad luck your way that you're going
To convince hardcore Trump
Bisnow evil
It'll be tough and there's no way you're going to convince people who think that vaccines are killing everyone that it's okay for Trump to be like
Things are great
Well you got too far down the road of the vaccines are killing everybody
That
There's nobody
Who could
Support vaccines that you could
Keep your support for it's like if Ron Paul came out and was like everybody get the booster and Alex would have to be
Be like Well Ron Paul was a great Patriot Buddies
He's too old now he's lost his mind
Something like that you'd have to lose
Whoever it doesn't
His dad could be in favor of vaccines
Mitigating committing genocide
Idea
At all
Acumen is audience
Trump
Hangers-on
They're still around
I think if they could accept this presentation of Alex turning the truck
Yeah it wouldn't be too hard for them
Except
Oh that's
Yeah yeah
Cereal wasn't going to do
It's not enough
Hey babe I'm dropping a big bomb is too much of a hard-on maker for all of these people to do that but
I've been seeing some people posting
Really drunk and started screaming
How many didn't know that he was being recorded before he went live
Years old
Posted
The implication that it's current
I want to say
A beard in that we don't need you don't need help to make him look like a piece
Alex
He's got more threats
About Trump's Legacy
From every angle
The globalist
More than they can
And their attempt
To take over the planet
Using this medical
Healthcare
What's in the Rockefeller Foundation
Operation lockstep
Is Destin
To fail
There isn't much
Set time for YouTube
Turn back from
If you only care about your
Yourself
Your leg
Will be that
Your legacy will be that
Your legacy
Is that of a
Child
Chiller
Using medical term
Still time for you to turn back
As their disgust over and over again operation lockstep isn't a real thing
It's a lie about a Rockefeller document and basically just traces back to a meme
What was list
Essentially what's happened is it the two of them don't agree on the issue with the vaccine
What's up level ice
Expect that Alex knows
The supposed evidence he's presenting is s***
So the last option left
Trump to help me expand the graph
What is to extort him
Alex isn't saying that if Trump doesn't change his tune on vaccines the natural result of that is the tramps like us
Will that beat out of
Monstrous baby killer
You saying what a trump doesn't change his tune on vaccines
Alex.
Yelling about how Trump is a monstrous baby killer
That's what's going on
Alex
I know a lot of
Dirt
Hotmail
The subtext
And text of this video is that the warning Alex has given Trump as a warning
But he's going to turn his audience against Trump
If he doesn't do what Alex wants to do
By calling him a monster is baby
This is meaningless and it's going to go nowhere for a couple Ruiz
First the Trump caught world doesn't really need Trump
Himself anymore
It'll take some effort to build up a new demagogue for them to Rally around but the physical person of trump isn't really that necessary
If he goes again
Pillars of the
Construct a Dogma that they've made then they'll have to choose whether they're more invested in Trump as a person
Or the Kovach
Conspiracies and anti-vax bulshit they base their right
I suspect the most with you the ladder and you can see the similar Dynamic play out in the world
Don't even really need Trump anymore even though there are the ideology was based on the idea that Trump was the anointed savior
Was going to release the Swarm
The storm
It is it is
Funny the
The framing that we dealt with for so long
Especially in the campaign for Trump
How to become
Is who is this guy
Why is this guy
This guy this guy always
When in reality he was only an avatar that was
Almost
Generated from the swamp of
Misery and hate
Hatred that was already there and he was simply a conduit for it to it
Absolutely
The second reason this is going nowhere is a shorter way of saying
Second reason is going nowhere is because the solution for Trump would be to give in to the demands of these
People who are threatened
I need to turn on him
In-N-Out
To preserve his base
That would be what it is like
I was kind of hoping
He'll do
This would make Trump look super weak
Which an effect eliminates the thing that makes him a
Appealing to the base in the first place
He was their strong man who's going to fight against their imaginary evil enemies
So he shows himself to be weak enough to take a threat like this seriously you probably get Alex
Not to talk s*** about it but the appeal that the Elders of strongman leaders essentially destroyed
Rendering him more less useless
Hi ever going to be your president and I have made it very clear iamsu
Servient to Alex's whim
He frightens me I don't want Alex to be mad at me it's not a good campaign rally and cry
Know this whole thing feels really similar to Alex lashing out at work
Brenda got him like a pig because Rogan wouldn't let Alex back on his show
Sandy Hook
In that case Rogan back down and gave him to Alex's.
Possibly motivated by a misguided belief that they have a meaningful friendship
In doing so he lost control of the narrative
Alex now more or less own to the image of Joe Rogan
For his audience and Rogan inexorably Public Image.
I don't think of the full consequences of that decision of really even
The Fallen Joey yet but I don't think it's going to look good nice
Cyborg
Trump will do that and he never will
Compass never going to see this message and even if you did you wouldn't give a s*** about houses meaningless threats
They're being passed off as a warning
Matter
Rogan only responded like that because he ostensibly believe them believes them to be friends
I think it probably was a part of it yet I think
Brokens also
Maybe he's a little bit weaker than
He likes to appear publicly or you just has a I mean
Miss blade
Misplaced
Sensitive
Empathy
C4 a weird lunatic reaching out to him
Crying in pain I think that's the most generous
Interpretation
So here is how this report ends
Regardless of what
We the people of America app
The world
What's happening
Wait why did you
Say President Trump is a third-person I thought this was a warning to
What's going on
And we are going to
Continue to Edge
UK others that
Aren't
And we are going to continue to
Politically and culturally and economically
Spiritually
Mobilize
To stand against this one world government
Medical tyranny
Cashless Society
Medical ID
Social credit score carbon
From being able to take over our lives
Dominator
Convert US from
Interplay
Regardless of what Trump
We have already chosen
To tell the truth
How to take out
Now Trump
Japanese decide
Which side is
The enemies of humanity
There are secrets
Okay
Call ride
Opposed
Hellboy made my greatest discovery yet
So yeah I think
In terms of trump picking site
I think he has
Are you already chosen
Believe them
Shouldn't be forced to get it I guess
I don't even know what what is he actually
Who care
He's just saying bulshit out of his ass
Always
Is real strong
Until here the visiting the message directed at Trump and that's affected empathy
Still, like pretending you're talking directly to Trump it's just a
Pathetic marketing ploy
Make your audience feel like they're listening to something important to do putting it on the record
Morality is talkingshit
I'm quite like an open letter on a Blog with 1,000
Subscribers today
Bring home to whoever is getting that open letter
So we leave the
Going to say warm Waters of
The Christmas
Special hook
Trying to threaten
Trump into going along with his
Agenda I will say it wasn't ringing ambassador
Bestway
As far as Christmas special
I mean the claymation was still in credit was this on the level of a Muppet Christmas Carol
Oh absolutely not absolutely not
So we get to the 29th
Smile and
The show starts out
Hot
Straight out blaming hot
My mind is for my soul has
Researching
Online
On the phone and
Just don't repeat
I say that to give me the bad news
We're dead already
Oh boy
Alright okay
Because I've read things
Printed off of computers I got bad news I got bad news
We're dead all
Are we philosophically dead already like 11%
Right
Estimated that that's your question
Hawaii
What was the last thing I expected to be the follow-up to I do all this studying
Little bit of a pause and then we're dead already
Your aunt asked me what the philosophically dead thing at that like
Alex does
Clarify a little bit
We're dead already
I only say that
Boo
Information for what's about to go down
The question is how dad do you want to be
See it is not the question
It is kind of a philosophical death
Only mostly dead
They're being gradient to death like
I guess Alex thinks that your things are going bad you're like a quarter dead
In a way you could describe
Part of you is
Is that more dead than
Not
Or if you like have frostbite really bad frostbite at your guys or something
I feel like maybe that's giving your foot
Anthropomorphism that might not be okay
I did
Hear that from reset watch
Not bad at all about it give you a sense of comfort to know that
That whatever happens in the present
Is it has already happened and you are already
No
I can tell
I think a bit of it
Is
Maybe understandable
Maybe some of it is not and a little bit of comes down to some of his personal business
That's being reported
Times now
Almost 23
2 years ago
How many times have I said this is an organized
Collapse of civilization
And the destruction of
Confidence
In our government
Institutions
Our family
Word for word or
Russian troops
Number one story in the world
Mixing up medication and blacking out and attaching herself police United
Charter controller
World
Number one on Reddit
Number one on Twitter
Number one on Google
Number one on Instagram
Number one
On Christmas Eve
Because it makes the family
Because it makes
Christmas
Because
On the people
Who really stupid
Alex is a high-profile media figure so it's not really surprising there would be a ton of stories about his wife
Getting arrested for domestic violence on Christmas
Susan Bennett a con the family or Christmas
Conversation
And it being about like his
Grandiose ideas of his own murder.
While I definitely don't agree with Alex about that nonsense
I do think that people didn't do a great job with the story
Hemet possibly there was a bit of schadenfreude the people were expressing at the idea of Alex being the target of domestic violence and I think that's
It's not cool at all
Making fun of victims of domestic violence
Ghetto we understand is
Even if they're assholes that's
Not appropriate and can easily result
The shaming
Stigmatizing in triggering those other Vic
Absolutely
Certainly a good enough reason
M22 not play that game
No without without all or any of the information because that's kind of
Of the point of my
Station on the show about a dumb joke and then I read about it and deleted that.
Dumb joke
Christ I had no f****** clue I
All I got was Alex got beat up
Very funny to me
Sure rest of it not funny
Or any of the details
I just reread it forces people
To relive their own b******* and it's
It's f***** up and I can appreciate that you know you taking
Some sort of ownership and responsibilities of
I'm having made a badge
No interest in
F*** that no
Fun like about scolding
I think that people who had far more information at their disposal
Made decisions
That was
Something bad cover
In a bit of a strange situation because I typically try to avoid covering things that are personal matters rally
Bring his business out on the
The streets
Which makes me uncomfortable
I thought about it and I'm not going to spend
Time on the story unless it's
Becomes like
There's some sort of a major developed
Met with it
I just wanted to bring it up here briefly to make sure the people don't think I haven't heard about it and send me 100 link
Time-in publicly that I don't
Support a fair amount of the coverage and commentary
Because going on about this story
Also some of the commentary that I don't support about it comes directly from Alex on his own show and that's kind of
Tough for me to ignore and I hate I hate
I hate this position not a good situation
Very
You know my heart goes out to those
Absolutely
Spend time with
Is
Stories
And news and
Lies
Is that Alex tells about
It's like a
How old is incredible
3% of people who died
Just just just just bombshell after bombshell after bombshell after bombshell
Was just another thing that Alex was pulling from Steve kirsch's stubs
Disposed
Dogshit
Isabella study the
Apparently found because Michael you Don sent him a link to a bitchute video about it
Is there a non peer-reviewed paper which was published by a group called doctors for covid FL
Because anti-vax Outlet leaning heavily in the direction of saying that the vaccines are a weapon
Doctors for covid ethics should be very much another red flag of like
Anunnaki was named hiding the most obvious evil
What are the founding signatories of the group is Michael G.
Who sent Steve Kerr's the paper
And of course
One of the other founding signatories of the group is superhit bhakti who's one of the two researchers credited in
In this paper
Is it clearly unverified piece of work being done by an ATV X Outlet being masqueraded as an actual
You're mistaking it it's clearly
Synergy
Jesus
I believe that
This isn't a study at all
If anything it's an attempt at a persuasive essay
From the paper
We here with present scientific evidence that calls for an immediate stop to the use of G Bass
Covid-19 vaccine
Reverse layout why the agents cannot protect against viral infection
If this were actually a legitimate study about whether or not deaths that occurred after vaccinations were caused by the vaccination
It wouldn't necessarily be a topic there was germane to the paper
This is anti-vax advocacy which is
Rising because it was written by an advocate pushed on another anti-vax Advocates Subs
It's almost
It's almost nice of them to lay out there conflict of interest
Up-top
Harem
We're going to tell you what b*******
And then give you the b*******
What does completely on verify paper did was
15.
Send it claims to Don histopathological analysis on their organs boo
There's literally no data provider
Even so that the vaccines caused these people to have heart attack
Honestly I'm just
Guessing that that's
What's the point because the cause of death of for these people
Aren't even list
Just that 14 out of the 15 had hearts that were effect
Didn't Subway that they do for their predetermined conclusion
The closest you get to data is a list of some demographic information about the people whose organs they allege
The analyze
One of them was he knighted
85 year old woman who died 68 days after getting the vaccine
She's almost 100 years old there's over two months
Between
My first thought is this seems a little thin
Similarly there's another patient with an 89 year old woman who died six months after getting the vaccine
People in their subject Pool died of an unknown number of days after vaccinations know when they got back
Well you don't need to know Dan you know that the vaccines evil
Two of them
I don't even know which
Vaccine they got
They got a vaccine
Maybe it was the MMR vaccine you don't know
This isn't the study isn't never pass any kind of critical review
There are other doctors and researchers doing histological examinations on people who have died after vaccinations
They are coming up with anything close to this kind of result in
Generally those papers
Actually have data
And aren't just like
I think you got a busted couple months ago bad
Real bad
Come on real real bad stuff
Here
I do I do like like a sofen
So dumb
And like
Steve Kerr
Is out there promoting it as if it's like
This proves
93% of people who died after getting the vaccine is so funny to me
That if you're going
To cherry-pick
Take that bad they're still there doing the 97% for voted for Putin think they're like
Listen 14 out of 50
I'm not going to say that everybody to get the vaccine
We all know that would be
Flight clarification
It's 93% of people who do die afterwards it was
Because of
93% of people who get the vaccine dying would be
People I always at I have more difficult time is like this is
Is the thinnest of soups
And
It's just
Yet another in a long
String of thin soups that are being presented by Steve Kerr
He's going to get to try again
People are going to be like shut up man
Homeopathic
Broth
It's so thin
Yeah
It's
I want a little bit more I want
Chunky Soup
I don't want to chili I'm talking about a good stew
I do want to chill out
Navigate to dog you love being generally
Does chili yeah
New York
I do not like paper copy
But this is the end of civilization
And we know that because Alex has a lot of stacks of news
No
This is the end of civilization as you know it
Score on eras of blessing
Trying to scare you
I love you
For what
We are in the middle of the New World Order we're in the middle of the mark of the beast tank up we are in the middle
This is one stack here
You're out of
123456789 10 11 12
31 stacks
Impossible
Buzz Marketing for Baskin-Robbins
Yeah I would say
Congratulations reproving you know how to
Workout that's good
Yeah I would like independent confirmation on there being actually 31 stack
I didn't watch the video but I believe it I see how much paper he generally has all the bat
Obscene
More sure there's 31's text of articles
In front of you
Who cares
Yeah there's too much to cover agreed
Just do one well
Yes do what
One-story well
Stay on topic
Digging into the details
That's your job
I can't trust
Rescue with one piece of paper let alone with a stack of
You got to earn
Semantically connected
He might as well be just grabbing random I find the grouping of stacks
Tubi
Chaotic
Yeah and
Just random
A large number
Go with flash card
Flashcards are the way to go cuz we know that most of those pieces of paper at most have a tweet on them
I agree but my point is this yes
There are Thirty-One snacks paper
But it's arbitrary why any of them that is one stack of paper
Yeah
That is just one big old stack
Is there any label on the stack like this is the this is the lies stack this is the other all the lights.
Zoomer stackin
So here we go. We're going to get into the first
Stacks
Golden tsunami will drive Health Systems towards collapse who we need trillions we need you
You in control
Healthcare system has collapsed
Okay
The best Healthcare System
So this was a story this fact is beasts of the stack
Actually really get into the actual article at any greater detail than he just did that
Maybe the story that was taken from the ASP newswire but I can tell that Alex is reading this headline
From when it was posted on ndtv.com
Is the new site primarily about India
India news
Screenplays for him to get ahead a little bit.
You might have to have gone looking
Anyway the underline article doesn't say anything about needing tons of funding or that the UN
To take over in a
Nevada Healthcare System
Just got out of a sad list of things that countries are trying to do to limit the spread of infection
As the looming
Hospitals being completely overwhelmed
Germany shutting down nightclubs and grease band music and bars and restaurants until January
16th
Had to like that kind of
Hey listen we're not going to close down bars
But I am close down to hang out
Itself actually written by mdtv which is clearly stated on their website
Except the headline this story has not been edited by NDTV
Hades published from a syndicated
Feed
All Alex operates off is
Because the stuff that he's saying never really has anything to do with the body of the Articles he covers
So actually in reality what he's doing is basically creating an entire narrative based on the editorial decisions of an
Indian news website that he probably doesn't even know exist
This is fascinating levels of stupid
Yeah
Because here it's just basically on headlines
Who knows who wrote most of these headlines
It's almost
A fascinating glimpse into something that I would never have
Thought of
Like that idea of just
God I need
Someone
Else to write the thing that I want to rip off of
So I'm just going to go dig
Maybe or maybe it's just the first one they found
Yeah
You're just going to be able
Ball on it
Bryant what you're doing
Is really just using
The basis of Fitbit editors website
Evidence of the globalist
Plans what is
Ridiculous send them
Sunflowers are
If you did that with all the people he lied about
You'd be running out of job
Will you be in chocolate shortage have to deal with Raptors anymore
The Raptors
He's going to read all the stank
It is about right here we go
Real quick it's really awesome that he's playing the mission impossible
Impossible mission isn't working
And yet some of the most insane gaslighting ever
This pack will self-destruct some of the most
Insane Gaslight Iver
Bill Gates and Anderson Cooper
Take away people's Social Security that don't take the injections
Clear as day
Warriors run by Pfizer
Real
Again we all know they got all over TV saying don't let you leave your house take your kids away
It's really pretty amazing to me that Alexandra thinks that if he's able to read off all the headlines and his Stacks that isn't turn 24
Printed out for him that's going to be an accomplishment
Or that it will have proven anything
It's interesting in a way like it might be fun to play some Wagers about whether or not he gets through them but ultimately
Who cares
Most of the headlines are going to be about the same story from different websites
Like how the NDTV article is just a
Aafp story with an in-house head
It's going to be most of
What he's got the cover
Raiders did do a fact-check of claims we're going around on social media that Anderson Cooper wanted to take away Social Security from people who didn't
That claim is not true
Who's part of a question that he was posing
Into Bill Gates because it was
An interview like is this something
Should be done weird though because
You know who really wants to take away Social Security from everybody whether they're vaccinated or not
Every politician Alex's ever supported those people usually yeah
2 is it's a dangerous precedent for Alex to be f****** around with where
He believes that in a journalist asking the question is the same thing as them advancing opposition because I
I would like to point to his entire career where he actually does do that quite a bit
Things that he might be bi
Getting sued over
So also Alex is making up advisor owns Reuters because
I like it's something he probably slept past the audience
Riders is owned by Thomson Reuters corporation which is majority-owned by the Woodbridge
Pfizer has its own company and has nothing to do with these other entities
It's just as a board member of Pfizer
It's just it
I mean
When you have so many parent companies and subsidiaries and this guy is on the board of this and on the board of that
You can tell somebody oh this is owned by some company and there's like
I can't look into it and it might be so f******
I don't know
Your mission
Should I choose with something
Is to read your sack never let's dig into the stacks
You always start on my right side cuz it's always the
Stop
Let's just do something different over here
Rodger science
Question is
I'm pushing vaccines
Rx-3 headlines
No time spent on any of these stories whatsoever here's the breakdown
What headline is about dropping of vaccine mandates in New York with Alex should be in favor of and kind of undercut some of his own men
Ameritas
But how they're going to force iPhone to get back
Specifically he said that they were going
Divorce every one to get the vaccine in this example is it people not force
Some people to get the backseat this out of the stack
Yeah it doesn't really help
The next to the comment but science from football player Aaron Rodgers which Alex doesn't think is going far enough so
Escalated for the Packers in touchdowns thrown
You got to trust them on the side is also third on the science list the Packers history
Shannon Sharpe
Whether I can think of other Packers player
Football was never one of my
I think number one is obviously Lombardi himself Favre
Bar was
Barbies
Play for the Packers just making sure
I told you what
And then the third headline that Alex has to be rounded out with him
Tentatively giving it up to ram
Pause
This is this is the tip
Hey Rand Paul said something
The end
Play for others
Go to write
Slater on his career play for the Vikings
See that's that might have been where I got any play for Wrangler
Keyblade for sending pictures of your dick B
Another headline
Here's a big
Heavens-above NASA English priest prepare
Father next big deals
Dismiss reporting this story because he
Just read the headline
Who's the story that was making the rounds recently but text about a program that was called societal implications of estradiol
Ecology which ran from 2015 to 2018
The idea was that there was a bunch of religious Scholars and they'd meet up at the center for
Inquiry at Princeton University
Discuss how religious communities would respond to the discovery of alien life
It should that ever happen
The reason that there were headlines about this recently is because one of the theologian
Reverend Andrew Davison
He's publishing a book about his experience child astrobiology and Krista
Doctor
Apparently it's takeaway was quote
The headline findings are that adherence of a range of religious Traditions report that they
You can take that idea in their stride
That did the idea of aliens being a threat to religious beliefs
Is over rest
I mean do you know in a certain he's kind
And if saying listen we can rack
Get the f*** out
I think it was
Made a similar comment
Number of years back about
A week out there ways
Is that you can incorporate
It's no different than
The original Church suddenly finding out that there were Aboriginal people in Australia
It's how can they be subject to the same original sin if they've literally never heard
Heard of this b*******
Do some challenges just the illogic
Bickley of
If there are
Aliens on another planet
Did Jesus die for their say exactly
And I wasn't there at the center for theological inquiry
These people are
Obviously
Experts in their fields
If the takeaway for this dude who is there is that
Play we can handle this mean it is
I think of word for it
And I know they would find it very sacrilegious for me to describe it as such but
It's a little bit like a writer's room for how are we going to deal with this
How much of a workshop World talk about ideas like how do we feel about this
Like a they have the priest
Paraphernalia discovery
It's not God pretty
From lasers
Hugo based on the headline that's the way you could report the story
If you read into what is actually going on
It's about preparing for alien discovery
Societal implications
Also Project Blue beam isn't a real thing
It was a wacky conspiracy theory a dude named Serge monast popular lies back in the 90s
What you probably crib from some stories written by Jean rotten
I like this game that we're playing though I was active
It's very it's a great game like it would make me feel good you get that nice little bit of
Endorphin rush just like that I'm right again and it's fascinating that like at the end of it he probably is like
Damn it I was efficient today
Productive I read so many had lied you really would have to be a narcissist to enjoy the
That though
Because it's a kind of like that Twilight Zone episode where if you always win at gambling
It's boring
Only if you're a narcissist and you always win at being right
It never stops being fun
I don't think I look that much
You might be having a bad time
Possible ready for another stack yeah
Get out of here
Anomaly on Twitter
Exercise
Was it a screenshot or did he type it out
That's what I wouldn't know was a screenshot
10 point Arial font
Screenshot he probably black and white highlighter
Somewhere omigod
God this is dumb one of those
What a terrible idea
Treating the top articles
One of the future this is it
Interesting story and it's definitely a headline Alex can use to rinse out all sorts of nonsense but
Especially not his nightmarish is the headline mites
Suggest
There's a program in China if it's been trained to use an over 17,000
Some cases to be able to take a description of a particular case
And determine if it fits the requirements of a specific crime
Currently it's only able to recognize the eight most common crimes that occur in
Shanghai
But obviously overtime as technology progresses you'd expect that number to go up
The Project Lead scientist Professor shiyang was clear that the AI doesn't take part in any of the actual decision
About whether or not to file charges or come up with sentences
That's all done by humans
It's cuz I process
Goes into those sorts of determination
Far more complicated
Did the capability to do
Their reason
To be concerned about the possible ways this
Could go wrong but Alex's coverage
Weigh-off
And it's generous for me to even call this coverage
If you don't go into any detail about this
Read the headline at make
Shut up
Constantly this is this is a little bit like
Everyone if all the varsity varsity
The next level players are all out
They at they're all out sick
It's like it's like an angry person who's not good at improv right
Don't understand
Top article out of each.
Let's continue
Winterdays
Headline
Infowars.com
Who warns of global Healthcare collapse that they triggered with covid hysteria mean
Wild Bill Gates and fellow blue blood
Anderson Cooper
Promote
Social security for Americans
Who refused the deadly gene therapy injections
Broadcast
That's not party headlines
Expose the latest
Covid-19 developments including the fact
93% of people who died
One of the stacks was a tweet
This stack
The printout of the Infowars page
It has an embedded video of the show that Alex is
Currently recording
Yeah
What is going on I don't know
Such a waste of paper
I do like how we move the goalposts
From I'm going to read all these texts to I'm reading the top one of each of these decks
When I was with comes back he has
What's the what you know what the most
Important
Sing it
This critical
You need to understand
Cogitate to reflect
To really
Assess
I've everything I've got her in front of me
Just because you don't want to miss the forest for the trees
Problem is not Klaus Schwab
He's not Bill Gates
Our problem is not Ted Turner
Or George Soros
Problem
He's not even Donald Trump
The problem is not
Give six morgue
Problem is
Because we're not
Making the people that are on the fence that we've elected to be our Representatives
Our Guardians
Damn jobs
Yes
It is your fault
You have not convince people of the dumb premises
You got it help solutely
Don't give a s*** about you
Google's everything you say is a lie or manipulation right
Yes you have failed to convince
A large portion of the public
And
The elected leaders
That you think have your back
Who are using you for an easy voting
I think he's learning the wrong
Should I double down
It's actually I think the lesson that he's getting
2 is
Christmas miracle
Does not give a s***
About his warnings
Is a Christmas miracle
Compass give a s***
I think Alex is just trying to adjust his expectations
Move things over to Rand Paul a little bit
He knows gene therapy
And he still
Not attacking was shot he just said hey instead of saying the shot
People really need vitamins vitamin D
It really a hundred percent
Grandpa's not doing that and so
About this this morning about 5 a.m.
Then I thought
Super smart
He knows damn well what's going on so
Let me say this
I said Trump's either super ignorant or one of the most evil man to ever live do this to his own people
He's lying to himself
Regardless
No I don't want to break his ribs I don't want to shoot at him like a Democrat does
For president someday
But whatever calculus he's got
Masses going on his head
So
I want to apologize to President Trump
Oh God
Yeah I just get the Santa's like alright
This Joe Rogan treatment for Trump isn't going to work
Maybe I can bully rampaul
It's like a halftime show to basketball game where there like okay
You win $1000000 if you can make this half court shot you miss it okay you win
$50 if you can make this three-point shot
You miss it okay you win you win $5 if you make this free throw you know what else it's like
Setting up to read all the headlines
About 54 president
Didn't work I'm going to go ahead and
Talk to you about Rand Paul
Derek from my grocery store will not condemn the vaccines
Serious problem from the grocery store has
Quite a bit of sway
Wrong Derek from the grocery store he's going to cut your meat too thick at the deli
People cannot have that the manager that groceries
He's great power
He's a great guy so Alex
This talking about like this this like alright maybe we should do at a game
You make some metaphor
It's weird
Compares
The
Bullying
The politician
We're getting these politicians to fight the globalist for
Haha is similar
2 when he was a kid that someone stole his bike
His dad going over to talk to that kid's dad
Okay so your
You're telling me
That he's boiling
Global politics down to my dad could beat up your
Bingo
How do we stop this how do we
Focus on Biden the puppet we focus on Bill Gates what's he done
Go after
If I was 67 years old
Bully from down the street was like 14
Michael wake me off of it
Why are you telling a story
Real quick we got to recognize this started as a hypothetical acknowledgement
It happened very well be like if this happened
And my dad just said
You're going to give me that bike right now
Listen.
Point was is that
This is basically
Exactly what you would expect in terms of Alex's belief of his relation
Itule battles
Fight for him
I mean that's that's kind of an apt way to describe any
Desire for a paternalistic
God-king I wanted Daddy
Think it's exactly how I do think there's something to be said for pressuring elected leaders
Do
Policy sets that are more in line with
Know what you'd help and I mean a good example of that Jen sake comes out and it's like f*** you will never send you a test and then
Couple weeks later they like okay fine we're going to send you a bunch of tests
Sorry it turns out we sounded like they assholes
Yeah there's there's public
Pressure that you can make theirs
Do you know
Around yourself
Primary somebody already
There are things that are much more
Productive productive
Mature relationships
With our childish
Sonship with
Elected leaders NFL
And how Alex
Cease all these pieces fitting together
That's not surprised
It's just
Weird that he articulates it this way
Whereas
He describes our elected leaders similar to father
I see our elected leaders as being a bunch of patches
Children with a lot of money arguing with each other about stuff that doesn't matter
Well they watch us die
I think that you're closer
Maybe not not full on but
Alex's decided
Rand Paul maybe is a better Target
Doesn't mean
Not going to still try and
I get that juice out of trouble
He doesn't know what's going on
Attention
Megan from Rochester
You know what I'm going to do
Not bad guy
What he's doing he's surrounded by bad advisors
He's got that
Multimillion-dollar social media network based on Mastodon
SEC network
What was the successful businessman
This is weird
Started with him saying we need to move on from Trump state of doing that he's like I want to get his attention by talking
Shiting dishing dirt
Way to move on from Trump would be to reveal all of the s*** they
That you've already known about him for the years that you've been lying about
Anything meaningful said he could repeal
Probably not grifter for the past our entire lives
Cuz they don't get their way
The news about the SEC looking into Trump social media Venture broke about like a
Like a month ago Outlets
All over the place
Seem like as counters
I guess next out in the show will see if Alex building T but
Spoiler alert
That's not the
Weak attempt at the Rogan treatment it's
Not going to work
Like Alex take your own advice move on
I think bullying Paul's a great idea
He seems like a worm I love bullying Grandpa
Burlington roll over and show you his belly all the time
It was on your show like 100 f****** time
Move on from dropping at
When on vacation
A picture taken of him and Alex wants to talk about that
Mary is vacationing
In his native state
And hanging his wife with a dog wearing mask alone on the beach
Totally to create fear
Hysteria
Solutely
But things are so dangerous
President of the United States
Beachfront property
With his new German Shepherd puppy they killed the last one
Po-boy
Breathe the air
Alex's referring Biden's dog champ there who died back in June
I think Alex might need to substantiate the claim that biking killed his dog for a particularly considering the champ was 12 years old which is
No typically on the high end of normal dog lifespan
Sphere pictures of Biden wearing a mask don't rank anywhere near what Alex does everyday
Plus you have to understand how this is a rigged game
The mask and Alex can say it's a dishonest photo-op meant to Sprint
Spread
Fighting doesn't wear the mask and Alex
I can say it's a
Example of liberal hypocrisy
How do you have to wear the mask but Lord Biden does
Games where it's at
Doesn't matter
Meaningless
There's no like
There's no compromise
Which it seems should have been very obvious in so many other avenues as well
We had likes a negotiating over a bill with Republican
Kids whenever you obviously know they're all going to vote no on it any
Anyways
Statement of we will do nothing
I will
Never ever sit a Supreme Court Justice
During the final year of a present
Did everybody knows it out with people who have explicitly made it clear they have no interest in negotiating
Naro
And engagement
It's fairly similar
That's going to go into effect
Guarding the Border
Ranbaxy
Really whiffs
On this one
Illegal
Not the migrants but anybody
Aussie
See how that works
Is a great example of how stupid Alex is and how his laziness Translate
If you just read the headline of this article you might come away with some of the conclusions Alex comes to
You need to be super xenophobic bigot and you'd still have to make up a few details but this is within the realm of imagination if you donate
Play look at the
The policy of the article at all
From u.s. News & World Report article on policy
The rules pertaining to non us measure
American citizens and permanent residents may still enter the US
Regardless of their vaccination status
Alex legitimately and literally lied
Making up that US citizens
Doing so helps him create a feeling of animosity in his audience towards Emig
Becomes even more flagrant as an instance of misreporting when you realize that this is a month old story
He's at
Plenty of time to hear about it look into it
Get the details down particularly considering I was about 10 hours of research a day
Also
Shooting in October 2021 the CDC and the state department announced new guidelines
Require all immigrant Visa applicants to receive a full covid-19 vaccine series
As part of the medical exam prior to being issued a Visa
The guidelines specifically say that if a Visa applicant refuses to get vaccinated they are quote inadmissible to the United
Midstates
Most of the undocumented immigrants in the country or people have overstayed their visas and even if there were black mostly folks
Sneaking into the country a rule that they needed to be vaccinated would be totally meaningless and unenforceable
What's mean expressed here is Alex's laziness willingness
The lie and his blanket hatred of immigrants
Nothing meaningful here at all
No
Just bigotry
Let's just talk a little bigotry in their otherwise people won't kind of get that
Vibe you know
How to make sure you're just reading through bunch of stacks you don't really have the opportunity to wax on bigotry
Away from the exactly so you got to find a way to slam it in there
So we lost a Harry Reid recently react
Okay love you a lot of different feelings about Harry Reid and that's not not a conversation we need to get into at this point
But Alex has a
The weird kind of insulting eulogy
Okay
To become
And all for just money and power in the system
You know Harry Reid very corrupt evil Chinese Asian
Okay
She could have been a real human
Very very very very very
Is it
Let me get these articles right now
What just happened
So weird
I think like I understand like dancing on a grave
If you're Alex
I kind of also understand being like what a loss
Is a Statesman
You know I can understand that response to
It's very difficult is what Alex just did like what a shame he's dead we could have been a human
But he was a Chinese spy
Who's died
What
I don't know
What I was very confused okay
So Alex
Has Steve Kerr Sean for the last hour mostly talk about this
Substack post that he has
That is full of s***
Royal isn't much of it there's only a few clips
It's dumb
Here's Alex's introduction
Computer science engineer shop multimillion-dollar
Subject
Huge huge article
We also posted infowars.com pathology results show
93% of people
Who died after being killed by the vaccine
So I'm flabbergasted
Because the underlying document here is
4 pages long and honestly it's really a bar like three in terms of actual text
The video presentation
Babies LinkedIn the article is
15 minutes long and a half
You know
Break I guess
Also because it's funny I want to point out the
First sentence in the video presentation that's linked to this non study is quote
I want to say first of all that we must not quibble about details
Alright let's not get bogged down with all the facts or whatever
Picture might be America perfect opening her presentation
Elderly devoid of detail
In any case if you
Curious there is no data presented in
Video
This is Akin
Completely meaningless thing I could be ignored out of
Until actual concrete evidences provided it by that I mean that I'm going to quibble about the details
You're not supposed to do
Yes I'll I think the reason for that is if
Equivalent method
Details
The details would look real dumb
This is
That's clip and they're talking about
Robert Malone
Just got a part of Alex's Christmas
Message
He
Apparently has been booked on Rogan great
Great great great great first talk about that occurs
Robert Malone
Because of what's happening is on a plane right now to Austin
Are not going to work so very very exciting
Excited
You know it's
Closes when he gets removed from Twitter another door opens which is
He's going to be unbroken and
And the people that I work with instrumental
In making that
On Ruby
Extraordinary
And
If we can get Robert
On on Rogan
I think that'll bring the house down
Who's the great incentive Rogan getting deeper and deeper
When do the world of anti-vax propaganda ultimately lead to a ton of people in his audience being hurt and possibly dying
To the tragedy to see how irresponsible he's being
With his platform is going to be on
Wichita's appear that he is
Junior on
Holyshit
What's the thieves claimed that he was instrumental in getting ballon booked on Rogan show that's probably true
Buckland Bret Weinstein was going really hard in the Ivermectin game
In June of this year
He didn't episode of his podcast Dark Horse titled how to save the world in
Three easy steps
The guest on that episode where Steve Kirsch and Robert Malone
Just after they recorded that episode Brett was a guest on Rogan's podcast along with doctor
A quarry
The founder of the anti-vaccine pro Ivermectin group the Frontline covid-19 critical Caroline
It's within the realm of believability that Brett set up that booking
Ain't given that Malone and curse word Gaston on brat show
Spreading vaccine misinformation I can believe
EBay baby open to getting
On the larger platform getting them up onto the big leagues if you're welcome
There's a subtle network of s*** heads that are desperately trying to court Rogan to utilizes platforms
Accordingly
Zestful according really throw to go along with it
Wow looking over the guest list
Ava Rogan for the past couple months
It heads
Shapiro Alex Berenson
Steven Pinker
I would think that Alex would be really concerned with his friend Joe buddying up with someone with such clear ties to Epstein
But I guess that's only a problem when he wants it
Anyway
Yeah I
Find this
Awful I think it's
Really really great
That
When you give somebody a hundred million dollars
They almost invariably turn into a right-wing show
Yeah
I think that's great I do wonder if this is kind of like
Performance art piece
Where's Joey
Trying to see what
He can do without them cancelling the deal how can I burn
A hundred million dollars like the fuc
Joker
I mean I think even without that hundred million dollars is perfectly set
You know like for life
Why not trying like see how far you
Can go before
Demodex
You got it we got to cancel it
At the same time
Heads on
He's
Clearly
Dabbling
Deeper and deeper into vaccine misinformation
Robert Malone on
I'm getting won't have our
Likes back on
You got to ask yourself
Well little bit of a question
If you're Alex
Maybe it's time to Sneaky Snake if I want to go back
Twelve-year-old me
Watching Newsradio on A&E
At 4 in the afternoon
Hey guess what
See that dumb guy
He's going to ruin the world
The whole world not just newsradio's world yeah it's weird for me too because I think one of my first
Interact
Actions with Rogan
Wasn't Newsradio cuz maybe
Didn't realize that with school he was
I wasn't aware of him as a comedian or anything
I think the first time he came into my periphery was when he was a guest on Loveline
Pretty Charming Gaston Loveline is pretty funny
To look back on that it's like wow him and Adam Carolla both both really really fell off
Dr. Drew
Awful I am starting to think that you should not give white men a s*** ton of money
Hey
I don't want to think anymore about Loveline
Don't do it
The guestlist is going to start looking a lot like Road into the past few months
I broke it
It's true now if they're not all crazy it's no
Sia anyway we come to the end of this and how is good as caught up
I know I know people who've been on Rogan
I mean it's just banana
Laura B
Anybody else that we might borrow
Red was on was
Chris
I don't know baby
Impossible
Realm of availability
Elon Musk
Otherwise we'll be back Jordan but until then we have
We do it's knowledge right.com
Next year
Siam
Let me down on team human baby
And now here comes
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color