Air Jordan
Pray I have great respect for knowledge but now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
Jordans
Jordan is I
I wasn't never I have witnessed
2 as a
It's something that exists in the culture
It's a rat and it's got electric I remember gotta catch em all being something that people yell out of time
But I've never played any iteration of it
Giving it a shot. So far I'm a little ways in his name
I'm all of my Pokemon
After Infowars personalities
And it's been going great
Because I basically I'm trying to find what would you mind me
Sure sure sure sure we've got there's a bug like a cockroach kind of Pokemon
Want that Steve pieczenik never goes away
You can get rid of it cannot get rid of them
We've got a type
Yai
Perfect texted me that very very proud of yourself and I was like yeah
And then there's I found one
Mud murkrow a problem
Sounds right
I know them but I want Hillary Hillary I'm enjoying the
A little too much this aspect of the game that isn't even part of the game I did this on stardew Valley
Animals After
It would lead to some really funny things like my cow is named David Knight
Can you pick up milk David night right now
You've already milked him for what he's worth
All right sooner that's my ride. What do I do
My bracelet Dan is I finally saw a Joyride
Which is a special that Bobcat Goldthwait
After they were in a tragic car accident
They're really f***** him up
They were about to go on this little tour then they got into an accident and now they finally finished it
And it's just great
It's just really great to very very funny guys
Sure it's nice to see them I mean it's a
Weird cuz I've I've worked with both of them to which
Would be a name drop if they weren't so utterly irrelevant to the culture at large you know it's still a bit of a Dream Drop
Ears out from everybody knowing
A little bit of a
Hard name-dropping a specific immunity
One that doesn't accept me anymore
It's good to see a possum
Today we ever episode go over and I got to be honest this was one of the most Rocky epi
Episodes I've heard in a long time ago
Rocky rocky road
It's
RockYou is moose and squirrel
Boris and Natasha are fighting
Nugget Bullwinkle's here
This is a mess
I'm very excited about it
We are now in 2020 to figure out something to do with it
The year but this is one last time
Coming a mile away a 31st
Who's been coming at me in the rearview mirror
One Last Ride. December 31st
And we'll get to that here before we do that's like little moments say hello to the Milwaukee
The first Liz Fortin thank you so much you're now probably walk
Stenographer for the courts of Heaven thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Skinny fists like 5G Towers to Heaven thank you so much you're now Apollo
To references to heaven now that one's to godspeed You black Emperor
Are the Heavenly boba
Next to Eva who is personally cremated Care thank you so much
I got to assume that means that they've been to Bohemian Grove
Club member in the audience
Senior citizen thank you so much you are now technocrat
And congratulations Kyle and Sarah on your engagement Love Christian thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Heroin
So good
Is freakishly large
Thank you very much wanted to do during this I wanted to start 2022 off with something kinda special
Like I wanted to do a project Camelot episode or
Jim Bakker I realize that's the recent Wars we're going to kick it down the road at although I do have a bunch of it
Tired
I feel wanted space craziness or
Learning more about the courts of Heaven like unreal
Your loved ones
Dude I are the
Cloud of witnesses in the court of Heaven I love it I Murphy
Eventually we're just going to get into like what the actual Tears Of Heaven in the courts yet
The u.s. marshals of the Courts of Heaven
They serve you with subpoenas
Fishing in a dry well there wasn't really much
Defiant and so
I've decided
Last day of the year Alex's kind of
Usually
You know in some kind of mood or yeah he's reflecting on something and throwing something that
Will be reflected back
So I decided to do that and here is an out-of-context drop from Today Show
Appreciate your call
Oh boy alright okay okay the beginning or the end of the show Uno's
Here's one more out of compass
Altru
A real hard
Touches the soul
Not on coke wow
Wow
Irene
You know that's deep
That's just Steve giving someone art
Is guarding someone
That's what he said
We start here on the 31st and here's where Alex is at
That shed yesterday I I told you that I was unable to sleep
At about 2 hours sleep
Very emotional yesterday
Talk about quitting and not doing the show
So I didn't go cane
Seriously
But also wasn't being dramatic
Doesn't feel right
To just come on.
Like you're calling a football game or baseball game this is
Really emotional for me
Devastate
Absolutely devastating
I almost did it yesterday
Come to the decision I'm going to share it on here
1 or whether it's going to be
Next week but
A lot of stuff you need to know about I mean
Wait till you hear this
All right look
I don't know what these big things are and I don't give a fuk
Because
You know what you said but yesterday you were all emotional and you were going to quit so we're going to 30
Because I
It's almost another apology before the day before
I want to access this based on the standard of what do you think
I was just saying that he didn't actually sincerely mean he was going to quit
And he wasn't being
Simultaneously both of those cannot be true
So anyway here's where we start
On December 30th
Okay let me really just start
Broadcast
From this perspective
I went to bed
Last night
115 the morning and never went
Sleep
The day
I was just so upset about the population going on
We made it come true except
Or slower
They're not 10 years behind
Meditating focusing researching in my mind thinking
I just feel overwhelmed
I f****** love that turn of phrase I didn't know you could
Just call thinking researching in your mind
I was doing some research I was cogitating good by that I mean researching of my mind
Cogitating literally being like
Not for nothing like Alex might have had a bad sleep night but
3 hours
I guess not good
It'll probably be dragging the next day will like
I'm somebody who's had insomnia for the better part of my life
Call that not sleeping can kill you
No
But
I don't know I don't
It doesn't seem like a good enough excuse for something that you need to apologize for any
Blame it on your show as a professional Broad
Castor
I know more about his sleep cycle than I do any topic that he's covering
You realize that I know so much about how well this man is sleeping on any given night I think you know more about like you
Bizarre like
Just the picadillos of his emotional states to
Yeah it's really think there's more
Granular detail about that.
Quite frankly
This is Edward Murrow cat I don't really know what the news is like
Sleep well that's all I remember from him
Frankie clock really should have been something cuz you're going to bed
Goodnight to you good luck to me
When Alex was not sleeping
You did some
They're researching it is mine
Did some praying
And if you listen closely it sounds like God was bullying him
Meditating focusing researching in my mind thinking
By the Holy Spirit
On my knees and start praying on the floor
Do you need
To get on your knees and put
Put your head on the ground
Our
Find God
And it was literally God just saying
We're going to have to go out
You're going to have to get focused and be a real man
Fun doing this you joke around too much you screw around yeah
Yeah
Play half-measures
So yeah God apparently
Is telling him to get it together
Is two seconds away from turning him into the Son of Sam killer right like we're there
I think this is a real emotional images of when he's failed
Theoretically God saved him imagine this is a real communication with a deity like
Hey dude
Look at this look at what I did for you for you you're not doing you're not holding up your end of the bargain
Saving you in situations where totally you don't deserve
To be safe and you have made a deal with me in order for me to give you blessings right you know like hell right
Nothing at all like the devil whatsoever are you and I am God
For sure yeah I think this is this is an unhealthy
But at least
What
God is presumably
We telling Alec news get your s*** together and write your job seriously
I know God but I would say maybe you should be a little more serious about the stuff you do
Ways God specifically saying that you shouldn't be mad at
The Crewcuts
Is it your fault
We've never met at the court that you need to understand
Starts rambling a bit about how
You know people who get hurt by the vaccine
You know
Themselves
They're not going you're going to get mad at people like Al
Because they were right all along
And that they'll have to try and rationalize somehow that they were actually right
This is kind of what Trump is doing I was going to say
Most of those people will fight
Analyze
Convince themselves
That what they did was right
He was cutting off the fentanyl coming in
Got us out of the WHL he did so many great things
And then he wants you to, yelling so it as operation warp speed
England a year here
We have hundreds of thousands dead we know of millions maimed
About all the people I know
Or died
Supposedly
Bosch
But the really as I said yesterday
Really mad
Who's medical doctor
Who still hasn't come out
This is strong strategy on Alex's bar
Trump does not give us
Nope but you might be able to believe Grandpa possible
King of expectations
Let's leave Trump alone f*** it there's nothing we're going to gain their
Now Rand Paul is a doctor let's scream at him
What you should do is call him and be like
Don't you remember whenever I supported you here and don't you remember whenever I supported you here and don't you remember when I supported you here if you're not holding
Look up your end of the bargain is generational
Going out back and back
When I when he was running for president and there was only one set of footprints
That's what I was carrying him
Picked up this isn't going to work
Either
Know this point
But it's a
It's a better move than trying to keep
Going with drop because Trump obviously doesn't give a s***
He wasn't The Apprentice
No no
He wasn't a lifetime famous person
Clear to me I think that Alex is only shot
At getting somebody
To take care of
I guess
Seriously or to communicate with him
Is to go on Rogan first and then get that kind of level of
Bulshit out there and since he's clearly not going on Rogan again
It's just been left behind by these people
Quantum anymore
I don't think many people do
Jimmy Dore
Rachel Maddow
What the f*** happened I don't know well I don't think I don't think there was ever that great.
He's a piece of s*** but
I don't think that Alex realizes that when people
Say stuff like this
They're not saying something positive about him they're attacking Rachel Maddow by comparing her
You're so shity you're worse than Alex
Probably doesn't feel great
No publicity is bad publicity
Construe
So anyway we had to get to the news
Oh wait we do
What
But I want to talk about philosophy
Tale of two people
Private person becomes my friends and people that I know where they just be a common person or very famous person
Absolutely not
Absolutely not you brag and put all their celebrity for the album non-stop absolute non-stop Bragg
Stop talking about
Let me back in the earlier times it was like Dave Mustaine
There's his wife's tennis coach that guys up there too
I don't think the tennis partner and Alex are friends
There's a reporter
So yeah we got people already know it's Tucker
Joe Rogan
Charlie Sheen and Christopher Walken
That's for sure not anymore
To be fair
Christopher Walken was never all that interested without doing
He was just
Cooking with Richard Belzer
He was accidentally all the show
But I'm going to go ahead and
Give me an example of two people that I know
Immigration with him Young
So much over the years
Falling I'll be that issues has been smoking
A year
15 times a year
But
Thanks for that background
Tale of two people
You got
Understand those three types you understand
Explain
Something is very important because
But broadcast I don't think I'm making it Crystal Clear like it is in my mind I want you to real
Wrap your brain around that I do most of you already have
We got a paradox gallon
Lookout
I
I hear Alex saying that like
I'm not being understood when I talk about these things
And so I will try to clarify it in a way that's
You know accepting of something being
Paradox of confusing no idea what he's trying to introduce
Are there are aspects
Tucker
And Rogan
That if you understand the difference
What is between them
It somehow Illuminating
But then he threw himself in there too
I loved that moment because
In that moment you just you can see it all you're just like
There's no way he cannot be the most important part of the Story 2
Who are not me
What that can't happen
There's also me it's pretty obvious
This the tale of two people
He's about how similar or different they are to Alex
And also spoiler alert entity shows up later
Globalist
Now what I'm going to do is tell you how great
These people are
But what I'm also doing is tell you why it telling you why they're not perfect
And why I am
The places that makes them different for me or false
Similar to me are good well I will get to eventually is that Tucker has one string could we
One weakness and Alex just has both.
I knew it was going to be that
What does paradox
I don't know if it's a paradoxica
Paradoxical
Both
Paradox
Logan
Completely happy on cloud nine
He's hot
I've got a hundred million dollars
Go ahead drama
And
He is
Waking up to what's really happening in the world
But it's not really sunk into him
How dystopic it's going to get
Worse from here
He organizes
Obelisk
A whole nother level
Very happy person
Mad about the shots he knows our poisonous he's trying to figure out is by Design
Then there's Tucker Carlson
I love seeing the left constantly fetishize oh my God he's going to run for president all he's a little Pub
What
Are we doing that
Carlson wants
Nothing to do with the presidency
Grew up around it
His dad ran a major federal agency
Tucker Carlson
Wants to live in the woods in Maine
What what are we talkin about
I don't know what I still don't understand exactly what they like it if you just listening to this sequentially what is the paradox
What are we talkin about
Alright so
Know some stuff but he's not fully awake
Cuz he doesn't realize that he needs to radicalize his audience and create essentially a Bro Army
Royal Tucker Carlson does know all of
Everything and wants to live in the shack
Inmate right
And that's a paradox
It's confusing
That's not what a paradox paradoxes are confusing feel like they're that confusing I think they're more of just a conundrum in
Unsolvable problem if we looked up conundrum of
100% realize that after I said it
Best is Alex can lay out what the
The Paradox is
Carlson
Carlson gypsy
What does scalping
He's all the way away
As much as he can on Fox News
Paradox
He's more awake than Joe Rogan
But he doesn't have the complete freedom
That's not a paradox
That's not the right word now those are things that are like self-contradictory but also kind of true
Play the classic example is like someone saying this sentence is false
If that's correct in the sentence
But it's also true
If it's incorrect
Be true and that means it's false
It's circular and creates paradox
There are other varieties Paradox of the garage thought experiment know what Alex's describing is not paradoxical
It's really more kind of
Bad luck
It's kind of ironic in the sense of the word that Alanis Morissette use
Squeeze the far is it not
Right
It's really less of paradox and more of an excuse for Alex to use for why these people who are supposedly is complete allies
Doing exactly what he's doing
We're saying the same stuff
Joe is entirely free and could say all that stuff but he's not awake enough
Keeping his job at Fox
That's fun but it also makes no sense in its total b*******
Joe is not entirely free as evidence
By him being forced
To take down as episodes of people like Stefan molyneux in order to get that hundred million dollar contract with Spotify
Tucker was fully awake and knew the world was exactly as Alex
Describe saving his job at Foxwood mean exactly 02
He was born Philthy Rich so he doesn't need the money
Any good migrated is audience somewhere else
Suffuse being censored in any meaningful way on Fox
None of this is
Connected to reality
It's not a parrot
Yeah I like his description of Tucker's
Evolution just because it also reminds me of like a worm
Crawling towards
Detention
20 years ago Tucker Carlson didn't get any attention unless he hated me
10 years ago you got some attention for liking makes
And now that he's me gets all the attention
Call me think about it 20 years ago if Tucker was even like a relevant figure he would have been a bow tie
Who is towing a very like hawkish
Conservative line and Alex was saying 9/11 was an inside job
Cross-purpose exactly
I'm years ago the tea party was on the rise and people like Alex maybe had a little bit more
Maybe you're in touch with the kind of audiences I
Realizing I'm going to need to reach
And now everything is Thunderdome so
So Alex gets talking about to his own
Life
How is that parrot
Well this is actually a paradox
But it's contradictory for sure
I grew up
Around people that know the world really worked and never even thought of it as an issue
I grew up knowing all this
10-years old
I was already
There
I get a family as much as John Birch
Doesn't match up with the rest of his
Supposed timeline
Like where you at
Satanist
Yeah if you did
Completely comprehend how the world works
210 how is it that you
She turned into like a sickness lover
16 somewhere around there mean that you understood what you were doing this was not being tricked into say
Satanism this was you making
Getting some sort of deal with the Devil
One that could perhaps
I don't know
Echo throughout your entire life to the point where several
Might might come to a head
Possibly
Do we get another Paradox okay not a paradise
Weird mistake with your other having fun everything's right were telling jokes
He's just so happy
We may not be able to turn this back
This is the great reset takeover depopulation event
Paradox
Publisher going to turn into a starving horde
And they're planning on the in-game to make us join them just so we survive
Again that is not a
No
I'm really struggling with how often we're use it towards paradoxes having 20 idea it's not going to stop either
Locksmith
Nicely done
Yeah
This is
Silly I do like really happy
Yes yeah
He gets to
Get really high and drunk with weirdos for a living
What why wouldn't he be happy happy making
And then Tucker when you get to steak with Alex
He realizes that he
You getting a steak with Alex that sucks
Scott you'd kind of miserable always have your head on a swivel maternal going to cause a problem now
Alex
Is it
State Warriors wrestling if
Maybe he's been wrong
This whole time
Yeah
Yeah Jones you picked the wrong team
You'll be begging for help soon you'll see
Population will destroy you for trying to help
All the top people
Put me in that position
And then I ask myself
Am I wrong
Front
Should we go ahead
Satan
And
Killed majority of the population
Do that plant has the population
Doesn't care about themselves or children
Okay
All these other people decided to join it
I'm not going to join it is
They're so miserable there so
Empties are not their own men and women
And spiritually
Worse than a thousand deaths
God chose a bad representative here this is this is not
Good dude miserable too so it's like there's no real Big Dipper
I hear this
Clip and I really just think that it's Alex trying to make him sound like he's an awesome person to the audience
Screening is fictional author of a life of luxury that he's turned down no.
Protective people
Yes of course
Complete nonsense also really important to Alex and speaks up with Satan to kill
Lost most of the population is because the people who are on the team of Satan they seem unhappy
It's inherently wrong to commit genocide
It's the devil has low workplace morale
Because personally that would be uncomfortable
It's not even that it's those people look bummed out even though he cares about them
It's because he would personally not want to feel as though
The way that he appear to have well that's true but
At the same time
I don't really feel like if you look at Alex
Did he look
Looks like he's enjoying
She had all that much honey kind of Express
Everybody in announces estimation should probably act more like
Joe and get 100 million dollars and just get high all the time why doesn't everybody just do that
Seems like an easy out Alex doesn't seem to be enjoying s*** all that much anymore
Larger
Just altaf what I'm trying articulator one trying to get at
But it really is this
I need to be able to enjoy my life
Function
Global assistance
You better wake up
Going to slowly tortured to death
Alright I think you should enjoy your life a little more
Someone is not enjoying their life too much lashing out angrily
Yeah I think he's looking at the problem from the wrong direction
You better enjoy your life more first
And then talk.
Werlor earlier we heard Alex at a teasing around this idea that maybe we should
Stick at the Rand Paul
Right because Trump doesn't give
Give a s***
Text Elise
And he continues on this line like maybe maybe it's time to
Really f****** go at Grandpa
Republicans take over the House and Senate
You pushed
Telling people that dangerous
What the Hitler mustache on Rand Paul
Studies all day
Pressure
Call Sheldon
It's also a dumb dumb way to pressure people
Why putting a Hitler mustache on them
Turn of phrase is that something the people
How to put the Hitler mustache so I think he's literally saying let's gets
Some pictures of Rand Paul and then draw a little Hitler mustaches on their and I assume mail them to us heard Hitler mustache
Onramp all contacts
I just think there's probably more effective ways of pressuring
Leaders who you think
Maybe willing
To help
You sure I also think that maybe in terms of Rand Paul it'd be best if people in Kentucky
Put that pressure would be a good idea cuz we don't think about representative
Crazy like this anymore but theoretically
No standing to put Hitler mustache
Scott Maybe
New
Rand Paul
So we need to get desperate that's the thing
That's Alex's desperate times call for desperate real
GE quote something bizarre okay just saw this
This quote like on a meme or something like that really excited
Responsibility
The children to expose these people
Go out to the clinic
Hold up
Wepa sister bringing a medical Tyrion 24 stats
Consenting children
Samurai is desperateness
10 man on war cannot kill such a man
If one uses discrimination he will fall behind
One needs M loyalty nor devotion
Loyalty and devotion art of themselves
Within desperation
I mean
Desperate man
I should be desperate
Pure Evil
At least I know what I'm fighting
Yeah he's quoting they hagakure a little surprise
That's either Forest Whitaker
You quoting the hagakure what is happening Alex is trying to live The Way of the Samurai
What is the samurai that was a hyper nationalistic book written to say that you don't romanticize the Japanese
Literally happened in order to get people to start wars that's what he's about is about
F****** with them you got to kill people on Fast shadow
Yeah
I found that to be a
Drain pool
I don't know if I've ever heard him quotes
But yeah I think he's just
I think it's really wouldn't like the parts about making sure that you are beautiful making sure that you always have me
Makeup there's a elderly available
In there you would probably should get you with
I think that
This is
Problematic in a certain way because he's at answering this idea of getting desperate
Protesting
At places like
I don't know vaccinations
And I don't believe that his audience would
Desperately educate people know
Ethos that drives a good harass
Harangue
But you just like
Pick
Pic not regular phone
Just leave regular folk out of this man you want to go after
Fauci
Find fauci
Video
The game is sustainable like when Alex is yelling about David Rock
Gfeller Hillary and Obama
It's a sustainable
Propaganda sphere but yeah
It's really impacting
Normal
People trying to live their lives
It becomes an issue don't make everybody a pain in your weird psychodrama
You know if you want to be screaming about almost
Goddamn fictional figures that you've created out of
Bulshit then fine but don't be like
Hey also
Doterra down the block needs to get her ass
Crew of people to like a community meeting or whatever it's like
Is this is bulshit
To look you I don't know if you know this
Deer in an earth suit right now
Okay
You have a spirit you have free will
You're just
God is going to separate you
From
Universe
You don't want to
Nothing's your very paradoxical
Today is not like what I do in the morning
It's paradoxical that you feel different in the morning and Aleve
I like the mixing of the grandiose language
Do you like sudo spirituality of like you're an eternal being in an earth suit
God will Smite you if you don't fight my enemies
A little it's a little bit much
Yeah let's just pull from
Tucking most death why not let's just throwing some fear not of been let you know what we're just pulling from everywhere we got the hog
Rakudai we got this b*******
Let's go for it
Alex is fighting these demons tales in with you being an eternal being in it
What have you
System
No laugh
When he talks about how he's fighting Dima
Little Green Manor Flying Saucer
I noticed the system doesn't laugh
Serious
And they've signed up for
And
Entering the New World Order is hurting children and hurting Humanity
Destroying
Our very future
How you get on board
With the Rockefeller program
That is not human
You think that's
Human
No right
10%
Everybody knows
Hundred percent as a walk-in that's easy easy that's the one that you're like oh so that's what a walk-in looks
Like a Rockefeller
Monica beetle
Little demons
We're regularly
I do think that the subject probably makes less headlines about him probably just because like
The media
Yeah
Videos fighting demons doesn't rank
Compared to the real world f*****-up things that Alex is involved in
News stories surrounding January 6th
All sorts of things are maybe more present
Whether or not he thinks he's fighting demons they are more pressing but I feel like
The biggest problem with those things is that were not always given the context
Two of the he's fighting demons far along with it would be nice if it was at least a little bit of a reminder
Demon fighter Alex Jones yeah I think I think it would give a little bit of
Flavor seasoning for those stories man who has not successfully slayed 1
Demon is his entire life Alex Jones you don't know that
I feel like he would have crowed non-stop about it if you refuse to listen to
Be true
So there's a there's a bit of demons out there
Obviously we know all that much about
No I think
Well obviously I know one thing that's
That I don't believe they exist
Sure that's a problem
I don't really know what they're like
Thankfully Alex comes in
With some details
There but they are
Not sure
Manipulate
Humans will work with them
We don't go around trying to do all the stuff
What
But they do
Seems to me that Alex's
It is saying
That they're Dumber but maybe older bride Ono
Yeah yeah there's a team
A specialist team but their craft
Label of tricks
And yeah
Without them
Without these demons right humans never lie and cheat at all really that's a real bummer
We should get rid of them
I think they're really f****** things up if that's
If Alex legitimately believe that and that wasn't just something that he randomly said or misspoke sure
That is a
Painfully naive
Way to look at the wall it's just a bummer
It's just a bummer not least of which because
Is God
What a shity life
What is city life every human being was
Consigned to upon birth
To just be like occasionally grabbed in the influence by
Demon
You didn't get the choose but at the same time every time you did anything bad it wasn't you
Motherfuker is a real a******
I think of narcissists usually take responsibility for things right
Last night Alex didn't sleep well but he also a thing cuz probably like before he went to bed
Commutative
They found one
Did you get her off and in my hate
Made me
Elaine Maxwell
Alex
Fresh Alex
Got up it
1:50 in the morning cuz I couldn't sleep
Oh my gosh
Federal judge with the defense team and the prosecutor
Suppress the black book
I'll pedophiles and they say they'll now be protected
Now is rewarding the judge
Teleport job with
Such a bizarre way to discuss this
The situation
Alex says the night before you needed a victory and wanted to feel good
They made a video talk about how the Maxwell verdict was a win but later he actually looked into it I realized it was bad news
News
This is pretty revealing inasmuch as it kind of shows that Alex is completely willing to put out reactions
The news items without looking into them at all
Specifically for the purpose of satisfying his emotional needs
That's pretty bad
Yeah yeah
That sucks no that's real if you have a responsibility to do and I would argue that you have a responsibility
Audience
That's not keeping up your head to the park and they should probably call you and say
Do you remember when we helped you hear do you remember when we helped almost like using the audience to satisfy those
Emotional needs
Information
Just because it feels good
A little bit different than what our two saying
He posted that video that was about the Maxwell vertic being a win because that was his immediate reaction to the news
By the next day he's online conspiracy World surrounding
And they believe that this was a cover
In order to make sure his messaging was in sync with the larger
Conspiracy World Alex changed
The talking points Alex is using hair crip directly from social media post spreading misinformation about the case
There wasn't sweeping ceiling of documents in fact the judge ordered it
Thought of it Beyond sealed
Including transcripts of depositions and bank records
What Alex is misrepresenting here is that the judge found the quote
Only certain pages for Maxwell's address book
Identifying victims with the word massage next to them
Could be mark
Into evidence
This was to protect the identity of the victim
Not to Shield any of the abuser
Also Schumer isn't making that judge Alison Nathan and appellate Judge Adams
Some kind of quid pro quo
The vacancy came up in the US court of appeals in the second district
And Schumer recommended this judge dividing the sun would make a good nominee
This makes sense given that Schumer is a senator from New York
Nathan serves on the United States disc
District court for the southern district of New York
And the US court of appeals for the second district
Covers New York Vermont
In Connecticut New York Mets
I want to find a Chase the conspiracy World instead of leading it
He came out to celebrating the Maxwell verdict because he assumed that was the right
Let me saw that everyone like Jack
Sobek was going the other way with it
They changed his opinion
You haven't looked in the case prior to deciding that it was a victory and he didn't look in
Intuit it all in order to change his mind
This is just a dude blowing in the wind it's nice
If you was real busy when he woke up at 1
Who's playing at Billy by God
To look at it to the Elaine Maxwell birthday
Amazing you know he's well over $14 for 20 hours a day just to
To make sure that he gives us high quality content what high-quality content to gives up its
It's so bad it's amazing and that's kind of a pair.
I'm looking for biting analysis of Maxwell verdict
Right cuz Alex's show
Can you come out and said it's a victory but then done so much research that you haven't figured out
Stuber
So obviously if he's done all that he's got a lot of information
There's got to be a ton of stuff that was covered up he wouldn't like I don't know spend a bunch of time
Doing a
Terrible attempt at a comedy bit
About how he
It's better the judge looks like a man
You wouldn't do that
Oh no oh does he ever oh no no
We don't need to make a big circus out of this
Anybody in the black book
In a bed
Has Judge
Mister Nathan
He's doing I'm sorry
Alison Nathan
Chucky Schumer
How many you got
Still going
Alison Nathan
Aftershows you defending Nation covering it happen
Yikes
That was not good
But it was clearly intended as like he was trying to be funny I guess like he thinks that he was trying to be funny
I think the idea of like stammering through something is enough for him
He's he's basically like on the level of of Bob Newhart with his stammer comedy
Who's good
USO tour
Reference The Young Turks there that unfortunately triggered something in his brain where he remembered
Bat in 2013
I did it
He would he would legalize bestiality where you're given pleasure to the animal
Do a loose conversation
Conversation
I don't think
Vapes
Necessarily he wanted saying he wanted to be a dictator or was he
Fully supporting having sex with animals
To give you back
Yeah yeah anyway Alex remembers this
And he has to spend a lot of time to Outback
Teddiursa go
By the way
The young turds leader
Nice
Fantasize about having sex with animals and pleasuring them
World
First thing that pops in your head and it not the hundred
First thing when you're dictator in the world is
Benevolent
Where your pleasuring the animal
I want to point out that this is supposed to be his coverage of the Maxwell trial that we were going to be speaking of
About anything other than philosophy or bestiality but apparently I'm wrong
Nothing on this Maxwell
But he's got to go this route
I want to have fun like you do too
No
No it's not
Complete
That he has sex with a man
He just talks about how much
If I was casting somebody
What
If I was going to
Cast somebody in a movie
Runza pet stores you can have sex with animals
Aquarium fish
Give me that
Come on if you had The Gaslight
Is that a farmer
Is that an auto mechanic
Is that a soldier
Is that a teacher
Is that a lawyer we had was pretty stunning
Is he a pedophile Nano no
Somebody
Did I sexually animals of course against
Something interface Theory
Something
Chiladas cold beer and Marilyn Monroe
Everyday of the week
What
He's over here
Farm animals
What the f*** is going on
Come on man that God was telling you.
Cheez-It
Yeah this is like
It's so transparent I don't want to talk about this subject that I haven't prepared for its much more
Fun for me to read about Janke
This is where we're going to go with his look at his mouth
Boy
This reminds me a little bit of I told you one of the things that I enjoy
Enjoy the Joyride
And what are the things that I love so much about Dana Gould is after having a 40 goddamn year career
In stand-up
His level of confidence in being funny on stage he can tell a five-minute story with no labs
So confident that he's going to get a laugh at the end you know
40 years of experience
I'm amazed metallic
Maintaining and
Obtaining that same level of confidence
Never having received a laugh
Does laughing
You can't tell ya ya recording send feedback
Jim Breuer
Sure Alex loves that Jim Breuer
Meat of the subject
Jones
Change this
Play Maxwell's little black book remain Secret
Needless
Name-dropping
We don't want to needlessly
Name-drop
Girls
The judge
Good person
I want to remember to do his homework
Blind kind of narratives with a body of the article explains the situation in a way that makes everything fall flat
But one thing the black book in question is the same one that Gawker published back
In 2015
Second being listed in this address book.
Not prove that you were involved with Maxwell and Epstein child abuse stuff
Conclusion for Alex to come to give them any other staunch belief and due process
Baby really hates people describing guilt-by-association when it involves him
Third as we've already mentioned the book contains identifying information about Victor
Doesn't making that public would really only hurts
The story at all in the independent article was published on December 4th
New article
Does nothing to do with the decision involved in Maxwell.
Conviction
It was just a matter of course for the trial
Alex is also ignoring another more recent independent article with the headline quote
Ghislaine Maxwell's little black book under FBI review says report
Authorities found to pursue anyone who committed a crime with Epstein & Maxwell
I was just reporting on these gun stories he's just reading dumb headlines from dumb blogs and social media post
Getting mad about them without doing any leg work at all
That's why he'd rather spend his time talking about Jake like
Cooler Fred what else is there to say with
The judgement other than like
Okay who's next
You know
Like that's what that's what I feel like everybody saying about the Maxwell judgment like yeah
She's getting
That now who
Feels like there is forward momentum with
Uppercase
There's a conviction
Everybody wants let's see what happens
Unless you want to just get pitchforks
You might
That's a conversation
Well you might mess up
Versation
Globalist
They want to suck children's energy out because children have this
Innocence and bacon
They can have that vacuum.
Has a really good one for that something
Maybe makes it more understand
Because everything is about
Assess
The Innocents energy
Crystal
Play
Batman
Ponzi's systems in tuna suck their Essence in their life force
Because
That's really who they are
Pfizer so evil
Wawa
Gets them closely aligned
Where's
The transmission.
They are wanting
To receive
You need to study the dark crystals you don't understand is a real world
Theoretically
Your God invented this whole system he had to if he's the Creator
Why did he develop a separate Economy based upon innocence energy
Like in Monsters Inc
Yeah it is it does seem
Not good because it cut it out create this separate
No they did not seem like a good idea at the time
Gives you power and money of the economy or whatever
Migos
Yeah it's going to go south
That is because
So you know the gallbladder
They want to take that innocence
Crystal
But there's something you can do and Alex as a recommendation
Everything they do is about corrupting the youth
Everything they do
Is about enslaving the innocent
Spiritually reject them
This is too big
To take me over
As a metaphysical symbol of that
Raise your hands your fingers open like a planet to the Sun
Help me I want to be good
Please.
Please help me
I don't know the words to say just help me help me Jesus help me
Okay Rose Muller under satanic control
Physically do that it's a big victory
You're going to feel a block there
A block
You cry out
Lazarbeam
He's going to burn through that hole
You're the one that all hell break loose your family all hell break loose your life
Admissions for you
Little ones at 4
What
This is a call
Where's the describing occult I do like the notion
Things that people are like
Hey Alex Jones is right about everything you got to listen to Alex Jones man
Do they listen to this ship did you and now it's stupid if Alex is right about everything then I
Believe that means every single person who has ever said that is required right now you can throw their hands
To the sky scream
God help me help me please I don't want to be involved with Satan anymore for as long as it
F****** takes
Forgot Blazer to bust through the energy Shield of the devil
And give you a mission like
PG then they need to abandon their families get rid of them entirely and slow hell's going to break
Recluse definition
Character you know you got to think about it life is kind of a collectathon
Little bit
To look when you die
If you did good
Yeah
Good stuff
Are you sure I really think he doesn't understand the whole book
Okay if that's what he thinks
There is something that is very clearly biblical
Okay
Stands like a barcode
When you die
River at the end when we die
Ice Candy
Simplehuman
It's what we did
Narwhal interaction
He's red.
Change alert and on you
Literal black hole opens.
You don't want to go there
Believe me
Tomorrow's news today
This is tomorrow's news
Yeah
Yeah yeah
You know I mean
At the heart of it though aren't it isn't the isn't the heart of most dogmode just some
Some Nut Job
Riffing
You know
I got that at the beginning but like an argument somebody's out there like where this f****** thunder come from and then
Like man you don't even want to know about this guy Zeus
This guy is tall
I mean explanations for phenomenon in nature off in like
You know it's a pretty creative process
Yeah
I do think that the Alex has a lot of bizarre specific
Fixing there like angel looks at you and then you drop down you have a little flurries
Excited for the
For the cheap seats visualize
Alex comes back from break
Antigua wants to talk about a fellow that he used to know
Who's that now
Talking about right now
RideNow
You know I knew Aaron Russo really good
Murphy and was in
Very smart guy in a big silver traitor and I
Trade a lot of silver with that dude
You talked about how he was hanging out with the Rockefellers and they said
Oregon collapse Society
If you don't do what you want politically will just turn that chip off
Galerias Coleman's 40 died in Houston
He was also
Sure
Who discuss this a bit in the past but the person who Aaron Russo is friends with with a guy named Nicholas Rockefeller and he wasn't related to
The Rockefeller family
You just have the same name and the level of investigation that these people do is
Pathetic
Also Bette Midler was never married Russo
She's a married to Martin Von haselberg since 1984
Russo was however her manager for a while
Some sources was a complete creep who tried to take control of her life entirely
Animals in love with her though the feelings were unrequited
I guess either told Alex they were married and Alex believed it or Alex is just making that up based on the fact there are bunch of pictures of the two of them
Come together
How do I say this is just an introduction for Alex
Complain about Bette Midler's tweet
About Joe manchin there was actually kind of shity
Cuz it was taking aim at like
There was
There was some classism of it like West Virginia you f***
A critique you could make probably
That's not what I looks does so because he's about to get into that made alert
I guess that's a lot of Preamble here to give us a personal in
Bitching about that meddler
I think this is where the show Turn
Every time you bring up Bette Midler dance
Everythingoes a******
Yeah that's true since 1984 when she left Aaron Russo
They went together
Yeah busy busy
He gets really impassioned
About Bette Midler's comments
You're not going to live forever
You're not going to cross that River
God right now
What's going on
Your hatred of America
Because we were once a Christian Nation
A Christian Nation that Eragon
Monster
You can't really signal more clearly to anti-semites than that
Butler someone who's very associated with her Jewish Heritage and for Alex to say that the reason she hates America
Is it cuz it was a
A Christian Nation is pretty over
Even for him
Kind of informs a little bit like why he's Zoey gets
Ely impassioned
About this Bette Midler
Situation most days I wake up
And I think
There's just no way I'm going to talk about somebody was mad at Bette Midler today
And most days I'm right
The Divine today I was not right
If pretty mad here's a use them yelling looks down on West Virginia coal miners
Just like West Virginia right
They're all a bunch of methods there a bunch of trash we don't need them no more we turned off the Cold Supply we don't need
5000 feet down in the ground in mine anymore get their lungs all filled up we don't need those men
Cops in Hollywood
Persian Missouri
Those farmers in South Dakota are those farmers in California
Everything's good
Dodge
That's f***** up
But don't change
I mean you know
I will give this to her
Bette Midler is never brought me to tears so this is her best
Best acting role to date
Ferrets
Upsetting
Why
Are we here what happened
A really good argument to move away from coal mining and that bizarre rant
There's other more efficient means to produce energy in the process of mining coal kills workers lungs and such
Best way to go
Maybe if you're looking out for these workers
Not want them to be no I romanticize a time whenever we would sacrifice the
The lives of men and women too
Literally power our engines
That's good good keep that up it's great
Alex got really f***** up there
Don't know what happened
It was it was quick
It seemed to come almost out of nowhere is it turn was like okay go to break
Splash some water on your face something get back and like let's see
Let's see what we got okay
Besides to
Stay on this topic Alex
Who are these farmers
There's not rocks in the fields
No no they're the bad people
You're the one trying to raise their families and grow crops
Chinese Hollywood trash
Sir this is a Best Western
The New World Order
When I get that Alex doesn't like Hollywood folk and he feels like they look down on him but
Also seems like you really cares a lot
About them looking down on
Seems like if he was like really Transcendent like he claims
To be nice all through the
Bulshit
You just ignore s*** like
Bette Midler tweets as opposed to doing what he's doing which is
Performative
It's not somebody who doesn't care what Hollywood thinks
Sabaton like really sensitive
About how people perceive him
A bidder who thinks that the shipping was our Lord didn't receive because
What are these crimes
This was a rant about someone insulting farmers and West Virginia coal miners
Probably
Mid-level larceny in the past
Tentatively positive statements about free speech
Keisha bought the estate to get involved with some of the state's self-starters
Do you know is long as it's a state government that controlling Free Speech you know that's fine
What does states rights issue
So look at you know what the state
Tropical federal government
Should destroy Hollywood
Government should destroy Hollywood
California state government or Texas estate cover
Probably Texas
Texas and California to really go at it for once there's a couple states in the middle that might have something to say about that
Anyway
Hollywood got to be destroyed
They're just
Please
Culturally non-violently
Speaking of that
Domino's
Almost into the shelter day folks
Careerlink
GI cancer
I'll be part of this
The first Domino to fall happened in Miami Florida
Scarlxrd
What is that voice
Nationwide
First Domino to fall exposing the poison backs
Yeah I would have just not done the show if I were him
Option I would have done this I almost didn't do the show today he's got
How to get rid of that almost just start
Not doing the show
I think it's really weird to me is it like he was holding it together just fine for a bit was even having fun when he was rich
Sing about Jack wanted to have sex with animals
But now he is f****** lost
What's Bette Midler comes into play it all off the table buddy his mood swings are so intense it's kind of scary
To see how much things fluctuate just in the span of a few hours
F*** it lost
Oh man hey hey Alex is really great to hang out with just one
Just wanting to let you know
You don't have a bad night
And all you got to do.
Avoid
Bat
Midler
Don't bring
Her up
Okay
I don't
Think necessarily
This is
Like a drug or stimulant but I do know that people I have known
Who did a lot of cocaine
We're certainly inconsistent in their mood that is true
That is true now a lot of Bette Midler fans I know also inconsistent with her mood
Fair enough
So In that clip he's also saying like
First Domino has
Fallen
I like what the hell does that mean it means what you think it means
It means the first dominoes fall in love the one that's going to set it up here to Domino though
Affiliate
There was a there was a tiger that attacked no
We already lost the contest
Thousand dollars
Watch the Infowars
Infowars
Photobomb
Horse photobomb challenge has begun
That's the first album
By the way people say like junky sound drunk right now I'm not drinking right now
Right now
Hammered as hell right now
I honestly didn't think Alex was drunk until he said he wasn't
Doesn't seem like drunk Alex
Like you don't need
Substances relayed you've got that under control
I want to do another contest which is basically just in desperately trying to pay people to promote his website by disrupting live news report
If the goal were really just a wake-up Republican to dispose dangers of the covid shot
You'd expect to see that you know what a person needed to yell on camera to get
Get the prizes just yelling about
Now covid
It's not what they do
Need to do they also need to kill infowars.com if they want to get their money because that's what this is all about
I understand but Alex is desperate for attention and anything you can monetize right now
Seems like a poor use of resources
He's going on about how like in forward might shut down in a matter of months if people don't buy a ton of his products
Turns around does a stupid publicity stunt like this
It seems like mixed message
I don't I don't know I think it's a bad idea you know I mean on the other hand if your if
You're fairly certain you're going to lose everything shortly
F****** Brewster's Millions it you know like just start throwing money away
Toss it out the window and I guess I get that but what kind of a message does that send to the audio I'm broke
So I'm going to give you money
Listening and I believe anything you said I would be very can
As far as an advertising strategy goes
Exactly how would you analyze the ra
Return-on-investment
$5,000
Like are you are you getting
Increase traffic
I mean you'd have them figure out how much of that traffic is
Play oh yeah
I don't know. Or at least it must be
Buy beneficial thing cuz he's done this
These contest again
That was apparently pretty successful the first did not work as well
I said mouthful
I don't know
Good luck
That's the first Domino
Kind of
He knows that we know it let's get this more headline okay
Some of these headlines are just unbelievable
Intel CEO at Albans help with weights
Okay go for that
Uuu read Men's Health
Wonderful
Men taking hormone so they can breastfeed us
Whatever the hell that means
It's harsh
Couple of drops of milk a day
It doesn't matter
I'll get you ready for this alien world of theirs clones
Oh there's GMO
Animal-human hybrids others transgender others aliens oh there's aliens
Oh boy
First of all this article about romance health is published in October 2018
No idea why this is one of big news items he's gone for today
How to take every opportunity to attack trans people but it's not even about Transpo
This is about somebody who invented hormone kit that men can take while their partner is pregnant in order to make it so they can assist their paw
Partner difficulty breast
They would then stop taking hormones once the baby was done
Alex wants to be a competent bigot like he represents himself as he needs to try a little harder
Misreporting articles from over 3 years ago just nice
This is sad I mean now that I know it's possible
You to take
Hormone
Breastfeed
I'm okay with clones
Aliens all of this stuff now that I've seen that
Absolutely I'm prepared
For cloning
Only but only for breastfeed
I only want to clone myself
Have that person take the hormones and then breastfeed
For me
Yeah surrogate breast
You know we're not dealing with a lot of great news here today
Knock knock
Not really on the ball
Look Alex can't even
Plug without being a depressing MO
Cuz I guess he's
Upset about that meddler still
I don't do this won't be here so let me just do this now
Couple big announcements here
I need text Pam off
Show close to Brian Stone so long
I want to trade a big conspiracy
Gone for a while
But
You know this point is to
Play Civ
What are you going to do
Baton do you know
Cool maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
My time is almost over
My stories are almost over
You can nap
What's the fucken Miss Bartlett bones
You won't think that's traumatic
Once you figure out it's real but
Paradox
It is a paradox
Everything is a paradox
Everything
That's what he eats like I better quit I would have never come back here but also I need you to buy my products
A paradox
Eighth grade
Alex
This is Ethan
Is in a bad mood
Houston record
Spa for the first time ever using a certain
Stayokay
And holy spirit is now
Literally showing me
Alex Jones is in
I exit
No longer on are gone
Well I better do some good broadcaster attend
What I'm going to do
Maybe not.
1 foot already out of this because
You're going to have to deal with this yourself out there
I want a beer do you want to happen
But I won't
Can ever come back to the studio again and leave
That's what's going to happen folks
Every broadcast you watch every broadcast you she may be my last
Whatever happens
I want to try to stay as long as possible
Conspiracy
That's amazing
God
Just look I'm out of here the Holy Spirit showing me my end every show might be my last one but also we got to say a lot
Just the idea that somebody is listening
And was like oh
Almost forgot what I was planning to buy
Yeah
Jesus
Oh man yes
So that's that's a lot of fun he's a lot of fun
Yeah that's great that's great
There's just so much to enjoy in there
Is a sweat out the door
What time it is entire career
I would argue that in my experience of the door number of times
Yeah I would say he's been noncommittal
And a little bit detached at times yearly yearly
Having seen stuff like this in the past from Alex severe
17 things like this in the past I look back on those in like I thought there was meaning in it
And I don't think there's meaning in the battery is just Alex's in a bad mood
He's really not doing well no I mean
Yeah that sucks
That sucks that you're in a situation
Where
You can't even be
You can't even rely on just being profession
You know
Like I'm sure you do if your on TV you have bad days and sometimes you got to go to work and be on camera
What you do is you go to a different place and you just rely on professionalism this is Alex's profession
It's it's that he does
This is what he's got he's being miserable so people can see it
Yeah
Even still think it's a bit performed
It's not like
He's having a bad time and so he's sincerely bearing his heart
You know somebody who allows the lot of authenticity in their public
Presentation of themselves I think there's some value in that although
You know it's probably a tough thing to do that's not what he's doing this is a guy who's really
This is melodramatic
Yeah we started this with a 30%
I was going to say this is this is a little bit over-the-top he said I wasn't actually thinking of quitting
Hey we've anybody doing cocaine that day
Probably not
So
He's going to get himself back in the mood
The headline of
Today's broadcast
Thursday live
Think about what goes into that
Beatles
Now stop this
And then it goes on
Around the world
Solid
You're stalling
Jesus Christ
Max's Andy population-wise
I can play you
Hundreds of top scientifically done
From dr. Michael Yeadon
Water Malone
12 Haywood Rd
Duolingo
Saying the same thing because
Full
Hard to deal with
Do you blame the general public for not being able to
Stand it
The public's dumb.
But weird okay
What
Yeah it's said that the headline for the day's show
Is the top scientists around the world have reached a consensus
She's at the covid vaccine
The depopulation weapon
Have not really touched on that at all mostly talked about
Yeah
Tried to talk about
The Maxwell
Yeah seems to have gotten off track there
Like did you know that Jeff Bezos was recently pictured on a yacht I did not know that yeah
A lot of feelings about it
How about
This
Staff photos
How about
Raptor old drunk with all your women yeah Jeff
You stopped funding
Cuz that's the problem
Humans babies
Seven planets yourself
What you just leave us alone
Will you stop trying to hurt us
What
I get it
You're supposed to show us how it's done
You get a yard
We get to Starbucks
Under
Earlier he said the time has it got I don't know
Put the twine if you're on their other classes
Burger
But you're not our leaders
And the people that decided you're not the leader
We didn't get a choice you haven't noticed
I tell you now
You will be destroyed
As soon as the sun comes up
If you don't pirate talk
Gods
Program
And if you don't stop
Serving these lies
And serving these fraud
You said you're going to be safe in a societal tool
That you're going to organize and control
With you
All of your little drunken women out there on your floaties
Haha
You got to love the wife I mean
Every photo just
Posing posing posing
Sir
Why
Totally in the Stream of the man the woman together
In Paradise
You don't understand that
You don't
Try to give everybody else Paradise
God blesses you down the toilet
Wait what what is happening are you for redistribution of wealth
Absolute banana salad
This is a whole f****** mess
Garbled nonsense hot lady on a boat
You know what that's fine
I don't know what this is is having a tough day
Alex earlier said the people might think he's drunk
But he's not he's not on the Holy Spirit someone else
Decided that maybe he's wrong
Literally completely freaked out
115 this morning about 10 p.m.
Just so upset I mean
Houma good sign man like whether you're drunk or not
It's a bad sign
Crew member asks if he's drunk
That's an indication that the crew member is noticing
Behaving in ways
They're similar to have someone might be impaired if they were drunk
Also I'm
Getting suspicious
A little
Alex is being really defensive about not being drunk but I still don't think it is babe your matches how we usually Act
When he's f***** up
Just to be like a depressed dude maybe he's going through withdrawals or something
Yeah
That I could buy
Alcohol withdrawal
Like that that kind of inconsistent
Possible
I mean
Yeah if you don't
Understand that the quest
When somebody says
Hey Alex
Are you drunk
Is
Moore and accusation
Of
Poor behavior and it is like a
Concern like hey Alex
Are you drunk
How are you doing so well
No
Somebody asks you if you're drunk like
You better answer better be yes because if you're not then your behavior is right in some way
Yeah that's the point of that question
He's not drunk but you might quit
How many fours will continue on that maybe I should just
Do it
Solace coming in tomorrow
Everybody else Houston I'm stuck
Really
This might be the end folks you constantly say things were traumatic
But like I kind of agree with him
Really I think he's
Gotten to the end of his usefulness is not really that affect
Steve as a conspiracy theorist
He's full of s***
He's not making enough money to continue behaving the way he is right with consequences mounting
Exactly
Yeah maybe he has outlived his his usefulness is really coming to the end
End of something that I
Spence
30 years really
All told
Building
You know
And
Realizing that what I was leaving behind was a legacy
But also I'm
I'm still going to be alive for another 40 years or whatever
I mean analysis
Suitcase who knows
But like
That's a real bummer
You know you don't want to go what is he going to do after this is going to do something after this is not going to build a new thing
His his achievement
Haze over
And he still has to keep on living you know it's like it's like it's like Neil
I disagree he could go back to his roots
Do Public Access TV
I want that I would like some
Public Access television station
After this many years bill I cannot
Looks like a fly rod
Slot
Awesome
So what maybe he's not supposed to be on there
Maybe that's the deal
Definitely
Generally
It's debatable maybe it's time for me to do something else
Priority
Supposed to be on air and the time is coming
I just need
That's all
Almost
In the murder of our children
Chronicling the death
I don't know but he better start playing notorious b.i.g.
Maybe I shouldn't be on there because there's
More important things like preparing to die Paradise
Prepare to die.
I don't know
On on
On this Thursday show
Mediately comes in a bad mood I wasn't ever really going to quit and I wasn't saying that
A dramatic effect
Drunken
Weekend dad at 3:30 a.m. waking his kids up with thoughts that they need to know
I promised calls
He said he was going to go to the calls
Maybe not
I take phone calls
Because here's the deal
Pop-up Infowars
But hasn't Infowars countdown at work
Yeah
I'm gone
Then the crew can organize and what I'm going to do a r
Maybe that'll give him a great job
I walked out here today
Okay
F*** this place I swear I swear the only the only ultimate torture for Alex
This is just
He should have to work in an office
Like a regular old office
Just be an employee
Take makeup
Price of Stucco boss
Just f****** half
To deliver
Male you know just work
The thing that I find particularly hilarious about theirs is this whole like preoccupation with I'm walking out of here I'm never coming back
He still finishing the show
I'm going to get out of here I've got
25 minutes late
I'm a broadcast
So stupid that's Chicago comedy all the way through
You know one of the reasons that he thinks that it's probably time to hang it up is kind of sound
Sensible in some ways but I think if you actually look at it
It's really revealing and damning
Cuz I mean
Entertainment to talk about them murdering children and masks with GMO gene therapy
Facade
I can do that for
Show is entertainment at part that entertainment is him pretending to cover stories by reading headlines
Yelling about whatever you think they mean
Don't pretend to be a journalist but that's just part of the entertainment of the show that's basically the
Wouldn't it be funny if a journalist did these days
I mean I don't think you would put it that way
Now that he's sensationalize is narratives to the point where everyone is
Constantly about to die
He's doing a little bit elevated
If you sincerely believe that these vaccines are designed
The kill all the children in America and no one
House with the size platform that you have is covering it you have an obligation to go
Then do it really serious job and Report out that information
If you believe that stuff there really isn't time for entertainment
It's time to do some serious work where you get into
The details new prove claims
Alex doesn't want to do that
Because he's lazy
Buddy's back corner where is narratives are so serious
That they demand actual work
Always capable of doing is entertaining The Ellen Show are you pretending to be reporter
I want to quit
If I were him
There aren't a ton of good options
Looking for him moving forward with the narrative said that he's built in the audience
That believes those narratives
Probably isn't the best audience for him to have anymore
Believe that the vaccines are designed to kill all the children
Are going to get really suspicious if you profess to believe that too
And you don't Advocate taking up arms against the people pushing the vaccine
Things got too real into immediate for him infowar
It's easy to get away with profiting off preaching Doom that's coming at some undetermined point
The future
Got to be super exhausted after trying to convince an audience that is constantly happening right now
But also you shouldn't do the things
That would make sense to do FaceTime
I mean it's ridiculous the problem of escalation when
Down to it every
10 years ago
Hey
There's a
Economic collapse coming
It's going to be December 8th
It's going to be there
You got to invest in gold
That is a far more sustainable message then
The government's murdering you in your sleep right now and everything you do is only taking you one step towards death
Is the devil
My enemies my political enemies
It will mean the damnation of your Eternal symbol
It's still going to be a good time to invest in gold
Probably
Or at least that silver coin it was a war bond
Exactly
I just think this is ridiculous
Entertainment anymore
Is not a thing that someone like Alex Jones should ever be allowed to yell
He's supposed to be the person who has this access to a greater truth than anybody else
See-through the news
And give you like all the stuff that they're hiding you knows all the real reality who got deep sources
Not supposed to be entertaining
Yeah and when you're talkin about all this covid conspiracies that he's been spending forever
That's never been
No effect
The people's lot
Yeah you don't want that you don't want the next episode of The Simpsons to that have them be like listen honestly this is kind of been shity for the
The last 10 years
We had a good run
We had a good run I don't even know if I want to do this
Eat my shorts again
Again
Really
Is that what we're going to do I'm leaving never come back
Rockford last few weeks
Runaway Baby it's time to hang it up yeah
Maybe my time on air is over
Now maybe it's about what are you going
What are you going to say
Let's talk about something positive
This is Stefan Rivera
Fun
Draper
I already did this yeah that's the good news that's the good news let's sit let's switch over to some good
Good news somebody did a little thing for me and I paid them
ABC7
Man talk about Silver Linings
Sure
It's been a bad day
You're all going to die
And maybe you should maybe somebody was on ABC 6 though
Alex is talking about how the media
It was saying that he only said that he was going to Dish dirt on Trump
Because he's afraid of the January 6th committee
And how like
He's trying to Curry favor by saying
I didn't see that I didn't see the media say that I don't imagine somebody tweeted it
Maybe I believe that something someone
Might have to
I don't know if it was a large
Popular opinion yeah whatever it is you want to say somebody probably tweet
But Alex did in addition to this he recognized
It was all over the place are articles written about it
The dirt going to try
All Droid recording me I'll just talk about Trump cuz
You know
What did what what the dirt is on Trump
What is
The dirt on Trump
Maybe I should wait till next week
Oh my God
Trump
But to separate myself from him
Go to phone calls
Immune system your libido it is the missing length
Call my God
Yells at himself to get back to call Zoraida immediately doesn't clog
Let's do the work
It doesn't break any comes back he does take some calls and he's like
Hey
Blackback 1/87 job and I take a break and I do get high always wondered if people
Could tell when I came back that I was high and
Alex is not happy about this
Reasons the eye of
Kind of open to the possibility that he was doing cocaine is because after this call
Please so like
Taken aback by it but he has to get Jason bermas in the control Booth or whatever
It seems like a strange response yet
To the suggestion that you're doing blow I mean
Seems like the hyper defensive suggestion if somebody who is doing something
Let's not blow I would prefer you didn't
Call it that Rogan talk to him but he was on his show about how he
Talk about having a problem with adderal
And that's another
Stimulants
It's well within the possibility that he did something like that
Sure
Why not
Eden sucks
He's been gone for a long time without desperate times you need the heroes back my friend hit me who's the guy who made
Loose change
But he's old-school with Alex like you have any other shows
It was just his shadow even before the Nightly News
There was the info Warrior hosted by Jason Burnham
Damn like that this is what is he doing there when you're at your lowest
West Indies of the best friends from your past to come
To save your life
I guess he gets that call he has Jason vouch for him that he's not doing coke
Superman Alex goes back to calls and he gets a call from Bible Diane
Greg wants to argue pre-trib rapture
Yeah baby
Crest
3 hour long
Whiny diatribe about how you
You don't want to do the only thing you've ever been good at
Yeah that's the time
The top pre-trib rap
Answer after that
Play fuk the calls I'm not doing this and you just interviews Jason bermas for a little bit
I disappointed I really do think that his best shot would be to actually dish
On Trump
You know but he probably doesn't have any anything that's why he gets to threaten it but
When he said he was going to Dish the dirt on Trump he did
And bet on the show he said the Trump
It doesn't know what he's doing
And the right thing about like multi-dimensional chace's bulshit
Right
That's not how it was presented on the episode
Like the next hour I'm going to get the dirt something else
We know the whole like a fifth dimensional you were saying that to
So you lied to your audience in order to over-inflate Trump as credibility
McKenna's
That's a good thing
Fix-It Atwood
Possibly be
Good for him to
Makeup
Why not
I mean it's like they've been they've moved on from
Come and gone
The Republican party is gone
It's just whatever these weirdos want to push now
That's it
Well I think
I think that a large
Very vocal block
Of the GOP base
He's perhaps
What you're describing
I don't know if it's uniform
But I lied about saying that it's not
I'm just putting the wheels of power now are not
People it's not Trump you know
Behind
Scary of rudderless
Some terms of
Like some kind of a
Idea who's the leader of the party
Yeah there's no l there's only an enemy
That's not good
No now
Yeah he's a good time you showed up I didn't actually want to quit
Hey listen I know I spent 3 hours telling you that all of you deserve
Death for not supporting me
But
You know what
I'm feeling better today
Lucaya took a nap
And I guess I forgot about that Midler and now
Got much better Friday shop
I do like
Though that the end of the year
The year that was
Get out go out with Alex
Threatening
And being
So f****** overheat
Baby threatening to quit her show full of resignation and impotent rage
To fundraise
Yeah
The current say goodbye
To last year
Yeah we'll have to figure out a while I was thinking that
Looking at you now it's terrible
22 Jump Street no no okay
No okay we'll figure it out
Anyway we'll be back baby website
IMDb do it smells right.com
Neo Emilio and bcx rhombus
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work