Damn important
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge vype.com
Alex
Indeed we are. I have a quick question for you sir
Today is Tuesday
Got my booster I got boosted
Real side effects to speak a little bit of a sore shoulder
Situation going on but
I was worried that there would be severe side effects not because I'm black
Vaccine skeptical
But because I went to a Walgreens to get the booster
And I texted you about it. Good something was wrong there was a bad vibe
In this Walgreens
I went did
There were too few people where was it
Which which one it was in uptown is a little ways away
Walgreens hasn't been there for 10 years old yeah I couldn't get that one in a close
To me it's a little bit of a trip but like
Yeah right there was like
There were there weren't enough people in there I don't know what that means but I could definitely felt it
Shoppers staff
Everybody there's just not enough not enough the lighting was wrong
The area where they had people go to
To get the shot the little back office room look like a holding cell
Drip
Coming from the ceiling one lights cutting in and out all the time like other Walgreens that I've been
Been to in my life I've been to pharmacies
You know I've seen the area where they have like consultations
MinuteClinic kind of Heaven aesthetic
Beatles
Comfort Inn at least office play
Looked like a biohazard container
Then I didn't everything was fine with the right back seat immune to malaria
That's for damn sure
Yeah so is
The teachers have gone to remote learning my partner of course has a teacher in the
CPS
And what's right about that spot is that when they went to take a vote
On whether or not to
Say f*** you to the administration we're going to go remote and let the chips fall where they may
88% voted yes
Banana
Stronger than the teachers union in Chicago
88% to agree on something means
God damn everybody was like this
Is f***** up so I'm very very proud of all of them for doing that and nobody break
In the goddamn
Hell yeah
Congratulations
So Jordan hey guess what it's our anniversary
It is our anniversary five years
Yeah that's right
January 7th
Was the first episode of the show back in 2017
Anniversary
Combining that with the fact that we recording this on the anniversary of January 6th
You don't we was our first episode recorded on January 6th
Might have been the 5th but it could have been yeah yeah I'm not sure
I was very much even from the beginning like we have
Quick turnaround
I've always operated
I think that means that the two most important things I mean there's the one
That's an interesting take on
That's cuz it's better probably to get him to take her to either we closet
Connection between the two of them perhaps
So I kind of combined
A bit of this
Hit my head and in my emotion
And I combine this with the fact that
You know our last episode
Alex was trying to
I quit real real bad time
And I turned on the 5th
Shows up 14 minutes late and I almost immediately have Mike issues until I got to go off air
F****** tired of that perfect distillation of the show
So tired of this dude
Until I decided we're going to go back to the past so today worry 2003
We're going over the episode that
Played
July 11th two
Okay right
Sure
But when was it recorded
July
2003 3 days different so I told you
That we had skipped
The 8th and the 9th
In 2003 because the audio was unlistenable
The 11th is a rebroadcast
Get out of here
But this is the episode where Paul Joseph Watson
Sometimes on a very young Paul Joseph Watson
And he's promoting his book
Until I decided I was give this a whirl
It's our anniversary this is for me I don't give a s*** I'm not covering the present today
I'm going back to the past
I figure that like
There's going to be something
For the SEC
You know like
Something there's going to be
Trump has his
Rally's Superior happening today sure there's going to be something
That is going to be wild and we'll cover that on Monday
No I I hope not
What are
Okay
You know what let's just do today alright
So first
Lydia and all her gay frogs thank you so much you're now policy want
Next time Alex has swollen neck
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much next to this person's been but the way they
Praise that in the message was possible
That's impossible
Possible
I'm a policy wonk
Sable the chalk forever and I will walk thank you so much
Disable dr. Little Goat
I'm a policy wonk
Dr. Little Goat
1 degree
The Goat restaurant in Chicago there's like a girl in a goat
Is it
Good that is a bunch of restaurants of goat
Amazing
Amazed
So before we get down to business on today's episode I wanted to quickly touch on piece of news that was breaking
Since we recorded our last episode
On December 30th a man named Thomas Apollo showed up at a clinic
In Tustin California
People who are working there giving a vaccination
Accusing the people of being murderers and they were making people sick
According to an article in the washer
YouTube post quote
Families together said that the members sustained serious injuries and was sent to the hospital in an ambulance
But they both workers are expected to make a full recovery Within
In a few days
Obviously given the publicly available information I can't sit here and tell you that this guy was a fan of Alex
Or that was part of it
And isn't Brasher but honestly I don't even think that's an important aspect of the story
For our purpose
An attack like this was inevitable given the extreme quality of the rhetoric that's flying around
Conspiracy and misinformation circles
You can't prank convince a large group of people that vaccinations are intentional plot
To kill their children and not think that some of them are going to take the next logical step
And try to attack people providing vaccinations
Even Alex knew that which is why he was building up this narrative in advance as we saw last week
And they're going to Stage Terror attacks and they're going to everything else in Guaymas
Do you understand that will say on the news that my followers blow up the Pfizer building or something like that
I know I know
We've talked about this a hundred times in the course of doing the show it's clear why a person like Alex would behave this way
His entire career has been made off of profiting from tragedy so I don't believe for a second
But he's not rooting for tragedies
Strike
At the same time when tragedy does strike
It's good for business
Business to make sure that the audience doesn't start to question whether or not the media they're digesting is part of Woods Drive in Vista
Having a prebuilt story in place of the audience blame someone else is critical
That's why I was doing this kind of thing
I just want to take a little moment at the beginning here to to point out this
Very clear dynamic
This the cycle that's in play
I'm going to Alex's talking about like the bombing of a Pfizer building or something
Extreme example but
I don't believe for a second Alex wouldn't say that this attack of
This assault of people at a vaccine clinic wasn't a false flag
Exactly what he's priming is audience to deny is real
I'm not so coarse why you use the example of
Blowing up
The Pfizer building because that's that sort of like
Hyperbolic strawman that is well safe you think that they would go blow up the Pfizer building not just go
F*** around with this place over here which
More likely to be what they do you go
Near home and I like the blowing of the Pfizer building cuz that's like your prediction inside like a
Looks like these are the terrorist attacks
I have like everything less than that covered exact
You don't act like a dick
So yeah I find I find this
I don't know
Shity
It's just the inevitable consequence of allowing this type of s*** to
That's just what it is
So it in the same way that we've just decided that this is how it is for so many
I guess this is just how it's going to be one of the reasons why
Did it really talk about like
Why alot of his rhetoric
These kinds of
Propaganda
Disseminating
Structures are dangerous
These are the things that, from it
Right and thankfully I mean I hate to say this
But made it sound
Minimizing I don't mean it too but thankfully
No one died
It was an assault
Not like a shooting or
F
So let's go back 2000
A pleasant sort of
It's not all that Pleasant
I was going to have Paul Wall
Bring it
Cowboys
Order out
Hearing that clipping
Books being released I realized that I'd never
Actually read that book
I knew that he had it I was worried existed but I never really felt any real interest
How to get down to it
I got the sense of what it was about the title order out of chaos like I was just going to be about that
The conspiracy idea of the hegelian dialectic
Fight beside in preparation near to give it a read
Bring up anything that Alex hasn't talked about on the show already
Everything is a false flag with its done by the Elites in order to
Increase their power you know the drill
I thought that maybe you would be good idea to discuss the specifics of the book but I realize that but
10 pages into it I had six pages of notes explaining the things that he got wrong
Search felt like this too big of an undertaking for just a normal Xbox out
Maybe another day I'll record a 13-hour breakdown review of Paul's book but that day is not today
Interesting fun fact though
This is the only book that appears
Ever been published by a EJ production
Switch of course transfer Alex Emerick Jones
AutoZone book 911 descent into tyranny was published by a different company called the progressive
Suppress
Who's the publisher that put out a bunch
Books written by Alex's buddy Webster
But also books written
By Henry Makow
A dude who is a stop
Really just doesn't like the Jews at all
He recently wrote an article titled quote the riddle of anti-semitism
The 87th is amazing quotes
Yeah yeah I would have
I would have expected scare quotes around that one
It's not great
You're correct
Here's how it starts
Quote is growing is the covid
Scam is correctly identified with organize jewelry Freemasonry and communism
No one can justify genocide but the stigma attached to Disturbia Define control
There's no but his legitimate resistance to the pernicious agenda of organized jewelry in Fremont
Masonry IE the New World Order
Bananas a little later he drops this gem
Most Jews and non-jews are unaware that since Antiquity Jews
Consistently been revealed
For a good reason
Jews are in a state of willful denial
They don't realize that Judaism is governed by Kabbalah which is satanism
The existence of Judaism is to take God's Place destroy Christianity and disp
Possess non-jew
Seriously ideas that he has Express
On a recent basis of trust me if you cruise around this website you'll see that
He's had this position his whole career
He's also been friends with Leo zagami for a bit so that's
You know is it's not something that we talked about you often but there is that element of
Genocide already
That always includes the like
Lest you worry that you can
Talk to them or even communicate with them
They don't even know
They can't even understand that they're working with the Devil
So don't worry about it
Don't worry about communicating with them and asking them any question
Cuz I can't
That you're not you're not going to be able to get to the bottom of this by investigating it or experiences
No point in doing anything yep just
Play back to Poulsbo
If you read the dedications he includes this
Alex Jones for awakening me to the New World Order in Publisher
Sing this book
Bulkhead even write the dedication to his book without lion
2013 interview with Luke rudowski
From we are change Paul said quote
Don't tell Alex it was actually David Icke that woke me up
Liar
Wow
Have an identity of his own back in 2003 so it's good practice to flatter the person who's willing to advance his career cuz it's certainly
Wasn't David Icke at that point
2013 Paul's in a much more secure position they can give to his real intellectual father figure
The turd in the punch bowl himself David
That's something that I'm Amazed
Did someone would admit open
Honestly
I would prefer to have been woken up by Alex as opposed to David Icke the third figure
Play as we get through
Okay
Paul's going to be coming up on the show but there's another guess
All your clothes
Call Greg
Accurate
Manipulate
Neutralized
I'm really curious about how this this isn't packing
No it sounds right
I don't I don't I have no idea
Well in 2003 that's hacking
I'm really confused on the specifics of this
Crunch when you use the slide whistle into the Payphone alright you can mimic the sounds and then you make calls for free
Osher
Bright
Right all right
Phone free so first of all the notion of putting RFID chips and all your clothes to Tracy who is a fear
Probably shouldn't be taken seriously
Is it conceivably possible with the technology
I'm probably but what's more important is if it's a practice
Plan that any evil entity would go for
The hurdles to this kind of scheme would be gigantic
And some of them are pretty much insurmountable
Even if they knew what shirt you bought to trace you through how are these folks know if you gave that shirt to someone else as a gift
What is there trying to trace you but unfortunately put a chip in the pair of pants that you don't like that much or maybe you grew out of
These are just behavioral concerns completely leaving aside the Absurd technological problems
Of isolating individual signals that would be coming in
If all people's clothes are tagged you also tagged the gift receipt
So that way if they return them or give them away you have
But then somebody's got to
Figure out how to transfer the tag
From the gift receipt before the person throws a ride
That's why you need a hand
2003 iPhone hasn't come out yet
I would imagine that this sort of like they're going to track you through your clothes narrative drop by the wayside 1C iPhone showed up and
David Federer
Could be like good guys a few years later
You would
Bankofam to track you
You will
Wait in line overnight for them to know exactly where you are at all times
A couple years later they probably felt so relieved
Didn't have to do this
Nonsensical they're going to track your shirts thing
This is so much easier
Catherine Albrecht is a radio host in a demagogue who's Big claim to fame is like being on that RFID train
Real early
And apparently she coined the term spy chips
Because that is a popular term
Nope
So she began his organization Caspian which sounds a lot better than what it stands for which is consumers against Supermarket private
The Invasion and numbering
This is a group that Advocates that stores shouldn't have frequent Shopper cards are loyalty programs
Had a kind of moonlight the B by fighting off the RFID chip as the mark of the beast
Love this group
Listen I want more innocuous lunatics none of this anti-vax loyalty program
I f****** join that group
I'm sure there's a way you could go bad
I just thought maybe we haven't
Explored it too much
Enough to figure out the exact way it's whenever they want me to go
Send off
Jokes on Walgreens account my old phone number
I'll see you or not
So Alex is think that he has a bit of a
Ambivalent
About some of the information that
The mighty
Have been gotten by the
The Spy ship
Right right right
He talks about like sort of good hacking and bad
The organization
Have the proper
Other nail calling
Don't feel like Alex really want to have to be arrested for download
Doing things
To be arrested
He disagrees with Alex political
Piracy is not maybe it's just in the
Excuse me I get a Feeling
Yeah but Alex wants to arrest
Political enemies
Cool
It's great I think it's a good idea to find any excuse to only attack your political enemies
I think it's awesome that we should rest this guy he's a liberal
Fine
So Alex Alex
Tension
Making 2003
I'm on air
I'm talking
Totally enter
I'm not
Non-Stop
Off-air
Me and my boys
Who are here in the studio
We have even more
Interesting
Informative conversation
Your
Morgan
Then we have on the air
Mark
Fireworks
Mortar
Before the batf
Fireworks
I got a
I believe
Market
Formative conversation
Good Shepherd
They argued about who had cooler firework I mean
This is quaint
I'm Blown Away by the stakes here
Right
It's still a dumb show
Very very but it but it's
It has it has this Vibe of like
We're having fun being my buddies are talking about fireworks
Whatever
It's weird it's weird it is hard to
Go right back
Amor
I suppose
Discreet pass
3bros can just get
Together
Complain about or compare fireworks right
I don't know Nann metaphorical dick measuring contest
Also this is such a fun topic for them to be talking about because Alex is entire show is about like police of Prayer
Fashion and all this police state nonsense and it illegal to have
In Austin 1101
One cares no one cares or works or cannons
You just begging for them to impress me more it but
People turned a blind eye cuz it's under
Stood.
Loser hand almost his entire
Assertive
Ideology
At least a large portion of
Unspoken agreement between power and not so
Analysis world because they're looking for every opportunity to jam you up
Your political ideology that is in need of being a jammed up and if your political ideology involves
Combustible
Whether it's a gun or a firework obsessed with taking away your guns
You think cannons would be a little bit
Stop up there
You think so
Turns out
Okay
Anyway
Ino
Alex
I can relate to what he's about to get into here
Sometimes loses the fire
For his job
Dinner
Sometimes
Loses the fire
Camp
Getting Susie Astic
Think about what he's doing sometimes I run into that
Chirality
Quitting his show and having outbursts of a little talk about it it's the same number again
But Alex has a private
True method
Forgetting that fire back
And I I kind of admire this
Perfume
Will
On the radio
How to do interviews
Lucifer
Where am I
Radio
Aw
And I
Rove
New World Order
With me
4 Yuan
So Alex whatever loses a fire
He listens to other stations to get pissed off and then he calls in using a dumb voice
Just anger that's so sad well I think it's probably
Pretty obvious by this point not really a revelation
Just anger
Nothing else
He needs to be poked
Buy something is poking Emmett's
Call in doing this down voice
But sometimes it doesn't work
Because I can't believe it
Just like call screeners don't want to put them on the air
Horseman at this I think is a problem for the Constitution
Cobalt
Bring up the heat
Alex
Prodigy
Why not
The president
Neocon
Is owned by Bush
Right but it's not cuz I got sold to a conglomerate
Yeah
Talkin about this dude on the are either
I appreciate
Many parts of this call screener
Howard somehow a slimy ghost
Call screeners call screeners not Power Trip
Schedule screen calls
Sure I'll let you on the air but you must
Solve a riddle
Clearly the patience with which
That call screener listen to Alex
Both in and out of his accent because I
Very strongly doubt he could keep it up for that
Sure could visit like the 10 a.m.
That calls printer definitely heard Alex drop it and then repeat it in the in the voice
I see how still managed to get through the whole
Even asked a follow-up question
What else dum-dum I have a spoiler for what's that
Greener interact
Didn't happen
Didn't happen like that I am I will guarantee that if I were if
If I were call screener and I were trying to run a professional program
I would not
Somebody on the air who's just going to clearly try and derail things
With nonsense conspiracies that
That we don't need that we've got over a hundred times
And that does sound like something you would say because you hate the concert
The tution and the founding fathers
Who died for your right to go on any radio show whenever you want to say whatever you
First amendment that number one amend
I think it's really revealing
That this is his understanding of the Constitution
And what free speech mean
Radio stations in Boston
Benjamin
Franklin got
Posts dumb s*** in the newspaper under a fake ass name I get to call into WM
NPP and say bulshit
But what if like they can only take six calls and your caller 8
Or whatever
Right
So dumb
The second amendment was about abolishing time limit
McKee really means this
But one
Couple things I'm going to guess that most of those four people didn't actually call them sold out
Throw that one in the
Alex took 15 calls and one of them was
Like
Someone was supposed to vaccines
So that kind of hurts his argument that they weren't letting anybody on
Wow
Maybe they just had like I'm not going to let someone on who's
Spouting. What they're talking about I want somebody who's going to make those
Peoplelooker
Stupid
Free pizza
Cool
Very interesting
I would save it for somebody who loves
The Constitution
Is a
Is a First Amendment absolute
He doesn't know I mean just because he believes that that station because it disagrees with
Temp should be taken off the air forever
By the federal government doesn't mean he doesn't believe in the First Amendment dance
It's just outrageous
Even going back to 2003 I was at a very strange
Position cuz he he really desperately doesn't want to be seen as anti-vax
As a whole
Because that's
Admittedly very dumb
Yeah trying to say that
Like inoculation to things
Doesn't work
Is it really tough
Climb
Denying the actual science of vaccination is
That's a game that Alex doesn't want to play
I mean when your conversation goes like this
Vaccines don't work
Do you have polio
All right so they work sometimes
Then you can't be all the antibiotics will get all of the numbers of diseases that have essentially been eradicated
Let's go down the list
But whatever I guess that's one angle you could take
It'd be tough to figure out what exactly is different to play is like I would love it if x
We're cool
I would love it
Totally butt
Evil people make them
Ygorganization
We didn't have all the ra
Femur
Mycoplasma
Mother
No
Health boo
I'm not talkin about these specific things that he's bringing up and rattling because they're all things
We've discussed
In past and it's all nonsense
I think the
Crowning nonsense is this idea that there would ever be
Some kind of an organization that is trustworthy enough for a Lakota
You know like a look
All of these other companies right
Scientist
And
Public Health
Non-governmental organization
They're all f******
But this one
There's a good guy
No it's what we need is a
Patriot Maxine maker because here's the here's how exhausted you get with them
And that's why they win
That's why they've won for the past 30 years
They're 40th
Is
They will say anything and then you go
Okay fine
What does it take
For you to just shut up
Okay you want to do if your your organization fight
You give us rules
Well I need my dad to run Pfizer
You're just never going to shut up are you I've already agreed to do whatever it was to tell you to shut up and now you won't shut up look f******
My dad needs to be in charge of Pfizer
That means he can run out of action,
All right to work and put him in charge Mike Adams health
Gives a lot of great advice third of course
Get a weirdo let's get a real weirdo
Everybody votes on the weirdest weirdo we can find that's number three who's nuts
Every four years
I don't know Lord monckton
Shut up
So the problem that Alex has really is that the global
Was there trying to make more and more vaccines man
There was a Alzheimer's vaccine candidate that wasn't trials in 2003
And the trials were abandoned
I say unfortunately because follow-up studies of people in those trials found that he quote halted and even reverse the brain disease
He's in some who got the shot
Obviously there are severe side effects
That's the case like it was in
In this case with 18 out of 300 patients getting brain inflammation
It may not be something that you can justify going any further with but
The idea that
There was some promise for a cure there was really exciting
Anybody's ever loved ones Alzheimer could tell you that it's pretty hellish Prospect or a canopy and a vaccine would be huge
The lessons learned from these trials in for further research and it's still ongoing
With a new trial beginning in late 2021
For a nasally administered vaccine
That looks to slow the progression
Yeah there's Prospectors things are happening this year
There have been
Nicotine vaccines that have been developed
But a 2008 article in the journal expert opinion on biological therapy
It discusses the state of these vaccines are the found the quote
Although these therapies have had some success relapse within a year is still high
So it's not really
The strategy the people think is like this is where we're going to go
I think one of the big problems that we have with vaccinations is that like
Easy
Slip into like all these are mandatory vaccinations
The way we should
Should sell it to people is with like
Hey guess what
We're going to eradicated disease this year to go down this path of conversation because
They're like first about there's not anybody who's a serious voice on 2003 advocating to either of these vaccines be mandatory for
People to take that's just not a position that have
That's a fake Point Alex
Degrading to argue against
Because the specifics album bolster this idea that every year doesn't more vaccines
Become mandatory
Which is nonsense
Mandatory I think we should all come together and eradicate the disease together
I think it's at framing is what you want to use that great but also you need to know that the federal government doesn't require
Any vaccine
That's a state-level issue
Which is why the ability for people to get various exceptions for things like school-related vaccine
It varies wildly
From state-to-state
Federal government and all the entities like the CDC recommendations on what people should be getting
How many states want to require you to get them
Musical shops be allowed to go to school
That's up to the state
Zolo debosier
Throwing out
Position
Melody ideas
Doing with the vaccine
In the current day but I don't
You can make
An analogy between
Some of these things
Like
Measles
Rrr Sandra Bella
Yeah shots did some states require
For people to go to school
Mandan Act
Pandemic
There are relevant difference
Is there a 2000
This this notion that the government
Just trying to make
Vaccines mandatory
State-level
And based on Alex's politics you should have no problem with that even if he's opposed
Yeah cuz he's the states
You get to choose these things
You know if you don't like it you can move to another state
Good answer to things
Politics in his positions on other things
That's
But you should believe me it's almost like this whole separation between federal and state government is kind of arbitrary bass tab
Find whatever it is he feels like his position should be at any given point in time
You bet
Also like he's trained his has to pretend
That it's not a state thing
But you have to pretend that it
The demand of the federal government is trying to
Force you to get these shots because otherwise is Ark
Falls apart
That's unfair you should have to get you
Look if a if a Band-Aid happens you get
To play that card
You can't just play a Joker
That's not fair
There's got to be rules to the game
Makeup it's a federal thing
That's unfair
I don't like it well that's what happens when you deal with Liars
So appalled
Joseph Watson
Pjw
Apostle Paul
Shows up no he's not
He's not figured out his thing
But
Alex Alex gives him quite a long
Introduction that I think is
Really dumb
Started
Because
Alright go f*** yourself
I don't work with many people cuz they're
Also
Don't work with people cuz they're not constitutionalist but you work at both British
That's cuz he loves the Constitution so much
I was already revealed the first talking about it
The constitutionalist who lives in England
Still with the British issue was Paul
Come on they don't even have a car
Alright whatever
Most Americans
Call Juan
Cruise
Football mouthpiece
Amanda
Today on the show he's got British Galileo
I like that one
Give me compliments
For complimenting you
So I was out today
Introduce
The earlier when you're discussing the dedications of Poulsbo
We mentioned that
He's given two different stories about who woke him up
The different points
His career
In this interview
He might have another third
IDs
Okay
Third individual
Jesus Christ
The New World Order
Yeah coming out
11 but
To be clear
First state or not get into death camps in England.
They do not come back to that at all I was very curious if this is that doesn't happen
The idea of paradigm
To the new world order by realize
Both ways
The right one
First place
3D
Liberal Channel
Controlled
Between Malaysia
This is a cold war
I'll be sleeping in the world
Joe
Now deceased
Banana explosion
Call Mina
So part of the thing that woke up Paul was the realization that the left and the right of funded by the same folks
Can I come from
Him reading the work of Anthony Sutton
I use work generously
Something is most known for writing 3
Books known as The Wall Street
Trilogy
Wall Street in the bolster
Revolution is about Wall Street funding communism
Wall Street and FDR is by finding fpr and Wall Street and the rise of Hitler is about funding of the Nazi party
So exciting and full of insinuation and rumor these books have been absolutely Trashed by historians
Who reviewed them
With one summing up the Bolshevik book this way
Quote
He tells us nothing new he does repeat unsubstantiated allegations
Cite the relevant facts make Auto warranted conclusions
A cortisol
Falling Leaf pedestrian Style
Ouch
Ouch little little slip-ups
None of the three sources Apollo cited as being the source of his Awakening are in
Anyway respect
We would like is a lunatic Alex is a narcissistic liar and Anthony Sutton to work
Critically flawed
Boils down to unconfirmed
Conspiracy.
So I
This is bad
I mean
It doesn't get more Father Son and Holy Ghost though that's right there
So that would make this is bad though
Who's the who's the Father the Son is Alex and then the Holy Ghost
The Sutton cuz I assume he's dead
Yes I'm okay
Yeah Allison probably block
At the idea of being the Sun
Father in the Punchbowl
But it also
It's it's interesting to me I don't
I wonder if in 2003
If Alex had that same negative opinion of David Icke
Cuz I know that by you no periods around like 2009-2010
He was having David icon
Yeah Ben and bacon sort of had
Right I think I think that's tough because
Is Bipolar person I like to keep a mood tracker
Do you know if I'm going out of out of whack you know
And Alex has that relationship with David Icke I feel like on a day-to-day basis it's like
Like him don't like him he's at 8 today and he's a to you know what I'm saying how far is things going to feel
Depends on what your opinion of David ideas
So a little bit of a primary source to bring up about this idea that all
Old people
Are controlled by the same party
Recently found
Article
Online
California
Detroit
Call love
Who was
Khrushchev
Find and dine
Ferdinand
Issaquah
Chris just right
The Cold War
Meeting with New York
It is true that Kozlov was a Bohemian Grove in 1959 but
The question we really need to be asking ourselves
If newspapers were reporting on the fact that our Russian guy was a
Suggested Bohemian Grove in 19
How secret was this whole thing really
Did Alex really do anything to expose The Grove to the world or was it something people reported on freely like
20 years before he was even born
You can find an article from 1959 even in the New York Times about cause loves visit to The Grove
Which according to Alex's mythology should absolutely have never happened
They were trying to keep this s*** under wraps
Never happen
So little known fact the folks to listen to Alex Jones
Actually DeLand Bohemian Grove sits on
Was originally part of our Russian calling
Neither dated back to 1812
Fisherman attempted to you form a foothold in America there the Russian
Florida College
It was a huge boss though as competition from other colonists elected the decimation of sea otter population
And the Russians ended up withdrawing
Selling off the land to Johann Augustus Sutter
Sutter would go on to find gold on the land and strike it rich
God does dumb Russian
The Grove is on part of this land which is
Hip Hop's
That there is actually called the Russian River
Science article about this even includes the lyrics of a song that they sing at the Grove called Lament
I hear some of the lyrics
Why did the Russians leave it and go back to the snow
Why did they leave this Bit of Heaven will never never know
This New York Times article has the lyrics
Do things that they sing at the Grove
Inside
Put like the access
It's clear like
This is written by somebody
We're telling me seeing shanties from the Bohemian Grove yes I get it fixed
The 1959 there
Pretty in-depth
Discussion of Stanford gone on there
Sweetly runs counter to Alex's idea that he would have to look in with binoculars in order to see
Druids years before Nixon would show up and get a handy so you know it's still not secret yet
Something
Oh wait look
The conflict between the US and the Soviet Union particularly in times or a 1959
Was one that said we needed diplomacy
Handle
They were our enemies on some level but there was also there what there was an estate of outright hostility
The politician like oslove would be on a diplomatic visit to the United States which he was
And while he was here he be invited to The Grove
It seems weird at all
I guess for Paul though it serves as proof that the u.s. in the Soviet Union
Just making the Cold War
Wait I don't understand what's diplomas
You get like
The person that you're in competition with or even at war with and you like talk to them
I thought war was about totally eliminating the existence of your enemy
It's mostly about screaming
Okay well that's good
That's one of the things we've learned for Alex over the years
In the
Department of State
Their Foreign Relations Journal
You can find
Like a long transcription
A conversation that cause laws
And Eisenhower had
That's just
I mean
How you guys been
Field Guide
You go fishing a lot we got this song
12 people saying it's depressing we miss you
In that New York Times article there's also like a conversation about how
I was very impressed by The Vineyards
In California but also thought that the Russians
Could teach them how to be more productive which is ironic because he ended up being thrown out of office for being
Later on and then
Brezhnev took over and Be Your Own Boss
You can't have the
Putin getting thrown out for being too drunk
No sir
So Alex gets into some conversation about this
Latest left and right saying
I honestly think that this is
A short clip but it's one of the most revealing things
In order
To understand Alex's Paula
When actually do
Who's this
Let me know plenty of people on the left or
Proposed to Wars
Under
Bush
As they were under Clinton
Name one American warrior that
The American left has stood up against to end like
Name one like what
Vietnam
No one will get into Maria definitely not into some ideas about
The opposition to the Vietnam War a little later
I think I think Alex is trying to play games here with the appearance that like under Clinton the left didn't
Opposed
And maybe some people in office didn't maybe some of them fell in line
But in terms of anti-war activists
People who
You know that's
That they have the same position on the picket line trying to stop Wars
Also in the clip I think you see one of the most universal Hallmarks of Alex's politics
You sincerely believe that everyone makes decisions on what does support or oppose based on what the people they are against
Bank
If my villains are in favor of something it must be bad
So I'm against
If my villains oppose something I must
Be good so I am all about it
Alex believes that other people think this way because that's how he's been
The difference for him is that the enemy he has is completely imagine
Canary and their preferences are just things that he's decided he's Dakota
From Reading headlight
Through using a psychic intuition Alex's figured out what the globalist are in favor of and this is what he opposes
Everything is for him is based on this kind of thinking
The globalist want people to be vaccinated therefore there must be a conspiracy involved in vaccinations are evil
The globalist are interested in conservation efforts and worried about climate change
Therefore that must be
Conspiracy day
Further some other nefarious aim
I was thinking about it and even in support of gun rights
It's could be seen through this prison
There isn't anything intrinsically bout owning a gun that Alex supports
His staunch gun-rights position is rooted in the belief that disarming the population is part of the plan of globalist have
To take over and it's absolute martial law all over the world
A One World Government
The only way to 100% real
Is for everyone in the world to be armed
But let's imagine the inverse
What is the prevailing attitude among politicians that Alex didn't like was that everyone should have
Pretty easy to see how Alex
Form of support of gun rights
Conspiracy get everyone armed to the population killed each other off or triggers Mass python
If the global supported gun rights
Then the only way to try and
Birthday Richie
To be in favor of the cronian gun restrictions
So you don't make their evil plans come
Well I mean you don't want Auntie's are getting guns
The 100% real group that is going to attack
Can kill all Republicans if they have done so
You have to be for some measure of gun-control there right
But I think so yeah
You picked it if you really wanted to get down to it
Almost every bit of Alex's beliefs system runs
At least through this felt
It's very f*****
When you are basic principles on doing the opposite of what
You think your enemy is doing
Nothing you believe in really means anything
And I might my point is that nothing Alex
Believe me.
Even his religious convictions could be seen as him trying to do the opposite of what he imagines
Does enemies want bike
He pretends that he's fighting literal demons wanted to
Destroy Christianity
That was basically just
Being a cartoonish version of a religious person that he presents himself to be on air
Like almost everything could just be
Yeah it could just be he has a massive dose of oppositional Defiance disorder that is
Combined with is nice
Statistic of tendency
Cease to create a
Human devoid of originality
It's the oppositional defiance
It's targeted specifically at imaginary position that he's ascribed to his imaginary
It's B
Kind of interesting
It's a little bit like he's created a black hole of Personality that just absorbs whatever comes near him
It also seems like a really efficient way to torture yourself
Yeah
Go to some calls calls with Paul
Paul calls
Hi Alex
Thank you
In Lima
We're talkin about
Italian dialect
It's interesting it says that I
Wisconsin from the steam
Karl Marx
Caught the Revolutionary fever
Drew heavily
Materialism
Depict
Where the other
Scorpio
Only inter
The world
The point however is
Change the world
Andymark
Interpretation of reality
Universe
You left by
Religion and materialism
The banker
Okay caller is reading from a blog post from 2000 by a person identifying themselves as they say
Diego police detective name
Philip award
It is possible this is a real tribution cuz I can find multiple news articles about cases involving a detective in San Diego by
That name
That's the case this isn't an article that you should be citing
Make any actual points
I found the blog post and it's actually a screed against
Community policing
And how that's just a Marxist conspiracy
If you read through it it seems like a really significant problem that this police detective has is the people are raising questions
About whether or not the motive policing that's
Become the norm in America
What's a sufficiently sensitive
Concerns of diverse communities
But they're supposed to be police
Accident by the way not bad
Is really pissed off at the concerns of white Christian man aren't the only factor that matters
And that means that we must have uncovered a communist plot
I mean if
If a detective walking a San Diego beach
Doesn't Discover a communist
But I'm shocked cuz that is
Communism City over there I've been to San Diego
I've walked
Communism everywhere
San Diego Chargers
Chargers
Charging
Credit card credit cards
Centralization of bunnies trying to get rid of musical dollar play Electronic
Were there
So
Apparently I don't know if there's a lot of things that you could probably say our
Are communists in nature
This is a little bit of a swing
I mean even talk him out
Which is again
Call me
Do you have fireworks bands are coming
Communist
I would like a f****** list
For them everything everything except to sit down and give me what isn't communist
Is communist
According to a diamond I can't tell you what
Honestly I'm struggling but according to this interview one of the things that is
Is acceptance of homosexuality
Decline of society
Can go to the
I'm fine
Incident
National Record
Spider-Man
Number 20
The degenerate
Norma
Natural
Permanent
So this is being presented as if it's something that has any credibility but in reality if you do find out where this list of 45
Indominus goals was right into the Congressional Record
You'll find that it was representative of Herlong for
From Florida and the comments
Introduced this way
Mr. speaker mrs. Patricia Nordman of DeLand Florida is an inarticulate
Communism and until recently published the deal and Courier
Which she dedicated to the purpose of alerting the public of the dangers of Communism in America
Miss nordmann's request
I include into the record under unanimous consent the following
Current Communist goals
Which she identified as an excerpt from the naked communist
By Cleon skousen
It's 1863
Florida Center representative
Thousands bulshit
Any Reddit
The Congressional Record tonight were expected to take it seriously
Gotta I'm not going to play that game
So along with the the rent homophobia Paul is
Is expressing in this list
There are some weird things
Vetta existence curious
Number 18 is
Control of all student newspaper
Which seems like a dog
No you got
Is my campus paper in college and I do take that publication seriously and didn't get the time
Game
We must occupy the student newspapers of all the colleges across this line
It seems like a waste of company this time discredit and eventually
Dismantle the FBI witch
Seems like something Alex is very interested in
It's pretty cool you know finding a place where Alex in the commies can find common cause
Discredit
It seems like you've already got your work done for you so just
Take them down
Number 42 is particularly relevant to today
Quotes create the impression that violence and Insurrection are legitimate aspects of the American tradition
Alex loves talked about watering the tree of Liberty with the blood of tyrants and he's been pretty clear that
Yeah even though January 6th was a false flag even if it wasn't it would be
Find because the people were there and they there right
To do an Insurrection of the election result
How to sounding more and more like a comet
Call me I'm telling you anyway this is a faecalis written by an 80, Dash it had those red to the Congressional Record
Meaningless accepted it allows Paul and Alex to lend credibility to their home phobic
The conspiracy nonsense
Yeah
Yeah that list is real bad
It has the same problem of those those those
Books that are like 101 ways to
Surprise your partner with but you know
Everyday dude
And then they run out of ideas where they like take a bath and you like
Anybody
Takes a bath man
The idea that there is
Try and convince Americans that Insurrection did violence at 5
Ifucking birthday
Every July 4th we're like
Hey
It's illegal to have fireworks but guess what the Austin Police do give a f*** I've got a cannon
That's the game
No we got this
Paul believes that acceptance of homosexuality is a communist conspiracy
How is we're up to so much more that can
Conveniently
15 with
But making Paul's bigotry not looks
It was the
Financial backer behind
So the CIA did have involvement with Steinem but Alex Apollo really over-reaching here
Gloria Steinem was involved in the CIA as part of her efforts to recruit left-leaning youths to go to a Vienna conference being held by cam
Communist
Effectively debate
The Communists about the virtues of America
She did this as the head of the independent research service and CIA funded outfit at Harvard
Steinem wrote about this
Experience in her book my life on the road
Alex honestly should totally support her work with the CIA since the goal of it was to disrupt events like this Vienna conference
There were seen as being communist propaganda
Yeah it was supposed to discredit and then eventually dismantle the Vienna conference
This magazine wasn't founded until 1972 which was a bit later than this and the magazine self was
Funded by the CIA
This magazine is not the initiator nor the most important aspect of Fem
But it was political magazine that was directed towards
Women and interest
Important
History as we all know feminism began somewhere in the 772
View the Paul and Alex are assessed facts and report information accurately
They're invested in attacking and discrediting Simoniz
So every supposed fact
Needs to work in service of that predetermined endpoint
That they're engaged
That that's the Elder doing
It's really stupid
The most
Kind of like
Soft
Misogyny there is just that idea always
Well there's no way they could
Could come to the independent conclusion that they're being so
F***** over by a financier who's tricking them
Essentially what we have here when you're blaming the CIA and Tommy's
Essentially the acceptance of homosexuality and feminism existing
What are you doing is saying that without these nefarious actors
Straight white man would rule everything and everyone would have
Accepted as an obvious evidence that straight white men should rule the world
Commies and commies work in the CIA
Scott it sucks ridiculous
You get down to it everyday I wake up and I look at the stars and I'm like obviously white male
I don't want to be
Women
Can work
If they want to welcome crazy
This is the 42nd clip-in Alex is a little unclear actually
What
But the CIA
Working is also a plot of the
The CIA
Should they so choose
They wouldn't
If it weren't for the Communist like
Women's Natural Instincts would override the the government's desire to make them work
For the commies in the CIA
You know
It seemed so and episodes
I'm going to I'm going to just throw this out there at
It seems like
Tumi
That the commies
That are most often reference by the anti-communist
Have nothing to do with straight white men
Despite the fact that at the time of Russia when they anti-communist were supposed to be fighting
Austria Whiteman
In Russia ultra-wide
So their enemy was all straight white men
But the Communists the enemy
Wright was the one who's trying to
Real white male hegemony
Right I think
That Alex could actually thread that meat
I don't think you have a problem with your rebuttal I really don't because
Based on his chauvinistic worldview
Right he would say that yes there is a straight
White male hegemony
In Russia
They're trying to undermine that heater
Because they know that will weaken America
Straight white male hegemony is inevitable it's just a matter of
Whether the commies or the capitalists are running the straight white male Hood pajamas because it's
It's being undermined as Anna
Attack right
And then the Russian straight white male hegemony will take over here
So almost
Ironically
They are admitting that all of the minorities of America are the
The deciding factor in whether or not coming is America capitalism will win
That is interesting I haven't unpacked that but yet Perhaps
Alex talked about this whole Defiance politics
I told you to get back to it as a related to the Vietnam War at this is so stupid
In awhile here doing
No Stan
Conservative talk show hosts
Oh
I forgot you guys still hated Michael Savage at this point Luther King Junior
If the CIA in the Communist had not hired a bunch of black people
To go wreck everything in white neighborhood
It would totally would have happened conservatives what a f****** loved Martin Luther King jr.
If it weren't for the pocket, I just think that
What Alex is describing is
Conservice being really dumb and I honestly don't think they were even as dumb as Alex's presenting them to be
Notion that like your support or opposition of a
F******
Would be dependent
The behavior of beatniks beatniks were more polite I would have been against the Vietnam War you would have to be
So
Detached
From the actual issue that you're supporting or opposing
But you would have to have no feeling about the war
Itself right you have to have no principal show conviction
People who oppose it
Horrible if a beatnik comes to your like bar
Okay and then you've got a little bowl of nuts in your drinking your beer in the beatnik knocks the nuts
Do you think to yourself what obviously
We should burn down villages in Vietnam
Conclusion to come to
But it's
One of the few things that I think
I agree on it that's the
Cops and civilized
Right
I hate Alex
I think you sucks
I think it's one of the worst
But
I see him opposing civil asset forfeiture and my instinct isn't to be like
I must be for you've got to be for the cops stealing things
But that's how Alex's brain work it is so dumb if he finds out that you're against cops
Stealing things I think he might be I actually haven't heard him talk about it in a while you might have gotten there on his own
For that matter
Do they mention Michael Savage
Beatnik past there
An hour
I didn't realize this but
Michael Savage's show on NBC or MSNBC actually got cancelled in 2003
The Alex discusses that
Pier
No Stan
Conservative talk show hosts
Michael Savage
Coronavirus
So I just real quick want to play for you what Michael Savage got fired for
Definition by Blackstar it is not
This is Michael Savage let's go to story
Give me a ring right here on the Sabbath
Oxidation go ahead please
Did you have a worst
The next one
Hey Michael Savage
I was flying to Laguardia
Yeah
There's two Undercover
Security guards
Yeah
Somebody was smoking in about
Someone was smoking in the bathroom
What happened
Affirmative flight
I need to suggest
Dynamite Takis
Alright alright
Yes I am I only get AIDS and die
How's that
Want to see if you can still meet you
You got nothing better
Put me down your piece of garbage
You got nothing to do today go eat a sausage and choke on it
Trichinosis
Okay let me know the night
Call Gyros busy because you have a nice night in the bathhouses angry at me today
Get me another one put it on the side of my tan
No more calls I don't care let's go to the next scene I don't care about the
Nothing
So he got kicked out for what
Yeah that was a particularly distasteful presentation that's a game
I don't know if Alex understand the First Amendment
Government had done something and respond
Monster him
Being horribly homophobic abusive to this person on air
Then I think you might have some kind of the first
Discussion plate
He did something
I don't know live show that was
Credibly
Awful
And again
The standards of the station that they fired him for about a First Amendment issue
Alex just
Do you want I guess
I mean I got fired for asking for a raise
So that's different that's different
Not sure how but it's different
I find it really fascinating to go back
These points
Deep in the past
And receive this
Completely
Infantile
Understanding
Someone is supposed to be a Bedrock issue
Super m
Yeah it's
Not surprising
I mean
Kind of a bummer
If it is
If it was that all something that you value
It would be different
I think
What he
Values
News about it
Is actually that it's been applied in such a way to his life
That he can get away with saying anything
Evaluate
That you're getting to something but it's the value isn't
The actual first
That would be a principal that he wants to
The credibility of reporting
The principle that he actually has his I don't want consequences for saying horrible
I don't want people to actually accurately judge
What I put out into the world to answer for it
Michael Savage shouldn't have to answer for
Horrible things you shouldn't have
Somebody fire him
Forward this
Think they obviously wouldn't want to be associated with First Amendment
Boils really hard down to just like I don't want to feel bad for the things that I say
And I should be allowed access to every platform or I'll drive My First Amendment right
That's nonsense
That's not good so it's a little plug
One of his films
I thought this was just actually really funny Alex has a master of raising the stakes
Hours and 41 minutes
I love that it's 2 hours and 40 minutes
Frankly it's 2 hours and 41
It's 241
I'm a truth that tip of the f****** spear here man I'm not going to lie to my audience
And say it's 2:40
What is actually 241
Actually I'm going to call it 181 point three minutes that's what we need to call
So Alex takes more calls
Smart Paul calls
Just got worried
North Carolina
Chihuahua friends
Australia no
Do you know all the rest of the country
All I can say is
Do people
Trying to tell people
No
What is going on
Colon complete
Play the music
Pinole
SanMar
Germany
Maryland
England
Wales
You know what's going on
Really
You might be onto something here
You're naming a lot of countries with something in common
I don't know where you're going with this
I think
I've listened to a lot of
Alex Jones
I've missed you a lot of calls
And I am
Flabbergasted
You did not interrupt him what that guy is
Verbal pattern is very slow
Bien during interrupt
Yeah out of Ireland that seems like a choice
Nissan Alex's Bart not to interrupt him
Yeah the only thing that I can see in there that'll be like
Why why wouldn't you interrupt
Which was
Not a
Thing
Add 2000
Not anymore
Yeah they renamed it wyaconda
It's a signal
2 white supremacist American nationalist
Do you not interrupting him when he's not saying anything and rambling
Is it bad
Hey he said Rhodesia so he's probably got something I want to listen
He doesn't actually end up
Saying really anything yeah that's not surprising you just wanted to say how great white people are
I'm sorry I get another caller and unfortunately this doesn't lead to a crack
Movie review
Illuminati New World Order
Is it
Also there are
Tearing something right now
Special effects
You still frame it
Frame by frame
I'm a knight
Don't
First of all
What
Yes the world does
Band together to fight off the air
Illuminati Style
I don't know cuz under the United States
Our weigh-in is still everybody who contributes to actually defeating the alien right
Are American
Jeff Goldblum
Will Smith but here's the
What you're not understanding here though is that this guy has been proven right
Okay
How
Is it possible
For neither Will Smith
Nor Jeff Goldblum to become any less attractive
This many years later
In fact I might argue that Goldblum has only become more attractive and it's silver foxeer
You know who's real sexy though
Hirsch
I don't know I think
I think
I mean what you got Robert Lozier in your movie it's clearly Illuminati
What
This is a dumb question I lose track of culture really quick leadership
They make a sequel to Independence
30 years later
Couldn't tell if I had
Imagine that Will Smith wasn't in it
I think that's why you don't think it's a sequel to Independence Day
Hearing about it and then not seeing it and then I don't know
How do I get to conversation about
To them talking about how the globalists are going to fake an alien invasion Shoreline order to bring us all together and create a world cover
But here is a Paul with a
The hot prediction
Down the line
Well obviously
Predictions that enforces got incorrect
I always write alien invasion
Fifteen52 2018 totally
Interview with Katherine Albright
It's
I don't care
They don't talk about any of this
Specifics of the documents that she supposedly hacked
Somehow
Or not I don't know what you just described it as like to use the Google search like a Boolean search bar on the website
Titan that you found some documents on the site
Autocorrecting is love
Describe
For Alex
He says that she was using like
Login information like brute-force hacking earlier and then she's like
Ida search
But thanks I don't know
Are they don't
Direct you to any actual primary sources I don't care
If I use DuckDuckGo
Dove
Grocery store card
So I am
They're scared
It's a snooze
Alex introduces her this way and I just thought this was
Outrageous
Communicate
Lottery
Microscopic
Cell phone since then but consistently on iPhone
It's this is Soca nonsense
Yeah like you're trying to make everyone afraid of these RFID things
Presumably for the multiple reasons of tracking and
Whatever pulse could be given off by it and you're admitting here that phones are more dangerous
And you have phones
It was a stupid
You know
Like listening back to these
Free SmartPhone era there is like that
That same thing you see in movies where they have to contrive a reason why you can't find your smartphone in a horror movie cuz otherwise the
Story would be like lot is over
What is so many conspiracy theories
Is even now have to like
Find a way to avoid talking about the fact that your phone does 99% of everything they've ever been afraid of
Since the dawn of conspiracy theories
How how is it
My phone tells me how many f****** steps
I've taken surely the government doesn't know where I'm
They literally do anything with your phone
Yeah yeah man it's it is true that like
Essentially
Give him all of the conspiracy threads that existed prior to smartphones
All of them should have just woven together into a grande contemporary that is this
Society collapses we fought a war over the fact that a smartphone
And then they should have had parties where they'd smash
Cell phone become some kind of
Like
People live in the woods
And I remember vaguely the movie Enemy of the State
And I'm like as I remember it I'm like
It was such a
Huge Revelation in those moments for them to be like
The government's doing this and now my god dude I can do that
I can watch my pet from
F****** space
Yeah it's fine
The fight it's probably Superbad
Whatever watch your pets from space you can't get to space
Estate sales
So quiet now
Yeah what are we going to do
2003's
Lower Stakes time
But I think you still get
What's up
It was stration
Of these things are actually still very relevant
This politics with based and essentially imagining what your enemy believes and then doing the opposite
It's soaking
Consistent throughout Alex's life
And
The use of
These imaginary enemies
In order to reinforce the bigotries that you want
Carryout
You know CIA and the commies want you to accept homosexuality and they're behind
It's all just
In service of intellectualizing your own bigotries
In order to make it not seem so bad that your plan
Yeah that's all they're doing I mean the thing that I
Immediately like
Reevaluate
Is those those that first week of covid-19 in about how
If we know it's over for Humanity
You got these numbers out of China I probably 100 times as many dead and then
Quick turn to like this all fake this is nothing and it's like
UCSF my immediate Instinct at the time was all he's got the March
King orders he's got the the line from all these people and now the more I think about it the more it's like maybe he just saw that people on the left
We're taking it
Seriously
You know and he's like well if they're taking it seriously it's got to be a conspiracy
Yeah you know like that's
Sad
It's sad
Imagine that
Analyzing Public Health
And then he realized what they were like actually this could be bad
I think I think there's a lot to that
Stream miss that he's gone down the road
I know that road
In particular does track with people
Continuing to take some more we take it seriously the more nuts he goes
Yeah I just wanted to cover this episode 4 was the
Bizarre conversation about free speech
Involved with him going
Call indoor radio show
Yeah I thought that was that
Was really fun just to imagine Alex sitting there trying to do a fake voice calling into a show
I'm not letting about the show and then him immediately calling everyone he knows how
You got a call into the show they won't let me on any baby
So far
Terrible Texan accent he lives
So we'll be back
Probably with a present episode going on
Alex is quit again
I don't know maybe he's going back to the capital today and
Taken care of
I would love it if we check back in on the present
When do radio shows
I hope you the best so good
Jordans
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work