Important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Alex
I've been a little bit in the in the weeds this weekend
I don't know
Whatever
There's a lot of things they probably contribute to that soda think I think that's
The others pressures their stresses of this that the
Do work-related stress has theirs
The anniversary of the six is
You know certainly not a pleasant time to be in this line of work not a great day for us
Who covers people who lie about you all the time
It was like
Painfully sincere and uplifting
And I think
British baking show telling you man good Lord
Seemingly sincere and uplifting
I think that the there's nothing
Vicooda
Amor
Cozy and happy
Then that
Lathrop they're competing with each other but they're not mad at everybody wants them to be the best
Right people people leave and they're happy for the experience they had
Never talked about like what they're competing for
Cuz it's just a plate
American reality shows are contest Roseville challenging for fries
Thousand dollars
The outcome there is obsession with
The process
And
Noticed
IWatch
Season 5
Is that like
The people sincerely seem to think
Viticcio other arf
You know something that goes a long way
All evidence
Zodiac
I think I think a lot of times it all shows
People don't really seem to enjoy each other's company
Beat the host
The Preserve.
Noah was great
Little is oncemil took over solid 10
A weird Elementary chaos
Absurdity
M5
He's always funny
Every time I watch
Watch that Edmund be like
You know that guy on The Mighty Boosh she likes
20 years ago
You get ahold of the Great British Bake
Yeah
That works well to Steve Harvey's at judge now it's all of it make sense
Court TV show
Legally buy tickets on TV
It is today we're recording this on
Sunday the 9th
Let's be official kickoff for awesome Games Done Quick
2020 once I saw something about that
Bunch of weirdos getting together and having a grand old time doing fun stuff and it's running
Great finding
Glitches to jump through in the game
I don't enjoy that as much as you do but I get it
But there's a lot of fun too that honestly I think it's more just I am so excited about like Mario and meggy
Megaman speed runs because it is like playing
An instrument
You know
It's all rhythmic it's all timing it's all if you
If you see the level music
It's really kind of beautiful to watch
What's an interesting take on it I guess I've always had such a different relationship with video games
Cuz I like
Enjoying the story
Yeah that's what's so
Such a big part of video game store
I bet it did
Kind of confuses me speedrunning is getting rid of the only thing that you enjoy breaking the story
Souderton today we're going to be talking about the anniversary of January 6th
January 6th 2022
Ski-Doo
Sure
We'll figure it out
Pulsar
Monumentous
Little bit of time
Maybe it will get an outburst
The first hex occult
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Grovel at the feet of your muscle Master thank you so much you are now policy walk
I'm a policy
Who is she walk from Milwaukee thank you so much and I apologize
Who really knows where his towel is thank you so much and I'll policy walk
Oh man that's a froopy dude say that right now text Crystal your husband is secretly funneling
Thank you so much you are now policy walk
Matt King of the reptoids
Look what this one I think we were might not have been super timely woke from the end of December but
Birthday to a thank you so much for now policy walk
IMessages birthday crack
Pictures anymore so you should expect
Three to six months
Glacier
So we're going to get going because my contacts drop
From today to the gravitas we're dealing with
Set the record straight
Ted Nugent about what really happened
On January 6th
Set the record skirt
I live in this
Where do I live in this timeline
It's a thing for Alex to
Want to happen on the show
Please explain all of momentous occasions in American College
Ted Nugent
Cool
So the January 6th episode of a show as a pretty severe title
The title is
Wake the f****** or die
The article headlined
Full full spelling or no no no no no no
Alright well then
Actually think
Something was very noticeable about this episode starts off the show being honest
And upfront about the fact that
He has to leave early to go to Family Court
Cuz I did have
Later in the day yeah hearing it like
Coup in the afternoon so you had to leave
Owen Shroyer did the third
Skating save some kind of weird stuff which I
Bravo-six weird I mean he should be taken away by the evil global
Stop
Instead it's just Family Court
Is almost humanizing
I guess
So he starts off the show
Deep In The Weeds mad at Ted Cruz
Court because Ted Cruz
Has tweeted the January 6th was a terrorist
This is before
He gets humiliated by Tucker Carlson man so funny and so Alex's is a little bit mad about
It is January 6th
2022 on this Thursday
At this time
I was sitting there watching Trump give a speech
Down the road
Kids were busy
Attacking
Thunderman police and was just a few dozen men
Breaking through the first barricades and the rest is history then the police standing down waving everybody in so they can get some Patsy stupid
Set the precedent
For chinese-style torture
America
Mia Ted Cruz praising at all yesterday obviously that's just
What's wrong with Ted Cruz is he smart
What's going on
You'll stab me in the back
I just can't help it
Ted Cruz is smart but
I can't
Get over how fantastic it is
How funny it is
Is and how complete of a coward you would have to be
To be in a building where you could have been murdered and then a year later
Browbeat
Tucker Carlson into pretending that you weren't going to be murdered yeah it's it's
Is fun thing in this dystopian world we live in to watch that utter humiliation but Ted Cruz had to go through
Rudolph
But he called the storming of a capital A violent terrorist attack in immediately the extremist pundits that essentially guide the
The GOP now
Swarmed
Showing videos absolutely no backbone Cruz went on Tucker show on Thursday the evening of this episode
To beg for forgiveness
It's almost as if he was worried about being canceled by a right-wing mob I wish I had been shot by you
Do people that would have made me a hero it would be a shocking display of cowardice except I remember the 2016
When Trump called his wife ugly and put his dad kill.jfk Cruz ended up phone bank
This dude's a total loser mean that's amazing I'm
Stabbed yeah
When you be sad if you would have left if I voted for Ted Cruz even if I believed in everything Ted Cruz believed in it's just like
You're such a worm worm
Jesus
Christ go f****** get tossed off a ledge by Sarah Manion
Watching
Tucker not accepting cruises
Apology was also really fun but underneath that there's a more troubling reality
Ted Cruz isn't some dumb-ass media personality he's a senator representing one of those populous states in the country
He has no ability to express himself if he thinks he's wanted to express happen to run counter to the narratives that underpin too busy
Models
This group of white nationalist pundits
It really doesn't bode well for the GOP and their politics moving forward
Let me they were good before but the idea.
The people who are elected officials
Need to pass an a******
Tucker's purity test
That's a sign that things are going to get worse
Oh yeah
Another thing that shocking about this is that
These people like Alex
Some Tucker they're pretending that this is the first time Ted Cruz called storming the capital terrorists
Daniel Dale at CNN
Find at least 17 other times
The cruises you that wording in the past
It's a consistent pattern
But they're sort of pretending that it's a one-off thing because that allows them to humiliate him and make this public just
Play of life
What happens if you go against the narrative
What's what's so funny about it to me
Is that
This is happening
Like I watch
That just happened
And then you read stuff
Like I was reading stuff today about how the GOP is
Officially trumps
Party and all that stuff
And the more I
Think about it the more it's like
Trump is
Not involved
There's it that you they don't need Trump trump
It's speaking is on the way by likely involves he's not the leader of
Needs to be made clear of is that the GOP is an inch
Hayirli media run operation
It seems hard to believe anything else
Yeah it's it's
It seems to be meteor
Threatened
Easily influenced
Speaker says you have to say is our social media trends
And stuff like that seem to be like
Really potent
In terms of of guiding stuff obviously I don't think
What's someone like Mitch
McConnell
Would be subject to that
He's losing power and relevant
I mean it is what it is it's just going to be a different brand of
Ted Cruz use that language
Calling January 6th
Terrorism
No reason
And I was there
Okay knows what the reason is not what you think
Alright it's an elaborate plan
The whole new system holding cosmology
Is it the American people are all terrorists
And that
Round up everybody
And shut down and populist movement
Ted Cruz knows that Purge is coming
Do you want to position himself
Pecan appointed
I'm not with the Patriot terrorist
The other shows that the false flag
Emotive need to stop them staging a false flag
Time the next 300 days
What 306 days out for the midterm
And if you don't feel
Danger
If you can't cut it
You're not dialing
To get that understand what you saying
I guess we're all terrorists now
Sure
VSP global
The Patriots when I put America
Everlast
And so in order to signal to the globalist
He's on their side
He will help persecute the the good American
Terrorist
Describe January 6th
Ted Cruz
Joined the globalist
You know
They've been waiting to welcome him with open arms
Yeah it seems it seems like this
The entry and exit of that group is
Super
In-N-Out
I have been part of this team
For like 30 f****** years
And I said terrorism one time and I have to get my ass flogged Jesus Christ
I did everything I bent over backwards for Trump
I could not have been less metaphorical
Yeah it's this is
Wow but I think that Alex does recognize that there are probably going to be right wing attack
Between now
AM PM
There is a high likelihood that that could happen
And Alex's preemptively writing a script
In order to make it
Very clear to people
That he had nothing
Things to do with a
Inspiring
So other supplies that I was asked about that covid measures around the world
This is a nightmare
Shallow rated
Takeover and so you've seen them in New Zealand
In Australia
You're not allowed to go out
Nothing honesty
Meaning was
What God created
Sun's not God but it's got dark
What
Talk to your neighbors
On billboards
Signs in the UK
Government Health ministers
Going
Because we don't want
Talk to each other
During a transition
That's a month old narrative
There was one comment that a person made the deposit of side effect of limiting large Gathering
Slow covid
Was the people who are spreading misinformation would also not be gathering
It's kind of a dumb comment
Particularly considering the fact the most of this misinformation get spread digitally.
Impersonate
That's what that other stuff
That's all just a load of b*******
I think about sunsets in Australia is a misrepresentation of comments made by Victoria Premier Daniel Andrews back
I can August
He was specifically responding to a question about a bunch of people gathering at Rye Beach on a recent evening
He said quote
I'm sure it was a beautiful sunset but that's not in the spirit or the letter of the
These rules
He didn't say that you can watch
The sunset or even that you have to stay indoors all the time just
The state of things in terms of the pandemic back in August
Victoria
Having Beach Gatherings is a bad idea
According to Victoria's covid
The case tracker they were having in the neighborhood like 2250 new cases a day
Hi January 20-22 there up to about 20,000 new cases
The thing about looking at people in the eyes that's that's a case of the even sloppier work on Alex
This was a meme that was making the rounds back in
September which showed up bar in London haven't posted a list of
Restrictions they're putting in place
In order to limit covid
Spread
What are the rules was quote
No handshaking high-fiving or extended eye contact with anyone not at your table
This was a joke
The bar in question is London field Brewery and there isn't manager Paris
Capone told Reuters
The health and safety of our customers and staff is our number one priority
And we're strictly adhering
2-all latest Public Health guidance
Inside The Tap Room
The reference to no eye contact was intended to be in
Engaging way to
Encourage customers to read and take
Notice of the broader guidelines but we've since removed it
In case it was distract
From the overall series message
Around safe safely enjoying the Taproom
None of the examples that
Alex has Europe
He's using to like illustrate the nightmare tyranny that's coming
None of them are real
His argument is so weak that one of his examples that he has to use as a satirical list from a bar that he saw into meme
Any never looked into
Nothing you saying means anything
I was thinking about that you know in Australia you can't even look at
Sunset
And I was just am really looking
Looking forward to the office
Australian Open next week
Where does a little bit later
If you have any feelings about that
Can't look at the suds
I see you trying to avoid talk about Djokovic
Moron
Alex's either using
The people make
Or misrepresentations of things in order to
Pretend that ohmygod tyranny is upon us
It's also in Australia
Cat exercise
Uno
Australia
But you can't go outside
Exercise if you don't have your little travelpass so there it is
Now you can't leave your house unless
You have the digital ID
And everything it takes to get that ID
Social credit score you must
Why would
And you are now in a Prison Planet
You might notice some like popping of the audio that's on Alex's on okay
It's
I don't know what's going on but he's already always been a lot worse
Fairly Reese
No I'm not mad
Alex is actually fairly right about the
This headline there was a comment made by the chief minister of the Northern Territory Michael
Gunner and he did say that going to work or exercise
That's not a legitimate reason for an unvaccinated person to leave their home
This decision was made because their new case numbers jumped about 60%
From Tuesday to Wednesday and then over doubled from Wednesday to Thursday
Until they were putting in this like for day
Pretty tight lockup
The reason for the vaccine requirements for entry to most public places
Just a matter of logistics
Steaks at this point for the Northern Territory
Has Gunnar put it
Quote we know that at home and in
Fatality settings are they
32 highest risk settings for catching
Can covid
We know that the unvax
Estimated are greater risk of needing a cute clinical
That's why vaccine pass will be necessary for entering high-risk Hospitality set
Not even bike
I'm saying we're trying to spread
If you're on vaccinated you're probably are more likely to end up in the hospital
And I be me what you want from us
Like that's that's the other cuz that's the question
Okay so now what
You hate that that's taranay
So what do you want then
Okay the comment about not being able to go out to exercise it kind of seems like it's actually a reference to unvaccinated people not being allowed to go
Go to gyms
With the even with a vaccine past system in place there's no way the Northern Territory has the police capability to check people
Vaccine status out on the
I guess someone's going for a jog
And while we're at it that's not even how this work
The police are enforcing this at all
Health Minister Natasha files was talking to ABC radio Darwin
And about how this place
Has an added responsibility on service workers
And she said quote
The onus is on the
Community to abide by the requirements
That doesn't sound at all like a tear anything but come on
Like I don't know maybe I'm not the best expert on this
Because I don't have a knee-jerk reaction to every me my see that makes me yell about how the devil is upon us
Spell I said that barely right there because the bar is just so low for him
The fact that he is just basically making
Recognition
Listen to it a couple other important correct
Company to make
This isn't for all of Australia and the rules still allow you to leave your house
Casper essential items and everything those are just from his imagination
Does nothing to do with the story
Just I just seen somebody
Walking outside of their house in Sydney just like slow looking both directions
Crossing the street putting their headphones into go for a jog and then
30 Scotland Yard people with billy clubs just show up out of nowhere just start
Territory
That's just what I'm seeing
Going to send all our Australian walk
The CDC has some evil plan
Which they have evil plans better than what
Which is a 0 plan
Look like
I need a citation my dude
Call prism
What was a Prison Planet
And then once everybody's in the prison planet in 15 shots
Government says it's the on injected
They're the reason you're sick
We've got to finally put them in camps
Let them be lazy I have to work
How do I know that well as historically have
It's also in the CDC documents
Here
We're going to put people that don't take the shots in camps
And we're going to make you work
I'm going to need the CDC document about putting people in
Cancel
I can believe that you would have to work also because apparently you have to work even if you're not
I just got to say this is a stupid plan actually it's completely in complex with the other aspect
Conspiracy that Alex has been trying
Motorbike open the vaccine
The kill off everyone to the globalist
Can enjoy the Earth without all of us getting the way but I guess the plan to put Alex
His friends at the camps
Then they have to oversee
Kill Everybody
At button
Instead
You create a Prison Planet
Okay you're right this is a bad plan got dumped you know what's weird like
When you go back through Alex's career the seems like there's an intense preoccupation with him and his friends being put into
FEMA camps
So many different Generations
The show that
A big fear that he's promoting but if you actually track the storylines that he uses to
Sell that beer
They don't match up at all
In 2009 it was owning a gun that was going to get you thrown into FEMA camps
There's going to be large-scale Gunn
Confiscation efforts and if you resisted you be sent to the camp
Then a little bit later when Obama was in office
He was always
Just about to pull the trigger on the FEMA provisional government
Which would make him the king of America which was planning to turn into an Islamic caliphate
And if you resisted is power grab you'd be sent to a Feen
FEMA camp
Vaccinated you're going to get sent to a FEMA camp
Don't lie a little bit boring for me at this point but I
I guess it work
Trial of the audio
That's the only explanation for why you just
Keep going back to that detail and all of his fear p***
Another reason is a super boring for me is that if the government ever did get the idea to start doing this
Is rounding up on vaccinated people descended to work apps
The people who are going to be on the Forefront of fighting against that or the very people Alex
Things are demons
Leftist bacou politicians like AOC
They're going to be
To this on principle what Alex
His favorite politician
Shrivel up like Ted Cruz and go along
To get along
Total nonsense
I'm tired of this b*******
Yeah you know it's it's really easy to drum up fear of being put into a camp if you're
Scare white people
Because historically it's never been White
People who get put in
So there's going to be a situation where it from
In the future
Next year
I made sure to say that it's a big bio-weapon release
Which I don't know why they would say that
That I have no idea
Obviously so much easier for them it's another very
Nothing we're already dealing I guess Alyssa going to say there's another bioweapon release
Another one
By the way is
Is murky language difficult to sell
But it's actually just going to be the vaccine killing you
Unless there's one way
They're going to claim a new bioweapons released in a year or two that's going to kill billions
Really it's a shot Utah
I'm sorry
Value unless we find how to reverse this order
Globalist Personnel are given the sailing shot
They're all in on it
The property they wanted
And show you
You see it all happening
See it all if you got an actuary I believe it sure
I mean can you show me one of those actuaries though Alex says actuary so goddamn much
As much as he says he's not mad at the crew
Why not
They got tables
Yeah so probably we're all going to die unless Alex
Can figure out a cure for the night
Alright
Okay so their plan is to vac
Vaccinate everybody and then neck
Steer
Announce that a bioweapon
Hit but really they're just triggering the vaccine to kill you
I don't even need to trigger the vaccine
According to Alex why do they need to add the bio-weapon
Seems like
It's a hat on a hat
That's an area I feel like
Disagree
I think it's I think it's all unnecessary
Very dumb. Dumb Alex has a guest
Is Ted Cruz in the year
Ted Nugent
In the year 2022
Show mr. Nugent
Well green see Alex and I got to tell you I sincerely wish everyone a happy
New Year 2022 but it's going to be
Be quite a challenge
This is a low-energy Ted Nugent coming in
I was expecting at least
30 more words to be programmed
Topman come on
Yeah I usually hear him
Chomping at the bit
So he does have some thoughts
What's the correct the record
Set the record straight
About what really happened on January 6th
You know how often repeat the obvious that I'm just
Guitar player but I'm actually a weed the people
Experimenter in self-government guitar
Player which means I'm
The world around me especially
And here's what happened
On January 6th
President Trump give a speech in a presentation in Manhattan rally
With good conservative
Families
Supporting God family country Constitution Bill of Rights declaration into
Did Ray apps
And a bunch of other saboteurs
A bunch of other provocateurs
Federal
Provocateur
Organized a rally on
Supposed to be a piece
Protest
Those that created
Violence
Those that turned it into work
Riot
Those were blacklivesmatter Punk
And knows where
Investigation
James Comey
J Edgar Hoover
Perpetrated all the violence
All the violent activity
Rest in Trump regalia
Who
Doesn't know this
Number of people
Okay
So now and hold on
Let's just throw this one out there
Okay
Did antifa or BLM ever say hump the air with their gun and threatened
Cyndaquil the
So many times
The guy who's threatening to help there with a gun and kill the president
They're more likely to be the ones who were going to be
Pelosi I got one of these for you
You just don't get metaphor
Also got a really suck to be someone like Daniel Rodriguez who was the guy who tasered off
Officer Michael fanone on the six
That's gotta suck to hear how easily disavowed and disowned You Are by the very people who whipped you into the friendly where you thought
Be necessary to taze a cop
In order to save America
I have to assume it be really disillusion
To see this kind of thing where
Because you took action in the way that these people were clearly indicating that you should
You now have to be cast off as a left-wing provoke
Tour just to make
The noble Patriots
Book bag
Turn you into that because you did what they wanted you to
Some sleeping sciatic and it's also disrespectful to the
Events that people like Alex and Ted and radicalized
Alex always says that you can tell a tree by its
It's fruit and I think it's a disgrace
For these guys to disown their fruit
In order to protect their tree isn't as shity as it clearly is
Nonsense
I I mean I hate to appeal to like hate have sympathy for this dude who played
My God if I was one of these if I was one of those dudes I'd be like
I'm going to sue Tucker Carlson for libel because I was f****** there and I did that s***
You have to know that
Do you work
Can you you have to see these people trying to cover their asses by pretending it was all false flag o'ree
Yeah whatever
Confusing I miss you fully understand actually that why there
Well good on them recovering the rain
It's like
You're sad too
Everybody involved in this
Said I would feel more sympathy
If I hadn't read in every novel about this type of thing happening
Every time
Yeah but did those novels include Ted Nugent
A and that's what my friends when they went to the government
Very peaceful fun-loving enjoyable American
It was all blacklivesmatter pumps
Oh my God you are
Dad really into denying January 6th
YouTube bully your your people in Congress
To do the same
America
Take a deep
And be sure you let your mare your Senator your Congressman your governor and the White House no honor
Regular basis
Autoweek
Epaces communicate with your elective
Employees
And let him know that you know January 6th
What's not in any
Directions
It was not
Pearl Harbor
And it was not 911 it has
Nothing to do with any of those horrific events
I don't think this little rat make
Makes a lot of sense
911 or Pearl Harbor
Insurrections however
Ted is currently talking to a guy who thinks both of those things were false flag
Horrific events
From January 6th
Nugent a f****** a****** but this strategies probably ineffective want to put pressure on the GOP politician
It does seem like bullying g into denying reality is
Been shown to work
So I wouldn't be too surprised if overtime
We don't end up seeing an entire political
Cool party that's fully embrace
Is that conspiracy version of January 6th you need to do
To prove
To our elected
Did politicians that this was a
School
Demonstration
Is to violently intimidate them until they agree with you either harass the shoes you need to really
Get into their faces
Maybe even commit a little violence
Take a turn for the worse in this club
No actually without him
Because I'm speaking in riddles
For me I think
Carlson or the model of America
You're just populist believe our basic rights and freedom
Unified people around all that
Ted Cruz
Chucky Schumer the Democrats
They're also Ally
Is super dangerous
If we know the Democrats or bad but if we didn't have Republican
Continually stabbing Us in the back
We would turn this country around what's your view on that
Ted Nugent
How do we create a populism in America.
You got me alright
Can you punch his phone backup for me in her
Are you sure you can hear me
I'm having phone system issue in here
The truth
We shall know
It doesn't report to a biking
That's shocking because I mean like the phone problems
Whatever a remarkable about this Tech glitch
Is that
Alex is like
It keeps cutting off
He said whenever he's trying to talk
End up going out
And then just him
Just leave
Not even
Like it's maybe his mic was off when he screamed that he's going off to rebroadcast for nothing
Yeah do anyway he leave
That was that was a f******
70s
That was
What's his name
To be the one-sided phone
I'm terrible what's the point of knowing if you're saying who's the person who's similar to Bob Hope
I'm going to let you go on that one I think it's time to that's not on home comedy
Alex comes back
And he's got that explained that he had phone is
Switch.
We know
Going on here
I only seem to happen
In clusters
It's been happening as you saw earlier in the week with my cutout
It's this system right here I was talking to Ted during the break
Hit the button
People building
I just learned not to argue
Hello
Just not doing it not happening Alex is known for not doing that amateur bulshit
5 minutes
I only did that for two and a half minutes but also I would say
More amateur is
Screaming at everybody last storming out
Yeah it's
I don't know if you take the high road on
Professionalism
That boat has sailed my friend
Chabad Alex is a competent broadcast
That's what we all know
God do you got it all figured out
Ted Nugent's gun phones still aren't working
But Alex
Who's Mike is back
And you've got the big news to report
Today
1 + 70
Private school
1 and 70 vaccine instead December microdot is
Her dad is at a private Children's Academy in Calif
Estimate
So first things first
Stephen Curry is not a pathology
He's a guy whose background doesn't
Computer science who lost
This f****** mind during the pandemic
He's pretending to be a pathologist selling dangerous bulshit to the segment of the media that a Critic
Thinking
Like Alex
But based on the story on Infowars just
Open case ain't the only link
But it has in this entire article
Is just to Steve kirsch's sub
Stack block
This is legitimately becoming one of the primary places Alex's pulling covid
Conspiracy content from
Like so much nonsense just traces back to that blog
To the Post
Substack has links to exactly zero primary sources
There is none
Nothing
Your
With your tone of voice is suggesting that that's a bad
But it goes to a previous article that curse wrote on his blog
Proof of any of his clients but instead relied on reporting based on something someone told him
Allegedly apparent
And told him the three children at Monte Vista Christian
I've been diagnosed
With myocarditis
I'm not saying that this didn't happen but I am
I am saying that this is something that you need to do some more leg work on if you're going to report it as a definitive claim
This is sloppy
But this it gets so much worse
So the ratio and literally every
Conclusion the curse comes to is just the result
Him guessing things
From the original post
Roughly half the Schooler boys
There is no never been a vaccine mandate at the school
So I'd estimate conservatively the two-thirds of the kids
Could have been vaccinated by that
So 855 / 2 * 2/3
His 200
85 vac
Vaccinated boy
So the rate of myocarditis at the school by my estimate is three out of 285 which is
Is 1 and 95 boys
That's me original article
They didn't have an updated because he's heard of 1/4
I've never been so shaken to my core
Damn that type of evidence
0 guessing dad
Three children at myocarditis he can't demonstrate that vaccination rate
He's even just guessing with the roughly half the Schooler boys thing
This 195 number means legitimately nothing he can't back this up at all
So then
His new post is about how he's quote
Heard that there's another case of myocarditis at the school which of course would make it one in about 70 using the same made
Numbers that he used before
It's hard to believe that someone could write a blog post like this and hit publish without feeling
Intense embarrassment
Listen to this utter horseshit
These are just the cases we know about
There could be other cases that we simply don't know about it because the families decided not to
To tell anyone
There could be subclinical cases where the damage is being done so slowly over time
And I bet
The boys of myocarditis are all recently vaccinated what a coincidence
Something happened and then say it's a go with what a coincidence
Clue that this isn't just bad luck
Which is not what you did prove
Bingo
Doesn't know what the vaccination rated the school is but he's decided that all of the alleged
For children who he's heard got myocarditis
This must be recently vaccinated
Richie condescendingly
Here's here's what I'm happy about
Alright
Local news has been dying
So I'm grateful at least one person is on the only one private school in California beach
Okay those Street
I would argue he's not a bad job of pounding that one
Nobody
Local news
Okay fair
He's not going to get a job with some
Sinclair tell you that right now
We contacted the deed of the school who said that they don't just give out medical information about students to random people
Which of course proves that this is a conspiracy and a cover-up
Everyone's in on it from the administration to the parents
Most of the parents apparently agree with the secrecy
They could speak out but chose not to say a word to anyone outside the community
Even the parents of the injured kids are remaining silent
Why not speak out
It reminds me of the fairy tale The Emperor's New Clothes all my God
Silent did the right thing
To do here
Suppose half the school died after taking the vaccine
What the school say nothing
They could save hundreds of thousands of lives worldwide if they spoke out and others followed their lead
It would destroy the credibility of the CDC and freak people out of their hypnotic
Plants doing whatever the CDC says
Wow
I a weirdo Without A Child Called up with school and ask for all of the kids social
Security numbers
And the school wouldn't give them to me does that mean they're working with the governments and honestly like
This sounds like it's written by a f****** angsty teenager
Coat of this is
So first of all unprofessional
Football chest
Whining
It's it's embarrassing I wouldn't give it a high-grade if I were great
No theories about why nobody is talking out no other.
How come you have fairies
How to clear conspiracy
So the first is that some alleged students at the school told him that the
B-school administered vaccines on April
30th
To the school
Must be afraid of getting
Sued
Apparently curse went on to bother the dean about
Quote
She stated in an email to me on January 5th that quote Monta Vista Christian School has never administered covid-19
Vaccine students or anyone else
Monte Vista Christian School has never hosted
At its real property or anywhere else
Any clinic or other event that which covid-19 vaccine
Where's my booster
Okay that means someone's lying why would the kids lie about that
Isn't that a spoon
Get the f*** out of here manojob
His other theory is a parents don't want to hurt the school and think that God will heal the the stew
This is primary source Alex is using to report at this
Conspiracy claim
It's nothing new really but this is particularly shity work
Suppose Maxine Clinic
At the school allegedly had on April 30th like
If that was when the students
Supposedly got vaccinated
Why is in the face of curses other made-up point about how they were all recently vaccinated with you'll remember he made up early
All this stuff that he's making up isn't internally consistent
The claim is going all over right with media and social media and the only support I can find for it in all of the articles is
This stupid blog post written by a grown man who sounds like a tween
These people are reporting this story based on this they should be deeply ashamed
Themselves they've done no
Checking in on the source or they're willing
The stand behind this stupid blog post
Can I find that accept
I got to say
I'm sorry I don't mean to
Keep it up
I find
That overtime
I have a very different
Kinship to a couple of Alex
Yes okay like sometimes
I find them abhorrent
Kind of funny
Like a Leo zagami
Sagami is crazy he did 9/11
All-time Hall of Fame
The pope is Jesus
He did 9/11
He's got it all
Obviously there's problems
I disagree with him on about everything
Back to an older time of Illuminati
Vatican conspiracy
Kind of with 70's house music at the same time I kind of can put up with Leo zagami
We can have an uneasy truce
Steve Kerr
I hate
I hate this dude
Happy pig personalized blog poorly-written
Information that he's putting out
Is Sophia
Do undocumented
Allows people like Alex
Sensationalize it even further
+ 8
It's just deeply dangerous
I think
It's really hard for me to joke
Even about how bad
Because I recognized
The dangers that are inherent
In it
And that makes me not enjoy
Covering his s***
Yeah his maybe Leo zagami
I mean
It sucks me up the most
Whenever it is this kind
Situation where you go back in your like there's really only this one dude who is saying this s*** and everybody's just running with it
What f**** me up about that is just like
That is
He's such a
Positive reinforcement type reward
For just
Gall
Just having the gall to say something
This.
When the straight face
Is rewarded
Beyond Your Wildest Dream
That's f***** up
That's not that's not good or not is like let's put that inside even just like
People
Do it
Making so many assumptions in terms of justifying
The claim that you want to make
Supposed to get in the actual information
That you can verify
I think that
Did the rewarding of that is got it
Give you all kinds of endorphin rushes if you're that guy why wouldn't you do it again
Underworld dumbass up stack I'm sure
So Alex talked about this a little bit more and
This is just
Pathetic
On Wednesday
Proceed report
From a concerned parent
Fourth student at the
Monte Vista Christian School
In Watsonville
Been diagnosed
Personality
Documented cases
At the school with an enrollment of about 855 students
Last month
Go to the beginning there Alex's correcting
Because he had said
Steve Kerr shoes
Apologist and now he's saying
So it's not apathy not a pathologist
But I want to still a liar
No wearing purses articles is he covering anything that a pathologist told
That is a loadable
Also Alex is reading an article from his own website that was written by a dawn Salazar
Does say that Steve Kerr's is a pathology
It's so weird
Almost like a Don wanted to try and give these stupid claims more weight by lying about
Credentials
Also another major Point here is that curse has in no way documented any of these
These cases
He's heard a rumor about them and he's repeating that rumor
But this isn't documented or proven in the
Every element of hikers report to the
The story is an attempt to create certainty out of
Insinuation
And then when Alex and a dawn cover
His blog post
They do the same thing all over again
Any point where it kind of becomes clear that curse
Blog post doesn't prove anything
It's fudge
In order to make it
Looked it up
Adan calls him a pathologist
Alex accidentally does because he's just reading add-ons article but then he realizes he can't justify saying something like that
3 scale the Pakistan get the second hand from a pathologist
These cases are documented
It's all intentional
Most of the stories
Meetup by Steve Kirsch
Or just things he's assumed for no reason
But it helps push the narrative in 4th profits from pushing so it's critical to keep the audience from realizing
But this is Steve
Curse fanfic
Which is why they dress it up like it's actual reporting
Stupid this is actually getting people killed
Because otherwise dunking on it could be good clean
Fun yeah
How much does it cost to
Subscribe to that
I mean it's like $10,000 you got
I don't know if there's like a premium subset but I was able to find this article for free I don't know what he's
Doing all boy
So Aaron Rodgers
Got a job
Quarterback quarterback Aaron Rodgers
Very beautiful
Football football
And this is a tension
He's a bum Aaron Rodgers calls out NFL MVP voter
Texas social credit score
Who's the best player
It's about to be submit
To the social
Credit score
That's what the
Do social credit score that Alex has been screaming about is
Who's the guy
When was some kind of like codified and centrally run
Something where the government takes points away or gives points based on your behavior
That's a pretty scary but I'm not sure I even care about the prospect of people making moral decisions when they're voting for the NFL end
Let me tell you something I hope Alex never hears about the Hall of Fame and Barry Bonds oh boy really out of hand
I'm sure you would care a lot
Probably if you actually think about Alex's saying than anyone
Actually on their conscience is kind of an instance of the social credit score
That's weird
Imagine a situation where a guy was running for a County Treasurer position
He's awesome but the actual work being a treasurer
Unfortunately
He's also pretty public about his belief that white people are superior to other race
What are voting against him because of that be
The social credit score company absolutely what you treasurer
Just let me do the treasury job I really don't even understand
Buy the stuff anymore like it
It's it's
It's so thin to the point of its
It's on Define
Why the picture in my head of a government system but now that he's saying that it's just
Something as meaningless as MVP voting
I am really lost
Also I can make a very strong argument that even if Rodgers is
The best football player in the NFL season
Him being an open anti-vax weirdo in the middle of a pandemic kind of reduces his value as a player
It may take him out of the running for most valuable player in my mind
I would rather have a quarterback is just slightly less good at football than him but it also isn't
The total a****** is probably going to get a bunch of my team's fans killed
I think I would have more value and having something at someone like that on my team than Eric Rogers
Man I wonder if I wonder is NFL stat people have tried to
Put that together like
Aaron Rodgers
Infected like a dove
His teammates
What is wins above replacement value subtracted by them being gone for a few games
Because of him you know what I'm saying we got to get the fantasy nerd father how much damage Rogers
Into his team by spreading the disease
Most Valuable Player commits a lot of difference
Thanks a lot of consideration
Highway this is all convoluted nonsense Alex's rambling about but it's cool to see that he cares a lot about football now
Super call him
Constantly talk about dumb football isn't a distraction
Divert men's insta
Think towards War absolutely because they want to fight the globalists
Feminize an entire generation
But I guess it matters a lot now that's
It's super boring Aaron Rodgers doesn't like Alexa
Fun
So I'm sorry I can't
I'm still struggling sometimes whenever we get to those
Different steaks
One Clip ago
Everyone's going to die from the vaccine next clip
Somebody's not voting for Rogers for.mvp
This is also a big probably wait till we get to the 7th
Is a roller coaster crazy
There's a massive Riddle That I can't wait for you to try on the ramp angle on the 7th
Alright another bit of a riddle hear that Alex
It gets it he's trying to introduce this clip
Of Robert Kennedy Jr
Who's
Talk about wife how she wants to back to
Peopleshare
Bourbons go off the rails
Robert Jr explains why salty is
Crime and Scandal end of a shelf butt
That's only one level
This is not about money
Drug rep for the company has the people following directives it's all about money
But for the group's above it it's about sterilization depopulation
Playing God
What they say
They want to merge with silicon to become gods
Only way to do that
Enough people these shots
And then test what's happening and see
What
Play what
Immortal cell lines
Emergency biological Immortal cell line
With a human
Synthesis
That is able to merge
Where did these nanotech
Synthetic
Matrix's
Alright
That they admit all this was carrying a lot of water
Put your weird move on Alex's part to play clip of Robert Kennedy Jr talking about how fat you wanted to vex
Snakeheads
Introduces it by saying that the clip you're about to listen to actually it isn't
I'm through
Tickets of Alex's goal is to make Kennedy's argument looks saying in comparison to his own
This is not a good job of that
Okay
Alright so yeah
I mean obviously for the CEOs and
It's all about money
But they don't even know that what they're trying to
To do is combine so if I understand now the vaccines aren't even also about killing people it's about mad
Anticipated
Gene's can connect with a mortal
Cell line and I guess
Call people who are going to die just as a side effect of
I guess of The Killing
The population actually isn't the primary objective
It's trying to figure out whose bodies can I merge with it let me throw this out there
Is there a chance that one or all of us a bunch of us might have those perfect genetics and then you know
Well now they're probably kill you
And take yourselves
I forgot man every tired so I was listening to take it real slow
One thing I noticed for sure that Alex is struggling to figure out how to emphasize
It's fascinating how you can
Feel the gears moving in his head knowing that what he saying is
Bulshit word salad but
Still trying to figure out a way to not sound like he's making it all up for sure
Matrix's
It's kind of like seeing
Somebody try and adjust well falling the air
It's basically the albino lion.
For the globalist
Relaxing about sterilization depopulation
Playing God and engaging in quote mad scientist
This Behavior did you think should be
Honestly though so far so good
I'm not
But I don't think we're off the rails yet
The plan is to merge with silicon and become Gods which I don't believe is anyone's playing but I'll allow it so we can move forward
However
How does merging with silicon make one a god
I guess there's a possibility of like it wouldn't die of old age maybe but that's not the only future you need to be a god
I don't think
I think you should probably be able to lift
Help your muscles
Emergency
I believe that Alex think
What's the vaccines contain like AI nanotech robots
So this is all a big
Take test to see whose bodies
You can merge with the vaccines and then from this they hoped
Define immortal
Cell line the converge
With vaccines cuz that'll help them
Merge with Gaston
Google auto nonsense and for one thing I really don't think Alex has any understanding of what an immortal cell line is
I suspect that he actually
I just felt never died actually the Mortal selves last for
Wherever there's a limited Supply you have to pay
Each one individually out if you want to do an experiment
One of your things like this I really wonder if the listeners recognize how ilex keeps adding
New wrinkles to his
Conspiracies
I have the plans of the globalist seems to change
Constantly but like
I hope I didn't I say it like
They all it dammit all that
Man the way he ended that sin
And two would like those
The last four words were just shopping
Not sure where he's going to land and then finally he was like
No one's going to buy that s***
That's cuz I'm just saying they admitted it so no one's going to believe this b*******
To hear some of you like citations but Alex provides
Little fish
Mention some of this earlier
Oh look
Technology wants Levi Global Elites will save you
60 minutes
Can we become gods
It goes on from there
The headline about human history ending when people become Gods isn't some kind of an evil statement
Threat
It's a headline of an interview from 2017 with an Israeli historian named Yuval Noah Harari
It's basically trying to just discuss his new book
Homo Deus
Which argued that with the Advent of technology that we've created
I was beginning to wield powers that we previously described only
Like the ability to create life
You speaking in a somewhat poetic way to express that when we are able to create inorganic life like a sentient AI
We can quote go to
The Earth Spirit and say what do you think about that
We're equal to
The spirit we understand
Not you
Ferrari has some very interesting thoughts
This is a futurist Theory and he's definitely not saying that humanity is going to end
Just it will take on an entirely new
With the world around us
That has been the case
Since human history has begun
Who's the meeting with Citation for the argument Alex
Macon
Interesting Lee the other headline from 60 Minutes is another interview with Yuval Noah Harari
From 2021 both interviews with dispatch
Is Ray Kurzweil not said anything freaky for Alex
Upset about lately
Futuristic is secretly telling everyone what's coming
Wild Alex's they admit all this
Guess what he's actually saying is that he has a couple Sensational headlines for articles
About interviews with a futuristas making predictions about where technology is going
Susan admitting anything in the things that are being predicted aren't even in line with Alex
Cuz bulshit
Stupid yeah that's
That's I mean
Fine
Some guy said something
And I'm like what
Totally
I'm Blown Away by
Okay
Is
One of the weirder things I've heard
Quite a while so we had a five-year anniversary
Kind of
Weird in a way that's a little different than our usual weird
Familiar themes website
Listen to this s***
Imagine how excited I was when I heard them
Alright next person
World
American Eagle
Horton
Ian
The world in the reason that's important is
You understand information
Understand
Everything else this is a Rosetta Stone
If he is
This is the understanding of everything if you can understand this
Ironic ass
The it's a mirror and that you are the most popular Time Magazine
Yeah I kind of thought there was a chance that was what was going to happen
Your guesses
And I'm not going to say yes or no I'm not going to give it away cuz it's a fun game
Alex is going to announce the most important person in the world
It's
Here's some clue that okay
Person in the world
Oh really Hamming it up to huh-uh
It's why we're going to reveal
Why
Person is the most important
Persona world
Soon as the most important
Curtain
Important person in the world
Understands that
The New World Order
So the most important person in the world does not know that they're the most important person right right right
I mean I would like a little bit more parameters on that do they know that they are an important
Person or do they just not know that they're important at all doesn't really clarify but we can say for sure that they don't know
They're the most support
We have week
Cross one person off the list, it's Starbucks
No
Still could be
Novak Djokovic
Courtney park in the world
And the spirit of what he's doing
Is the essence of what we're about to
Is it a little question who this motion
Call Joseph Watson has happening in the land of tyranny
It's not Djokovic
Well that's good
Cuz I do think Djokovic
I believe he is the most important person in the world
What he's doing
Requesting
A place where he can
Train
They like
He's not asking to not be in like a quarantine
He's just asking for a quarantine where you can
I'm praying for the
The open you want the Billionaire's quarantine
Basically I don't know why Alex
Labeling data hero
But whatever
I mean I assume that
These labeling got a hero because right now they're keeping Djokovic in a notorious Refugee Hotel
That have
Has been the housing people for upwards of eight years
And what was very funny is that the pro Djokovic protesters
We're right next to the anti-refugee protesters
And they were like
Hey man
Guess what else
These guys are protesters were like this problem first
Expected
They were like fuk Djokovic
People trapped in there Frankie
Chucky videos
It was amazing
It was a huge surprise
So
What is
Less on expect
Is it Alex
Get sidetracked before he tells us who the most important person in the world
Nothing more frustrating than knowing we have
Cancers and the key
To defeating this evil takeover and stopping at dead diss tracks
But instead I just can't get people conscious
Focused Eye Care
Get the message
Ashley
Finally finished
That means we're going to go along hellish nightmare
Most people listening and watching will be dead in 10 years
He's sworn to kill you and your family
Lockdown shutdown
Brown cyber shutdown
Completely been totally overrun on the streets
Electricity
Who's the most important person in the world Miami
I mean I don't know muscle memory him doing these rats
Come on man
You started this off
Beauties
You can't you can't do this to me
Djokovic
Well if it's
5 years old
Then I suppose
It is
It's probably still Netanyahu right cuz he was the canary in the coal mine
And it's time to pray
Right it's not
I can't slip
It's not that guy
But I'm not going to say yes or no to any further
Possible person
Alright I'm pissed off
Because
I have this weight on my shoulders and I know I'm right
I know it's going down
Documents
Comfort zone
The enemy's going to win
Because they're going to
Criminal Society while posing as the saviors the whole time
Go to deliver the most important information ever
Wow okay
There's one thing people aren't in right now it's their f******
Comfort zone
That's opposite
For most people know I don't think of any people are in there
Alex has dark many times in his career but have his job is to wake people up out of the transit
That's why he yells and has a gravelly voice instead of the soft-spoken
Kinfolks at MPR
You're trying to lull you to sleep
Steak and Shake you out of that
Sleep course
When I'm looking for someone to admire I can
Tell you that it's going to be the person who gives themselves
The job of beagle
Can wake people up to the globalist blocks around them
Only to lament that they can actually wake people after the globalist plot surrounding
When Alex is he can't get people to wake up isn't
Sleeping person
Asphalt
It's that there's something wrong with the person yelling at them to wake up
What Alex says stuff like this I just hear him saying
I can't do my job which is imaginary to begin with
Woohoo
Now it's important
That we
Never
Take responsibility for our own actions
Or hold anyone responsible for their
That's what is
He's going to move us
I will say though I'm excited to hear what the most important information ever is
I mean
Got to be something really
Deflating
Constantly builds things up to be the most
Important information ever or house
Reset Wars with the most important work he's ever done and then it's always a bust
It means nothing to do with him.
Maybe people are sick of the bulshit
I can't say f****** if it's raining.
In the world to reveal
Go to deliver the most important information ever
People actually understand
All the southern credible news I've got in front of me it's very important
You's a byproduct
V
Disease that is the New World Order
Window dressing
Oh God
We're not going to find out who the most important
Thursday
Everywhere you remember where I was when I was doing stand-up you know
Sometimes
To keep things interesting or keep things fun they bill at we be like you know what
I'm just going to do none of my picture I'm just going to do nothing but crowd work tonight
And then maybe you keep a clock
Can somebody and be like I usually do
210 out of 20 exactly
Has anybody ever put Alex on a clock
For like how long he can just
Build something up for it you know like how many segments
Can you go just saying nothing
But how
The next thing you're going to
And you can't even do your job anymore
I mean he would he would
Solo
Yeah brutal see if he actually does
I mean obviously
That's for sure
You can restart the show lineup
Nasty stuff
We got a lot of really good reports here
That was a really really important
Was it
Grieve are something we've already aired because I can't do my job
Wow
Admirable
I mean you know I like
I've sometimes been emotionally incapacitated to the point where I cannot do my job however
I tried it
Not do it while I was doing my job
You know what I'm saying
I totally understand people needing to call in sick or take a me day
Totally totally
Think it's worse if you go to your job and then
Complain about how you need to take a me day
The purpose of what your job is
Can you throw a hatchet at the wall you're in trouble
Yeah that's not good
No I was going to go walk around the parking lot
Recent report around the parking lot
And that's that so
My God will be back I guess after this break
I want to show you today
Infowars.com
Mom and dad, still be there
I just doesn't
Shelterbuddy
Wow what an intro
What It intro for Gregory
Goddamn
You just don't get it other place
There's nothing
Corporate
That will allow you to do that you're fired
That you don't get you don't get multiple those
You get one of those in that you're gone let alone is happening over and over and over again
And honestly I think I would be
He totally bored of this if it wasn't within the context of him teasing who's the most important Friday so funny
I just don't I just don't know how you
I mean
An actual broadcaster honored to be like I got to go walk around the parking lot
I guess what you all deserve to die earn to die before I said that
Comes back
Tries to restart
The show everybody shouldn't he's going to get to who the most important personnel
Who is the most important person in the world
Start of the show I told you I'd come back and do it
I told you you all deserve to die
Here's a problem that it's harder Harmony the show
My knowledge base is very
Everything I look at every
Jeep multi-faceted and multi-dimensional understanding of it
Not going to reveal the most important person
Complain
His job because he's so smart it hurts that is
I mean
Yeah I mean wow amazing wow just wow
It's that
Good stuff
Really you're going to look me in the face
And tell me why
He's not going to look you in the face cuz there's rules against session 2
But he is going to tell you I'm so smart it hurts
Apple Home Improvement related
Japan
Can talk over
So Alex
Manslaughter
He just needs
To be able to say the right words
I quit
That was great
Logos already
The way he's describing like
His
To do when you don't know.
Defeat the globalist it almost sounds like he's like if I can get the spell right
The word order in the incantation correct
It will work
This is just
Ridiculous
My mind and
Moment of understanding all those points I want to make
It all just dissipates like
Gas
Into The Ether
Explain the song
Will grasp also absorbent and understandable
More frustrating
Don's because you are weak about myself
Killing everybody enjoying
I can't say a fun doing all the time
For the children
Who's the most important person you are a fucken monster
Do you understand this
He will defeat the globalist
That this is the most important person in the world are we in right now
It was a short walk there's a parking lot
But we're still
A fool
This is at least 45 minutes into the show
No problem I'm probably alright
Okay
No it's multiple segments
This was supposed to be done already
So much
Yeah okay
Gases
Warrior heads
I mean you know I've obviously I think my guess right now I'm sticking with Rand Paul
But that also seems really dumb
Which is also why I kind of think it might be true
Paul a little bit more
These are trying to bully him
Right so that kind of would be somebody
It could also be somebody who's like the most important person in the world
Target
This is the most important person in the world
And if they're the Domino that
Making out
See now that's fascinating because there are multiple
Simple ways that you could interpret most important
Justin Bieber I'll just say don't worry about that okay
We are
This will pay off
Schlafly
Is she dead
Appraisers about your I have to look up is Ray Kurzweil was dead
Abstract report
Oh my God if it's Betty White that's going to be beautiful
I can't say
Alright so here's a list of Alex comes back is a little big
The most important person
In the world today
I know
Understanding where we're going
Real quick
I know you're yelling about cuz it's frustrating it's a little bit frustrated how repetitive
Little bit of a thick skin buildup because I know how repetitive his bulshit is over and over again
But in this case
Incredibly grating
Adenoids
It's almost paradise in it no it's
18 more infuriating comparison to be putting this off
Protests
Too much does not even come
Close to cover
Who is this
Elon Musk
Is it
Maybe is it
Maybe
The current pope
Give five more exam
Novak Djokovic
Who is it
Who is the most truest in the most understandable way
Kraneshares left and right
Can actually speak to people in a human
Don't tell me it's f****** Joe Rogan
On this planet
You know the answer to
The rest of the story
Wow this is
Getting to bees moving it around a little bit now means
Like communicating
I don't know
Look
The riddle
Did the Grand River
I know
Is someone important because they were
President of the United States
Yes she's someone important because
Movies are handsome
What you got about Brad Pitt
That is
Somebody the most important
So where you define who the most important person is
Says to you are there's a big study
Is that the more celebrity-obsessed you are the lower your IQ and the less money you make
The more you believe in the system
The more you go along with its propaganda
The more disease and dumb down and poor you are
What get to the point what are we talkin
Well that study would like a Hungarian
Study
Small guy couldn't even if it doesn't even
Cloosiv
You being a causal relation
Celebrities in
Whatever
How much is Just obsessed with going off on side bars
Just like this
Right now
Talkin about this study and celebrities being dumb
Or this
Did you see the establishment wants you to be alone to be dumb
2B disease in Dodge
Garbage
Consciously is garbage
What
You're ugly Hubbell in your ugly face and your ugly kids in there do you finally be free cuz you won't be
Be around
And just because you got the general mass of people dumb down not aware out going to get themselves
Globalist
Crap all over other
You talkin about you man
So I ask you again
Who is the greatest living person in the world has the greatest
Potential
This is such a mess
Alex has been
Teasing rambling is whole episode so far about a healing with the most important person on earth is but now he's moving the
Apparently now it's the greatest person on Earth are the person with the most
Potential to empower Humanity
Alex thinks those things are interchangeable that's fine but it also speaks
To his subjective beliefs
Someone else could easily believe the most
Important person and the person has the most potential
Are two different people
Like you touched on a very strong argument could be made that you can make these separate
Most important person could actually be a force of evil
Important to the volume neutral concept so if you were terrifying dictator who was working against
Cause of Empower Humanity
You are a threat to everyone that person could easily be the most important person in the world
It's interesting
To see how disorganized Alex's thoughts are even about this
Clearly intentional
I mean I just get caught up whenever
We are gone they'll finally be savings like Alex you think whenever you get rid of all of
You just talked about you man that was you it was you dude
What happens when your enemies are imaginary and their plans are things you imagine them doing
It is
Coming from inside the house
So Alex
Dipset explaining his criteria
For what makes a person
The most important
See now I've done now I'm interested is a little bit helpful
A somebody's movie star
Somebody play football
Earbuds
Give give you
What you did in the in the corrupt system
How much you care about you married
Northstar
Is my
Expelling us out and laying out with his criteria for the most important person in the world
Who doesn't make it
Clear of
Make it clear to me that this is a subjective
Canyon Alex has
Does really mean anything when ever he gives this honorific
Title it just means Alex
Likes this person
Yeah I mean
Really when he said he's going to clarify what it takes
To be the most
Important person
And he's just created more Quest
Directions for me to ask about what it is his new subjective measurements
Actually me
Well I think that you should
Keep in mind but also throw it right the f*** out the window
Cuz Alex
It's shifting around a little bit
Who's the most famous who's the richest that's not the winners
What is the proper demanding
A lot of snacks to get you mad
Real
Focused
Christ-like way balanced
Who's the most
What
Is the most important
So I guess now the most important
Person title that Alex is giving out his really better described as
Person disseminating ideas that Alex likes who is also not a well-known lunatic or bigoted so they fly on
Under most people's radar
Is that how we describe the most important person
So who do deer make other gases
Is it cuz we're getting more information
Now that the bar is set so low I almost want to say
James O'Keefe or something to draw Spyro
That's enough
James O'Keefe
Now give me another game
I want to try and get a galaxy of thought
I mean
God I'd want to say it's Steve pieczenik but I just can't
I just can't
Alex's
That time I was going to last a little bit longer then
Is it even worse is that curse himself is it at shity sub stack that's most important person in the world
Alex
Isn't reading actively a Steve Kerr's headline he forgets who he is
But also interesting Lee
Another
Steve's are terrible on a Corolla
Gerbils on a Wire
Maybe this will help you out there's a couple more clues
It's about the most important
Who's the most important
Humans going to be a model for us
Because Sinead O'Connor music
We are that person we realize that
We have the key
Destiny
Because I've seen it
Understood
First tell you about the person
This person does not want to be president of the United States person cannot stand Hollywood
Okay
Slime
I wanted I want to tell you something
Yeah
I actually knew who it was
Immediately
I thought I did
Do the only person who knew immediately okay
I don't want to Pat myself on the back too much
Locate time there's a new clue if you can no no I don't
I doubt
Play this game because I don't get to know the answer in advance
You know what I'm saying but I think if I didn't know the answer I'd still have a couple of thoughts
CG my hat because when you have those around your head I'm not behind you being like
Trying to embarrass you
Alright
Here's some more clues
This person cannot stand New York
Hollywood rich people
You don't want to hang around with the system they don't want to be embraced by the system
Are disgusted
By the system
Schmidt
Turner Ted Turner
Depopulation
Islamic side of Patriots now
This include him because of all the talk about billionaires
But he's a blue blood
True I mean
But that makes me think it's Tucker Carlson
Maybe this will help
We can disclude 1 /
John F Kennedy junior he still alive
Alex isn't going to publicly comment on that
Elon Musk just not the most important person in the world
Agree
You so precious
The most potent
Person in the world
Can you understand that it is now moving towards that
Crochet gravity
We didn't learn the secret
I will tell you when we come back
Motherfuker
The most important person in the world
We must recognize
From amongst our people
Who is the best
Promoting Humanity
Take on
Somewhere between
Sacrilegious at this point
To do the Andy Daly podcast pilot
Project
The episode where they did the the long story
This is exactly like the moment whatever the cop
Who is the most
Dammit
What's your job I shall
What do you do when you go to work
I shelled shrimp
Fuchsia
Yeah
It is a little bit little bit
Playing handball with the curtains as they say you like trying to figure out like right who is this person
After the break before he goes to break
Sacrilege
Come back I'll tell you who
Most important person
In the world is
I want you to understand it
Burning yourself
Ask yourself
Is this true to God the Holy Spirit
And it has the same thing I am you'll get the answer back
Absolutely
Like this is the example for all of us
We got it we got it
Live like
This person who's the most important person in the world at the mold ourselves after them because that's what God wants us to do
So I assume it's
Jesus Christ
Otherwise this weekend
A Little Bit Stronger
I never even considered
Did I take it that was who Alex's going to say
What I was listening
Nope not at all
Rebecca break and Alex is going to
Give other people some bad news
You are not the most important person
Long and hard about this and
I know I'm right
Who is the most important person in the world. Donald Trump Kate McKinnon
Which wake boat
President
Is Russia the largest landmass in the world
I could be at but he's not.
Would he have gotten like a letter
From somebody if you just said Russia
And not Russia
The largest landmass of the world
I think he just likes to and I'm watching this
British Bake
Michelle and like
Decoration is important presentation is
I can understand
Beginning anywhere closer
Nope
No Boris Johnson
Peacefully
Rebelution
Then we can really have a future
A real shot at
With Russia and China
The Middle East
I know
Who's done the best clean professional
Level-headed job
Some of the thing to tell me
I understand that
Knows this person like Ron DeSantis or something
Is it is it one of the shittier GOP house members is it like
Kevin McCarthy or something
Can you imagine the middle of course not
Jim Jordan the f****** hilarious
All right we have one last
442 rovito
But this one actually Alex
Completely shift what the
The Pointe Apartments
Who is the most
Most important thing in the world
Forget the world populace I was waiting for it
What's common sense
Codswallop
Common law
Who's the greatest populist of them all
So now it's who's the greatest populist
It's most important person
The greatest
I mean I'm going to go with roots manuva
No
I want to say that you have been done Dirty by Alex
Amber you have already said the name of the person
Guess before it's revealed that I have said
I'm going to I'm going to disqualify Sinead O'Connor
Good call
I bet the only one
You don't know who is it
Well
Who's the greatest populist of them all
In America and his example around the world who's listen to in Japan
And in South Africa
Mexico
Who all over the world
World leaders
South America Brazil
Who do they talk about it and who's the unifying
Pro human future against the great reset the New World Order
Do you know who it is it's Tucker Carlson
Tucker Carlson definition
Person in the world I told you got done dirty
Joe Rogan me and then
I know but he was talking about who's the most effective
Cuz it for me it was either Joe Rogan or Tucker
But come on man
That's f****** b*******
I honestly I thought it was
I couldn't imagine
Tucker's too much
A dick I think he's
Exactly who Alex wants to associate himself with right now
But also like
I don't want to
But I ain't from the job it was Taco
F****** course
Second
Thought that I have is like Alex's so little to talk about on this episode 3 spending
Our building up to saying the Tucker is the most important person in the world
It shows so dumb
But God that's great that was refreshed me
That reinvigorated me on my you know I mean
A couple couple weeks ago Alex was talking about how the anger is just say it's all juice
That's what it is that's what fuels
This has been one of the more infuriating
Hours of Alex content in my entire life
That's what makes
I've traded muted my anger into for the people
As manifested through your engine
Great Plains
Alex talks a little bit about why Tucker
Get this little bit of a title
Somebody like Tucker Carlson
Nose
Zetas
Cruise
Got a talking point
Slenderman Dead from the establishment
Are preparing to claim that the American people
Stop and bring in martial law
And the lawyer
The bush minion
Please reposes is a patreon all these years
Who is a wolf
Has to be cut out
And destroyed
A populist
Tucker Carlson
Just
Forrest Gump
So it's all just a reaction to Tucker's interview with Ted Cruz
Irene
That is it is such a huge at that really is like a huge interview
The idea to me
Of being alive
The building
For the first time in my life and my entire political career really being afraid
That a mob with
Tear the walls down and kill me
And then a year later
To have to sit
Across from that
Whiny sniveling piece of s*** Tucker Carlson
And lick his feet
That is
I mean like in the body of me right now
I'm ready to kill Tucker Carlson if that was me
Ted Cruz I would have leaped across the table and started strangling him
You have to recognize how week
Ted Cruz news
Track record is pretty shity
But that's bad man
So Alex talked a little bit more about this that interview actually is slightly different take on it than you do
Terror attacks are coming
Trying to stop it
Fox News Republican
Stop putting up
Who is Mitch McConnell
Ted Cruz
Poison
Call yalom
System
When they better start
Charles is God
To get actual Free Will and have his own voice on Fox
Slip their what actually makes
Something to Tucker's the most important person in the world
It's the in Tucker Alex he's a person who actually has the ability to humiliate senators and essentially sway power
We're on the right wing
DC someone who if he can piggyback it Alex can use to re-establish the illusion that has any effect on the real
World
If Tucker can humiliate Ted Cruz and Alex pretends to be totally in line with Tucker and secretly his best friend
Then it's kind of like Alex inspired Tucker.
Humiliate Ted Cruz
Enough Alex is really the one
The power
This way politics
The final game for Alex to play and though I think it's
Stinks of desperation
It may well work a little bit for a while
There is no Central problem with this though and it's
People should ask themselves
If Tucker and Alex are such good friends and on exactly the same page
Why is Tucker never had Alex on any of his shows
Like lately on any of these
He has multiple shows you the radio show you how
TV shows
Why doesn't Tucker show up as a guest on Infowars periodically if they're couple of the very few comrades in this fight against
Possibly more bitingly why wasn't Alex interviewed for Tucker's documentary about January 6th
He was at the Capitol and clearly Tucker and no problem interviewing Shifty weirdos
We had Ali Alexander interviewed in it
The fact the Tucker seems to have a staunch resistance to being publicly personally associated with Alex
Show me something that causes the audience asked
Some salsa.
Is this this is Trump all over again basically
Pokemon allister show wants to
Kelly's book
In December 2015 and he never came back
He never publicly Associated himself with Alex and anyway
The narrative
We're on the same page came almost entirely from Alex's story
And in the end I think it's pretty safe to say that most of them were made up
Now looks at the jettison that mainstream avatar for him to live vicariously through but
Because Trump likes the vaccine
Seems like maybe Alex is trying to lean hard into glomming onto Tucker in order to preserve some
Image of relevance in the actual world
Also there's absolutely no chance that Tucker makes almost no money at all
According to CNN back
In 2020 he was making ten billion dollars a year largely based on the fact that he showed drugs
16% of the channels
Entire ad Revenue
That number probably went up a bit but maybe it's dipped sent
That's because one of his main sponsors was my pillow
A Mike Lindell might not be shelling out as much as money these days
If he was
Family fun
Salad Days
Yeah I mean with Tucker though that's that's
He's at that type of money that you don't eat
His salary 10 million dollars
It is not
Wrap it up
Like he owned
Part of fox
News he's got a billion dollars
Is an error to a two large Fortune so
Death
But you know it's not
Cialix an hour
About this
That was an amazing performance
Truly
There is
There's a part of me that respect
How hard
It's a commitment to a bad B
It's not
It's a commitment to imagine there's a difference between somebody who really muscles through for a bit that's
And then there's
Best glitches just like
Yes uou will keep saying failure after the break and then rambling about bulshit
Yeah I mean it's not Neil hamburger
No but
Boy it's
At no point
Time did he ever think man I got to stop doing this
I just got I just can't do this probably not and I think a big part of it too is that Alex
Keenly aware that
Like if I do this
Maybe
People will report on me doing
Our butter Tucker's the most important person in the world
Which
Associate me with him
And get me more attention and I
Exactly what he
Start stalking
Glisters understand
Pickup
Brazen. Carlson real estate Alex Jones
That's not what I did
He's just he's begging for them these headlines
Please
Subway map that's very sad very very
Enjoyment I had
Yeah and I think there's a reality
So you got to got to wrestle with but at the same time
Man fun
Very fun
You just got to leave the subject
Stop text man y'all make this up text Tech
It's just a
Simple rule
Alex is something I really weird
In this next clip that I think
I don't think he actually believes
Celebrate the people that tell the truth
We need to promote the pie
Populist
People that are fighting for your whatever gay marriage
Play human future. For everybody
Talk about group is attacking Mountain
Talks about
Humanity as a whole and believing in ourselves and coming together
Is the good guy
So if you talk about group
You're the bad guy or good
People all the f***
I put this together in 5 minutes
But boy there have been plenty of hate crimes against
Ladies and gentlemen
Because the leftist
Judges
And the leftist media
Atelectasis
Time and time again
Hugo free
Before election
Hear the lamp the saying if you're white especially
Bumper stickers
There social workers that ask him questions under desk or Mommy and Daddy
Because foster home especially of your blonde-haired
This little girl
She better be careful
Have the height
Use white people
Data minutes just
From five minutes of looking
Anarkali miscut that because
The Whitney says there's bumper
Stickers of it's okay to be white
The next thing he says is I'm going to make a shirt
Yeah
He doesn't care
It's a red herring when it's
Sort of non-whites
When it's proves that he is not erect
You know advocating
Sing for their outright
When it's white people
It's not really even a group
Bright or
The alternative
Is that Alex does a
Don't think that people who are not white
Are not part of the totality
Humanity
Alex kind of realizes
I spent an hour of my show
Doing that talker thing
I was bad
Wanted cover other thing okay
How do you spell all the time on that
Tech CEO on
White when they're Platformers exploding
I just got launched sound
Alicia's coming up next segment
Yeah so Jason Miller the CEO of get her used to be a part of
The Trump Administration
You got some
Flotillas to bring about
So many flotillas
Jason
Tossed about
Yeah this is just pathetic Alex's just trying to
Piggyback on what Rogue
Grove Transit
Fix a guitar
Welcome back ladies and gentlemen we have Miller with us she's American Communications
Advisor spokesperson
Presidential campaign
Marcia 21 Miller became a contributor
Newsmax Miller levings position
Trump spokesperson in 2021 to become the CEO The Social Network Jetter getter
Been on there a while at hundreds of thousands of followers
Friend Joe Rogan
Promoting in
Over there
Independent groups out there
Got the Joe Rogan stamp-of-approval so now we're going to promote it as well
Supposed to be this free speech
Platform bed
In December they kick Nick Fuentes off the site
Christ after that
Get her also banned user
Composing the word groyper
Because Fuentes his fans were posting too much about how he got kicked off
Also just after get her launch we should not forget that their API was so weak that hackers were able to scry
Personal information off a ton of user
They got hacked immediately
So also there's like the Stanford andradite Observatory cyber policy Center they did
A review of debtors operations
In August
They found some
Kind of
Some fun
Stopping and also some.
Fun stuff quote
Dinner markets
Itself is a non-bias social network where users are able to post content more freely than Twitter
In some ways however get her is more restrictive with content policy than the platform and contrast itself with
Example in the app but not on the website users were initially prevented from posting
Expletives
Presented with an error message of
Sorry we don't allow abusive work
You fundamentally don't understand your audit
Search
Abuse is the point
More troubling less funny
That this report also found quote
Very few if any mechanisms for detect
In spam
Violent content pornography and child exploitation imagery are present
Get her instead appears to be relying on community reporting model
Which has not proved
Successful
Essentially there is a program that
I can just
Entirely block
Images that are in the database
The child explode
Sites like
Twitter have that
Software horse
And there are
Crile images that are child exploitation images
That are in that dataset right are used by researchers like people at the cyber
In order to test if people are using that saw fryer
Use these tests images on Twitter and they were able to post them
Right but they don't have the sort of
Standard block
Right on this
So if I understand correctly their first thought was
No swears
And then their next thought was
Child exploitation
I don't I don't know if they would be saying it's fine but they didn't do the requisite steps that most people use in order to
Safeguard against the concept weird that somebody from the Trump Administration would just go off all half-cocked without a full
Support structure in Flames very strange
There's some fun stuff in this interview
Large question is like I do. You worked
For the Trump Administration why isn't Trump on guitar
That would be a big
Why is it Trump
Promoting gender
Dancer Alex and bedroll just be very blunt
Even before I formally launch get her I was in negotiations with
And obviously he has a big name
President Trump's ratings Gold Everything
Turns into something
Exciting
Big
Inga by sports franchise
Somebody else came along and made
The dealmaker and cheeks
Trump is buyable
The thing about
The person you want
To be your
Commander-in-chief
Chief is a cup
Complete lack of loyalty
In the face of a larger offer
Yeah
That's
Chest
America
Trumpets indoor Center vaccine how should water bug get her I mean
Free Speech platform
Except for the kicked off Nixon
Well
Pictures of Kelso
Proposition
Nobody is going to get canceled or sent to digital jail or
Algorithm
Making your political opinion
Pornography
Do not allow
Twitter
Taliban
What
Mention climate change
Then you can have free speech my dude all those things are widely discussed Twitter
Is climate change denial vaccine denial
Election denial
Spell
Yeah it's interesting the way that he's
Is defining free speech
No pornography
Whatever is the family site
Yeah yes that's no muslim
Extremism
But you're
Really going to just cater this to why text
Exactly that's what we're trying to say free-speech meeting white people only people who
Bird is Nick Fuentes because
You're running a website
Could get in trouble listen
We want a white supremacist website that doesn't have any overt
Supremacist on there we don't want to be storm fronts come on
Creepiest thing
That caters to people who kicked off Twitter but they were going to have to kick them off if they behave the way that they did when they got kicked off
Seems like you got a good business model got it
Anyway you also
Can't use
Some words
What is long
Is your able to
Control yourself and illegal activity
We're going to the racial and religious
Then what's free speech mean
What does it mean
To you
It just means that I can't say capitalism's bad that's what free speeches
I think I
I think
They want to be able to be in charge of
The social media platform
Be able to restrict
Things that they want
To the things that Twitter Caesars
Things I like things I don't like
I have thoughts
My notes
It's alright to be
Incredibly boring
Prospect
Wolf do not believe that this website is going to be
Over and over again
Parlor Gab
All this stuff the whole reason they like
Twitter is
Is because there are liberals for them to
To b**** at
To argue exactly
But if you put them alone they won't like it
There's no one to b****
That's the whole point they just recording at each other
Antagonize because that's
A sport
Yeah I know that's
The game absolutely we would love you to stay on better
Social media experience
It's 44 a lot of folks
Is
Based on trying to rile other people up
Because it's funny.
That's a whole thing and I think that sucks but
In a vacuum where it's all people trying to f*** with
Each other
It's just not as effective
Anyway you're so close to gutter
True
Choice
Alex
Alex comes back
He's quite a while interviewing
Get her
He's minding our talking
I've changed my mind about who the most
Important
Be steadfast on that
Batman
He is not done a whole lot on his show
Modeling hours
I got to talk about something
Warchant
I know a lot of ways to reach more people I know a lot of ways to get more information out
And yesterday I plug 30 seconds in
Not plugged
Everybody knows people don't do it again
Well I meant let's see
Entirely accurate I wasn't really paying attention but like
You don't get to give yourself credit for not blocking when you storm out
Yeah there is that
Really big
Long plug for Tucker Carlson really
So this is Alex
His response
Essentially to the news breaking
10 post
Sebastian Murdock released an article
That's a company financial documents
Turned over the process
Discovery
In the face of the Sandy Hook case
Alex Jones Infowars store made 106
55 million dollars over three years record
Show which is fair but it also leads to a number of inaccurate and possibly just Hasty conclusion that I'd like to touch on
Before Alex even gets into
The first thing is that this spreadsheet that I was covered in
In the story it only reflects sales number
This is nothing about profit or actual money brought in by Infowars above
Expenses
It's very unclear from the available information what kind of profit margin Alex has on these sales
The actual amount this money reflects Infowars bring in a number that's within a range
And it's really hard to determine where we are
Or inside that ring
That being said
Alex
He's making after the
Expenses
Still a very high amount of money
This number has 106
85 million so split up over the course of three years
And Alex probably has a massive overhead
Add from payroll to lawyers to business-related tank expenses
He also constantly runs
Free shipping
Specials
And there's a column in the spreadsheet that is sales shipping
Is that reflects
Some expenses he has to cover from free shipping
They could be looking at a decrease over 7.5 million dollars in this time.
The impression that I get from these numbers is that I actually would have
Expected them to
Higher
165 million actually seems low
Yeah based on
What what's going on
People don't engage in this kind of s*** head grifting that Alex does if it's not massively profitable
So I'm not sure that any of these sales figures really surprise me that much
Another thing that really confuse me about the discussions surrounding the spreadsheet is the impression that it was like the
The sudden massive jump in sales
In November 2015
The beginning of the spreadsheet is for September 8th
2015 and it shows $15 worth of sales
The next entries for October 5th 2015 which owes $81.90
Some sales
Which kind of implies that there weren't any sales in between
Then by late November you're looking at sales over 30,000 a day
It just goes up from there occasionally topping 100,000
Until April 2016 or
It's pretty routinely 100,000 per day
That pattern
Some people have suggested that he started making money on the shop around this time but that's just not pause
The Infowars store Viet primarily operated in for store.com or enforce shop.com
Is existence of at least 2010 and an article from 2010 Intex
Texas monthly
Discusses the claim from Alex that he made one point
Point five million dollars in Revenue
And sales from the store
In the past year
Inconceivable that he could be getting
Periodic sales of less than $100 a day
And some days apparently not bringing in any sales at all in this. Prior to September 2015
Then you have to consider the money bomb
Already did and it's done over the years with
Predate the time. This spreadsheet cover
Money isn't reflected anywhere
I can't
Prove this
But my best guess is that this Saturday to reflect the migration of sales to a different account than they were
Previously counted in
I can only theorize on this point but
This document begins
Literally at the exact same time
The 10% the owner of Midas resources in Genesis Communications
Which syndicate's Alex's show and was it
His primary sponsor was in court dealing with a case that would lead to him losing his license
So precious metals
Began on September 11th 2015
Announces money bomb in 2015 was on September 16th
Azerite it's very difficult for me to believe that this timing isn't a coincidence
Plausible to me
The prior to Ted's legal problems coming to a head
Their finances might have been more intertwined than you would expect
And after Ted was no longer able to engage in his primary business
Infowars started keeping their finances much more stepper
Very basic level they raised about a million dollars in that money bomb and that money is absolutely not reflected
Cinema spreadsheet
Even though in theory
It does cover the time. After
It should be
Another thing that's important to remember is it's a spreadsheet is barely labeled at all
And it's really up to the person looking at it trying to do some
Exactly what these numbers show
Princeton's one column says total sales but nowhere in this document is
Explain what this is a total sales of
It's assumed that this is the total sales from the Infowars store but that's not concretely shown in the document.
Itself
It's a pretty good assumption that this is showing Infowars
Store sales
It's still a little bit of an
One point I want to make about the Huffington Post article is that
Context is
For instance the article contains this paragraph
The gamble of backing Trump appeared to pay off
Of the more than three years of data reviewed by HuffPost Infowars most profitable days happens around the 2016
Presidential election
The day of the election November 8th and forced or more than doubled its sales from the previous day
Making a total of $660,000
Next day after Trump won more than 8,700 orders were placed in the Infowars website
Totaling nearly 850
$2,000
It's fine to connect the surgeon sales to supporting Trump
But it's also important to point out the
The Infowars did a.50
You two hour marathon over the course
Those days
Which probably has an increase in sales
I bet you know what that have that impact
That is unimportant
Context to why the sales are so hot
Yeah it is
Is it is it was weird cuz I couldn't read the I mean obviously the
Conceit of our show bike ride
He couldn't avoid seeing some of the numbers and then going over like
We talked about him during that time.
And seem like little things that don't quite make sense in in that
You know
I think that's
No
Scents that I get from it is
Like
Okay this is interesting
Probably a minimum
Yeah but it's a minimum but then also there's there's obviously expenses that are taken out
Translating glimpse
But I also don't think it
I think it raises more questions than it answers
I mean your
You're right
It seems low
Time. Before this you still making it
Imani group in the supplements was going back to at least 2013
Remind I remember
Actor Group B
Very happy
I think there is a broader picture
That that
Is not available
From the information that right now
And I would be interested
More information as it comes out
I do think that the timing of this document starting
Lost his license
If it's a coincidence it's an amazing coincidence
A very lucky one
Into
So Alex
Rant about money
Of course
Look
Really want
Last year we sold $30 worth of food
What's the
Million
Doesn't matter what we're doing
Show my house
Coupon the money into this
Ashamed of money
My mission is not to just have a bunch of money
My mission is to build an infrastructure to resist the New World Order
I only want to make money to build an anti New World Order infrastructure
Like Alex having to distinguish between which of his multiple
Houses he allegedly had to sell
To stay on a property let's
Literature that we all know that it was money he spent on a home no one could live in
The fact that he was able to sell this house is clear evidence that he never actually needed it to
Begin with but there was something about having both
People houses that was appealing to him
Maybe was the luxury of it maybe was a convenience or like easy
The investing aspect of it
But whatever the case
This was achievable only because of the money he brings in from the show
That money could easily have gone towards this infrastructure he's
Pretending to be building but Alex prioritize things like having multiple homes or buying a tank
For having the ridiculous gun collection that he has
You can claim that he wants this building a new world order infrastructure that's great but honestly it's just a way to keep the audience pacified
About how much money you got
We bring in
No it's not going to an anti New World Order infrastructure
Unless it's code for his lawyer
You know it's just
It's just great when you're populist leader as a room
Where everything's made of
If gold it just makes you feel like yeah
On brand
Alex
Is kind of spiritually correct
I have heard him
Say that they make like millions of dollars
I don't think he has like 50 million a year
Close to what
Excited
He has said the dates a lot of stuff
But at such a discount you're still getting high quality products
Yeah
I don't know
There is a middle ground
Is accurate
You still lying a little bit
How honest he is been about
He's not lying totally
He has
Talked about
But bring in a lot of money
Defensively had
Say
Listen I do have a s*** ton of money
But it's cool
This is the first time I think I've heard him say that he hits his second home
You just say I'm selling my house
Yeah yeah
Yeah anyway I'll be gets into the actual Huffington Post story itself
And he gets a
Few details wrong
Big Tex has trillions in spies on you and sells your data and sensors you
Good big Shaq
Was there jumbo Jackson
Google has more than 20 people worth over 50 billion dollars
That's okay
Look at this
Made
They think you're so stupid
You mean the word is gross
165 million over 3 years
Little exaggerated
Jones has 165 billion dollars
I'm curious about
Fairly accurate
That's it that's interesting
I don't know if I believe that
These are the numbers that I gave them
And they're fairly accurate
Fairly accurate considering it's the information that you gave
Is a little strange
Also the article doesn't say that
He has 165 million dollars that's
Hawaii that Alex is using to a straw ban if you will
And also it doesn't you needs to give it
But also look this article has some unintended
Sconces
And here's one of them
Servitude Christian broadcast
Run businesses in a million dollars
Oh my God
Ariel
Unreal
Like Scrooge McDuck in DuckTales diving into gold
Vizzini's money anybody knows if he's got your money
This is how you do it
Yeah yeah
Like this comes out he's like oh yeah
F*** you I'm going to Alberta
But why why would you think that this would affect him like
Yeah what point do you see a televangelist with their own
Jet
Before you go oh they don't care if they're rich
The Post article was till like
Information
That response if you want to make more money though it says
To be outraged you bestowed are you
Crush me with
Response
I'm going to raise more money
That's cool
Alex
Goes out to break
This is disgust
Message great part about it is
There isn't any money
That's why they're so pissed
I'm look
Essentially laughing
At the Sandy Hooks
That's that's basically what
He's laughing now you're never going to get any money even
Emancipated
Is this a bad mentality it's
It's a mark of a disgusting
It is it is
Super villain
It is really really f***** up it's it's literally in a movie whenever you finally get to the bad guy
And they've stolen all your gold and then they're like huh
I scattered to the Four Winds you have lost your life
That's it
So look Alex is going to take a week off
I thought you going to take the rest of his life off
But he's
But this article is
Changed
I'm not taking off down I'm not coming in here and I'm not wanted
Home sales pay that officer sign
Projects
Televangelism
Seriously
Exhausted
Wow no vacation
Classic Jim Bakker I'd like those were the days when Jim Bakker would be like
You're going to give me more money okay fine man
Committed fraud you guys got to give me money to come in
Yeah
It's pretty fun
I would say that
Based on
Is the temperature around Infowars prior to this
And how Alex was quitting a bit and storming off air and he started this episode off by saying everyone needed to Diane
Walk around the park
Vacations probably not the best idea
He forces himself
To come in to raise this $3000000
He might be
Everyday is that next week it could be a struggle
I could be a struggle
Bible
Irene is he's kind of a little bit like
While you're listening to this you have to be like I better give Alec
Like some money otherwise he's go
Keep telling me I deserve to die
And that makes me feel bad but I don't like being told I deserve to die
Flies
Something out
I don't want to be a dick I'm not saying this article is bad
At all
Criticism
Are perhaps interpretations of information from this that I've seen on Twitter and on social media
You're nitpicking
No that's it
There is an accuracy in the article and I have to give it up to Alex he is
Totally correct
As much as I do we can barely pay the bill Jones told the caller on Thursday during a segment
Prompting
Not going to stop
I need your help Frank
I need your help
Oh okay
That's absolutely correct.
That's why I said that on Thursday
Play that commercial
Yeah that's alright
Breaking bad but still not saying Thursday I mean you didn't say it Thursday but he did say it
I have to give it up when Alex says something that is actually
So look
Trump
He's trying to eat you know he's trying to make you social media thing he raised
The billion dollars
Imagine what I want to do with them
Billion dollars
$400,000 in my bank account
Which operation is biggest
The future in operate
Social network
Dollars
I don't have money
Can have them give them
Weird voice
Got to get pissed
Billion dollars today
Familiar
So the first hour of the show is an outburst
And then
Teasing too
Announce the Tucker Carlson's the most important person in the world
Then the second hour is largely an ad for Gap
I'm sorry not gator
Don't start with G and do the same thing
November 3rd hour has become
Alex
This article by screaming about needing money
This show is worthwhile
I'm starting to think
That the reason he took
Such a long time in that first hour was because you really it's it's kind of thin
I think it might be a little thin
I wonder if almost like this news broke
HuffPost
Thank God
I could see him being like that I'm about this
Material
To look we we make jokes
Redo
That's something we do
And storming off his show
Then look
There's only one reason that
Cuz of you
Cuz of the greatness
It's cuz he loves the crew
Show many deals lined up and so many big
Things ready to go
You ain't shut nothing up
You not shut
Jack
God
Besides my heart goes out
I can't imagine
Anybody having an offer for Alex like what he's going to get a shoe deal
Have no idea
What are you
You talking about unemployable by anybody else he's not even allowed to visit
His best friend
It the Fox News Studio
You're not allowed in there he's also
Apparently not able to be on his other best friend
Chocolate
I don't do the people who love him
I don't think he's employable YouTube I like oan no absolutely not
He's not employable he can only beat his own boss
The worst
I don't think it would be interesting
For anyone to like give a book deal no I can't imagine
The only thing you could do is if you're like a venture capitalist billionaire
Who wants to be like
Alright
There's a lot of money you be weird
Yeah it has to be like I hate no-strings-attached
Figure out what you're going to do because
You can't and if you was going to do that why wouldn't you do that within the
Reset
Talk about that
Even though it was the most important thing he's ever done. It ran out of
Steam real quick
We'll get to that eventually I promise
January 6th
Bad the daily interest
Expatriates
Beautiful people
Happily fam
Did you know it's also Alex's wedding
Anniversary
I did not know that
Globalization
Democratic party all dressed up as right now
There when I got married
On January 6th
My new wife was pregnant with our wonderful daughter this morning
I want to be out of enforce in 5 years
God has really touched my heart
The other leaders
And just people that are going to stand up and wake up my wife look
Big Island
Bad job
Four Seasons
Oh my God
Joe Rogan
The Joe Rogan
It is going to be the guy
Havana Joe Rogan will be my successor
So if I understand correctly
On
His fourth
Wedding anniversary
He was at the overthrow of the cap
From what I understand I think his wife was there too
The Great
I might be off on that breaker
Her being there
But look good and also let's not forget
The day we started our show was it was his wedding day
This is too weird this is getting too weird.
Simulation as f***
5 years ago freaking me out man it's freaking me out
So
Is
Man
What it what what are we doing
No idea
So look and wanted you wanted to quit
Because Rogan will carry the mantle
And so I told her I said
I said within five years
One film a year
Cuz I really want transition out of this
We're five years later
Book a year anniversary
A lighter
Is that cuz you guys got married
Promises
I don't know
But
We're winning
Okay
What
What was that you said I never break my promises and then use you if you revealed that you broke your promise
My wedding
Wow that was
That was
Weird that was a deeply personal moment that I did not need to know him
The Patriots
Yeah it's been 5 years
And that's when his timeline
Was that he was going to quit right they told his wife
Opening never breaks promises right
Implication here is I'm f****** out of here
Yeah that seems to be the application it's the only of
Let's try and Trace the emotional
Through this episode
You're all going to die again all deserve to die I got to walk around the parking lot
Tucker Carlson's the most important person in the world and if you understand this
You understand everything
Gator is very exciting
It's super exciting
The globalist publishing this article about how I make money
I'm going to make a lot more money but also I got a quick I got to get out of here
So we're going to be plugging non-stop for the next week I'm quitting this show I promised my wife I would
We are going to be doing nothing with plugin for the next week and there's no one to give the
Show to just Jo Rogue
He's not going to take a shower
Somewhere else in house everybody stop everybody sucks
Going into something big
Metamorphosis just happening and I
Quite sure until I go through that psychic wall when it is but I know it's bad
I know it's a big cat
And I'm going to follow
I'm going to do it
But it
Picture word of mouth
Your financial support
Tweet today I'm unfortunately the last time
Well above
And don't worry though I'll fake cry
As their houses burn down
Just like a f****** decision
We're don't don't do this we're going to be gone and be gone in a year
I'm so tired of this game
He is in and out game
So many corporations that would
Kill to be able to get away with an ad pitch that's just if you don't buy this you're going to
To die if you don't eat dinner
Second we go off the air the lights go out in your f****** death
You're going to die
The only reason that the globalist are at Bay
I'm not killing you and your family is because I only two sitting right here which you won't be in a little bit
Just walk around the park or things
He's not going to be there to protect
And I mean he did plan to take next week
And he's not doing that he's not so you can buy more things now to keep him from
Leaving
We have one last clip here
And
This is so much of a bummer
I told my daughter
Particular
Play some
You want to go to this kind of music
I'm going to go home tonight I'm going to tell her sorry honey
Because
And we're going to come in here with a focus
For like 2 hours and shove that up the New World Order
What happens when you mess with Alex's he disappoints his daughter
My
If you don't buy my products
You're going to die
But more importantly
If you don't buy my products
Have a good day also would think that this story flies always keeps
Promises
I mean I can't imagine
Dad can we go to the music but you know what
Yes and then a little bit later so I have to fight the devil
Butterfly daughter
That's okay that's just the way it is
What a what a whirlwind of a couple days
Emotionally spent
The track of these two days
Definitely won't be remembered nearly as much as the previous January 6th
Stupid in its own right
Is it it's not
The capital Has Fallen
But it is
The most important person and my daughter said
Your fault
Only people that bought more products
I'm sorry
We have
Website
Dot-com
Bell Ruckus
What the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color