Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge babe I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Brown's little bit about Alex
June
Again.
Quick question
Who are you
Put a new cover art on the on the show This Is Us
Kyle back by a guy named Jackie
Yeah set this design
Cuz I really like that and
Don't think about the freshening things up and that you know is our anniversary for the show and I felt like
Timing is perfect
I figured out what I've been doing wrong in terms of why are like a really old
Yeah cover art was showing up in like apple podcast
I'd size but at the image wrong it turns out
Apple podcast
Except so I figured like
Bucket list
One Fell Swoop
Thanks to Jack that the image is really great and I appreciate that.
I love looking at it as well defined in there
That's really great
Confuse baby pink guitar
That's a deep cut
Stroope yeah we will not explain it
What about what about you
Okay
Garbodor really really terrible
There's one moment in the film where
Part of the reason is bad is it
Incomprehensible and what's comprehensible
Incredibly stupid about their backstory her journal
Yeah yeah so apparently one of the deviants
Slowly there supposed to be this race is Monster bad and the Eternal Spider-Man bye-bye you know the whole deal
So one of them gain sentience
Right
And slowly starts to think and feel and has
I thought after absorbing one of these dudes
Alright
So
They find out that the god that created them both as really just been
Like playing
Ants
And putting them in making them fight this whole time
Right
So the guy that came sentience is like hey
F*** this noise let's team up
And go after the real guy we're just Pawns in his dumb game where is the people who were victims here
Both of us you and me right now
Murder this guy who just gained sentience and was 100% correct about everything
Because the only good guy in this movie was murdered immediately
The sensible and Eros my brakes
I think it was an unintended
Microcosm of the Marvel machine
You know like
The one bright spot that said listen
We can break through of this
Goddamn Orthodox storytelling method
This is all made up
We're just fighting for no reason we got it changed
Is like that means you nailed it
I'm glad that you dug deep and found some so meaning in that movie I did I do not seen its when I say I heard it's bad I'm just
Get off
Gimp ass real bad
Jordan today we have to go back into the past
About 2,300 take AAA separate
Journey
Today cuz I
I was thinking about it really I don't want to
Luck and talk more about the same
Stupid
Spirit like the covid
Conspiracies and I don't want to talk
About like
James O'Keefe project Veritas put out of video I don't want to hear about it
Rand Paul got into a little fight with the fauci
I don't care in me off Alex probably going to have a fit
I don't care
So I just was like the present day I gotta let it let it simmer for a little bit better then on Monday the
Who's the most important person in the world
We can about it up if we can't follow it up
So I need to go back to the past an Excursion based on
Some
Things that I've stumbled across
Online I want to explore some ideas that I had about them
But before we get done
Business
Like you and hello doesn't do walks
The worst candy and ends this thank you so much and I'll probably walk
I am now the Scout walk
Keon the trisexual and being thank you so much
I'm a policy against the common Florida berbagai thank you so much you are now policy walk
Thank you very much do wonders if you ever cross paths with the movie theaters
Columbia Missouri in the mid and late 2000s thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Hey there's a
Decent chance
I guess
Anyway Jordan
So
Look here here's the other downside of this
I
Yes indeed we just got news that
Dirt roads got arrested that one was kind of big
And boy I would love to talk about that
And said we're going back to July 23rd 1860 the first time we talked about a civil war
First-time Stuart Rosenthal restaurant
I was his response to this will be very Illuminating very interesting
I can't wait to talk about that on Monday
It frustrates me that there's no way for us to do that for this at the brother
I was going back
Through
Some of the archives
Absent such of Alex's shows and other things on Infowars
Was
There's a bit of a pattern
As it relates
To how are you
Our cover
And so I noticed a number of things surrounding in particular
The end of April in 2009
Which is when the
The H1 N1
Swine flu pandemic
Was really getting going and and the first cases were identified
I started to recognize their some
Things that would be
Well worth our time
Time to look at as it relates to Alex's behavior in the present day
Enter awesome
Connections
Almost
With a little bit of a comment and that is that I mean it no way to minimize the impact of the 2009
Mate1 N1 outbreak in this episode
I'm not I'm not
Minimizing or belittling it
It was a serious Public Health event and a lot of people got sick and died
I think it's pretty clear from history
That it wasn't that severe an event is what we're living through it in
In the present
The point of this episode that I put together today is
Look at some of Alex
The coverage from the early days of H1 N1 or swine flu outbreak
To highlight the ways that his rhetoric was almost identical to the way he behaved in the early days of the covid pandemic
At the beginning of 2020
Alex's tone is changed a bit since that point but
It's my contention that
He's only had to change his rhetoric because he f*****
Over the course
I'm going to argue that Alex has a method of responding to things like novel outbreak
There is absolutely nothing to do with the reality of the situation
But is actually motivated by the utility
Did this method has in terms of building and pushing
Determine narrative
These Central narratives are
The virus is man-made
Its a bio-weapon
It was deployed in order to put in martial law
It was deployed in order to make people get vaccine
And that the vaccines
Will be mandated
I understand clearly meant to her
In addition to these narratives I contend that Alex also uses some Hallmark techniques in order to reinforce his narrative
And use asset strategies in order to get his message out
3D broadcast from 2009 I believe that all this is pretty clearly born out I hope that looking at this week
Be helpful in terms of understanding
How meaningless
Was Alex's stories about the present pandemic really are
Earlier I said I was narratives about covid arso convoluted and like all over the map right now because he f***** up and what time
I mean by that is this
In the past I was able to maximize outcomes by following basically the same script that he used at the beginning of the covid app
Penney's instances weather was the avian flu in 2005 Ebola in 2014
481 and 1 into a 2009
Public Health
Response was Compton
And we got lucky
So the diseases didn't end up causing
Service social
Disruption that we see in the last few years
That's the sweet spot for someone like Alex to work in
There's a legitimate Public Health concern that he can spread b******* about but the adults working on the actual problems are still able to get
Their work done
To avert any real long-running trouble
Alex get the fear Monger make it
The claims and then when things died down he can move on to another subject altogether
In fact because
Things are being
Competently handled
He doesn't even really have to make a story like h1m won't be number one story in his rotation everyday over and over
Alex would have had every expectation based on every single time he's done this in the past
The covid-19 way
But it didn't
And you stock
I believe
Things gone poorly
In the past
And other in
Census
You would see a similar deterioration
Just trying to
Stay keep his grip
All narrative
Things
Spiralizer
Control
The obvious
Usually the most important
Not most important
But definitely not coincidental
Thing is that
The president that he wanted was in the White House at the
The time that he did not get what he wanted
Made it look like he got what he
Is this irony
It is not irony so much as a self-fulfilling failure Prophet Morissette ironic
So we're going to start here looking
Sing at an episode of
Interesting
Jason bermas back in the fold now course the one of the guys who made
Yes
Alex
I guess
Became best friends
Forever
I honestly think if you look back at some of the earlier times and Infowars history like around
These
2008-2009 this stretch
The time
Shows a lot to Duesenberg
Terms of
First of all douche
TS
He was the guy who would fill in for Alex when Alex had no other employees
She was the person who Alex had like as another show right when there were no other shows
On on the Infowars Network
Look up Jason Burris has the show the info Warrior
That's evenings
Cleveland Show
And on this April 27th 2009 episode
Alex is filling in cuz Jace
Time is running late
And so Alex gets into a little bit of news
About
The h1ad Watch
Genesis Network Folks up there
If you get them aligned and somebody's not for Mexico or doesn't have family in Mexico or not from San Antonio other areas
Weather Al Briggs
Nashville to call in later
Just in the next hour after we get some of these calls
From Mexico or areas affected by this new
Designer virus is exactly what it looks like
So we have a presentation already like
This is days after the first cases are identified
In the United
States
Pretty shortly after that news has broken
The first cases of neck
And already this is
Predetermined to be
A designed virus
Is manufactured
They did this they put that they cooked
Pizza formula Ozark reaction
Is just like
And he doesn't even know how to speak of viruses that aren't designed like the idea of
Do the designer virus the flu you know like
I think a lot of times you could look at any wild born
Virus
You know disease
And you can find something
Suspicious about it
Probably find
Something that's weird about most
Diseases that
What I mean
Viruses are weird in the first place they're alive but they're not alive what is that even f****** mean you guys are driving me crazy shirt
Suspicions on there are elements
Prince of swine Avian and human
Floozy
That makeup
This this new novel
Package
Surprising
Experts
You're not scientists and researchers who weighed in rd2 even at the time
Talk about recombining
That happens
Like let's say one pig is infected with
Multiple
Viruses that they will trade genetic information are
And various different
Toulouse combined
Basically as much as he has for this was designed
Thursdays
Hallmark's
The three different
Types of
Blue Apron
But that's you know
That's stamped
In the in the narrative immediately
Once you know that it's
Designs
We got to ask yourself some other questions
Also is swine flu biological weapon excellent article
That is up on prisonplanet.com that bermas is going to be going over
Another one is swine flu a biological weapon
Printer friendly version of that
Yeah I just got to stop over printing here man
He act like he's reading to headlines
Has he considered the overhead that comes along with the amount of toner to use
It's got to be me
It's crazy when I was making the button
It was
You're like no expense
Everyday what are these facts about
Empty paper
Yeah it's unreal
Probably not surprised
But this headline with Alex's reading suggesting that swine flu could be a biological weapon was written by Paul Joseph W
Paul is hip
By this point 2009 and seems to be aware that he should probably cover his ass
So this article starts like the
There are some factors
It suggests the swine flu killing people in Mexico may be a biological weapon
But obviously no such
Conclusion can be drawn at this time Manuel done Paul
Delete a false story is that there's no conclusive answer but wouldn't it be fun to spend the next 12 or so paragraphs heavily insinuating
But you don't have a conclusive answer but
What you think of this wine for probably is biological weapon
Has written largely relies on an alleged
Source who spoke to former regular Infowars ghast Wayne Madsen
Wayne is one of Alex's old best buddies and he was the guy who broke that story about Hillary Clinton
Personal chef being found dead
With a note attached to him that said call Larry Nichols
So you know that this dude is credible as hell
He stopped talking to Alex a little bit after Alex wanted all the info
For Trump
A lunatic
Probably sent those bad for his brain
William Source apparently told him that he was quote
Convinced
Current outbreak of a new strain of swine flu in Mexico
In some parts of the United States is the result of
Introduction of a human engineered pathogen
They could result in a widespread global
Pandemic with potentially catastrophic consequences for domestic
International travel
And commerce
Who plays with the knife's edge
Stressing that it's too early to say anything with certainty but also and the article with this paragraph
Quote fears that a mass pandemic was being ready does a biological attack have rumble.on and the
Conspiracy Community ever since 9/11
Investigators point to the highly unusual number of deaths of top microbiologist
Suggest
The people with knowledge of the program are being eliminated
That's funny
That's a fun
Since 9/11 conspiracy might have said that about every virus since f****** before that
Through dead bodies into
Two castles
They're like all those guys are man-made that virus
You know ucuc historical
I think that 1918 was prior to
Theories about that one
Meow
To ask Pollock what investigators are pointing
To this kind of stuff again
Play it like this
Some investigators have said
Seems like a some b*******
It's been used to freak readers out make them have fears about this Mass pandemic being launched
Biological attack
Just like in forwards does all the time it seems like
This this and that to justifying whatever it is
Insinuations you're making throughout the article is just like well we do this a lot
Don't you understand it's normal for us that's wrong that's wrong
It's important to understand that a large part of what Alex has been doing over the course of the current pandemic is part of a larger pattern
And seeing the same stuff play out another. Then it could be really helpful and illustrating
Exactly
He's full of s***
The reality is he's doing these exact same things that we saw the beginning of the pandemic
Here in the past
And you would have been doing exactly the same thing that he's doing good luck it better public
Responsibilities are brakes not getting as bad as
Things have gotten
Today
And we see like a really concrete example
I'm also it's up to 149 confirmed dead in Mexico
They're clearly suppressing
Those numbers even according to the BBC
It may be difficult to remember this now but when covid was just emerging
It wasn't a huge denial is
It's about it he was a sensationalist
And one of his main narratives in the beginning
Was that China was suppressing the numbers of dead by
Attic magnitude
I think it's probably fair to say that there wasn't totaled
Transparency with China's reporting
But that has no bearing on how irresponsible and dishonest the kind of reporting Alex did was
This is from March
May 4th 2020
Coronavirus situation in Mali
Biological weapons expert
Top scientist scanning the virus and saying it's man-made
You got to get ahead of this if you notice
Virus numbers
Thousand confirmed we're locked in here a few minutes go 24,000
The internal Chinese numbers that leaked
Rocket publish in China by the people daily
24000 dead
Yesterday
They're doing is they're just
Putting the number of dadaism
This is part of Alex's early sensationalism which employees because it's profitable and generally there isn't any real
Consequences because
Public Health Protocols are handled response
At this point Alex and every reason to assume that the 2019 coronavirus will be like all the other house scares heat sensation
Flies in the bath
And this was the model that he is used to maximize his profits he's behaving exactly the same way
Easy multiple elements of this
Exact same script
The it was a maid in the lab without held by a build by the bad guys
And also they are covering up exactly how
Hey did they there's a grander scale of the death
But they're lying to us about
All consist
The only difference the only thing that's different is that the person he wanted to be running the
Country was running the country
At Cross purposes
This is with the organization that was supposed to be the adults trying to
Stop all this
Crazy how that works
It's almost like there's a very simple direct lesson to be learned
I don't think we'll ever do it probably not
Alex also
The present things that you would do
I guess you just do this all the time actually isn't really a connection
Between
These two insta
Centers of Public Health
Think it's kind of
Consistent pattern that is
Misuse of sources
So he has an interview that he's going to bring up
Has interview with this retired General Honore
Which is I know this name
Because Alex will reference him a lot
But it's fun because at this point 2009
I'll just no idea who he is
It's really fun to watch him trying pronounce the name
Avon prisonplanet.com there's another
Headline of a CNN clip-in fat guys let's get that video clip ready
Put on a play that clip
Coming up once Obamas is
He ran on the show
Retired army General Russell
Believe you pronounce at Honore with
French
Squiggly on the end of it
How do you pronounce that
Honore with it come out
Retired army General Russell
On the Run
Mexico from
Able to find that out in all previous pandemics
The question now is
Big heart
How to start it it start from me
Occasion of ours is coming together or did it come out of the lab all those questions have to be answered
Most doctors medical doctors virologist we've talked to their own record said it had to be weaponized an engineer will tell you when we get back
Po-boy
You can see here this that makes very clear parallel between Alex's swine-flu coverage until things began with covid
He's focusing attention on building up the narratives that
The flu came out of the lab
Bad was built
Bye-bye
Got to get it out
The reason he does this is pretty simple but there's actually two prongs to it
The first is that if it came up from nature there's no real bad guy
I'll just trying to deal with his wild-born disease that threatens us all
It's not really all that
Exciting
It came from the lab and there's an entry
These meddling scientists as either outright villains
Or people who probably meant well but we're tampering with forces outside of what God wants man to tamper with
Would you like to us meeting more movies about mad scientist than there are of like
The crops aren't as good this year have we rock
The second reason is because reporting
All of these potential outbreak stories out of their roots in the lab
It helps
Bolster anti-vax
Text narratives General Trust
Austin science
There's an added element to this to which is that they it's always reported as vaccine research gone wrong
That led to this lab accident of the release of this alleged bioweapon
Which has the effect of associating vaccine development With Disaster
Any audience is mine
This interview that retired General Honore did with CNN
Between him and Donald
Here's the exchange that Alex's basing this
Insinuation
Lemon is pointed out
People isn't important
I'm part of a national strategy
D2 Public Health
Response and Honore says quote
Informant
So people can make informed decisions
That will help us that will help stop.
The spread of the disease but you know the key question we've got to ask is
We think it came from
That's the conventional wisdom of most
The next question is how did it start
Where did emanate
We've been able to find out that in all previous pandemics
The question is
To get at the heart of how did this start
Did it start from the occasion of irises coming together
Or was it did it come out of the lab
I mean all these questions have to be in
I don't seems I can possibly splitting hairs but I sincerely believe there's a relevant difference between someone saying it's important to understand where
Where the virus came from
And the way Alex was reporting
Hang on these,
The difference is that interviews like these with General Honore are open-ended
In terms of laying at questions that are on the table where is Alex's coverage is designed to lead the listener to a predetermined
Conclusion
The goal is to cover this as a lab related outbreak in Alex uses
Is autoreise comment further that goal
You can see that by the way that Alex is tailored the headline as to only include the part where it's suggestive the virus came from Lab
And of course the part of
The end where you saying that all experts are saying that weapon.
Yeah that part
It was really a
Yeah it's a little over a little out of hand
You know like he was like we don't know exactly and then they turned into this is a bioweapon that's a little bit
I do think they're like
He saying that all the EX
Experts and scientists that we've talked to his that that
Possibly
If you didn't specifically only talk to crazy
We talked to three people with rabies and they all agreed and everyone in the mouth
Stories of all the people that I talk to that everyone at rabies
Spoke to upset
Yeah and insult
Of course
You know we have this establish
This is from a lab
And now we got to build
LSU's the club with a retired General on CNN pointing out that this could be made the lab when you get
All these different viruses mixed together
We were you get the a pig for the swine flu this bird flu and human flu
I all mixed together
Classically historically
That isn't here in the lab and then you always have it coming from the East
Blue season 2 always comes from the East they do streams always
This originated in Mexico City
And I don't about it since I March 18th Elation we're busy covering it up
So scared is cuz it's killing healthy
They all virile 18 to 30 year old
I meant women mainly the death tolls now upwards of 149
Whitewash number
Doesn't really dishonest way to leap off of Honore CNN interview
There's no reason to believe that just because the 2009 H1 N1 virus had elements of swine Avian and human
That means it had to be made in a lab
Conclusion for a number of reasons
The first is that it's entirely possible for this kind of recombination to happen in nature
Pigs or people could be infected with multiple flu simultaneously and then they can recombine and ways with a trade genetic information
According to the CDC quote
Each of the dream segments within the 2009 H1 N1 influenza virus
Have been founded pigs for more than
Send 10 years prior to
To the beginning
Have a 2009 H1 N1 influenza outbreak
Pics of long been considered a possible mixing vessel for influenza viruses that originated within Pig
Big Bird
In addition a 2009 nature study showed
That Resort meant between influenza viruses found in North American and Eurasian pigs
Had already occurred at least once naturally
In the five years prior to the I-10
Application of the 2009 H1 N1
So they're pressing
Yeah see now this is one of those times
Times where I feel like
Scientist need somebody like me right now
Next to a bar
Explain that
Right cuz they're like
And then the other viruses and then they recombine and that's how we can see that stuff and I could just be there and be like
F****** sidem
And then we be fine everybody would understand that better than its more relatable
Best eyesight isn't an approach
There's no need for lab to be involved to explain the complex nature of the virus but Alex's obscuring that and it's a further push it
Is predetermined conclusion that the virus had to come from a lab
Justice is done consistently since the beginning of covid he's jump
All over the place
Trying to find these weird
Explanation for why it had to be
Baton the lab
Been falling flattened
He's kind of forgotten about
As for the idea that flus come from the East
That's actually kind of been borne out by Reese
Search but it's not a
A study by the University of Chicago noted that
Between 2000-2010 87% of the quote
Most successful globally spreading strains of H3 end to originated at East
South and Southeast Asia
M3m to of course being the most common disease causing
Strength
This is a high number but it also does tell us another little fact and that is that it's not unheard of for flus pop-up another look at
There's a good 13% there that
And this is also a successful global
Spreading strain
Pretzel
You know if there are
It doesn't have to have come from the East
Easily have popped up in Mexico
That is not
Like some sort of
It comes from the East
Because Easter's
Concept and it comes from an environment and an ecosphere
Please just because that's where it is in our head
It could be anywhere
And there's there's some
Non-consensus what side
Series about exactly why that phenomenon is the case
Weather has to do with
Something about population
Patterns ardesa do with the
The climate early
Clear but there are people themselves
Doing a tune-up
Weirdly close to that
2009 H1 N1 date affect younger people more severely with people over sea
65 being less vulnerable
However what do you think about there being a cover-up of anything is just not founded
In any way
And here we see another common feature of how Alex reports on public health matters in the immediate
It's important to cast suspicion on all other sources of information so no matter what the reality of the situation is
You lead with a
Accusing them of a cover
By this point the CDC was already posting updates about what information have been learned up till that point
The center for infectious
Disease research and policy were sounding the alarm
State governments are posting guidance for people to panic and help them guide
Themselves through any possible
Health problems
Cnn-ibn reported on cases that have been
I confirmed in California to I do I don't know what to a cover-up Alex's
Talk about cuz there wasn't
The suggestion that there was a
Crucial to undermine and Trust in public health
Expert which helps Alex present himself as the
Actual expert to Azadi
Around every corner in the present pandemic there been accusations
The cover-ups
Because it's an easy thing to do and you've never have to back it up
Nope
Play Sia.
And if the thing about that makes
It's so good it's no matter what they're telling
Cuz yes you
You see all this stuff
You can always claim they're covering up something
Sure it's in the news that their cases in LA but they're covering up their case
What's magical about that too
As if
You just have a vague notion that there's a cover-up your mind gets to imagine whatever you want as you want yes
And if months later something comes out that wasn't in the reporting
Any anoculus reason for any reason
I secretly knew that all
When did I didn't say that did happen to be the case is the one that I'm
So at this point
I presented you with this information and how do you feel about what Alex wants the audience
To think about
This
This virus feel like
Lucky one
What's to let them know that the government is murdering them as they speak
And that if they're not terrified and giving him money
It's all over
Brothers cover up
Wilshire battery wanted specific
There's cover up chairs this was
Clearly made in the lab who's covered down
It was a bioweapon most likely came from outside the United States
And
There
Like reporting fraudulently low death number two more people are dying in this off
Do you think kind of thing you're supposed to be scared of this study be terrified
I feel like that
The tone
We get to this boy
Deftones now upwards of 149
Whitewash number
But much still this is a bunch of high
Pictures of regular flu strains every year millions of people worldwide
1000 / 15000 year in the u.s.
Even more Mexico
But when we see all this so massive media have to question
This is an important element
The presentation to zoom in on real clothes
Infuriated Alex doesn't want his daughter
To actually be super afraid of the H1 N1
Flew in the same way he doesn't actually want the audio
To be afraid of covid-19 or did he at the beginning
He wants to build up a sense of fear Foster distrust in Mainline sources
And then transmute that fear that he's established
Into being fear something else that he wants them to be afraid
Possibly
Company profits Amour
Pushes his extremist agenda
Generally usually
You should be afraid because these people are clearly building a virus and a lab at the bioweapon it's killing people to rate the globalist to cover up
But also it's all because
Please kill
People thought all black people every year
Really kind of an insane thing
If you stop and think about it's jarring what he's implying and then the
Just like
But hey don't worry about it's not flu
The first part of this would lead you to think you should be very afraid of the fact that you villains are created by 11 and for some reason there
Covering up how many people have died from it
Heavily implies that the virus is something to be deeply can
Concerned about
The second part to play
That sends the message that this is scary than any of flu every year
That's crazy this is confusing if you don't pay attention because it's inherently nonsense
If it's all hype and no different than every flu why does this coverage
Exist
Is the numbers are no different than they are every year why would the globalist put out decrease death numbers
What sense does that make
It's the same as every year why would the globalist need to cover up the flues existence for a few months
Does Alex's implying
Alex wouldn't have gone through all the effort of laying that track
If it weren't for the purposes
I'm shipping
A narrative down the road
Towards what he actually wants
Sporting Store
Right
I mean
Insane
Okay
So you're telling me that the flu
Who is not man-made
And he's just a natural disaster part of the natural order
I assume you probably would rather not talk about that
But but like okay
Scared of a tsunami
Tearing the entire East Coast Park
But that's horrific what is tsunami but rain
Comparison arizola
Yes that's
Terrifying
The but nobody's Direct
Thing that it is
Even more of a crisis that needs to be reacted to
If just
1 dew drop the bomb that
Who gave a tsunami on the coast
Georgia
That's not as bad as God level strike of the entire East Coast
But that's a guy doing it we got to react to that real
Is who knows who knows what
It's up to you can't be saying like hey don't worry about the government created by a weapon to kill a bunch of people in Mexico but that's no
The flu like no girl we got to deal with that now we do but
Alex wants to deal with it in the way that he wants
The deal with that and I did already
Kind of get assigned
Based on
I don't know everything we've gone through the way that there's going to be
Beers of lockdown
Years of vaccinations being forced on you
Can't exactly you build up the fear the way he has so far
And then deflate the fear the actual
Condition and use that for your that you've built
How to build your own gingerbread house
Saphir that looks like a FEMA camp this is really really scary now calm down
This is not what you should be afraid of you should be more afraid of compound
Move this way
So Jason bermas comes in
He shows up. He's got some thoughts
Check my emails last night
Apparently Baxter is going to be the one in charge of immunizing for this
Yeah that's right go ahead and only 2 months ago and
Mid-February
I actually was late February the Bloomberg reported on it
I'm there
Sent out
214 separate countries this
Batch of
Anti bird flu vaccine
That contained
Two different strains of bird flu
And then a third strain of flu
And this is just incredible to me
That we would
Allow Baxter to be the people in charge
Of inoculation and immunizing
The populist
Mistresses
True from WebMD in 2009
46% of the vaccines manufacturer to the United States were made by Novartis
26% were from sanofi Pasteur
19%
Mcsl 6% from medimmune
3% from glaxo Smith
Klein and none of these are Baxter's Secret
Baxter talked a big game but they ended up getting beaten out by other suppliers that came to the market
In October 2009 after Baxter had one part of the contract
Display H1 N1 vaccine
Things to the United Kingdom
It came out that they had been forced
The payback million
The state governments were overcharging them for products
To the past and committing Medicare fraud today
I mean
Hot water who Among Us has not tried
To commit some
Sort of Medicare fraud Auto large-scale
Additionally Baxter did have a mix-up at a lab that they run in Austria being a little exaggerated Viber
Actually happened where live avian flu hit
Contaminated some experimental samples
That they'd sent to a couple other lab
It was a bad mix up and could have had some
Some seriously bad cops
But ultimately just ended up killing a few ferrets which is still sad right but investigations into it
Sound no hot like no
We only kill.
No power player
There wasn't
There's a specific goal is being pursued by coverage like this
The pharmacist doing
Caswell
The point of this is to establish the groundwork that there's something suspicious about the plans to develop effect
Maxine for this new flu virus
There must be a real
Reasons of the globalist are having all of our vaccines made by there's one specific company that recently bungled a shipment of experimental sample
They must want to have these vaccines if they put into
Contaminated to
Introducing these sorts of narratives
What is the first step of the essential pivot that need
Needs to happen where the fear that being built about the virus
He's transformed interfere about the vaccine
That's
Eustis
It's pretty remarkable how this is almost just muscle memory for them to be able to
To build up and move
Yeah I mean
The thing about
Like ways to combat
Bulshit
Is that they have to constantly evolve
And the thing about bulshit is that it's
State exactly the same for mine
Entire f******
And it just comes up and different
Spots like wackamole
You know yeah I think I actually we're going to get to a pretty
Pretty Salient examples
Here's another
Peacefully gets brought up that I think you'll see
Heavy
Overlap with a
The swine flu
All over the media people are hyped up I I didn't see where I was cuz I wasn't in the city but you can bet within the next week if they
This stays in the news
That people will be wearing the mask they will be wearing bandanas around their face
I mean this is a big ball I was already in
Associated Press this morning
How did the federal government came out and said yeah people need to go ahead and start wearing masks
Affected areas inside the United States show
Either the government is viciously
Hi bring this to get people to take more vaccines in the text
Dakota antivirals
The wife lose been mentioned
Right now tied into Rumsfeld in the bushes and
Not even now the president current President Barack Obama
Is a profiting from that
So you can see here this almost identical language to the president
Just fear hysteria and it's all in
Services
The forest vaccines on you
Fwiw Alex never got to the second option after bermas interrupted
I've no idea what they was going
Wayans brothers
Tamiflu
Tamiflu is not a publicly traded at
It's a product that's produced by Gilead
The reality to is that Alex is wrong
Gillian was not
Seeing record stock prices in April 2009
Their Peak was on August
Fourth 2008 coming in at about $28.50 a share
The Davis episode is recorded their shares
They hit a high of $24 in 11
Their numbers would start going up eventually but it wouldn't be until late 2011 and a large part of that was likely due to enthusiasm
Acquisition
But they've made buying up a ton of Pharma companies like
CV Therapeutics
CGI
Shockingly
There is some truth to the claim that Obama had a very small interest in Gilead
In May 2009 CNN reviewed his financial invest
Predominantly is Investments were in US Treasury Bonds in like
Accounts for his children
But he also did have money in an index fund called Vanguard
That fund is holding
Things in a bunch of other companies
And Gilead is number 10 on their list
The most held
I think so
Very indirect way you
Claim that Obama profits from Gilead but what Alex is claiming as a bit of a stir
Yeah if Alex just wants to go all the way in
Book officials Campground stock I'll join them in that but otherwise
This is all just blustery nonsense
Yeah yeah I'm for the no public
Look official Zone in stock
Cafe life safer
Too obvious
Yeah I think of an ideal world everybody should be able to invest in whatever they want
Close to there
You see here is another standard feature of Alex's public health coverage
There needs to be an insistent that insistence that Alex's political enemies are painted as corrupt
With their motives chalked up to their financial stake
It needs fine.
These pharmaceutical company
We saw this exact Same Song & Dance Play out in the covid pandemic ever
Trump was in office so it wasn't going to fly to start tossing around ideas about his
Dances so
The safer route
Insisted Bill Gates had the patent
But also the virus itself
Well you might have had some interest in pharmaceutical companies or he does through the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation
Gates doesn't himself hope at dawn.
He came out as
In favor of dropping the patent protection on the vaccines in order to allow greater access
For them a developing country
Although probably too late on the
Maybe maybe
Come to that conclusion a little early
Play tourettes to the list of owners of the patent
We're making money off of Axion but to be fair to him
Like you didn't know who fauci was at the beginning for a while so you could
Syracuse massage
I think I think what is
Is ridiculous about the
Bisnow especially on his face after having lived through all of this week
Put this
Type of conspiracy to bed
There's only one way to
Evilly profit off of
Pharmaceuticals
Annette's just
Plainly taking
Insulin
Charging $1,000
You know like we see the Griff
Tough
To conceive of
Who is doing something more
Yeah in our faces and on
What are bills
The real problem is that Obama has some money in this index
Text Mom that hold some Gilead
Michelle was really into
No diet
And I should tell you also hold a lot of stock in McDonald's
The point here is that all leaders who advise
Caution or public health measures they're only doing so because they want to create fear hysteria in order to Corral you into getting this
Because then they profit from
This story plays out over and over again because it's a myth
Cycle it's not actually analysis of the news
This is basically Alex's
Version of Joseph
Yeah it doesn't make any sense
It doesn't make any sense cuz what you would do
Okay is you would want to
Get the population
To all have some sort of
Version of diabetes
So like if you wanted to invest in a pharmaceutical company
And then create a conspiracy
That would make you a ton of money then you would do that and then you would try and flood the market of the United States with some sort of high
Sugar content
You know something and then you what you really want to do is get
To really be into it so you put
Like I should have cartoon characters and all of these people they would advertise it for you and then they would push that out there
And then so many people would get an image
You become part of their daily lives
I'm sorry
You can even take a step back and look at it like
From the perspective
Financial motivations really were guiding some of this stuff
There be no reason to actually backs
Funny people
What's the company's got me
Please contract
That's good enough
About the next one at 4 you be dead by then there's just a lot of a lot of balls
Need to be chocolates here
So speaking of balls that need to be juggled Alex has a lot of iron
In the fire and I mix
Metaphors
And there's a reason for that
Don't come piling up my stack of news before you came in because
Imma be on Coast to Coast AM for several hours tonight
Yeah I know I've got a
6:45 this morning which other slept in
I had it for a half hours today when we went to Dover drive so I'm going to get out of here
But one of the biggest stories
Look for while we play this clip I had it here in and I can't find it
It was up on infowars.com
Back in early March car tomorrow to story when it came out in government documents
But the Nets
The government has predicted a deadly pandemic flu
In 2009
In 1996
Wow so we're talking 15 years ago
Smoking gone offline
Planning this season
Amazing
Because you see to the major elements that Alex needs to make his whole pageant to success
The first is have a platform that the larger than his and presumably more mainstream that'll allow him to come on in
Present himself as an expert suggests
Are the present-day that's Joe Rogan
Job but in 2009 Rogan wasn't a gigantic Lee popular podcaster
It wasn't useful for alley
What's in that way
We will do in a pinch
We'll get to that in a minute
But first I want to get into that second Bass
The almost too perfect
Document that Alex's found
In order for this whole charade to go off right and for Alex to be able to come
Control
Directs Their Fear there needs to be some kind of document that could be used to illustrate that the globalist have been planning this all along
Which means that Alex is right and that means you got to listen to him
You're not current performance of this play
They're actually a ton of documents that if it this role with Alex and his menagerie of weirdos cherry-picking things to suit their
Precision proof
Definitely that this pandemic is
Is a false flag made up there is a raft of Toronto
I would say the bass on my experience velox
Stop document is the one that Alex seems to prevent is the most concrete and most persuasive so I'm going to give it that title
For the present-day pandemic
And here in 2009 we happen to have another
Two perfect document
I'll tell you the tracking this one down was really hard
Because Alex gives almost no details on it other than it was on his website
Possibly in March and apparently written by Kurt Nimmo
If you try to Search keywords like
30 million dead prediction 2009
1996 something
You don't come up with anything but
Thanks to the way back
Machine I was able to go through all of the headlines published 2009
And I get paid
This current number article is headline US Air Force study proposed 2009 influenza pandemic in 1996
The underlying document is a thought experiment from the air University tiled Air Force 2025
That's described as quote
A study to identify the concept
Capabilities and Technologies the United States
Will require to remain the dominant are in space force in the first quarter of the 21st Century
This document is literally the exact same thing as the lockstep
Exact
Eczema
Nefarious plan
This was an exercise
To brainstorm what the Air Force would need to do to
Continue effectively into the future
In order to carry out that exercise the research participants
Created six different
Alternative future scenarios
Explore possible challenges in
They use three variable
American worldview Tech
And the world power
Each of these at two values pause
American world you could either be Global or domestic
Tekkit either because
Constrained or
Exponential
And the power grid could be concentrated or dispersed
For instance if you want
Explore World War the American world global
Tech is constrained and power grid
Is dispersed
You be looking at their scenario tour title to Gulliver's Travels
There are five other scenarios but for our purposes we don't
I need to go through all of them in my new.
Details
Each of the scenarios include the section title to plausible history
Which is an exercise description of how the world got to
Point it is and their imagined version of 2025
These are Imagine
Made up things
And if you want to go eat
Cherry pick whatever you want out of it
Princeton tennis Gulliver's travail scenario China broke up into 15 new territories in 2006
And apparently this year 2022
It's just a title
Africa Wars
Outlook
Does Mario Kart demo is decided to focus on is one called digital
Cacophony
This is one where the global global American worldview
Supernatural Tech
First power grid
In this scenario is plausible history there's an influenza the kills 30 million people in 2009 but there's other things in here that
But to be red flags for anybody thinking
This is reflective of planning
Princeton
And it's plausible history we're supposed to reach the state of abundant food due to genetics in 2002
Also the UN dissolved in 2000
It's also going to be tough because I'm 2015
At least 48 countries have weapons
The mass
Also in 2020 we buy that point we have a ton of space settlement
Oh that's nice that goes along with the flu
Parcels
If you read the report the flu outbreak is included in this scenario is a reminder that though this is a possible future that's dominated by
A technological advance
Quotes
Technology could not solve some old problems
All right so I figured out how to do
Defeat Alex
Game here
Alright
No one can think about the future ever
Never engagement
Don't you dare do that
Take historical things and then put them in a possible future
That's just you saying that the future is going to have you have a calendar
Burditt
Yes every calendar that has more months than the day that you're on Burnet anybody ask you what you're going to do tomorrow punch
So-dimm Ozark was really interesting too because
He's trying to use this document to build a conspiracy about the Baxter flu lab mix up
But it happened
Previously
Interested
Is it merely a coincidence
What's the Pentagon would propose in 1996
The deadly flu pandemic
When live
H 5 n 1 avian flu viruses are discovered in vaccines produced by Baxter International plants
In Austria
He goes on to cite Paul Joseph Watson
The fact
Baxter mix it's deadly H5 N1 virus with a mix of h3n to seasonal flu viruses is smoking
Wright's call Jose
Watson
The H5 N1 virus on its own has killed hundreds of people but it's less airborne and more restricted in the
The ease with which act
Can spread however when combined with seasonal flu viruses which as everyone knows are super are born in
And easily spread
The effective approach
Super Airborne super deadly biological weapon
Of the sort
Proposed in Air Force 20
That's a lot of supers
Very suspiciously those last words
Quotes of the sort
Proposed in Air Force 2025
Those are part of the quote
From Paul
That was Nimmo adding a little editorial and completely fabricating the idea that this document proposes of biological weapon
Sure nonsense
In the scenario they say that no one ever figure it out if it was a naturally occurring
Fluor it was a
That makes
Cin-cin the scenarios parameters
It's a world with
Boundless dispersed technology and Power
What are the main Hallmarks of a
The challenges that they have is that there is an increasing number of states
And non-state actors that have weapons of mass destruction
Leaving the Genesis of his flu outbreak ambiguous creates flavor
In the picture that they're painting
For the scenario exercise
Anyway curtain Mo sucks
And even he had no clue that this would be able to be
Best one that holds extra narrative didn't really go anywhere
So now Alex is digging back taking this
And that's the same article that
Paul Joseph Watson opened with
Some are saying
Like he was very circumspect
Expect about
Not makeup
Not being like this is true
I mean these are different articles but
Yeah
A little bit of an ass
This is the exact same situation with the present-day use the Rockefeller lockstep document this is a useful tool for
People in the Air Force
Educational program to explore what challenges the military May face
If certain variables of social organization
Can go different ways
This isn't no way predicted
I guess it's as predictive of the 2009 flu
As it is of the UN dissolving in
In 2010
It's not an act
Accident analysis coverage of both the H1 N1 flu outbreak and the president include
Wheatley misrepresented document
30 uses
For knowledge on the part of his enemies
It's because he's a liar with a pattern
And he needs props
Is The Carrot Top of liars
It's at the point now where you like
Do they have a flowchart somewhere
Pandemic they've got break out the flowchart that I start here and then just keep going
Down the Cascade of b******* that organized but I think it's just
You know like that these are the elements that way to do it and got a pole from the way to do it
So now let's Lubeck to this Coast to Coast
I'm not going to make us sit here and listen to it all bit by bit
But I could not help myself
So I created a Supercut of some of the high points of the the episode
Alex is on with
Giant sea wrist and regular Jim Bakker guests
Steve Quayle food like to eat
Introduced the sex robot sure and he's one of the other you know Shady Infowars
Steve
Like six and a half minutes long or so
What does the only way I could boil down the experience of listening to this whole episode
Monarch
Flu scare
Right here on Coast
That is so
Far removed
From
Teresita
Air Force put out a doc
Painting bat bike
30 million
People would be
They know that
We just heard from
To believe
Concocted
Released
Documents
When we broke
At Issaquah
Infowars
I'm about that
In two
An overload here but
Designer
Virus
Clearly
Involved
When you look at this
Out of
I believe
Are they going to play
So that's where we
Neon records
1 record
On record
Like that
Happen
This is a
News story
4 years
Easy
To pick up
Because
What you
Broadcast worldwide
Imagine
Fury that's go
Exhibited
Throughout
Love the world
Find out the bill
This was a
Genetically
Biologic
Was in
Instantly
Now those are my
The scientist
Search that
Hours of the
Midnight
Superbad
Better using this
No it's not
Bad
The unifier
Mexico
Believe
Typing it and using it
Corruption
That's why
Right now
Episode in 20
Only forward
For the president
Shook the hands of somebody and
Call over
You know he came down with
The disease
Very
Saturday
Call Jonathan
Security
We are in a total
Warm
I believe
Symbolism in
Be more exact
Leave that you're seeing
Implemented by
Powers Boothe
Car
Two ultimate
Wipeout men
A pandemic
Flu would not
Everybody
After Time
It's given his ever
The time it's given
I knew what was going on
If Mexico
Waste
And we're getting these report
That is
People
Don't know
Asians
Their backs when they're a baby
Asian
With a mixture of
Bloodline
Yes that's a big huh
Marvel
I guess the
Grouting a
Nothing to do with Spa
Play I can
With how they was
With this 10 congrats that's great Gorge active participant
He sucks but like you see a couple things
Like
The nonsense aside
A couple of other added elements are the knee-jerk continuation this is a race specific bioweapon
Play at the beginning
The covid stop it's a very
Standard feature of Alex's coverage
And also the other thing too is the notion that this is meant to stop Revolution
Mexico
Stop this Awakening against the the globalist tyranny
It's exactly what he was saying about in China there were people who are rising up against the
The CCP
And it's got to be political
King sad it makes me so sad
I think you would be very sad mostly anytime you listen
Dacosta cup
That's true times it's fun but most of the time
Here's what I'm saying
Okay we don't need we don't need
Laws
Restricting
We need a bureau of enforcement of prediction
Alright let me know so if you go on the radio and say some s*** that's
You can say whatever you want on the radio but it up somewhere
It goes on the board
And there's a dick
And if you contact tracing
For bulshit like you have to follow up on E
Each prediction
And then you have to come out and admit you learned something
If you're Alex on this s***
A2000
Somebody comes into your office they go guess what it turns out you're full of s***
To go on TV
I do apologize and say I learned my lesson if you refused that you lose your prediction on there you go
Just needs to be regulated we need regulated bulshit we don't need outlawed bulshit
Picture though I support your your bill proposing
I'm running for congress
But like
We should all be so lucky
As Alex
Stab friends
Like all these Boynton our careers with
White audiences that are willing to engage with our bulshit
Narratives that he's pushing
On the show with Jason
And he's just
Shined them up a tiny bit made them a little bit harder to track down exactly what he's talkin
About Andy's disseminating 2m to George's
Audience
Android has a very willing active participant in it in the same way that Rogan
Yep through negligence
Or actually being interested in
Spreading the Alex
Send it
Outschool
Exist without the
Yeah I wouldn't be able to attract people
To his b*******
The dumb dumb who's willing to say that's interesting say more about that or
Haha
You know weld all you have to do that's what they need
Honestly I think never say say more about that because I never get any cheaper
I'm interested in your topic
Keep spewing bulshit you've interested me anymore
Play yes that's what I
So Alex left
Bermas
Because he had to take a nap or whatever shower to get ready to go
I'll go check out
We're going to jump back in
On Saturday May 2nd
Alex put out an emergency
Alright hour long
Special
Animerge
See
Has ever done about this wine
3232 the bullet points I've written here then I'll go to the news that backs it all up
A huge mind control X
Exercise
A literal war on
Freedom and liberty
Worldwide estate
Place
And you can just Google
Un says swine flu outbreak good for globalism
Global essay
Flu outbreak
Good for World Government you will see them in the news
Bragging the dishes helping them set up a world governed
They need a crisis
The offer their solution
Exactly where it is
Is Highway
We do this
Enterprise
Particular villain
At this point and its leader security
Napolitano
They love it
They're also admitting themselves is
Napolitano said last Sunday
6 days ago
Will probably fade out but another big pandemic
Will come
Will happen
Is a foregone conclusion
So let's not forget about that
And they're saying
Images flu will probably mutate
Ride around the fall in flu season begins we better all go roll up our sleeves
Get the shop going to have right on time
They're talking about
The federal government paying for 600 million
Joseph Humphrey terminal in America
Do you know how much
Prophet that is
When they're talking about the drug companies
The chosen
As much as
$20 for shot
What's the
What's 20 *
600ml
You can figure direct mirror of much of Alex's rhetoric and covid 2
And the current day was Bill Gates saying that there be future diseases that Alex
Theme to be suspicious
What are the past it was
And of course it's fear-based exercise
It's another to get everyone to take Taxi
Possibly just motivated by getting $20 per shot
For lunch specials
12 billion dollars
That's a lot of money
Especially to
Trulia.com
Absolutely so this is
Staged man
Understand the reason this is a dangerous
The beta test
As the economy continues to collapse
We can
Predicted this months ago their model
Don't control will be stage biotech
Datastage biotech in order to retain
Control as the economy collapse
This is
So consist
Love it
You just keep hitting the exact same points
This is clearly a designer virus we got to watch this is serious
Because they may move on us right now with martial law
Globalist argue Genesis
McDonald's chemical biological radiological testing on us in the past
We need to take what they're saying serious
But we believe it's a hoax
Well
He's now becoming more clear thank God it is a hoax
The lesser of two evils because
We know that it's a hoax
For them beta testing their federalization their takeover
And coming martial law
What could be in the fall of the winter
Of this year and early next year
And they even admit their beta test
We got clearly a designer virus erisa hammering that home
And now we have this prediction that
By the end of the year early into 2,000
We got martial law
None of this happened no
The Bureau of enforcement needs to show up
The reality is
Played out in 2009
Is
Ideal almost for everybody right
People got sick
The way that it weekend
And
Became
Start of a flu
A knot
Some of it was necessarily more dangerous than than normal
Hey that's great for the population
But it's great for alley
Because he
Can forget about all this b*******
But it's going to be tough to forget about it now 2019
20/20 2021 and now its 2022
The presentation to Performance
Surrounding code is not so far off of rails
But it's going to be impossible
But I'm making is
What
I believe
I believe that he thought he was doing another one of these yet until he wasn't
Yep by that point it was too late
It's too late
Yep you know it's almost like if you are Act
Actively searching for bad governor
And then you win
And then something that needs good governance happens
I think there's an under-appreciated at element for Alex that like his conspiracies legitimately rely
Lion diesel governor
Be things if what he wants to happen happens he
Is f***** so he needs people to ignore him
And give him money
Which is a tough tightrope to walk
Get sooner or later people are going to pay attention to you if you get enough money
I'm here we are
Subway
Napolitano
Sunday in
Napolitano Homeland Security head
Briefing
She said to everybody out there
He said
There
Is no need to shut down the Border or shut down and fly through anything
Because it's already spread everywhere and there's no way to stop it anyways
Besides Neuer worth
Coming in
Break room
This is an absolutely an accurate description of those comments that were made at the press conference
Speaking of efforts of the Border she said quote
We have implemented passive surveillance protocols to
The screen individuals who may arrive at our borders
All persons entering the United States from a location of human infection of swine flu will be
Be processed through all appropriate CBP protocols
Right now these are passive
Means they're looking for people who asked
Think about are you sick have you been sick and the like and if so
Then they can be referred over for further examination
Depart from that press conference that touches on the possibility of new strains popping up is not
Napolitano but
The comment made by the acting director of the CDC
Dr. Richard besser
Spencer says quote
We Analyze That
Strain are continuing to do further analysis of Xtreme
And we expect to see the emergence of new flu strain
That's something that we are continually watching for it
I'm sure they were ready should restrain emerge
That's not that there's. Immunity and protection in the community for it
This train is not unlike other new strains that have emerged
It's an assortment it's
Scott the genetic component
From a number of sources
Including human swine and avian sources
And that's something that you see with noose
Not that
It's so it's so crazy that. Cuz I feel like this is a fundamental thing that hasn't
Really been communicated to people
Add to the level that I think a lot of people just assume other people understand it but
But I mean viruses reproduce
And they don't clown
It's not exactly the same you'd like people to go on TV and be like okay
You know how when you have kids
Right they don't look exactly like you
Get right and then if you have like a billion kids
Eventually over a long enough. Of time
They're going to look completely different from you this is like that but because viruses do it all in like a day they do
Do a billion of those in
The day it happens faster
Do you understand now it's just like us
But it's a different thing
Well I think even that isn't
A good enough probably right you're really right honestly I think I think that
You know
The idea that you would have a and then once it transmits
Still a
Could be better
Reticulated
Kind of what bastards point
That there are combination
Sounds of things
Different sources
Isn't something that is
As surprising or weird as
It may seem
None of the comments that Alex describes
Napolitano were accurate in the least but that doesn't really matter
This isn't about reporting news or depicting reality
This is my caracteriza
Anime enf
Particular way
They want the virus to spread
Because doing so allows them before his vaccines on people and put in martial law so naturally
Napolitano isn't closing the Border
Intentionally
To make a virus
Spread bore
The enemy wants the public
2bm horrible fear so if course Napolitano ominously predicted new and worst strains of the flu
Which Alex interprets essentially as a threat
Just as he did with early Bill Gates interviews and the present
One thing I should know that
The looking at
This discontent
There's a tremendous overlap in terms
The tactics of narrative elements that Alex is using
There's a glaring difference
Interpret the stuff that I reviewed for this episode I'm not saying he doesn't match
Anywhere but
All the stuff I looked at it doesn't bring up Bill Gates
It's at all
Weird diseases Bill Gates
In the council 12
In 2009 I think he was probably Middleman
He's probably still very involved with world of Public Health
You know you can't really involved when you got several billion dollars hanging around able to
Direct his attention
The government figures that he didn't like
Bill Gates
Maybe wasn't nearly as much a
An evil figure
He had Obama yet Napolitano
Your billionaires
Because you got the government the most evil one you've ever had before it's got a Obama there
Makes more sense the idea that Obama would be able to put in Marshall R40 vaccine
Where is the leap from Bill Gates be able to do that is a little tough
Yeah you pull that off
In the present day
Not smoothly but he's done it and it helps that they've already created a massive mythology around Trump
Divorcing him from the reality of who the person is to the point where you can
You can say both
He's the most powerful man on the Earth
And he can't do anything about anything I do know he was tricks like this again
Unstoppable can't do anything
Here's some of the exact
Same sort of rhetoric that we see in the present
Republican by the phony Boogeyman terrorist in a cave
We're all guilty
The government gets to get involved in our lives and tell us what to do with
Our body
Inoculated
Inoculated to put us in prison we don't go along with what they say
Florentina's Lockhart cities down
Already beta testing with hotels in airports
And some people's homes in Texas
Does the galifornia
People are on quarantine
Police out front
He think I'm on house arrest
Actually tricked you that is eclipse
From 2020
It's not actually but it could have been you believe me
No that's what could have been
It would it's waiting is it
It's 2000
Debuted
It's almost indistinguishable from a lot of stuff that used to think about
Truly
Absolutely
Wonder One
Brutal
It's it's very clear my name
So
Look there are people who are fear-mongering
CNN
There's other people who aren't
Now here's an article not
Fear-mongering
Sign points to milder swine flu outbreak
Sphere
Don't tell CNN that
I don't tell CNN cuz I got this one article
Does Argos from Fox News that says is a Mach
The article
The quotes that are in it or from the very people Alex's
Claiming are hyping this up
Fear-mongering
Princeton
Dr. Nancy Cox a flu Chief at the
CDC said cook
We do not see the markers for virulence that we're seeing in the 1918 virus
Hope all is sighted in that article is suggesting that the
The flu may have run its course
Like ordinary flus
Alex wants to have his cake and eat it too any achieves this by crafting in Turkey
Get stories based solely on Headline
This box article is saying that the
The signs are pointing to a milder flu than
Want to beard
Just countered with the established
Meant to say
But because he ignores the body of the article Alex doesn't have to attend
Explain the fact that the article is based on comments from the people within the very establishment
Protractor fear-mongering bring in March
The law
Also if you look at the coverage
Of comments made by dr. Cox
Find articles in NPR
Who's titled flu Jean suggest virus not as deadly as 1918
I guess what you can even find an article from CNN using
The exact same quote
There is a story that Alex wants to
Hotel has no relationship to the reality in front of him which is why headlines are is most import
They're often flashy in vaguely written either due to life
Constraints or desire to drive clicks to website
Unless they're really easy to misconstrue which is about
75% of Alex's journalistic tool
And you see that in the present
You see that in the
Yeah you do I mean you do have to give it up for those solid 18th century newspapers in
Britain in the Lake Worth
Yeah
There is that
Around the World in 80 Days has like those character titles
Best cartoon
Novel of a chapter title
Ya solo
Where are we I think
I've made about a lot of the points that I wanted to make sure I hope to demonstrate with
You see you see these exact same tricks
A formula more or less play out
That's where Alex used
The beginning of the coverage of the covid pandemic
That you see here
With
The 2009 H1 N1
And now there's a little bit more to talk about but also this
Special that he did ends up going off the rails a little bit something nice to enjoy
European almost like dessert
What's this song
Instead This directly
Even in 2009 and emergency Special Report
That is an hour long
On the topic
Well I mean the topic is still more or less
Like
Consistent throughout its about what he has an idea for something
That actually is a lot of fun alright
Okay let me go for the other knows I'm about to walk we're going to call the White House on Air I had to mention that we're going to call the White House myself on air
Coming up in a few minutes
Then we're going to open up
The martial law what they're selling what they're pushing why this is so important
You're watching this in a month on YouTube
Music
You call the White House too because they're planning to run this in the fall to winter
This is great training for us
4th Ave North, the military takeover and locked
Inoculations for your safety
So you need to call Obama and the look Jack
We know what you're doing we know you're using this as the economy implodes
As an excuse to put troops on the streets and bringing martial law
Inviting College Ron Jack
You know I mean
I think what would I do appreciate that is I would speak to the president of the United States that way sure
Walgreens
Jack Obama did sort of curate the images like I sit down and have a beer
I think is anybody would be like
I'm going to I'm going to allow people to come buddy or friend I ever had
I think it would be Obama
I think Nixon to take a swing at you I think Nixon depends on how drunk he was
Sherp
Jfku get away with it
Well
What we called
Sure
Anyway there are some other things that are parallels to before we get to the actual song
Nnnn Bay admit
Reuters AP that were
This country and control their directing
The response of the CDC in the states in North
Gary Wertz his force inoculations that you have no rides
You do read all this for yourself in that this link
All week long up at infowars.com and prisonplanet.com
And imma give you the name of it
It's
Organization checklist for influenza pandemic
Preparedness planning on that list all International laws and treaties
Now that you this is real
The United Nations really exist here it is right here
Hey. Tell Glenn Beck this but
This was a document that the WHL put together in 2000
5 because of the avian flu outbreak
This is not a list of Demands the World Health Organization is making of everybody
A helpful guide to establishing best practice
This is to be able to be ready to respond in the possible effect of a new flu strain emerging
Where Health officials need to respond quickly to uncertain circumstance
It doesn't list any treaties or whatever Alex is saying that's all the
What is made up but we see here another direct parallel to
To the present day
It's important
The Takeover plan the
It's being facilitated by the outbreak is being run by the international globalist bodies that he imagined
In this framework looks like Obama and Napolitano or bad
But they're really just under the sway of these folks like The Whole30
We seen that time and time again in terms of international cooperation
The collaboration is presented as the
World Health Organization ruling Over America
Can sovereignty
That's a meaningless argument for Alex to make but it's
A very good way for him to fear Monger to his audience
It's been trained for years to be super afraid of the inevitable day when the UN and the international bodies were
To take over the United
He was doing that in 2009
He's doing that
Prior
Hurry up
Another
Maybe needs another
Bridget from that the predictions board
Just a one-trick pony
Yeah I mean
Sidetrack
Just sold
It's so disappointing that it
It still works
You do you
What year did you dream every if you spend enough time reading human history
You dream of that
Slow gross you know that like
Lesson upon lesson we grow in WeChat brick-by-brick
Book up in a new way
You learned your lesson from that and you can do spirit and it turns out you can just do the same as yet
30 years of being a millionaire
Well as long as
Do you have friends
Like I already and Joe Rogan
Nonno's in Richmond
Never go wrong with them
So anyway here's some more parallel to the present
Think about it
Governments everywhere on the verge of falling
Falling all over Eastern Europe they're falling all over the planet
Because of the world implosion
As they set up a new Bank of the world the new carbon tax
Are they lockdown cities how do they set up a police state
How do I ban public Gatherings have they banned protest
How many grandstand to save
Say hi Bob
A designer fluid out of designer flu
Scientist
Knuckleball
Looked at it
They would at least go yeah this is totally new and novel
Looks like it's an engineer this is scary
Fear
Was something special they got for vaccine for the black man
Does this type of stuff thousands of times
The all of this
Is
Exactly
I'm sounding like a broken record
So Alex is going to build up to take
Can call
Galt
The call to Obama
Look at what's going on and call the White House. The number when calling the moment 20-24
Revive shakes 1111
These are just papacy's are just actors
The real government is run out of the Rand Corporation and the Johnson Farm relation
Brag they shut all the real policies
The military dictatorship
I'm not in Virginia.
Northcom
Remember you're just crawling like a
So don't be rude of these actors
You know they work hard man they're tired
But now they go home Obama smokes a cigarette
Maybe it's a derby or something
No he's a really good actor he presents the script
Don't be rude let them know hey we know your actors
And the people will back you up
If you just won't stage Terror attacks are you know when your bosses take terror attack
Tell your bosses we know their hyping this
Sell the public important occupations in Roundup
We know Obama
Yeah but also be polite
I mean
Crate I love the offer
I love the way they're going about it
I think it's good advice
Certainly
You want to communicate with people if you want to reach
Like I do understand
You really see yourself working together with somebody when they approach you like that
Listen I know everything that you're about to
To tell me it's a lie and you're just an act because you're a f****** act there's no way for us
To communicate a real way
My presentation
That is a part of your act also
Sight unseen
I will not tell you what you need to agree with
You have to just guessing and everything and then I will believe you
Call Great clouds tricycle
We're calling the puppet so let's go ahead and call Obama
I'm going to go ahead and
Talk to him right now let's go and call the White House
Call Leah
Local theater going to the bathroom right now 2024561111
Call the local actors
We're sorry Your call cannot be completed as dialed
Call Michelle work
I told you the concert
Interchanging
Day today
The constantly changing the number
Stephen Starr
Favorite child
This is a misdialed and then has to walk it back to be like no it's okay
Conspiracy change the number routinely
Couldn't couldn't just let him try one more time before you go with it
Conspiracy
Then I never tried in your truck
The numbers Goodwin way
What World Cup
Lifeline the office is now closed
Comment is very important
President
Please call again between the hours of 9 a.m.
Not real quick
Do you get this answer message before we
Continue further
Clear Lake
He's going to
Pretend to leave a message
But there is no like answering
Moschino
There's a bee
Keep of the phone hanging up
Leave a message
No there's no voicemail voicemail he's really going to try and sell me
Them message literally said call back
Tomorrow
Eastern Standard Time
Friday
Direct telephone number is
Again
Thank you
Hi this is Alex Jones I'm a syndicated radio broadcaster and producing them
Viral
A videos on the web.
Yep down there is the latest version of
Presidential actor is this what you think leaving a message.
Just call the White House and let the person answering the phone said you should give this
To the higher-level while speechwriters and the people actually
Riding the inscription plays
For the actors
The American people are aware that Obama and George Bush and all of them are just puppets
Total new world order Papa
And that the posted infowars.com are not closed
On Saturday night
Yqr
Because this is the real world this is not a Shakespearean a thespian
A Troupe of actors we are info Warriors
In the Infowars supposing the New World Order
This is also like
Even if you was leaving a message this is
Useful
It's my specially a plug
There's nobody there leaving
A fake message that they plug for how great
We're not off
0 people but you're doing an emergency showed you usually are not
If I had it this isn't life
The show
I was going to say because
You could have edited out
The part where you left a message
2A not voicemail I think Alex is really into the authenticity of like
No
Just let him see it all
But I mean
Here's the thing
Okay
Nobody told him
Nobody but they don't take a message I didn't give him like a signal of like
He called beforehand
Before the show and they said that they didn't realize they don't
Ava ancestry
Well yes it is Saturday evening so they wouldn't have answered
Either no
But that doesn't stop him from
Continuing I'm leaving a message voice
It really puts the crazy
Crazy parts
We know you're not really even bad guys
Your actors
Your Hired Guns
To get out there and read off teleprompter
We understand that
But we're just saying that you was a puppet
Since you actually talked
To the bosses
Abenaki and pulse
Kashkari
And Geithner and others
We're just mid-level menus themselves to the Rockefellers and Rothschilds another
We're not your slave we're not your property this is our Declaration of Independence
My John Hancock I'm Alex Jones
I want to sign my name
Bisharp
Simulcast on radio and TV
I want the White House to know
We are not putting up with
Anymore
I'm not your slave You Don't Own Me
And you can stage all the bird flu swine flu crap you want to get involved in our lives
Poses are saviors in our bosses and shutdown public assembly is collapsing from your new world order
You guys did bring the drugs in together
We know that the
They staged this blue situation is a way to unify the people in
Get folks more worried about surviving then
Then I being slaves
But just know this we're not cowards we're standing up to you we're speaking out against you where where
Have your activities you want our comment
It's this
We know you as actors
Are aware that
Real human beings real people who aren't buying it as a puppy
Electrike
Are beginning to wake up what you're doing and we're not looking at the puppet Obama
The puppet bush
Are the puppet Barbara Boxer we're looking past the Papas right now
To the elite Mexican troll
And Ron Paul's got bills to audit the criminal fed private Federal Reserve Atlanta
Above all laws
Onlar NewsHour no police no judge node branch of government can even look at it
That's asinine exposing that
We're going on at the fabric and abolish the fat just like Madoff
Founder of the NASDAQ
Criminal one of your bosses
All of your end up going to prison after you been tried by
Junior Pierce
Unless you turn State's evidence
Against the New World Order today so again from infowars.com on the frontlines of the Infowars
Frontline's
True Liberty
This is my Emancipation Proclamation against you
I am not a sucker I am not a slave your neuro-linguistic programming and brainwashing gotten work on
Call me
And I'll say it again like they say in V for Vendetta ladies and gentlemen
Ideas
Our Eternal ideas go on forever and you can't stop the signal you can't stop the
The truth but you should join Humanity you should stop selling out to these degenerate
Old Potbelly European Rothschilds and Rockefellers
It's disgusting
The Joint Humanity White House
She lucky
Stop being actors join Humanity stop being puppy
I'm Alex Jones from Austin Texas
I hope you listen to me
Wow
Can I go long message if you'd like to go ahead and call up there ladies and gentlemen
Oh my God
What a
What a Showman
Ice
If I was at the White House
And I saw this
The next add be like well we got to have a voicemail
Maybe we got to keep that we got to keep these or actually I'd be like
We did it would not allow you to leave a five-minute message
I just say
Alex probably Ed run out of things
The cover I had planned
This chunk
And
I got to do it I got to do something
A stand-up and like
A b not working Jerry got to finish it
Power through
This is really dumb but if you think about it this is also an analog to the present day
These days
Every important person in the world
Comes to his shows we can just do full-on wrestling promos calling out people like Bill Gates
And the audience gets to feel that vicarious excitement of pretending that Alex is talking directly to
And telling truth
The power
You standing up to the tyrants and you're part of it
In 2009
Alex couldn't really pretend that anyone Empower cared all that much about what he was doing
So this is how that same kind of vicarious thrill for the audience was convey
How does pretending to leave a message on the White House comment line we're just drones on and on and declares independence
Which is supposed to be like a thrill for the listeners
It's pretending to take a risk
Which is clearly illustrated by Alex pretending to sign something with his John Hancock
This is meant to evoke the idea that the signers of the Declaration of Independence were taking a serious Risk by putting their names on paper
Cause was unsuccessful they would be immediately killed
For treason
This is the same kind of risk Alex wants to
Pretend he's taking by faker
Leaving a voicemail for the White House
I will say that it's kind of hard to tell which version of this is
The sketch that he's doing is satyr like
The version of the present or the past but I think it's probably the past because it requires the top
Of the fake,
Nightline message
No
Any any human being
I don't know anybody even being who is gone straight from poetic irony to Poetic irony
Unscathed
I mean the man
Literally left a voicemail to nowhere
Perfect microcosm of his life and career
Are you talkin to no one
Unassuming that somebody there listening to him and not just
Assuming nobody knows full well that no
No one's listening he wants the audio
Dance to believe
That he is talking to
A man walking from one poetic irony to the next
Just like not even bothering to look
The abyss don't even bother to look at him anymore if you miss
Blowback
This is over
God I've got to get a beer
Are we one last clip another parallel to the Press
We want it happens video go viral
People know this was all a mass hoax
We hope they're still a small chance that it may turn out deadly but certainly engineered by
Designer
That is extremely viral check out all the facts check out all the evidence check out all the information that we went over
Re-upping some of that fear a little bit and then trying to use it to promote
You know you got to share all this information
Got to make this go viral in order to protect everyone from the thing that I'm making you afraid of
Is called that the actor
For sale you know your clothes
I understand maybe this is retreating some territory a little bit
Inasmuch as I think that we've we've hinted at
Talked a little bit about
How some of this Dynamic works but
I felt that it was worthwhile to look
A little more closely at some of this
This formulaic nature of
The way that Alex presents
His coverage
Especially in the early stages of
Pandemics or Republican
That one of the things that I think is a limitation of this
Is obviously later on down the road Alex will transition this into
Swine flu vaccine is dangerous there
Horrible side effects that are coming from the swine flu
But it's almost impossible to
To create a parallel
How to how
He ended up having to weave things with covid-19. In his career because he never been
Stuck in that far out on a limb before
You never was forced
Do whatever he's doing now as it relates to
The swine flu or
To Ebola
And I mean I guess I'm thankful for that because that means less pandemics got out of hand
Is a limitation in terms of being able to trace
Like
This is the step that happens when your
Forced to
Right not move on
Right I mean
Awful part about alley
Is that his
Type of
Bulshit I guess can only flour in a stable environment
One that doesn't fluctuate so far off course that it gives into any of his extreme bulshit
And if
He is allowed to flourish in a stable environment
His presence will be a nun stabilizing aspect of it
Which will then lead to where we are now
A stable environment allows Alex to exist
Allows him to grow to
To the point where the on
Stable environment takes over
And then the cycle begins again
For 30 years
Well maybe we'll have learned better headlines
Mudlogger
That's the key
Makita information traveling my contribution to the information Warfare
Insisting the editors write longer and better headline
Long headliner make very
Clear what you're about to say
But cannot be Miss cover
Julie redundant to like to the Prairie Square even after they've explained their point they're like butts
Seriously we're saying this
Specifically
Not other thing
Anna like a breath Seas cough cough Alex
Serious
So we'll be back
On Monday with look at dealing with his old buddies roads getting arrested
Freeway and I bet it will not be great
Since that news broke a little bit earlier and
You know all of the
People who are most instrumental in
The rise of the Oath Keepers I don't think you can name somebody more
Intimately entwined than Alex like he's been around since before
They were an actual organization Stewart Roads
Gaston Alex's show sent
Announce that I believe so
Germinated through Infowars
So I can't imagine Alex taking this very lightly
Up until then I always website
5 - 8 Jordan Emilio and Leo albizzi Xbox
And now here comes
Sex robot
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color