Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
Pray I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing
MoneyGram
Dot-com
Acknowledge
The young man known as Alex Jones
And that's as much as I can get fancy on it
Is a little bit of Arissa little
Not quite the the intro that
Cement your legacy
Yeah so hey to Jordan
I have a question or you sir
Question
You go first
My bright spot then is restart the new season
Upgrade Pottery Throwdown
You know we've talked about the Great British baking show
And one of the judges is this guy who is an exceptional and incredible
Pottery maker emotional man
He cries like six
Episode
Paul Hollywood give them a handshake in your life who is weeping
He just cries and normally it would be like disingenuous bulshit but this time
He's f****** love Pottery too much
It's crazy
I may have that may give it a shot but that you're talking me out of it actively with it
It's amazing Tuesday
The pottery then no they don't
The coolest part is in the first season
There was the assistant guy who would do all the
The Kiln Pottery and then put it into the
You do the same
And then
At the beginning of the pandemic
They couldn't get
Co-host
So they gave him
Break the system
Diamond in the rough
Wow credible know who killed
To be a trans person who is kicking ass
It's amazing so we could hire another assistant but not another co-host
TV is the credit okay
It's cheaper to hire from within this is confusing but I'll give it a shot
I'm so happy my Brightspot Jordan humans
A little bit
I can sense
I had a bunch of little irons in the fire that are coming to fruition
Down the road and I feel I feel
I feel alive in the work which is getting a little bit frustrated for a little bit but I feel I feel
Second wind
Upon me
Also
Either something
For today and that is that I have a new text
Democrat drops out
Ooo-wee Aria
Bright spot of my shorts
The first Vivi that you're smart your nail polish
Do Yorkshire Stephen peeve
Yorkshire Stephen text americh not Emerick
Thank you so much you and I'll probably walk
I don't approve of this
No no more
Like we have three technocrats today to say thank you to in celebration of this.
So first I went on a road trip and all I got was addicted to this podcast thank you so much you're now a technocrat
Next
Mark
But not Mark Richard
Thank you so much you run out
Technocrat
An embed singing along to the theme song Jordan I'm sweating
You are now.
Technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
My enemies
Ali G for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
For you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
All your s***
Maybe the next few moments
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologize to
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
Thank you so much as a little inspired by
Call the story picking up random things that he said I decided to
You really gave it and it was a whole paragraph honestly yeah yeah
It seems like
This could all be from the same episode
100% could have been every 15 minutes you just cut
Play different clip that's what that's my favorite part about it it's a it's a Pastiche of
What kind of different episode where this Behavior
Japanese
Keep popping up
Today we have an episode to go over going to be talking
About January 13th
And figure something out
Okay
On this episode of course
That is the day that Stewart Roads got popped
Duro's went down
Oh yeah
Erodes the leader of the oath keeper and
Dear dear dear dear dear friend
Valic
Guest of Alex's show for 13 years
You would say
Thickest additional
You got arrested and apparently an FBI raid
Or something
Did the situation is kind of
Nebulous and I'm clear on the on this episode
Because the news break
Lakes in the middle of the episode
Spoiler alert get word of this
Cuz Alexander text him about it
Alexander has the scoop
Okay and Alex thinks he's got an exclusive
Two-story Antilles
He is pretty excited about it
IFixit
Maybe people expected Alex have a total freak out like RNR new technocrat drop right
He handles it shockingly well which actually leads me to Theory and we'll get to that theory over the course of
What episode of a Feeling
About 2 about
I think he knew this was coming
I think he knew when he
Chewed up at work
If there's a good chance
Stewart was going to get arrested
Imagine Stewart
Staffieri inkling that
It was going to happen
600 week we start to show off
Fanta Alex
Scott win
Of some
Chimera related issues
I told you they were going to
Human clones
Sheep
Cows
Gross human organs inside of them for transplant
You said I was crazy though was already happening before I was ever on the air
28 years ago
First perceives a heart from genetically altered
New York Times
If you're just listening to this show you might think of the New York Times is reporting that that pig was there was the source of the heart that was transplanted
The thing itself was part human
Because that's how Alex read the headline
But everybody
Alex is lying and adding things to the headline because that's the only way he can make himself sound interesting
It pays off the impression that he's always been right about every
The actual headline is quote in a first man receives heart from genetically alter
3rd pick
Alex is just
Decided he's going to report that the genetically altered part of this headline
It means that this big was part human but that's just him making
King stuff up
In reality the genetic alteration of the pig and undergone was a gene editing process quote
To remove a sugar in it sells that's responsible for hyper-fast organ rejection
This is one of the greatest challenges with organ transplanting
Even though in theory pig hearts are compatible with our bodies
He's generally speaking
Genetic alteration that removes the particular sugar
In terms of solving the gigantic problem
Of organ shortage
That the people will have
Then they need trance
Wow
Another important thing to keep in mind is that we don't actually know how well this is
Going to turn out
Just yet
The article in the AP about this note that back in 1980 for child named baby say was the recipient of a
Planted baboon heart
Actually survive for 21 days but then died
You're not far enough out from this
To know exactly how well this is going to work
This is wild stuff but it's not at all the kind of chimera shirt that Alex talks about all the time
He believes that there are fish with sad human eyes swimming around in tanks in the basement of the lab at the University of Austin
That's the level of thing he needs
Before he can claim any kind of I was actually write credibility
I'm not going to say that
Don't
Get where Alex is coming from because
When I hear
Genetically modified pig heart
Put into a man
I see the week before
Whenever they went temple of doom on a giant Pikmin
602 sterilize your hands
First
Cut around it.
It's to the skin is too thick
Yeah
I mean
Are we at we know this from list
To the show
I am talking about it just been a little bit mad recently
No argument for me
He's been mad that I think is
Bulshit
I tried my best and I prayed about it
ITube not get angry
And
The biggest thing is
Personally on us
Or show me where the top and so crazy
As a man it is almost like I don't even want to address it
Or talk about
What a set of brass balls.
This dude has to complain about personal attack
Being at this careers essentially been made on
Hey characterized by intense personal attacks on people based on lies
And misrepresentation
Don't care about whatever personal attacks Alex thinks he's dealing with
I wasn't doing show enough that I know when he says personal attacks
He means things like
Sandy Hook families suing him because of his personal tax on to them
He's awake baby you can't resist making himself a victim of every story because he thinks that somehow proves that he's
Under attack because
Cuz he's so right all the time and he's dangerous.
The system
Does the performance of Nursing
Anti consequences being misinterpreted
As
Integrity
You consider personal attack
Let's brainstorm some personal tax would calling somebody a demon be a personality
Yeah
Saying that their faces
Hideous be a personal attack
I mean it's certainly
Would arguing that they were perhaps a pedophile cabal member
Be a personal attack
See him it seems like it okay
Well I think Alex might have been guilty of his own personal attack
I think
Vets
Like a lot of those
Senses that you're talkin about our public figures
+ 2
Like some degree yeah I kind of got a
Shake that off
Like Hillary Clinton's never going to really be all that could
Concerta
Private citizens on the other hand
Alex's personal checks on
Private
Petro
So bad
I'm talking about the personal taxi at the deal with oh yeah
Don't care
Alex I think his religion
Manteca
Lisa's uShip
I signed on to this I wanted to fight evil
I want to stand up against corruption
I am so blessed
And More Lies than ever been
Unbelievable
I'll be up to be someone alive God
I'll just say this more than
Caroline
For the average human
I'm just.
And I it's just people tell
That sucks
Let stuff go to cross to bear. Literally he's not that align with God
What a curved cross to bear
I feel like the Bible please remind memory other
Growing up in the trees Jesus
Going to also
Isn't particularly thrilled with people who use religion as a
Performance
I'm bragging about your connection with God on a radio shows probably something that most folks would use being
Lubbock distasteful
According to the Bible
You know I remember him talking something about humility
Amanda
Boy
Claiming that you are closer to God than most people
Coraline's God than most people in the weird thing to say
Yeah it's
It's a probably exactly the opposite
Thing that the Bible would tell you is beside his clothes
Bet you would finally ends that sentence with
It hurt
Writers maybe you're not that closely aligned with Jesus at all the fires of hell
So this kind of weather versus this brings to mind is Matthew 6 verse 1
Beware of practicing your rights
Just missed before other people in order to be seen by them
For then you will have no Rewards
From your father who is in heaven
Later in that very same chapter quote
And when you pray you must not be like the HIPAA
Street corners
Truly I say to you
They have received their reward
Yeah I think we've talked
Many many a time about praying on are being super black
It's a it's a
Something goodbye was pretty clear but like
You're not going to get anything for this
Because the presentation of Raichu
Dismiss that you're you're tricking people with
That is your reward you have gotten it already. Whatever you need
Danger Millions don't
And gotta do is not going to give you s***
So what
Do you think Jordan
Last couple years
Coverage
And wrestling with this
What's covid about
Oh boy
Oh God
What's the plan
And every time you ask me this question I feel like I could come up with 6
Steam different ads
What do you think that over Arch
Plan is
The overarching plan
Is to replace humans
With
Cyborg
We've talked about that one I think that's the one I'm going to go with
Has been a plan at some point I feel like that's the one that's the winner for me not today
You know what all this is rather
This is a declaration of war
Criminal group
Hijacked our nation the world
Of exactly what they're going to do to you and me and everybody else
Training wheels
The military at the hospitals and
All of this is just a behavioral you ready
To soften us up for martial law
Oh
I thought it was to kill everyone I thought everyone was dead already
I'm going to take a nap already
Recover the bioweapon
This is Bishop doesn't even make sense
I told like
What you have to do is understand that this is
Convoluted and impossible to follow because there is no Center to it out
What is preaching
Forget about the fact that there isn't a real world nefarious plan is covering
There isn't even a concrete plan that Alex has made up that
Explains everything that's going on
Do you have to jump around from framework to framework depending on what seems useful to him that day because
You just making up a story as he goes along
His heart and the weight of his career really drive him towards wanting to cover things as a plot to get us into Peabody
Can't specially him his body
But the real good money right now in the
Conspiracy world is anti-vax
Extremism
So it's hard to know which way to go sometime
He's lost
Spinning irreconcilable yarn
Because he has no idea what to do in an actual emergency
The only knows how to respond to fake ones that he's made two
The freak-out is audien
It still doesn't know what to do
He's just scrambling
Every single word he says is on the brink
At any moment I might topple off
Unlike some headline he read
I don't know what mood he's in whether or not he's hungover
Going into your mouth
Yeah it could be were all dead
Covid is a plan that they've had forever to depopulate the entire world
So the globalist can run around in their new Eden
That's one thing they could that could be there or he could be that all of this has just been an excuse
To bring in
Tops
In the in the hospitals
And checkpoints in order to
Soften us up
So they can breathe easier and I know I get that but if they're not going to
To kill us all and replace us all the cyborgs are like
Move into armored
Ridout's in and let everybody else die
We're doing just fine on the road to martial law without a
Global Escobar you know what I'm saying like
The regular old folks
They're on their marching towards martial law we don't need global
I want globalist to bring the heat
That's what I'm saying if you want something a little bit more creative weather weapons not just
The jackboot
He loved the government on my throat I think I might advise or you just be wait until Alex is in that kind of mood
Wait until there's a natural disaster that out
Explain away as not being a consequence
Right
Stuckey's if you will
American Republicans here
Terrorism plan
Opposition
Create one-party state
5 inch tall stack right here in others
Admissions
Republicans are terrorists
The new Nationwide group
Who's going to watch you
Control you
Teach you than white people
Alright
The end of the American Republic
The title of the show that he's in the middle of recording
That's the page that has the embedded video out
So that's awesome
Is kind of what
He hits on over and over and over again
In the beginning of this episode
This idea that this weekend of the Republican they're banning
Any kind of dissent in all this
It's so
Kind of focus
In that direction
Believe me to think that he knows that's who it's going to be
It seems it seemed almost like
Softening us up
For the blow of
See if they get Stewart
They're coming after you are very rarely Fifi Matic
Coherent
And this this to me felt like
Distinct
Pics of
Preparation
So Alex
And some other stuff you want
Let's talk about
That is how he's always right
Since I mentioned this
By c.s. Lewis
Screwtape letters
C.s. Lewis quotes
Sonny said he cannot
Present State understand eternity
That is what Mortals
Misunderstand
They say of some temporal suffering
No future Bliss can make up for it
Not knowing that heaven
Once attained
Even the glory
Pleasure they say
Let me have but this
The consequences
This is absolutely not from the screwtape letters I was about to say there's a countdown on it
Not being from the screwtape
That's the only CS Lewis book Alex
This is read or listen to sense a lot of the others
Also some of the ideas in like Mere Christianity or the problem of pain might be challenging to digest inator
I don't think he's up for
I guess he's probably maybe read The Lion the Witch and the Wardrobe and I would guess what he thinks I has landed a globalist
Alex is obviously a fan of the screwtape letters because it's a work of fiction that's written as a series of correspondences between two demons
Who was written in 1942
Stickley recalled the book being
Very popular in the Evangelical community that I was apart of in my youth
I wouldn't be too surprised if it was a it wasn't a similar situation with Alex
Someday and growing up
Very accessible to
The church communities
Trivia
Be teacher in Calvin and Hobbes
Named after the screwtape letters
Is wormwood yeah
Constellation of the demon in the book it
Also I think that's Alex
Like I think you read the word son there and that's what made him think it was the screwtape letters
Cuz he's forgotten the demons in that are uncle and nephew not fathering
The cord that Alex's reading is actually from another of Lewis's novels titled the great divorce
Also I have
Absolutely no idea what this has to do with him like demonstrating that Alex has been right about anything cuz it's under the hashtag
Indication of him
Maybe
Racks cuz he insist
Play trumpet different book
Yeah that's a little kid
Confusing
This episode
Starts out
So boring
They
C.s. Lewis Miss quotes are where I'm at
That is a good point
Eddie in it on a good day we skip over him messing up c.s. Lewis
Sometimes that is a waste of our time for today
Today
Business
Pics the f*** out
Is a Prison Planet
Understand everything here
This is all
Little bit more than just a test you see
What
He's a prison
This planet
Is purgatory
And if you fail probation
What
You cut off a god
The Gods like I'm going to give you one last chance
Body-conscious on this planet
We'll see what you accept what you what you go towards
But I'm going to warn you one more time I'm cutting you off
Regatta
That really freaked me out because
A completely shattered what I thought Alex meant by prison
Complain that this whole time
I have understood the term like the way I take most sane people
You're trapped on
Yeah I had absolutely no idea that
This is what
He met and now that I do I'm struggling to grasp what it means and how it impacts
His ideas
In his world
If what he saying here is to be believed then part of the prison planet actually involves us haven't been
Sentence to being here on this Prison Planet
There's something that precedes our birth that we did that was bad and required God to give us this Cosmic probation on
That's pretty f***** up and I would like to Alex to explain more about
Yeah I would need a lot more biblical
I think I think one way to look at this has to be talked about original sin but I wouldn't
I think that's the case because
Alex wouldn't go along with the belief that all humans are inherently born
Guilty
That would fly in the face of his steadfast belief
Individualism
Free Will in the rejection of guilt by association
No idea what he's talking about it
Fascinating
Like if you die young does that mean you got out early for good behavior which is why Only the Good Die Young
Possibly
Who knows I mean Janis Joplin's gone
Are near-death experiences just meetings with the parole board
Like what's happening
There's so many possibilities for this imaginary friend a snitch
Possibly none of this makes sense
And if I had the gas
I really think it would just him freestyle
That's what that's how I heard
I didn't think that this is actually something he believes
Are you stalking
Penny doesn't realize the intricate nonsense that he's implying
At least that's what I thought until I heard what he said neck
Devil worshippers are going to Andrea Victoria Morales jump
Okay
The domestic Terror
The evil one
The Badman which of course I'm not
The point your fingers
I got your trying to get you to
Get out of this together
Last year
And I know you song You Are
So you will pay
And not by my hand
I just want to wait from you
God has promised
He will separate us from you
Jesse's everybody exits California New York
Play the left
Imagine that spiritual energy
Alicia
Being away from them forever
Penne pasta
And they're gone
You have total completion total peace with God
Had to have the cash you had free will
You did some bad things
I fear
We don't know yet
We are
Are here
Jimmy tested
What
What is me
I wish
I'm telling you
A lot of trouble cuz if you think this planet is bad
I got a good look at it
Weather.com
Tomorrow's news today
And you know what I'm thinking this is
Starting to put everything together okay alright
All religion
Ginger Trail all real happening all the time okay
Alex
Is a demon
Who escaped
From hell
Only to wind up on this planet
Alright
Living is demon leeway's and all he wants
To get off this rock but he does want to go back to hell
Here we are
This makes
Perfect sense
I think it's interesting that he describes himself as a trustee
So f****** weird
I know know what's happening
Alex Munoz
What goddess
A skier
What would like why wear on a Prison Planet
Can't say it on the radio because we're not supposed to know this
Let me reinterpret that for you reality
Alex got in over his head talk
About this and bragging about how he knows Cosmic Secret
And realize like I better stop this because
If I say anything concrete
I can't walk
Pocketbac
Vague I can imply that I have this magical mystical knowledge
Specific people hold me to that
It's something really serious to hold you
You two that you think is is
Cosmic
Like
Spiritual reality
That you're aware of
It's not like
Something that you could I could maybe get a little bit wrong
Right pretty concrete
And you don't want to be nailed down like that cuz he was making s*** up
Yeah I'm a little bit frustrated that we can go directly from a hashtag Alex Jones was right clip to Alex
Jones claiming that he is seeing hell
And is escaping the
Purgatory of manhood by
Asking God to remove him
Trustee powers
Yeah but means well that's if he's writing about that you can give that hashtag
Haha
I don't know how we would ever know
That's a great thing
Completely under
Unfalsifiable it depends on whether or not we have near-death experiences
F*** you too Alice for this nonsense presentation of
I know
I know what we did in a past life or whatever but I can't say it on the are your self
Saying that I apologize to Alex for not recognizing he's a demon who escaped from hell and is trapped in a human
Body on Ark
Planet
Some interesting like
Like movie and
Demon trapped Escape From Hell trapped on a prison planet of Earth
Rye Arts
Right-wing conspiracy
Yeah yeah
Got just what the f***
F*** get out of here believe that you would
Allow that to happen
And let somebody record it
Be proud of it
When are the next day
Anyway
Ocean
It really hit me in the last few weeks
They're just so fantastical
Ashley be living this life
Bubbles plans.
Social credit scores 20 years ago in Hollywood
People that eat too much fat
Will have smartphones that track what everybody does
Course you know it's a total nightmare it's on Earth
Rules
For so many angles to this there's so many angles to this
Thought about
How I'm going to cover this
Poorly
Because this is so important
And then I just get here to the point of talking about it
It's like such a big deal
Talkin about it almost lessons
This isn't just something we're talking about this about that
Mike's
We're about to have a hurricane here
It's about to be winter time
So it's about to be summertime this is
End of civilization
And they're running around
Tell people that are going to buy into it
Doesn't exist in the same moment as a minute and a half
Nothing
Killing time
Yeah but you noticed that Alex memories
Weirdo esoteric ideas
It cheapens it to even talk about it now
You think the afterlife would be the cheapest
This kind of same game it's usually with like I don't want to get into
The News-Gazette
Prepare
And people
Expect me to actually know the stories that I'm
Going to get into
Yeah just making
But how I've seen hell has the Hallmark of avoiding doing a book report
Like you know Miss
Listen I would love to
To tell you about the Adventures of Tom Sawyer
And Huckleberry so please do that
I-88
Too big of a
Honestly it did you have so much going on all of this stuff
This is a classic hits 100 years old
Who am I to report on a classic car
People who have done doctorate
It's interesting really when you think about it how many behaviors Alex demonstrates on arrows that are there
The children
There's a there's a lot of overlap
The news Alex talks about a meme that he saw
You give such contacts to three weeks ago
Letters to foia requests have summer systems in Europe
In the Netherlands where there
Bleeder their Parliament
Is getting orders from Pascua
The forward to the Dutch version of it in
Tells the leader of the government
Have you heard of the great reset
So I went to completely bungled this story and gotten all of the details wrong
He's doing this intentionally because that's the only way to get this story to fit into his predetermined narratives of class swap secretly controlling
All of the world's politician
So the first error is that this wasn't something that leaks like the beginning
System
An MP request
Did some documents and they were provided
These were not secret documents they are just in
Invitations that were sent to various Dutch politician
51st World economic
Forum
Did the organization that was started by Klaus Schwab so that's how you factors into that part of
Alex's reported this as the leader of the parliament getting orders from Schwab which is a lie and the invitation
That were released didn't even
Include one
For the head of the parliament
Body of government in the Netherlands is called the House of Representatives
It'll really have so much of a parliamentary leader is they have leaders for each of the parties
That are represented Within
In the house
And there are a bunch
House does have a group called The presidium
Which includes the speaker
And 9 Deputy speaker
So I guess this maybe would what you'd call a house leader
Speakers currently Vera Bergkamp
Map of the Democrats 66 party
And she wasn't one of the recipient
Map of the invitation
And so this is a little bit
Murky
Invitations went to finance minister wopke
And the former Minister of Foreign
Development Sigrid kaag
This is not weird
I don't not know
Also along with these damn invitation
When's the government release some correspondences between the wi the world economic forum and Eric weebs
The minister of
Economic Affairs and climate policy
Regarding a letter of intent
Explorer Grant from the world economic Forum regarding
Creating
Food Innovation Hub
So none of this comes even close to what Alex's report
Okay so
It's a
Deadly secrets
Terrifying
Because
The finance
Person
Got it is talking to the finance body
About getting Finance
Yeah it's okay it's big
Dud the first part of the Galaxy sayings
Context of this
So the video that Alex is covering
He's talking about was posted by a Twitter account called Ringo Lennon last July
Who's actually posted by a number of other accounts but I chose that one because their profile image is the Infowars logo
So I thought it was
I was expecting it to be the be
Alex said this happened the other day
That's great
It is true that this video shows a young Dutch politician named Gideon
Ameri I met her in
Prime minister mark rutte
What he thought of the book The Great reset
Ricky says he did
No the book and then Gideon produces a letter that Rudy it sent
Klaus Schwab thanking him for sending him the book
Gideon accuses him of lying and then the Prime Minister explained
But he doesn't have time to read every book that he gets that new was polite
Response to Schwab
Dude
Interaction was super popular in the dum-dum conspiracy world back in July
And I guess Alex just saw it and thinks
Or
It had something to do with these misrepresented World economic Forum invitations that came out recently
Do the shity work all around
Just nothing
It's worse than nothing
Is a full story that's the that's the stand-up comedians
The other day
My one-year-old needs she's six now the other day whatever I wrote this joke 5 years ago
The part about
The prime minister of the Netherlands writing
The forward for the Dutch version
Of
I have no idea if that's true I don't
It's definitely not true from the video that Alex's siding
It would seem odd
Yeah it's okay
I don't know
Anyway Alex thinks he's got this scoop
The scoop about the Dutch Parliament
That happened last year
I picked it up yet
Heliball to death
Passionate about
Is the forest
Is too busy to be Satan
Seems I'm trying to run every aspect of your life
I think Paul probably said that I could write an article about it cuz
Probably did last July
Oh my God this is bro
Exclusive
Oh my God I'm not going to send an email back on this
Oh I forgot I've got lost in my Spanish
Who's trying to cover this end of this the Republic news and how like
There their opposition the Democrats are
And all this
I kind of wish on it so you got try again next time
Try again next segment
This Is Not Mere building suspense
Who
Is the most important player with millions of a couple million
100000 person
Football field
Conservatively
Really
Exaggerating
Please list
Chameleon
Humongous
Choked up because the audience is so bad
Because
I don't come up with words to describe just how damn evil this is
Timor
Flight 567
I'm trying to say that the exaggerated also lies a lot
This is just more killing
Time is so stupid
That's amazing
About that audience
And I like
That is absolutely exaggerating
Play Shreya Ghoshal radio
There are millions of people listen
Including his dreaming numbers in his download
That means that he
Conservatively has
Twice the audience of Joe Rogan
Oh yeah easily I assume that Joe will be coming on Infowars
To start getting more viewers
Years ago he did cut an ad where you said that
Conservatively 10% of the world
You did say that
I'm close to his wreck his ratings
This is this is stupid
I would guess that maybe
Maybe
2 million people live with
In the range of the station
Play I was just on the radio
Maybe
It is possible
Where a lightning strike to knock out every other form of entertainment available to people within this
Radius of space
I would be surprised if any
Fiesta Fringe radio stations carry his show anymore
Any of those stations that like maybe played him like on
Rebroadcast on The Late Shift
Make a coast to coast
I imagine those people have gotten
God
Cut cut
Chord just be so funny if like
Local NPR Chicago Philly
It just was like we're going to play an hour of Infowars everyday we just have to work tomorrow and what are we going to do
Play another all things
Is considered what are going to do
So today we're going
Switch things up on Sunday we're replacing Garrison Keillor
Gilmore Lake Wobegon
God that beautiful hair the better really strong women are above average
The better something is looking
Whatever
Yep
Alex's got a giant audience
Some things are bad so he feels real responsibilities
Don't think that you'd actually
List of
Unquote
That there now
Noosh
Just like this
Main Street Main Street Banks
This is yet another story Alex's
Completely misreporting based on misreporting done by other sloppy blogs
This is a story that traces back to the Daily signal which you can
The media Outlet by the fact that one of their featured news categories listed on the homepage of their site is critical race
Spirit yeah
That's an indication that
Really our reporters aren't there more of s*** hat
Yeah that that type
Type of website is like we're need to hire somebody for just
Jews segments like oh no oh boy
7 people and they critical race Theory feet
Alright whatever
Okay about so this article was published on January 11th that appear stupid written by two fellows at the Edwin meese
The third center for legal and judicial studies at the Heritage Foundation
Which means they are
Cool
They're reporting on an announcement that was made by the pretrial services agency in the District of Columbia who are going to make
Maintain records on employees exemption
To take vaccine
If you go when you read the posting in the federal registry it
It's very clear this is an administrative decision and it only applies to be
Employees of this age
They have the ability and the authority to do this and there's nothing weird about this at all
However the daily signal reports this very suspiciously
A tiny administrative agency in the District of Columbia announced a new policy Tuesday that will likely serve as a model
For the whole of
Push to assemble
Have Americans who objected on religious grounds to a covid-19 vaccine
From there the Articles pretty dumb and boring
But using this article other Outlet start to play a little game of telephone
On the 12th of these citizen Free Press published an article with the headline quote vitamins quietly
Creating a database of the unvaccinated
Which is a mischaracterization of there already dicey source
After that Alex
Skip this and becomes mainstream news admitting the bidens creating list
Devon vaccinated people so you can come
Your house to take a shot
That sounds right
This is a pathway that b******* Alex reports typically goes
There's something that's not really that controversial that's the primary source
Which gets covered by a group of s*** had to sensationalize
And then that sensationalized article is covered by even more disreputable Outlets who slapped this on his head line on it
At which point Alex reads the headline and makes up a story about it
This is the quality of information you give someone like Alex is worth
Is just
Sweetly meaning
I feel like the Heritage Foundation
Is the world
Largest
Per capita maniacal laughter Factory
Like after every
Evil thing they do I expect them to be like
So ask for the white people can't get Anna
Way Messier on Alex
This traces back to a video of a person going to a covid treatment
And trying to get monoclonal antibodies would being told that he apparently can't get them
But he could if you were Black Or Hispanic
The video is Shawty and it's not very clear and it's definitely missing context but that's what it appears
Michelle
I left that one important
Detail
The person in that video trying to get the antibodies as Infowars employee Harrison
Well there is that
There is
Alex says that the mainstream media admits that white people can't get monoclonal antibodies
Video on his show the night
Before and intentionally edited out the part at the end where the healthcare workers tell Harrison
But he can't get the treatment quote
Because of a lack of underlying health
Tucker did a painfully racist segments based on his manipulated video that was produced by fours reporter
Without disclosing that he's Infowars reporter
He's just a guy man just somebody trying to do junior varsity
Project Veritas
That's f***** up it is that really need some sort of intervention if Tucker Carlson is playing an Infowars video on
On his f****** show
That many people to it without any Kaiser hospital where do citizen reporter
For Infowars that's f***** up
Weather playing the video
Harrison of Texas or whatever their handle days
And then his slug for like the works
His future news. News
Which I guess is another one of the redirect URL is that Alex has
To Infowars or Bob and I video
That's f***** up as anybody
Where you got this
Information from
Because you know it would be suspicious
Really really bad
For Tucker if you was
Strength to carry off of this
Very racist segment
Appointment
Horrific
I mean I'm sure it's pretty par for the course for Tucker play
Man so some of the other stuff I've covered in this episode
Is really bad work likely Dutch Parliament
This is actively malicious
There's no way the Tucker doesn't know that Harrison Smith works at Infowars
There's no way whoever put
Lease together didn't know that the nurse
Explains why he can't get the treatment
I decided to cut that part out so they can push the racist narrative
Alex knows that Tucker is reporting the story based on his employees bulshit
But still reported as the mainstream media admitting you can't get antibodies
If you're white
These are all intentional Act
And they're designed to elicit a certain reaction in the auto
And that reaction drift
Pretty much all the way into white nationalism
These people don't actually think that white people can't get monoclonal antibodies
Pretending that they
I do think that is
The most effective way for them
Past off
Spreading the racist messages
Hi behind like being offended if someone suggests that their race is my God
I just
If that's
That's so
F******
I that should be on
Every news station right like Tucker Carlson plays Infowars clip
Just like nonstop
Tucker Carlson
Drive to Trojan Horse Infowars content
Where's video
To make his Infowars point to you
But I mean
How does it how can you get away with that
Baby won't allow Alex Jones's name to be spoken in a positive way
Yeah and like clearly
Someone at Fox News new did absolute it in the Chiron putting
Harrison of Texas or whatever, would have been a problem
And that's why
That should be that's
That should be picked up
That's such a f******
Blatant example of every
It shows a lot of intent
I'm start a riot
That's so bad
So Alex
Gets into well
The meat
The meat but he's been putting off okay
Maybe you've been putting it off because his his lawyers have told him talk
And I have had lawyers and other people
Basically asked me not to
And in respect
To them
I
Around them so they wouldn't be involved and reverse-engineer already.
And I don't need to even tell you what personally happen to us because I have it all
Right here
Cover but this is really bad.
This is like
Erwin's in Northern California
What you got about
This is not
I'm not happy
And believe me I'm in this with you
To my eyeballs I'm in this
Debrid probably somebody out there
But he does understand what power so this is Tyson all that as well
So you don't like him anymore
Beats around the bush is really bad at getting to the point
She is
He is done a parallel construction and figure it out that the FBI has a counterterrorism investigation
Open
Into him
And the Army is involved or something
Okay it's it's a wide-ranging
Conspiracy that he's got support for this evidence
Is that some of his vendors
I've told him
Set the SBI is asked
Some questions about their
I don't know if that's true or not but Alex is a
Extrapolated that out into
I have a empty terrorism investigation
There's FBI agents following me everywhere they've tapped all my phone's all this
And I think
Some of this
Is
Like I said
Because he knows the
I think it's some of it is.
Prepare
And a little bit more
People happen
Maybe Alex is going to be nice
Here's Where We Are
Months ago the FBI
Came
Sam
Montoya was out here at the office
Bellator SWAT team
Owen Shroyer got arrested and indicted
About what you got indicted for
See you at you got these did this
So the Preamble of
Yes
Serramonte got in trouble because
He videotaped
Himself doing plugs for Infowars
Wow breaching the capital
Iom got in trouble because
He had a
Deferred judgement
From the last time
He got in trouble
And I didn't do his community service violation of
When he was at the Capitol
This is just like
He's trying to build this up as like
Some kind of it they're targeting us specifically not there
Very clear reasons why
You have other people didn't
Really it's an attack on white
White people
Spectrum
It says
FBI counterterrorism
The Main Tera threats
Wrong.
What an incredible
I don't want to be enemies with Waze
They are enemies of this country
Attempt
To format more feelings in the audience that white people are under attack
That's about all that's going on here but some great news for Alec
He doesn't have to worry about Andrew
McCabe because he retired from the FBI in March 2018.
Did I miss something that big though it's
Because you just
A couple of names that he remembers
Christopher Ray might actually be trouble because he is still head of the FBI but like you said
Be cool right like Trump
Appointed him
Neither Republican
Cool man now he's been overtaken by the beatsteaks I get something I don't like
Right tomorrow he's actually secretly working against the Deep state right
Yep it's
Pretty
I mean it's cleared
It makes total sense
Alex's lawyers have been talkin with the January 6th
Committee apparently
This might be some of the stuff that Alex's lawyers didn't want to
I'm sitting here
They're just a sideshow for the just Apartments doing
Telling them that
Domestic terrorist
Material support to terrorists
Okay.
Organizing
Almost rallies around the country
And the peaceful ones in DC that led up to January 6th
Where is
As the driven snow
When it comes to 1
Why the hell would I want to
January 6th committee can't charge Alex of any crime like that better be the responsibility of the Department of Justice
Switch the committee is not
The public face of
Regardless of what Alex
I suspect he thinks it is because in his ideal version of Politics on
Summit government
While Trump was in office Alex would have loved committees investigating Hillary's emails or Benghazi to just some Byerly arrest
That's what he wants
He wants that kind of abuse of power to be directed towards everyone else's bathing the same way when they're not
This is probably what Alex's lawyers don't want to talk about
I like.
Because it's actually what the
The committee is saying but because
You might be in hotter water than it seems
So this is the date like this the David Stewart Rhodes is
The news of his arrest broke and I want to make a bit of a retraction on some of the thing
Things that I've said before on the show
I've been of the opinion that Alex is kind of grandstanding about his concern about the January 6th committee
Actually any trouble but I want to rock
Walk that back
I think Alex should be super scared right now but I still haven't seen any evidence that he could have beat could be arrest
Active participation
Hit me very clear conspiracy that Stewart in the other oath
Keepers are charged
It's very clear
Conspiracy though and we know how close Alex and Stewart are and how the two of them promoted the January 6th rallies together
Xfinity damaged
Control together afterwards
I don't believe that the two of them were in contact with
Each other
I don't believe that at all
They just don't know the nature of that contact or any of that like how it went
Stuart himself was in the clear because I assumed that he would have maintained a safe distance from a
Incriminating conversations
That are maintained in writing
But now that I've seen the evidence of the a diabetic I know that's not the case
Sabertooth completely fuk you guys were doing the leaderless resistance this situation point
Not knowing what evidence exists
The contacts between Alex and Stuart makes it difficult to gauge how worried Alex should be right now but on the scale
I think it goes from super worried to skipping the Border level worry
Also it's
Hard to tell but I think there's a part of me that wonders
Like I said like
Alex knew ahead of time
Stewart
Was going to get a ray
It's felt like
I don't know how to describe this exactly
It didn't feel like Alex learning something on the Fly I mean but that's normal for these types of hypro
File stuff
Write like
The people like Rodger Stone when he got popped
Was like
He knew they were coming he didn't know the day or when but he was like
I know I'm going to be hit by this event
Yeah I would say
Vets
In these kinds of cases there
It's rarely a flash ring based on what I've heard
Stewart's lawyer
Probably some kind of an indication that they can do
The time
And that information could have got talent
But like I said one of the
The feelings that I get
About him knowing is I can usually blows up about Saturday
He can't handle like incorporating new information
On-the-fly
Where is this
How he learned
I'm still going to Analyze This
Even though it's looks like it's confirmed
This is how are you
Dealing with like one of his best friends getting arrested for
Conspiracy to storm the capitol
Like he's heard behind the scenes from Ali Alexander it turns out
It's dirt roads has been arrested
And he's like well we got big news next kind of
Alex does a weird how well it fits in within the theme of this
Show
If this doesn't feel
Write to me
What is a scam
Just doesn't
Ikea
I can't I can't put it any more sickly then like he loses his s***
When there's a tech problem he storms off air
Yeah who's the guy who's
Who doesn't handle bad news well
Stratosphere
Awareness of a man's mood
When it comes to having listen to thousand
Thousands of hours
You got me beat
And if somebody came
Say honestly
I know that he's acting out of character for
I'm pretty sure that the
Yeah it smells
Exactly
If you ever get to the news right away
Because he wants to announce that class Rob needs
Criminal illegal
Hijacking hostile takeover of the government
They've stolen all the money
Right now they're doing that to the old garage
Garage
Here to be demolished cuz you just ugly neighborhoods
You want to kill me you're going to have to fight
Schwab
Remind me to go crawl over in a ditch and died
Got it
Join us here with us you see as we need you
That's it
Present
Hey you guys give me the willies
You guys but I am accused of orchestrating a decade-long plan that I can prove
Your bunch
Two jerks
Bunch of jerks
Killing everybody
A bunch of losers
Where I was like nothing means anything
Alex finally does get the go-ahead to announce
Has been arrested
A Wego
Okay this just broke 20 minutes ago
So where to go
For sure
Let me have the lawyer that was on the phone
Joining us next hour
And olly Alexander as well when turning on that has
Of the Takeover of America National Security State
It is the Patriot
Domestic terrorism
Donald Trump
Terrorism Donald Trump
What
Not rhyming
Banana I don't know what's going on anymore cast of losers
Norm pattis an ally Alexander coming out
We don't really have any
Exposure to Stewart's lawyer Jonathan
The Mosley so young who knows maybe he's a
The great guy
But the other two
Whoa
Top luminary
To hear it when those are the guests that are coming up you want that
Best-of-the-best
And when it comes
To being a s*** head and being a s*** head lawyer
You don't get better
I will say that I did get Alex
Is
Pretty good
Coming up with a narrative
Like that
So he's learned
Rhodes has been arrested and
He want he gets defensive
About other people thinking that Stuart was a
The Fed
Right that was what's a lot of people have
Only friends right with you because he hadn't been arrested arrested
He's the one who got everybody's Alex focuses on that
And then comes up with another story
Infiltrate
Apprehensive
He's a distraction from real
Interested
Because it came out in Congress
Now the head of the January 6th
Lawyer
The head of the gen-6 too many lawyers said
Amory Upson go in the building
Unclear that up y'all don't get arrested because of
It was by being there you was in violation of
For judgment
From a previous case because I want failed
Community service
You violated an agreement that he entered into willingly to avoid consequences for his past actions
And that's by you
Do your f****** community service you a****** nice
Conspiracy is the new preoccupation of the January 6th at the nihilist
And essentially just boils down to this
EPS was at the Capitol on January 6th
And on the 8th the FBI released
An image of him
Hey somebody that they were looking for information
Then he didn't get arrested and so the cracks Lutz and Alex's community of put two and two together to prove that he's a
He was the one secretly running the operation
Is it stupid and if his logic holds then I guess Jay Johnston was also there under FBI Deep Cover
This narrative around around this
Keep shifting because you're like Alex just throwing at whatever thin bulshit they can
Sometime and create distraction from the reality that he has friends and Close Associates and follow through on
Bringing caches of weapons to the Capitol
That day in
Explicitly premeditated plan to stop the certification of the election result
First it was a nebula son named Aunt
Antifa and BLM folks who were dressed like Trump supporters I must have done
That is clearly John Sullivan who was the ringleader in a couple more iterations of this cycle
Andreas has a new sacrificial lamb for the right way
Doing media
They're hoping it'll stick and it'll just be
We'll figure out another guy down the road
Having
Clear text messages
Stewart Roads like
Hey
I love that you're bringing weapons to overthrow the government
Friend we will have a quick response for so you can play
Create
Overthrow the government and everybody up in a conspiracy with
Hey on the way to the capital from Texas I'm going to by tens of thousands of dollars worth of weapons
An accessory
What is a f****** bad criminal
Sloppy
Without any actual evidence
This guy re apps has been blamed on the capital by people like Charlie Kirk
Marjorie Taylor Greene Matt gaetz
Santa Cruz even got into the act after he was humiliated by Tucker
Richarlison
For not being aligned enough with the extremist wing
The party
As it turns out this is really simple an explanation for the removal of eps
Picture from the Persons of Interest list
Sturgis no longer had any questions they needed answers
About from him
Set the investigation I procrastinate got the information they needed
There are a bunch of other examples of people whose images have been removed and not all of them were because they were arrested
This isn't that unique case
Texas absolutely he wasn't running any false flag
He was however previously the head of the Arizona branch of The Oath Keepers
He was interviewed by the January 6th committee and this baby should be put to bed but it probably won't be anytime
Because their high-profile media figures are really closely connected
The people who are charged with a seditious conspiracy
Be targeted campaigns against anyone
Even former leaders of Stewart's own organization
Is it can help build a narrative where folks like Stewart now it's a really the victim
Gems in this whole thing
It's sad and honestly really dangerous
Like I can't I can't imagine that Ray isn't feeling very safe right now has a not-insignificant number of heavily-armed
Lunatics think he's responsible
They took down the Patriot leadership ends with us
The country
Malachi
This is probably not a great day
I would assume.
But
This is bulshit
Any of the way that he's being
Put up
People
Congress
Are trying to use this as a Smokescreen
To excuse the behavior of
People who are right-wing extremist
On
He's a private citizen
This is unacceptable
Well what you're forgetting
Reading is that
This
Whole thing was also funded by billionaires and their members
The Congress in the conspiracy as well
I think we're going to
To find that you can put a lot of money towards f****** up a private citizens life with no consequences for
It's it's just
Yep
I mean like I never wanted to be in the position of like
Defending
A former oathkeeper who was apart of
The events for this kind of behavior is is so dangerous
It's not so much defending him as
Refusing to allow a scapegoat to be put in place
You know like f***
Do you you don't get to get away from this
Even though you have several billion dollars
Stewart's not a fed
I just kind of hard to believe that Steward was a fad
Definitely has
Got you hot
You want my analysis
That's what's going on
This is essentially The Narrative that Alex is going to run with
And that is that you know Ted Cruz
He started questioning
About Ray apps
What's going on with this guy let me keep got too hot so they had to take us to a road
I guess I better probably plays with the audience but
It's very stupid
So
Alex makes a little bit of a tactical error
And that is what he starts saying a bunch of things that really really make Stewart sound guilty
Oh that's not good
I interrogated Stewart on air
Once a month ago about
Take show
Mozart
What 95% on Saturday
Guilty
And I was just like wow are you flipping out like
Probably let me see Joker
And he flipped out on me
Does persons
Boy I hope that's
Subpoenaed wow
Wow just revealing the existence of that is a smart move
Stewart
Completely freaks out on Alex but questions about the sick
God dammit this is why the globalists are such s*** is because they're the imaginary enemies of people who are like
F****** stupid
This is terrible
Yeah
Should have known better than
To grill Stewart Road
Why is any
Call question
To this guy after after the sixth when I asked him to wrecked pointed questions about his info
12 men in the sixth lie think I think that the question I've obviously
But I think
Did the presentation that he's trying to make is that
They pointed questions of the grilling we're about him being
A fad
But I also think that any of those questions
Would touch on things
That would be really tough
Stewart and surprised you're not a fed well I tried to overthrow the country
I'm going to have to ask you about everything
So look
I can't I can't stop loving you
Innocent it looks for you to say
Also I have a tape where he answered questions that makes it look very guilty that I didn't show you
Do you now because I don't want you to think he's guilty
And that's why I can't show you this information
Probably going to like
This tape is he he would make it
Somebody else's like
Oh we've got a tape of Hillary Clinton looking real guilty describing how she wasn't on Epstein's Island and then she
When we lift out
The kick people's asses
Yeah
Nothing
I feel like Alex
If Ever I were in trouble I would not want empathetically I would not want him to
PR for me cuz he's going to end up accidentally or maybe even a
Stuff that sounds a little iffy
Accused
And I don't think
Which of the Thousand members infiltrated
What's wrong
What's good
At this point Alex
Should be putting the pieces together about this obvious puzzle
He hasn't read the indictment so he hasn't seen the concrete evidence of Stewart's direct involvement with these allegedly dalu
Delusional Oath Keepers who thought they were under the orders
He's still trying to spend this as best as you can
But that part about how Stewart wasn't denouncing The Oath Keepers who went in and makes a whole lot more sense now in hindsight
He was hanging strong with them because he knew that they
Concrete dirt on him and he would get arrested for sedition
Conspiracy
If they put this dirt out
He wasn't about to hang them out to dry and risk them talking
The stuff that Alex is saying if it's
Incredibly perfectly with the side effects or Stewart was running a group of people who are planning to disrupt the certification of the election
By storming the capital if it came to that
That's why you blew up at Alex when he was questioned about things on that show that's why you didn't turn on the arrested oath
Compelling circumstantial case that's
Is guilty as hell
This is not good
You know I asked him to
You say there's a bad idea but he wouldn't he said that he loved it and it was a great idea and that he wished that he was the one who let it and he was the one
This seems really sloppy and shipped but like I still think this fits into the
Notion that Alex knew in advance is going to have a repair is that well
This is still the kind of thing you'd expect
M22 beer a like about
Crystal dust cover for apps
I think he's a True Believer
Oh my God
Write-ups
So we should support story
And worry about Stewart
Play me concerned are because
Very smart guy
Please also extreme
He's a real man
A folks who don't know their new Leicester baby
And sacrifice yourself a romantic
I'm also a realist
In that Romance
Humanity
Not let me get my
Play
Warren store
Over and over again
That
He was infiltrated years ago
I love the idea that Alex
Breakfast and I would like if there's any new listeners let me explain what romantic means
Like this is something that we go over a lot
This is from our earlier at the
Episode ardyn forwards when I explained what a romantic was
I don't expect new listeners to catch up so dumb man like
The facts of this case like as laid out in the indictment
Possibly be a cover for re-up
Like someone
Existed until the right-wing social media decided to blame him recently up there's a little while back
He came at everyone's mind
I get the sense that I may be making some of the same calculations that Stewart did when did abandon the arrested okay
Stewart becoming on in Fort Worth since 2009
13 years of the two of them being a social
I wouldn't be too surprised if Alex didn't want to run the risk
Stewart talent
Tails about it
Maybe about Alex's finances of the way the show runs or how little he cares about the audience of the things that he said
It kind of feels like there's something because
If you're in the clear now is exactly the right time to pretend you never met Stuart Road
Anybody who says that you are a
They're floating a raft of dirty lies around
The easiest thing to do right now
Stewardess f***
Half of all of Alex's audio
It's already thinks he's a Fed
It is Ray Epps nonsense might be playing on the social media right now but it's not going to work for the long-term
Over-committing to this is a bad idea
Yep just saying f*** store Road
Fine no consequences
It's
What is it when he says his lawyers say there
Looking into me for material support
For terrorism
It's hard not to think
Maybe he gave
Stewart's
Some money
And then we're in real trouble.
You know
Even if he didn't know what it was for is Stewart took money from him
And then went and bought guns and put them in that cash
That's hard
Yeah
I would wonder about that
I think there's an outside possibility that's correct but also I
Would wonder
If Alex
Who's giving it money money that's what I'm saying I'm saying that that's such a
Thing that you wouldn't even
You know
Definitely Alex
Allowed Stewart to have airtime to spread conspiracy theories worth money
If it was he recruiting use it you know all of that stuff that's
I mean knowing what we know now about Stuart sacks
That day
The notion that Alex
Allowed him to come on air and
Create a false version
Of what happened
In order to
Yep
Aspersions on his own guilt
The standard of evidence
Needed for that but
It's a conspiracy
He's out there
I'm just saying that once Stewart got really puffy
For this
That's a
Story now
I will I wonder
Kind of feels to me less like Alex is worried about criminal exposure by way of Stuart
I'm bored about like
She knows a lot
Yeah you knows a lot about my s***
And then also like
I can't imagine
If your Stewart Road
Being like let's Loop Alex in on them
Rehab
Pisgah military unit write that we're going to have weapons caches and stuff like
But tell the guy who
Keep his goddamn mouth shut about anything for Amazon are 4 hours a day
Yeah go ahead and tell him on Tom's
I highly doubt that
Yeah
But you know what
Thinking back to that time there was
Quite a bit of chatter from him in the end it's the same stuff that it always was but like
Ditto
What
Who cares I think it would be we'll see what happens
I need to be the world's worst idea to tell a lie
Romantic
True
Alex Alex
God is my witness
Come on the show today
I say I don't think so
I'm just really worried about Stuart broad's
Last night
Rose last night
God is my witness
Before God almighty
I wanted to love him and
He wasn't wrong
What is happening
Okay so Alex
Dreams about Stewart Roads
The night before I start the show talk about that
He's just I think you might be sick
Yeah probably I think he's a demon from Hell who's wearing the skin of a cube
Psychic after-the-fact weird how sexy you really good at that
So a comes on
And we do learn over the course of their conversation
But he is the one who
It got in touch with Alex
I told him about this
You know I wanted you to be the one that broke the news
One of my attorneys I have four
Was on the phone with Stuart Road
Well he was getting arrested
Needs to answer
Look up
Real quick that means that
They have the same lawyer
Both have Jonathan Mosley as their lawyer
For the America
American
Innocent
Am I question
Is this
Raid from pressure on Congressional Democrats
To elaborate on
Conspiracy charge
Compartir
Every conspiratorial see dishes
You know a paramilitary
Alexandra seems to not understand that any searching the went on after or long with Stewart's arrest wasn't fishing X
Expedition
He had all the evidence is presented in the indictment
Plenty to charge him with and arrested
Quick search on a raid done because what a charges Stewart is looking at is for Destruction
Evidence
So you could have been helpful to make sure he does know the opportune
Destroy anything else
I know it sucks for these guys that the fact
Sitter coming out in the basis for the investor
Allegations actually being revealed
What is the effect of completely deflating the fanfiction they've been selling their audience this whole time about the six
I know that sucks
That stuff and it's probably even more so for Allie considering it
He's deeply involved in planning the rally at the Capitol and
Most of the real hardcore right-wing so probably think he's a fed or
Snitch because he agreed to testify
4th January 6th
But the reality here is that Stuart the rest of the information that was made public
Because of it completely demolishes any of the nonsense arguments
Alex & Ally you've made about the
Storming at the Capitol being an orchestrated false flag
Diva Emma deep state
Continuing to pursue
Conspiratorial narrative is going to force people like Alex to come up with Evermore
Complicated explanation
For the new information that comes out demonstrating that right wing
Extremist planned organized and carried out the events of January 6th
For the purposes of disrupting
Transfer power
Of course they can't really do the opposite either because that would require them admitting
They were either knowingly or unknowingly part of that plan
Alex is going to soon do the move where you transitioned into a new narrative
He said something like
We know stage of the six boat move on from that because the midterms are coming up in the globalist going to steal
Something like that we're going to focus on something else
Let's not relive the gate the documentary is not going to be
I doubt they're going to be like Hey listen we're going to have to issue Corrections on the
I'll tell you what we have got a laundry list
I've been on purpose that might conveniently just
Be taken off
Selectman Stuart
Shirt roads
Man
Why is the JC
On clearing rayence name when he's the only one on camera
I can sort this out for Ally
The reason that the January 6th committee is tweeting out that they interviewed rahab's and that he isn't
The fact is because of you and all your s*** head friends are insisting that he is
How many calls January 6th
They're investigating the events of that day and abscess someone who was there
Things that night
The person that they thought they might want to talk to maybe it's meant formation
So they put out a statement that they interviewed him and that the allegations about him are true
This is a great example of a right-wing media rhetorical
The January 6th committee did this and they're being criticized for
Why are they so eager to clear this guy's name it's suspicious
However if they didn't interview apps Ally would just be saying why do they refuse to interview
Is that your view them and then they didn't put out of state
Why won't they reveal what they learn to the interview
This must be a cover-up
Actual interest in the things that are happening in reality
There's a predetermined narrative have to be presented to the audience through the
The filter of that narrative
Instances like this question Allie is asking are telltale signs of people who are operating from a
Your position
You should never engage with
You're never going to convince them of anything because they don't care about reality
Also without you saying about apps being the only person on camera doing anything illegal is absolutely a lie
There are a ton of people who were on camera assaulting police officers breaking Capital Windows another property
Who sang it's just a
Webcert
Didn't do anything illegal on camera
There's a 45-second video that
It's going that is made the rounds all over social media where he's talking to another guy the night before and he says quote
I don't even like to say it because I'll be arrest
I'll say it we need to go into the capitol
If Allie thinks it's illegal to say that
He has a poor grasp on Free Speech
Is universally applied
Everyone he knows would be in jail
Alex would've been in jail years ago
The reason Alex
Get away with the kind of clear incitement that he does
Is because Free Speech rules in this country are super permissive by Design
And nothing that apps
Day-to-night video is illegal at all
Dumb and it's an indication that he's probably should head but if Allie thinks it's proof of a crime
He needs to go take a high-school level Civic
6 class
Is that prediction after he reads the indict
Stewart's
I don't really care because I know he's never going to read it they just going to keep pretending that there's no
Evidence against Dorney got jammed up a cover-up wrap
It's all
Bulshit
Ali Ali has been on
Alex gets
Jonathan Moseley
Stewart's lawyer
Play Ali's lawyer as well
On
I don't know if he understands Free Speech either
I'm going to ask the question again why isn't Ray ABS arrest
There's no good reason for it
Even if
Wondered
He still on
Challenge
So there's no there's no one else who would be
Conspiracy but him
Show
No one else
Innocent explanation
I don't wish anybody to get arrested
The government's Behavior it just stinks
It doesn't stink to high heaven
Nothing
Illegal
If none of it is proof that he is a leader of a seditious conspiracy
But
Be taken by Stuart as illustrated by the evidence
Show
I just can't think of anybody else who could have let any sort of conspiracy
Beyond
This person who the right-wing has just
Decided is a great path
It's crazy
I mean it
The coming for this lawyer to be
Sing like this to need some sort of
Massive kashuv
Text messages or evidence
In order for me to believe that somebody else
Could have led
Please client
For the
Incredibly talented Jonathan Muslim maybe something was like 48 pages long
This lawyer I got
Alex says he gets bad vibes from the globalist till I get bad vibes from this dude
I don't care
As most of his defense is just like
Everything is a lie I didn't do it
It's just empty Proclamation
Everything is a lie and I can prove it and then no proof at all
If so
I'm not going to spend much time talking about him actually
Short and boring
But we we do we do have to record
Ignite something
I don't think anybody can deny
Did Biden in the great reset in the covid BS and all of this is
Funny my God Joe Rogan's up was a Mainline liberal the system got so bad he woke up
Burleson
Play Joe Rogan
Join everybody else just wants
Future for our children
I think you could make
Something of an argument The Joe Rogan
Headache sort of democrat Vibe earlier in his career
You know I think you probably could
Baby
He was a Mainline Democrat who
Took copious amounts of drugs
Tucker
National piece of s*** right wing
Was on
Hardball as the Republican as a Republican
Who wore a bow tie he was on Hardball
As William F Buckley
Play Juniors f****** Minimates
Hehehe
The staunchly defended the Bush Administration
I think it's fun
To say like
Tucker was just a regular liberal and then he got brought over
I think I was actually can defend that in his mind
Because he thinks that neocon deliver right
Total hardship everybody who didn't try and overthrow the capital is a liberal
Well I mean to him based on his
I'm right wing
Everybody's to the left of him relative to him
Tucker even in like
Was a liberal apparently argue now
I know they're pretty similar.
Norm comes in
Nicholas time I saw him he had a gigantic ridiculous beard
But he shaved
Fall
He's getting angry
I think that there is a stand-up careers going on well end
Twist with Norm
That I find upsetting
That is every time I hear him he's angrier
I watched last night for the first time Merrick Garland speech about January
Loaded up or down on them
But when I watched him quaking in his loafers in Rage
I thought there's something wrong with the man and there's something wrong with the country.
But here's what he said
What he said about
What he said about the knowingly or unknowingly
Two events
You are a co-conspirator
You are not a co-conspirator in a crime unless you engaged
Self-consciously deliberately
For unlawful Purpose with another
The mat Garland didn't say the five officers died on January 6th
He said quote five officers who responded selflessly to the attack on January 6th and since lost their lives
I was lying about what Garland in order to be able to call him a liar
Norm isn't really doing much better
Merrick Garland said nothing even
Close to what Norma's claiming in the speech that Norma's claiming to a watch
This is just a made-up characterization of Garland
Is quaking in his loafers and rage
I can't find another
Instance of Garland saying that like in another speech
Has a citation go for it but
Norm if you wants to clarify where this came from
I'm not going to try and hook this down
Read the transcript
Does the speech that he's referring to the dorms referring to
Is it making s*** up to be mad about
Stupid all I needed to hear from him
Is that
Casual nonchalant the January 5th or 6 I don't remember what
F*** you
You remember God damn well when was the speech
Twas the Night
Before I try right that's what he's referring
I think Norm
Might have enjoyed the
I think
The great lie on the American people
I mean for Kamala Harris to stand up in front of the nation and say
January 6th was like setup
September 11th
Lake Pearl Harbor
No it wasn't
January 6th was like 70
It was like
Concord
When the people wake up
And think enough to appear in a public place and demand answers
Investigating
But they're going to get weapons caches in the Triad
Storm the Capitol in order to stop the the counting of the votes in the Electoral College
You know what
Congress should really look in the mirror
Yep
But I need to make some changes but that's a ridiculous thing to say
I know that nobody in our Far Right Movement
Would do this it's got to be antifa who was leading it who is instigating it now obviously in reference
I view it exactly the same as the American Revolution notoriously peacefulness
American Revolution
Ed Concord
I think one of the problems
With this
Show and the community around it is like
Event like they can't even get their stories
Alex probably wouldn't want him saying something like
Easiest kind of complicated to to work in with the other stuff
He was hoping for Wrightwood
Begin a revolution
Bitter lawyer
Yeah
Interesting Lee if you pull up the indictment
Boat store roads
One of the things one of the messages he sent
On the set
As things are growing down
East Side quote
Hey the founding generation
Storm the governor's mansion in Massachusetts
Sontaran feathered is tax
Collectors
The Macy's inductee in the water
Didn't fire on them but they street fight
That's where we are now
Next comes our Lexington
It's coming
It seems like normal
Pretty close in spirit
Real guilty
F****** guilty
What am I
Lying to our f******
Faces so I think
Even Norma smart enough to recognize that there is a threat
His clients
Ability to operate
There is
There is a
A threat that the world will start looking at
People like Alex people like
Mike Stewart
As opposed to like I let him be
Recognize the danger that looks like this present
And used to be more of a headache to engage
Then not to-night now it's starting to look like we better engage before Epic
Becomes too big of a headache
Exactly
In order to insert a disc
Deflect from that
He has to mischaracterize
Why Stuart got arrested
Criminalize ordinary behavior in it
Watertown the conspiracy requirement to almost meaningless dimensions
If if in fact a green to go to a protest
I'm in agreeing to stand outside doing
Try to try to delay
Congress for doing something your
A federal agency from doing something
We're trying to hinder them from doing something
Expression of protest is now
The considered under dispatch
President seditious conspiracy
You notice how the people who were just standing outside and protesting like all those
Hundreds and thousands
Message first edition
Conspiracy
It's interesting
Weirdo Norma's completely ignoring all the parts in the indictment where Stewart is Buddy's make weapon
Fascism
Start up quick response teams
To bring guns to
The capital
So weird that they're pretending that Stewart didn't
Discuss how he and others might have to quote
Takes two arms in defense of our god-given Liberty
So weird that it doesn't come up there the person with Road
Message their group chat during the storming of the capital and said quote
We are acting
Like the founding fathers can't stand down
Bruce Stewart
And I agree
This is just such b******* of a move for Norm to get on the show a
Pretend that all Stewart dated
To get in trouble with go to a protest with
Some friends that end up getting up
Cowardly in a deceitful way to present this information
Annie knows what he's doing
Yuba City lawyer but yeah that should be level of
B******* right there
Chris already totally 100% billion dollars Alex no please
But this this is
He's you know he's ready and I
Clear about this
You know
What he is doing
Is lying
On air
He is not
Not lying
No
There's no way you can tell me
But you think he made a mistake or left it out on Max I don't believe that
You know he's a lying person who went on the
Airwaves
Specifically intentionally don't let it be a lawyer anymore
To look at this is the end of protest
Now protesting is going to be League
That's untrue Alex thinks
Something a little bit
They have been making
Yeah well
Basically they're they're hiding
Needle in a haystack
Elevation of
In solitary confinement at disappearing
Block lawyers
Martial law
So I guess covid not going to kill us all again
They're going back and forth, zigzagging throughout this episode
I guess it's back to martial law because that's more relevant to the
Store Road stock
I hate it whenever he has
This kind of Gaston cuz
Cuz he just wanted to it just sounds like they're two dudes getting drunk at a bar
Talking about politics
I don't know anything about
Sure like also
Bold
To complain about not producing documents
The Alex Jones Show
Discovery in the stacks I couldn't find it might have been a legitimate argument
These five are through all of them
Look
I wanted to print out the documents to give you but I ran out of toner
Too many stacks
Edit toners
Yeah you're just a clip of a door being a dumb dumb
Well I mean I tighten the narrative now is
The following if you complain about something and you happen
Baby why your why didn't your a white nationalist
More your white supremacist
I'm not sure I have the governor
Dwight's
I think
I think if you say
Bad if you complain
You're a white nationalist
They call you right now
I would I would say that to say that I think is very overlapping with white nationalist
Go so far as to say if you were
Justin Missy
Synthrapol wasn't a racist you would have said
I'm a misanthrope
Instead of
Misanthrope
I figured you'd be misanthropic towards Alex
You're missing your misanthropy is directed and in certain ways
All you're trying to give up
Eli what you actually believe all you do know they do this every
Every time you go out
You complain about 1
Specific race doing one thing that maybe isn't even true and they all call you a white nationalist now also
Forget what Norm stand-up B was
Insurance all my God
I got a dork
We went last clip and it's Alex
For what concerns
It's a bummer
Bone broth discounted
It's all there in Foursquare.
The leaves fall off and on about some nice exercise now
I love this Krewella we been in the same building 15 years
I've been on here 28 years but
Can you guys decide not to support us
And you've already done so much that's what God wants
Play happier
Wow joke
We've done our best here
And a good news here is my best work was done 20 years ago
Or 5 years ago
So people would know what was coming
So
I want you to keep us in the game but it's up to you
You want to see the game go to enforce where I time the products you needed
Kill me
Never see me again
Listen
I get it
Maybe you guys don't like Lucky Charms anymore do you want this leprechaun to go away
That's fine
If you don't want to support lucky f****** charms
You don't have to buy any of this s***
You killed my God just kill us
I mean it's unbelievable
It's beautiful outside that's beautiful at work
Mystic cleats you don't like f****** clean house anymore fine mr. clean's go away
I was thinking about some of the aspects of that
I mean I think he was bad
Consistently but he was better five years ago than he has now
Bye-bye virtue is going from like a d to an ass
Yep you know like
If it's still worse
Sure this is worse
I also do grieve it to his earlier career has
Made the present
Worse he did do his work earlier
Look dude
This kind of sales picture of
Like hey
Sportas if you want your going-away whatever
Is
That makes me sad
It feels like
What Elizabeth Cady
Stanton tried to do for the glass ceiling
Alex is trying
Need to do for the concept of Rock
You just keep music
Keeps breaking through it I mean there's so many so many different
Layers
Sorts of rock bottom
There's be angry I quit Yahoo
Occu
This sucks I'm ever coming back
The anger
There's denial we're winning
We're waiting
Right there's depression certainly
That's where we are now
Taking it to accept
Dabba dabba dabba dabba dabba
That's all my heart folks
Outback
Rebecca
Full circle baby
Sojourn
Little button on this Alex was that surprised by the news
Store getting arrested
Don't know how much
Awareness he had of the specific of him getting arrested that day
But the way you reacted
Is not how we normally react
Text to stop
It seems very very bizarre and out of character
I don't know
I don't know I wouldn't say that he knew was going to happen that day but if he didn't get a text like in the past 2 or 3 days
If it's like it could happen any week now or something like that
Exactly I'm definitely absolutely C
Stuart himself knowing like
Hey
This is getting serious
We'll see we'll see what happens
Alex realizes more and more than his body
Straight up
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color