Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Fix it around a little bit
About Alex
Joan
Indeed we are.
Then I have a
Quick question for you
Search
What is your break
I mean my brakes by
Obviously
Is that now that all the Djokovic
Stuff is been
Deported from Australia
Trailer for the next 30 it maybe has died down but this
There's not going to be more trouble
Beyond that
The Australian Open has begun sure and all three of my rooting interest one with
Djokovic out-of-the-way Rafa's got a real Clearpath the favorite
This year I would say probably Medvedev
Okay wait to present president
He's a
Yeah I know but
He's got a good shot
Andy Murray old man Andy Murray is back
Exact
Exactly he hasn't been relevant for tennis in the past 10 years and he's back anyone last night as a wildcard
Incredible
And then Nick kyrgios is also he's still going along strong and I
Can't wait for him to put it all together
Alright well
You enjoying your tennis
Indeed not what
Is your bright spot now that you had time to ignore me
My bright spot is at it's going to be
It comes up at the end of it
Episode
At the end of this episode
I knew about this thing
Episode
I could not stop laughing
But first before
Before we get into the episode that will lead us to my Brightside
So long 20 21 blackjack
You're not about siwa
Aaron from Massachusetts
The excommunication station podcast
Wicked weeks.
Growing up in the evangelical church thank you so much
Listen
I have no problem giving a shout-out using
Like a plug or whatever I don't know I don't know if we need a bio
Shout out in an address that was a bit of an address
Text Megan
I'm a policy wonk
Accessbcc
What's today's episode
Is obvious that the play on
Seditious conspiracy
Sid Vicious
Conspiracy
Dirty business
Where can I buy Funtime so I got to I got to thinking and wrestling with
Mention that there was an interview
But he did with Stewart Road Indian twas
Disaster
It's newer freaks out on him and so Alex never post
I was curious about
This
I knew that there had been a number of times that he'd come in and said like
Hey we got set up this way
Was bulshit
Of those interviews that Alex
Misrepresent had put it out
But it turned out that I'm banned. Video Alex posted this
Old interview that he had never
Shut up
Under the headline like
You can never buy me you can't
Talk me out of this you can't
Threaten me hopefully I'm Stewart Road close to that
I'm so I
It was like
This looks familiar to me too like
It seems like
I've seen that before I'm not sure that I had
Watch it
I don't know
Why Alex characterized it the way he
He did there's not really a fight and it or anything
But I did find it in
Interesting
Cover that
For today's episode
And see where the
The mood took me
See where things went to be talkin about this interview
Alex recorded on July 2nd
And it was supposed to air on the 4th
Amanda never did
Confirm because I went by check to the July 4th show and instead of an interview
Yeah Alex interviews judge
Joe Brown hey what's White
Can he do that
Youcam in the like a ton but every
Newsies showing up what a weird thing I had no idea was true
Exactly
Abso
Here's here's the thing
This point
An article had come out
About sewer
Calling him Buffet
The right-wing was
Like you're a goddamn thing cuz you haven't been arrested yet
Enter this is how Alex
Starts up
The interview
And starts up a conversation
Talk about this upstart
Stuart Rhodes is the founder of Okafor this 11 years ago
He's been quiet
In the spotlight
January 6th
Obviously
Before that
And I wanted to give him a chance to come on because we saw this revolver article
That came out
Abased
We saying unindicted
Conspirators in 16 case
Raise disturbing questions of federal for knowledge
Thought that was a pretty important article because
Portland
Racketeering things
But then there's a new article out that a lot of questions about only Randolph Air
And that's
Story-based
Chipley well Federal
Protection of old keeper Kingpin Stewart Road
Breaks the entire Capital insurrection
Lies
Wide open
So this rhubarb revolver article was one of the early attempt
Create the false flag narrative Atwood
Stick with the right with medic minute
I don't think it
Really
Totally work
Two things of evolved
It was an interesting first attempt given Ohio like what we seeing something but reading it does give you a sense of the sort of fact that they were rest
Slime with last June
And the end of July which they've essentially decided to all conveniently for
Forget since
Princeton this article points out that most of the attention in that media space
Has been
60 Minutes erection
Because most
Most of the people who went into the capital for tourist
Like Maga moms who wandered a little further than they should have
However this article argues that they should start dealing with the reality that a separate group of folks
Were there and act
If that day
Up until now the overwhelming perhaps
Exclusive sharabi counter establishment reporting on 16 is focused on
Absolving the first
And this is a valuable thing
The notion that these harmless Maga mom's wandering around the capital word immense
The terrorist engaged interactionism
Absurd
However the possibility that the federal government had undercover operatives are informed
It's involved in the events of 16
Trump
Planning to text
Fusion compels us
To turn our attention to the second
Category 4
We're especially interested in the unindicted co-conspirators who belong to any of the big three militia
The Oath Keepers the proud boys in the 3 percenters
Indeed it is these militia
Two groups whose Behavior statements
I'm planning leading up to and during 16
Most closely aligned with the violin insurrectionist
Caricature
We hear about in the media
In which the government claims to have been going after and it's
Its aggressive
Prosecution
Okay so the person who wrote this article has been killed
Actually it's actually Darren Beattie who is in Tucker Carlson Patriot first documentary
Get away with it
Personal articles fully aware of the fact that members of The Oath Keepers Cowboys in 3%
Implanting
About doing it
Exactly what happened
And that fact is really inconvenient for the right-wing media that spent years
Protecting these group
And pretending that they're actually just the victims of antifa Newport
Protectors of Patriots didn't mean for you to do the things we told you to do
And we knew you were doing
In order to counter this problem it's essential to make the very obvious right-wing extremist
Government operative
It's doing a false flag
And at this point
At least revolver was
Totally willing
Throw folks like The Oath Keepers and
The proud boys under the bus
The reason to dightman's of Thomas Caldwell one of the oak
Keepers who is now charged along with Stewart
Conspiracy case
Including a couple of unnamed Coke and
Conspirators
It's a reason I mean recent
To this article
This article has decided to interpret
But people who are fat
In reality that's an honor
Conclusion because these co-conspirators May well have been on name because name and them could do damage
Do the building of another
More important
Possibly like a case
Charging Stewart with a seditious conspiracy
Anyway
In June 2021 there was at least some willingness on the part of the right-wing media to cut bait
With more extreme groups
In their ranks and portray them as feds
In order to save
This probably didn't
Stick because for a while
Didn't seem like any legal action was happy
But he kind of died down and it didn't feel like there was any real need to throw these guys out after all
That was a huge mistake
Propaganda tactics
All these people knew damn well that the folks who were acting like military units in
Storm the capital of where is there militia buddy
And they should have known that it was only a matter of time before that was going to come out and it's going to look really bad to be associated with
So the other article about Stewart being The Oath Keepers Kingpin is being
Protected by the feds
That's just another revolver article also written by darebee
It's a stupid article that's just based on the fact that Stewart hadn't been
Indicted yet which was probably the result of the investigator
So they wouldn't end up going off half-cocked
Charging a revolutionary minded militia leader
And then give him a massive propaganda Victory to use
Rally his arm
Turning him not just from martyr to Untouchable God hero that's
That's a good idea when you're dealing with someone like Stuart Rhodes you cannot miss
So it makes absolute sense the investigators would
First prosecuted lower-level cases
Number to build the
Base they needed
The charge Stewart
And that's exactly what Attorney General
Amerit Garland said there was the doj strategy in his speech
Those commemorating
Anniversary
He said we watch The Wire recently and the guy said if you come at the
The king you best not miss and he's
Kingpins all week
Kind of just when you walk through the garden to go to wash your back
We build investigations by laying a foundation
We resolved more straightforward cases
Is first because they provide the evidentiary foundation for more complex cases
Investigating the moreover crimes generates link
Linkages the less OverWatch
Hobart actors on the evidence they provide can lead us to others
Sue may have been involved
And that evidence
Conservice the found a
A further investigative leads and techniques
Yeah you seem Law and Order
Basically exactly what was going on
Darren Beattie at revolver was doing exactly what
He should have
Been doing from a propaganda and cover-up respect
He was a temp
Please protect the larger right-wing Griffin
Machine that relies on it
Inciting revolutionary feelings
By smearing
Disowning the people who actually followed through with those revolutionary feeling
So like
I think he was
Doing what he should have been doing and terms
The scams
And all that people decided no
We prefer our Revolution that's why we're all here
Let's do this
It's a really interesting Dynamic to go back and look at to read those articles and be like
Yeah y'all y'all should have
Like obviously Stewart Roads isn't
The FED but if that's what you need in order to
Extricate yourself from him at The Oath Keepers of The Proud boys
You should have done that right
If you if you're interested in maintaining
The business that you're doing
Right I mean
Just like we talked about
Less time with you they can only flourish in a stable cyst
And then
Because they create unseen
Instability they break down there on time trying to correct
Executive create that table system Aaron Beatty is trying to right the ship
Eventually much smarter
I mean I don't want
He's dead now but it is what you would do if you were doing a better job
That is what you would do
More or less
Very happy about one particular per
Thanks for joining
Yeah thank you and I want to
Give a shout out to Harrison Smith
Awesome Porter there yesterday
Play pretty-much dismantle
The revolver headpiece on me and called it what it is
Do deaf amateur earpiece
He went through it paragraph by paragraph on the American Journal of the great job
Way2go Harrison
Man a lot of stuff
You say in retrospect about Harrison Smith
Always just makes me think
The capital Has Fallen
Can I watch
The videos of Harrison
Someday at about
Vespa
The video debunking the revolver
I'm going over but I don't care
Another video
Stewart got arrested
No
He he was doing it out to disprove he's not a fat now kind of thing
One of the things that I video is he pretending he wasn't on air on January 6th
The Patriots
Really weird mean
That's just one of those things that should
You own that what you wear it like a badge on your chest
Fallen quote me
Quotes from Harrison Smith
Tattooed on your forehead
So
Is the temperature here
But honestly like he can laugh at all
But also he's going to sue
It's a pathetic
Darren Beattie is writing for Southern Poverty Law Center or
BuzzFeed
Sounds
Ascot
Pete Santilli fingerprints all over it sing crappies been spewing
And it's kind of weird Vendetta time session has made like a man crush
Where were some hippies like this their goal is try to crush you
When were the crush meetings is to accuse me of being a traitor to my country nothing more important to me
The only my
Devotion is the crisis above motivational country
But you know what
My ass off when I read that
And so ridiculous
Wander Beauty
I'll be showing
Pete Santilli
Ejaculation
The rest of my Nexus 6 to 8 months in a row
Room with him as much as possible a little contradictory
From a
What your reaction actually is stand for
So yeah this is so hard.
You can't
Give me the
Two position of
Literally in
Jail for sedition
Screaming
I love my country so much there's nothing I wouldn't do for my country
Exactly what they think that's how they think
Yeah but they're dedicated Stewart is dedicated to his country but his
Is country is only a conception that existing is mine and it is not the share reality that we all have
How are government and civics
He's hostile to that his country
Bucking Pete Santilli
He's a radio host
Who was also at
Do you like the Bundy Ranch and at the mouth of the occupation there
I believe it was at the one that he getting arrested
Dino Charge
NFL getting dropped
Sure that's where the big feather in the the Santilli cap are looking at the length
The time it took to get to Stewart Road
This because they f***** up the Bundy s*** so incredibly badly
It seems like
You could have you could have maybe arrested
In-store backpack
I'm probably I don't know
Again
Important
To go off half-cocked
With revolutionary
Butts
Talked a little bit here about his beef
Pizza antille
Drill into all this past stuff on the ranch
Impastor
You are a refuge
But just
Kylian
Because I think he was set up by the fence I got out of jail
What is the issue between you and Pete Santilli
Well for one I opposed
A dozen
Walking tours were there
And before Amity even did it
Who's actually good point to bring up which is a good indication that store probably actually has a track record of
Thinking for himself and making
You might think it's someone like the head of the Oath Keepers of being favor of every single right-wing cause celeb but that's not actually true
Stewart he was in favor of any took part in the
Bundy Ranch standoff in 2014
But he was very
Critical of the malheur Wildlife Refuge
Standoff
Initially he didn't want The Oath Keepers get involved it all ain't thought that it was
The fight that was worth their time or even had like a righteous cause
Let's do it but eventually he did give in and he said quote
And oathkeeper team to Oregon albeit without long guns or camouflage gear and only
To quote
Keep the peace
Great I mean
Just just
So
Kind of
That's what I think
Pete Santilli was deep in the malware game so this could explain some of the tension
Between him and Stuart but if you look a little bit deeper that. Around the mouth
Patient you begin to see some real disillusionment with
Stewart as the head of the organization
And some of it did involve
Pete Santilli
Store was not a very popular guy after some of the events at the Bundy Ranch
Bunkerville
He called it
It's easy to remember the key in The Oath Keepers were there
But it's less well remembered how they ended up leaving
German article by the splc quote
In May 2014 The Oath Keepers were fixture at Cliven Bundy
These cattle ranch
Did Nevada
And tell Road
Claimed to have received intelligence
Have an imminent drone
And respond
Multipool do Keepers out of what he called the Killzone
Would you let other militia Matt at the camp
To talk openly about shooting roads for desertion
In the end they voted unanimously to announce The Oath Keepers and the Drone strike never came
Rhodes was a bit humiliated and he lay low for a bit but popped up after that to the shooting
15 or 5
Police officers were shot
Stewart re-emerged
Pissed off
Some people
Susan delemus the wife of an oath keeper who was it Bunkerville wrote an article titled quote
New Roads comes out of hiding and that has the nerve to ask
Will you take up arms
The fight marks
Is Terrorism
This article was published and was spread wide by
Pete Santilli
So it seems like this be
With them
Predates males wearing have something to do with it
In the intervening years there have been some of keeper cells that have broken
With a national or
Organization
Specifically because of a disc
Trust with Stewart
There was a cell in Josephine County Oregon
Who carried office
Successful
And far less publicized
Turn off of law enforcement
Happy Sugar Pine mine
And they kind of had a
Their local Leader Joseph Rice said quote
We have flag rank officers and
Senior officers military retired that have made the statement that they would not join the group as long as Stewart Road
Wasn't charged
Stuart is not a leader he has no leadership
Ability he's self
Remotes
Rice would also say quote like a moth
To the flame he flies in throws up a PayPal
And then disappears
What are the big issues do with it this group E of the from Josephine County Oregon
Is the
Because they
Lychee used what they had set out to with the
This was used as a jacket
Giant marketing
Peace for the oak
Deeper life is like this is the kind of successes we have
Where I believe
The people on the local tip
Didn't feel like the National Organ
Renovation really was responsible
For the success that they had while we're trying to
To take credit for all right
In the stretch between Vacaville and Mal who are there
Dissension in the ranks
It's related to Stewart's ability as a leader
And a bit of this was publicized by Pete Santilli
And then Santilli was there at malgor and even got arrested there whilst or dad to go back
What is initial position to knock
Get involved by sending smoke
Keepers in after
Books like Stuart are basically on Ableton
Accept personal responsibilities
Eat or somehow those bad times
What happened in the damage they did to his
Mutation
I would say that hopefully getting arrested for sedition
Conspiracy help store
Get some of this
Pizza Philly did ya
Is
The terrorist crab
That is kind
The funny thing about having a leaderless resistance
Senses that your local leader would like to
Credit for his s***
And the national leader can go f******
I would argue that
Maybe the local leader just doesn't want the national L take
Taking credit
Well know for sure
You could you can imagine
Not knowing anything about
The guy who was the local
Perhaps
He was more interested in the solidarity of his people
Oh he's holding
Maybe
I don't know anyway the point is that people didn't like
Stewart that much after the Bundy Ranch
It's weird cuz they are old
Cosplaying but
To varying
Degrees in some of these people really are f******
Straight up retired military with a a
Intense amount of ability
Youtrading another bunch of these guys are just assholes who on the weekends have a long gun
It's crazy
I need some of that bar business
People are they're just they're just got to own a f****** tire shop
No I mean Stewart's kind of a businessman kind of a
It's like they started the KKK all over again
The dues the f
The merch recruit other people in order that yeah yeah the whole thing
So bookstore didn't want people to go in
Capital
Chicago victim
If you really think about it
Of January 6th I know for damn sure
I didn't want
Investigation
I did not want that.
What is your position on January 6th and
I've been through this before the same thing
And we all go
Caught off guard we all got suckered in
Were there bucket or is there no doubt about it
Target of the DHHS
Boj
We're doing everything I can
Victim I'm a Target
And you know.
That's supposed
Yeah and I
But I honestly probably work
The disappointing
As long as information isn't
Really it's not a long-term
Strategy
No it's it's sort of a Band-Aid
We do he's doing his best to can
Knowing that like
Salman I smoke come out and be like hey I was the one who led the fucken assault on the Kappa
How do I get that
I think of you can't
Just be like
Suck my guys
So anyway looked Keepers were there under official auspice
And we stand for the Constitution always have
And we were protecting people on January 6th Matthew van as we have done in the prior
Stop a seal Rally's in in November and December in Atlanta
Have you done for the entire
Ministration
Minimum Street Wichita
And speakers and the best
And I'm not for sale
You can't buy me
Blackmail me
You can intimidate me or shut me up
Melissa put me behind bars or
Scrap
Destroy my character
IPad new
Nearby bars
I'm going to guarantee they destroy your character as well
I think I think that he might be able to
To get lucky
And go to prison for the rest
His life and become a patriot hero
That's maybe the best outcome for him in terms of like
Moving forward
Somehow like
Getting off
I don't I don't imagine the paper World trusting him ever again
No I don't
Also want to live in a world where
30 years from now
F****** Stewart Roads is though
White nationalist Mandela
Getting out of a
F****** right
Yeah I don't like it all
I don't
Steve
Watching this and watching some of
The other interviews that he's done
There are some where he's at the eyepatch
Somewhere he doesn't
And there's a striking difference in the tone
He does not seem nearly as scary when he's doesn't have his eyepatch
Like what is a
Huge element
Of his present a
I mean an eyepatch really does do it though
If you've got the courage
Words to just wear an eyepatch all the time the remarkably menacing
Dictation
A other choices you can make
Eyepatch
Justin the one he uses
Nice people
So
Houses like a man
Hey man
I know he's not doing the family
Hey we knew each other
Like a long time
Keepers I was interviewing you back
I've only known you because of you.
Wanted to get Stewart Roads on rug
Because
Text Giordano stork for I don't know
How long ago was the Stewart that you are
Working with
Congressman Ron Paul because
That's how long I've been interviewing you
1990 899
So but I don't think you and I
2009 star Troopers me.
What were you doing in between working
Photographer Paul and
Okay bro
Wasco
I just remembered having you on before us
Keeper Dumber you founding out
Confused because Stewart did start coming on Infowars
Just before The Oath Keepers existed but
Is really close
His first appearance Alex was on April 8th
It's 2009 and it was
Kind of predicated on the idea that
He was a former Ron Paul staffer who was part of the ascent
50 party
And he was talking a whole bunch about Revolution
This is clearly an attempt to obscure its part to do so
The preemptive advertising
Because on April 19th
Patriots Day
He gave a speech and Alexa
Canton Massachusetts announce
Sigelei formation
None of the Oath Keepers
I need B on with Alex
Twice
Between April 8th
And the actual amounts
Are like
Are you was clearly doing some
This is why Alex thinks that he was talking
Alex does remember the formation of The Oath Keepers happening
Doing it but the relationship
They had barely predated that at all
And it
Pretty clear that
Stewart's that we contact
Did you
It's because maybe a press release they like hey I'm getting ready to start up here on Military
Get on the ground floor of this forgotten
Point
I think you could
Argue is a little bit
Between the two of them
Alex is trying to ask Stewart
Questions
From BT's article
And Stuart seems to think
That Alex is to
Suggesting these things
There is a little bit of a misc
Communication between
The two
Answer like a try to give you a chance to respond
Little bit of that
It's not that aggressive
And it resolves
Excel fairly well
Hey what's up miscommunication
Minutes into a 40-minute interview
Like it goes on
So like
But here's a little piece of it that I thought was particularly at
According to the indictment you were having a 5 minute 25 second phone call
What person can stating at 2:31 p.m.
Which overlaps with a precise minutes
No Keepers got the Moltres
Formation in just minutes
Later went up to the capital given that you were the head of the Oath Keepers
A person 10 was your ground Commander that day
How could you be having almost respond
Almost
1/2 minute
Phone call
Whitewall your troops
Are lining up in the formation
I know that they were lining up
The formation to do
What did you talk about 45 minutes 25 seconds
What's your ground operations Commander while they were forming
Questions on the internet
They put out saying
If this guy's indicted
Talking to you
Then how have you not been indicted and I don't give him a chance to respond
Whip has not been indicted
Operation Chimera that day
I'm just sitting here
Going all these articles in the questions because I'm actually trying to get you to respond to these
You don't respond it was
Horrible reception
Trying to reach each other
In a massive
You were there you know
You can't hear a damn thing
Spotty reception desk
Pause.
So I don't believe that
But Stewart is actually right about the bigger picture
The person that you was on the phone with at 2:30
2 p.m. on January 6th
Hadn't been indicted
And he's still
Haven't been indicted
Give me a diaper for Stewart and his associates this person is just referred to as quote a person whom Road 2.0
Did as the operation
Leader for January
This person is Mike
Wixom
There's a very good chance that Simmons hasn't been indicted yet because he's going to be facing
Can even more specific charge due to
Personally took
Or possibly he's a cooperating with
Miss at this point
He's going to be charged
With a lesser crime down the road
Or he
No
The most terrifying Prospect for someone like Alex is a third option
It's entirely possible that Simmons
Hasn't been charged
Because he's connected
The other
Allegations that are ongoing and they don't want to pounce
Because doing so could jeopardize those other
A possibly relevant detail that is that along with being Stewart's operations leader on the ground
Simmons was also providing
Security for Rodger
Stone that weekend
Zero chance he hasn't been indicted yet because Simmons could be
Be seen as a witness
Send the case against Rodger or possibly that he seen is connective tissue
Between the road seditious
Conspiracy
And a circle that includes Rodger and Alex and Ali Alexander
Stop the steel rail
This is all conjecture and it may not be the case but
It seems like if you're someone like Alex or Ally
The fact that Simmons hasn't been indicted or named at this indictment should be a Cause
That would really worry me
Yeah if
The indictment includes so many
Communications between Stuart and everybody
And this guy was in on those
Communication
He's he's
Communications with him are in the indictment
Exact
Yeah and
And he was at this high of 11
He was the operations
Commander
We're not f****** around with this
This dude is not just going to be okay
And everybody else is going to look at a movie like what if your role is
To provide
Security for people
You have a lot of people who could do that other than your operations Commander
The operations Commander for
This big
Event
Aunt is also providing
Security for Rodger Stone
Like his photograph
With Rodger
Is a little bit dicey
Well I mean you could argue that maybe
Providing
Security and also being in contact with Rodger Stone while you're in contact with the p
People that your operations running at the same time I mean
That might be bad
I think there's a lot of possibilities
The come up there and the thoughts of what it could imply
Are none of them are good
Call Alex and his home
World of cronies
They got of it
Somebody
Somebody get Rodger Stone on
Anything
We've already
He got away with it
What do we have
Oh you just have to
And the charge stick
When you can't get apartment
Jesus
Provocateur on January 6th
The globalist were wanting a day
Trying to
Sparking Insurrection Idaho rifle
Actually trying to provoke my guys do things are illegal
I told him to bring guns in a da
Don't bring anything illegal in d.c.
A warning
Opera
I can get you snared in d.c.
Is complete garbage
It starts playing little fast
Loose with the truth here haha
He may not have wanted is Okie Brigade be arm the whole time but he also was an active participant in the creation of weapon
Cash is just outside DC
Work react
Action forces could be deployed to bring them in and you know
Bring them to his housekeeper birthday to shake out hot
He texted we will have a QRS
The situation calls for
Also it's funny that Stuart says that he wanted trouble he would have brought a rifle because
If you read the indictment
You'll find it on the way from Texas to d.c. Stuart quote
Approximately
$6,000
In Texas on an AR platform rifle
And firearms
This was on January 3rd which is an addition
$5,000
C-SPAN on firearms
Equipment
Yeah and $4,500 more than
Despite all January 4th and
Mississippi on Gunn equip
Right right a lot of money on the way
If you want
Trouble he would have brought his
Spun gun from home
Osher his trouble.
Some people's yearly salary on guns and gun parts
On the way to DC
Yeah yeah
It's a ridiculous amount of shity bought
That seems
Like a guy just looking to have a fun time I don't know why helicopter
Just for you
Further it's b******* that stewardess saying that he didn't want violence
Because that would service Altima
My goal
The goal of that day's actions was to disrupt the certification of the election
Can put Stewart
Is a big picture
Her guy and for him
The end goal is action
Penzeys for the president
To declare complete emergency
I called The Oath Keepers up
Under Stewart's command to be the new Army
This isn't something you
The preoccupied with for the better part of my history listening to him on Alex's show
That's a very clear objective of his action
If you consult the original indictment of his associates you can see that he even thought that the January 6th could serve as a flash
CashPoint for that scum
Pass
Antifa
Kinetic back on them
I will eat
Sacrifice myself for that
Let the fight start here
That will give President Trump what he needs
Frankly
Hey things go kinetic good
What if they throw bombs at us and shoot us
Great because that brings the president
Bring the president his reason and rationale for dropping the Insurrection Act
We hope
He gives us those orders
We wanted to
Declare an insurrection
Had to call us up is the militia
Probably one of the few people who actually did hope that things
Got to a worst-case scenario on January 6th
61 Stewart Road
He believed them things went completely off the rails
Strumpet
Bring in The Oath Keepers as his personal militia Army at which point
Stuart could do what he feels the current politicians
Some soldiers don't have the guts to do
Namely arrest and kill his political enemies
Ideally without concert
This interview with Alex's
Is a fairly decent
It's spinning things to a person who's financially and ready
Mutational required to agree with you
But it's embarrassing
Sing s***
Nothing but disrespect for in search
Going to walk stand behind their failed attempt
Insurrection
Boo
Yep I say boo to you Road
Have courage inside
We'll talk about it
The thing is that
Interest me though is that when you look
Look at the PowerPoint presentation released by Trump
Her not release my drop but that thing went over the one that included
Declare National Emergency
Not do the certified it was also a constant
Topic
The whole thing
Write it Stewart came on out to show to advocate for that open letter website
And
DIY ideas
Set these people are so deluded
As to think that they could
Trump
Ultimate power
And then he would
Cold
Military it do
William dollar thing is I got to call if a dum-dum Oath Keepers
Keepers of the f****** loyal
Stan
You need you need them because also they have C
Secret members of the military within their ranks of the military will come along
I mean you want them as a death squad but you're not going to call them up till work
For you will probably want them
Time to do some dirty work
And then
To wipe them out like Hitler
Oh my God you guys are so evil how could
Could you possibly do this evil horrible Act
I mean whatever
Ripple effect
Of that fantasy scenario ever we could
Lexibook in terms of like how that would play out they were going under the
Yeah like that is the goal that he is wanted for a very long time
This is something
For the better part of the Trump
Administration this was
Something that he was at
Forza
Keepers to be the actual Army
I mean
This is
Clearly if you look at the key
Communication
He had this
Something that he was looking
Maybe this will be the time
It's the last
David
The hard constitutional deadline for the election to be certified
The time
For trumpet
Call us up
Yeah
Violin
What's good give him the pre-tax
And forever
Your end goal is
To kill your political enemies
You the only the state gets
To do that without con
So you got to be the state
So
Earlier we heard
Stewart say that like
You know him
Talking to people
Just attempts at Kohl's
Because we just no reception at all.
Earpieces
Try to be on a radio
Stop the crowds going in and I couldn't hear myself it was so well
That's ridiculous
We're trying to get ahold of her
You're not Azar security detail, here
And we were supposed to have
Area in Northwest
It was a schedule event. That was supposed to be
From
With a million people there sings the frogs in election
Peacefully
They were very successful hijacking and taking over
Blue
Pictures of the calls that he had there were like 30 second
Kim's long those are probably attend
Call
That's even conference
Call people like
Another Point worth mentioning is the Ali Alexander got a permit to hold an event at that space by
Filing for one with a dummy organization name
One nation under God
Because he knew that they wouldn't give him a permit.
Bastille
His permit was also for an event with a maximum attendance
50 people which was
Obvious
Obviously a number that he knew he was going to
Exceed
Title loan
Is probably something they could get Ali charged with like
Criminal negligence or something similar because
I have an event there which he got a permit for under false pretenses
He was drawing far more people to the area right around the capital than was safe
According to what was allowed by his permit need did that
Full $4
Dunrite fraud
Yeah these are all various elements of
The chaos that occurred that day
You can begin to
Missy various actors who made intentional choices that led to what happen
Whether or not they knew what would happen or even coordinator
Google teach other
Trump told people at his rally to go to the capital that he was going to come with
What you didn't do
Alex Letta March to the capital of people who were only getting more and more amped up along the way without
Screaming should about 1776 into his bowl
I only set up an event at the
The capitol grounds
But he knew was going to get out of
Control just based on the numbers of people who are going to be there
Stuart Nadeem coordinated to use military tax
Fix to move through the crowd at 3
Reach the capital
While haven't weapons caches nearby for when Trump decided to make them the new Army of the u.s.
These people like Ali and Alex better f******
Pray that they don't have any texts or e-mails lingering around
Indicate that there was Gordon
Nation between these
Groups
Yeah in terms of what they were doing
I could actually believe that
There was
Just a bunch of
F****** weirdos who were old
Spiritually on the same page
Coordinate with each other
But
The prospect that there was
Some kind of like
Conscious
Knowledge of each other's plans yeah
But I know
No that's conspiracy
They better
F****** pray that there isn't
Some signal message
I thought might be encrypted and not be able to be accessed
Because
Yeah you know reading through that
You've got to figure these guys had to have just assumed
That they were going to
To get away
How could you do that
I don't I don't know if I'm boring
Inclined to believe that they thought that it would be
Successful
Or
That they thought
That there
Comms remorse
Secure than they thought
I mean maybe it's just this is what happens whenever your entire organization is not like trains
Insomuch as grew up watching movies
The movie room
These people are actually ex-military they've had a lot of them have had training a lot of areas at Lely rela
100-percent I understand that part but
Really you think that just a signal alone if there were articles written in 2018 about they can crack
Back signal I understand there is a conventional with
People have that it is far more secure in uncrackable
If you didn't read that article maybe you would
Protonmail
Texas or whatever you know like
More secure than other deliveries but
Do planets read
So
Who's Bonnie
I think you should help try to lead an investigation
Who did that
And you're blaming you so I mean how do you think I should lead
That's kind of what I'm doing now is
When you had a bunch of shows about it we've had
Big debates about it
Become a big issue with an L
Can I put you in the middle of it
I would say that if Stewart was in charge of
Investigating this would be a short investigation
Fox placed in charge of who killed
Sweetheart
Absolutely
Stewart
What's the the government
The dump all the
They have because he knows
Whistleblower could
Antifa provocateur
I call on DHHS
NSA
You guys can still do a data dump
You can do it right now
Don't suppose all the dirt
Aldi
All the provocateurs you know who they are
Go to the data. You do it anonymously go do it
And anybody out there
Blackmail
Or two words
Store bought out
Will forgive you
Expose it be whistleblower
Difference
Do the right thing for your country
It's fascinating to hear this knowing what we know
Nose
This is such a fraudulent performer
Videos putting on
And its operating under the assumption that he
That information
Does exist
There are whistleblowers were being blackmailed into not talking about the antifa provocateur
Like those people exist and he's reaching out
He's fully aware of his actions
So this is
This is local news
This is the husband who has killed his wife
On TV saying
Where we just want to find her
We just want to find her she's lost
We want you to come home
Knowing full well that her head and hands are in his f******
Drunk it does have that vibe
So
We were like Alex
Let's stop using words that make me feel bad
We have to stop
We should stop talking about military formations and
And storming the Capitol in insurrection
What it was you said
Protest
Small elements
Were some people insult the police
Hey
They got their problems
Because we actually saw the
Police officer
Everybody else and walk through doors already open
Sweeney's.
And look at
Big picture is
They're using like the reichstag fire
Peter Peter Noone at 11 to turn out more inward on us either reject an entire.
If I were Stewart I would also be employing people decide using words
Like military formations
Because when they do they're just talk
I'm about Stewart's
If you read the indictment that Stewart's facing the idea seems to come up with
Princeton
Quote on December 12th 2020 the North Carolina chapter of The Oath Keepers
According to the leader that chapter will be focused on
Vehicle operations roadblocks vehicle recovery Convoy operations
Setting up hasty ambushes
Reacting to ambushes
But the first thing we're going to
To do is fall into formation when we Assemble
When things got going to Coco
Conspirators Farm
Stax I moved information to approach
Steve breech
Of capital
2:35 p.m. bags Watson Hackett more shell and others join together
Formstack
Maneuvered in an organized fashion.
The steps to the Eastside Rotunda
The doors each member keeping at least one hand on the shoulder of the other in front
This is the same type of formation that was used by the other co-conspirators in laid up stack two
Resisting the urge
Gotham stack really hard
So difficult
I'm with you obviously wouldn't want people talk about military formations if people were using on January 6th
Because he's ahead of a paramilitary organization using military formations that day
It obviously doesn't want people to use the word insurrection
Cuz he wrote to open letters
To Trump
Published online where he was
Desperately begging Trump to use the in
Insurrection Act
His friends could pretend to be the army
Enroute text in Signal messages
While the storm was going on celebrating it essentially as an
No no no you don't understand okay so what
What happened was
Antifa
Were surveilling the o.c.
Keepers in learning their training methods
Alright
So then whenever they went
Instigate the used the knowledge that they had gleaned from watching The Oath Keepers
Who are by the way so well-trained they would never
They infiltrated all of the cam
The signal Chats on
FIFA made
The things that he was saying really does feel like Stewart's like man I'm the only person here who wasn't antifa
And all those things I said
They're pretending to the dangerous extremist But ultimately is also a boring one
At least partially because his revolutionary spirit is kind of entertainment
His desire to make money off his revolutionary bran
It's great to be into the Insurrection until it doesn't work
Because then you have to
The business
If the Insurrection had worked and trumpet invoke the Insurrection Act
Inmate Stewart the head of a
The newly deputized militia
You'd be hearing
Very different tone from him but things that he did in the lead-up to
Baby Bratz
TV all the time with
Tucker Carlson
Saying hey isn't it great that I made this a fast
Just country and none of this would have been possible without the intro
Planning of me and my friend
Such b*******
Need be like
The f****** swapfell
That would be
Excuse that store ears is about the fact that
Keepers to go into the
We can't really deny that
Finally true
In order to explain that away
Here's what story uses
And it's
Horseshit Merlot Universal two weeks.
Interviewed me ice I give an interview with them against legal counsel advised
Guys were doing
Nellie told me after the fact they went in the renter Medical Aid after they heard that Ashley rabbit have been shot
Interview where they were they found themselves
Well you know they were like
Guy walked up and said you know where to get your phone without trying to arrest you
You know an Indian
Is everything like you said it was and your interviews and media that
All you got
Anyting
So
They were asking me about what our guys didn't I said hey
They went in only because it hurts only been shot
Ashley told me and
The best of intentions
This complete bulshit
Ashley Babbitt was shot at 2:44 p.m.
Any kind of have to assume that their wooden
Be immediate relaying of this information to people outside the capitol
There's a decent chance that if you were in the crowd it would take longer for you to learn about that
Someone just watching
TV
Being a generous as I'm willing to be let's say that it
Took 6 minutes
That's four words get out from the site of the shooting
To The Wider population outside
Sure it's arbitrary but it also doesn't matter
By that point co-conspirators had breached
The capital and we're in contact with him then
What was
For example
A 235 Meg's Watkins Hackett Marshall another's join together
Formstack one
Harrison joint
Stack one when it reached
The top of the staff
At the top of the steps back one pushed forward as part of a mob that aggressively advance
Store the Rotunda doors
Assaulting the law enforcement officers guarding the doors
Through objects
Chemicals Dorothy officers at the doors
Hand-pulled violently at the door
At 2:39 p.m.
Remember stackone join the crowd and forcibly pushing against one of the Rotunda doors and align forcement officers guarding that door
The mob
Change the doors and the stack one member enter the building
Shortly after the mob breed silver time to doors Meg's Harrelson walk
Can pack it more shallow than others
Force their way through the doors
Into the Kappa
Dissolve
Before 2:44 Wenatchee
Tobacco shop
My advice
And this is been the case
Ever since I
Watch reality TV shows about like First 48 and all of that
You have the right to remain silent
Yeah if you could just not go to the FBI directly to the
Take I have to take that as
Coming from him as opposed to something I know.
Good point possibly
There's no chance of
But their actions could be motivated by a concern about a person being shot
In-store knows what he's doing on this show he's lying to provide cover for himself and his militia
3 minutes
Before stackone made their Advance on the capital Meg's
Who was apart of
Taquan
Was on a conference
Call with Stewart
And it to 44 the exact time Babbitt was shot walk-ins announced on their Zello walkie
Kataki Channel quote
We are in the mezzanine we're in the main dome right now we're rocking it
They're throwing grenades f****** shooting people with paintballs
One minute later stackone members
Began trying to force their way past law enforcement who are blocking the path from the Rotonda to the Senate chamber
With walking
Push push they can't hold
After they got teargas today decided to retreat and some of them went to
Look for Nancy Pelosi at the house of
Cuz they were worried that she was injured by the tear gassed
Such nonsense
Back to indicated a plan to enter the capital even earlier
When between
2 +
2:30
A member of the group heard the people that breach the capital and replied quote
Now we're talkin
That's what I came here for
Suspiciously absent from the conversation
Be motivated by concern about Ashley David getting shot
Which also hadn't happened
Actually make it into the capital until after the shooting but their actions and words prior to entrance
Very clear what they were doing
And why they were doing
Another important point is that even if his militia goons were only going in because they were concerned about someone getting shot
Does anybody
What the f*** did they think they were going to do to deescalate the situation or help in any way
Okay because he wanted to sound like they wanted to help
But if not
Actually
Because that may be able to shoot people
It would be adjusted
Application for them to other people
Since they were born
Also there's pretty clear evidence that
Stewart new appetime interested in providing Medical
Before 2 p.m. almost an hour before Babbitt with shots
Someone asking the signal group Stewart was in
Are they actually Patriot
It's not those who were going in in Disguise as Patriots
It's cause trouble
Actual Patriot
Pissed off Patriots like the
The Sons of Liberty were pissed off Patriots
Just after that walk
A member of Stack one who would later
The capital and try to storm
Set on their walkie-talkie Channel quote
It is spread like wildfire that
Betrayed us and everyone's marching on the capitol
We have about 30 to 40 of us
We're sticking together it's
Into the plan
What was the plan exact
This plan to hang out
Security for people like Rodger Stone and then going to the Capital Gazette
Provide emergency medical assistance but no one asked you to provide
Direction
Nonsense
And it strains credulity
Believe that your would ever think that is people behave the way he's trying to present it to Alex this is
Dogshit
Cover story
Is bad it's a good life of the audience though like people who watch Alex's she'll definitely believe
It's not going to play in court
Like the clear timing of action
And statements
It's
It's a clear lie
Episode of CSI Miami
I don't know if we're going to find this guy
Nope this is a 5-minute episode ATM he did it
Let's go
Stewart's even lying about
The like I've asked my guys
I got some eggs and daddy told me that the only way
He knows that's not true he's created a complete fiction he's he's written his movie where he this is how if we had
Plan to kill everybody
Here is a
Flimsy rationale that sounds kind of Defense
Ansible
So
Shity so we were hunting leprechaun
We thought that DC was a great place to find them
Cuz it's a leprechaun
Because the Deep State hates us they've taken away our payment processor
So I booked this is just funny
Follow his own advice
Okay
I told my guys all the time
You should presume that every chat is going to
FBI has found the painful and stressful country
But what you have to do is say I'm not going to let that stop me
Community organizer
Yeah man
Wow real smart
How
I mean
I do like the idea that maybe that's more of any
In retrospect
I kind of thought
Because of that I think about it
I have a lot of incriminating s*** in my tech
I really wish I had said all that face-to-face
I need to remind myself to assume that there are snitches and every chance
I will be a smart idea to not
Have people know my face
I think I should do that one
The interview
A little bit of weirdness but really not that
Bad
Ultrazone org
Fourth of July but so you can go do is bring the declaration independence
I think about
Long thin abusive they suffered
They're comparing when we are now we're pretty much the same place
What up surnames would you like to debate those guys
No I got nothing for him
Are there ghosts around
Are they
Thank you
That's really weird
It's the end of the interview a kind of sounded like parts of the
Was clumsily edited
I thought maybe there were parts that were
Wrong about this but let me down the road of life
Figure out like
Can I find this
Like posted before
Right they was posted like the
Is there any
Indication anywhere the week
You can find
Curious
According to Alex
Text your lady said this is recorded on July 2nd
In 2021 it was supposed to air on July 4th
It doesn't appear on the July 4th sure like I said he interviews Judge Joe Brown
That's less than
Belen radio
I went back and I listen
Listen to July 2nd show and sure enough Alex's discussing his plan to interview Stuart that day
You two are on Sunday
What you wanted to take off because it was the 4th of July
Understand
Stewart absolutely did not
Flip out on Alex
Some of course of that interview like how it's presented
And in fact listening to it I
Can't imagine what would make Alex not Aaron
The only parts that are even a big deal
Contentious or that they when they have that misunderstanding or Stewart doesn't realize that
Someplace on the roof
And thinks that Alex might believe it
And then the stuff about pizza and Tilly
I think that part at the end
Is Alex is offering Dave Stewart
Debate Santilli so they can work out their issues
I think maybe
Leesburg got mad there
But it doesn't seem like a reason to Shell to the interview
Yeah something wasn't
Right to poke around
And see what's up
First thing I did was check on infowars.com see if they might have had a post
From July about Alex's interview with
When you search their website
Stuart roads now
You'll fine
Quickly that they have scrub the site
Of all but a few mentions of him
There are three straight post
It come up in a search
First Alert roads that have nothing to do with him
I am at one with a title like
Quick cure for the alive 40 hour emergency
SimpliSafe America transmission
Or maybe he was a guest on that and it still comes up
The only three articles that, but have anything directly to do with Stewart are all from the past to we
About the charges that Stewart just caught in one is from two weeks ago and it's just a Tom pappert blog
Entry about how real
Text John Sullivan into roads are set to testify
I'm not sure that held up well
Stuart is becoming on Alex's / 30
13 years
Countless headlines of him calling for revolution
They don't come up on the site when you search for him
That's so weird
It's such a good coins
A couple more articles come up if you do a Google search
Which of the Infowars
Four pages that much of nothing
Before last March
Weird
That seems insane
There's a section of Infowars website that's an archive of their heads
Some of them are pretty interesting
Sing like
Stewart Rhodes
Bill declares war on America
I dare you to try and guess what year that was from or what bill it stock
Talking about
I'm going to go with
2013 and
How about
The
I don't know
It's 2011 and I don't know because the body of the Articles missing
The game again
You're in the ballpark ballpark
Learn of America's coming civil war
Keepers Stewart Rhodes reveals What could
Be in America's future
Could be from any year
I'm going to go
25th
Revolution
Then going for a
Maybe
DF rainforest advertised how complicit a wire and that actually facilitating
Yeah anywhere close to where he is now without Alex
I mean I would say
That I wouldn't
Wants to establish a pattern of the
Behavior
Especially if
Especially if I were the person who is Khan
Constantly arguing that it was
Who is always
Advocating for violence in politics for that pattern of behavior to be
So consistent everyday anyone talking about antifa
That could be trouble
Possibly worse however was the results of my neck
Poke
See if I could find if there was a reversion of this
This video
I search bam. Video for
4 Stewart Road
And there's a couple of posts on there that Alex you probably
What is a video where Alex and Owen Shroyer interview Stewart
With the title quote
Patriots plot there
Recapture of America in d.c. this weekend
Videos from November twenty
20 and the rally that they were going to was the
The climactic endpoint of Owens dumb stop Bastille Caravan Rush
Optics are really bad
It definitely sends a strong message did Alex and Owen and Stewart
Collaborative plant help
Patriots recapture America within a few months
January 6th
They were doing so under the same name
Stop the steel
As the organization that Allie Alexander ran it was instrumental in planning the rally
At the Capitol
Have they switched most of their headlines to just like
Exhibit a
Exhibit
The video was from November 10th
If you consult Stewart's indictment you can see at this same time he was also a
Actively planning with you
Keepers to disrupt the election results
Quote on November 9th 2020 East Rhodes held a private GoToMeeting
And online conference calls
And video cam
Frances via the Internet limited 20 keeper members title
Oath Keepers National called Members Only
Which is attended by Meg's Harrelson Watkins all of them
Parks
Including the person who roams
The operations leader for January 6th
That's it
During the meeting roads outline
Plan to stop the lawful transfer of Presidential Power
Including preparations for the use of force
Innards those listening to
If I had to guess
The November rally in DC was too soon after the election to try and coordinate
There wasn't a fever pitch yet at that point since a lot of people were still hoping
But some kind of evidence of voter fraud 2 come out
And drop would still win
It wouldn't be optically good for Stewart
Use that rally as the jump point
And I guess
I had to guess he was probably using it for
There's another Exchange
Indictment mention
From November 9th
Put on November 9th 2020 Caldwell reach
Delta roads to
Provide the results of a likely reconnaissance trip
You taking into Washington
Did DC and coordinate planning with roads For an upcoming op in wash
10 BC
I would be surprised
Stuart knew well enough that this was
The time
But that rally
Could still be useful for PR purposes
And to get acquainted
North Capitol
Useful like March
Is a president
Kind of Porsche
For that
Looking at more
Videos on band a video there are multiple videos of
Store coming on to declare the sixth they plot
Talk to frame the Patriots
You can find the video from July 1st 2021 where is Harrison Smith
Defend Stewart
From accusations he's a fatty
Big gap between them and Stewart's arrest
I honestly find it difficult to believe that Stewart wasn't on a
Any of their shows between those dates
But I guess
Possible
I can definitely see Alex getting worried about the
The FedEx on him and throwing his friend of 30
18 years off to the side
Possible
But that's wild
Not only are there no results from Alex's own show but there are no results from Harrison show
Who went out of his way to debunked
Revolver articles
Spruce
Don't make sense at all to me
Weird
Can I watch the video and the only explanation I can come up with his
Who makes this joke about
If Stuart wants
Come on in Dubai
Pete Santilli
Stewart does look
Mad and he says know that you'll see him in
He still appears to be
We talkin
He doesn't look very happy while Alex quickly and
I can imagine that Stewart yelled at Alex after the show and is there cuz he was joking about the stuff that takes very seriously
Going to kick santilli's ass
Which Alex
Blitz torte was Galaga
Going to kick someone's ass
That happened after they stopped recording or after the inter
Go to bed
I have no idea
Is it a dead end
Until I saw one more thing on Van
Dog video
You
Are you Columbo and there's one more thing babe I video there was an interview
Stewart Rhodes did on July 12th
10 days after hours
Has failed interview
This was with a just another Channel which correctly was a show on Rumble that followed Owen on the Caravan
And now I guess they have their own show on Alex
Great
Wow
The video is titled
Cook exclusive FBI allegation
Dusty roads clear the air or muddy the waters
America you decide
I got to thinking hey I'm America I should decide
You are America
I live in the whole interview it's dogshit
It just start saying the same kind of stuff that he'd said that as the cover Story the Alex interview
Way more clear that he thinks the whole thing about him being fat as a personal attack
Pete Santilli
Really clears gets madder and madder about Pete Santilli
Maybe one might say a kind of
Moving one's Anger from yourself
To another to really be insist
Until he has a crush on him
However it in all that like
Ignorable nonsense
There's One Moment of clarity in this interview that I need to bring up
2nd episode
And this is my brother
This is your bright spot
The interview is being conducted by a host
Just another channel name Brandon
He's joined by a co-host
Name Jeremy who he disguised himself
Is an oath keeper
Hayden Stewart in a woman named Angel whose husband is one of The Oath Keepers who got arrested
In the first indictment
Kenneth Harrelson
Who's also now charged with
Wow
The whole time does Jeremy guys are going on and on about how The Oath Keepers are totally cool
Which is what I would expect
He's openly bragging about being there on the 6th
And haven't bought brought weapons to the stash spot being a bit confrontational that if you ask me
It all comes to a head in this clip
Is the thing that
Is Moe's
Disingenuous
Tumi
Is that
All the footage that has
Has been released of that
Hotel room
They have that same footage
The list
Of lodging
I believe that my lodging
Which was a RV
A park 10 miles
Outside of
DC
In College Park
Is literally redacted
And it's because
I know they tried to read
Recruit me
Info
That's why I continually say
City people date
Intentionally or ignoring my
Dissipation
In January
Because
My testimony
Completely blows their entire
Bulshit
Narrative
Out of the water
Because I said in on these meetings
I was there
The night before
Or I was there on January 5th
I had guns
In that hotel room
I was on the video camera
Picking up my guns next day
Jeremy Brown
Isabelle to you
He's my favorite insurrectionist I think if I had
Massachusetts
So this video is recorded on July 12th
Turn on
September 30th Jeremy was arrested
Remaining at any restricted building or grounds that lawful Authority
And knowingly and with intent to impede
Or disrupt the orderly conduct of government business or official functions
Engaged disorderly artist
Tropicante
Restrict
To building a rat
It's not just a Cockiness of the Icarus Style flying too close to the Sun that makes Jeremy my favorite though
He's the stupidest a****** in the world
When Jeremy was arrested
Naturally his house
And cops found about so what you do
Tons of ammo and dicey guns like sawed-off shotgun do it also to hand
Yeah I was going
Going to say there's definitely any
Explosive or two
The reality is that he probably would
Ended up getting
How much time for Zach
Cuz I'm 6
Restaurants
7 grenades is not great
In 2020 I do got some
31 months
Without the correct paperwork so Jeremy might be in
Better
Before he got arrested
Put his house for sale on Zillow and was apparently going to be living in an RV
Picture of a whiteboard in Lizella list
Thing which included a bit of incriminating information
Incriminating information about it about what weapons he had on hand
Including flashback switch
Definitely wouldn't be legal for him to have on hand
It's also introduced
The new problem for Jared
This picture claimed to show that he had weapons
Including flashbangs which were not found by the cops
Lobster in the search
Which would imply or provide probable
Cause to suspect
Becky moved them
And it turns out
Transporting
Explosives is a
Crime
The federal agent actually had to type this out
Start my training
Expertise General familiarity with
Small confines of an RV the fact that the trailer was purchased approximately a month ago and sits next
To the RV and the house within the proper
And that it's unlikely that an a
Individual with Market at home available for public
Inspection with guns and
Explosives inside the home
It's probable that many of brown
Possessions including Electronics guns ammunition in Opelousas
Which constitute potential Evan
Into this investigation
Has been moved to the RV or
That's a really long way of explaining something very clear
But they weren't there so maybe they're next door also because it's fun
The FBI search warrant also says that the agent publicly-available video podcast
A person one
In an interview posted on July 12th
2021 Broadway
Bookkeepers HUD January 6th
There prior to the riots
He deposited guns with other of Keepers in Virginia and retrieve them after the riots
I would not have
Admitted to a potentially that's a 100 years ago executable crime
Definitely
This video that
He did with your roads
Probable cause
In the FBI search
By God
He's insisting on taking his case to trial so we can blow this whole thing wide open so I look forward to that Gustav fizzling out display
Morning Lee
He claimed that the FBI tried to make him an informant
Or whatever
And
From what I can understand
From the allegations
There was
A visit that he got
From the FBI at some point
About
Shouldn't use posting online
Which
Based on the other things I can tell about him
Maybe he made a threat
Of some sort that was relevant enough
As as somebody who's a member of The Oath Keepers unlike a former
Green Beret apparently
Play Michael Irvin
People taking us
The credible threat
I don't know exactly what the case is about that
And I can find
Blogs
That he released
Video
Record
Bfbi trying to make him an informant
The Oath Keepers
Video
And apparently it was supposed to have been played in an interview with just another Channel
So I'll know
By the justanotherpanel
It's not on the
So if it was on there it's been since
Don't know where I don't really believe necessarily what's going on here
But I do believe that he posted on Zillow that he had a
I mean this is just
It's just a bad movie it's like a it's like a heist movie
Where does weakest link
Is glycol
I'd suddenly spending 10 million dollars immediately after they did the heist
You're the one who's getting this caught man
This is why if I'm doing conspiracies
Alright
I'm not doing it with any of these
I'm too I think I'm only going to go with like
I guess cartoon characters who are used to stealing like the Hamburglar sure number one in my conspiracy who are you
Oh really a conspiracy charge
I want to go with verbal Kint
Verbal Kint
Spotless record
Did doesn't crack under pressure
Absolutely that's buddy the the Kobayashi
Private my first round pick
The trick to conspiracy
Makeup
Nobody even alive
So you got the Hamburglar okay
One of the spies that was X
Executed in the 40s
PS4
Nevermind I'm going to go with a walk to the water
Do you can't have
Okay I have a lot to
Google hamburger
Their rules are rules are changing
Okay overpowered pronounce okay nobody with superpowers
Thinking somebody who'd be really good at
Not getting involved
When things I don't want them involved in
And maybe having a lot of information that there
Disposal
I was also trying to think of somebody who's maybe a mute
That's not a bad
Chooses not to speak
I think would be like maybe some kind of a punk type Greaseman like an Ocean's 11
You've got you've got the acrobat
The Chinese acrobat guy who only speaks
In Chinese and everybody understands him and it's kind of a joke
No
You don't want to
You don't want to inexplicably be able to understand Chinese
April
No I prefer I prefer somebody who
Will not snatch
Because they don't
Okay whether willingly or
I know the joke you're making
Appreciate that
The reason I have a Paws bear is because
She is not saying she doesn't speak the boyfriend of the song
Sister is I would have liked to track the logic of the joke of like who would I drafted message
Was it the bassist
I don't know
Who cares
My-oh-my Brightspot terrorist who posts
Plans on Zillow accidentally
Just an amazing amazing individual
Mystery Still Remains of why Alex
Wooden post
Other than like offending Pete Santilli
I can't see what
Exactly Alex saw that was threatening
Interview
It seems to me that it
More likely bet Stewart sets
After work
The steward said something afterwards or something it was like I don't I don't want
What do you think Alex would respect
That's a good question
But also has no his buddy was ready to kill the president
Are the vice president
He also he also got to consider
The possibility that
Stewart said don't post that
That led to a fight
And that's why I Stewart haven't been on
That's true
That's awesome
I'm something else to do and it ruined
Is July 4th
Are deducted
Joe Brown
You got to think about this in terms of like
Real-time yeah I don't know I really I really find this
To be kind of an open question
Like why this wouldn't
Pet store
Possible
But then again
He 10 days later doing it every recess almost the same thing with a smaller channel on Bandai video
It seems like he was in
Consistent
His message app
The other possibility like I said is like
Alex does have Pete Santilli on
It really has a bit
In the past possible that he doesn't want to start beef
Somebody who's a little bit
Closer to being accepted by the mainstream of the right-wing
Where is stewardess
Frenzy friend
She doesn't want to get into another pechenik
Stay the night
Tell me neither of them are employees but yet maybe that would be too much of
Try to take sides
I don't know
I think more importantly
If you listen to this
He find
Just
Pathetic
Control
And coming up with him
Excuses.
Dad
Compelling to Alex's audience No Doubt
Of course especially without any other information
To contradict
Things that you saying
That are clearly
I mean the thing that gets me
Is that
They have watch Stewart Roads go on Infowars
4 years
Calling for violent Acts
And then they're going to just
Except it all by the way Stuart roads was all about medic
Why only
Selfless
I don't know if we'll see what happens but you know we'll check it again
Until then we went
We do it smells right.com we aren't
But until then I'm Nino and Leo Abby the Explorer
Alex
Christian color with huge fan I love your work