Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of imposing
I need money
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Acknowledge
Lean and talk a little bit about Alex
Jardin
What is your bright spot
Actually like
A couple of things that we've kind of fur
Forgotten to even touch up
Lakers news
We've been busy with other stuff
That is so the first thing is that to Nick Fuentes got subpoenaed by the January 6th committee
I think that'll be fun to see what happens with that is that
I just should have come up somehow but
Natural place where
Doctor group is now a piss doctor
What
What happened
Your group is the guy who was at advising
The qanon guy who came out and was talking about piss drinking is being a cure for covid
Group yes
Dr. Edward group veterinarian Supreme do Chiropractic
The other one
Keep thinking veterinarian cuz there's no way a chiropractor
You should be anywhere near a medical okay
He's moved on from the happy Waters of being Alex's doctor buddy
Slightly less happy water
He calls it I believe like ammonia Layton Waters golden nectar something
Call Dad it's just interesting
Info on when we see like these the side characters of your pop back up
Two places
Score on the world
6th season of the show
We got a third season
Cast member coming back up and
Camarillo
Anyway
Spin doctor
My price 52 princess are you
What I said now
Your father will disown you
My bright spot
Jimmy Olsen yellow
Power through this way I. Going to be able to
I'm going to do it
Fantastic awesome
Give that illusion I have not enough check that out yet
What day is
Car detailing
His last one was basically a companion to
Madvillain forgot
Is almost 121 could have been part of it and this one is it
Great
You're very lucky that I can't think of anymore spin doctor
I really saw it in your the back of your eyes like every word I speak you're like
Is that the one I can turn into a
So hey Jordan 22 here today
We got some very interesting things happening
Of a certain somebody we haven't talked about 8
Quite a while
Lawyer
Liberals
Excited to get down to business on this episode before we do
Take a little moment to say hello
Surfer stuff
Theme
Turtles
Next shout out to whoever registered as my grandpa Jerry
Hearing Jordan say thanks Grandpa Jerry made me and my mom cry thank you so much you are and I'll probably walk
A boy
Try again
So next time we have a couple technocrats first Kyle thank you so much
Foxtrot
Technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Miami
A little break e for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
And all your s***
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
So better today
God that's going to play at the I swear
If that isn't what plays
Is on the career retrospective
Retrospective for Alex like 10 years from now
That's it's a perfect encapsulation of his whole career I think I could actually even I had to
The retrospective if people wanted a little bit more minutes today
Reviving Outburst oh yeah
Jordan is an out-of-context drops
From Today Show
Binky
Baba
That's right
Squiggly
Qui Qui
Breaking Baba
Views for blanket
That sounds better
Because he was he was making fun of masks
People like wearing masks
Anthony realized he had to explain as much fun
What is child.
It's at Plum and grey
Start off as Alex starts off
This is weird
And as much as we have a right with this illegitimate government of the Declaration of Independence
You don't have the organization of the Statesman the leadership
Pretty good
Do business
I was just trying to have a really interesting weird middle
Path about 6
And whether or not to overthrow the government.
Pittsboro just got arrested
So maybe not maybe I should
Leave it open
Open Super wait for somebody like Alex is like
Entire personality is based on like
I don't know King George
You basically just masturbate about the Revolutionary War
Everybody like your King George
Sweet
Also I don't I don't know exactly if his
Characterization of what King George
I was doing that the
The colonists
The revolutionaries had a problem with
I don't know if that's exactly accurate
But either way
Alex is at a place where he's like
Maybe I should walk so
Some of the stuff back
Maybe maybe I should be a little bit
Be careful
With the breakdown of civilization when the breakdown of society
The last thing we need is
Paramilitary garbage
Who is Hannah
Keepers
Who is proud boys
Ideas and things are spouse
Militias in the Constitution
It's in the Bill of Rights
That's a normal male instinct to good
You should try to protect yourself
Please try to work as a sheriff's
You should use your influence to City counseling and school boards and everywhere be heard
But
In places like North Carolina
In Kentucky and Virginia
What are recruiting young people online and others using Q
Might be asked if there's a big present
You really work
For Trump DC going to do this
Choo choo launch sometime
Before the midterm to bring control martial law
I'm a non-attorney spokesperson represent
It's really weird this timing for Alex
The jump-off being super into militia and revolutionary paramilitary.
Alex is talking s*** but I think he's keenly aware there are a ton of
Rewi heavily-armed dangerously prone towards violence militia members out there
Who been fed a steady diet of ideas but have a global history
Going to take out the leadership
Then they're going to come to your house to
Peculiar family
He knows that he was a part of a line that up and Bang the Drum constantly and now
Probably the highest-profile militia leader in the country's been arrested for sedition
Conspiracy
It sounds like maybe Alex's read the indictment by this point he knows that store
Alex isn't so stupid as to not understand that there are violent lunatics out there who were waiting
For the sign to jump off a
Start shooting people
Likely c-store getting arrested is the sign that they were waiting for
I hope that there aren't too many of these
These sorts of folks and that they'll end up choosing not to hurt people but I think the possibility
Is there
I feel like this
Just kind of why Alex's predicting this kind of false flag
Sending a message that he isn't that the paramilitary stuff
I think it's because he's really worried at this point there's a possibility that there will be some paramilitary style reprisals for Stewart
And he'd rather not have to deal with those very clear consequences of the last
13 years
What is broadcast career
Either that or Alex
Actually as proof of
Q style Commando camps in North Carolina
Which will then get blamed on paper
I would say that if he has evidence like he claims he does he better percent that s*** right now because you'll be a gigantic news story
Being done online on the internet that should have left a trail that Alex
Pretty easily
If Alex claims that his number one mission is to stop this supposed uprising
That would probably be what he does
But the reality is that Alex doesn't want to stop
You just wants to lay some groundwork so if there are some right-wing attacks will be able to point this b******* to insist
They were actually false flag
He's interested in harm reduction
But only the reduction of harm that week
Come to himself
Right that's
That's the game that he's playing here with you
I'm not into paramilitary
Militia guys
Stop being so maliciously
I do I do like that
It is that one kind of thing of of like
You've created such an imaginary world
You can't reason
People down from
From this
So you have to engage with them in the imaginary world of like
Hey don't commit any violence not cuz it's wrong
But because there's a
A secret magical organization that's trying to
Take advantage of you for committing viola
Butterbean would stand to reason that like
I guess if you know yourself to have not been part of an Internet Q camp
Commando thing
Then what is the problem with you committing
Cuz they don't know if it cuz you might get your buddies
I'm taking in
I guess so
I don't know anyways it's all just the same thing he does all the time whenever he's
You know pretty worried that the heat is a little too high covering his own ass
While since we've heard Alex get really mad about Brian
Stelter
A possibly impossible goal for himself
Alright everybody knows
Jeff Zucker
He is the mouth of the world order what you hear is a script
Eastbay
See how you look
Gives me the heebie-jeebies
Play what he has to say
Come on
Portent
Coming up next
Warframe for my normal
Things are too dangerous right now
Things are too dangerous for me to make fun of Brian stelter anymore it's just
Look we all had our fun
You know what
Once they get roads
Gun caches all around the capital
Do you know that they can't allow people to make fun of seltzer
Well they can allow it but Alex has a higher calling
He's got to be very serious
And so we'll see
It's bigger than Hip Hop.
See if he's able to hold his tongue from until already
There's no chance of that
And that is
Telkom
Wheatley fictional stories by interactions that he has with people on them
Love it
Christian
Beautiful black
Grocery store yesterday
Have you taken the shot she said all man they made me take the second one
Worst thing ever worst thing I've ever felt
I'm just now getting over in
My stomach hurts so bad you know Ma
Should yeah
.
Serious mental problems
Problems for 6 months
Was this was a beautiful woman
This is wild
The notion of Alex
Hi I'm Alex Jones from Infowars
I mean
Never happen
You know it's amazing how you know you
You all three words beautiful black and Lady
All fine together
When they come out of Alex's mouth in that order
Deeply uncomfortable
It's it it feels weird
I think fairly
Charismatic
Welcoming
Dice p
People I think wooden
End up having conversations with people about their meds
Spell cycle
Mostly wood
Not have those conversations with random people on the street
Yeah yeah yeah
Vaccine
Just a complete misrepresentation of a study
But you never actually read
Totally imaginary
But he just keeps talking about it
I just feel like asking I feel like saying hey
How are you doing
You check the shot she's old
I'm just now starting
Tell real this is
Randomly
Walking into a grocery store
The first person I talked to Scott hurt by it
Statistics
Avatar bad
First person I seen uniform
Again this never happened this person didn't exist this conversation is fake
The flimsy is b*******
Something interesting here that Alex brings up at the end that I want to touch on
He seems to be expressing that the fact that he talked to somebody who had an adverse event
From a vaccination would constitute stronger evidence about vaccine side effects
Text and data
This is really weird that's obviously not true but it's actually completely true for how Alex
Some gauges of information
Information is entirely story-based
And data isn't really all that
Compelling as a story
It's hard to read two numbers
Anecdotal stories about people real or imagined supposedly been hurt by vaccines
Stories are super compelling and he's trained izadi
It's worth far more weight on stories
Did someone could just be making up
That Maywood on data
That's a really big problem for these so-called information War cuz it's really more of a storytelling War
Yeah
That's what he should call is is show
Story time telling more hour
The mob story slam War
Oh man drag queen sad hour
So what man there's a
Obviously this
Those people who are putting it out there the vaccines are safe
Uno
All of them are getting paid
Thousands of influencers
Billions of dollars
Just the last year's that numbers about 6 months behind
Last year
Remember thing I can tell this is a completely made up stat
Story
There have been attempts to use social media influencers to encourage people to get vaccinated but that was a big dump by Pfizer
One of the more high-profile examples of this was
In Colorado where the governor hired a PR come
Pretty called idea marketing
To handle all the public facing aspect
I'm spreading vaccine information
Their contract was for 8.8 million dollars and it appears they enlisted 120 influencers on social media
Picking them up to $1,000 a month
To promote vaccine
According to their planet.
Twitter publicly-available they budgeted a total of $286,500 for compensation going to end
This is Weston that was paid for Google ads over YouTube ads and it was a bit less than they allocated even for
Spanish speaking
Can cable channel
This was last year but in December 2020 there were solar stories about influencers in New Jersey making money
I need to do similar stuff
This is more or less equivalent of a
PSA in our new social media
These people do have to disclose that they are being a making paid post
What to do if a company pays
There's a flip side of this and I'm sure Alex doesn't want to touch
May 2021
News broke that online influencers were being approached
To spread misinformation about the Pfizer vaccine
According to a New York Times bees
Mirko drotzmann a German YouTuber who comments on health issues
And has 1.5 million
Subscribers
Was approached by a mysterious agency called fazi
FaZe
About being involved in a quote
Information campaign about Pfizer deaths
The aim was to make Sensational claims about the vaccine
She's deadliness in about how everyone was covering it out
Essentially it was an information
Campaign to do Alex's show
Simultaneously
A French Health YouTuber with over a million followers was contacted by the same age
Gypsy with the same offer
Their Revelations like two other influencers coming out and saying they had also been approached
The agency is actually really shady to and according to this article
Hard to tell like
What it is
Exactly
Leo gressett posted screenshots of the messages he got from the person at the company who identified himself as
Anton
Willing to pay
2/62 videos
Instagram
Tik-Tok or YouTube
Warning the divisor vaccine was deadly
Antoine also asked him to quote act like you have the
Passion and interest in this topic
While avoiding terms advertising and sponsored impose
Material should be presented as your own independent view the p
Pitch set
Things get a bit weirder though
And by August 20-21 Facebook at a move to
Kick the fazi agency off the
The platform
More information was coming out that it was a quote
Subsidiary of a uk-registered marketing
For whose operations were primarily conduct
Did from Russia
Stream Bridge Raymond Lyrica
This obviously isn't the same
Some government plot already
But it does provide a very strong basis to conclude that this was a
Foreign misinformation campaign that targeted people in other countries
Also apparently at one point to some of the campaign was to
To spread the narrative that to the Pfizer vaccine
Was turning people into chimpanzee that's probably true though
Probably true good stuff
More Insidious
Open psa's that are being done by social media influencers who disclosed that they're doing PS
Alex doesn't care about this order story at all
Is the misinformation that's being spread is in line with a message that
If you wants to amplify
There's no good explanation for the agency's actions so the best way to navigate the stories just to ignore it and that exaggerate or lie
About what the people you don't like
Yeah
Yeah I mean I like that I like that company
I like that idea of such
Complete like
Hey either capitalism going to work or it's not you know I'm I'm offering you a bunch of money
You can either say no and there's no consequence
This for me I'm some random dude in Russia
Are you can take my money and I get what I want like that is a completely zero risk situation
I'm not entirely sure based on the information that's available
Actually
Like real
The ability to follow through with these authors may have been
You know I'm a little bit
Confused about it but
I also know
People go along with things and then get screwed by deals
That never pay off
So
Somethings made me fall into that
Yeah the first thing that I thought of whenever you told me about that was just like
Those roommate
It's cancer or they're like oh yeah I'll pay you the first
Second month's rent but I'm out at semi-state right now can you send me a little upfront so then I can
That's good that's got that Vibe Oliver
Yep so now Alex realizes
It's time
Baby
Blasted through 30-plus minutes of this transmission today I need to start digging into the news
I covering it all for you today
The first big thing I want to hear
Is Brian stelter which means the mouth of the establishment
Attacking Glenn Beck
Because he said I was making up the FEMA camp plans
Backup Mama to put American
Documents
That Obama Was preparing to put American
Education
Brainwashing term
Brainwashing
Not not accurate are the mouth of the establishment
Which is it in opposition
Jimmy Hart the mouth of the South
Got to keep those things that the stink
They are they're not the same
This has been my wrestling reference of the day
Check that box office
That's on the Whiteboard right there
I guess we got to talk about stelter
Alex has got a tip his cap
The people who are really doing
The good work
Here's the good news
Tulsi gabbard we got one back
We got
The lames going forever
And everybody else Congress people on both sides
Global government
Exercise
Then we'll understand
Control
Putting in a permanent prison
They won't be able to do this anymore
So I guess it's easier to bring in martial law type denada going to kill us all
Also Tulsi gabbard
It's getting to be a little Annoying that is great list
That was a great list goes on and on
Also like it makes me think of a hit what happened to that narrative where Jack Dorsey left Twitter so he could support Ali
I remember that.
No I think he's joining the team that's
Killing everybody again
Oh no
Alex has some other people who are heroes
These Heroes
We are here
I don't know Rodger stones come on he's had a really bad
I talked to him yesterday
So you got to come over here
They should all come on at 12:30
And he's so sick
We'll see if he's with us next shower
Remember all those descriptions of how Alex
What's the saying Rogers doing cuz it doesn't sound when he finally does show up
Also the next level is like
I was just uses a whatever you want
Is next level be supplemented next level
Rogers covid Next Level most covid anybody's ever had
So now that this has gotten out of the tip of the cap to Tulsi gabbard and the announcement that Rodger has covid
Yeah we get
Well that's what made me suspicious that he's fake
But I think
He might not be
For some other reason
You might be demonstrating
Summit
New
Problem okay
I will give this just a spoiler alert
He seemed to be slurring his speech a little bit
Oh that was not something that was a Hallmark of his previous.
And that is something that could be associated with
Damage that could be done by koe
Sure absolutely
Hesitant
Fake
Although Rodger makes it very difficult
His stunts people's people on the planet for whom guilty-until-proven-innocent
Should probably be the rule
Yeah
I'm so it would go
Stop the time
Practice written this book
Tucker Carlson
Questioning
Little people
Close everything else is open
Box Store
Alex is missing the point of stelter's beasts here
The notion that the global Elites are using covid to reshape society and crush the little guy as Felder puts
Three small throwaway line that he uses to describe Glenn's book is
The piece is actually entirely about a specific
Claim the back makes on Tucker
Commercial about officials in Washington
Meeting to plan internment camps
To put on vaccinated people
Tucker doesn't ask any
Gender pushback at all
But just listens with his wife quizzical look weirdos
A take on that is the central thing that Alex needs to refute
If he's going to cover this video which will see if he does
Funny actually
Gets out of business
Also really Alex needs to update his dog
Does he really expect
We're only big
What stores are allowed to be open at this point
I got you something you remember saying from like a year-and-a-half ago that just
He doesn't realize isn't true anymore even if he back then
Yeah I don't know what it is that
Or not
Parts or is that that narrative whenever you start as muscle memory start digging deep back in there you don't know what
It's still part of that
And he doesn't
No so it's just going to come out
Yeah it's like
I threw up a little bit of
Like a demon coming out of the CERN collider that narrative
Just pop back up
So
Galaxy be interested
Primarily on Focus
Kissing on the wrong
Beginning of
Smelter
P-Square Huey's East suspect
The Glenn Beck
May not have
Written the book because
Back starts with this is the best book I've ever read
I mean wrote
I wrote that it's okay with making fun of that
Oso
So you didn't we did have a Ghostwriter
Okay
Does it matter
The point is he's exposing
Hey Global compilation
What's unfolding
Things in the book
Was no evidence
Is it just made up
The great reset
He does say that the Washington
Is made up though but you can see here how Alex is intentionally misrepresenting what stelter piece was about
So you can get mad about it without exposing his audience the actual point
If you just insist that he was claiming without providing any proof of X book is all made up the audience
Going to turn the lies that
The claim is that still there was saying that the great reset is completely made up the audience can conclude that
It's. There's an intentional liar
And this critique of stalkers shity journalism should just be ignored
At the end of the day Alex is basically just trying
Provide cover for Tucker like some sad underlined signify
Anything bad that said about the boss
Yeah
Specific thing that Glenn Beck talks
What about is completely made up and that is the story about
Should stay preparing internment camps for unvaccinated
Native people
That's because that's totally made-up
Piece of legislation passed in 2003 in wash
Washington title wac 246
6-10 0.040
This legislation allows local Health officials to quarantine individuals or groups of people in very narrow cases
Where there's an emergency regarding a
Chemical biological radiological agent
Or a communicable disease
If you read this with very Paranoid Eyes there's a way you can make it seem like it applies to covid but it doesn't
This was passed in 2003
But it's
Discussion recently but not because the government wanted to make it apply to code
In June 2020 the Board of Health passed the engrossed substitute House Bill 1
Change stigmatizing language in wac 246
Stash 100 in regards to HIV and AIDS
This was something that HIV Advocates have been pushing
Forsyth 2014 when Governor Inslee had set a goal
Ever doosan AIDS cases in the state by 50% by 2020
This section wac 246 100
Is something that has a slot in the agenda at every Board of Health meeting
Because they
Discuss what
What's going on
Updates need to be made
But this argument gets made if they're planning
To do this
20 when the sexual
I feel was Pat
This is a real a real thing
But there's also a fake
Fixing that
Stelter brings up that he applies to
People that Glenn Beck
Claiming there's going to be in tournament
Cancel.
There were a couple of viral posts on social media with a headline from a site called the value
Has American not vaccinated
Before 2022 will be put in cash
Supposed to satire and it's labeled as satire
If anyone took the time to read it they would find some red flags like
This paragraph
Many patriotic America
Can living in Texas and Florida have announced they have no plans of going into such camp
One texting tweeting
Yeah good luck I have mines around my Ranch
That's good luck to the feds
Another Floridian tweeted
Will there be a mess in the camps if so it isn't really that bad
Local kids are actually looking forward to these camps as they believe it'll be
The closest deliver gets getting laid
Well also not having to get a shot
At the same time
I'm not even sure what the joke is there but I really really don't like
This itself is just a post that they stole from the stock market and then reposted on this body walk site with
Reposting on value Waukee
Screenshot and then Cheryl Oliver conservative in conspiracy-minded social media where people can take in the message without
Reading the clearly absurd article that is labeled satire
Adult poorly-written Joakim not be passed off as a serious article and Pete because people don't look into things they just assume it's
This relates to our subs
Because stelter brings up that claims of internment camps for the unvaccinated trace back in some cases
Satire
But I do think that he needed to do a better job of
Distinguishing
That as it relates to the specific example of washer
Washington state of that camp conspiracy
This is your uncle article is background to the real misrepresentation of the stuff
About washing
Updating the language in their bill
To reduce hiv-aids stigma
This leads me to an unfortunate point
And that is what I'm going to have
Have to take stelter to tasks a little bit here
But for different reasons than Alex
Cuz he's ugly Ono
Well about the Washington State campus
Conspiracy USA Today fact-check said that this conspiracy started from a satirical post
That is not true
The USA Today article is about the valuewalk article that I meant
The better to go but it actually has nothing to do with
Specific case
In Washington
Except like I said
As like pre-tax
Extra background
This matters because filters pieces about missing information and how sloppy mistakes from the media
Can Aiden spreading bulshit
He's somewhat undercut by the fact that
He himself is making a sloppy mistake here
And attributed to watch
Conspiracy to this satire article
Instead of disgust
Actual misrepresentation of the Board of Health bill
That mistake whatever the cause can be used by people like Alex to claim that he's covering up valid concern
Very least
Undermine the idea that people who are critical of right-wing misinformation know what they're talking about
I wish you done better here but at the same time Alex
Sister lying about the conversion of
What stop they're saying
So that he doesn't have to deal with a broader point
The Stompers making which is actually
The broader point is correct
Write the sloppiness is just there which is important
No I'm
Yeah but it's like what are you going to do journalism tired and it's not like they're paying him hundreds of thousands of dollars
Is there something or he has a giant
I-team available to him or anything along those
I feel like
Run into the
This a bit
Like these thought
The answer is
But there's there's a part of me that feels like
Obviously coverage of this misinformation stuff is important that needs
Speed needs to be done
I wonder if an organization
With paradigm
I'm like CNN
No is actually the answer is already
I did I wonder if
Those those Outlets are actually even possible
Of presenting it in the way
Wow that there's
Their shows run as it is
I don't know I mean ignored it seems like it might be possible but I
I I don't
It is only possible to the extent
That the other factors
That they have to
Kowtow to will allow it
Like as long as they're a prophet
Driven Network
Misinformation is also part of their job
You don't make money by telling people
The truth all the
You know like it that's just how it works
When you run
So many different ads
How many different things
When you're trying to tell all of these different stories all at the same time
In such a short amount of time you're going to lose
A lot of s***
And you're going to wind up doing
Sloppy
Right
It's it's kind of similar to what we're experiencing here in so far as
What you can
Can do is you can say that this is tracked
Back to a satirical piece
USA Today fact
That is a true demonstrable
Right but it's not
But it's not
It's a condensation of the way that the entire sequence
Event happen
And so instead of
Misinformation maliciously
They wind up because of the
Constraints of there
Time structure because of the constraints of
Money and so on and so on and so forth
Doing these little things and they add up
Often times
It's the result of
New shows
Are made run maybe their needs
To be some changes
To that
I don't know exactly what those changes are
But for my purposes what I'm most
Interested in is
Particularly when the subject
It's being covered
This misinformation
And
You know stelter's calling out
Write like
Media entities that are
That are like they make a mistake and that it's
Poundstone
But you can't do that you can't do that and then make this kind of a mistake
It's just b*******
Well I mean
There their trap
Because the people who have been on the misinformation beat
Have gotten really good at it over the past five
5 to 10 years
And the mainstream networks didn't bother
It wasn't really important
Into them they were
Just doing the news
So now they're trying to step into space that
Well-trodden by people who are very very good at it
And they don't want to hire them and so
Like I don't know what speaking for myself I don't want them exactly
Exactly
Yeah I don't know
So Alex has some clips
But he wants to promote that he doesn't
He doesn't have or Lisa doesn't ask
Can we play
Glenn Beck
Thank you you're so dumb
Yes you put the cheapest
Protractor
Guys are all talk like that
I think I think Alex is doing these impressions
Because he promised
His hat Subway was talking about
Like just childish outbursts and so he has to do these voices
Right right right he's got to have an outlet
Yeah I would love for him to
To play the clip of the head of Pfizer saying
Oh we put the chip in Algood
Yeah I don't
Confident
Teddy's making this up
I'm also confident that he never plays it on this site
Yeah sure
Alex ends up playing this
Shelter
And I did notice
That he does not interrupt
Because I think of you'd is holding himself back
About this
It's professionalism I have to be professional ow
So he gets about a minute and a half
The way through
And here's where we're at
Sit there and listen to
Amazon right now
Because
20 seconds
Notice
He says he did he even showed his book
He showed his penis on air
What
Free speech
I'm not sure I've ever seen Alex have so much
Nothing
Like I said he doesn't talk over the cliff with any other up to that
I'm so confused about what he's even mad about like I don't remember where I watched it I remember stelter saying anything about showing the book
So I went back and
Listen to it again
The beginning
He says this
If you take a step back and think about it but covid-19 pandemic is a chance for salesman
To self fear
Take the unvaccinated Glen back who's been selling his new book
Sick with covid
He said Schilling his book
That was just so much nothing that he went back to the start of the video to find something to get mad about it was a word he misheard
Oh my God
This is pathetic
Wow wow
Well thanks Alex ends up not being able to
Mr. Potato Head here we go
That was that
Up there
Literally
It's all over the world
Do states have bills
Anyone they want
In the government
Children away
Announcements
Stupid
Just couldn't do it
Couldn't do it I think it is admirable the effort that he made though
For him especially
You can almost
Feel Alex kicking himself at the beginning of the clip though knowing that he'd essentially failed his own self assign tasks
As for the snacks are news Alex has about KFC's leading with lying about the Washington
Sense8 story that we've already discussed to
The fact that was his go-to as a pretty strong indication that the
This pack is probably just printed out memes and poop
I guess he's going to get into this tacky though so let's let's go
Potato Head.
Mr. super Potato Head
Nonsense filter blast
Covid-19
Directions
This is exactly what is she in the legislation and exactly what's been implemented outside of it
Emergency order by the governor Washington
Conspiracy
Alex is making up that part about the Washington bill
Still just about the updating of the language we discussed earlier but he's pretty committed to covering for Tucker's negligence
Defensible
After this other document I believe that this is what I was referring to a couple episodes back when he said that the CDC had documents about wine
Internment camps
Sounds like what the f*** is he talkin about I think it's this
The first words that really jump out to you when you hear the title of this document or humanitarian setting
That should tell you a little bit about the context of this document and how it's about strategies they could be
To limit the spread of covid
In settings like camps for displaced persons
And refugee
Now the title itself might make you think that this
The document that laid out
Plans
Instead it discuss the pros and cons of exploring
Specific strategy
BB shooting approach
To explore possible challenges that one would have him
Implemented
Approach was basically a plan where you would have areas
In these places like refugee camps that would be isolated from the larger camp
And what you do is you put people who are at higher risk
Developing serious covid cases there
Has a way of shielding
This can be done on various scales
It could be done within a household even if you
Just had a part of the house
Chernobyl
This is what
Disgusting
Also it would be a mistake to assume that this document thinks that it's
The great idea to use this track
Do you also
In theory shielding may serve its subject
To protect high-risk population
Confirm disease and death
However
Implementation of the approach necessitates strict
Security protocol
Inadvertent
Introduction of the virus into a green zone may result in Rapid transmission among the most vulnerable populations
This approach is trying to protect
This is very sexual problem
What is called out
If you read the actual entire document You Come Away with a Santa
That the CDC is saying that this approach
May work
But there's no empirical evidence that it will
And at the challenges and downsides are pretty real
Take this passage from the summary
Quote Public Health not only focuses on the eradication of disease but addresses the entire spectrum of Health
And well-being
Population
Displaced due to natural disasters or war and conflict are already fragile
Experienced increased mental physical and or emotional trauma
Well the shielding approaches not meant to be
Be coercive
Hit me a forest or be misunderstood that humanitarian settings
As with many Community interventions meant to decrease covid-19 morbidity and mortality
Compliance and behavior change are the primary rate-limiting
Steps and may be driven by social in Emotion
No factors
These changes are difficult
And develops table setting
They may be particularly challenging and humanitarian settings
Which bring their own set of multi
Faceted challenges
That need to be taken into account
Okay
It doesn't seem like they're saying do this
This isn't about the creation of any camp
Unvaccinated people to
It's about how best to serve folks are in humanitarian settings already
Folsom
The CDC public
Affairs specialist
Told fact check
That the document itself was only prepared as a response to a paper
In the London that came out from the London School of hygiene and tropical medicine
That argue in favor
The shielding approach
So in response to that they didn't analysis
Also this was primarily an analysis at the CDC CDC did as a resource
Are other countries who have larger populations
Displaced persons
I wear this question was a much higher priority
All the stuff Alex is a bulge
Like none of us has any connect
Listen to reality
Although the title of the document if you ignore the what it is
If you are the everything title doesn't really work
Because it has humanitarian settings
And it and like I don't know
I guess it sounds scary though okay here's my
Alright
My pitch is
We do setup
Alright
But
We make
Them so
Like the best
Horses
Really great water ever access the water
Inflatable thing we can lay on the end of your jumps off of Guyana
One roller coaster maybe two I don't know I'm getting ahead of myself
Budgetary restraints Minecraft
But the point is
It's we make it so nice
Eventually everybody in the camp
Realizes that the real camp
Is the United States
So there's going to be hallucinogenic
Okay
To get to cuz I was away
Operation
Look it up
Why did Alex's reading this headline from Mike Adams light natural
Look it up it's written by a guy named Ethan Huff but I got to think about the byline name
Do people arriving under because otherwise holyshit this guy cranks it out
Kennedy blog is that was Ethan Hawke's pen name
This blog post was really just a reposting of something from another blog written by a guy named
Steve rotter
1 days
Steve was poking around on the website of the world domestic
Preparedness Consortium organization which is a federal organization
Train people in rural
And tribal communities how to respond in cases of emergencies
Like natural disasters
This is a great program
In no small part because it helps these communities have autonomy
And not rely solely on the more develop resources of neighboring more urban areas
I think point out areas with smaller populations will likely
Not have the tax base that would be required to staff Public Safety age
Please show the rdpc helps train folks for free to help there
Right
TPC offers
Constant training opportunities in both in person context
When available
And on their website in Virtual class
Steve was cruising around their website and found a training course available titled E3 isolation in Corinth
19 for World communities
He misinterpreted the context of the organization and decided to conclude that this was a nuke
Or that it was somehow related
The covid
But that's not the case
It's important to understand that a lot of the courses that the rdpc offers are facilitated through University
And of course that Steve is up in arms about
Is one that's offered by Eastern
Kentucky University
Be confined at existing as a course offered
In conjunction with the rdpc sense
Years before covid
What is even a thing
It's actually slightly unclear to me but based on our current website it seems like
EK you handle some other courses at this point
And the quarantine classes now done by the Northwest Arkansas Community College
For the sake of clarity
The syllabus for the course is available on the rdpc website and explain some of the class involves things
Legal and ethical considerations of isolation and quarantine
My Ding-a-Ling
Getting into the developer details
This becomes important because what Steve is done for his blog post
Is that he's gone into the course module and selectively
Taking screenshots that he can use to make them
Look sinister
It takes a page that discusses the differences in legal and ethical considerations you have involuntary vs. involuntary Courant
Teen situations
Play the this is about getting people to
Comply because
They point out that involuntary
These are more taxing on resources
And much more complicated regarding
What is this
Dealing with that is a descriptive reality
Is is being represented as like
Yeah we got to coerce people to do is voluntarily with them
I mean it's it it is it is like
The far-right has this
This
I don't know if it's
Coordinated
It feels like it is where they fine
The most
Innocuous
Just good idea
Just like hey
Here's what we're going to do we're going to help people learn
Respond
Emergency
Nothing beyond that there's no
No nefarious element to this at all
Like something that they can turn into fairies
Like it's just
Because it's it is utility for the larger argument so they won't pay
Totally thought that was bad worse is his handling of a slide about how responders need to respect
People's privacy
He acts like it's somehow about being sneaky but it's clear from the slide
It's disgusting
I'm concerned about a stigmatizing illnesses or potential illnesses
Can be inside a community
So you should
Advertise to the neighborhood that someone might be sick
That's what this is about
No I thought you were supposed to get pictures
Pitchforks torches
Straighten
And in such a way that
Could be a perfect jump off point for a shity blog like natural news
The Christmas story even further
From their post regarding the need for privacy
Quote the emergency responders holder Victor
DeCamp
The rdpc encourages them to be as discreet as possible in order to
To keep the ordeal as much Under Wraps
As possible
You see how this goes
TPC training courses something has been offered for years and was never notice
Just until it became useful to push a covid conspiracy
And you can see the
Consistent pattern in bulshit dissemination on full display
Courses benign and a helpful resource that's provided to Rural and tribal communities
T-brace a horrible blog post misrepresenting it which is his picked up
And further sensationalize play natural news
Alex been reports on the headline that NaturalNews put on the article and makes up a story about what he wanted to me
This pipeline is very
Consistent
Alex can pretend to have the Deep sources that he has all he want
But really you just as stacks
To print it out pages of bulshit blog post
That don't have
Have anything to do with the reality of what underlies
The b******* that he's talking about it's just
I get I grow frustrated with this clearly
Traceable patch
What a fun way to view the world
Pads
The government
Is coming to
To take people away when they're sick
And
To be kind
They have a training module that make sure they know to keep
Quiet
Right so you don't mess up with anybody's private
Really nice
Just you know that's
The cover-ups
What kind of insane person would look it up
F****** slide-in be like what
Obviously they're training people
Keep it quiet when they abduct
Bavarian I would be crazy
Alex
Another
Peace and it's tacky
So far
Here's the worst part
48% of Democrats
People shoulder their habitat
So Alex has two strikes
From the last two Club
He saved himself from striking out by getting a ball on this one
Going to I'm going to skip that town hall post to just go straight to the Rasmussen data on this line
Headline from January 13th
Covid-19 Democratic voters support harsh measures against on vac
I got to save
Too far off
There's an important distinction to make by what he's reporting though and what the actual survey
He says
He's saying that 48% of democratic voters want to put anyone who doesn't get a vaccine in a
I can't but here's what the report actually
Nearly half 48% of democratic voters think federal and state government should be able to find or in prison
Some individuals
Who publicly questioned the efficacy of existing covid-19 vaccine. Social media television radio or in
Online or digital Publications
It's not for unvaccinated people it's for people who spread misinformation it also
This is a bulshit question
Based on the way the B word
You can tell from the result is at 48% support
Possible fines
Or
That's too broad of a question to me many
Do all of these people actually just
Supported a fine
The result could erroneously give the impression that they wanted to imprison people which wouldn't be reflective of their actual position
Liberty Elementary statistical information gathering
F****** in this question
Should never have been worded like that
It's the result
So this report question is do you think people who lie should get consequence
Difference in believing that people who lie about public health measures should be fined or they should be.
That's my point
Your question is so over broadly that 48% means
Nothing right
To agree that people who
Maliciously lied to get people killed or punished for it
Be a mechanism for a topical
Yeah so that's at the old the survey also found
45% of Democrats
Would favor governments require citizens to Temporary live in designated facilities or locations
If they refuse to get a covid-19 vaccine
So in some ways Alex isn't totally lying but the spirit of what the survey says
He just can't keep the details with a number
Another interest
The point is that if you look at the more detailed breakdown
Only 22% of Democrats strong Lisa
Support this idea well 33% strongly opposed
Overall it seems to me like there's greater opposition then support
For this even among Democrats
29% of democratic voters support temporarily removing
Custody of their children if parents refuse to take
Take a covid-19 vaccine
I'm not really sure that I agree with those 29% of Democrats and also
You look at it the other way that means 71% are not in
In support of such a plan
So take your pick on how you want to look at
Also this isn't the question to ask people about actual
Proposals this is a hypothetical
Overall the course of my time doing the show I've
Come to be a bit skeptical of results that I see from Rasmussen
Early reporting the results of this poll
I'm not sure that the results of the Pullman
Nor do I think it helps his argument that the government is making camps
The lockup
It being one of the three pieces of evidence you provided to defend Glenn Beck and Tucker
Ridiculous segment from stealth
Criticism
Yeah I don't even see how it's relevant
I haven't even done that question so f******
Stupid
Did you support
What do you mean what does that even mean
Do you support taking somebody's kids away with a refuse to give accident if they test positive
Get them to a hotel that's the same f******
Thanks you're taking their kids away
Like who
What they're trying to say and it's such a
Stupid question
There are different ways that you could understand
The question
I think it's a bad idea I think that I would to be a with that 71% that is probably like
I figured that causes more problems that it might alleviate
Probably not
Another another piece if he strikes out
Casey At The Bat as it were
Here's another one Utah's largest newspaper called for unvaccinated County lockdown enforced by the National Guard
Yourself
OKC astruc
This is an editorial
The paper isn't calling Freddy
Isn't even calling for what Alex Clare
From the Arctic
Quote
Were you taught truly civilized place
The governor's next move would be to find a way to man
Campaign we should have launched
The year ago
Going as far as to deploy the
Metal guard to ensure the people without proof of vaccination
Would not be allowed
Well anywhere
It may be too late for that politically and B
I've noticed that the right-wing and right-wing media figures like Alex in particular really ever
Convenient and I suspect intentional inability to understand the difference between an editorial
Piece of news or an official state
Because he plays fast and loose with a
Distinction between those things
Report an op-ed as if it was a demand being made by a newspaper which in turn
Delete the unjustified conclusion
I suspect he does that on purpose
Because it's really easy
Any day of the week
You can scan through enough papers
If you do
You'll find something in an editorial to get mad about
Tattoo the laziness
You can tell the based on the headline that Alex reads he's not actually talking about the real editorial
He's covering a zerohedge article that's mad about the editorial for him
Just bullshittin
Meaningless anyway you strike out
But that doesn't stop him
From claiming Vic
To CNN's got articles about all look at your other getting smart
Australia walking buddy
Portal kill you
Little Shack
Fighting depression
I don't know if this is true but I heard a rumor that Brian stelter is in the New Kingdom Hearts game
Call Tres Amigos wholesale problems
Yeah I went out with his failed across the
The board
Is dealing with the actual points
Failure is
Decided not to attack Selter
She also failed
Yeah
This is really sad to like you provided these specific citations Aleve
Just got here and I guess he thinks that's enough that he can't
Declare Victory but it isn't at all
Filter central question was about the Washington campus
Conspiracy in Alex didn't demonstrate in any way that it was a real thing or the
Spell there was wrong
He was flung around a bunch of headlines that he pulled from dishonest blogs
To create the impression that camp
Being made in some vague
Play somewhere
Or maybe the Democrats support
The dump
He didn't even address the actual points Elders video
He's acting like he's
Trying Alex's arguments are meaningless
Nonsense
Stupid
Yeah in the in the baseball metaphor it would be like if journeyman sec
Second baseman struck out
And then just started running to first base
And celebrating it through is bad into the crowd and
Ran to second base was screaming and everybody's like oh my God and then he got the home
Any declared a homerun
And that's how the rules of baseball were
Exactly how it works
So here's how Alex
Yeah there it is Bill Watsonville
It's not a rumor
Scalp
I need your support. You all you got
We are the black sheep
So it does
Arab talk about the afterthought
Hi this is just a Gateway pundit article about the same washer
Language update due to talk about earlier
The correct team of sleuths found this wording and the wac 246 100.
Quote a local Health officer May invoke the powers of police officers Sheriff sconce
Constables and other officers
And employees of any political subdivisions with jurisdiction
How the health department to enforce immediately
Orders given to effectuate the purposes
Other
In accordance with the provisions
Of Baba Baba
Found this language of something new or a new bill
That is not part of the statutes
The past in 2000
The whole thing is about the revisions they were made to remove stigmatizing language and it's not recent either
Like I said that's up to House Bill 1551 pasta
June 2020
Does Gateway pundit article is straight up stupid
It ends with this ominous line
Wac 246
Dash 100-0 40 was certified on October 25th 2019
Months prior to the coronavirus outbreak in the United States
That's efficient the first case
First confirmed case of covid in the US was diagnosed in
In Seattle on January 20th
Florida Steve pieczenik
We all know that we all know that
The implication is supposed to obviously be that they pass this law where Health officials get to be like cops just before the first cases
Cobra diagnose
Because they knew the cover was coming
I'm not at the hell people get to act like cops to put Alex and his friends into FEMA
This is just really bad work for a few reasons
The first is that the language about health officials taking on police
Responsibilities was introduced
In 2003
You think the larger set of permanent rules of the Board of Health predate that button 2003 large-scale revamp of the doctor
I was passed
Hennis was part of wanted
The sections it was Amanda
The second reason that this is stupid is because the
The claimed this rule was certified on October 25th 2019
Is just based on the fact that the bottom of the
The page that the on the website of the washing
The state legislature where they posted this rule
It says quote certified on October 20th
But that doesn't mean that it was past or even amended the
That day
If you go and look up other documents from the washing
State Legislature
You'll find it
Literally all of them
Include certified on October 25th 2019 at the bottom
It's really hard for me to tell precisely what the deal is here because I don't work for the Washington legislature but if I had to guess
In October 2019 they went through a process of updating all the files that are posted online
And a certification date
Words like that
Okay added a new online portal to change
Documents are acceptable
And so in order to do that
You have these listings of the
The existing statutes
And they are certified by
The statute law committee
Washington legislature
The idea that
Did the date involves anything related to any statutes went on the book
Is dumb unless you think the state of Washington establish their Department of Commerce
In October 2019
There's this unfortunate dynamica to play here and if you're a reporter at the Gateway pundit Evan the smallest amount a day
Digging would puncture gigantic holes in
Understory
The goal is to arrive at a predetermined
In conclusion that provide headlines or someone like Alex or your parents on Facebook to get mad about
Hoping to anger them
We can drive traffic to your site boost ad Revenue
The best way to do that is
To be lazy
Do not do any of that digging that would end up causing Your Story 2
Fall Apart
If you see quote certified on October 25th 2019 on that page
You're working
Is done because your assumption fit the narrative but if you explore it more reality might not you don't want to
To deal with that
Oh yeah
Stelter was wrong and Altima
Medley after all this
Think he hasn't demonstrated it
Anything he's talking about is more than a rumor
Are dumb conspiracy blog headline
Yeah it is a little bit like Gateway pundit
Or like
Digging for oil
Alright whatever pop
Pops out of the ground there like stop jigging we've hit oil
And all they do is hit sewer pipe
Absolutely for the s*** work
So we we get off the stelter tip that's basically his
I do think he managed to insult him
But he still didn't
Was gone
So stelter business
Check okay
Now
It's Raji tile
But
She had a fever come on
Appreciate him coming on
For survival
Cuz I let him call me a Russian agent
Put on coffee and tea and stuff and my kids attacked
Call me Russian
Lawyers here
Bugatti
You're not going to just shut up
Why the hell would I want to do that
Got Hijacked
Involved
BoBoiBoy Rhino holes crack
People who are involved
David friend of yours Adelaide
So anyway Rodger a he's he's decided that it's time
He's going on the attack
Rodger Stone joins us to talk about who he is going
Here today
Rodger Stone thank you so much for joining us
Alex Hirsch College
Great to be here
And I guess right off the bat
I want to thank the thousands of people around the
Curry who have been praying
For my recovery in
What turned out to be
A much more
Call struggle
With covid-19
Then I had expect
It is only by
Following a strict regimen of ivermectin
Hydroxychloroquine
Including
Gay
Claritin
Chick-fil-A
I and others
And for the helper
Truly truly gutsy
Courageous doctors
That I can finally tell you that I am
Back to work and feeling normal
Again doesn't quite match
The way that Alex was describing his case
Earlier than a or b
I think as we go through this we're going to hear him
Talking a lot more slurry than usual
And
I don't know
You could be drunk
But on the other
It could be a neurological side effects
There are bad like a mild stroke
It wouldn't surprise me that a regular thing and I don't want to make fun of that
I wanted to be as respectful as possible
Well still make
King fun of Rodger cuz he's a f****** a****** and I hope we'll be able to stay on the right side
Yeah
So Rodger this is the thing that went around Twitter
This is truly
Terrific
And I had all of the worst symptoms
The fevers
The sweats
The cough
The congestion
The body aches
Dementia
Tony fauci in his red Chinese,
Grads
Do superb job
In the formulation
Audition bio-weapon
Something just doesn't feel right
Like I know that those things can be bad side effects
Text but that's kind of like
The generic list
Side effects
It's just something weird about this
This is off
Yeah
I think it's probably just because it's Rodger
I think it's because we're trained to be suspicious of everything he does
You're just waiting for if if he was laying down bleeding from the skull
I would walk up to him and I be expecting him to have a knife ready to stab me if I went and asked him if you like jelly
Exactly be like immediate like listen man I'm sorry
You earned this
This isn't me react
Humane way to believe that that's marinara
Yeah
Anyway
Look hydroxychloroquine Ivermectin
Sean Forte I think he's angling for a bukit
Look I don't know what all of his politics agree
With all of mine but on this issue
Do Olive courses on the issue of cannabis legalization
I totally agree with him what
It was very courageous
You know they go after him
I know they try to shut him down
But he did was right I honestly think this man saved
Thousands and thousands and thousands
A lot
Whoa
Lego werewolf
Wow
That's
That's depressing
Being
Fundamentally
Not entirely
But fundamentally at fault for the millions of people who have died
And then saying that we've saved hundreds of
He's a real tough pill for me to swallow
Yeah it's
It sucks to hear a really fuksas my head
Really makes me mad
Not good
So in addition to declaring victory over covid
Is on for another reason
And that is
People now
He's about to sue everybody
There are irresponsible elements in the
Fake news media
Or recycling this notion
That I had either advance notice
Or some involvement
In the illegal act
Facts of January 6th
Legally permitted events
January 2nd
I did have a voluntary
Security detail
From The Oath Keepers
All of the other speakers
At that conference
They were courtesy of those running the
Legally
Permission events
Did I came in contact with these in individuals
Proves nothing
Buy Lettuce take
Bill Palmer
The Palmer
Report
Summer is going to be sued for 10 million dollars
In the California courts
I think it's actually more suspicious that The Bodyguard was volunteer and that everyone who is high-profile
AO keeper with them feels a little more
He was like oh see everybody had one
That's fine right
Somebody connected to a little Hub what's going on is everyone was involved with the
Conspiracy to wait no that's not what I'm
No I mean I don't know what he hopes to achieve with that bit of information but
Also The Bodyguard had wasn't desenio
Keeper like we said on the last episode it was my quips Emma
Stewart's operations
Weider
Approve any Real Deals on Rogers Park but it does explain why people have questions for him that they want answered
Also again
Whip hasn't been indicted or named did any of the
Nancy I was probably isn't a great time for these guys
Go to shift the narrative
People for saying things you don't like cuz these guys are
Free Speech Warrior
Yeah
Sale of free speech so much looking to sue media figures you know I think that's fascinating
I would like
For Rodger to sue me for defamation
Well I separate myself
Jordan may be about to say
It's not possible it's like cuz it's it's about defaming one's character
And the damages from their independent defamation I also have
But you could also make the argument that the public
Sure absolutely so the standards for defamation.
Even though I just don't think it's pause
I think there's
I think he's horrible things about himself
Google pictures of Wreckers
Constantly about how he plays up that image of him as a villain or whatever Richards
I don't know it
I think the same and Rodger would be hard I think it would be
I think I
I don't know if anybody has up till this point
Bill Palmer apparently
Better get his f****** checkbook ready
Good luck
Bell
Bring your check
And your case
Accounts of defamation
The number will probably end
Being much larger
Because you haven't been
Cautious
You haven't
Also
Would make it
Not true
As senior
Officials confirm
To the Reuters News service
The FBI found
No evidence whatsoever that Rodger Stone
Or Alex Jones
Was involved in the conspiracy
To commit
Any illegal
On January 6th
Show Mr Palmer
It's your turn
Produce your proof to the contrary
Produce your Witnesses
Contrary
There are not
You're going to be writing a huge
Palmer
I for one can't wait
I don't think it Rodger understands that he's a public figure in order to make this case fly he
He's going to need to establish actual malice on Bill Barber Park
I don't think he can do
It just seems to me like what's going on here is that like Rodger wants to get that old manly blood pumping again
Eating people game for awhile so now
I think he's getting a little overzealous and making a comeback
He had to be a little bit more like cautious when he was waiting for the
For the delay low for awhile
And now he can go back to being a real s*** head
We all just been waiting for it
So let me put
Any journalist who wants to go
Step up right on notice
Choose me
Being involved in illegal activity on January 1st
Washington d.c. you will be mad
With a lawsuit
It's in the past you have accused me of being a Russian Trader
You also
Faced with a lawsuit
Show lawyer
Liberals
I'm not turning
The other cheek
See that reform is learned
Take the things that Jesus himself
Directly said and say I won't do those my face I follow the law because I would say
Adjusted made me find God in the most sincere way I will
Turn the other cheek
I was sooo you f***
What I found is most important about faith
Is when it conflicts with what you want to do
Your faith actually says it's okay for you to do that
Yeah yeah The Gospel According to Rodger
True strength is when you need
Something believing in faith and then when you don't need it
Throwing it away
How expensive is a little bit self-conscious I think he's aware that
The audience might be like talking about this s*** all the
It's getting a little boring
We know you guys are detect
Are running on January 6th
Opposition or terrorist
Kingpin Mastermind terrorist
People need to know that this is a serious issue with it
This is a big issue even miss McConnell
Problem
You're absolutely right
Tulsi gabbard's and Mitch McConnell
Hey when you got the two of them together
That's the most by party
Listen thing I've ever heard
To me like what super innocent people do
This strikes me as a weird
Threatened massive lawsuit against journalists to say things that you don't like cuz from where I'm sitting at
It's just looks like an attempt at intimidation
Rogers suits are going to go anywhere
Somebody writing an article about Rodger possibly being in trouble
There's no actual bearing on whether or not he's actually going to get in trouble
There's no real world
Consequence I don't know
This is feels like a perform
Alex as the victim
Then the whole thing
And hopefully makes people afraid to put pieces
Together as it results
As it relates to connect
3 people
Who are at the capital of
Chill people's desire to
Cover these stories
And it's a fear that Rodger is going to
Sue them
Headset said that
False
You know I would like whenever Stewart came on
Knowing what we know now and it came on and just
Started lying through his teeth about how
They were all
F******
Giving Medical Aid and s*** like that
Like it that's that's where we're at like
Hey how dare you say that I had anything to do with the six I'll sue you cut
Six months from coming
But it still has the same sort of effect
It's Shifting the
Discussion into like
You going on the attack and yeah and what have you and
It's I don't know it just doesn't feel sincere it's
So this
It struck me as a little weird
Can barely talk
No I got
Delta
Gorillaz on my chest for 2 weeks almost killed my dad
Annalee still no
Not where he was
Coors Light Rodger didn't. It's a very serious bio-weapon they scanned it two years ago
And I knew it was about 11
Older subject I wanted a little bit
In the next segment
I thought you made it and that's come out in court
Yeah Court okay the court of
I've been recorded public opinion specifically on Alex's show
I just I like that clip a lot because Alex was talking about how
You got covid
And it was like a gorilla was on his chest
But the way you saying that he says
Okay to grill on my chest
For two weeks almost killed my dad almost killed his dad
Flashlight
There's a ton of interpretation based on Louis speaker
King that are fun
That is nice
Anyway I would like to see the score
I would like to see a grill on Oz
So I don't I don't know if you would like this is
Martin Luther King Day
So I'm sure we're going
To quote him
No not so much
But Rogers going to tell a little story
By the way
Your wishes might
I need to know
Today is Jonica Martin Luther King Jr's birthday
Birthday
What people don't know
On the
Murder
King
Every politician
Aspiring to be president
Headed to Atlanta to get a
Photo op with
With Coretta king Teddy Kennedy
Centergy Eugene McCarthy
Bobby
Kennedy
Get Clark
Frank church and others
One man asked to see credit
Private
That was former
President
Richard Nixon
He flew to Atlanta and got a
Private audience with Coretta
Envelope
Weather check
Paid for the entire
College education
Of all of her remaining children
He also did not want
That information publicly released
Richard milhous
Nixon actually even says like on this day when we remember Martin Luther King we should
Should also remember what great things like this
Giving them a check
So this seems like a weird list at first we talked about those politicians cuz he says Dick Clark but he's not talking with the Entertainer
I got my head but immediately I was like who is the ball drop
Arizona politician who was elected to the senate in 1972 and for that he was a
Assistant to Jon Culver
How u.s. representative from Iowa
Dick Clark
So the story that Rodger is telling his one that has passed on by a king family friend named xernona Clayton
But other folks are not so convinced
This actually happened
41 there's no evidence of this check and if it did exist it was never cashed
Secondly Nixon Aid Dwight
Champion told The Daily Beast quote
It's like I'm a hundred percent certain
He would never give her an envelope
There's too much open to interpretation and wrong
Interpretation to do that
Have you think about it would be a very nice gesture from human-to-human when it's Nixon at MLK's Widow the dino
Hammocks are a little murky
I do think it's important to point out is that according to other Nixon age of this meeting with King was not really something that Nixon wanted to
Just a secret
Nixons visit with Miss King what was off the Record but that evening in Key Biscayne
Nixon wanted to know how it was
Playing
Tape and reminded him that it was off the Record
Nixon
Expected news of the meeting Woodlake
And was Furious when told it had not
So nickroo another Knicks
Sinead called Atlanta radio stations to
Tip them off that Nicks
Some had been seen at the king home
But when reporters called the house no one
Confirm the visit
According to these AIDS going to visit Miss Cain was away from
And to get out of having to go to the
The funeral cuz I didn't want to end it didn't work he still had to go to the funeral I don't know what the reality is
I kind of think that the
Point about Nixon not giving King an envelope because he'll be widely open to interpretation
Makes more sense with the other facts of reality that I factored in
I'm not sure
You know I
There's something there
Another point that I saw brought up
Was interesting was
That
Nixon was friends
With Martin Luther King senior
The two of them were on friendly terms
Was suggesting
I could see a possibility where he
He asked
Martin Luther King's father
If the kids were taken care of if there was a college fund for them
It's a happening
Like something he never would
You know I mean this is a good tip
I'm going to throw this out there
Doesn't change my pic
Opinion of Knicks
Does not
Affected even a little bit
12 look
Route from Rogers perspective
Whenever You Remember by Luther King you must
Remember that AJ's Martin Luther King Jr's birthday and also the anniversary of Richard Nixon showing that he is
Just as good of a person is Martin Luther
The King Junior sex exactly the case
No s***
So anyway Alex has some thoughts about the I Have a Dream speech
Amazing
Was it terrorism when he got hundreds of thousands of people are more
Voting rights activist
Wasn't
What was really happening when the election is Democrats and asked for four years before
Constitution
Oh man I guess there must be some kind of real important difference
What happened during the 1963 Civil Rights march
1963 no one storm the capitol
No one knowing that even if you seems like a really important difference at Alex's just ignoring
If Trump and all of his followers are just
Hung out outside the Capitol in the area today
What's 4 + Wade signs of
We probably not even remember the date January
6 at this point
It'll just be another impotent protests fueled by misinformation
Alex wants to pretend that the man wants to arrest everyone who was there but that's not true that's his
False strawman that he's created
Being arrested or people who
Also
No one criticized the March on Washington for jobs
The freedom he should look into his own history and see what the John Birch Society was saying about it
Yeah there's a book called the world of the John Birch Society and
Discuss the response to the March
Societies response to these developments
Was both to considerably increase the amount of time and attention
To the question of black civil rights
A frame the issue within the organization to Broderick and
Conspiratorial understanding
Of Communism is determination
To take over the United
The progenitors of Alex's entire worldview were
The time of the I Have a Dream speech that I was Professor to love so much
Attacking King
As part of a secret communist plot to overthrow the United States
Which by extension would mean that the March on Washington was secretly a communist March
Attempting to overthrow the
The United States
There would be that
It's fun for Alex everyone supported King in 1963 but the reality is that if he been around back then
At least half of the show would be him reading bulshit headlines about how King was work
Communist Chinese
Destabilize America
Call just nonsense
Even possibly
Project himself back to that time and realize what a dick you would have
Unreal
And still is
Yep.
I think this is on
Unfortunate
This is dumb
Those who say
Question Lee reaction results is treason
Their own actions when they got beat by
By George W bush
Everything they are they're accusing us of is exactly what
They did
Real quick question
Results particularly very close election result
Is that was all the folks like Alex and Trump were doing then we wouldn't be in the situation where right now
Question anything
They said definitively that the election was stolen of the Trump won which is a crime against all Americans and people needed
To stand up a
Against the steel
And the cover-up
Even Rodger stupid ass was saying on Infowars the North Korean boats full of ballots were arriving in Maine to steal the election
He did say that it's b*******
Compare this at all to
The response for the 2000 election when does
Supreme Court essentially decided
Conceited
Also Rodger should probably pump the damn breaks
You're considering his involvement in the 2000 election and how we essentially facilitated a false flag
To get counting of votes stopped in Florida
Mysterious parallels
Smoothies
Sting enough
He probably
Would threaten to sue me for bringing this up let's
Hey it's important
For those who weren't around back then the 2000 election hung in the balance depending on who won Florida
Where the results were ridiculously close
A recount had been underway and then on November
22nd 2000
Republican protesters showed up at the Miami-Dade County location
And intimidated the officials there with loud accusations that they were stealing people
It also physical action
Joe Geller was in the Democratic party chairman
For the county and he was on hand that day
Quote this one guy was tripping me and pushing me and Kicking
We're called gallery
Who is now a state legislature
At one point I thought they knocked me over I could have literally got stopped
To death
The Miami-Dade recount ended that day
Billy Bush was certified as the winner by 537 votes
It's on November
With this recount as well as the one
Palm Beach County
Never actually being
Just went back and forth in the courts and we all know how it is
It went great
In 2008 Rodger Stone told the New Yorker that he had essentially been running the operation
These protesters who were actually just GOP
Staffers
Into the recall location
To get it shut
I set up my command center there walkie-talkies and cell phones and I was in touch with our people in the building
Our whole idea was to shut the recount down
And that's why we were there
Another GOP strategist Brad blakeman also take credit for running the event
Who is him who is responsible
Causing a stage Uprising that was intended to disrupt
Carrying out of the Alexa
For the purposes of installing his
Preferred candidate George W bush
If I were Rodger I would say
Simply not bring up the 2000
Doing so
Has the potential to remind people that he was deeply involved in an event
It's a weirdly similar to the events of the 6th
Kind of
Shut up about that Rogers
Fitbit steps
What serial killer should they always show up and they all want to be smarter than the
Topsail want to dive watch true-crime ship before so I can show up and they're like
You'll never catch me and I like to drop hints that they did it
I'm going to be given credit for but they don't want consequences for not saying the Rodger orchestrated anything on the six
I'm just saying that his actions in 2000
No that's what I'm saying to be part of a pattern
No he's Bragg
Every time he brings up the 2000 election as something that went
Well he's bragging about how he made it happen
So weak
Get to it we get to talk
Some other issues
With Rodger cuz it can't all be
Lawsuits
Martin Luther King
Talkabouttd
Trump
What's going on with Trump
I was talking to Rodger yesterday
He likes the president respect
As he was with with with
Yesterday
Really just worried about Trump
And
What you say that she is
Well I don't mean physically I mean
Direction has Diet Cokes again I guess
I guess
Snap now he's too feeble in the mines and
So Rogers main point is that he takes issue with
The drop is making
Endorsing the right candidate
It's some of his
Cheeks come off
Little racist
What perplexes me
Some of his endorsements
Endorse
Congress Marriott
Diaz-balart
Miami
Donald Trump
Mario diaz-balart
From the Frito Bandito
Tell you that if it wasn't
Doris Diaz Bellard because he was one of the members of the House of Representatives
The joint
Sue Texas versus Pennsylvania 2020
And results
Seems like Trump is going to be willing to endorse
Subscribe to the idea that he actually want me
Those guys in that in that
It's how the mob
Yeah
A couple other people that he takes issue with but
It gets to another Hispanic person
Boy
Anna
Lena Luna
There is no such person in Napoleon Ilona is not Hispanic
Picture of her with an assault weapon wearing military
And she said quote
Until you have some
Build
Blood for this country UK
Understand
For freedom
Anna Paulina Luna never served in combat
And Hurston
In the Air Force was not 16 years
It was 6 months
I have no idea what Rodger is going on about this conversation makes no sense
He's attacking Luna is a bad candidate Alex says that you'd be good
Play Senator Blumenthal and Rogers
Yes
This is so convoluted because Luna is running for the GOP
The primary to represent Florida's 13th District
In the house of
Meanwhile Richard Blumenthal the senator from Connecticut
These two people have no direct Connection in their election election would
Replace Blumenthal
But anyway
Luna's up against a stacked
Field of four other candidates in the in the primary
Even if she wanted to be facing Charlie Crist
Forever and the general election already beat her in 2020 e53 247
Really exciting Cedar were back in the arguing about GOP primaries season on Infowars
It's always so fun cuz I was getting
To Bringing complete lunatics with zero chance of winning any prize
Pretender way up in the polls
Seems like a Rogers is hyper focused on local races in Florida 2020
Because I think locally
Keep him there but I don't know if this matter is to Alex's audience and
Since a little bit of bit of racism
Going through this
This man talking about local politics
You could just write a letter to your local band this stuff about her military service I mean like
Whatever I don't know what the reality is but if you're going to take issue with this
If you got a lot of people with Stolen Valor I'm in your ranks that you need to work out from the top and then go down
And we'll see how long it takes you to get to her
Yeah yeah I think she's a small issue compared to some of these other weirdos
Alex he's a picture
This Anna Paulina Luna
And now we're going to get real
Oh boy
Bigfuture news coming about her
Well it's actually questioned her last name is meyerhofer they truly
Yeah that's a weird question
About a good question at all
Repeat question
So I'm not even going to descend into this
Like very clear races signaling and trying to
Discuss this but I will say that just because Luna's birth name is Anna meierhoffer
That is that is her father's surname that doesn't mean that her mother may not have been in
Entirely of Hispanic
Percent
It seems like Rogers is pulling at straws
Very racist strawberry
His drawers Luna was popular because she was supposed to be something like the GOP Trump World version of AOC
And it just didn't work
Charlie Kirk initially recruited her to do this Panic Outreach for turning point
Get the extra run for office
Which she did unsuccessfully in 2020
Recycles repeating now and I guess Trump is supporting her as he didn't
2020 in Rogers
Racist Lee pissed off
That's
Just
Well you said
She wasn't Hispanic
So what is
That's the answer is
Person answered she is a person
Do the person just like you and me we're all people man yeah
Yeah you keep such a bizarre train of thought on Alex
You know like hold on before I can even begin to discuss insurance
The human being
First no
Her genealogy
Yeah
Also like this strange Vibe of like
She's trying to
Trick you
Yeah
Hey listen
GOP voters
This person is it actually Hispanic the thing
No are you
Are we against
Thinking about this
Cuz a lot of eye contact
The redundancies but a lot of
Rogers appearances threat
Sue everybody everybody's going down expect us to get service from point
I kind of figured out what this is
Alex this is a change for me
I'm tired of being on.
Fence
Infowars in Bigfork
People kissing
For my legal defense to defend myself
Now help me go on the attack
These people these mangy
Indoor courtroom
And shoo them and say
What they have. God
It's a little too obvious
It wasn't paying the bills people weren't excited about the legal defense fund anymore so you trying to rile people up and get them
I'm excited promising that you're going to take these dirty leftist
The court make them pay
Brian like
Has never happened
Strand of fundraiser of the idea that you're going to sue people hate this kind of pathetic
And exactly what I would expect
Simulacra
Yeah
You enjoy paying for my legal defense
Natural territory for Rodger
This whole thing is like always Beyond
Never be defending yourself
You have to
Because the consequences
Not doing so would be
Pretty high the water is used to submit in
I mean something you can make
Never one of your wackamole signs a new little hole you know it feels safe enough to pop back out
And just
So
Exhausted
This point
Episode drama Rodger getting covid and suing everybody being a weirdo
Stop being a racist weirdo
This piece of s*** and I wasn't ready for this
I really appreciate him coming on Jimmy Kimmel
Actor
Fortunate Michael in Delavan put in prison because he was questioned the election
That's our big push God Mike lindell's on now
What happened to him
Isn't there and it hasn't he done enough
Drugs to just knock them out for a while at least
Flabbergasted by
The meaninglessness of this episode
Full it is
Of of dangerous weirdos
Amazing anyway Mike Lindell has complained that his bank doesn't work with him anymore
And dammit you got to tell your friend
You guys
You go out there you might have a hundred friends or
Whatever you got
Email dammit
And you are call them
Can you do this
We all need to hear about
But you're not hearing
On your terrible news Outlet
News
About anything that's going on
You're not going to tell you that
Company
Charity and
Network does helping addict
Wants to cancel it
Fox News
So Michael remember to take a minute to reflect on the fact that Fox News isn't providing the coverage that he wants because he
She's no longer a major source of their ad Revenue
Have you thought about this for a while you might realize that no one really cares that much about the nonsense he spews
It's just in your financial interest
The humor Mike when he's paying you a bunch of money
He's here spreading the message she wants to ident forwards because
He's a sponsor
Back in the day
Marty Schechter could come on and do f****** Limerick now you got your time
Can do whatever you want to sponsor Alex Gaby
Navigate to come on Inn
Complain about the
The bank and I wanted to work with him anymore
So it's it's sad let that be a lesson
To all of us never get it
He's clearly a dick
Never allow yourself to be deluded into thinking
That
Time that you're paying for
In that is indicative of
People's real response
Add time and then
We'll just bizarrely all of a sudden really being
How seriously Fox News takes your complaint seriously into a point where you say
Think that there's more meaning to your shift and there is
Have you learned the hard way that when you stop being one of the main advertisers
All the sudden they don't seem to care about your b******* that much
So weird
It's almost like if Julia Roberts
Had left
Richard Gere at the end of the movie
Because their financial
Action had been
Spiritual sequel
Sunnyway Altos.
Store
Barber shops in Taken
What you got in power the first
5 years was
His political enemies
King away
And then you know what happened
Notes to listen to so much of this show because
I start picking up on trends that might be settled
The Casual listener
Princeton's Alex always says that whatever he's trying to build a narrative about was actually the first thing Hitler did
This is my to leave the list
The conclusion that if this thing Alex is yelling about his allowed to stand then we're going to progress to the subsequent things that Hitler did
Here we see Alexander the first thing Hitler did was take away his enemies banking inability to do busy
That's because he
She's talking to
Mike Lindell who wants to
Complain about his bank account
However in
In the past when he's been talkin about grabbing narrative
He's very insistent that the first thing Hitler did was take the gun
This is really just a cheap trick Alex is using to try his imaginary enemies are using the same model
Hitler used
Regardless of what he's actually claiming they're doing
Yeah I mean it would be at that now and I don't know if this is
Possible
But if there was like a document
That Hitler had on like day one like an executive order
And then he just like
Laid out all of
You know like the whole Nazi plan
If you say that the first thing you did was ever
Sure you know
I also think that it's kind of missing the
Leaving the point regardless of what Hitler did first second or third
I do think
Kids missing the larger point
Alex might not care about that point
Yeah I have an apology
You should
Glendale
No I didn't realize it back
I didn't realize he's got the goods
We have what
Delete it
Show this is going to
Telling everybody when this comes out
Coming out this month
It is going to be a game-changer
But our big goal is
And all the states by the way
Electors
Any day now state
Could pull down their electors and then Trump will be president
What I'm sorry I should have taken Mike more seriously can't
I mean this guy
I think the thing about Mike
Is
She has to believe
That literally
Everyone around him is insane
Right
I think
Fast because there's no way that you can really believe in your mind that you have
Definitive proof
That Trump is still the president and be ignored even by Fox News and s*** well
You can look at that rationally and obviously I'm the insane some people are probably insane and then
Easier to rationalize if everyone else is in on it
Everyone else's
Paid off
Right now you can use that
Yourself
You could just say like
Soros is paying them to
Do not take me seriously or something imagine what it must be like
Like to be in a space where you're like
Definitive proof the biggest news in the history of the world
Reminder about how information he had would make a 90 Supreme Court case
Trump into power and it was so close
Winston Staffing
I appreciate his
Can-do spirit
It just keeps
It's going it really does
Boy it is annoying
So f******
Mike Mike's
Concerned about the midterm
Of course because there's
Other ways people
Can vote
In Utah
Officials are
Experimental pilot program in the gym 2020
Municipal
Counties in
Utah
You emailed in your boat or Utah
Senior vote
Did you hear that
Gmail
So Mike isn't being honest about these pilot program in Utah
You wouldn't text in or email in your vote
What they were exploring was a broadening of a system that uses blockchain to allow users to
Devote using their smartphones with an online platform
Do they make is describing it as reduct
Because he wants to belittle the idea to make it look like a clear plan to steal vote
The bill that was passed in late 2020 just allows municipalities quote
To choose to permit a voter to vote by electronic means
Approved by the municipalities election officer
Do you talk County Clerk auditor told Deseret News that they've been using this function for the past five
No problem
And that it is particularly useful in allowing overseas voters like enlisted person
Devote with less hat
Saugus bulshit
Upon Richard ComEd
The government said
Surprisingly this one actually works
No this is a good one
It does look
We're just as shocked as you that this work
Reached for comment the Utah government said Mike's going to flip out on this one
So in case you were
Concerned about me.
Tell him
The truth about
Mike being a sponsor
Enclosing
Both
Prodigy
Promo code Alex at my pillow.com
Hundreds of amazing slippers and
Sheetz
Amazing
Affiliate link
Promo code
I just so you know you want to live in the world
Where you don't have
That
Supposition right next to each other somebody being like
I know the politics and I'm going to get my president elected because everybody's cheating
And also
I sell towels and
Yeah well everything is a bit strange to just like zoom out
We have
A pillow magnet
Radio show promoting
Could still become president
Two years after the election
Like to a guy who has a affiliate program
With his pillow company
Conspiracists propaganda
Yeah yeah
I mean in a reasonable World everyone could just step back and be like well whatever that is is wrong
I've been wrestling with this I do think that
At a certain point
Obviously we can't really because we
Focus on
These kinds of worlds
Talk about this information
Honestly think
Maybe there should be a blanket like
People like Mike Lindell
People like Alex
People like Rodger
Don't even engage
Tweet about him
Whatever they're saying is not like
Bikes on here saying that
The he's got to be brought down
This big news is going to come out
Yeah we don't even
Don't even engage with
These claims
But engaging is
His kind of Point what are we doing
What are we doing
And we were playing
Clips from 2003 that could have been
Today
We got a little bit here at the end
Weave
Gotten through with the
Sticky
Ben R22
Rodger Stone
Glendale
Shelter
And now it was supposed to show talking a little bit about a news story that is
About Jen sake the White House spokesperson
Think about how Russia is going to pull a false flag
To get into Ukraine
Great Bob there was this conversation that went on
And
Alex
Okay
Let's go and get to this is a big deal
Video of
Admin says Russia is going to carry out a
False flag attack
On itself
Justify invading Ukraine
Staging false Flags
You absolutely do his entire early career
He believed that Putin did the apartment bombings
Volkswagen
Is very
Very clear about until he was
Food was great
At least according to
Most of Alex's career that is absolutely the case
Give misinterpretation though of what sake is that
Directions to
These Liars
Flags exist here she is
Information that indicates brushes
Reposition a group of operatives to conduct
There's this interesting dynamic balance is insisting that this is like
That made finally admitting at 12 Flags exist
No one has ever said that. Like don't exist
They just
Complain that Alex
Thinks everything is supposed to problem I'm experiencing right now
Is that
I know
That they have been Russia
False Flags
I know there been United States false Flags
I know that
Plenty of false flag
Right
The one time
The Alex
Could just be like
Just anything just anything other than well I don't think that there's accident this is actually happening
How dare you tell me that the government is false flagging
I'm mostly more interested though in
Pretending
People would say they didn't
No I bet I finally
That's not they never here
Very dumb
But not as dumb
Hazard last
Bit of
Highlights
I lied this morning
Stachys
Yes we got to peel that off real quick before we get out of here
VR video
The Sunday show
And it goes on from there
Sabotage
Humanity
This article is an editorial written by guy named Joe Mathews titled quote
California should abolish Parenthood in the name of echo
Alex is reporting this as a serious suggestion but if you taking the time to read the article he would have seen that it's obvious
Police at Tire
Joe brings up the inequalities in reaching for families and terms
Ability to bring up children
Mysolution
Making raising your own children illegal is simp
And while we wait for the legislation to pass we can act now
The rich and poor should trade kids
And homeowners might swap children with their homeless Neighbors
Now I recognize that some naysayers will dismiss such a policy is ghastly even totalitarian
But my proposal is quite modest
Effusion of
Traditional philosophy and today's most common political obsession
Him saying that his proposal is quite modest should be an immediate took off that he isn't being sincere
It's it's almost
Too on the nose
Although on the other hand even that isn't enough for people to not take it as satire
It's a little bit clunky if you're trying to behave like a literate
I literally cried
The author seems to be making is that the ultimate end result of many of the ideas that are pushed in the name of equality
It's like someone actually having the idea of universal orphan Hood
Really some fat up
Quote those critics any mind
Because they just can't see how our Relentless pursuit of equity
Mike Bertha Brave New World
Again
Anyway Alex not only doesn't understand the difference between an editorial and a news story
He also can't tell when articles are sincere or if their satire because he doesn't
Read any of the stuffy reports on
If all you know about the article here is that line you've reported like Alex does
Because he's stupid and lazy and
He's reporting a satirical article as is real
B o
Hellboy
The bomber man
This this is Nikki couldn't
Cram anymore references in there
I just I wouldn't might have been this is a little Swift
Jonathan I think we're having a little bit of a devil that you know like just
Just really hammered at home make the make the lines and
Acrostic to spell Eva
Say a secret message
Alongside that be great I have it
T-bill thx-1138
Solutely
So
Come to the end of this adventure and I think stupid
Sumter
Realteam real developments
Rodger
Apparently had covid
He's going to sue everybody
Michael and Dylan
As long as he has the money to do so
And you're going to need to provide it for her Thursday
Mike Lindell is go to prove within the next month
That
The election was stolen
Or
I need your money to do that when I got to go buy pet pillow you might lose that money could and also getting
Yeah
Alex
Control himself
Brian stelter
Pieces of evidence he provides about anything is either complete bulshit or
Satire article that he doesn't actually real or fake
Hopefully this time
Call mr. super Potato Head
I don't know
Look we'll be back I wanted to do more I wanted to cover a couple episodes on this episode but I just couldn't news
Too there's too much going on
And so we will we will check it
See how Alex is doing on Monday but
Tell them we've website
We do it's knowledge right.com
Also on Twitter
Yo I'm dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color