Alexandra Thurston color
We are like to sit around
Started very cheerleader
We are
A couple
Give me about
Nestle Milo today in honor of the hundred
57 books Milo yiannopoulos
Actress
Publix
Family weird weirdo
Energy drinks
It is a generic basketball player
Is chocolate flavored
The first kids are like cocoa processed with alkali
How is it was pretty good
This is this is best served
I agree with that recommendation
That's pretty good
Eric just like chocolate milk is exactly like
As much as I like it alot
What's going on
That is not a first and last name as far as I can
The first name
We appreciate it
What's the weather today
Thank you for joining up with the team
Please reach out
If I you would like to become a policy wonk
You may do so by going to a website
The sport the Showbox
And throwing up
A couple of Duckett
Clay Aiken may or may not
Send us an email now let's ride
Gmail.com
Aiken tip email address
Where do you know I just feel like the most random person that we
We could be obsessed with all
Some other American Idol people we could choose maybe adjusting
Whatever happened
From Justin to Kelly
I don't know
3 *
I worked at a movie theater still on excusable Behavior
We talked about it a
We're recording the new listeners. Explaining what the hell is going on at all.
Alex Jones
An out-of-context drop
From Alex Jones
Start to show off
The guest appearance by one of our favorites
Ms out-of-context drop
The man
SMS
The liar
Larry Nichols
Bubble show how to kill him for the microwave across the street
They wanted a shut up a screen not much on this Earth I know he would be shut up till somebody is not being
And shut up and you and I can
Only realized
Oops
I accidentally said that the government wants whatever they're saying to be out
Either either you killed her with a microwave.
You could just go to his house
Sherp
They have released that information order to taunt us letting us know that the rule of law no longer applies to
Anybody above us
Stature
Stability of a coming together
Happen is
And this is where damn cut
It's me off I start playing the playoffs music
Talk about Louis Farrakhan
He doesn't know that there is obviously the global to want him trying to start a race war cuz otherwise
Microwave gun
Not realizing mythological slips around perfectly on them
Them
Northstar raceworks
Anyway
Today Jordan
Part of my investigation
This thing is sprawling
To join up with
Team Trump
So far if you
Irish Times
24-hour
You got a full day ahead of you of figuring out what we've discovered
We're harder to binge
Just about everything else is no doubt about that
Be it to give you just like a brief recap what we found so far
Is that
Ignore the idea that
Trump is running for president
Then started talking wild s*** about him talking about how you knows
The Donald Trump
The frontman for a Consortium on the
East Coast he explicitly lays out mob connection
Talks about how
He's in bed with the clintons
Probably laundry
His track record is terrible
He's hooked up with dice
See people
And then out of nowhere
He's like
Stop talking s*** on Trump
The whole time he's enjoyed his rhetoric
Any thinks the things
The Trump think about how
Mexican immigrants should be coming into the country and what have you
He likes it
I hate Hillary
So much he's willing
To be like you
From
Ghetto what
June
So now we're into August
Yeah nothing is really evil his position is only become more
Hey keep saying things I like
Because Alex is crazy it so Donald Trump
Coming then
Very much so happy with him
Pushing that marriage
If you want the ramp off
Exactly
That seems to be his position is I love Rand Paul I want him to talk like.
Donald Trump
He's tried to get Jesse Ventura
Or at least be like not yet
He's also expressed
Support for
Ted Cruz
Support for two other Republican
What room is not running for president
He's all over the place
Trump is the last thing on his mind
Terms of
His horse
You know what it is
Is kind of good
You think about
Who else
Could have been
Like imagine
Authority
Terri Andrews
A lot of
Christian bulshit on top of
Will take I would rather have a
Ted Cruz will be able to get things done
Better Department
You know it would be
I think the machine would work
Work faster
No resistance from the gop's Trump is a bumbling f*** ingrown hair
Escape from l.a.
America
We lose all cows
I want to talk about it
We can talk about it
I don't talk about l.a.
Today's investigation will cover the period from
August 27th
Where we left off on August
6 last time
Just September 1st
And I don't want to put too fine a point on it
I think I've cracked
I think
At the end of this
Episode I will reveal a piece of information
I was unaware of
Have you were unaware of
And I've not heard anybody bring up
And I think it explains
Just about everything
Okay that is a big clay I'm being a little bit too over-the-top
Installment number six
You were like
I think I've got this one I know
That's the ever-evolving nature of his investigation
But this one
It gives motive
It gives opportunity
I think there's a lobster
Let me tell you
It's not as
Conspiratorial as
Let's say
You know
Some ideas of like Putin funneling money
Contacts
It's not according to Occam's razor
Much simpler
I think
The next investigation that I'm totally wrong
This is something pretty big
Alright let's do it
Start on August 27th
So Alex Jones
Isn't that a weird place
Because
Virginia shooting
It just happened
And in the meantime he's also being a
Tax by
A sheriff
And it becomes like
A really weird place where he's mad at top
But also love
Was cops
And he's in the he's in a very strange dancing
Space for a lot of this
It's time.
Yeah in the first clip you talkin about how
The Sheraton
Spokane
Did come out
And said
That a lot of armor
Vehicles that they have and heavy
Is
To fight against
Constitutional x-ray
Malicious
Which is what they're more scared of
Terrorism Muslim terrorism is going to Spokane
It doesn't seem like a hard target
And that is what he has to say
This is wrong and others picked it up
He first came out and said we're Liars it's not for us
Then we should know you're a liar so he said Alex Jones
Anybody
Something's about to happen
Really see this is a prime false flag zone
Common Sense tells me
USAA Insurance around real bad person
He speaks with a forked tongue
I may just go to accounting nearby when I go out there
Is jurisdiction with with the history of his deputies
This is a
I'm not sure I'm speculating there but
Keep that in mind his feelings on this Spokane Sheriff
Another guy
Spoiler alert it's Sheriff Clarke
Yeah
Alex loves
Why aren't these people in jail forever
I don't know
Edgewild
Skeleton
Still be in jail after he dies like hanging like in Amityville
Original stamart skeletons hanging
It's f****** hilarious days Alex
Oh you son of a b****
I'm coming
I'm coming to Spokane
And now he's like
I might not even go exist
Furlough
So I love that cuz
F****** coward when it really comes out
I wonder is there anything
More important now than death threats
Yeah it's still scary but yeah
Like if I say I didn't like the first episode of leftovers
Mima that it's okay
Listen up
You are making a death threat online
F****** at least go
Hold on
I don't agree with that at all I don't agree with you I don't like that your problem with
Death threats online is with their Idol
College
Columnist
University
Missouri
Actually inflammatory
Italy student newspaper
And I would get that threats a bit
Universal response was
F*** you
Nothing ever
Enough policy wonk
Get out of
I can't imagine
How many deaths
Call Zach Alex Jones finds out about us
I think he might have already but
Dynamite I'm not saying that
And some sort of like
Conceited narcissistic way I just think he's Teddy enough to have a Google alert
I would not be surprised
Some internet whatever is aware of
What we're doing
But the second that like his audience really become
Globalist
Connected
The Soros
Roblox
Heart out so I
Ton of evolution
Position on Trump
But I did notice of this
This clip
Indicating
Assault
In his
And I know the arguments both ways very well but I'm very much into the Second Amendment
You also have entertainment and you have
Out of the picture
Guns are used for recreational purposes
You know if you're sitting in that cabin someplace and you're not armed and somebody walks in with a gun
I'll tell you what I'd rather be in that cabin with a gun than not with a gun that out
He likes them a lot more cuz he started talking about.
Call Manny gloves
No actual evolution
Service position
It's just everything
He loves
For once
Restrain
Giants
A really good class
Jumps off every caller give some information about
Conspiracy
That's true I've been trying level sources
That ends up being the worst decision you've ever made
I really got a mole this one over for a couple
I think I actually I think I do know the answer to that question
Like does he know.
Does Alex
Chilenos
Like has he actually been told some
Something that makes
I think it might be a piece of that
Says different mob ties he's it
It's a Hatfield and McCoy situation
I think there may be a negotiation
Been going on behind
I think
This publicly being like I like him but I don't trust
Is his way of publicly being like
Sending a message
You need a bumper OfferUp
I think I realized why Alex was being a coward about the Paris
It's because he hadn't taken his super mail yet
Him taking a super male Vitality for the day
So he was a little cock
Little estrogen field
To take his medication
Amazon air and it's super fun cup
DeSoto
Hair on the TV / radio show
Survival Shield
Once a day
A little more
Out there and see how it works for you for years ago I started this
Hindsight 20/20
Stronger
I have what I just put water
Rock and roll
A secret
I can't reach it was somebody give me my methylcobalamin place to sorry
Running at the glass during the break
You know what
This is what I do at least once a day
Things get better around here
I really appreciate your help
I can't really
Someone ran off with that it's probably probably wandered off with it
Show me about Ramadan Mountain Water but
The old stomach
Write down the old jelly
With major keys
From the first time you drink whiskey
Tastes like Mama's milk but
I drink this
MorseLife
Yeah he needs to be careful about his Clockwork Orange reference
I don't think he understands why
This is the voice of a generation
3 minutes on air
Mixing
Wow
Are you cooking
Secret 1212
Methylcobalamin
As opposed to whatever
He argues that
B vitamin B12 can be derived from like
Cyanide or something else
And there's is from something else
I don't know I don't care
Anyway
I love it I love it when he really goes for it
Uneasy
I'm going to sell product but I refused
Thing about it going to
F****** overdosed
Super male vitality
Pennywise
What are the big missions that Alex is on
During this
. is
He needs
The shooter in Virginia
The 2 News
People live
Facebook
Open Twitter
He needs for that guy to be on meds
He needs to learn to be on cycle psychiatric medication
Because he's
Said that
He's already set
Call
No in order for his narrative to work
About like Shooters being can
Control
Because mental health Mental Health
That's a real issue
It's all about Mental Health
Now admittedly
Mental health program
Destroyed the welfare
On his on his
He was a Republican
Resident but
Mental Health
Play Alex's position is
At least
A third of what mental health
Practitioners adverb
Is brain control
So
You have a problem
Is really struggling because
Coming out that he was on
Psychiatric
Yeah and I might have actually
Contributed
Nuts
Let's find out
Tuesday
I want
To talk a little bit about her
Maybe
Shooting was fake
Uses a very weird maybe it was
David Knight
Go to Virginia
On the highway
Apparently across
The street from like the center where the shooting happened
It's talk it's a bad shot
Have no news
They have nothing
Alex is talking about
Maybe it's fake
First-person shooter shooting
That's cuter three times it looks like and she wants
They don't believe that they think it's fake
Aurora shooting estate
Wild boar I shot Elgato
Sometimes you shoot
What's 7 mil mag
Is blown in half
It looks like a first-person shooter map
Houses Beyond
We saw the night before
He's robbing the bank
Nope
But
Watching that video while you're talking
Play that again
He does he plays it again
I can't f***
Frozen bed
No
I'm not ready to say that this looks
The responses good
But the true comedy
Hesitate even to call accommodate
No it's such dark
But
2 days
Later on in this episode
There's a story about someone
A video of it
The playback
So he's willing to play all these
Propaganda Center for Medical progress videos
He's willing to
Repeatedly play this
Shooting
Video
Being sad
Frankie wants to kill some
I think so too big Alex
Is living vicariously through this video
As like a
I have always wanted
To do this kind
PCS it as helping
His goals which is causing strife
Fear and strife
This never would have happened
Protect
That argument is made
Of course it is
King Corso
Yeah if this person was doing their job doing a remote
For a local news just had a gun
They could have
Not Ben
Surprise
Yeah what
Anyway
I just
Wish they would understand
That I don't
Tear what
Solve the gunfire
As long as it's
If that means everybody gets
Cigun
Fine
Give everybody done
Prefer if it was socialized
Play the government administers
You know
Gives everybody
You got your Obama gun
It's just how can you not see houses
He's giving a remote
If you think
This lady is going to be doing her work
And then
Jesus guy and pulls out a gun on
Another
How much more Wild
I'm not sure I would now good God no
Next clip of Alex Jones talking about homeless people
Immigration
Messiah
And seen homeless Guatemalans catching fish
With a piece of monofilament
They're really sweet nice people
What is the government doing here everywhere else just opening everything up
It was
With a fire going over across the creek
Okay fine
These are countries Grizzly Adams where the 21st century
What's the reason
Because when it all unravels and melts down you know what storm
And they're mixing radical jihadist into this
Because the public doesn't have logic anymore
The public doesn't have logic anymore
We're going to bring a Guatemalan Grizzly Adams
That what don't you get the f****** public
If you don't have a lot of
Their industry
People they figured out how to
Great
I'm a little jealous of their lifestyle
Living at living out in the Woods fishing
I don't like to eat
Fish.
Define like a I don't know a mule
To kill everyone
Domino
I'd like to point out to that if you
Live in Chicago
You can go down
Lakeshore Drive
And you will see
White
African-American homeless people fishing
It's not
Some sort of weird immigrant thing
A lot of homeless people find food spam
How we treat our people
Alex
I'm glad you took the wrong lessons
Took the wrong lesson from
I tease
On the last episode
But I figured out where Alex Jones is
Chimera narrative
And now it is time to lay that out in the open
Alex Jones
Reveals
Text Cliff where he got hit
To all that fraud
Not a good source
We are joined by Steve weld.com
The 1st John 4 years ago
Dogs cockroaches mice
Wow
Alright
No
But you can't go to sleep quail.com
Ivory
Steve Quayle is a loon
Stevequayle.com
Steve Quayle
Bar none
One of the craziest people
I've ever encountered in
Our
Alright
Looked in Tulare
Write this guy is
Any tune
Like
You see my book of notes Here
Pretty detailed notes on the episodes
I have about
What's about to happen
What the next clips we're going to listen to is
Steve Quayle is
Disguise
Okay and he doesn't get into this
But
You know what
Website
Steve Quayle has his own gold sale operation
All right all these dudes
I have that sort of Link
Sell gold
That's what you do
Steve Quayle
At least is
Kind of in
Innocence
But his insanity
Not
I mean
Racially problematic beliefs
He also believes it like
We can encounter anybody
No
He believes that Nazis survived World War II and have a base
The ice of the polar caps
T.i.
Out there
We when we talked about it last on the show
I'm not sure I think he probably does
The last time we talked about it
Because Alex Jones was talking about how he
He's basically a prophet
And all this predict
Come true
Does not true at all that's absolutely absurd
He's also written a ton of books
About how I
The Giants
A real not Monica Sports
Biblical giant
A real and that the government
I'm just trying to cover up them
Author history
Destroying the bones of Giants have private rooms of Museum stuff like that
A perverse race
Madness I like that the government is
Is trying to hide them but they're still like
Government
Episode
Like there's something about there's Indiana Jones
Building Museum
Anyway I
Here is
3 clip
Steve Quayle
Samsung
On Alex's show
And if you listen to these clips
And consider that this is the guy
Who helped Alex Jones baby fetuses are being
Call zlateva today
This is our profit
What is this it's like a movie
It's like we got possessed or something
I don't like it
They going to kill people
Re-education Camp, I apologize for
For 5 minutes
What do you say to that who are the players what is the end game you were saying it's spiritual
Spiritual because you know what I've written about Stargates and by the way
I just want to tell people if it's important what we're talkin about Alex
Subscription you can download downloader.
DVD true Legends and why this is critical okay
Is it's really critical for people to understand that and one of his Revelations of that I've B
Amazing 90 minutes we actually believe now that
Through some pretty amazing genius-level mathematicians and Tim alberino being down with the film crew
Believe we have found the Fallen Angels linguistic
People go on and it's going to be important let me tell you why this is important
Because of spiritual nature of the battle when the sickness come out
10 years ago about this
Dr. Shi and Unit 731
Tried for war crimes for the life of vivisections on human beings by the way.
For the Chinese one the main reasons the Chinese
Hate the Japanese so much the atrocities under Japan we're just
Over to the experimenters
The American citizens are
Call of Duty if you want baby parts and all the lists of
Other food companies everything you can understand something has changed at a genetic level
I want to so isolated and so non-human. All of the normal god-given qualities of
Passion of love understanding want that okay they want a totalitarian
United States what was the name of the survey that you and I broke on there
I sent you an email we talked about another the one that showed the population of America taken out 80 90 million
Expanding on this
Dodge swinger
CC creations
Yes they are and the reason for that
The owner of the Magnificent
Some things that men
In their honor of God look at this
We could go no prayer in school now they kicked God out of everything that universities which most even Christian Center
We got it in
What is 731
Some Chinese military group or something like that
Working with Doctor you
I don't know I don't care
It doesn't mean anyhow
I'll look it up
Eating baby parts
Changes us at the genetic level
Yeah it's like a carrot
Did I eat carrot
Makes you healthy
I mean
Genetic level
Unit 731
The colvard biological and
Chemical warfare research and development
Unit of the Imperial Japanese
Chinese Army undertook lethal
Experimentation
During the second
Sino-japanese
Is war
Of World War
Alright believe everything you said there was responsible for some of the most
Notorious war crimes carried out by the
Japanese
Unit 731 was based
Did the Ping Fang
District of Harbor
Largest city in The Jeffy
Estate of
Andrew Cuomo
Now
In Northeast
The linguist
Well where else would you
Southeast China
Don't play this game I don't want to play this game
I love it I don't want to play this game
Do you know there is some piece of real-world stuff that I haven't looked into
And that's being pretty
Text I've been Skype
Just cuz I don't know one thing about this
Who cares
We're practicing the argument that we may have with
Well you didn't know about Unit 731
You don't know about Giants
How I'll handle that argument
Here's what I'll do
I'm going to punt on units
Can have it
Let's talk about more important issues
Like the Linguistics of angels
What do you think
What
In South America
Is going to discover
At the very least
Look for
The language of fall
I don't know man
It's wild stuff
Hey but it's you know
It's like
It's this idea I think that
I'd attend Lovecraft
Throughout like this idea of people getting in over their heads
Like a lot of the protagonist
The Lovecraft stories are like
Antiquarians is like
Just a researchers are professors
Cuz everybody is basically molded on Lovecraft
Himself interested in
Old-timey stuff
And maybe you'd like to read and write
I accidentally mixed up with Kong
Or
Yog-sothoth off
Because the only
Santa's looking
And so I think that that's
Kind of
Spiritually I don't think he's ripping off of crap but I think that's
This mathematician was
I don't know notice a notoriously field
Got to go out there in the field and find new numbers
So look
Unit 731 might've done some villainous ship
But there's a
In the world
Taking into consideration
Supernatural
On that whole statement obviously The Illuminati's going to say we were seeded by aliens
The Vatican is getting ready to baptize aliens
That's not what
Why does the Vatican
Get ready
Tobacco
Do they are they
Different equipment
I remember hearing something about that
Just like a hypothetical conversation that it was like
Like if we do eventually meet Aliens
Do we would be open to that
Terrible
The first thing that they think of with aliens
How do we make them cats Larry save their souls
What you got
Well I differ from all those guys is this
Easy for them to
The Anunnaki name them whatever the gods I've actually dependa gonz calls I think
Sumerian gods all those things are fallen angels masquerading as something
You know somebody from the planet and terrorists in order to deceive in order
Perpetrated
Populated the planet and even all the mesoamericans recorded Native Americans work
Court
Play the bones why do they hide all the
Reuters I'm not painting yet but I will obviously be coming soon sometime
It's the greatest Snowman
Who created the alien
We're seeing the pope show up on the 23rd
September has done an amazing job of you know basically
Writing out at the vatican's on
Idea can you have an alien save
Cancel that is no
Because Jesus didn't die for the angels that since he died for mankind Jesus
Around
Book of Revelation
Come down
Knowing he has but a short time
People can't separate the wrath of God which is at the end of the tribulation
What about the
Eminem
Music by here
Oh man
I love I love how
If they're so close
These people are so stupid but they're so close like
Aliens created people will who created
Well who created
The laws first met
It's Turtles all the way down my friend
You know just like Larry Nichols made that logical
Slip up at the beginning of the episode
Steve mehdi identical
In terms of not recognizing what is words in
Imply
Just crazy
Basically ripping off
Snow crash
You know what else
Express
Zacharias
Pitchin Road about
Okay I don't know
They want I'll deal with Zack
Do you know him well enough
The Columns Akai do a couple of his books
All right along with Erich von daniken
Are the two guys
Could say are the most responsible for the ancient alien
Phenomenon
Okay if the TV show a very based on a lot of his research
I believe Giorgio Tsoukalos
The guy with the crazy hair on that show
Zecharia sitchin
He wrote the book called The Tenth Planet
Is a series of seven books
I read the first two disciples
Garbage
I basically just missed translates a bunch of old Sumerian texts
Do
Make the argument that oil and Anki
R2 alien gods
That existed on our planet
They created Humanity as a
The slave race in order to mine gold for them
Adara salon
Is gold or something like that
In order to fix
The environment of their planet
Something along those lines
Anyway
They come back periodically because
There on planet
Or as
People call that Naboo right that has a elliptical orbit
That's why we got X-Men
Elliptical orbit goes around much longer scale
We are aware of
That way
We've had telescopes
Outside of our range
It's has been
It's been too far.
There's a good possibility
Ability there is a
It's not that
I'm pretty sure
The argument was actually on
One of the big
Over
Flying fish
That that was when Planet X
Was going to come back
Sumerian gods
Which had become since the last time they won
I mean
Translate
Erich von daniken
Zecharia sitchin
The scholars are not they're not
Accurate there
They are not even accurate in their name
Those are not real
I like
I like him too but that
Doesn't get more made of maggots
Come on man
He's making
Do that stuff
You know all of the
All the ancient alien theories had tons
Giants
And stuff like that
And so like
Alex is allowing a guy who'd believe this stuff based on
Wild interpretation of the Bible
To be on his show and his
Response to everything
It's so it's so cowardly
Even
Even fallen angels
But I didn't know there were any actual
Fallen one
I believe
Look up know everything about the Bible but as I work all day
Search about angels
They're not supposed to f*** ladies and they came down and they sucked lady
Outlook
Fallen angels in the Bible
I don't believe there are
Who cares
Good point very good point
I think that I'm being honest
Unfair about
Steve Quayle
We could be being unfair to about believes in flight
I thank you gentlemen
I am a question to Steve is prompted by your discussion he had to
George Noory
Earlier this year
Panda Express
Steve
Are you still
Expecting some sort of
Planet X appearance event
Early next year
Well I actually did
I think we're
Senior
We're experiencing the gravitational
The climatic in the volcano City on there's all kinds of
Strikers and gravitational pressures and other pressures
Being placed on there so yeah I think you're seeing it
Alright
Planet X is already
Gravitational pressure volcano
Ain't good
No brains
Cockroaches
You do not have a good source
So probably not
I think this might be time
Time for that narrative
Creepypasta
Possible who would you believe
If they were telling me that they were actually like what
What level of credulity do you have to have
Like if Stephen Hawking
Do you know what
When I was working with the government
We put a
I would say
My man
I don't believe you
I think that
Until someone
Where to
Fully layout
How's that work
Write the point
That I'm a hangout with cockroach
I don't think I'm going to
If you have cockroaches
And Noah
I got nothing in common with a cockroach have nothing in common with a baby
Middle-aged cockroach
Sure
I'm in hangout with that guy
Kind of tragic
Cuz the Cockroaches
They're homeless real
Yeah there are there fish
Cockroaches
These Guatemalans have teamed up with these cockroaches in power
Calvary August
August 28th
And all this episode we got
The most weird stuff
Little bit of weirdness
The very bad admission
I will get to in a second
Begin
Start
Making a pretty
Uncharacteristic
Praise
Kind of statement
A former world leader
And yes it's true the globalist went into every country to try to stabilize you just say what you want about South Africa under apartheid
What is socialism
Asthma
Almost all of the countries money
College
Real jobs highways aquifers jet aircraft jobs
It's gone
Because he was a cocky peacock
Overall compared to wanted to build up Africa
Old-fashioned prosperity
There it is socialism don't work is a philosopher
Resources
Old days gold
Oil and water
Aquaphor
You just given that oil
You know why Alex supports
Because he was trying
To implement
What currency was trying to get off the
The petrodollar
Kill them
And also like
Of course he hates
The central bank
Wreck
All of qaddafi's like
Gassing is people s*** like that
Does believe in
It's very scary to me records
Just go back to your Google Hangout
Deal with the United States military
Super weird but it does illustrate what is priorities
Games are for him
Prosperity
Trouble at all.
Next clip
A little bit
Discussion of trump
Episode Alex Jones I think it started
To show some crack
Grandpa
Starting to resent
And Paul not listening
Two months now he's been on the air
I like
You're the best
But you need
To start being a dick
You need to start being at like attacking
Attacking Hillary you need to do the
Much harder
On immigration
To be embarrassing in public because
Yeah
You're not getting on board
Right starting to have that
Nimaway from Rand Paul is his own Petty resentment
And I
Chimeras
I want to illustrate what's happening with the collapsing borders and where
Your phone calls
Forget to go there
Criticize rampaul
Tried to be friendly about it
I can't find a
I want to believe
He's got a checkered past and so
You got to really have some reservations
I mean we can see it
Starting I feel like
Starting to drift
Rand Paul butt
The same time every time he says
He does not trust
Trump still
So there we are
How many weeks are we on with
Like he's constantly ever
Talking about Trump
Like nobody at this point of course no but
We could stop talking
One of the big problem
We got billions of dollars in free
Like how
How many times
Can you say I love by don't trust
Yeah it's over and over and over again
Doctor house
Dr. Cudi type situation
Title of house
Interview with Peter Schiff
My talk a lot about how you got a bike
He also explained.
Buy property in Singapore
I really looking to buy property
Looking for property Market
So I've I've done a little bit of looking at
Peter Schiff
You've lost a lot of people a ton of money
I'm not in it for the short game
Yeah sure
We're down right now
Especially when you're the son of someone who
Didn't pay taxes
On billions of dollars
Got a lot of people because of it
Stepped on and also indicate
Weird
Allegiances in terms of who he's pulling for in the 20s
16 election
Liquor has less baggage
Gets to the blue-collar workers and people
But
Hillary is a woman
And really is a trump card
Carly fiorina she's been on your show
What is I mean if you had her against Hillary I mean
You take away the woman advantage
And now you know it's going to be a woman president a matter who you vote for
And I think
Arena
Yeah I think Carly
Productive
If everything is just based on capitalism
Fremont
Is essentially endorse half the field
Carly fiorina fall
Hunza people he saying like
Everybody but Jeb Bush
Yeah
F*** you to Jeb Bush
This weird
Rockies game
What's going on doing that to any of these other candidates
That's true
Behaving very weird lie down on one side of the other with every everybody
I hate you
No it's super f***** up
Chris Christie is a fat piece of s***
The globalists whatevs
0 reservations in fully endorsing
Too much further like
I hate feelings about the candidate
Who's next
He doesn't have any responsibility for this
Situations that happened
In the third world
Then
He takes it but
Opposition
So we can stop there
And it leads to another position
Each of them are not great
But together they're very bad
So here we go enjoy this
Is delightful control
Just want to risk everything
Police themselves are
Places to fight the policies
Schizophrenic
But I have no responsibility when somebody somebody in
Nicaragua or somebody in
Want to have seven kids
Define culture
Run-of-the-mill basic flavors
I don't want you telling me what to do
Because
Average
It's
Gorgeous
Click
Alex wants to f***
What is
What's on power rack
Thinking of racism
Not sure if it's
What is that Eve
I don't know
Women
Now they're only amazing
There's there's no whistles what is happening
What I don't know what that's doing on his ship
YouTube
I think it's his internalization he's project morning
Like
What color of women
Now we know
Close it up
Some of the issues that we should deal with
If you were an actual show the guide
Bring up in
I wanted
Interesting and important
A lot of the
Stabilisation in third world
Population
Has benefited greatly in a civilization
Sort of
Often has exploited and
You could say that you have some responsibility
Population
You're super again
Contraception
Those sort of educational reproductive education
Whether it be in this country or other country
So what are you shut the fuk up people in third world countries having seven kids
Wonder if they have access to healthcare maybe it wouldn't be
Alex
Stop f******
That's one word
Like who he's attracted to is
Such
Zane guilt
Like it is
She always does
Whatever he seems like
So you're saying that
I don't think it's racist necessarily to be attracted to someone of your own race
I think it's races
Has to be exclusively attracted
People of any race
Like when you finish I there's a lot of people fetishize like Asian women
I think there's a lot of people
Lenny population
And I think that's wrong cuz you're treating somebody as a thing as opposed to a person
Yeah I don't see that
I don't think that that
At the same time
Recognizing
Often
Statistically
Someone is one of race ends up dating someone also erase a
That's not racist
Do Alex Jones being like primarily
Just Proxima
Yeah
Chicago is just around the same
And it's cultural to
That's absurd
The things that
I refuse to answer that question.
Whatever
Is very
Especially the wolf whistle
Insanely
It's it's pudding
Himself in the position
Like all that matters is he's at
Doesn't matter of anybody else's
Distracted
He's the one who he's the one who does the is the Arbiter of value
Using outright misogyny in order to dodge racism
Very strange
I'm so fascinated by these things that he embodies
It doesn't even realize
Like you do
Never gave a second
Thought to that
No
That was
Fuct
Play my prey
SMS
Like he seems
To be a
Product
The product of his environment but the distillation of his
Sure
Is absorbed by
A lot of people
Where he grew up
Texas is
AR
Most
You name it
Is Olive
These things that are ingrained in
Do you just pee
Purely by
Is osmosis
He doesn't even necessarily need to
Oh this is how you
Women because
It's just
They are
Bizarre ideas about chivalry
Infantilized
And because of his
Shutter lag
Self-awareness
To him
Is that your child
His
Every
Anyway let's move on to this next clip
Alex Jones
Explain
One of the negative outcomes of immigration
Babies Rock
North African town
Thousand people in 2000
They would not lovingly take care of them
Images
I come in your house
Eraser erasers I mean certain point
That will make people go
Yikes
That'll make people go Hitler Hitler
That was actually
It was it was between Breaking Bad and go Hitler
You do you know the the
The presumption in that
Sentence is that Hillary
Just had
Schleich I've had enough
That's what made him break
That was as opposed to
Just being hateful from the jump
Scapegoating
Beat
The constant
Rewriting of Hitler's motivation
To just justify whatever it is
If you want to say
Is banana
Especially when
He may
Entirely believe with someone who believes that Nazis still have under-eye spaces
At the polar caps
Well if you go to any North Africa
You might wander upon Hitler
That's how we got there
Also I told you earlier than Alex Jones on this August 28th episode makes a startling admission
And here it is
I think this
Is deeply problematic
And Alex might not even recognize what do you think
Transgendered lives matter
Who won the Democrats
Sticker 6 months ago
I don't care I just want to
I want have a limited run of Hillary Clinton for prison t-shirts
Okay
Hillary for prison
Yeah he stole intellectual property from someone else
Another one
Profit off of it
Limited run
It's one of those things
He's just getting the word he's sold is made
So much money on those shirt
It's absurd that is
Would like that might be the admission of a crime
I don't know who owns
I don't know who made those bumper stickers
But it is bumper sticker
Email us I'll send you this clip please do Alex Jones
Also the other day
From prison
They're talking about the private prison
Blurred Hillary
I'm not a hundred percent sure but I've listened to his number of times I believe in what they're saying
Is Hillary divest
From prison
She has
Taking money from the private private
Prison industry
Super f***** up I believe
Kanzashi you slave
Problematic
I think that Alex Jones
He's being a little bit fast and loose with this trying to
Pretend that these
American Transit
Youth are on the same
The reality
Celery
Stop
Incarcerating
Alex Jones
Do you want to talk about that issue all that much
Oh yeah
I don't know I don't hear it I don't hear it come up much
What's August 30th
You're done with the 28th that was a Friday
On Saturday when I come back Sunday
Even god Ra
Sundays
Balloons
Is going to be pushing
The race war has already
It's already
Dip
What is a race
Swarm
That music is really loud
Yeah music
Even within his like
These dumb white and black
Alright
Congratulations
You should really
Turn the music up more
Race war is a
Camp of
Brainwashed
Yes
Start at the beginning
The Triumph he wants white start killing black
Blackstar killing whites
Media doesn't report on the fact that black people are killing white people
I don't know
So that it's not black people and white people lining up
Have to kill each other
Black people
As his brothers
Yeah
So I mentioned earlier Alex Jones
Endorses someone
For president who's not running
You just doesn't
Infer why
There is a fully justifiable resentment
It's not brainwashing it's like I'm totally on board
Murdering sits on the white people is like guys
Come on it's time
Come on do it
It's a remarkable
Restraint a very admirable
Quite frankly
But
Just say he's already said
Someone else
Broadcast worldwide
Infowars.com
That says it all national
At Horseshoe guest of this broadcast as well.
Educated inform
Code word
I'm out of course is Sheriff David Clarke
Hour-long speeches
Online
I've seen the speeches and he just really
You know what he also has got he's got dead people in a
Is jails
Yeah
I'm not using cards or a teleprompter
It is so important
Alex Jones
People on the right
It's a propaganda point.
They get to make
We don't use teleprompters
We're just real
Yeah there's there's a feigned authenticity in that
That they used
To attack people who have scripted speeches as like I know you're fake
You idiot Spence
Time thinking about what you want to say
What is wrong with you
I'm being real
Dumbshit pops out of your mouth
Absolutely works
Stand up
Also these people who you think aren't
Scripting things
Are just people who are good at making
It seem like they're not
They're not giving
Off-the-cuff speeches
In the same way that a good stand-up comedian it seems like they're saying something for the first time
And that is the illusion
Right
These people I'm sure
Speeches the chair Park is given
I'm sure they're the same thing
Even even in here
Crazy
For Sheriff Clarke
Dads
White coat
What year was always been used to imply that
That that that
Prizing thing
For a black pearl
Bigotry of diminished expectations
Very guilty
I've often
Talked about
How I believe that Alex Jones
Super into white identity
Stop
Maybe
Shuffle on white nationalist
Did not realize
Right
Two clips are going to justify my position a little bit
Call prisonculture
Culture is fusion with a bunch of Misfits
Sheriff Clarke and then I'm going to walk through all this
Going on in Austin
That's another example
Look up real loud
Local government doesn't want
Yeah I just
I don't want to say I love it
Because I don't
But the. Just a quote
I have tons of videos of black people beating up white people
What else
Come on
Like
Beating up a white lady outside like a 7-Eleven
All of these things
There's Justice
Vacations but there's more going on than just
Random Acts
Violence
Provide the knowledge fight position with
Which is toxic
Crap I don't know
I don't know
If you want to get
Scared and scare your audience
Based on
Weird video game stuff all over again
It's a good game to play
You scare people you can make money
But at the same time what you're doing is in
Incredible Disturbed
Sprite you're just making white people
Scared of life
If you don't have it
Amplified
Racist form of what
Local news is done
Forever
Rainbow party
Stuff is just that
That's cool
That's just cool school
This stuff is like it really is a preemptive Justice
Application for when white people
Who killed black people
So he can justify
Yeah
It's really it's really bad
We've been oppressed by black
People for too long
I mean that PC argument is sort of along the same line by these minority groups that are legitimately
Jesus Christ really the thought process
Because what they're doing is they're trying to change speech
To change the way we do
Define things at that point they'll be able to get our guns
That's basically
It's it's caca
So I feel like I've been like a little unfair
As hard on myself
As possible in terms of
Not making
10 claims about Alex
I can't really back up
Really afraid of white Jenna
He's into those narratives
Was a little bit like
It's not really fair to me I didn't really talk about that
He uses some of the similar terms
But here I was wrong
To judge myself
Over more of what's Happening where
The Country Inn
White people
The fairgrounds
Black females
Will just come up and beat them in their life
Neighborhood
You're white
Eminem TV show
A report coming up
It's impossible
People vary within groups
About average
It is so wild country girl
I can't even say the n word
Just it inherently exist
This is
A push and a move
To genocide
Any type of white Western culture
Type of white
Speed later
Because the globalist want to kill everybody
But it seems to be
Incredibly past
About the first part
Nothing
People are this
It's some sort of weird kind of Jedi Mind
That he's pulling off for his list
It's like listen people are all the same
Black people are beating up white
All the time all over the place
Black males and black females are attacking women alone
Even uses chillary in terms of nights
Women never really know what he's talking about
Yeah it's it is
And
You know what a weirdo because he uses that you shouldn't be in the
Neighborhood
Has been used
Murder
Yeah
Other one
The other way around
Is one of the most
Her if we don't like your kind around here is it historically White
Fred's
Actually I'm a little bit ashamed little while to formulate
One of the things
Things that this serves
This sort of
Alex Jones.
All times
Examples throughout
Speech
Feed into
What are you talkin about
You know Muslims
Wanting to implement Sharia law
Stupid and secretly Satanist
Black people are beating up white
People in droves
What do you doing is he
He's teaching his audience
To be afraid of strangers
He's teaching his audience to
Further insulate them
Themselves
Because these black people that you see on the street you don't know who they are
Just out of nowhere punch you
Write these Muslims might be Taurus
These other white people that use if you don't actually know them they might
We're trying to
Help the globalist
Which is pretty much he's doing Charles Manson he's doing a ridiculous fear of string
If you buy into him
If you buy into what he's saying
So much occult
Absolutely
Isolate isolate
People and reinforce their beliefs
And for the worst and not just that but
You are somebody
Because your isolate
Surrounded by other
I think
Pressure on YouTube
Get back in line
What are you going globalist
Play that
That's how you kind of
Get that caught lie
Mentality that group
To really take over
Yeah
Totally
You like that narrative is the one that
Is is the reason that they
Constantly afraid of that race
That push them closer and closer to me
The only thing that's missing from Alex's I calling is
Group family
They are in an army that's what I like
That's not
The words
So Jordan you know that I'm trying to figure out where Alex Jones
Narratives begin
I've heard
City sights
And found that they did not say what
Example on this episode
The bit about Aldous Huxley
Aldous Huxley
Speech that he gave
The 19th
B2
And I'll just let Alex speak his
We're going to have a high-tech
Pharmakeia where we drugged you and dumb you down
An end sexual activity
And make you asexual
And then basically face humans out entirely and go to machines
His brother
Which actually runs the UN he was
Director-general of UNESCO
I don't care my brother runs
Ice cream shop
I'm not in big ice cream
You know I don't know
Anyway
This is Alex Jones has been into
Do for quite a while
He made a documentary years back called
Endgame
From Huxley
And all I owe him
Let's just listen to this clip from Alex Jones documentary
Shortly before his death
British best selling book
This entire documentary to I should
Today is
Fascinating
Because visually there's not much for him
As though you just played weird images of like brain control
Images of people being fingerprinted
Associate things with things
Really
Manipulative
I am diarrhea
Caterpillar Brave New World
We said another catapult
Respectful
George Orwell's book 1984
The
Scientific
Will be probably
Eventually
So there's a little bit more this time but I wanted to cut in here because Alex's
Is cutting up the speech like crazy
Very different parts
It's a 45
It's a 45-minute lecture that he gives
Ultimate Revolution you can find it on YouTube
The Charming order
The thing that's important is Alex Jones's argument
Aldous Huxley has admitted
He is a part of the
Is Henry
On the use of the word we
In that clip right there
Developing
It's like that from a different person
He's clearly talking about there just being a
Trend in humanity
Universal we absolutely
Me and my me and my Global is PALS over
Presenting this lecture
Let's finish the clip
And then I'll explain what the lecture is about
Automatically disprove his earlier statement
Like the first line where you saying that
The parable of
Brave New World
Maybe he has a little bit of
Personal self in
Is more right
Orwell's book and I'll get to
Happy food
Decent stand
Angie
Refinement
This was one of the same side
There's
Hey you
I think it's my duty to inform you that
Spooky background music
Great Lakes
Ominous music behind
Hopefully we are
Buccaneers
For about 45
Music behind me
May I bring my own
I'm going to be in the entire time
So
Speech
How old is it 1984
Fortune
Right up top
This is something that Alex big cut-out cuz it's in that
It's connected
Do the stuff he was discussing
At the beginning
Terrorism will not be an issue in the
He's the reason the 1984 is not
Compelling model for him
If he argues that it's written in
In a time where terrorism is in the public conscience
But because he had written
A Brave New World
Terrorism wasn't a hot-button issue for the world
Because that consideration wasn't
And everyone mine
And everyone's blinded by terrorism
A1984
Control state
Is so predicated on that
Yeah but it's flawed
Which is a prediction is built entirely around
Total Wine
That we
We are in
Beijing in production
Probably right about the pharmacological
.
Lot of people
Melanson
In the speech he goes on to
Start about how like
That sort of thing
What we know now
About pharmacological
1 cups
But you could take multiple substances what are you doing drugs if your knots
Possible
It does lead the audience
Is his version of thing
And in the speech explicitly says
That one substance
Not possible
Beach his mainardi
The ultimate
What are you getting at is
History there been a bunch of revolution
Agricultural Revolution
Innovation these sorts of things
King about
About whenever Humanity made one
Yes from
To another yeah
The ultimate life
Revolution
Is that all the password
The all the past Revolution
If you look at them
Agriculture
Mechanization
Do you sort of revolution
We're external Revolution
Human
But we're not really revolutions
The humans
They were you know we learn how to farm
And therefore our lives changed the revolution
Our Behavior adapt
Sing to an external thing that we've created
This new Revolution that he's talking about
Humanity itself
Can affect
Its own mind body
Revolution would be
Internal and that at that point there would be no need for other revelers
Right
All he would jerk off to
Yeah probably
Important
We were
We were we were talking about this a little bit last night
We were Tilton
Two beers
A wanted man
Points
Of his
Argument is
If you look at the study
There is a
Subsection to population
Percent
Is almost impossible to
Similar L 20% that are very suggestible
How to be hypnotized
Super easily
Sixty percent of the population
Somewhere in the middle
Placebo effect
20% of people report
Placebo
Medication
20% of people
Will not
Respond to that and 6
People that or somewhere in the middle
So
She is warning
More than any
About the fact
That there are a large
Group
Of our population
That are incredibly easily suggestible
And could be a
Voided by a demagogue
No
That's alarm is not
You very accurately describes
How if someone were to
Utilize
Some brain control technique
Expletive been developed
Some sort of propaganda techniques
But Alex has a lot
You could get
A very
Portion of that 20% of
Super easily
Suggestible people
To get on your side
And that could
Swing the entire political landscape
And even and when they are on your side
Actively
Against their own
He is incredibly prescient on that
Yeah I've been all that other stuff about the
The future scientific
Ditto
Dictatorship
Please that
Use as a negative example of what could happen if charismatic leaders
To wish ill
Coming to power he phrases it specifically as a negative thing
It's something that we should be worried
You know this 20%
Suggestible people help you
You swing the political lamb
Landscape over to this demagogue leader
This person who wishes to be a dictator
They're really smart
That they'll end up doing
He is trying to implement
These pharmacological means to make you happy in your
Make you happy within your bondage
Bratz
He's not saying
I'm in with them
And we're doing this
Yeah he's saying it is like this is a really negative outcome that could happen
At these are part of
The pieces
Make it
So I correct
Almost immediately because the cultural revolution
Yeah but he was wrong about the terror
So anyway
The reason that I made a big deal out of it
This is because
Every time Alex has like a foundational piece
Says his
Worldview with
Really important to knock it out
Because it's always a lie or
Are we can see right there in the clipse we play
Him literally editing
Collectively
The audio of that out
Clarksville Speedway
You can go listen to the full thing
If you want on YouTube like I said I think he's a great orator there's a couple of moments that are genuinely funny
He's a Charming guy
I don't necessarily agree with everything
He was about
I think that if you look at his biography he's kind of an a******
Yeah
Miami
Journey to the End of the Night by El estaline I think it's a great book
He was an anti-semite I don't know what to do
They were very
Take razors beside there also
Shity
Alex Jones
You are lying about Aldous Huxley
Congratulations
I'm proud of you later not on this episode but
It's always
Complained about
Most
That he does
Take me out of context
I never do that to Megyn Kelly
F*** you
Yeah your entire reality is based on that
I'm certain if we
Entire breakdown of
Endgame where The Obama Deception
One of his documentaries
And I guarantee if we start picking up
Piece by piece of Park
Will find almost every piece of evidence
Is selectively added or taken out of
Yeah so if you want
Please don't donate cuz that's gonna work
Documentaries like to
Anyway
August
30th to get through
Before we get to the big
The big enchilada
Discusses his audio
Exercise and the personal
We reach 20 million people
Post office shows
Which I've been doing exponential
Exposition
The New World Order Engineers do not like me
And the responsibilities I've got
Is just
Talk to a lot of things that have been posted anonymously on message boards and stuff
The Illuminati
The truth to you before they do it
It comes from like
Anonymous posts on message boards of people claiming to be Illuminati Insiders
And stuff like that
Really long question-and-answer session really big piece
Of this
Internet mythology about the Illuminati
Did they use this thing called lesser Magic
Where they reveal what they're going to do to you before you do it so you have free will to try and
Them
It's nonsense it's absolute bulshit
Has no basis
Isn't anything
If you want that to be
Your burden
Proof
You are failing
Not good
I do like that
The truth in that he
He did double his audience
Exponentially
Really but he is telling us now that it's about 4
Predictive groundwork for his
Now I have 40 million Arthur stereo
This thing I want to take away from that is I don't believe you
18 million listen
At this point
But the idea that he would go from 8
18 to 40 million listeners
In two years
Is unfair
There is literally no way that
That kind of growth happen
Without
Him becoming one of the biggest
Plucking stars in the world
Like he would be mobbed everywhere
People would be
Camping outside his Studio
Yeah absolutely I was trying to look up like a ratings
TruTV shows
Diane like
You would be the most popular thing in the
Of course
Outside of people making memes
Clowning on him
I don't think that's
So he is just
It's just a lie
Does Mexico have to do with why the globalist
Super into immigration
Flooding with left of Western Europe
Sliding glass of America
With a political point
Every single argument order
In the west doesn't capitulate
And give them what they want
Corner
We given the terrorism we roll over
We know you're playing you Despicable Me
Core people
Behind the scenes
We're facing
Nope
Hardcore
They're killing each other salute
You don't like people
Right right
Do you understand what are you saying they're about
The globalist plan
That he can
Conceives of his head
They're paying people
Probably
Printing is VI goodies
Do you like medicine Medicaid
And if they don't
Love the Patriots.
To the
Right which is
Of the goals
You have millions of people ready to write in every major city
If all you want out of that is like
Hey come on guys
Let's use trans
Instead of tranny
You might want to shoot higher
Yeah
Seems to me like a pick your battles
Situation
Possibly
That goes back to the being afraid of strangers
Narrative
These people are paid to basically be there as a warning to us
We don't go along with it they're going
You step out of line they're going to destroy all major
Tri-Cities right
You can say
They are going to try and kill everything they are going to kill every cop
On every
Beyond Dearest
Yeah course
Gray fighting people
What your your priming your audience
It's for the moment something goes wrong
That's the signal
It's time for you guys
People preemptively to Future violence
Responsible
Yeah
Next caller next caller
Here is some good evidence
Because I legitimately sucking huge racist caller calls in
Alex Jones
It's cool with it
Great I Am
He doesn't push back
At all
Call
Summarizes guy calls in
We would probably
Hang up on him push back
The because Alex
Welcomes him on the show
Reinforces what he saying
Ura
Pocket racers
Yeah that's not me using Code words
To try and like take away his free-speech accurately assessing his behavior it like with
The former Grand Dragon
Right
Information
Advance
I'm supposed
To be against
This guy cuz this guy is right
Unlike that
This color
Has no baggage
Associated with
Even pretend that he's
He can just jump in
Happily for calling what's your view on all this
So much that I want to say that where me and my brother are really really
Hardcore supporters are showing pointed to my point I just want to say
We love your cameo in the movie A Scanner Darkly
It was brilliant
As a white male I'm so fed up with this whole blacklivesmatter thing
I think it's totally
Critical 480b cool for black English white people but any kind of white person even looks the black person wrong
Racist
That's what Obama
Reconciliation this country
They know what they're doing is going to make white people
Incredibly racist
I can't agree more like
Everything MTV Downey everything is all the major corporations are doing 50
What race divides
Down the middle I mean
Identify with Mexicans and vice-versa and
I mean what the endgame I think is it
Is it really really really bad
Revolution because I think so many white people especially
Show me hard-working whites are so fed up with saying
You're racist because of this home
BS White Privilege propaganda
Appreciate your call
The system knows is a revolution coming because of the
Criminal government
So
Yeah I don't
I don't get how you can buy that
What do you mean by that
Black lives
Matter
Tearing down the Civil Rights funded by Soros
It's inspired by someone who killed a cop
I just
I don't understand what you don't understand
Hardwood and whites are sick of this s***
4 sticker
All of that s***
Horse like there's no way that this guy can
Can actually think the caller or Alex
Everybody
I think that's possible
You think so
I just I think you're giving
I think there's a lot of people who are too stupid to look at relevant sources I think they're people who just get trapped inside.
Bubbles of
Right-wing propaganda
They reinforce each other
And they just don't see anything outside of it
And because those right-wing propaganda site
Are so vested invalidating any other news
Do they ever think
The trust
Oh here's this perspective
Or they see us story
From somebody who's involved with black lives matter who's explaining what the movement is about
I am dragging up gives a story or even like a Shaun King post something
That's a moving personal story
Just paid your paid operatives
That's their perspective
It's insane
What is the law
If they just
Go
Maybe
Maybe that's right
Make black
What is the Lost
Is conservative propaganda Outlet
Dude the game
Just be like hey
You know what
This is right
No is good
Is real
Game where every point
Every
In terms of the score
Not in terms of pointers like
Okay it's the same reason that the NRA would
Fight
Nails for you to keep a bazooka
The same reason to have assault weapons
I better
Rite Aid's Biggs
Same reason
If you give an inch
They think
Everything
Is gone
So every single time there is a
Like some sort of an argument and they have a position in it
They have to stand by it religion
You know what they might
Be right on that
Cuz everyone's just like your bunch of assholes
I don't want to fight anymore or you look at the Clinton
Bill
I would love to
To say with you looked at the Hillary Clinton
But if you look at that that triangulation
Strategy
These conservative
Yam
Only destroyed
That's word end
You gave them a name
Symmetrical War
Situation where is trying to compromise the compromise
I will never be
Realize that given a chance
The other side will f*** them over
So rmx or pure in their intention
Themselves to be way less forceful
Remember seeing that right now.
It's f****** healthcare's
You see the class were
Warfare
Like billionaires have been waging a war
Against
One of us blew up a rich guy's house all of a sudden
It's class Warfare all of us don't do that but
I'm not encouraged
But the same thing there is
Really is happening
How many
Times can a cop murder
Murder
That's what that's the whole point of black
Matter is that
We don't want to kill cops
No we want Justice
We want proof that the rule of law applies to
Everybody
Everyone's lives matter
That's not
Not happen
So long is that
Not change
How can you interpret it as any
But white
People are still trying
There are so many instances of like
Vino concert
Tatoosh analyst
Sovereign citizen
Attacking cops
That's because they don't recognize their Authority
Probably
Call Flags anyway
It's such a tangled logical bulshit
Untangle it
Present
I just don't
Like what
Constantly thinking about is there a way out of this
Snoke
Because it seems like there is a
Doing is really documenting the behind
Embassy in s*** that's going on that no one's paying attention to that we'll precipitously and our world
Because we spend a lot of time with Alex
And propaganda
We see things a little bit there's a little tunnel vision
You know there's a lot of other stuff going on in the world
It's outside of Alex
Course that is
Insertive
It's impossible for us to listen
Listen to a doomsday prophet
Any of it like
Bleed into art
Titusville
Then we're about to get to the big
Business
So Alex
On August 30th show
Before
He goes off air
Mentions that there's a big enough
It's just insane.
You're on
Your Sunday show
So you're probably just
Teasing people on the road
Maybe it's the fourth hours coming back
Which it already has basically as Rob do
Like Joe Biggs host
In the fourth hour
Also Jakari Jackson he still around is good for that hour
Sometimes
We still not seeing him
This
Is the big announce
It comes on August 31st
Incredibly boring show otherwise
Cuz it's just him being mad that people killing cops
He also says mother nice things about Sheriff
But this
Is the big enough
And I think
That it might be the
The key to understand
The left-wing they can come from religious cults they should come from a far in in
By the way
Experiment
This is just poorly constructed on his part
Yeah it's really hard to lift
That drops out here
Jesus Christ
Free speech and the globalist left has
Accomplish
Stations in groves
Are not free market
Systems free of competition by offshore combine
How about the law wars.com
Is the left-right paradigm
I want really governing and controlling Society on a mass scale
Bullock is that was legitimately his goal
If what he thought was
Really controlling
A terrible rip-off
And thinly veiled anti-semitism
I would be like
Yeah
If those were his legitimate goals I don't know problem with destroying the right left narrative
I don't think you bring in 3rd 4th 5th party
And I do think we should take down the robber baron
As we did
I don't disagree with that bring back a new deal of very socialist
It would be a good idea yeah but we haven't gotten
Subtract
We have reached that legendary
Colossal moment in history
Thousand years of human development
Operation
The first SpongeBob
And cable stations across North America of millions of more people
Looking for answers
Broadcast live on the 16th
Investigative journalist
Anne Moore
We are seeking a raise a million dollars so that we can reach
100 million
Extra people in the next year
We are
If you put together over you
100 million different
Individuals
Complete
And other regulations will cost us
$39,000 a month
Thousand dollars a year
Dollars
Portion of what we need to do this but it's important to ensure
With the collapsing economy
Exposing globalism
Operator
As we prepared to walk
Level
Global Awakening
They're not allowed to talk over this
Pain in the face
He uses that Gandhi quote a lot
Sucks for saying that
Because there are a lot of people who are just being mocked
You might be misinterpreting if there's an X
There's not
I have a lot of in
Information about this
Money bomb
That I don't think his listeners were pretty too
I do know one of the things
Is that he constantly
Before this is talked about the price
The closed
And these sorts
To feed how much does
Does closed caption
Thousands of month
I'm taking issue with the fact
He's pretending with these are new expenses
These are things he's doing already
The video cameras the crew
He's doing that already
You put the video tape
Live on
The internet everyday
Those are the same cameras you'd be using
This is either not new expensive
This is just I need money
Right this is I need a lot of money
That's because
There's something going wrong
He doesn't have the money
Keep the operation going
Okay
Here is where
My job as an accountant
Comes into play
Really like a good accountant
I don't know a lot I didn't study
There are certain things that I'm aware of
Because of that job that maybe
Some people are
Y'all one thing I'm aware of it
You know when the end of the fiscal year is
Holyshit he can't pay his taxes can't paste text
He's already laid the groundwork
For like
The irs's
Collectively trying to
Intimidate
Bully the movement
Lois Lerner is selectively all these Republicans are being screwed over for taxes
He had Peter shipping his dad on
They talk about his dad laying out this text Meredith
I think he's incredibly concerned that he's not going to be able to pay for what he owes to the government
Wow
That's why you do this massive money bomb
Right at the end of the fiscal year
By the 30th
When you have to figure out
Even consider that course that's what's going on
Wow
Trouble
20 million
Unique listeners I have no idea what the idea of actual hits to the website in
And unique it
It's are just anybody who randomly goes to one of his unique
Weekly there are 20 million different
People there's not here
Currently
I was probably about the same
Kids like 150 to 300,000 people that go to his website everyday that's not unique
Hits
Yelp I mean his YouTube numbers are incredibly skewed
Because he's double-counting
He's counting his show
Various places it's posted
He's pouting a little clips that he makes
Hope things
Scrubs the show
So like if someone watches a three-minute clip
Anime start watching the show and turn it off
You know that's too hot for him one person
Right and they go in like maybe check out one of the articles
It's the same thing that Trump trying to do with his budget
His audience is so much smaller than anything
They're not buying his f****** weirdo product
In order to keep this operation going
Straight horse f*****
At the end of this year
Cuz he has outgrown
Hit his ability to
It's the same reason I don't quit my job to do this show
Because I will be
Broke as f*** yeah I can't do that
He is living outside his means of propaganda
He is screwed the timing of it
The fact that it came up immediately
He teased it one day ahead
I meant an ounce
We're doing this
27 hour live broadcast
Sticky with Lelo amount of money
Lueken's liquor
Logan 80s we were going to do a dance competition
Car Wash otherwise old mister Moneybags
A hundred percent but he knows that he can't frame it that way
Otherwise otherwise he
Completely invalidates all of his
There's no power behind his organization
Well then did that ad in our etherion
Which is over to Trump
Does he get paid
We'll get to that does he get paid
We'll get to it I'm not sure
He is
Text Mommy and that's why I'm alright
This is one of the things
Is that
I think we've been remiss
And not considering as a motivating factor
Like it's the idea of
Keeping his baby alive
He's essentially broke or not broke broke
He's not liquid
The red
He has a personal wealth
That he could just
Funnel in
Multiple cars that are Myra
The direction
He personally
Can't pay a tax
I've no idea
It could be a combination of all those things
So obvious because of the timer
Fiscal year
And that it's out of nowhere is
Goku in
Occam's razor tells me
Is tax-related
Oh man so brilliant the other thing that I think is important like I said
Is that a motivator
Factor for him to flip
Could be
That he realizes the existence
And the growth
Of his business
Is screwed
Without some sort of hell
I believe there is a piece of it
You know like
People get
People make really bad decisions when it comes to
Trying to keep something you love a lot
To keep businesses afloat
People risk their own lives
To save loved one right
Decision strictly speaking
So I don't see it as necessarily
A possible
Then he realized
Infowars
And then we will be the example of failure
Against the globalist
Is that would be an outcome that he
He could not handle XO you make a deal
And that gets back to why
I think there have been the
I like him but I don't trust him
That's why he's teasing Trump like that
I'm not doing that
Any other candidate
Even when some are saying
Fairly similar thing right
So
I am inclined to believe
And I don't have firm
But I'm inclined to believe
That maybe he had already been contacted by one
Donald Trump's people and that's when he stopped talking about the mob
Swing in
Hey baby I'm open to it
Maybe I'm open to it
Through his
I don't trust him but I like what he say
And I'm this money
Is
Opportunity
I believe the reason for the money bomb is motive
And
I think I haven't listened
To a bunch more episodes after this but I
Pretty I feel pretty comfortable
That the switch is going to come pretty quick whether or not Rodger Stone shows up
Lurking in the shadows like that man
This point
How funny would it be if it switches the second Rapaport
I was right there by prediction but it wasn't Rodger Stone
It's all joy is the only
With his neuralink
Programming the clearly doing
We clipped we have from 31st
Eclipse from September 1st to get there before we wrap this up
Right
Next
Through the mercy
And that could be where the money's coming from might not be drunk money
Milo
How could they not look at Alex.
It is entirely possible that Trump
Self is not the source of the money
Right already indicated
Trump is really as rich as he says he's broke
Yeah
Is
The source of everything already told
I think that
Some of these
Investigations that Alex is really worried about in present-day might have the authority to
Figure out some of
Maybe we'll get to the bottom
I accept the possibility that I'm wrong
Works
Damn.
Appeared yet
Those are the big moneymaker
When I lost leader
In terms of free shipping
I don't know if
Active right all the f****** time
T-shirt there usually on sale for like
6 bucks
There's no way that he's making a good amount of money unless I
Unless
Cheapest parking shirts in the world
Let's
Conservative estimate
Isolde
Right maybe
Donuts
Reasonable
Let's say let's go 500,000
Exist in Alex
But that's like $500,000 Hillary for prison shirts
If you multiply the
By let's say he has a profit margin when you include
Shipping
Panhandling in it
That he's covering
You have a $6 shirt
Maybe the shirt itself costs like
A buck
To ship a box to ship
Kind of heavy
What's a buck
Let's go out now I see I see your TV show with you as well
Historical B
Buck to make a buck
If he gets them in a big enough bulk order that's reasonable
Bideford shirt designer
Or whatever
So
Multicolored that's
Going to come into it
Discharging stick
60 bucks for dollars profit on each
The entire shirt operation
Bring some two million
Operation
In terms of
Employees payroll
There's no way that that is a big enough like even this money bomb saying he needs a million dollars is
That's a dumb number
To pay attack
No I think you need more
World based on how much it would cost
Studio
The rent on that place alone
Crazy
I think that that is the
Come hither
To the donator
I don't know
I think we're getting a little bit too speculative
But we'll see what happens in the next few days
15 *
So
Before the money bomb that's
Suggest
It's money
Right I think
If you make
Before
During
Any of those could indicate to me
I think so I think so but we'll see
I have said a lot of negative things
Never enough
He's horrible
This next clip the first one we're going to play for
September 1st
I honestly think it's the worst thing he's ever said
Damn I'm not putting
To find a point on this
I think he's a f****** a******
And this is terrible
Furious the latest one
Terrible
False reality
Cars driving off cliffs
Not blowing your tires
Just the most ridiculous mindless garbage recruiting movie for the FBI
Homeland Security in the CIA
With this I of God software everything real time with this system
Just just just just utter
Comic book garbage
Gave me such a headache
But I had to get out of it
Alex what are you go f*** yourself why don't you like fun movies
These are awesome
I can't stand what
Comedic effect
Let's really take a closer look at
First of all it's a fiction
Movie so you can stop pretending that people are looking at it like a document
But then beyond that
It's really interesting about Fast and Furious Beyond them
Kicking ass
Those movies are awesome
The other thing is it's one of the
It's a movie
That uses a really interesting strategy
And that is
Incredibly multi-culture
All the characters
Different places
They have that Tokyo Drift movie that brought in Japanese characters
There's African-American characters
There's white characters
There's a character's there are people from all walks of life represented
There's women who Kick-Ass
There's all sorts of empowerment
For all these different types
Two people
Beyond that
Ate their set all over the world so they have like this really positive view of
America is well as like Barcelona or Brazil
Now that there is
Incredibly uniting movie
And so many ways
And the fact that I
I think it comes from his inability to deal with the idea that these races are working together I think that's
Part of it
Okay
Cuz that's so big a part of life Fast and Furious
Successful is because the people who were like
Japanese
You can see Han
Is the character and relate to it and see themselves represented
The badass character
And it's huge Hollywood
It's it really great
It really great for people
It's really great as a movie
I think they're wondering
The Fast and Furious franchise that I have
Ever heard Hansen's blow up
Do blowout
I love those movies
He's angry that it's
Movie like
He wants more Cinema verite and his fast
Full movie and one of them they drive a car
Out of a skyscraper into another skyscraper
Do you know why
Parachute with cars
Cars out of a plane parachute gland on a hill
It's awesome because of Operation Dumbo
40%
Suck yourself the Great
Certainly better than
Games
Even better than
Scanner Darkly
My baby.
Immediately
Alex Jones
Is known on the streets
Is the number one defender of the second
We've seen in every instance
He sides with guns
He says really stupid bigoted stuff
Because of his love of guns
He justifies
Almost every bad position he has
Because
Eventually it will
Do you think
That he has a
Concealed carry permit
Because that's illegal Intex
Utah
But you know what
Don't you just be a little bucket
I can officially tell you basically a race Wars
Go f*** yourself.
You don't have a concealed carry permit
What the f*** is wrong with you
You talked in the past about carry and gun
In the past
Concealed carry handgun
Fair enough
He's not going to hide
Concealed carry license open carry all the way
Everyday
Parking permit
Live the life you pretend to live
Next flip H Jones
As he is want to do
As he is known
Preemptively blame
People
Underprivileged classes for the impending
Civil War
It's going to
It's that it supports the Immigrant
The emigrants
Who are heavily depicted in
You're being
And you got to realize you were under scientific
Because once you fall
What's really going to like the police out
Break music
Right on the Raceway
What to say about that
That's very curious franchise
It's just standard stuff
Just like
White people kill black people it's fine it's just protecting yourself that should have been
People they're going to go out there going to
Cause the Patriots to have to kill everybody
The type of ship
He's putting out there is
Putting out all of this
Sphere
Black people
Has to in fluid like all of the times that you see those cops murdering
Specific
There their description
Things are always like
Ohira
Who is 65
He's a huge guy and I was scared for my life
Amplified
Perception you have
From this
Always be on alert because they're bigger they're stronger than
They're doing all of these things
The only way to protect
Is why firing
Let you know what whatever I realize
Strangers earlier
What I really should have said his be
I realize I kind of s*** the bed on that turns of phrase
Booby prejudice
I mean
That's the long and short of it
That's kind of what his operation is largely about
Even more
How to be
Aggressive
The people who listen to Alex Jones
We're coming in
No coming in like
Normal regular ask
Hang out with and then
Alex Jones
Radicalized
And he amplifies that
You feel good about it
Which Wich
Shoe that I have
Because he's always fighting against
Feeling bad
Portable bigot
Because he's always like
Don't make me
We feel like I'm erased
Don't make me feel like this
He feels good
He feels good about fighting against
Give his listeners that kind of
Blankets
Except
Hope they feel it vicariously through
I feel good I'm about my
I don't have to hide it I don't have to fight against political correctness
Argument
Is always
About
Feeling good
Your your
Why is it wrong for me to be proud of my whitening
Yeah
Why is that wrong
Princess
But
I don't know
Proud of
Cool about it
Celebrating
Heritage
Necessarily
Comes at the expense of recognizing
The realities of
Your life
It has been
Great because of the oppression of other people
Like if you're unwilling to look at that because you're proud of your
German
Swedish Heritage or whatever you know whatever
Ethnicity whatever culture you come from
Is it comes
Expensive recognizing the reality then that is
Disagree I disagree with
The reason I said that is because
Some people don't look at it as
Skin color is much as it is a look at it is
My German heritage
So I like to wear Lederhosen it
That's something
They can play it
Of course they do
And Alex
Help
He's bringing it up like that argument of the West
Culture that
Skin color
Celebrating the fact
For some inexplicable reason my ancestors were like ants but without the
Enjoying and celebrating that culture that that has
A with a lot of
Cloud cover and so our skin is white
Doesn't f****** matter. I mean that's
Faribault
That's the problem
The problem is the idea that
The only thing
That you have no control over
Your skin
Very quintessential
Yeah
The idea of being
Proud of that
Insane
But that's why I phrased it as being cool
But anyway
We have more to get through
A little bit
We got to guess
Michelle
Are most hated
Like guy
Larry NEX
Stevie Larry Nick
Text
Unfortunately he does not have any more gossip about TV stars that Hillary's f***** I was hoping
Good stuff unfortunately he's
Which now as I was the last
Case the last time he was on
He switched
Do the Obama wants to be king of the Muslims narrative
There's not a whole lot of
Hillary Trucking TV
Beastars
Bye.
Easy going
Does he have a dead drop again if he's murdered
Is an address
Crazy bulshit moment of the day
Sexually too crazy
But what about
It's super crazy
What is it when Obama was elected
Everything in it and then shop
Anime craze
Water issue now than the day the man came in he is
The riots get activated out of Cheers Bar people don't understand when these Blackbob start run
Dial into the neighborhood people are doing this country
Call up and say please send the government and stop it protect us
We will call for the federal government to come in and protect us we will
Funny things
Secondly the other thing is that black
Mom
Yep
Great
F*** you Larry Nick
F*** you matches your Eternal perspective about the world
Is really important
Is that in the first month
His presidency
Donald Trump
Did threaten
To bring the federal government
Chicago to take care of the violence issue here
It's not us calling out for the feds come in
That's your guy
Calling
To federalizing
Text your guy doing the thing that you've been most afraid of
For your entire career Alex Jones
Trump is doing
Totally
Totally fine with it or love it
It's in Ghana
F****** gun
Like for the longest time I was like you know what nobody wants
To take your guns away we just want
I want my house filled
I don't have a house
Bedroom filled with all of the guns you have become radicalized
I would like to say I want to steal your gun
Underneath
Deep Earth iodine Crescent
People's guns to be taken away but in the sense of like
Turning
Your weapons in
Plowshare
But I don't want individually to live in a world where we were past it
Do a like
What are the most
Successful things has always been
Gun buyback
You know like no question to ask
Will buy your guns back
Constitutionalist
We're going to have to break into their home
Recorder many British soldiers
Because the Constitution doesn't mean anything anymore.
And I want to take their guns
I don't fully agree with you but
Just cuz I want to I want to move along here cuz Larry Nichols other point
Abundant wild okay
This is
This is delicious
All for the civil emergency
We will will be the ones asking for it because you know what will be scared
Will be scared that something else might as well known y'all going to think I'm crazy but get ready to grease the banana truck
And I'm fixing to tell you there's a reason tube
Glass relations with Cuba
Alex you know you people yourself
Under prices condition in this country
You say Obama and his people and I'm sure the general Tortola
When it comes to telling American soldiers Crackdown on the people of America
Julian pretty quick
Ramadan
He's gone to the one military force that I personally ran into a Nicaragua
No in here under the auspices of all
Milling Allmendinger military
Keep us in line
Apathetic September the Washington Post and restricted documents
Kettering a civil emergency
Obama and the clintons
Those are stuff about
Exercises of operation
Wikipedia Fredo
They're Crossing the Rubicon my friend Canadians in the Mexicans and Obama and the Cuban Army
The widely known Special Forces absolute
Every country up
Cuba not even on the radar
That's going to be his fourth military
Larry Nichols is awesome
Half of Cuba
Then they can take everybody down lyrics
They've been training to America
Alright I really think that the world needs to have a good long conversation
About the fact that so much of the propaganda about the
Comes from Larry Nichols
We really need to understand that cuz I don't think
You didn't know his name until we started going through this I don't think most people in the world know who the f*** he is
They don't know that
He is the source
So much of this s***
And he's the kind of guy who's like
Obama wants to become the king of Muslims worldwide
Come King
Also Obama
The second line
You only normalize relations with Cuba in order to get their military on his side
Richardson radio show and said he was a hitman
For the clintons that killed multiple people and then later said I was on pill sorry I didn't mean that I wouldn't have said that
That I was on Vicodin
So much of this hatred of the Hillary and Bill
Comes directly from him
Lying
And if we could just have a conversation about that
And look at all the evidence
We could get rid of
So much of this
I mean we wouldn't it wouldn't work
But if we could have done it ten years ago right it might have helped
Like if we could have
If you look
Legitimately look
At the situation
Around all those allege
The murders that the clintons are responsible for
You realize that it's all bulshit
Right
It's it's nonsense
Of course if we could have nipped that in the bud way back then
We might have a tattoo
Like the right-wing might not have become what it is now
And I see a lot of that at the doorstep
Fox News and Rodger Ailes
No shirt but they were playing into a lot of the stuff that Larry Nichols starts exactly that's what that's what they were
To actually look into like other guys
Write this is crazy
He's talking about Hillary Clinton f****** Markie Post
All the time
Francisco
Hillary Clinton
Weather
Although it's
Meetings with design
Smaller-scale I legitimately feel like
We just
CrossFit
The point where
It's too late
With Alex
But what am I
Sincere feelings about this podcast is
I look at what happened with Larry Nichols
Clinton
You know 20 years
25 years ago
I see where the road could have gone to
And the better world we could be living in
I see what's going to happen with Alex
It's going to be worse version
Discourses already
Descended to Alex Jones level
The news is covering Alex Jones story
The president
Is saying Alex Jones talking
Point he's emailing out Infowars
It's only going to get worse
Larry Nichols corrupt
The discourse
Politically with the is assaults on the clock
Hammond news
Bucking Gingrich
Alex Jones
Who's going to turn things on its head even worse
If people like
Like I said I think we've already crossed
The line where is it possible to undo the damage
But God damn it if I'm not going
To try and push back
Because it's
The influences
It's it's omnipresent it really is it's really really bad and I appreciate everyone who listens and
Do it one more quip
I realize I want it I want to say this
In terms of self-exploration
You're in the moment as we're doing
Michelle
Yeah I'm like
You know that thing you said
15 minutes ago
Take a look at that
All of my things really forget what I
And I'm looking at myself right now and I'm like
Did I make
Too big a deal out of that money bomb
Is that did I I mean
I think this is better
I am exploring like my
I'm partially critical all the time I'm right there with you
If you did
Know what I know which is
You might think I was being a little bit extreme
But listen to this
Call Zan
September 1st
Joe Faker real caller
Hard to say I think
Uno's let's go ahead and go
You're on the air Don welcome
Canada thank you Alex longtime listener and supporter
Thank you brother
22 Mile Papa care what you're going through but
I know everybody on yourself are on the fence
It's about this Donald Trump guy running for president here
I'd like you to see if you would approach this fella and see if he might want to support
That's coming up here in the next month
Prefix with kid gloves which is great
Because we are the real deal
In South Texas last month
I guess
And so
I don't trust him at a gut level but I
If you want to win
Economy Inn off services
Real estate
Money longer
Economy
Right there Alex
Contradicted what he said in the past
The frontman for a Consortium
Service
Related
Texas money I was just said that in the past
The factory switch the story mean
So there's that
Cuz why don't you get drunk
To give you the money
Alex is like
He doesn't say no
Well
Hardcore politician
Things wouldn't get robbed
Convincing himself you know
Trump just
Reference maybe I should interested
Prosperity
Piece of it that almost
Comes off as a gut
Which is like a most mainstream politicians wouldn't get involved with us
You mainstream politics
There is almost like a challenge
There's code going on here in terms of like
If you look at it as
He's just talking extemporaneously
It's pretty weird
He's got a weird head space
But if you look at it is
This is maybe communication between him
And a Bag Man or something like that was some negotiating
There is a subtle indications that he is
Sing
Ready to listen
I don't
Necessarily agree with you in
It seems like you're giving them a lot of
Credit or you're giving Alex
What's a lot of credit for
Being able to build up a narrative
As well as
Communicate
What are you talkin about there is no narrative today
What are you
Sing about the narrative
That's just my position is
I really like what you saying but I don't trust him
Okay I suppose I suppose The Narrative that I'm talking I like I like what you're saying but I'm ready for you to come
About the narrative
There is your building up this is capable
I know you're
Reminder the clip-ins
What
Becky to make your argument
Invalidated
Y'all warning with Proviso
How much of the money bomb
Price of million dollars on the 16th
Mega $50,000 Januzaj here
Network TV
I want to take a little
Weird phrases
His part
Know what he was saying
I'm giving him the benefit of the doubt
A warning with Proviso
Your Proviso is
What's condition of Anna
Agreement
But I think that
He's right on there
It whatever
The agreement is that Trump has
To be real
Like he's made it alright to his listeners
I'll give you that
That but it is an interesting term
Cuz if usually used in contracts in
Could or could be a little
That you're going
What's the lot done
Very inexpensively
Fox News
Hundreds of millions a year to run
We run this operation for
It's well over 10 million dollars a year
That's why I spend so much time to selling product promoting
And I'm trying to do that because
We have to find ourselves so we can be independent
See if I got money from Trump
When people claim
Holding
I've been bought by Trump
From a cult Brothers
Where the products we sell in the services we have
But
It was no strings attached
But I appreciate your call.
That's weird
That's not great
That's not really good
That's real bad
100 million.
No because
10 million dollars doesn't have strings attached
Other than the money that we sent to Iraq that is still no longer
Preemptively
Getting again
Those accusations
If you took money from from Trump
So I don't want to take the money
Flash Forward
Hypothetically
Four Hands
I wasn't going to do this
Immediately started being his biggest cheerleader
Right
Right I'm not saying the Trump gave him 10 million dollars
Suggested
He would like
I think
Very
Very good likelihood
What is mercer
I think
Whoever it is there someone giving him money
This is
I think
I don't know how to say
What are minutes because I'm making a weird argument
Making a weird making a very well-thought-out argument
And there is a lot of
You know
There's there's a lot of Circa
And it does
If you are looking for it
At 8
Yeah
I think you're you're probably on
I think you might be right
Probably at this point.
I think my quibble is in the idea that Alex
Can Maine
Maintain
That kind of cocky
I think in 2015 he was a bit smarter than he has now
Well that's
Pressures that he has now he didn't
More relaxed
And I think in that relax
Also super male Vitality top headspace
I don't think that it's that crazy that you would be able to
Keep that going
Because otherwise why wouldn't have been convinced
Trump keep
Yeah that's being Pig
In terms of being
Does a cocky dick hole
In terms of being against
What Alex Jones
Perceives as
The establishment globalist
He clearly is the gotten pissed off a tramp all throughout
He doesn't
Forum
Yeah but then you've got the
The other argue
Of why would
You change your mind Trump
Was
F****** joke never been a joke salad
Throughout the entire time the things the people had made jokes about
Alex
Still being like how you look at it
Here's the other part that we have to take into consideration
Donald Trump
Campaign
Largely worked off of propaganda in
In Gossip
There was a major like whoever was running his campaign at any given time
Seem to be very interest
In rumor-mongering and propaganda
To think that they wouldn't have actively tried to
Court Alex Jones
Subway
Is crazy
Do you think you think it's possible that they came to Alex
I think Alex at the moment
Talking about the mob tonight
You think so
The other check
Past I don't know if I could
On a gut-level I don't trust him
He was talking much more specifically
About how is your name is Genevieve you get arrested if it's Trump you don't
Right he's not Richie
The frontman
Before that
Day when you made that pivot
He was talkin about having
High-level information from people
He was using
He's everything that wasn't his Source back then
Laundering
Yeah I I I don't think necessarily it was someone
I'm from
Campaign
Intermediary
Some cut out
Is Rodger Stone
So I I think that's possible and I
I don't
I don't know if it was a situation where they were like will give you a ton of money to
To promote Trump
Not something like that
I think there's probably some bit of an in
Influence
Situation
You need a favor we need
Well and they can sell it cuz
Do you know Alex
So jumpy on guns
Immigrants
Abortion
Yeah
Is your guy
They can use
His vague
Suggested position
Trump
To feed into Alex's need for a savior
And isn't it
Right
I think that and Rand Paul is not paying
Alright
Ego
Motivation
Schlitterbahn
Yeah I think
She got the broken
I think it's not all that crazy
Suggest
That turning point of I'm not going to
These negative things about Trump anymore
Would precipitated by something
It possible that one of his employees and legal
Just like you could get sued for that or something
That would be enough
That wouldn't hold
Kraken Court
Yeah I think
That
When you combine
A surprise money bomb
A day after
With
The timing of the end of the fiscal year
You now have opportunity
You haven't needed on Alex
Cuz part that can be satisfied
Buy some really rich donor
Here is the here is the other conspiracy
Go from there
The money bomb
Cover that's what I was
Obama's like
Stated our goal for the month Bob which suggests that the listeners did everything
But maybe he got a lot of that money
Play from
Intermediary or the Mercers
That's what I've done what I'm talking about in terms of
Like the the motive
Alex's need
The opportunity of
The cover of the money bomb is there
In terms of
Cloaking thing
Cuz it doesn't have to change what is listener
He's already laid the groundwork with I don't know if I can trust him but I like all the things you say
You should support Trump wear support Trump
And all you have to do
To make
Have you like guys
This is enough
I've heard enough
Rand Paul is great but he's just not doing it he's not
Hardcore enough
Right he's not going to get it there for the Patriots
It's bear everything is in place
Yeah at this point
Basmati bomb happen
Whenever we were
Starting with investigation
Right I have no idea and want
Police came into play
I like this is
It's feels
Feels like
With me too many predictions on
Investigation
Yeah
I don't know we'll see
Damn it I want you to know
Second investigation
Hi baby girl trying
Maybe
But
If you'd like to check
Now it's right.com
Knowledge underscore fight
Get more followers
ITunes
Will be doing in a few months
We won't know
If you like donate to the show though you can
Acknowledge fight.com
Support
Are we would appreciate if you could be great
Ulta
What else we got
Mom
Usually we end with a B
Has not yet you keep it up
Is all you
F*** you Dad
You and I are enemies we have a
Three Rivers shared anime
That's right we do have a chair.
Baby yungin. Young man by the name of John Rappaport
Who can go f***
Listen up
Jon rappoport
Go fuc yourself
Controlling
Alexandra Thurston color