Damn important swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Fight.com
Selena took a little bit about the goings-on in the life of Austin Texas
Indeed we are flourished
And I can't stand though I do have a question
For you or what is your bright spot sir I was browsing around
Video of website
Peeking around poking trying to find something to cover
But this was a bright spot
Laura Loomer was on the other war room
Or whatever
Owen
You did not put Laura Loomer in the title of the video
Do you have to refer to as
Female journalist shows video of democratic election fraud
It's gotten to the point where even like
You can come on oh and show but you're not going in the metadata
Even Infowars thinks you're to talk
That's amazing
Poisonous if I understand that video
32 that I skipped over
Pictures running for office again
Yeah baby
Going to be fun midterm season heating up and it's like there's going to be
Some of these these weirdos can't wait
Anyway what about you as much as I enjoy
Space to harangue you with tennis
I'm going to do self it's fine I've learned to zone out
That's fine I'm just I'm just going to let you know that I'm very excited my bright spot today
Day is that guy album faces into the quarter-finals he's into the second week of the Australian Open
And this is exciting
Because Gael Monfils is one of the most incredible tennis players
He's easing I mean it's just amazing using Magic
Thrilled to hear it and then tripped and then hit the
Handy Switch the tennis racket to the other side
Dear Lord
He's never won a major because he had The Misfortune of Being Born during the time of the three greatest tennis player
Whoever live
Agassi Sampras
Third guy
This is his maybe best chance
Near the end of his career win a major final
Because Djokovic wouldn't get a vaccine
Vera was just knocked Rafa still coming hard okay
Don't know if he's never even made a final before so this would be exciting not least of which
Because
If he were to do so you'll be the first
Black man in Olmos
50 years
And it is been he's one of those guys who's always had the talent to do it
You know if you were born in an era without the three greatest tennis players of all-time sure
He would have had two or three people play basketball in the time of Jordan
Sorry
You are great but f*** off yet you would have chips in other times
Totally
Unfortunately
Let me when you figured like
Between Federer
Nadal and Djokovic
There are 20 major 60 total major
That's 15 years worth of Majors that are just
Knocked off the face
The planet that's crazy when you stopped
To think about it we got it we got it
Monopolistic
Anyways I'm excited I hope he takes it and it's it's something I'm rooting for Harrah
Today we have to go over but it's a little off the beaten Trail not necessarily as
Off the trail is
Project Camelot
Psychic in preparation for this
But I just it wasn't good enough
I wasn't weird enough it was just like
The psychic was just saying that everyone's dead and been replaced by clone Leo Pros killed
Open 2008 has been alone ever since
Sometimes there are multiple clones of people running around
Psychic as much as it is
Just keep Minaj
What we got going on is it at the end of last week
I'll Ted's a bit of a family court day on Thursday
And then Friday you'd expect you to come into the show the head of steam pretty excited for the possibilities
Doesn't come in on Friday of course I went Royer, comes in and does his show
Actually no current stuff and then on Saturday
Alex dropped a little gem
Right into our little plate
And that is a emergency Saturday broadcast
Right there was an emergency
Do I record this
Abba
The great idea
Aw thank you so much
Thank you Sarah
Text your Uncle Matt and sleepy Margaret thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Thank you very much your uncle man
Marshalls
My dude
From Algonquin Illinois
We may or may not have given this shout-out at the time but it was quite a while ago
Baby
We should have been more punctual about this cuz
Happy birthday Nikki
Happy birthday in order of us possibly being late.
Born
Is the condition that leads to death
Life is a disease that ends in death
Sojourn
Today
January 22nd
Saturday's date
Struggling this weekend with like I slept on my neck wrong throwing everything off
Like it's hard to sleep it hurts to stand up
No worries.
To be standing what do the active
It's just
It's miserable so if I'm a little wee wee football injuries to my back
That have bothered me for 15 years so yeah I'm with you
I wish this would that bother me 415 is Levi used to it
Brooke ongoing chronic pain not sincere I apologize for
We start off here
Alex
Awesome big
Nusenda
It's not real
It's Saturday
January 22nd
Have got
Credible
Newsalert
Huge
Stories
First off
Official
All over the
Europe
Canada
States
UK
All four of the places in the world
The mask
Checkpoint
Kenzie
Vaccine
Passport
Sports systems
On your phone
And
Boobs for 4
Inoculation
Just a week ago they were saying
In Europe
Bored
On February 1st
But suddenly
All these
Government in
All the different
Medical
System
CDC
Turn the United States
National
Health Services
UK
They all came outside
And said you don't what
Ending
All of
That is an amazing way for Alex to start this show and that would be a massive news alert
Operates with his narrative
I think it's a huge indication that he's looking for an off-ramp from the covid Asteria
Dominated the show for the last two years
I'm going to attempt to lay out the picture of what I mean by this
And I'm going to start by addressing the reality and falsity of the news that Alex's cover
Mostly this has to do with Boris Johnson announcing that England had reached
Deacon terms of Omicron
Miami covid related restrict
Go to bees
This coming Monday
Granted
CBS quote the restrictions being lifted on Monday in England were some of the least stringent imposed across Europe
Even so this is one of the countries that Alex thinks is the most important in the world so this is a major shift
Wisconsin Boris Johnson says please stop paying attention to that whole party thing that I had that everybody is just not
Stop
So Alex is reporting this as the NHS giving his advice
Matthew Taylor the CEO the NHS Confederation the organization that represents the health care entities that provides
Uses for the nhsa
Images under significant pressure
Even with restrictions at many people going further to protect themselves and others the number and hospital with covid is high on the number
Numbers are only going down very slowly
High numbers of covid patients and staff off sick has the inevitable effect
Only work
The Health Service can do
Including the Urgent task of making inroads
Into the treatment backlog
And getting back to
Performance performance
In addition Taylor encourage people to continue wearing masks
Getting tested regularly taking sensible precaution
In addition the British Medical Association was quoted by the guardian is saying this decision was quoted not Guided by
The data
Also Susan Hopkins the chief medical adviser to the UK Health Security Agency quote
Urge the public to take our personal Behavior seriously and use face coverings when in crowded places
Among strange
There are many many cautious voices in the UK medical community and there are also many commentators who like your cell
Self are pretty convinced
What's the poorest John's
The move is a calculated political one
Which is designed to save his position
Well putting the public at right now
So you're just telling me that for the past week people within his own party of Ben
Calling for him to resign and then suddenly and conveniently
He does the thing that other people might want that could cause a lot of controversy
Taking away from that store
Conservative parties
These restrictions lifted
He's convinced he's giving a concession because they have been calling for him to resign
Shooting was looking really bad for him
Like the conservative MP Christian wakeford had defected to labor and David Davis before
Brexit guy
Essentially equated Johnson to Neville Chamberlain
Wait up using the virus or the conservative I am take your pick
The Daily Telegraph reported the quote 11 lawmakers submitted letters of no confidence in Johnson
54 letters are required
Trigger a leadership challenge it but there might have been more that were submitted that weren't made public like he was in
In the soup
Listen there's there's nothing like the thick of it to really make you appreciate
The British political
Open system
The reason that the restrictions is kind of the move that Johnson was because like
You said
I was in trouble because BYOB parties
What time Downing and Arizona housing these people and they they they were like
You know I think the French aristocracy were right on and I don't think anything negative ever happened to them so let's just do the same s***
Guardian points out
It's fairly safe to say that this is decision of it's based on politics not science because Scotland Wales and Northern Ireland
Call keeping many of the restrictions in place
Like required Mastin public transit
And in retail setting
A similar Dynamic is an effective
Ireland
Where many settings are no longer required masks but still exist on public transit
They're going to ease the restrictions in the hospitality sector and pubs are going to be allowed to be open past 9 p.m. again so there are
Some moves that they're making but also some
Restrictions that are staying in place
Here in the United States the Supreme Court ruled the bidens vaccine or test mandate for businesses wasn't going
Stand still appropriate in healthcare settings
In terms of what restrictions exist the CDC doesn't really set any of that
They give recommendations and then the actual decisions are mostly a state-by-state thing
Various states are taking wildly different approaches so I have no idea how to even address I was just playing
The United States drop the Black Sea
The craziest two words I've heard anyone say about any politics
. yeah
January 20th the cdc's website still recommends everyone over 2 years old should wear masks
The people to get vaccinated and maintain
Well-maintained just
Since when possible
The same state-by-state Dynamic is also true
In Canada
National rules for example non citizens who aren't vaccinated or only able to enter the country under certain circumstances
Aspects of national
Distraction
Various provinces a lot of them are actually extending covid precautionary rules
For instance on January 17th British Columbia's Health Ministry announced that they would extend the covid order quote
That will keep
Gyms and fitness center is closed and limit Gatherings at events and restaurant
In almost all Publix
Meanwhile Ontario is easing restrictions gradually with businesses like restaurants and theatres being able to open a.50
Capacity beginning January 31st
Then gradually heading back to normal over a matter of money
At the same time Quebec has decided to not lift
Different places make different decisions
Alex Singleton on the news
From England that decided to characterize the entire world based on the
And self-preservation base decision made by Boris Johnson
There's a good chance
That will play to his audience
It's dumb
Putting aside the real-world for a second it's critical to understand the move that Alex is making with his narrative and how he's able to pull
Pull it off
Alex has built up the image of
Clearly Draconian covid tyranny not only is something that's coming but something that's already here
The checkpoints the door-to-door forced vaccination
It's all happening
This is very sensationalize does a version of the world am to engaging with reality this way service
Two important functions for Alex
First
Keep his audience in a state of almost
Hypnotic and impotent fear where the only solution available is to sport Alex so he can save
You
Secondly
He knows that none of these things were ever going to actually happen
There were going to be door-to-door forced vaccination
It really serves as a perfect horror scenario that he'll eventually get to take credit for stopping
Are you saying that he didn't really believe there would be Daleks with guns going from
Door-to-door anybody to believe that 10K well.
You get to the first hints of this from this claim at the end of the clip where Alex
The saying that all these countries mysteriously simultaneously made these announced
Which is obviously meant to imply that they were acting in
Concert in reaction to something
We're just going to be claimed to be the mass Awakening that Alex has helped app
But if you look at the actual state of things that the actions of the various countries that he's referencing
What he saying isn't real at all
It dangles by the thread of Boris Johnson
Decision until very recently Alex has been calling a globalist Raider
Who pretended to be a paper in order to get elected then turned on the people
So
You can see
The
Stream over sensationalize rhetoric about like
Door-to-door forced vaccinations are italics we forgot I right
So easy to forget about that
It's so easy and yet
Impossible I remember it on my deathbed so you have those really Extreme 2 weeks from now
Really extreme things are never going to happen
And
Because they're never going to happen whatever Alex
Decides to take
Play stop it by way of his Mass Awakening
I mean he's seeing hell
So
To try to get out of this f****** meatbag letter
What are is going to do recent War
He's going to
Present as what is the
The reason that all these countries
So why are they in
Just now
Because the
Deaths
Our way down
No
Is it
Because
The bureaucrat
Just want to give us our
Respect
Because they know all over the
The world
Powerful
Opposition
Has formed
Governmental Corp
Private
Visual level
There was a massive
Hide
Resistance
But they wouldn't be able to stop
A huge tide
Peaceful
Resistance
Majority
Conservative
Stories
And of liberal labor
Party members
UK last
Boris Johnson
And said
We can outvote
With a super mature
The same thing
Still happening
Canada
The same thing is now
Turn the United States
I think it's a strange for Alex honestly
I don't know how he's going to explain it when there are still covid restrictions down the road
Like if all these governments figures are so scared of the powerful
He's helped inspire
Seems like it would be impossible for him to explain them reimposing covid measures in the future should that be necessary
Seems to me like an indication of a desire on Alex's part though to change the status quo of his coverage
I don't know if it's going to play
Like it does seem like there's that there's a
There's something that
Is underwriting
Yeah
I mean
Because the reason that I feel that way is that he's written this fun fantasy version
End of what happened to Boris Johnson
And I guess
Both help with explaining be like he's a traitor part cuz I
They blackmailed him in
Conversion of it is nonsensical blackmail public everybody is
Effingham be blackmailed
Yeah
Yeah it does
I feel like there's other ways that Alex would report stuff
If you wasn't looking
Looking for like
I want to stop talking about this s*** for a while
Yeah
Is it
I mean thing about it is that it feels like he's trying to take that early
You passed
Because right now what
What we're seeing
Tumi
Is
Complete abdication of responsibility from
All the people who could be taking
Right so at this point
They're all saying that we are simply giving up to the mathematics of human behavior
Rather than any kind of intervention
To change the result
So Alex is maybe right of just saying like
If they're going to say that everything's f******
Confine
Then
I might as well too
Clyde Weaver
And we won cuz they're capitulating in the sense that they're trying to guess like the rest of us in the same way that Alex is always
Always wanted them to
I guess so but I still think
The even if
There are like massive your responsibility is going on it terms of
Many state governments in terms of their responses
I'm taking care of the public
There isn't nothing being
True you know there are still some in position
True that's right for Public Health
I don't know
It is weird
Death
It's just I mean I got
Maybe just Alex want to win
Dictate that
He much like we are
Pretty sick of him talking about f****** covid
I can imagine
Exhausted
Pointless
Okay
I found this one
Steve Kirsch blog article for a couple days and then everyone's going to get bored of it
Yeah I'm going to need to
Ukiah
Constantly be on the treadmill
Have to be exhausted and we've got upcoming
Oath Keepers and Stewart Road s*** all of this
Is going on coming his own trial all day
Why not
Declaro win
It is no longer people are pressuring me so I might as well just lift
All these restrictions Alex
I've got a lot of s*** going on right now I might as well just say at 1
Parallelogram
So I think Alex is like take on it is more just like
The public is woken up they're not buying the official narrative
The Publix.
Buying
Narrative
And we have the medical Serv
Private incorp
Around the world
Leading the way exposing
These so-called vaccines
Gene therapy
But actually erase
Your immune system
Avast
Majority of peace
Dying
Vaccinate
To put out fake
Headlines of your
20 times more likely
Hospitalized
Do you have another shot
Not true
Put up fake
Headlines
Ninety-nine percent of husk
Fertilizer unvaccinated
Versace a year ago
All of it
Giant live
The private and corporate medical services aren't exposing the stuff Alex is claiming
That's just as cherry-picked Cadre of lunatics long time
Call Steve Kerr
I wanted to take a look at Alex's claim that these stats were lies though
A bit off
Depending on what date is that you look at
Like whatever Alex's sink according to the most recent release from the CDC or 15
Times more likely to die of covid if you're on vaccinated then
If you are
As of December 8th was a rate of about
2 deaths per 100,000
.47 / 100,000
Numbers from November reflected a 68 times increased risk of death from covid vaccination persons
Compared to those who have gotten the booster
So
I don't know
20 ballpark
Even Alex's freedom-loving Texas state government release date of this past week that showed they quote
Unvaccinated Texans are 16 times more likely to die from covid related illnesses
Been fully vaccinated Texas
I'm at Texas
This week the CDC released a finding that unvaccinated people oversee
65 and older were 49 times more likely to be hospitalized
Then people over 65 who have gotten the booster
Unvaccinated people age
5264 or 44 times more likely to be hospitalized index made people
In the same age range
When you include all
People over the age of 18 of hospitalization rates were 16 times higher
Hit me up vaccinated cohort then ended
How to claim these are fake headlines Ali Wong
Hotspot potatoes bearing out that you are far more likely to end up hospitalized or dead
If you're on vaccinated regardless of what age group you're in
I I just
I don't I don't know
It's it it
It's nice
But that's backed up
Buy a lot of science that we can point to
But at the same time
Man that's a f****** point of vaccine
Dude
I'm glad
I'm glad that it's true
I'm glad we got the numbers
Exactly
But come on what the fuc
Point of even call to get a vaccine if you don't
Amici's
Jesus Christ right right I mean the numbers are all just like working
Stop
Theory that leads to a bit of like an introduction of a predict
They gas-lit us with
The corporate media
Wachusett
Every level.
The local health
July
Hairstyle fail
This is a very historic moment
Across the political Rubicon
Now they claim they get rid of her
Is a year ago but I said they bring them
They know the opposition build to a point
Defeat them
They back off
We go back to sleep
Back again
That I'm pretty
Here
They're going to
To do it again
But not right away
There's a fun story but it's all just based on things I was imagining
There's no indication that I can see that any restrictions our guidance has been enacted or lifted because of
Beer about being defeated by Alex has awakened Army
In fact I would suggest the only people who seem to have mold of their behavior on a fear of people like Alex or the politicians were doing
Exactly what I was watching
Badoo
People like to Santa San Bruno weather bread is buttered they can see that they need to cater to
This extreme anti-vax building block or else they have no future in politics
And then I guess there's Boris Johnson who was less afraid
How the power of
He was afraid of losing it
Government because he got caught having parties
Well the public was sacrificed
For the public good
The situation with Boris looks close enough to what Alex needs it to look like in order for him to write a compelling story about it so that's why
What he's doing
The whole world is mysteriously simultaneously dropping covid restrictions because they're worried about Alex
The truth movement being too successful
And toppling the entire globalist
It's so stupid but it's
The closest thing to an off-ramp I think Alex has seen in a long time
I don't fault him
Protect
Yeah yeah
This notion that they eased up the restrictions in the past when they were in danger and then tighten them up when the Patriots got complaints
It doesn't really make sense
Considering that for the last 2 years consistently and incessantly anti-vax assholes have been yelling about real and imagined
Public Health measures
At rally school board meeting City Council meetings and of course on Alexandro
Gun shows
There was no time when the anti-vax assholes Geico
Complacent
Constant barrage
Entire time
AMV idea that these covid restrictions are being just drop simultaneously
Alex says England
That's about it
The rest of the country singer named don't even actually
Support the argument
And even then
There a ton of countries in the world that he's just ignoring it
Pretending don't exist
Index on the financial times
Nearby Oxford a researchers at Oxford
Anything strange at the index
Pics of government
Government measures
Walking in early this year at 43.5 to on my scale this is on January 15th
Emily jump
61.11 on January 8th
Wow
Yeah that's like
Go to a party you lose your
Yeah they had to postpone impeaching a president do to covid-19
That's a good that's a good sis
Well they're not forcing anybody to get it they are launching door-to-door vaccination campaigns in order to make the shots available to anybody
It also came out this week that many albanians were no longer allowed to enter Kosovo as they had enacted new rules where you needed
You have proof of getting the booster or current PCR test across the border
This weekend Kosovo enacted new rules regarding entry and they also said a curfew and restricted restaurant hours today
Needs to be closed by 9 p.m.
Also in their new rules quote
All employees of public institutions Central and local public Enterprises
Private businesses organizations as well as other entities
Must possess one of the following in order to be allowed to enter the work premise
A gun
No proof of vaccination or proof that they have a contraindication that makes them exempt from vaccinations
Also Master required all over the place
Also this last week
Please put in a new rule the people who wanted to enter the country
We need to purchase travel insurance
To help offset the covid cost
Overtreatment Sandlot
Expenses for people who need
Quarantine
Alex should consider this a major move
But he seems to not care
At least partially because the story doesn't fit his current narrative about this suspicious drop of all covid
How restrict
In Alex's defense
He could not to point
He could not point to where any of those countries are on a map
Probably not
But maybe maybe want to go to Europe
How about that loves Europe
Go to Germany
Play some Alex has routinely said his deceit of the New World Order cuz of Angela Merkel
Seventh grade choir negative covid test
Restaurants
The rules also continue to policy restricting people who have not been vaccinated from attending gather
But stay in urine
Emily just
Titans are rules
About where I where you will need a green pass to enter
It was announced on January 20th
Have to take effect in February and last until the end of March
And will now of this past go to a Barber and Beauty Salon
And this is also in addition to the places you already needed one like
Public offices Banks
Some post offices are you don't need one at Aaliyah's gummy party
That's true
Stop
Let's also check out grease and learned about how they've elected to keep their current covid restrictions in place
And what's this
Find the elderly
On January 17th Greece announced that they were going to start
Finding people over 60 who haven't been vaccinated 50 Euro Mom God I love Greece
I f****** love that s***.
Finding Daddy for not being vaccinated
That is
F****** great this was this last week I love it in the same time when I love it
Everybody's dropping all the restrictions percent chance they won't come collect on that but just that they would
F****** put that out there
Love it
Let's not let's go a little bit towards towards the east find Turkmenistan just put some new restrictions
Tire place on January 16th which included quotes
Stepping up enforcement of mask-wearing
Restrictions on businesses and something else should be deeply concerned about
What are the new rules says quote the doctors nurses and medical students are to be assigned to
Control points on highways
At the boundaries between Regional centers and District
To carry out
Enhanced check I f****** love it
Goddamnit what is East Berlin just had a bunch of weirdo.
Stares at the border putting up the the
Start a roadside checks that Alex has been obsessed about forever
I would be pleasantly surprised if there was a roadside check those like you doing okay man
Right diesel there's other examples but I think the point is clear
Alex's world use very narrow and predominately just involves countries that he thinks are white
There's a ton of varying responses to covid in different countries because these different countries are facing different out brake pads
Engagement with the world is to skim the story about Boris Johnson makeup a fun story about it then use that story to character
Tries the situation in the entire world
The globalist are super afraid of Alex's buddy so they're loosening up a code restrictions except for all the places
But they are loosening restrictions and they're actually adding new ones which I was just ignore
The larger point is nothing Alex's saying is in anyway connect
The reality
He's predicting they're loosening up
Restrictions imposed
Because I think he probably realizes on some level that based on the anti-vax forever and
Complete responsibility or public officials are showing
There's probably going to be another crisis
Before this is all over
This isn't laying the groundwork so things get out of control again
Partially thanks for the bulshit he's spreading
Public Health measures that are being discussed are actually is a further attack on free
Freedom in the Patriots
The circular are the circular game is getting really old
It's it's a little bit like
Predicting the financial crash after 2008 and you you watch all that stuff happened and then they were like
What if we did nothing about it and you're like okay will eventually it's going to happen if
In the same way as like
Hey you know theirs
Mutation
Covid
Like you know if you don't do anything about it they'll probably continue doing that
Predicting another mutation
And it's not a
Difficult
Thing to do
But it's it's it's actually you're wrong
They're making these diseases in life
I wish I wish that
The globalist have enough of
The public
Want to have vaccine
And and want to have social
But they have now
Twenty 30% they need
The beta test the social
Credit score
Work out the Kinks
And get it ready
Plandemic
He's been saying okay
This plandemic sending
But a new one
Coming soon one another
A virus pop
And he
DiCaprio in Olive
Show you
Coming out of the
Jungle Juice
The world
You're going to die of a noose
Super virus
Hamburger
Are you have a car
Are you at
Heating and Air
Vudu
Nelder cooking
This garbage
Open labs
Let me go to the most telling Dynamics they really indicates
To be that Alex's knowingly Fellowship
About pretty much everything you talked about is this selective ability to understand things are inter
Connected
Princeton's when it comes to bring up his conspiracies
Everything is connected
In far-flung Industries
In different countries living at different periods of time they're all working together for the same goal
Even more to the point he understands the trends can have an impact on other trends
For instance economies in the developing world wars and the impact of negative effect on the supply chain ultimate
Dab affect our economy
Alex gets this kind of interconnected
However when it comes to the relationship between deforestation and disease he pretends
Ensenada understand what people are talking
They're animals and he quoted jungles to use his term that we aren't in contact with him
When their habitats are destroyed some of them made migrate into where humans live
In some of these animals may carry diseases we've never encountered
Before and we may be super susceptible to
Pretty pretty simple under
Understand dynamic
Pretty well understood how
Climate change and the destruction of natural environment like Forest
Is closely associated with
Disease
This isn't even taking into consideration the dynamic we're like
Why she eating bacteria can only survive in warmer water is so as the temperature the oceans increase in your chance
Encountering it would go for a swim
Has going up
I do believe that our to be capable of understanding interconnect
Missing one instance and not in
In the other
It seems to me like a pathetic
Display of willful misrepresentation in order to misinform the audio
Also
I love
Bill Gates Leonardo Dicaprio and all of them
Don't you worry what a group Bill Gates and Leonardo DiCaprio simultaneously came out with all of them
NSAID
That f****** jungles man who are the rest of them
I mean I understand that Leonardo DiCaprio was like
Michael Shannon
Well I mean he's definitely in there
Probably
I spell Hamburglar buddy
How dare you
I think I know that Leonardo DiCaprio was involved
In that 77
07 concert
Worldwide Coronavirus
It's like a few times Leonardo DiCaprio has been like hey how about the environment maybe let's not
Destroy it on his giant f****** yacht
Bears
Yeah I don't know I guess he is
He's going to pretty soon be called Bill Gates Nuevo
Puppy gets into the council at 12:10
@aoc
All the Hollywood
Would trash like
Aforementioned
DiCaprio
Telling you
That it's imminent
They're almost all of us
Shuffle.
William Shatner
Gets off the spaceship
Few months ago
Thesis
Too bad everyone will be dead on the surface
44 fall right
They have let all these p
In on the depop
Hell they look
The public
They got walls
New York Times
Looking forward
To the end of
Humanity
Representation of what Shatner said
When you get back
I was overwhelmed with the experience
Sensation of looking at death and looking at life
And this you know what has become cliche over how we need to take care of the planet
But it's so fragile people say oh it's fragile no no no
There's this little tiny blue-skinned that is 50 miles wide and we pollute it and it's our means of
So I mean mischaracterization
Entitled look
Forward to the end of humanity wasn't about how we're cursing need to go
Piscifun misrepresentation Alex can make because he only engages with headlines and he likes to pretend that looking
Forwarded this case
He's like how a kid looks forward to a birthday party as opposed to looking
Forward in terms of thinking about the things in the future
The article itself is really mostly about how if the ability to download your brain into a robot does come over
Like that
There's a really good chance that it's only going to be available to people in the upper echelons of society and that's a nightmare
The last line of the pieces quote
Transhuman future in which mortality is optional may sound like paradise but if it come sooner for some of us than
Them for others
It could prove to be a dystopia
This is almost two-year-old opposite Alex only knows the headline of using to argue that the globalists are planning to
Wipe Out the population
It is just embarrassing
After the people saying they like a o c and Beto commenting on.
2018 ipcc report
And it was
Too much them saying that everyone's going to die
Princeton's aoc's comments were taken out of context
Just pointing out how the younger generation see governmental in action
Quotes
The world is going to end in 12 years if we don't address climate change
And your biggest issue is how we going to pay for it
You see what the account
The only person
I consistently see going on and on about how everyone is about to die is Alex Jones
What is in a bad mood we're all already dead
When he's in a decent mood
It's just people that got vaccinated they're going to be dead in the next few years and he's very sorry to have to report this music
He's the one doing The Sensational sheet music using folox sure
Nonsense I know you are but what am I
Is the end the end of humanity their Longview Lone Survivor
All the people on the left
Sensationalize
That's the main issue all of us Lone Survivor going to be real bummed out by their negative Nelly bulshit
I'm saying that's the problem
Yep
Yeah it's it's a
It's annoying
Yes that's what I would say
So course
Operation lockstep comes up and Alex lies about that document a little
But the good news is
If you read the Rockefeller build
They plan to have the
First phase lockdown
4 years
Then pull it off early
Bring it back
That is good news
This time after
2 years old
Form Soma Chiapas
Position
That attracts
Bring down their whole system
Getting off now
Again
Go away
And then they can move
Text weapon
Cyber attack
Sure
Telegrafi
That's why we've
Stay vigilant
Focus
That's why we've got a bra
Bring to Justice
All the liars
During this entire process
Like fauci
And others.
Purposely lied about the
Oh
Statistics are going to jail Alex
And his entire crew are all getting locked up
Jail people for lying about
Statistics are the people currently lying about statistics
Yes so then yeah
Decent almost cautious pick for him
There's a pretty high likelihood of something happening that he could portray the Cyber false flag
So his odds of getting to portray himself as a prophet
For just making a bland middle-of-the-road protection up pretty good here
Always growing
People are engaging with NF
Do you have that sort of thing these days leave the door wide open for something to happen on that front
What's the could wipe out a ton of money which I would call the Cyber false flag
If you could just call the drop in Bitcoin
Price if you if you really start digging into how big of a problem ransomware is starting to become a
It's like a little boy
These are all possibilities that would not need to be false
Oddities already
Primed the audience to experience that way
But it gets even more flimsy because we've played this game already
In February of last year Texas got hit by that massive winter storm that knocked out power to a lot of people
That was the result of poor oversight by the electric reliability Council of Texas or not
I am faulty infrastructure
Largely due to Texas's
Strong distaste for regulation it's a good thing that after that crisis happened they really mobilize
Regulations
Voluntarily pay for it out of the goodness of their hearts especially if they had downloaded their brain into an immortal cyber
They would
Really care a lot about you
That power crisis a cyber false flag
This is the kind of standards
He's going to need the claim that he's right about the
This prediction
Almost a non-existent
It's like a limbo bar the top of a doorway
There are really serious winter storms that have been happening
And are predicted to through the weekend in places like North
South Carolina
Much of South Texas is under a winter storm warning
The point is that their number places that aren't necessarily known for their tough winter weather that are looking at
Some challenges
And it may just be that another city loses power temporarily due to a snowstorm
I was just cyberpunks like prediction is attempt to get ahead of that possibility so he can profit off it
If it does come
Come to pass
That's all that's going on there
I mean I think my
My big
Biggest problem with all of these doomsday predictions is that
Quite simply due to the behaviors of
The far-right
Extreme weather events in destabilization are almost guaranteed so predict
Getting them now is
Is frustratingly easy like you guys made it so you could be right
Like everytime you predicted
Ship before you were wrong
Stabilize the world so much
Gold might be going up to levels that he was talking about
I don't know it's annoying
Down is, that's completely made up and what this lie is meant to do is convince the listeners that the actions taken by Alex in the
Anti-vax community
We're not only righteous
But they were also super effective
That's an attempt to one
Plane Victory and to
Solidify the argument that if Public Health measures are raised against than this kind of ridiculous responses exactly what everybody
Needs to do cuz it work this time
Yep I have time
How to make buddies were able to
Defeat the globalist in 2 years where is that
Globus plan was for obviously
How's the weather on the subject of how weak are these globalist
If their plan is either imprison the entire world or kill everyone off and they're doing it because they're beholding
Too literal Satan how does it make sense that they would back off because Alex and his friends were whining for a long time
God is behind their whining then
Nah
Handlebar liners who wind themselves
Because it's just
The made-up story that I was telling political decision
BYOB parties
Has a second
In the beginning of this piece
Prominently all
The only Solid Ground he really has to stand August Boris Johnson thing
But he has a second piece that comes up
It's very dumb
There's another
Short clip
The Bill Maher show
Dot-com
Showing a Libby
New York Times columnist
Coming out in
Calling to covid
Tyranny
Catastrophic
Moral
Slime
It was all a fraud
Is Barry Weiss going on Bill Maher show
Fairly certain I called her a fascist to someone she works with
I think her career trajectory
Has been such
That I would never call her a liberal
I wouldn't call her on the left
Oh no she was
Very essential in whitewashing and promoting
The
Quote-unquote intellectual dark web
Anti cancel culture University arrival
It's ridiculous
And if you really go through her columns in the New York Times I feel like she's an aspiring slave owner
You know like somebody is really going to work her ass on one of her co-workers is going to get mad at you.
We're going to care about what people on Bill Maher show say figure out why Alex likes to pretend
I don't know if I had to guess I would say it's because the show is
Like it's really intentionally iconoclastic and it's
Supposed to involve comedy
Sort of shore sometimes people say things that are B inflammatory or at least more so than you'd see on a regular news program
Because people speak so loosely at something
Versed is a joke Alex comments people make on their present them as if they're the gospel of the globalist
My best guess
Whatever the reason it's just such a bizarre inside trend on Alex's show where he thinks that the globalists are speaking
Cancer Bill Maher show
Except that Alex likes Manuel has been a secret Patriot this whole time
Man I can take it off
I think the thing about
Bill Maher show is that there are no relevant political late night shows
Anymore
Like it just doesn't
Exist and Bill Marek
Guess was relevant 20 years ago
So that's like a
Alex's mind is the last time something was relevant
Last time I watched it I was when I was 50
Righto maybe my memories are a little bit shaded but I
Seem to work all Politically Incorrect
Being like
At least a little bit more interesting than his current show
Maybe we were all just wrong cuz we didn't know
SNL was good when we were fifteen that happen
We both live through it yeah
Yeah it's it's strange
I don't I don't know
I just I'm so bored
Of pointing to a Bill Maher can't believe anybody still has the time 4
Who has the time for it so f****** watches that show
Tom Kenny
He's fine
So I was just like a I had a terrible Flash
You said Tom Kenny
Not because of anything about him
Because now I have to go through my mental Rolodex of like have I heard something bad
Storm the capitol
SpongeBob cause problems
I was looking around like I was on Twitter
Abducted
F****** 5 foot 10 and he's white dude from the 90s
3 of a great game you have it something I did
Tom Kenny
He's okay
He still good
Alex has been Vindicated
Predominately because Barry Weiss was talking s***
Yeah it was a lonely place
Months ago
It's been a rough process
Fastest route it but I knew
The Infowars axes
Information Warfare
Shock troops
Uproot
And it's our job to
Tell the hard facts
Upfront
Not popular
The public is it
Fort
Because if
We don't
Play out these hearts
Facts
Nobody else
That's why all of you
You watching all of you
Do you understand
Valuable
Infowars
In the last 2 years
Fighting with us
All the things
Shredder art
Spider videos
Had to share so many
Great Patriots in
Information
Joe Rogan coming out against it
Tucker Carlson coming out against it
Nothing about a year to get going on
Once I saw the facts
They did
Wow that is the most narcissistic thing I've heard since I watched that Barry Weiss
Clip
What is particularly interesting about this is this doesn't sound like somebody who thinks they're going to be gone in a in a month
Mother to preparing for some
Tamara.
That is true
Is it busy
If you still was in sort of a mindset of like
Doom is around the corner then it would be like
I will
I have been Vindicated in a pond I will write bye-bye
My tails on the wall in blood
He'll be something far more
I don't know h
Just it has it has a tone that's different from
Maybe some of his other previous
Works yeah I mean maybe just took a day off you needed a day off and now he's back in the playoff everyone
The family court
Brightwell
I don't know it does feel like he wants to lay some groundwork
And I don't like
No battery
Yeah that sucks
It's also if you kind of cut through the facade in that last clip what Alex is saying here is that he saved the World by state
Taking the Gap at forcing out the truth until it became acceptable
For other people to join him like Tucker and Joe Rogan who are apparently too cowardly to do so previously
Work for Alex
You would never have heard Barry Weiss go on Bill Maher and Tyson bulshit that's a win
Alex's pretending that he saved the world but nothing in the world is actually change
Other than Boris Johnson's decision in Barry White's one of Bill Maher's show and talk s***
That's all it behind Alex's navel-gazing about how he's a hero because he was into the anti-vax yet
Before it was cool
Save the world's trash he saved the world
The materials that Alex uses to make his argument this video are lies about statistics
Why is my block step documents
Some comments Barry Weiss made
Boris Johnson
A video of Robert Kennedy Jr
And a story about Aaron Rodgers
None of this means anything
That's not a great list
Snow
No no I wouldn't want that one on my like PhD thesis that wouldn't go well
We got some more lies about lockstep
Locke supplies
Globalist are the criminals
Or desperate because of
Nationalism
Trumpism
And populism
And people waking up
So
The Rockefeller Foundation always said nombre
Breaking lockstep
But they would launch
A virus cure
To bring in
The tyranny
The overnight doesn't mean
That
We're starting
So incredible
I was starting to win now yeah
And then we were all dying but we're heating up
How to make an all this s*** up about this Rockefeller document and it's so funny
You're wrong this time
You can hear this clip of the way that Alex tries to play non-committal with this s*** like your
Frustrated by
Victory but
Then I what nothing actually happens he runs the risk of his listeners being like hey you said the globalist are backing off
That's why he needs a reminder that there's a good chance that nothing is going to happen and things are still going to be bad but
While maybe a death
The flimsiness of the information that Alex is providing and the
Sort of ambivalence that you see
It was traded in this club
That's the things that kind of make me feel like what we're actually seeing is more just an indication of Alex's mood turning a little bit
Whitmore Manor
That's kind of the
The feeling
Yeah that's that's
All the News That's fit to print
A 7 out of 10 today
So
I think that it would be fair to
Special report after this point is
Is it pretty positive
Pretty much like
All the way
All the world are dropping their covid restrictions
That I know fills with white p
And even those aren't but they might as well
Sure
Oh
Because we're about 20 minutes at the report now
Cigarettes
Bring in the new system you got to crash
The old system
And the Davos group
IE the Bilderberg Group
Telegraphing
But that's their next phase
They're also telegraphing they're going to have carbon locked
Take down their virus
Dino folks are aware that stamps they're going to back off on that
Only launched a bunch of Nuit
As much good news is I gave you earlier
Quote you need to get ready
Prepared
To get right with God
You have a self-defense
Flan
Affordable food near that water
Oppression you have neighbors
And friends that are awake
You know what's going on
Gaba Mutual
Aid agreement
To take care of each other
With what's coming up
You'll need those neighbors for a source of food and Chase
Things go bad got to eat their ass is so f****** whiplash
Defeated the Great
We have defeated the bad guy
Worse things are happening at great man that cool
Thanks dude
I just think that this is that
Tizen release balance that we see with Alex all the time it's like a victory but not really cheap
Now that your hopes are up
Yeah it's emotional manipulation
But I will say I'm glad that Alex at least
Glad Alex says this I don't really care
Not when the offense
Violence
Arrest all of Congo
You could Fire by the just
You could change all the judges
But unless
We become aware of the globalist
The big Corporation
Manipulating our country against each other
Will never fix
Cities
Our counties are states back
Nations back
Take
We've got to take our
Our lives back
And then we have a chance
Beating this peacefully
Buy a global
Awakenings
The globalist
Regional conflict
Fights
And Civil War
Further destabilizing
Crash confidence in system
To go down all at once basic
To bring in their new
Global corporate governance
That's why they're racing the
Get there
Social credit score
Vaccine passport app Stan
Back is a new day
Such a great representation of had nothing Alex's means anything or even is internal consistency
He simultaneously saying they're replacing every member and Congress and every judge wouldn't fix anything.
But somehow the solution is a bizarrely vague notion of quote taking our cities or countries are states back our nation
What is he
Replacing every member of the government would do anything but instead what you have to do is gradually take back these government office
This is like what it what does it mean
It makes no sense unless you understand
Taking back our cities and states
It's something that's done outside of the electoral process
So that's a little
Fun subtle message corporations back most I think he just said that as part
His his thing but the more I think about it like Alex
What do you think that would look like right under your
A control a common
We need to nationalize the means of production
That was also says the globalists are racing to get their social credit score in place by way of vaccine passports
But this whole report was predicated on the idea that because of the massive push back to Alex's help Foster
All of these countries were simultaneously dropping all covid restrictions and backing off
These things are nonsensical right now but they're still holding them over your shoulders like
I'm going to get you
Alex's
Extemporaneous speech is full of contradict
Because details and reality honestly just don't matter to him
He's basically just trying to fuc
With the listeners feelings at this point
The only real point is making is once again
Trying to make sure that no one blames him for any possible right-wing anti-vax terrorism in the future
It's really strange Alex hasn't brought up that his former guests to the the head of the proud boys a militant arm
The Fraternal Order of the old night
Based Stickman AKA Kyle Chapman
Who recently arrested for allegedly attacking healthcare workers in Idaho
There's that other guy who attacked vaccination that vaccination site in California but that dude wasn't a regular passed gas 20
Alex knows that the level of tension is rising to a point where more attacks on vaccinations providers
It's not out of the question doesn't want to be in trouble when that does happen or could happen
He wants to be
Be able to profit off them
So that's how we Act
I wonder if I wonder if it if it is the Infowars office they have like a
Not March
Nesper like
Almost a ton
Do you know of like
Which of these people is going to go to jail and whomever is the last
SWAT man
You have that kind of a gambling pool
Based Stickman 4 payout odds
I didn't think that would be kind of a member of the. Of
What time when based Stickman was coming on Alex's show and I would turn it on
What is happening now it's like oh well basic man was
Provocateur
Lightning based stickman on your
What else do you have
You've got it you got it
Kevin's just smash it
I
It was a simpler time
Haha what those were the days
Was going to cover
They just give you the second Barry White's was to
Awakening
Victoria Secret Ed razek
Right now you're all going to die
So the second narrative is about
Russia and Ukraine
Third is about a prediction
But Alex has about winter
Season 3 big news story
Imma give you this this one pretty
Quick
Because
Alex's just saying with Russia and Ukraine
That no matter what happens Russia is the good guy
That leads me
Chili's
Horse right here
Giant palette
Billions of dollars
Semantics
Muscles
Anti-aircraft missiles
You name it
Delivered
Having put on the US state
Twitter website
Masses
Of us
And NATO troops
Forming all around the borders
Will Ukraine
Y'all telling you that Russia
What is eminently about
Invade
Reason Russia's building trips up
Is Lacey
The buildup of
The West
Russia doesn't have a history
Since the early 1980s
Strange Donuts
Hey
Can't argue with that
Alex phrasing things I lay is just because it's convenient for his narrative
Further the situation that we're seeing in Ukraine has been going on a while
I understand for 3rd 2021 The Washington Post reported on Russian troops to the Border Uke
Like it's really complicated I don't dig into it too deeply today but
The point I want to make is that it's very
Clear that Alex is presenting a distorted version of event
Nordby will sell his narrative that no matter what happens
Russian
It seems like a strange position for someone who's this
The staunch anti-communist but
It does make sense because Satan on the Democratic party those the real
Yeah
And yeah so like
I think he also is just piss
The people are talking about the potential of a false flag
It's really rude I read all about the government the United States government literally being like
They're going to launch his false-flag and I had to I felt like Alec
Places like you
Mayan
The globalist always
Convert a
Projector
They have the history
They have the motivate master
The troops first
So I would look for them
To attack Russia
Russian forces
Defend themselves
Order
And it said the Russian.
And now you have
Biden's
Election
Plan
Unified
Find a proxy war
With Russia
Like a necessary midterm strategy
Well I mean you don't want to lose
Control of conquer
So you should probably risk it all out total nuclear winter
Has essentially convinced himself in his preaching
That no matter what happens rushes The Vic
If Russia attacks it was because the globalist secretly attacked them first
Maybe the globalist ilapak Ukrainian forces to blame it on Russia but no matter what if hostilities break out
Alex is already determined that the globalist will pull the false flag
Based on nothing
Except his imaginary track record of the globalist bullying false flag
Let's be clear Alex's track record of accusing the globalist of pulling false flag
What is horrific
He's constantly wrong about pretty much everything he calls a false flag and I'm only saying pretty much
Because there's some situations where it's still unclear exactly what happen
And I'm just not going make a determination on it
Literally ever
Everything that happens or Alex imagines
Is going to happen is a globalist Volkswagen then
Never actually is
It's all in his head
It's a way for him to preserve his worldview when reality
Constantly proving him wrong
Let's just
That's that
Blanket denial of reality wasn't the missing Malaysian plane a false flag
That was something I say it was
I do know that he said it was but I couldn't remember the exact specifics of it so I decided I wasn't going to bring it up again
Yeah Everything is Everything is Everything
Local things even
I don't know
The designation of a park
The false flag
That's the global is trying to take over public land coffee place was a false flag
Oh yeah that was the communist
But whatever
That's about it. Russia butt
He's got some insane lies
About that last year's
Storm that hit Texas
And it hits really close
Is that of Dallas-Fort Worth
Cbslocal
And this is my frustration a year ago at this time
Almost a year ago
6 days before a giant
Blue northern
Polar vortex
The
National Weather Service say Noah
Toltecs
You're going to have
Serious
Freezing temp
And you better get
Power output
What up
Power usage
Before the blizzard
Send message
Dubai the ministration
Early February
We need author
Possession
Turn up
Are gas plants
Anarcho plants
Because the solar
Plants and
Windmills
Will not delivering
Power
The Federal
Refused
The emerge
Agency authorization
Under law
You got to get authorization
And pay millions of damn fine
Or you go to prison
You get indicted
Completely made up story about what happened to cause the storm to be so bad in a power outage
Images of severe last year
And it's painfully obvious has come up with
His piece of fiction to explain thing
The problem was largely based on the Texas power grid was separate from the National Grid
Because they wanted to evade Federal Regulation and oversight
Since our power is supplied and operated by deregulated private
Maximize their profits and that meant cutting corners
And things like weather protections for stuff like ice storms which are on
Common insects
There was a big dealer back in 2011 and it caused a bunch of blackout
What's after which it was recommended that precautions be taken in case this happened again
It's all on regulated
There wasn't any mechanism to force anybody to take these precautions
So they didn't
When the 2021 winter storm hit their power sources were ill-equipped to operate in freezing conditions
And this caused the wattage output to go down
The problem is the fact that the state's power grid is disconnected from other states which are on the Federal
Because of that it was really hard to redirect power from
From other operating grades
Into Texas is Grit
This is a complete failure of Alex's political and institutional ideology
The power grid was run exactly how he go to wanted it to be
Consequences
Blizzard that left hundreds dead
Because billions and damage
I was just a coward and he can't accept the things he Advocate cause this power failure
So he has to make up a fun story where exactly the federal government sabotaging Texas but not allowing them to produce nearby
True this is really sad
Yeah
Here I was
11/2
Reading the actual state of Texas state
About lettuce
Turn up power on
Said said no
They would even let text
Just pay the fine
Alex is reporting of this letter was
He was saying that Scott sent a letter to the Department of energy and they denied their request to be able to produce more power
Alex to report in a piece that he posted last February 20th
But acting Department of energy secretary David huisenga had actually accepted
And approved our tots request
6 days prior on February 4th
I want you making s*** up back then
Please continue to now because he's an a******
I realized about the world in order to make it fit is it
Extremist ideology
Nothing more is going on here there's no way to admit that it's your fault
Will be a fascist unregulated
Pro f****** capitalism as fascist
You can't look at that and be like oh
Well maybe we should accept other points of view
Sure
We got like this
Alex's b******* about last
And now there's winter storms
Who's that are threatening in Texas
Forecast
Answer this is hot on Alex's mind again
A story that he's totally wrong about
In the media
A year ago wouldn't tell the truth will they tell the truth now
Eureka
Kermit 25 Texas power plant
Headline should be
Power company told by said they can't operate during storm
Not true
Really false interpretation of the story about Texas pipeline
Give me the breakdown
This was about a company called Energy Transfer LP having a financial dispute with the company that runs these
Buy Power Plant
Vista Corp
They racked up a huge bill from the storm last year in that transfer was threatening to cut off the gas to the power plant
Appealed to the Railroad Commission to step in and say that they can't do that
Particularly during the winter since I will be Danger
20th
2 days before Alex's recording this special report
Energy transfer had withdrawn their threat which
Should I kick the can down the road
The financial dispute is still there but the gas is going to keep flowing
Anyway this is nothing to do with the federal government telling people they can't make more energy that is
Completely made up by Alex and has nothing
Things to do with the story
Seems more like Vista Corp
Just doesn't want to pay the bill
But also they were the position where bills were made
Considerably higher because of
I don't know you like all the price gouging I mean that's kind of that you could
Except that you f***** up
Or you could just tell people you're not going to
I always think
I think that in this
Instance
I guess if you're like a real
Market
State person you'd be like well they have a bill and people are asked
So they're the wrong
You could also look at it be like what this company that supplying the gas is like this is
Kind of lighting
Extortion
Absolutely cuz it's not
Power plants that suffer it's the
Customers that their power plants
Everybody over
Anyway the points
To is that like
I was just totally wrong about what the
The story is about easing baking up a federal government line in it
And then he's also
Not telling his audience that it has been resolved
Two days prior even relevant by the
It was there's a headline
You got a headline so f****** just cuz
It doesn't mean anything anymore doesn't mean you don't have the headline
The article
Dismal
When you go read the article
It's the truth
And they say oh yeah
They're not given emergency Opera
PlayStation
Feds
Are ordering it
Turn off
It goes on
The pipeline company emergency transfer LP
Run by Dallas billionaire
Kelly Warren
Women that needs to pay 21 million in penalties
Barber Supply
Play phrase
Knocked off gas pipeline
Dominion power outages
You let Benny text
The dark for days
On the state was experiencing on
Usually frigid temperature
Then it goes on to say they're not going to pay him again
So
I'm explain again
The feds
Don't
Let you
Turn the power on
21 million 25 million
Find Power Magazine
Operate
That's what's going on
That's WhatsApp
Can we live in Idiocracy
The 21 million figure that Alex is siding isn't government finds
The amount of energy transfer was demanding that Luminate which is a subsidiary of Vista vistro
Hey if they wanted to continue bumper
It's nothing to be paid notifying from the federal government
Even as Alex's reading as you can tell that he's struggling to make this fit his narrative science it's another
Company that's run by an oil billionaire who's demanding payment not the government
He's going through you can
Hear his mind trying to insert words
Flag
You just want to sit there be like Alex you realize that what else what you read
The government was not mentioned
And it explains the money it was all in there that you read
Could you read out loud billionaire as though that was the good guy in the story
And it's dead
I don't understand how he expects
It's that to not be like the most embarrassing read
Imaginable
This is a story that I was reporting based entirely on making s*** up because the reality of the situation is actually
Scathing indictment of capitalism a deregulation
He can't deal with that so instead
Puppy story to report to the audience cuz it's more fun
Hey let's be Escapist
Hiding this
Oh the Infowars tip of the spear we're fighting the big fight
We're trying about headlines oil Baron says what am I supposed to be slightly less of a billionaire
The winner of this story
This is why it's really frustrating that Alex
And this
Report on like a really
Condescending
Just remember
Powers out
Blackout
The government
Has blocked us
Carbon is evil when you're very body
Made out of carbon
All right here's the final
I appreciate you all watching
Ridiculous
So
Yeah he's he's decided that the government is blocked all carbon
Yes
I need to explain something to the left
All right and that is that if you are made of both
Carbon
Nitrogen
Hydrogen oxygen
All of those things you can cram into your body in whatever
Ratio that you desire
Take a bunch of nitrogen
Crannet right in your body
Only the left would think that is a bad idea
To cram nitrogen into your body
Cuz they're dumb
Totally
Totally dumb
A protects from
So I think the Saturday report was coming
Disappoints
The Ventura stairs
I do think that Alex is trying to bail on
Some of the covid stuff in order to move on to something else
Like this cyber threats or
Oh you know spending less
Time of this
Special Report on covid-19 on
Ukraine and weather storms is a good sign right now he's spent way more time on timer
Goddamn
What do you spend more time on it in the sense of life
Declare Victory and all these governments are afraid of him isn't
You know they come with a cyber-attack which I guess
Ukraine
But I guess I were to act like isn't included in the things that they're afraid of from Alex and his Awakening Buddies
You'd think that they would just not pull anything
Right
Little holes in the defensive Auntie back
Text people's you know like
Next thing is going to be too many horses
And they're going to be like we got to have a lockdown from all these f****** horses everywhere
Yeah this is all dump
I am interested to see what happens when
Alex is back
Can Studios going to be back to his old bullshiter
Tubi
I assume that will be happening within the next week
I think that he needed
I think you needed to feel good and so this is the way he
You know he did it by lying about Boris Johnson
Some s*** and then
He got it out of his system and then decided to scare people more at the end
Little bit enviable
Sometimes you need a win
You know sometimes you just need one and sometimes you don't get one but imagine if you when you needed one
You could just say you got one and that was
Exact
That's amazing that's a superpower
Yeah yeah we should all be so lucky
Just declare win right now we've won we've defeated Infowars forever
With this episode we one we've pushed them back we did it we put some back in town
Well you obviously in the meantime
Go to bed Jordan
But until then I'm needle I'm Leo MDX blarcom
And now here comes
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work