Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
College vype.com
Alex Emerick on the ongoing adventures of
Dream swirling
Yeah I what will get there
What's up
My bright spot today is bright spot of anger
The anger is that no one told me about a thing existing before
And I stumbled across it and now it's all I want to do
I found that on YouTube
There are a bunch of channels
That are just like
Estate set up a camera and animals show up
Fat bear week like 10 years but I thought that was
The special event no man realize that there were these cameras that you could just watch
Live all the time in desert and it's a watering hole
About 5 minutes I'm watching the civics or Ibex whatever to pronounce that
Drink from this Watering Hole like this is fascinating
Big showed up sitting alone in the apartment I cheer
The appearance of another animal I'm telling you right now you can get so many camera
Letter just 24/7 on a nest with eggs in there
And it is yours I do I don't want that that's too much like tension entire life just sitting
I don't want I don't want to be like waiting for the egg to hatch or something like that that's too high stakes
But watching the world
I like that you are in some sense digitally retreating to the wilderness
Like you can't go and move into the middle of the woods but you can through the vision of a desire is been there
This is the only way that I can manifest it look at that guy
It's all about you what your partner is a teacher
And that means that right around teacher
This time of year
All of the Girl Scouts circle like vultures on week teachers
Ready to pounce
You do your part right right so despite the fact that I'm sure it's in some way some sort of evil cartel the girl
Girl Scouts
A s*** ton of boxes awesome
Of our order still open I'm pretty sure I might need you to put in an order for me
I've got some okay by the second hand
Super intent to distribute boxes we have Samoa
Tagalog Tagalog
I've had my fill of those
You don't want to know okay that is a pretty bracelet
Look I like sweets
Say that I like sweets when times are tough
What things are good
I'm so Jordan today we have an episode to go over that is being log into works and
We've teased this a little bit but not very specifically
Things like I've mentioned that I have some side things I'm working on
Things like when beginning of December
We had to pass nobody yes
And with all the become clear
Ion today's episode
Looks like a little moment to say thank you and hello doesn't do walks
The first of the revs Lang thank you so much
The reverend's Lange properties maybe I'm not sure
We have Jordan thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk me up
But we also do have a couple of technocrats in the back
Sorry Adam
Made me give more money to Dan and Jordan because bear won't stop howling about globalist
I'm a policy wonk I have risen above
Miami star
Go take a little break you down
A list for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order and f*** the horse you rode in on and all your s***
Maybe the next few moments broadcast
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow he may be
So thank you all very very much so Jordan we have some breaking news
Who's in the world of Alex and recording this here on Tuesday of
Pressing issues that we talked about on Friday
We
Have for you today
An episode where we will be discussing some depositions from Alex's San Diego case
And I felt like you know if we're going to be talking about this we should probably check in
Discuss how all this came about circumstances
Conversation
With Mark Langston
Well joining us here in the virtual podcast
Over Zoom
Did she like the honeycomb hideout there was such a good man that the Bishop Don Magic Juan
We're off track
Joining us here in the honeycomb hideout
Aziz lead counsel for the plaintiffs and the Sandy Hook
Lawsuits against Alex Jones
Mike Baxter welcome back
I'm not using the name
That's fine so frankly there's a no boys allowed policy
I can respect the rules
So welcome I we wanted to do a little preface to this episode because it's
Monumentous occasion I think it's stitches is how I would describe it
Some would say narrative twist
In things and so
What are you taking away into the present to give us give us the lowdown on what's up here
Regular listeners now
I've been following the podcast for a little while now
And they've been doing some analysis of our lawsuits and in such intoxicating
And talk to these wacky gentleman
And I had become sort of I guess you could say over the course of Lost
Peripherally aware
Of the workout
Snitch
Sometimes
You know mainstream media is even I see profiles
In Fairly
Publication describing
The unparalleled
You talk about the grey lady
But you got to take that with a grain of salt to do the same thing newspaper
Iraq
Play Store
I went ahead and checked it out and
Darn this guy really does know a lot about Alex Jones
And I was
Me and my partner Bill actually had to do that
And so we watched
Instead of a couple weeks and
They probably flew by
Time flies when your brain is melting
And then I knew
Not
Tribulus
Facts on my my brain in perception of the world
So I guess I was so excited to meet you
Who's been living in this
Damn do a hell of a lot about Alex Jones
Judgment
Discovery
Which is about the plaintiff
They were harmed by some of this condo
I'm in NS required to take us
Corporate
Alex Jones
And in doing so
I knew that I could use
Dance
In this process
So that's why I reached out to Danone sa Dan would you consult on this case
Ann and Dan said you know what I I'd be happy to do that
Recharge
Completely pro bono
In my defense I said no
I think you're right
The way you're saying this is like
You asked and I said yes and I don't think that's exactly accurate I struggled with the decision
Because of the
The potential ethical implications of like doing this podcast
And like inserting myself
In some way
You know I would never I would never want to put somebody in your position who's a commentator and a person who has collected knowledge on chosen this way
In the position of testifying at trial or being a witness to jury would ever hear from
What happened
You can tell I from here to screaming
And I think you know
Certainly
You can so fun cases like this
Provide
Some of them do charge
And that would have been totally above board to do but but I really
You know II
Is it a lot
I mean I'm not I'm not going to
Definitely
Really appreciate it
I love the Jets
You say nothing
Pro bono but I don't want to put you on a pedestal because so many people
Unrivaled in my career
People will step out of the woodwork
I'm happy
You whenever I can
And so yeah damn Dance come aboard and has been helping me quite a bit
In terms of doing this case
And one of the big surprise for
Is that damn
Personally accompanied me
As my consultant
Of the
Corporate representative
And if mr.
Yeah so your humble narrator
Not more than
Or feet
Across the table
Johnson South Bend
Representative
And I want to be clear just be in case anybody has any kind of misgivings
I did not interact with them
In any way
Rick
I was a silent
Person in the room
And I've had no contact with them outside of the room
So it's not like I shook Alex's hand or like
The reason I said no initially cuz I was slightly worried for your physical safety to be in the same
Camera with Alex Jones
Peoples guts in like a good old Teddy will get to that later
Sandworm
You know already dammit
Helping me formula
A person who can put his finger on Spa
I know I know
Is it true you need to ask
What
So your service is really
I really want
There's there aren't
Alex Jones for as much of a phenomenon as he is
And for
Culturally
Influential
He remains relatively understudy
Both in
McKennan Park
Actually
Strange how much
Mythos
Is
Very shallow
People don't really dig down
Into that was
That that was really really valuable
Irishman
It's overwhelming and thank you for
For the kind words I don't know I'm surprised that when
You came back you didn't report to me how invaluable your work was you kind of downplayed it which is not like you at all
Till you come back boastful like it weren't for me this whole thing would have fallen apart that's you
You right I got the flashing it's out of my system before I went cuz I bought a new suit
That was that was kind of my way of like a little
Walk around with something
Where do you where we got you a suit there was an adventure for the both of us
Let me tell you what's up well
Not great and I get dirty real fast
I clean up okay
Talked about
Before you had decided to help me and consult with me on this
Is that if you were going to be
Offering me advice
Singing some of the proceedings
You know
Part of your in system Quizlet
What you doing I need to be able to continue to do that about
And if you were an expert witness
You probably shouldn't be doing
Right because eventually your testimonies going to have to
Yeah but if you're just
And when it comes to things that are in the pub
I couldn't stop you if I were
You have a First Amendment right
Going on
What was the 1st Amendment
Take that Mark you can't stop us even if you f****** wanted to
Creative right you know
We'll never know.
It's it's
And I knew for instance
Deposition
If they did the
Public record would be
Be part of that and what happened
So that your listeners understand
There's a protective order of confidentiality in the case
And it provides a process
What's by whichever party
Give testimony
It provides them in half
Do that
And in this
Much as they have
Chose not to
So very
The deposition of Alex Jones
Cast into the public domain when they became on challenge
Filing
In this case
And so there's been seduced
Documents
In those depositions already
Uninstall that's not my public record
So now
You're a little bit about it
Talk to you about
MMA I want to stress to that like
It's
I can't
What are the downsides of me
Like being in the position of like doing this episode and being there sure is that
Obviously I experienced things
Some of those things I can't talk about
Because
They are
Part of what is in the public record there will you know there will be a lot of things that
I'm not really material to the analysis of the depositions themselves
You know I have
You know some thoughts
If you wanted to you you couldn't even talk about
The mutated
Second human being coming out of his chest
Kawato I believe was his name I told you that in confidence you can't talk about
Kuato okay that's my
Bi-polar Jordans
Oh my gosh
That's kind of
Not not for you because you know.
But but so that the audience understands how you're talking to
There are some brown
That that Dad has to observe when talking about these things
I want to that is that
Because his
Consulting position gives them access to things that do not become public
There there something to eat
Like conversations we had in between breaks and stuff like that obviously
Everybody's actually
Do you know you the things that you go into a deposition room
And in 90% of what
On the record videotape Rollin there's a transcript
10% of that downtime is off-the-record there things that happened there 2 off the Record
Obviously anything off.
But now we're
Where
Made
Call the mother corporate names
Just the irony
But the fact
The choice
Hours that came to be
Not make these
I am very
I believe
Those people who are following this case
You understand
There is a lot of enlightening
Information
Yeah do you speak
I'm glad then
What are the wonderful person I process
Is that when things do get into the public record this way
That Court proceedings can be critically discussed
And that's something I'm goddamn
But yeah there aren't there are certain
No, too
I probably had to close out probably edited out
But yeah it's like if you asked me what Alex smells like I'll have to cut that up
Likely
Freshly done laundry in the spring of Normandy
No none of that kind of the thing is is
Dengar
Inside baseball process
Legal proceeding that a lot of people don't normally get
Cuz I spy testimony but it's not in a courtroom
You know we were we were in a friend of mine's law office
I'm in
You know you're in this very
Where you at
Videographer in the room
Reporters
Taking everything down you got all your pairs of lawyers in the room and you got the witness
And you're all in this this room together
Jennifer
What are these depositions I think when is long as I-5
Yeah yeah the corporate representative going with Dario was
Most of the day
Yeah yeah it was very
But I'm actually you know the thing is we've we've talked about these depositions
And in the course of caulking for consulting firms
That's all
And I'm actually
He's become a little more public
Hear what people's reaction
Brodersen
Yeah cuz unlike I think
Jones's first step
The first corporate representative
Which was very shallow and very guarded and very mockery
I mean it was just a kind of a farce
I think this is a farce in its own way
Slightly different farts
Yes
Comedy of errors
We We All Electronics know that we recently
I brought a motion for sanctions
Based on the scoreboard
I want with Daria
With Daria correct in and that was because
They had been ordered four times
Give a corporate deposition in the course of these cases
The first 25 digits in Show
And in the second space it robbed
SpongeBob do
Oblivious to the fact
That the wall required him to
Repairing anyway
I think what you meant to say was I f****** Legend
Yeah that's going to go down in history as making one of the greatest episodes of all time
Call Rob the Sharpshooter
They also tune engineering
Friday in Ni naar judges straight
It was a
An offense
Deposition
Daddario
Yes exactly in the wake of an already
Offensive
Depositions from robbed
To get your act together for this they still haven't
But we recently brought that motion Friday
They were sanctioned
And I want to stay the
This is now
Open find
Before ever actually have
Pretty wild
And so we're still trying to see what the full fall out of all that is going to be
But yeah this did this did not go well
It's it's all you know it's disappointed when I showed up in Austin
Because you'd only told me there was a corporate representative I didn't know who was going to be
I was really excited for the possibility that we get another round with two I thought that would be a lot of fun
I meant learning that I was going to be Dario's like man she might
Be competent
The best
I thought it was so interesting and we'll get into this like in more by new detail in the course of the episode but
It's Robert Jewish but in a very different way
It's beautiful yeah it's
Yeah it's it's really interests
Yes
Like I say
That's why I'm glad it
I think this was I want to say this for the audience's benefit I think this was one of the
More difficult things
That I've had to do first of all to not talk about this beginning of December
Was when I came down to Austin and not being able to mention it or not being able to
Be like
All the information that I had that was in those depositions I had to not know
That was hard for you but that's easy for you I didn't say anything which is the real feel
F****** accomplishment that's what I want to get across here
Somehow I didn't break
Who you going to tell your dog
It was really challenging and
I'm glad that you know we're on the other side of it now because it is a bit of a relief
And then the second
The Second Challenge was really like
Questioning prior to agreeing to come down
Whether or not this was
An instance of
I'd like sort of affecting the content of the thing recovery
Really wrestled with that and I struggled with that question cuz it's been something that we
A policy that we've tried to maintain
As it relates to
Alex's show people to call in
They showed to f*** with him in order for us to cover it on the show
I felt like this was important enough of a thing to do
It's a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
I need anything I can do to help
The families is something that the
Is
More important than our show evil
So
Therapist that and also it wouldn't have the same
Actual
Presentation is someone prank calling him
This was assisting in
These are questions that may be fruitful to ask this is Beazer ideas to you know
The check in on
I think that is materially different then
The way that we
Haddock non-engagement
In the past but I think it's on the right side of it
This case is so different than most forms of litigation because of its subject matter
That when you might need for instance an expert on
You know
Pipe metallurgy
Plant explode
There's no chance of that same person is going to be critical to
Critically covering
In the media are you're right that's not a thing
What was interesting about this cases when you're in this kind of media litigate
The only people in this country who are genuine Bonafide X
Rapunzel are those who how
All of this media career any gayson
And in our our first
Sabine bruchmann Kowski
Who is the managing editor of Snopes
And and she had
I feel like she sort of a modern-day Cassandra of she was saying in 22
Here's what fake news
The same sort of discussion of
Weather
There is this
Scientist that says
The subject of your inquiry should be kept in isolation and you even your you you shouldn't let your interactions with their effect
Observation
Right when there's beat the idea that Brooke had the entire play
Critically government
About
Is because
Danger
Apartment
And therefore to offer that X
Batista people were trying to vindicate that the court of all is
Is a noble cause
And that's why I asked
That's a different type of
It's so strange
I think it makes it very difficult for people in your position to ever testify
I could be impeached as a witness so easily based on 100 things I said on my pocket
I mean it doesn't just know exactly I'll stand by everything I've ever seen
I think I screamed at you about the alien phones getting pregnant
Linda Pugh playing on the stand no good
Nearby Jordan on the witness stand and I'm thinking bad loan Order episodes left it was just shaking
Let's go
No that's not nice
I would be far more clever you do the scene from the critic
Oh yeah
Sister gives me gas
Alright Darius Gilroy
We had to go to Academia
Ride Like the people were far out
Great Hulu
Who kind of Buicks
And as much as they
Study his effects
Nobody
In this country has studied.
Internal mechanic
Infowars workout stories works out
Process work
Nobody said
I mean it's just
There's nobody who's in ended
It's weird that there was this vacuum that when people saw what you were doing the reason it was so well-received
I need for that
Nobody has started
So that's
And I'm going to jump out the window
See I thought I thought the way it worked was
If you're fighting against Godzilla you don't go to like a regular old army or whatever you have to get Mom
Night so if you're going to depose Alex Jones you can't just go with some X
Somewhere at a goddamn University
Weather for King Ghidorah
You can beat King Ghidorah
This might surprise you Jordan but my my
Litigation
Strategy has not been mostly informed by 1960s rko'd
Tokyo pictures
With monster movies
We had some different choices
Godzilla did not immediate
Then I guess we have some differences of opinion cannot be resolved
What time I think I think Mark strategy probably speaks for itself
Movie
Well I I want to say thanks for inviting me to to do this and also thanks for
Coming to do this
A little intro piece
I think it's important to
You know recognize some of the
McCants
Of what's going to come up
Headlight laying the ground rules is important
Oh and I don't think I could have explained how this was made public record I don't know if I fully understood it
Here's the best part
Angry with that
Advantageous
Saint 14
You know it is if that's where they stand they want to let it all be
Beginning you know we've had
Revive documentary
We we have HBO's filming everything
And they've been
Receptive to that
Nobody has even asked for a gag order
Because God would Jones's say
I mean if you just if you just turn on
Why what's up
So it's advice counterbalance that
With a with a good thorough
And None Shall
I'm glad you're going to
Well
Awesome I think I think on that note if unless you have anything else to add we should get to that
Thorough thorough
Thank you for a
The setup here so I was there
You were there
I like considered the the idea of like just going over these and not mentioning that I
Mario little
These depositions are a my name is
Real air of impropriety that I would have covered them and not brought that up
A show about us with a host dedicated as to find the transcripts from this.
Position to discover that you were there
Today what we're going to be doing is we're going to be going over
The deposition is the corporate representative
Daria Alex's assistant
What other.
Very mysterious person in the world of Infowars and now we get to
About 6 hours
Position is Alex
And we were going to be going over Alex's first and then darya's for service structural reasons
And Jordan has an out-of-context drop from Alex's deposition
Parker Banks
You know who that is
No liar to be alive
Big sis dare he
Alex knows damn well who Jar Jar Binks is
Deposition Bart is bringing up some of the talking about Sandy Hook stop at Alex
Gave it his response
I'm to the general question
When things you just talked about is that you have since this lawsuit
Started
You said some things about
I said things about
Organizations in groups that want to get rid of the First Amendment trying to use me as a case to do it
Okay well I what I'm really talking about is you said things about Sandy Hook
Self-correct
I have I have talked about
About the coverage surrounding it in a lawsuit sand
That ongoing process
Well actually want to ask you about a little something else
What what
Every second one thing that you have said a few times
Is that in terms of when you did
Say that Sandy Hook was completely
Fake synthetic
They're actors
Xcetera
You said that you've apologized
Correct
Well first off I said I can see how people see that and I also when people said
Please apologize. And I seen some of the anomalies that I think we're
Wrong
People requesting online
I'm sorry for
For questioning up Sandy Hook but it wasn't intended
False wait
I really thought maybe it didn't happen
And then
Intensified
And people
Being falsely saying that I was
Currently saying those things and then exaggerating when I said
As away as a political weapon that Hillary Clinton was using
To beat me over the head with it
In 2016 on record run
National
Against me
Play edited types of me
Talking about Sandy Hook
First of all injection Don responsive
A couple moments
Now there's an objection of not responsive cuz you just rambling about the first of all first of all
You talked about Sandy Hook itself after you've been sued
Hillary
No question
A couple times where it's just like
It's a it's out it's outrageous
Mark will have to ask between Alex and sometimes like you know what question
And there is
Slight confusion
And so
You know the question then comes up of like
You're saying this is your you're
Understanding of how you covered Sandy Hook and then
We're going to be able to play for the jury
The opposite this is why should they not see you as a liar
Good question is where Alex goes with that
First of all non-responsive
Second of all
You mr. Jones you understand this jury is going to watch the videos
Of Usain unequivocally not I see how people
Unequivocally
Sing Sandy hooker
You don't get to interrupt
You understand that sir
You're here to answer questions
For this jury
And I want you to listen to the quest
You know this jury's going to watch
Videos
Of Usain multiple-time
Over and over again
Sandy Hook is completely fake
Completely synthetic
It is not
Real
Right and you're going to sit here in this chair and say oh actually what I said
Actually what I said is I could see how some other
Could think it was fake
You know the jury's going to see those videos
And you know they're going to hear your words
Do you think the
Seriously whatsoever when they
Things you said
Dino
I know that the jury is going to say I always heard that
People are innocent until proven guilty not guilty until proven guilty they choose that the systems actually scared for me to pay
Truth is deep down
I have still have real questions about Sandy hook him up with your mom
And the CIA visiting Adam anthem for half of the FBI's I was in an entry news
And just all the bizarreness that went on
The public still has real question just like it about jussie Smollett
A baby that never actually die or wmds in Iraq
Or just you the Gulf of Tonkin or operation Northwoods
Or Bubba Wallace or or
You're so many of these things have happened most of these hate crimes and type things end up
Being false flag so I still
When I look at events question and say could this could this be staged we look for telltale signs what does that mean
Means that he is going to take some lettuce and cheese and put it between two big slices
Is a chicken called a sandwich
So we'd like response to this question because
What are you trying to say is that events sometimes or suspicious
His list baby he doesn't understand the conversation
People didn't think that the Roe v Wade baby was dead
That's the whole point of the storylines that is kind of a big dog
Beginning of December in this deposition recently
I'm pretty sure he still thinks the rovi way baby was d.b. Cooper though so I think he does believe that
That is if everything is connected
And then
You have the Gulf of Tonkin
The wmds in Iraq is in the same conversation as Jesse small
Wallet and Bubba Wallace racially-based
Antagonistic narrative I don't I don't know if Bubba Wallace's situation with the NASCAR
Garage is on the scale of lying about weapons of mass destruction would say there is
I would also say that now in the deposition for damage
Address for the case you've already lost
Not the best time to say I still have questions about the screens move
Cute easy giving these examples when he's liking all of these hate crimes end up being staged or whatever that
Are you compare Sandy Hook a hate-crime to you is that is
Is this the connective tissue it makes no sense it's just I mean all crimes
Involve hate
So aren't all hate crimes crimes and crimes
Strange tactic that's being deployed and I would advise against it
I'm loving it so far we're two clips in I think he's going to win this thing there is
To be a friend of like you're describing is doubling down
Why not it's really that me we've already lost
Yeah so Mark kind of pushes on that that angle
Mr. Jones
Video of you
Because of
Question that
Female synthetic everything is
Opportunity
So now you're back
Your audience
No that's
That I'm proud of the video and I'm proud of my statement in this full context
They will love to ride a sassy line
American traditional challenge authority
Turn out to be
Okay I will be Vindicated
Marks of at you can hear Mark smiling you can hear her laugh
A couple times to Jerry's ejacular nature
Going on here
This this is a good this seems to be a good line of questioning
Preceded like you lost this case by default right now you're back to suggesting the Sandy Hook was fake
There's probably no consequences
Push down a little
Please keep that promise
Okay but second
What has happened here
Is now that
You got beaten Court
Now that it has been granted. I didn't get beaten Court
Organized crime syndicate
Default has been granted
Pretend anymore.
That's what's going on
I know that's not what's happened.
They definitely sanction
With all the stuff we produced
I believe is a fraud
Because they're scared
I want to tell Jerry that this man is guilty now you decide how guilty no generators
Josiah
If someone is guilty or not
. not how guilty they are
You got can try to do
All your antifreeze Peak stuff
All you're doing is waking up America
There's a real Trend here the beginning of the deposition of like
A bit of going back and forth
Let's have a little bit of getting us out of the system,
Actual solid questions and like pieces of evidence
On the back but it almost feels like let's let's warm up a little with
Alex wants to do that a little bit
He gets he gets to throwing out stuff like but people do have questions I'm proud of this state
I meant that maybe I actually was right when I used to
Down out of the way I'm up top will get all the
100% anybody celebrating anything yes absolutely
All you're doing is waking up emergency
Alright so let's just be honest about what this is
You got mad after you got defaulted and you lashed out by saying that Sandy Hook was fake again that's what
No
I have privately
Call Mike ruane.
I said I really have real pleasure
Truth about this
I can't 100% prove it was
Totally staged
But the CIA was definitely involved
And
And that came out and then I was
I was told again
By high-level folks in the CIA that it was stage back in the time
That's why I went with them and also with Wolfgang halbig said
And other so I really believe that that that that that she looked at
I'm going to guess the CIA prison Alex's referring to my Beastie pechanec actual real source
I'm so
Sure that came up
I necessarily and episodes that we've done
The CIA wasn't involved in the shooting but when the FBI released the redacted reports of the effects defecation it include
Interviews with people who knew Adam Lanza and his mother
There's one interview that they conducted with the person whose name is redacted which was filed in a report that was dated December 16th
This was a friend of Lanza's mother Nancy who had her over to the house periodically
Quote what Adam Lanza was in 9th grade Nancy told redacted into a government computer system
Adam had made it through the second level of security and when he tried to breach the third level the screen went black in the authorities
Showed up Atlanta's door at 36 Yogananda Street
Nancy believe that the authorities that showed up at her door were either the FBI or CIA
Nancy had to convince the authorities that her son was just very intelligent
I was challenging self to see if he could hack into a government system
If you consider this an illogical picture of that full interview it's fairly clear that this was not a reliable assessment that Nancy was
Making then that's where the CIA comes from its Nancy saying that these people were CIA that showed up
What event that's described in this interview involves that friend leaving invitations to a dinner party and all the neighbors mail by
Nancy never rsvp'd so this person asked why
Nancy said it was closed because there was no return address on the envelope
She had thought there was a ax in it
This is what I was using as a foundation of his assertion that the CIA was involved in the Sandy Hook shooting
He's spinning conspiracy theories about the shooting wow Underoath in the deposition where he's being sued for things relay
Spinning of conspiracy theories about the shooting
Just seems like you can't stop
Like it's this I don't I don't even know why you would do this
That works in an argument setting like if you're arguing with somebody on a podcast or like
Piers Morgan or this is a great strategy to use but
I don't know about in court yeah I'm already at through the deposition as soap
So far I'm like okay
He is clearly established that learning is not a possibility
You know what I mean like it's not going to stop I think it's probably learning is counter to his business model and could probably would have been a
Maladaptive
Strategy
Early on
Which to me says that if I'm if I'm like
Hey
Here's how we punish this guy if you wanted to stop
You have to bankrupt him
That's the reality of it cuz he's not going to stop he's or and if he's if he does stop for the Sandy Hook family
It's just going to go somewhere else and he's not going to learn from the behavior cuz in the depositions for the pager he's already lost
Yeah it does feel a bit like
That's that's your purse
Alex is pretty mad because he has been defaulted and he's lost these cases by default he believes
She's complied with everything
That's been requested of him course the little bit embarrassing
You repeatedly said
That
Is court process
Lawsuit
What just happened
Is all a sham
Because you turned everything over
Right
Yes I always Shroyer you never sent him one deposition one document request one thing
He was defaulted along with me and if that isn't
Fraud the nothing is
Is I need you to
You understand that you have some case there was a
Court order
Requiring
Owen Shroyer
I know he appeared for a deposition yesterday asked you asked for it after the default
Neurosurgeon
Do you understand there was an order
In August 31st
Asking mr.
Require
Owen Shroyer DePere for.
I don't know what you talk about yeah you didn't know that
So you got on your show without even knowing
Discovery
Yasso big claims that I was making noise like complying with all this stuff when confronted with like this is something for
Do you know that
Nope don't know that say what I would have said which is just like
Really it's been going on that long how the time flies
Just stop and take a moment to appreciate where we've all
Got into let's just forget about this case friends
How many lawyers I've got to meet over the course of this thing
So many new friends the real default judgment was the friends we made along the way
I want to make one really important clarification
I've done a little AB
But the only things that I've cut out our when there'll be a call for an exhibit
And then there was a long stretch while the exhibit is being
Pictures of like
For the sake of listening
Things that would provide greater context
Or
We do miss representation
I just want to do that whereas I usually don't be totally clear
So Alex has been confronted with the fact that in fact I get called for a deposition at
2018 and they just ignored ignored
So you got on your show without even knowing
What the discovery was
Did you know in mister mister
Mister posner's case in mrs. Delarosa
You understand there soon
I never said her name I never going to say I'm not asking you about what you said
Correct
Start their you know there's a lot I know I didn't get a hearing trial and I would judge that I was guilty I don't believe that I live in the Soviet Union
Richard Jones you're not answering
You can goats in just a minute right now you're not answering
I'm asking you
Do you know
That Leonard Posner and Bernie Delarosa
You know they served
Discovery
I believe so I guess you know you didn't answer it ever
That's not true
You're going to find out a lot of things you don't know
Itsannemoore
Not like you got a bad grade on your homework
Turn it in
You didn't know that
What were the depositions we had in all the 1,000 documents
Definition
That's when we'll get to that let's talk about that in a minute but first
Mystikal mr. Posner mrs. Delarosa
You don't know
But you never answer
You don't even know that
In front of me a little bit of
Gaston and bravado once the actual like actual information is
IC IC Mark broke out his tap
Dancing shoes upon which to dance on Alex's grave I believe
I think I think you can tell there's a there's a tone of this is after the case is already
First time
And so
There is there is kind of a familiarity that maybe wouldn't be there in time the date
And so the list just goes on of stuff in Discovery that Alex claims
He did everything for but did not
You got Mission Posner mrs. Delarosa
Were you didn't even answer discovery
You got Mister Haslam defamation
We didn't show up for defamation
Answer any discovery
Destroyer
You got mrs. Lewis case
David's
Senior lawyers
Screwed it up
And you got Mister husband's ie
Would you just got sanctioned cuz you sent Rob due to the deposition you couldn't answer
In all of those things are true when you get onto your show and you tell the
Your show
But this is all just a kangaroo court and you completely comply but got real rooted
That's not true
Or you weren't
The way you wanted it and it should be on the issues of what did I say on here
It should be maybe Richard Delarosa
Have the right
Do you agree flutternut
I've been upset for the deposition you have not sat for a deposition
Mrs. Delarosa
And they have that right don't they
You really don't know yet probably a difficult question for Alex
Answer either in the affirmative or the negative questions
Doesn't want to answer
What are you
What a bad day
Especially in your deposition where you're f***** up
To have the lawyer remind you
You're not even a third of the way through the number of cases that you've ignored
Yeah it'll be challenging not only have you been getting enough in my class
Your other classes as well that you took previously
We went over there and if you'll recall there were a number of times where
Sourcing was discussed in a video or on his Show and Mark would ask
Where did you get that from Alex these cases with
I don't know but I could get it for you give me time I could get it for you
The circles back
Remember we talked about last deposition
About
The Bloomberg email
We're Bloomberg send an email out to his people
Say get ready in the next 24 hours is going to be a big
Remember that
That was a new story on
Yeah and then we talked about it for a while because you had brought that up to me you were like look I don't have the email itself
That was something I was reporting on I had there was a story about it and I was reporting on he remember that
And then you remember you told me you
Yeah I believe I said that and then you never gave it to me did you
I'd be honest with you back so you don't really have that much in my mind
Have much respect for any of this
That you have respect for America I need
Nailed it
Give of that you don't have respect for the proceedings are going on your respect for America
That was if you can't handle the truth will be delivered
It would not be a classic movie Moana
Electric
That was pretty interesting that response I think was shocking
It's just an outright combative miss that is it is fun it for the sake of a
Podcast legal system
Oppresses anybody really bad really really bad now we get to a discussion about
Alex is audience size
This this might have been a mistake on Alex's part
I want to play you a piece of audio
From from
Your radio show
Videos
This is going to be exhibit
A revolutionary war 1776
Audience
10% of the United States
10%
That's true
Guesstimation
I don't know
You're the one
It's a very short clip I need another context
Uky the hurdle Club
That's an advertisement for some sort of
Pill or something
I'm asking you right now
Is 10% of America an accurate representation
That's true right
Major media
I would say a large percentage of that agree with my worldview but I mean I would say 10% of countries
Watch something I've done and agree with me
And then globally
Another 10% right
Is your Infowars programming
Is not bound by us
It's the internet Tab
You are right
Interglobal
Maybe 10% of the globe is listening into Infowars write imagine
Temperature in people
Let that soak
That's
That's more hyperbole but the English-speaking world the outside
Whoa
So this is a bit of a misstep I believe on Alex's fire because he's in a deposition where the goal is determining the damages
He's going to be facing in this case
What are the relevant questions when it comes to defamation particularly in a case like this where the defamation was broadcast
Is that how many people were exposed to the defamatory material
In the interest of his case should make Alex downplay the size of his audience but his ego won't allow it so he says
Oh that 10% of the English-speaking world or about 135 million people are in his audience
Essentially admitting would have been exposed to the things that he's being sued for which
Is unclear if he even understood that in this question
It's not like it was like Mark is clearly asking like these like you got a big. You got a big show big audience
He's writing a puff piece about it so funny to me because
It's from 4 I mean like I can see this perfectly just from Alex's tone of voice is just like
This is a man who knows something's up
You're saying all the right things to make me save the things that I want to say
So these questions of like
You got a big audience don't you Mr Jones even the way that at Marcus phrased it is of course Alex is going to say well yes
My audience is huge you know he does smell a trap
Not well enough
It's so funny to me
It's so funny to me he thinks the Trap is coming but the Trap was already sprung my friend
Lawyer is asking this question so like 80 in front of the jury
I think he's a monster but he did
And you got 135 million regular listeners what are you supposed to say take the time to ask this if it wasn't
Part of something a point you're trying to build Alex's just helped that point get build
Possibly build
Through like just looking at web traffic or whatever Alex has done a great favor
Would say establishing a self-reported audience size you can just feel how stupid he is
Brutal so this is a particular highlight for me down for this because
We've established there's this really large
Mark wants to talk while again do you have a responsibility to not lie to your audience
This is great
Hyperbole something very familiar with
Yes
Talk radio
Exactly
When addressing.
Audience
You're United States and Global audio
Would you ever intentionally lie to them
No
Let me play another
Like you really want
Your back and forth
Stop. Org
Faster.
How many people View
Well I guess I guess we could
Officially put it to bed. Technically probably kill the guy
But he has not killed anybody
That's such a great like little ping-pong Exchange
Yes lion
And every time every single time I answered a question and Mark said
Let me play clip for you I'd throw the desk Alami like you win if you got it
I think I think another response will be like
Just sitting there like how am I going to say this is out of context
Clear yellow something I stepped on a nail and then run
So this is the point here in the in the deposition where we start to get around to some documents and some exhibits being interred
And this one was a bit of a curveball
This was a surprise
It's fair to say that litter Posner in freezer
Systems have had a nun
No I am not number
I don't really follow what he does so
Can you do shows about them
Correct
I mean I refresh my memory
So
I will refresh your memory about what you know of
I'm saving boxes 25 you ever seen that before
Not remember what is it
You produced me
Just a couple months ago
In regard to Discovery request for documents
SSO document
That was in that folder
That's it
And that you agree with me a pierce
To be a very large
Text me about 187 page
Comprehensive background report on
Cosmo
Oh I never ran a background report on Posner
I understand that you probably
Someone email is this and then we opened
I did not know
You just go through the email most of it even on open and just send you guys everything
I would imagine what I've never run a background thing on buzzer
One thing we can agree on because you look at the bottom of that document says fssp
Tx-dot
Five five
44 correct
That's a Bates numbers y'all use
Give me documents
Document right here came from Infowars corporate files
I thought you said we were giving you any.
Are you so we didn't get weird or default I gave you nothing you didn't respond
Responsive to document
But I'm just telling you I've never looked at the that's not what I'm asking you
The news about
Play in Florida doing a background check on him and so I figure
My mother sent us this I'm just guessing
I don't know what this is so let's not do that anymore I think they're on Alex's part 2
Try and evade with the with the laugh
I'm going to be a road that Alex is going to be able to go down I'm so instead
He's like what I heard there's a guy in Florida that's obviously a reference to Wolfgang halbig
To say his name and he's okay
Remember this whole thing remember we got served in 2018
I don't even remember this guy that's a strange
This exchange cuz Alex he's actually confused by the presentation of this document
And it's a gigantic and extensive background check on Leonard Posner one of the parents of the children killed at Sandy Hook
The fact of free speech systems turn that over the cases bizarre
The fact that was in their files to begin with his bizarre like all of it does not
I suspect based on Alex's attempts to Workshop an explanation that one of two things is going on here
Either he knew about this document and is surprised to see it so he's trying to come up with a cover story
Or he had no idea about its existence but he realizes how f*****-up it is that that was in their files
So he's trying to come up with a cover story for the unconvincing
Just left open for a jury to hear
Without any explanation or exclamatory contacts on Alex's Park
I don't think the existence of this document looks
Good no no I mean I believe that Alex is never read
187 pages
I mean
Of all the Epic
They were going through the things they want to give
Which
Obviously we know excludes so many things
And they were looking at the one violin
Leonard Father's Day
And they were like let's put this super suspicious massive background report that we totally didn't have ordered
As for confused by its existence
It states it's so bizarre and especially considering the things
Now that's discussed about Alex and the publishing of
Partners address
Distance of this kind of
Extremely thorough background report
Is is not great one that has a lot of personal information about you
You would you know if
If I were somebody who had already had a default judgement against me
In one case
And then specifically
Releasing it private
Persons information was at fault in another case
I would not want to have a big stack of that person's private information
Opportunity
Information well here's
Possibly have come from I just listened we walk down the streets and s*** falls from the sky
But this is a nice little semantic game Alex tries to play about this
One thing we can agree on is that in the files of free speech systems is 887 page
Investigators comprehensive report on Leonard.
What are you
No no no no
According to you I want your testimony before I don't care if I'm staying
You put this is your base number on the bottom
Correct yes okay this came from enforce corporate okay
I think the fair is a good Dynamic going on where Alex keeps trying to get around things
I think that Mark strategy is flexible enough that he can allow for Alex to say some b******* and then run into a wall
With some of these deflection tactics
I think it's very good think it's a lot of fun
Yeah you really have to establish for awhile in advance that know Alex
You sent this to us
This is yours not mine I'm not making claims about it this is what you sent to us
Sort of linguistic and rhetorical Dodges that he uses it as nature
I'd imagine.
Should have put a pin in them the message that I'm not going to put up with this
Going to be a non effective and unsuccessful strategy
And I think maybe how you have to talk to him a little parental book
Well
If he didn't sound like he had failed a book report every time I answer to question maybe you wouldn't have to talk to him like a f****** joke
Perhaps
So they they get into talking about the events where
Letter Posner contacted Infowars
With a polite complaint
And then it went from there
No Mister poisonous started in all of
Privately complaining to you
Infowars you agree with that he made a private
Yes
And he was very polite about it wasn't
It's a long time since I saw the email that I think so
Okay and
When that didn't work
He complained again but this time too you too
You know about that
I really don't remember you know mister
Right
No
November
I remember people said he was going around getting lost of taking down all of them
And and
It made you mad didn't
I told my crew members
Sandy Hooks at our baby
Stop covering Buble
Let's let's keep that one in my phone is okay I want that in the legal record
For the rest of my life I want the legal system to know what I said
But the way Alex answered that question is really puzzling to me is very confused
First Keys aware that Mr Posner politely complain to Infowars and was ignored
Then Alex is unaware that Posner went on to complain to YouTube but when confronted with how absurd that statement is
Considering things he said publicly
Alex tries to explain how he could be mad at Posner about Free Speech issues but somehow not aware that he could blame
Alex and gotten the strike on his channel
You can basically hear the gears moving here Rises Alex is trying to come up with a just plausible enough explanation for
For all the details he thinks he has to account for like Ono the reason I did those shows was because I heard that he was getting
Things taken down all over the place and was against Free Speech nothing to do with any personal interaction I had
My Revenue stream being shut down eventually do to the germination of effort
From this one particular man I wouldn't pay attention to that at all please
YouTube Millions
This is this
This is just confusing this is this this answer is is Bazaar
Long before you guys are assuming I would scream at people that they even talked about it
Because it's Tar-Baby
That's why I told you I just had to compartmentalize it out there because it's just like constant
Imma Sandy Hook man I killed the kids
Hi people afford US much good won't go get held up kids
Whatever
Adam Lanza
I mean I just
You guys used apply for me
People think I killed the kids
All the stuff just
Do your worst
What was my question
Answer your question
He don't know what it was you were just talking
Right now
And so you just started talk
You didn't even know what's up
Do you want me to
Sweetheart do you think you're at
Regarding
The YouTube complaint that made
Is I killed the kids just
To me that's the answer that question
So this transitions Haram
Posner to Albion questions about another parent
Jamaican Kelly
Piece that I was so mad about
Damn.
Establishing question here
When new husband
Okay first of all you know who Neil house
Was right
Yes
So when you hustled appeared on Megyn Kelly show in 2017 do you remember that
When he went on there
And said he was upset
By the things you were saying about saying
You believe them
I thought it was all done very theatrical and being a very canned way but I do think parents have pain over their children
But it was all done and infomercial feel to it
I don't care really what you think about Megyn Kelly or
Nbcnews run by the largest
Weapons Manufacturing
The world you know like I do
Yes they make
Incredibly edited
Videos they
It's a complete
Mini p.m. sure if you've ever seen an embassy
Reproduction
Lights in Carrollton
Staging that I know that I know it looks like a
I'm not asking about
I just want to know about
Did you believe
Believe about what
When he said he was upset
You said about Sandy
Yes I will
I think a really good approach that Mark is taking with the questioning
Where you getting out in front of Alex's criticism of the media
Best deflect for taking responsibility for his actions is 2.2 other media entities and yell about the mistakes
Mater how they're corrupt
Introducing that on his own Mark is essentially taking that tool away or at least weakening its impact because
If Alex tries to employ that Dodge the response he can clearly expected isn't that distracting argument but something like we're going to
Agreement that the media isn't great but that's not relevant to the discussion we're having
This is something that I think is a really good tactic you can use when you're talkin to hyper evasive people who are also full of s***
If there's something that the standard rhetorical Refuge if they tend to take
Staking out your wrong claiming that space makes it so they're less comfortable retreating to it
And that's that's that's a good good ploy
And at the same time you've resented this to being like did you believe
No hassle in what he said this about his kid
Because
It's kind of relevant
I will take you back to the night
First all that Megan
Which
Probably was a surprise for you considering that it was not what she
Represent
Correct
Yes
And on that night when you saw that video
You saw mr. housing saying though
I want to take you back to
That date
And that date
You understood
Infowars two were to make a video
Same Mister Haslam could not have held his
Sun
That would be very
You understand
No I did not understand that
Okay
This is bizarre
Because he has said
Already that he understood and believed on Megyn Kelly show
He was upset by the things that enforces said
But somehow now he's saying that he doesn't understand that saying more stuff
What are human emotions contradiction that he's making
Not that is kind of bizarre
Alex excuse me do you understand basic human empathy
Just sauna
Well after the Megyn Kelly peace Owen Shroyer
Story where he
Yes I recall which is part of the lawsuit
We want to know why did he do that
Who who gave him the the idea to do that do you feel about it now
Who
Do you know sitting here today
Who made the choice
For Owen Shroyer to put those
Claims by
On the air about Neil
Interview
Do you know who did that
It was a live show that's that she's not a video we made it was a live show
Ali Reza zerohedge article he just read an article
Jim Fetzer
Remember that
I believe he was in the article
And you understand that a video was made for that and uploaded to YouTube
Would you have any reason to
I'm not sure we would have her YouTube
You also know that a month
After mister
Destroyer made that
Video using took that 5 minute video
From the live show
And played it on your show
I'm at my PS I guess I got
So
Whose decision was it
If you know
For him to
Basically give more air to mister pets
Those islands decision
My friend
Yeah that's
No it still doesn't excuse Alex's re-airing of the video
That was your choice
Based based on what Alex's just said yes Owen obviously has control over his own show
It's a live show he chose to do that
That means that Alex having the same control over him
You would assume that chose to are the exact same information on his show I'll look I don't
Time for those kinds of little decisions
There's a rebuttal to this in a follow-up question that
Mark may have some information that runs counter to to this thing that I look the same
I talked to him a couple days ago
And he said no he didn't
Read it at all word look at research
Somebody put in front of him
He doesn't member who
But he doesn't
You didn't do that
Mini doesn't research
Somebody puts it
Your phone's going to be doing that video that didn't agree with us okay
Bread so this? Moses brings up a point to put the Alex in a really uncomfortable position
Give me the impression to be that Infowars reporters are all in-depth researchers who bring their own work to the show and deliver
More hard news
It looks like journalists kind of
The problem however is that
He was just reading an article someone put in front of him with no awareness of what the article was or what the sources were
Position of having to claim that Owen lied
This is likely because the alternative open the can of worms that Alex does not want to have opened to the public
The question
Who put the article in front of Owen
If isn't lying then someone in that studio has a shocking level of editorial control over what goes on on the show
And we have no idea who that person might be
You can see how this question alone could lead to some discomfort because if such a person exists you have to ask yourself how did they get the
Editorial Authority is that part of their job description
What kind of digging do they do into the sources that they are providing for the anchors to just say on air
On the flip side of this it open opens up a question about who can and just tell Owen what to say
Say on air
If a person who fed him the story with someone like a boom mic operator then that raises the question
Can anyone just put something in front of Owen and he'll read it on air is the news
That's that's troubling the Anchorman Ron Burgundy territory
Option under the bus
The other option involves the possibility of some undisclosed editorial manager given Owen the story to report
Or the possibility of a complete negligence and lack of oversight about everything they put on the air to the point where
Any person who's there buses brake Screech so loud
I just had to stop for some reason I don't know what could have
It's strange it's understand the Instinct that Alex has
But yeah this this point that Mark brings up of
The conversations he's had with Owen Wright
And it's it is very counter these are doing a counter either
Bus metaphor two buses heading for an intersection
Other under both are being driven by Keanu Reeves in speed
What I eat what I find interesting about the shofar and
Really what is going to
Do Alex and
Five more than anything else is that
Alex is ability to understand questions is so shallow
That he doesn't realize that by answering one of Mark's questions
He is then raising the possibility that more questions will be asked like he doesn't
Get that he believes that the answer is the end of the question that's probably because he's used to monologuing what I'm saying and then
Also having interviews with Gaston his conspirators Coke collaborators with him
So this is a completely new concept to him that the answer is also a consequence
Leads to more question Rapaport whenever a follow-up
Why can't I have a deposition with John Rappaport I answered one question why are you asking more questions about that
When I have conversations
Alex Alex has to really put his foot down and make clear that like no one runs his own show
So the only two people in the room
We're probably going to have any influence on what goes in front of the anchors
Say
The producer
And the person was researching checking
Right
Know them know the way
The way it works is the host
. is telling me what the plan what articles
Owen should have been the one who found
That's what you're thinking that's how it would normally work he would have found that article hundreds
Hundreds of articles
Then that is why I do it this way
Imoan basically
Rooster Booker everything
So the way I sit there and I print hundreds of articles
Well ride direct people to
I just say go to these 10 sites and print everything
Okapi
And then
Other people there and chosen to do it the same way
Anna just constantly
More information coming out as the day goes on
Talking parrots eating amount like throwing 90% of 7 ft in front of that assistant
But that the radio host run the show it's a radio show on TV
If a radio show
It's not journalism it it's not you
In the main if it's just like Howard Stern
Or it's just like Rush Limbaugh
And you're playing Clips recovering articles are giving your opinion
Okay. Journalism
So I may I agree it's a radio show on TV ironically it is neither of those things
Sure it's a roundabout extremists Topix
Embark wants to establish that this information that Alex is using in the
17 videos that he put out to people like Jim Fetzer
And whether or not at that time he had reason to believe that Jim Fetzer was not a good source
Back in 2017
You had information
Routine information
That caused you
Weather mr. Houston
Correct
Yes I did I did see an article questioning it
Information
That information was raised
My mister
Correct
I don't I don't have no iPhone
Infowars
The company itself
And understand
That there was issues
With mr. feathers credibility
Correct
Direction form
I mean I can't really speak too much because your credibility
So this is a trap
Obviously the question being asked
The answer is in the question of
Just jump at their information is also more or less a statement that like
Do you have any reasons to doubt his credibility
And of course there's an email
I mean I can't really speak to
Other people in your company
To you
Correct
I don't recall
You're a couple watching talking about jump
No
If somebody
Call Watson in 20
Lyrics Chief reporter by then
Did editor what is he
Decided self
He also did some hosting
Yes
Is mr. Watson let's just say again
That Mr Watson
Somebody whose opinion nearest
Somebody you will If he if he brings you something you'll listen
Right
May not always agree
Yes
Mr. Watson had come to you
And told you
Alex
Confessors batshit crazy
Would you listen to him
Taking that into consideration
Yes
This is I think this could not be more like a fork
In chess you know like when you've got your night in the right spot and you're listen I'm getting your queen or I'm getting your
So how do you want this to go and Alex does not understand what's about to happen to him
The email of other people
Buckley is on Alex's is hearing this and now
Not realizing that was about to happen is exactly the thing that I mean this is amazing
I want the hammer to drop
My friend this frog is boiling formation that called into doubt
Mr. Fetters credibility
You would check in and verify that before ever relying on
I can't talk about the hypotheticals again
Discussing already told you that ninety-eight percent of all we do is covered news in the public domain
Opinion
And so I'm not
A journalist Wall Street Journal
One year-long investigative
Journalist
So I'm a radio talk show host
The put the show on TV
This whole thing that he's doing with like I'm just a talk show host I think it just feels like a you wouldn't hit a guy
Glasses
Over here I'm not causing such nonsense I mean like
He's also trying to prevent this idea of like everything we cover is just like mainstream Media stuff
Like he pretends that he has high-level secret sources and you constantly taking primary source.
Events are coming up with fantasy interpretations of them regularly conducted those softball interviews of dangerous
I have a lot of the time he's even reporting stuff based on fake stories from his past or esoteric dreams that he came
Prophetic we can't blame him for that
Until we know he's not a psychic
Okay we can't prove that yet
So I'm going to go ahead and air on the side of where I'm at
Doesn't necessarily come down about this email from Paul but we know that it exists
Need to bring it out now because you have Alex always listening
Old grump David Knight
David Knight is a
Talk show host
Easy work for you right now
He did work for you
Yes
When did he leave
Remember correctly about your ago
And then he's not come back anyway or y'all still doing videos with
No
David Knight
Did not
Between David Knight
Remember some
David Knighton
Steve pieczenik did not get along
I guess
Big night
Incredibly critic
Nothing Steve
China Cuisine
No I don't know where that
Can you tell me what David Knight isn't worth
The company anymore
David was saying that he was being censored and no one was sent to him and he was just unhappy
And
Alright
Made some comments about tactics and strategies to use an appositive
I do have to clarify that
Mark has a slightly incorrect piece of information that he's putting out here
David Knight was totally into what Steve was saying about Sandy Hook still promoting the Sandy Hook was fake on his show and tell
At least 2017
David got sick of Steve when he said that the Las Vegas shooting was fake
And that led to the deterioration of their working relationship
I meant David got really mad when Steve started coming back on the show around the lead-up to the 2020 election
David was insistent that Steve was a con man and the stuff about all the balance beam watermarked blockchain was stupid
Timothy was just lying to Alex this is getting fired and replaced by Harrison Smith hosting the American Journal
Truth to the tension between the two of them
But David night actually was totally fine with this
Damning for David Knight
Sure Alex is like being censored
Was a lying piece of s***
You wanted anyone until I fired so now we learn a little bit about David nights
Actions
Hook timing this is weird
Confronted with a marker
No one will notice about this document as you look down in the bottom corners there's no numbers
Bottom corner
Blank page
This is I'm going to represent you this document
Former lawyer
Database
So I don't have an ID
But looking at this email
David Knight's name
2in from
That's one of your employees
Yes
And
I'm going to go ahead and read this for you here this is
The date
June 19th
You remember that the Megyn Kelly and
Right
Yes
In fact
One of the videos that your company is being sued for
June 26th
Yes and then in July you also
A video about these
As well correct
Baby bean soup
I don't know
Yes
Doing updates so you do know you didn't make that Delights
You know that sitting
The shop
Video
Well I guess you didn't make the video but somebody did
Somebody made a video of that
Uploaded it to the
What I'm trying to get cuz you've you brought the
What is distinction of a
A couple times
That nowhere just a live radio show it's not a video
But there are videos and they're uploaded to YouTube
Correct
For the radio show
Could be totally different than who's watching you
Correct
So now we have this video we have this email from David Knight
And it's from David Knight
To David
Rent
So sending himself something
Guess
The subject line
Is it says Connecticut carry
Releases
The troubled past
Of Neil Hess
And then do you see
There is a link there
From ammoland
Dot-com
Correct
Yes
And then it says sent for my iPad
Right
Okay and then
This email here was sent to himself at 6:12
You see that yes
Everything I said about this emails accurate
You have any reason to think that
This is not a true and accurate email from Infowars is 5
I don't know I don't know either you gave it to me and it don't even know
Reason to dispute this
No I don't have any bruises good
So we we've got this established it's David night
Around the time of the Sandy Kelly interview
At 6 p.m. was emailing himself and article
How is dirt on me last one
Now
Interview are
But there's more
Let me show you this Tuesday
Similar email without Marxism
You see this is 6:18 2017
Yes.
I'm just a couple days
Before Owen Shroyer
Video
Correct
Yes
And you remember that Megyn Kelly
Interview
Your profile came out in
In June 19th
So here we have Again David Knight
Send an email to himself David Knight
Speak the truth 80 at Yahoo is that another one
Gmail address
I don't know
You'll never
No
It says subject
Neil heslin father of Sandy
Criminal charge
News
And then there's a country
Oracle link
Yes
Himself
Set himself this email
At 2:56
6 in the morning
You're any reason
But this isn't
I think this is a good strategy that's being employed here because there's no question for Alex to answer
Other than just like be a reason to believe this is an authentic
Or to spend anyting
There's almost
Definitely no information that Alex could give about these emails that would be useful but letting them just sit there
There there's clear indications that senior employees
Everything that they could used to smear hassling at 2 a.m. or 2:50 something a.m.
6 p.m.
Almost like it was his job for the day it's such a bad look almost as if somebody had directed him to find
Information on Neal hesler been up all night working so hard on it and then later
People use that information burning the midnight oil
It gives an indication of a kind of vibe baby there was going on
How did Ford's play I want this
So because there's I don't know maybe the appearance of like
Looking for ways to attack this person who is in the Megyn Kelly interview seemed like maybe threatening to Alex
This is an important question which is like do you have any reason to believe that these people were faking
Their grief
Does the company have any reason to contend
Call first let me ask you
Do you
Have any reason to
The any of these parents
Faking their Des
Stress over it
I did not kill their children
And
I didn't visit out of my angel's house CIA
And no one sued me
Back the time and I was actually talking about it was once I became extremely famous
Hillary Clinton issue about in campaign ads
And then Trump won the election
And then I became this big supercharged political Target is low-hanging fruit
Nnnn nnnn I got always the Sandy Hook man
And then and then they leave the DVD
Gun control groups
The Democratic Party
Basically
Attach themselves to me
So that every time I was in the news they could then bring backup settings
But for the gun control advocacy that they have
Natural this long process
Has as head has been
First of all Jackson non-response
Was any of that
Was any of that meant to be a reason that you can't end
Where to send Michael a faking faking their distress
So they're just stress over what you said
You admit that
Then then that distress
I think I think when
Since you can understand how
When new husband
I spent the last
Heroic child
Looking him in the
I didn't kill him
I know you didn't
Please let him just ask you
I know I've got my client
You're not
Can you kill these kids
Nobody's saying that you
You caused that grief
Let's make that really clear
Nobody's saying that
Parents the word grieving over the death of
Their children that's the thing that they went through
Has nothing to do with you
You get that
Their grief over the death of their children has nothing to do with you you get that accept them for the gun-control though that it was projected on
Blaming us for their gas
And we don't accept that
I don't even know what that means
You asked me a question every time some crazy person on Prozac
Doesn't kills people at the CIA went visiting on record
And then we get blamed and we're tired of being blamed
You can almost hear Alex starting to turn into like show mode here almost here that's flip gets wet
Because there is a guy I guess I'm going to go out now or I guess I'm going to get really combative do a performance
I was in reaction to him being forced to say yes that is you know
Once he got that negative
The that
That terrible headspace of just having to say
Yes I know what you're saying when he couldn't deflect on anything right so then it just turned into him being like
There's only one way for me to take control of this again it's in response to the
The like the other objection non-responsive it's like I'm not even getting gate with this
You're going down
Listen I'll take care of my client the f*** you are yeah
This is a does not Barney
Text clip Alex and he
It's unfortunate what happens when you get to the show mode
In The Wrong settings
So here's the deal
Here's the deal
The court of public opinion
Knows that people have a right to ask question
Now in high side I saw the families it look pretty legitimate some of the nominees are not to not be true
And then I said I was sorry
And then I got sued
And she looks just a sitter and pretend
That Alex Jones in red pajamas like the devil running around attacking all these people and that's not the case
Let's see the people
New Hustle
20 / 2
Cherish memory
Putting his hand through
Mistress Troyer
Menu
Get on TV
Andros curious doubt
About whether even held his son
Whether he's telling the
Truth
Any did that after he had asked you to
Stop
You can under
And why that man might
And you can understand how he's on TV on an actual program attacking us
Yeah you know why you did that
Tell me why do you do that
Because Megan Kelly went to organize the whole thing for publicity
Contixo go after the Second Amendment they used for political purposes
American people and then get surprised with people
Think it might be stage might be might be sympathetic
You think Neal Hustler
When on National Television
To ask you to
Stop
As part of a pot
There are the interest behind it and the money and and end of the financing
I don't represent any of those
I don't represent Megyn Kelly
Add Megyn Kelly in this chair right now believe me let me talk another something
So now Alex has gotten himself into a strange position where
He's trying to claim that these people were doing these the sort of
Pageants to das Amendment and
It's fun when you're on a radio show and you can drive
Specifics of like we talked about my client here
Alright having to dance around all these things and asked like to be specific is like
Kryptonite for allergy and you can see that
Almond and he tries to continue to justify a lot of his behavior because
Have a notion that
The Sandy Hook
Parents got political share and that made it so he had to fight them right
Do you
Have any reason to
That these parents
Grieving process
8:30
Husband impact
That's a hypothetical question I can't speak to their emotions
There's nothing
I did not kill their children
They became political and used
That deaf
To them for their advocacy against the right
Bear arms
And so that directly put them in
Opposition
Politically with me
So they stepped into that political Arena
What what did
Do politically
Did you ever say anything about guns
I'm talking about
Nicole Sandy Hook
Situation in general Bandit some of the
Look at it did start Louis
I don't have it all in front of me
That's such an illustrative moment
Alex is trying to come up with a justification for his actions because he's being confronted with the reality that he traumatized
In the place he decides to land that they use their children stats for political gain against the Second Amendment
Marks were bottle is so revealing because Alex can't name a single thing that these two people who are suing Alex ever did
Advocacy
He has no idea what these people did or didn't do
His response was just the normal kind of Dodge you'll use when he's being questioned by some s*** head like Rogan
Who does go along with whatever Alex says
Here's why this is key to understand
Alex didn't say or do the things he did about the particular parents who were suing him because they were in opposition to the Second Amendment
What happened was that Alex saw the conversation surrounding Sandy Hook shooting their hit being a threat to his gun
So he decided that the Sandy Hook parents
Which he needed to attack to change the narrative
Really care about any of them or what they were doing or not doing individually he saw the collection of families
He's as an entity he could attack and paid his coming after the Second Amendment and portraying them as being actors is a really easy
Midway to invalidate them to his audience
Maybe some of the parents of gun-related activism so to Alex that means they all were and they were you
Using the shooting to push their agenda
To undermine what he perceived as them use in the shooting for political game
Alex attacked individual parents cuz he felt that by doing so
He was in validating the group as a whole and protecting the Second Amendment
Right it's pretty clear
Based on the way he's describing his thought I thought pattern and this is when I would go back to the earlier question
About Neil heslin
When he was on Megyn Kelly and Mark really forced Alex to get to this place of like yes I do
If
I mean he's a human being
If your son is died and you hold him that I get that that would hurt
I get that
And then even then he can try and justify his behavior after that but once you've established that he can look at it
Another human being and say yes
My actions hurt you that is under underlying all of these justification you got to have to go back to
You like just most Elementary let's get agreement about air
But you know you hurt
You can understand that
Until then whatever justification you have
Is still undercut by the fact that you know that you hurt them right but I think even in that case even with that
That established Alex could still Retreat to the idea that hurting them is an unfortunate byproduct of defending the second
Sure he could probably justify that in his own head it doesn't sound good
We're well in far beyond anything sound
That train has left the station this seems to be a bit of a pattern of behavior
That Alex has
And this is where
Really was
Like this is where I think turned and I was really shocked that this was happening
So we know in 2012
Right wouldn't happen
You got on TV and started talking about it being
We know that
Soon the rapper I had Quest
No new mr. Jones I don't understand this whole thing about questions I don't get
If you say Sandy Hook
Fake that's not a question
That was
That was years later I can see how people think it's absolutely fake
There's no code of you saying I can
People spend
You keep repeating that it does
Okay well that's what I remembered our last deposition I showed you clip a clip of you saying
Totally synthetic
We made up with actors
At first I thought they killed real kids
They didn't
But that's that's that's that's
That was
And you did that
In 2014
He did it he didn't 2013 you didn't 2014 you didn't
Correct
I got to go back and look but I definitely said that I had serious questions about it
Could see out they will see it was stage with all the
Bizarreness
Michigan
Sandy Hook
God it's weird look at this
Somebody needs to answer
You wouldn't be here today
The reason to
Statements that I want to talk
As you admit
That over those five
Without equivocation
Fake
Children did
Die
Actors
Parts of differ
You said those things
Can you know just admit that for the jury that you said they're going to see the videos can you build a Sandy Hook them self
Wild
Yeah I couldn't believe my ears within this goes on
Can you know just admit that for the jury that you said they're going to see the video
Sandy Hook
They should look into it themselves
And see why people ask questions
No I really hope
I feel like Alex is really deeply implying fit
He is right it was right about it being fake
I think he's absolutely contending that it is still fake such a bizarre thing but you can tell if you're watching
We're listening to it even you can tell that it is
Sort of visceral response anger behind
Like
Like it because I think it's largely motivated by
So many attempts of deflection and stitches not really working out
That's maybe the value in soda cutting off exits and like okay
Now you've nowhere to go other than you now we're going to
I mean you also have to cut off the physical exit Financial exits as well as
We've had to cut off a lot of exits to get to a place where Alex is here
True that Outburst enjoy that like
You're afraid that they're going to look into this I hope I hope your bananas man
Navigate to some more emails and one of the what about her email
Turns out we're talk about some emails that have to do with Jim Fetzer
Before we broke we had talked about weather
Infowars head ever
Promoted
Jim Fetzer
Get more viewers
Can you weren't aware of
Not my memory
Imma show you the park
And I'm going to go through this whole thing with you to see
She has no memory of promoting sensors.
I want to start at the bottom
Without pausing though
And he says Rob Jim Fetzer
Together a book
On Sandy Hook
Amazon
I've decided they want
Handle it
Jim wittig
We were both
On the phone
Both just on the
Jeff rense
Jim gave
Alec
Tracy on
Promote the book
Outlook
Still running
You flip over
The next message
Okay before we going to gym Festus message you know Jeffrey
Yes
Do you remember Paul rent the Paul Watson also
The same time that he told you
Crazy that
No
Going up to Jim Fetters email
Identifies himself
But he says
Rob
We are making the book available to the public
Free here's the covering
PDF several sites are now offering it I would be glad if we're Alex
The same I'm sure James would be glad
You come on with me
If Alex won
Interview is about
The stunning of
I think the latest
Case was
Pentagon pay
I read that correctly
Yes
And then Rob Do-Right's back to
Jim Fetzer
Says thanks for the heads up
Sent the links to at dawn
And he is writing an article about it
Please let us know if
If there is a bump
In download
Rob
Diary. Coronavirus
It's not great I think I think you like giving these email
Maybe you can dance around like we get a lot of emails
Rob is Robert is riding back hey I sent this on to add on Salazar's
Please let us know if our cab campaign for you as effective the moment over had a moment you said let us know if there
There's a bump in traffic you are recode like you're in the f****** case man
To them I would expect to be in the f****** case has very least you're admitting at least accurate
Pasadena-based interest in how things go look
Cuz if you're not curious just like you be interested you're curious to see if you should do
Do-it-yourself Oregon if this is something that people are interested in
Will you give me market resistor tracks are audio
Information is largely was behind the zerohedge article
In the video that ended up
Bobbing party this lawsuit point about this actual zerohedge article
Seems to be missed
Then you recognize.
Yes
Zerohedge article
You know why it might be relevant to this lawsuit
This is the article I was reading that
He's been sued for and the
Cobra jacket with Owen
Has big blank space in the middle of the page
Seems to be awake printed from the internet
Blow that big Blank Space
Do you see where it says except this.
Does not comport with
Social story
Just forgot
And then it says
Jim Fetzer
Professor emeritus
At the University
Give Minnesota
Who wrote a book
Cleaning Sandy Hook
Stage
Notes that be
The facts of the case
Haslam statement
Behold his son
With a bullet hole through his head
Could not have half
I want you to flip to the 3rd pick
You see that first sentence
The first paragraph there it's
Just one long sentence
Okay and what how that paragraph begins is by saying
It's entirely possible
You see where it says that
That wasn't said by info
Here's the problem with their shoddy strategy of never
The things that the actual article that they're getting sued over actually
Says in it that a maybe he did for his son
Is that just to justify position of he couldn't evolve
So one way makes money in the other one doesn't I feel like we both know which way works
Yep that's that's an unfortunate thing to have to
Would end and this might be the crazy thing for me right but if I had spent my entire career not reading things
And then suddenly was starting to be told more and more
Terrifyingly that the lawsuits weren't going well I would take
And maybe a whole week
To just really read through everything that I'm supposed to know about
Be surprised when I was in a deposition
And maybe I wouldn't get caught in some of these f****** traps you don't want to have a
Sort of consistency
Heavy breath of grief
Oh no
Deflation is not a ongoing thing you want to feel you want to be deflated and then done you know what
Constantly keep going your your response to seeing something that is really unfortunate and damning
Shouldn't be oh no not again
You just put those needles in me so the idea about his relationship with Jim Fetzer
Like he didn't trust him as a source
Even before hallway the 2017 still getting Sudan
It's at this is weird
Okay I'll show you what if Martha is
At 11
And I know that this has a really like
I have a lot of stuff
The only thing I think when we get into this.
Quickly discover that it may not be
Necessary
Read all of this.
But if so I may need to give you some
What I want to ask you about the
Document
Up at the very top
You see that this is an email
About a month after you were
You understand that
Peddlernet
What is Nico's job title
Okay and then
Daria what's her title
She was
Sound operator then
Sedation
Yes
And so Daria sending this to Nico
In the subject is
Forward
Vanishing blog
Not only is
Noah Pozner
Fiction
What is Fatherland
Have you ever seen
No
Auto Pagani.
Maybe I should talk about it
Right after you
I mean
No I've no idea
I find this
Tubi
Very surprising
Because I mean revelatory it is revelatory
More surprising to me is that
It appears as though he still thinks he's out of chance you know it really feels like the way he's too
Talkin he's like
Okay maybe I lost on this question maybe I'm losing on this one but next one maybe there's that glitter glue
Camera light I can sneak through operated
I was in this deposition I'll be like literally everything I say you're going to have a clip for so f****** say whatever you
You want to say here's my answer to your question
Yes or no whatever you want I will just say I don't know over and over again and then we'll go home
Bull run up run out the clock on this thing you one man
Yeah
So of course they're more documents and shifting now over into the Wolfgang
How big section of of some of these documents
And Mark brings up this email this email is
And I believe
That's some of the goal of this is just make Alex recognize like
Add source
We should be trusted
Little bit about Wolfgang halbig
You know what I mean when I talk about this
Super Bowl picture
No
You know what I mean about the Superbowl choir
A fourth grader
Yes I've heard of that okay
And that's when I really started thinking it probably did happen if I can just get to
Crazy that's what happened
I'm sure you would have marked as exhibit 12
You'll see again at the bottom there's no base
This one
Is dated 1190
18 2016
I wasn't going to hear the end of 2016
It is from Wolfgang halbig
To line the main people it sent to
Include Nico
Then
Several organs
Correct
Just robbed you
He was also another
Employee
And then Jay rinsed
You think you're being fair
And then also copied there's a cc line
And there's several other people
Kopyor
Either
Media organizations and there's also
Government address
Yes
Also a bunch of
You see that
I never attachments
Appear to be PNG
Images
And then the subject line
Says Trust
But always verify
Please verify with your
Uncle
Thanks
You see that
Yes I'm going to go ahead and read this email to you alright
Rob
Please send this video to your uncle the former FBI
Pretended my Connecticut
Freedom of Information
Hartford Connecticut
He told me that I was right about
About what would happen
Gave me a
More courage
He has friends you can
Verify this video to be actor
And now we know the
Let the children
Supposedly died at Sandy Hook
Or at the Super Bowl
On February 3rd 2013
And that is why we have never ever heard
Think about it for just a second
They sing before 110 million
People worldwide
Jennifer Hudson
They have 87,000 people in the stadium if over 3,500 news report
And we never have one interview in the newspaper of
On television
From them why
Just think about how much money came
I'm flowing in after that February 3rd
Super Bowl performance
Across the world
Why have they never performed again if they were so great
To be asked to sing
February 3rd
Wino appearances on the national early morning television
They sing before 110 million
Simply disappear
Even Beyonce
Where are they are they all dead
Threatened by the NFL and CBS Sports
And by their own parents never to talk about the greatest day in their lives
Are they part of
Child trafficking
Who would do this
The fourth grade children when we all know that children need to ask
Express their feelings or emotions
Where can I have long-term mental health in
The blood that is a YouTuber
And then it says please have your uncle verify and
And tell me
That I am not crazy
Because I
Because I have now run out of funds
Chasing the truth
Please help
If you can afford it Wolfgang housing and then he gives his address
Correct
I've read all that correct
When he asked them
To verify that he is not crazy
That's not something that
That is what I really started thinking that it probably did happen one
Thanks ducks eat oranges
Tonight
But I'm not the progenitor of this
That is I'm not saying this
You have to understand that wolf
Yes when he first came out to livestream on national TV that's why I was relying on him
So this is an important foundation here that's being built through this email because it kind of boxes Alex in and honestly he
Did it to himself
Because he's getting presented with a clearly insane email that how big sent Rob do trying to reach Rob's uncle
It's not coming from a credible person but he also
How big is a credible Source prior to this
That's why Alex tries to use this excuse that it was actually decided that how big wasn't a good source
Kennedy shouldn't listen to him
This is a really dumb piece of information to Alex OfferUp essentially unprompted because what does it put the
Deadline on the point where you yourself are admitting you had no reason to take this person's claim seriously
Yeah this is basically creating an unanswerable question for Alex if you can demonstrate that he took how big's claims
Seriously at any point after this and that's a real problem for Alex's appearance of consistency
Double-edged sword because Alex is also essentially testifying that the things that how big did orseund Infowars
Prior to this
We're not enough to get him to think that how big was.
And shouldn't be trusted as a source
Remember the day this was November 19th 2016 was when this happened
Yeah I mean that's what that's one where you really that's it that's an own-goal
That should be that's on Alex right there cuz the moment you are like
Given the opportunity to have a date
Stamp on something you think and you're Alex don't do that about a good idea
I think we talked about it like specificity is a real Danger
Whether it's email or this time
This story was being pushed by how big is too specific for you to be able to play games with you can
Which again if I'm doing this
I would say look into when I actually started listening to how big and when I stop stop
Talking about how big you might not want to do that it was real bad
Not agree to a date prior to the end of when I started talking about how what's fascinating about it
Music you listen to it or something
That is not a question that Mark asked him at all which is why I'll amazing
Over here because the last clip in the next one
Because it's not really relevant to some of the questions we have
A consists of Mark and Alex discussing how the alternative media is really important in the country because the corporate media isn't really something
We can trust to get us out of the mess we're in
Mark keeps trying to work on in a recognition that it's important for the alternative media to hold themselves responsible
When I get things wrong and Alex just goes off but I was the victim of the mainstream media is out to crush all at alternative media
It's a bit circular thing but it seems like the goal is to try and attempt to build some rapport
Effective possibly confusing Alex and getting him off his set
And it also makes it so the kinds of rebuttals can't really be used effectively
Alex can't excuse his behavior by condemning the mainstream media is marking to say you're telling me man but that's not what
Talk about
Does it get just sort of creating that
That's a camarada real most interesting that Alex is so
Such a weird dude
That you can play both good cop and bad cop
In the same deposition
You do like he's he's
He's f****** pinned Alex's ears to the wall
And and he still and Alex's still like you don't like the mainstream media me neither man
I think we got a lot of it is weird to hear like there's a bit of guard letting down
For your benefit
F****** railroad spikes through the Stigmata bed your f***
There's a bit of that and then another email from Wolfgang halbig is brought up
I want to show you this
Desert Marquez
This at the bottom it says fssa
What's TX
Europe
It is from Wolfgang halbig right
To a couple email addresses that I bet you don't
Another
Yeah the one safe and sound schools.org have you ever heard
Not my memory
I'm going to assume though that you see the address
Is is written to somebody named Michelle
Yes I got
And then
The subject line is
Irons Michelle
You stopped using
Josephine and making money
Speaking engagement
You saw that
Yes
December 21st 2040
At the bottom
Document
Glad yes
Attachment Theory see a bunch of PNG
That's correct
I'm going to go ahead and read the email to
Are you all right
This is another email somehow big and you'll notice that this one's dated prior to the one about the Superbowl choir which is
Where Alex is claimed to be realize how big is no good
So this email was an Infowars corporate files which itself is weird because no one seems to be copied on this email at
Itself
His existence of the files implies an awareness of its contents sent it wasn't emailed to them
Yeah so this wasn't good enough to get how they blacklisted and this is a mess
I'm going to go ahead and read it
You all right
Michelle
How could you and your husband as responsible parents even allow your precious child Joseph
Hoping to attend.
Filthy and deplorable looking
School
This school has has you must have known
Is and was a toxic waste dump
As reported by
Environmental
You requested more money
City of Newtown
L before demolishing
School in transport
All of the high levels
Lead paint
High levels of asbestos
And especially the high levels of
Pcps in the groundwater
At Sandy Hook
Out-of-state
Josephine your child should have expected more
Before that tried
Saturday is a pear
You are supposed to
Protector from
Sirius lifelong health
Sender to that
School everyday
Why would you as a parent and all those other parent
Supposedly lost a child
Gunfire
Allow their children as
You did
Mysterious toxic waste
This all unfolded before the first shot at that
School even occur
Did you not see the filth
Deplorable conditions when you went
To that school
Are you blind
I do not understand unless you ask
Explain it to me
And the world why you and your husband
Spell Josephine
Who is a nonverbal child as you stated in
Oh that was a big sigh
She's as big site
From all the serious helper
But you sending
A daily basis
Now you talk about schools to
You have got
You have all these experts on your staff who are now part of your conspiracy
They should be ashamed
If their actions in
Supporting you
A mom puts her own child at risk on a
The daily basis and
It is now the expert on school security
I look forward to meeting you one day
What I can take your deposition
The shooting but why you and your
Springfield jokes
By sending
Filthy and deplorable school with all that toxic
We call this child in danger
When you know the danger.
Expose your child to
Serious lifelong
You must have known without a doubt
Pictures do not and it says Ally but ugly
You put her life in serious risk everyday
Knowing how filthy and deplorable that school is
I am enclosing
Photos that you must recognize
You took your child
School and having a child and special needs you expect
The school environment
School climate
That allows children to learn in
Right
Please explain to me if you
Can wise
School principal Dawn hops
Would allow our school to be so filthy and deplorable.
There is not one female Elementary School principal in this country
Deplorable
Inside and outside
Most of all allow her to become a toxic waste dump
Placing every child in her work on brevity
Right
All the picture
Taken by the major crimes
Please respond since
The expert
Wolfgang's
WWE
Sandy Hook
Dot-com
I read that correctly
Yes
How you feel
Horrible
I never seen this before
We had it
That's all
Do you know
This is an email where how big is harassing and terrorizing the Sandy Hook family
This is before the play where Alex said he realized how big was Bad News Bears looks bad
And see if some of these groups are a little bit longer wear marks reading these emails and I think it's important because
It honestly was kind of a revelation for me to be understood that no how big was
Characterize this way the contents of these emails
And it really it really did make me
More seriously or anything cuz I already felt this was pretty serious.
Good personal space Park way more visceral and the actual Behavior
Is that he's contacting these family members into the things that he's doing it simultaneously to the time when Alex's promo
Loading him
It sucked it really just gets
Pretty inexcusable new rule for my life
Beaches that
I don't want to be around people
Who
If I were to have their emails read to me in a deposition
Are both
So awful I would have to sigh and put my head in my hand but also so long that I have
Have to do it multiple times the other a bunch of most like
You think you could not get more opportunities for one man to say oppa
Oh that was a bad one there's more
I guess what there's another email
Michigan Marshals exhibit 14
You see if the top is another email from Wolfgang halbig
Yes right this one
You see about right here
And so you see on your document to you
Enforce email address
Yes that would be robbed you and Nico who's email
This was
March 21st 2017
Got the subject was
Anyone needing the address for a visit
To welcome them to Florida
Please call and this was a great day
Who says that you cannot catch a big fish
In Florida
Subject line says
Just forgotten there's a PNG attached to
Is that correct
And then I'm going to go ahead and read this email to you
Here we have another email from how big and the date on this one is March 21st 2017
The timeline this is supposed to be after he realized that how big was not a good source
Possibly a Content warning this email is very disturbing I don't want to just spring this on people
Without a little bit of a heads up explicit
And then I'm going to go ahead and read this email to you
It says Nick and Laura Phelps did a great job at
Newtown on
Newtown Connecticut on December 14th
I visited their own today
At 1924 Westover Reserve Boulevard Windermere Florida
And thanks to Lieutenant van Gailey
Telling me during my wellness check of Nick and Laura Phelps
That they no longer live in Newtown Connecticut
And that they are no
And they are now Richard and Jennifer
Guess what
He is totally right
And can you believe it that my Newtown Police
Department guided me in the right direction
They have a
Beautiful home
Three car garage
They were not home today
But the good news was that
Female moms
Your children standing outside their homes
Observe me
Wanted to know what I
It was spring break it is spring break for Orange County Florida
Preschool children
I showed them this picture and I told them that I did not want to go to the wrong house
Surprise nickandmore up for Newtown Connecticut
AKA Richard and
Jennifer Sexton
I took a few minutes for them to look at the
The pictures
And then when they ask why I wanted to
I told them that I had been in Newtown and wanted to surprise them
Open a living for
They asked for my name which I gave them is Wolfgang how big
They told me how I would know them knew them and I told them if they had
They have been on the national news
So I wanted to
Miguel
Our conversation was all about Newtown Connecticut
So she said do you mind if I text
I said absolutely not
Waited about 10 minutes only to learn that they did not know me
Surprise me
They verified the
Pictures and why would she
Text them about Newtown Connecticut
And that someone from there once
Open to visit
If they hadn't if they were not Nick and Laura Phelps
Richard and Jen
At first I did not went to interest
What is a gated community
But several
People told me to
Just go on in there there was no such
Security guard at the
If there is
CTV they will see
Being told to go in and that is the only reason or I would not have
Now who says law enforcement
Thank-you Newtown Connecticut
Police Department
You turn the document over
First of all read that email correctly
And then on the back
There's a picture
At the top it says Sandy Hook hoax
Correct
Yes it has arrows pointing to the Phelps
At the bottom it says playing the part of
Yes
Horrible email
I never seen this email and it's
Yes I don't like this email and again this is someone else will King how big
After I'd already clearly know that he cracked hub
So that's that's that's not my work
Sucks dude bragging about stocking grieving families and that's unbelievable
Joe Pathak f****** serial killer that's a serial killer that should be treated with the same level
True Crime Tavarez a serial killer
It's hard to imagine something more unsettling in the context of
Like what Wolfgang could have been doing like most true crime documentaries the cops are the bad guy
Guys I don't know how much you take
You can see Alex essentially taking the bait that he set for himself
He's established that he knew how big was no good after the Superbowl thing in 2016 and then after that now this is
This email is
He would but like I said this is a trap that I'll accept by giving a pretty specific time.
When he has no excuse to not know that how big is it reliable and this immediately becomes a problem
Yes I don't like this email and again this is someone else will King how big
After I'd already clearly know that he crap table
So that's that's that's not my work
Next month
Ur22 video called Sandy Hook vampires
Someone
I've seen that
And during that video you repeat it all
I don't remember
But I believe it was about
People using it
Continue to try to get gun control in money
So yeah we have we have a demonstration
After this
Even though all this to your timeline doesn't make sense
Even after all this b******* that stocking a family's
Email the core fighting emails being sent to Miko and Rob like
After
The 2016 point when you had every reason to doubt his credibility as an expert
You're still repeating his things in the Sandy Hook vampires video believe he
That's
That's just dumb
In every direction
All the time it makes it so much easier 2.2 like okay so it's not supposed to trust him
Give me that that like
Tiny glimmer of hope of of just like now you know I haven't seen the video
Dude
We're at our whenever of this if he says he's got a video of you saying it and you have
Haven't seen the video
Click youcanplayit anytime man it's here I don't know I haven't seen the video
Is only going to get you out of answering this question now it's not a good answer. Good excuse
God damn it I mean I'm not even associate
Did with him and I'm making the sounds that Alex is making
Michigan
At the bottom you see it says FSX
TX
Dash 04
0027 corporate files
Just got
The top it says Wolfgang halbig
Right that's what's from
Okay it says to Wild Rose farm 1740
Gmail.com
Do you know who that is
The subject line
Says
How could you as a mother
Stop and buy your special brand of coffee on
1/14
B12
When you heard as a mom that shot him
Fired
School
You read that correctly
Yes this is a March temp
Email
Correct
He says in this email
Scarlet
It is just a matter of time
And all that money you have has to be returned
How could you even stopped
To buy your coffee
And you bought coffee for two other people
What kind of mother does that especially when you see on the news
Tell everyone how you ran across that fire
Parking lot
If you did
You would have spilled the coffee
Do some serious soul-searching
Does the scam is up
Wolfgang
Phone number
I read that correctly
So at least end
Infowars had in its corporate employees had received information
How big was harassing
Track
We get millions of emails I've never I never seen those up until the time of these lawsuits
Understand all I'm asking is
Infowars received
Yes
Another email where how big is harassing the families of Sandy Hook victims
Being Incorporated
From March 10th 2015 Richard Pryor to dispose cut off of Alex thinking how big is credible
The picture starts to come into focus a little bit where you at how big demonstrating a pattern of behavior
Reason to know about giving their access to these emails news director for the Nightly News being copy
Almost all of them also this doesn't come up in the deposition but Wolfgang how big was a guest on Alex
It's a show on March 4th 2015
Just six days before he wrote this email harassing Scarlett Lewis
And like
It's not hard to put some pieces together of
Wolfgang is on Alex's show
The website is website
It's conceivable that donations are
Are accrued by his appearance on here two days later he's engaging in this Behavior we're here asses
Grieving parents it's it's disgusting
Yeah yeah if I'm Alex in this situation I hear those three emails and I immediately switched actor
Texan I just go
A real piece of s***
We got to go get him and then I grab everybody and we go to Newtown Connecticut or whatever you need to go in Texas
Let's go see Mark you're deputized
I do this everybody has guns now cuz I'ma get my horse
Jesus what a piece of s***
F***** up f******
Wow
Yeah
It's also
Interesting to recognize that these evasions of I didn't know about this stuff no
No one knew about this stuff we get so many emails it just doesn't really fly
I wish we would have marked as exhibit
UCF football team is fsse
TX.
This is a 2015 email sent March 6th
Yes
And this is
The top email is
Nico
Forwarding something
Direct
And it says forward
Distance from a third-year lost
And then it says
Some comments on how big's last interview
Prolost
From a gentleman Neymar Darin from
It was sent to me.
Your contacts
He writes
Two cents from a third-year lost
Madam or sir
I'm in my final semester of Law School
I listen to the Wolfgang halbig video and some significant alarm Bells went off
I also wrote on the YouTube page but I copy and paste
Okay so let's so I just get this straight
Starting up 3130
He filed his lawsuit in Seminole County court in
Florida
Not in federal court in Florida but in State Court
There is a legal requirement called quote standing on
He does not have standing to sue in Seminole County
He was not a party in the shooting in any fashion
There is also a concept called quote jurisdiction
Either the man is lying or the judge is insane
A Florida county level judge would not have jurisdiction for any reason other than a contract or
Her crime issue
Indirectly involving how big
Something is completely wrong here
How do you say
Quote in the federal district of Florida quote
Or whatever Discord it might be if the state is split
That may at least be
Possible
This is completely insane
And cannot go anywhere but into the trash
No standing no subject matter jurisdiction no personal jurisdiction
Two cents from a third-year law student who is
Legally current
It is
Demand seems to be
Be grasping and stretch
No judge in their right mind would do such a thing as he describes
Here's an example imagine there's a crime in Las Vegas and the criminal killed him so
There is no law whatsoever
That would allow Alex
Or anyone else to file
San Antonio for anything regarding
The crime in Las Vegas
There's no claim that can be made in Texas
For something that happened in Nevada
It is a rule
Are there
So here we have
That not only
Did Infowars receive information
Suggesting that what how big was up to
Was completely insane
Enduring Brumfield work
But actually Nico ended up
Forwarding that information directly
Correct
Yes
Which is good that he found that we got 10,000 miles there like we did
What
It's good that we found in 2015
David wasn't shown to me but right
And so that's why I was
Yeah that it's good that it gets good good for you right now
Make my jaw drop more like well it's good that he found that once
Wait how could Rob do have kept this from me Rob I'd like you to also me
My friend bus
This might be bad for me
You know what
Rob sounds like a real piece of s*** is going to be busy
Very busy for awhile so
The pattern with these emails that is its kind of
I've been Illustrated I believe is
They have this horrible behavior that Wolfgang is engaging in evidence of
Is
Clearly in Infowars files people
On these
I cc'd on these emails such as forwarding them further
Emails
Is forwarded further from Niko to Rob is
The sanity maybe you would take a second look at the person
And notice that hey there's these emails where he's harassing Sandy Hook family members
You might you might think that would happen but I guess it didn't
This is a bizarre sort of picture that you get from these
These these emails but I think it's it's remarkable to see that Alex's response to this is
Bordering on what he would expect a person to feel these emails and like this is a horrible
Email that's that's awful I didn't know about this
That's exactly what you would do if you didn't know
Bad feelings
So after this week into a little bit of a conversation about dhanbad on D and
Alex sending him to to Newtown and
What is the plays the clip of Alex calling bonati the Kraken
The Krakens of mythological Beast right into
Alex respond to like you know the Krakens that's not somebody that
You knew he's going to go cause trouble and obviously that's the case
Of course
Which which version of the movie are you are you talking about
I have a lot of thoughts about movies
One last clip here from Alex's deposition
A question of
We've seen a lot of bad behavior from folks within Infowars Avi
Sandy Hook and Wolfgang
The question of editorial standards and
That kind of thing comes up she could have
Your company
Has never
Discipline
Due to
False facts
I don't remember
Good work not barns
You think it's possible you may have discipline Brad
I would say false
Robert
Pictures of the trouble for
Talk about it
I've tried to like you know
Stay out of it
And myself back into it
Stop
Strikes against
Remember Florida Posner
Optimal make a big thing with me and when I pause or I barely know who he is and I've seen him in some shows but I know I
I just did not
Yes I mean I did not want to
I had seen
Some of the anomalies
Proven
Amelie's
I wasn't sure that it was staged
Go back and forth
These Mysteries
What
So that's that's that's where I stand on that
That's not that it's not an ideal answer everybody
Have you punished anybody is there any consequences for anybody who's published.
Hey look at this industry I don't know I don't know how you could take this
To a jury
And not say to them like listen
This is a man who's already lost the case this is a man who's Underoath
Haha in a case that he lost
For saying that this is
Real
This isn't real
Or might not be or he still has questions over it we're well past the point where you can say like
Oh we'll have our day in court
So there's no way to do anything other than say this man has to be stuck
I think you know I think I think a lot of the
The appearance that you get from from this deposition is certainly a lack of remorse
A lack of haven't learned anything or lack of
Even seeming to be willing to understand the problem basic comprehension of reality
Yes
There's also clearly an indication that
He intends to continue them
I mean and and almost a a strange extreme solipsism
Is this like what are you talking about this happened outside of what I experienced so it doesn't matter
It's not real
Cuz I didn't read this email so it doesn't matter to me
Yeah and even beyond that
Like a real lack of institutional guardrails
Play Infowars where there is no
It's like standards for what they can or can't report there's no consequences for anything
Standards for sending the f****** prosecution
Plaintiff
A f****** black
Which you don't know you did you did what we got it before we would start with the journal
Wild
What's in the building
Tenaya Jordan
We jump over to the the deposition of
Car Polo boy
He was a little disappointed I believe I said that's what I'm talking to Mark that it wasn't robbed you again
Characteristics
Who asked
Yes
I think that will probably skip over a fair amount of this because it is
Deposition was a lot of just like I don't know
Like does the company know or not and I don't know I can't know if the company knows I don't know I don't know
Yeah there's there is a a ton of that and the position itself is like 5 hours
Long fry I'm so chop out a fair amount of that I just talked about what is
Doesn't matter what's the point here I got a little bit of like what would it be
We like to depose Donald Rumsfeld
I think it might take less long pauses before answering
Flicker single question
Call is much smarter than Alex
To you that would help you I will say that I think that some of the strategies that she doesn't Floyd terms of answering questions
Not much better and maybe are more shocking and way more expensive than other things out.
Strap
At the beginning of this at the start of question to try and nail down how much prepper
Duration Daria did for the deposition
And with whom she consulted
The preparation is clearly minimal and the kind of repetitive simonist get past that babe
How about its disgust
I'll put it this way on a scale of 1 to 10 she's not very prepared but a little more than Rob do
1.2 baby
It's not zero
Number one
Presenting Daria with a folder that she had brought along the container
To introduce into evidence brought along
Beautiful know I understand I've been given a folder
You do recognize this folder that I'm holding right here
Okay I've been told that these are documents that you review
Prior to this deposition
Yes
So you have taken
The documents that you prepared yourself for today and put them in this holder
I'm going to right now
Individually
Yeah.
Okay
Remember what I'm going to do is I'm going put a sticker on this folder itself
And we're going to mark that is exhibit 1
I want to talk to you about some of the documents in here
So each exhibit is going to be like
Without giving away any privileged information
This was the first one
Yeah I'm terms of like what day
So this was my first moments of being in the setting and
I was just like
I'd like I got to get a seat belt strap
Because here is where we begin with these documents
Marcus is 1 a
You recognize that correct
That's a document that you reviewed prior to this deposition right
That is the Wikipedia entry for false
Flag
Can you tell me why you looked at this document
I thought it would be a good idea to bring it on the rapper
Atomic number
If I could have
I understand we're send fact let's do that
Is referring to is the sourcing and research that went into the Productions of the videos that the
That are listed in the plaintiff's case so I don't know
She needs the false flag Wikipedia page for I felt like this had not started well
I was I was worried
I mean if if if I'm thinking about this now and I'm thinking about removing this
Sticker that says 1A
And putting a new sticker on that says great job
Four stars tell her to go home go by there
Chris Rod so here's the next document we get
So now I've handed you what I've marked as 1C
What you recognize correct
Correct and that is the Wikipedia entry for the reichstag fire correct
Stock fire was hey
A Nazi party arson attack
Correct
Can you tell me why this is Robert to the
Same answer as for
Go to previous
I thought it would be
Documentary
Some of the points
As an example of
Okay another Wikipedia page to paraphrase the one funny thing Pete Holmes ever said it's
Seems like you printed out a part of the internet for us to throw away yeah yeah yeah
It's strange because again as a corporate representative
Lionshare of wood
She's supposed to be discussing his like sourcing and Personnel who worked on the videos and question
And that is nothing to do with the reichstag fires Wikipedia
Fair enough
Open t1d
You recognize that
Okay
Where does can you read the website at the bottom what website does not come from
History today.
Okay so this is a history today article
About the sinking of the Maine
Correct correct
The USS Maine
Was a
19th century warship
Correct
And that warship exploded in Havana Harbor
There is significant
Historical evidence
To suggest
But that ship was intentionally exploded by the United States
That correct
There is a cop
What I'm what I'm wondering is from reading that article
Did you come away with the idea
That there is substantial evidence in other words non-trivial evidence
Which people could use to support the idea
But the USS Maine was intentionally destroyed by the United
What's a 1
Heard that
Can you tell me why
Particular article is relevant to your testimony today
It could be viewed as
Example of false
Throughout history
Cool
This point I think it becomes a bit clearer that the strategy the articles that has in the folder box
Illustrating that false Flags
And plus it's not right or left field for Alex to question whether any of that may or may not be another one
That's all good and well but it's really Superfluous to the questions at hand
Most interesting is that while being questioned about the article concerning the sinking of the Maine
Unwilling to commit to even saying that there's evidence it was a false flag only going so far as to say that there's controversy she's kg
Early early stages of this I thought
There was a little bit weird haha
But I guess maybe it could make some strategic sense in the air in that like to prove anything
The false flag
All you have to do is prove that some things people say are
Right eye I mean I want to ask this I just want to ask this question over and over and over again to all of these people
Call just like
Let's strip away all the b******* on a fundamental level
Do you know why you're here
Like just
Just like
Why are you what are you here to do
Yeah you know it's going back to have to get back to like fundamental
What is water is it the wet stuff is that it
Is it something else is it can you brief wash
Hey listen if you think waters are and that's how we have to talk about it and I have to say water is air and Air
Bridgewater that's f****** fine as long as we agree
Communication is the definition of terms you can't really
And I do think that has come into a problem with
Interacting with folks from Infowars As It Seems
From these depositions in particular that I've seen it.
It's it seems like you're not having your talking in different language
When we talked to Jon Ronson very briefly had this moment where we went kind of
Far off any just said you know he was wondering
How is it that we can Judge Alex you know just in this sense of like
Do we judge him the way we judge other people because he's clearly not
Like other people
Who can you judge him by what is the standard by which Alex can be judged
And it's like
When you have an entire organization that is thinking it's totally fine to print out a Wikipedia
Article and take it to a deposition
I don't know
They're alien
That's what that's what it is
What is like
Is this somebody's trying to Bluff a report
Like it like it like it doesn't care
Or is it active insult
Complete aliens I don't understand what is happening like the rest of these documents I'll help you sort that out
I'm sure they will
I'm going to put in front of u1e
You recognize that correct
Wikipedia entry for the Pearl Harbor Advanced knowledge conspiracy
Correct
Is this the same answers the other doctor
So this is another example
Potentially
What's The Back-up would you call this a false flag
Let me rephrase that
If the allegations about this conspiracy theory or true would you consider that a false flag
Another Wikipedia article about conspiracy theories about Pearl Harbor at six point made
I don't know you don't understand why we need more
At least of the documents are all just Wikipedia Pages some of them are bios for weirdos
Like the back of a book jacket
Yes it is an article
Nicole.
From
The website
Which
Biography
Which I wanted to
Okay so this is just biographical information about one of them for sources
So you got Wolfgang halbig bio
I am another buyer.
Alright I'ma show you the Marcus 1H recognize.
Dr. Steve pieczenik website isn't it
Enough with your biographies of dr. Steve pieczenik
And you wanted to have that
Steve pieczenik is somebody who has appeared on Infowars at one point
Talk about Sandy Hook
I do regret that unfortunately in this deposition more questions are asked about Steve pieczenik
Yeah because I think it having anybody has to answer for like
Some of the bulshit bio
How much of this do you actually think it can you tell me what's true and what's not true you brought it into evidence
That's what's going on now I mean I don't think it matters much
But at least it seems more relevant to
What you might bring
Right then there's another document in there
And this is where things start to get
Real picture things are real f*****-up at this point is really weird
Okay I'm going to show you now what I have marked
That's one eye
You recognize that
That's a guardian article right
Guardians of our newspaper brittenum I read about that
Article says
Its headline says Sandy Hook father Leonard Posner on death threats
I never imagined having to fight for my child's life
What did you need this article for
Why did you feel you wanted to review this article.
After this there is a long pause because a long pause
I don't know if it's a long pause of like trying to remember why or is it was like how do I say
Goes off
Love f****** rails
The reason I wanted to have this article
Is that I saw it
One of the victim's mother
There was a
Information regarding
And her request
President review
Seems to me that
The motivation
Death
Man another reason for it is cuz a bunch of people are saying that travels
Could not be a reason for it
Oh boy
Oh boy she is a guardian articles that references How Stella Rosa
To have an open-casket funeral
This feels real marked I see I'm not stoked about the direction it's going
I mean if your child
Right
What's a 6 years now your child walks in elementary school and is massacre in a gun
And some news organizations are saying that your child is
Can you see that a possible way to combat that would be to have an open cast
That's not something you would ever consider
You could use converging help somebody else could consider
So you think
That this
Jewish families
Choice
Turn open casket funeral
Fairchild
Was politically motivated
I'm going to inject his being outside the scope for corporate representative stefanik
Discuss this objection and then they determined she should answer the question
I thought Brad finally had one good thing might be fine but it's it's
Answer the question the question back okay
And
What has being Jewish
I'm not here to answer
I don't know
Make my personal opinion
And I would never
People have open-casket funerals everyday don't they
Yes however considering the circumstances
And how
The child was
Figured
Okay
Sorry I didn't pick up on this but the reason that Mark brought up the fact that the parent is tuition decided to have an open-casket funeral
Golfer Sun
Is because that's a huge deal
The most Jewish Traditions it's not acceptable to have an open-casket funeral
Out of respect it's traditionally understood that you're not supposed to gaze upon the face of the deceased
Person of Jewish Heritage make a decision to have an open-casket funeral because people were saying that our son didn't exist
Very strong conviction that the world not be allowed to pretend that this didn't happen
Or try to meant mentally hide behind safe images
Asmarani cuz the mother in question told the forward
Quote I just want people to know the ugliness of it so we don't talk about it at stract Lee like these little angels went
The heaven know they were butchered they were brutalized
And that's what haunts me at night
It's a subtle Nuance that's being hinted at in this question that's completely missed by Dario because in preparation for this deposition
It doesn't seem like she's done all that much
Spill
A little better prepared than robbed it's impossible to beat that bar never going to do worse than him
Wild Thing
I mean the worst part out I guess drunk
The strange thing is I believe her
But
Partially because she's on the other side so she's not going to do that stuff because she knows it won't f******
Do a thing I kind of agree with you not emotionally agree that she is not lying
Do this for political reasons and if you had a heart you would never do
Somebody would do it sounds it sounds like
So we got another article this is weird
There's another article about that right
Exhibit one
Jay
Do you actually two separate articles
About Noah Pozner funeral having an open car
Correct
I pulled this one article because of his LinkedIn the guardian
And I wanted
I'm thorough baby
Okay
And so
Of all the documents that you've reviewed
Regarding the plaintiffs
The only ones you've reviewed that you chose to go review
We're two articles about mrs. Bozeman choosing to have an open casket
Correct
That wasn't the real
Article
That's not what I'm asking you
I'm asking you of all the documents reviewed about the claims
Before this deposition
The only two that you did review
Are articles that discuss Noah Pozner funeral having an open casket
Correct
They happen to mention
I'm not saying that I'm not I understand what you're saying
Let's make it even broader than for you
The only two pieces of documentation
If you have reviewed for this deposition about the plaintiff
Are two articles
Both of which discussed in the article
Noah Pozner open casket
Correct
Tell me any other information from those articles that you believe is irrelevant to the deposition today
I've already mentioned.
Physical body
Okay so when it comes down to the documents that you reviewed for this deposition about the planets
The only information that you really cleaning from this that useful to the stuff
Deposition
How to
Add concerns Noah Pozner open casket and appearances
Correct
It was used
I'm not asking what it's useful for
It's this is bizarre
Like it
Do you have Wikipedia articles
Steve and Wolfgang self-written correct and multiple articles about to deposit
Noah Pozner having a open casket funeral
Subtitle this deposition
It would be
When you say it like that weight
Every time it's like she hears it for the first time
Oh well when you put it like that it sure sounds like I'm an a******
Deep bizarreness
This is just the amuse-bouche of how bizarre this is going to get
Mark tries to get into the actual topics that she's there as a corporate representative to discuss
And that's that is a
As a dead end
Number one
Is a sourcing research
The videos described Appliance petitions
When the last time you watch those videos
Backup made an assumption that
If you watch the videos
Ever in your history of in divorce
What okay
So what you say is
That in preparation for this deposition you didn't watch those
I'm sorry
Well I've already answered
Right now I understand that you have in your history Infowars
You probably on occasion seen some of these video
I understand
What I'm asking you is since the date you were told you were given this deposition November
And you were preparing for this deposition
So
This is
The bad start cuz you now know that like you not going to really be familiar with the V
Videos in question
Right Alright is kind of limiting is your ability to testify as a percent
Yeah
Once we established here that she hasn't watched these videos and preparation
It turns out the also that bike by extension that means she doesn't even know
What they say
You see that
Paragraph 14 identify as of January 27th 2013 video
Entitled
Why people think Sandy Hook is a hoax
Okay
You're familiar with the claims made in that video right
Fraction form
I don't recall the exact video
Inside sitting here today
You're not coming with the claims made in that video
And because of this
So much of the questions that are being asked end up being a jerk guessing I don't know
What are the sources with as well I would assume that it's Wolfgang halbig
Or you know like I have an educated guess that it's this person
What did you do to try and figure out if anything I'll who made this video who worked on this what are the sources
I mean how do they pick who shows up for the did they throw a dart or something
Like what is happening I think there's an Infowars Elder who goes into a trance
Choose somebody bananas
Yeah confidence with which you would walk into what amounts to
The end of your professional career
So we're going to skip a bunch of the back-and-forth of just like
Who did who did this
Probably Wolfgang probably will
And there's a lot of it because it's not relevant
Sure of how
Unprepared she was for this deposition and the lack of respect being shown
But it in terms of we're doing the show also right
It was clearly in the room
A question about
The Super Bowl
Right so this is the pic of it Alex was asked about no B
Pico and we we couldn't determine whether or not Alex at answer if this is crazy
Actually he did you did say it was crazy
Here is a market beginning to bring this up to you Daria
I'm just trying to make sure
Have you or have you
I don't recall
Reading desperate
Change
I'm just started the bottom here
And this is this document of readings from you is
Marked f.s.s. Texas
Fsspx
Dash 03
And you will see the bottom email mr. how big right to Nico
Do you know who Nathaniel folks has the person who copies
No
Nickelodeon Infowars employee
What's a job title
At this time
He would be
Niko's no longer employed by Infowars
Infowars possess his last known contact information
Mister how big in this email
States Nico the picture of the Sandy Hook Elementary School choir
Is one of the keys
Other pictures are great for discussion
These
Are the CT crime picture
Yes
Fumiko responds and says got the Super Bowl picture thank you for sending
We will be having we will be calling you on Skype at 1 p.m. eastern time
How long will you be available for the interview today
Thanks Neko
I read that correctly
The final email says
As long as you and Alex can put up
Yes just help you refresh your memory about what the Superbowl picture is
Niko's response
I will see if I can say one positive thing about Wolfgang how big is it sometimes
Wolf
Yeah but it's not consistent
Yeah I know I think if my name was Wolfgang I'll be constantly making people call me wolf
We get to talk about the Super Bowl tickets
God this is
I don't even I'm
Having trouble figuring out how to display
Prepare you for how insane I can't be prepared
Michelle Martinez
You take a look at that picture for me
Do you see at the bottom corner
What does fsspx
For sex
Yes
Have you seen this picture before
Personally I have not
This was a document though you can tell from it
Number to bottom that was
Produced by the company correct
Can you read what it says at the very top of the picture there white text
10 Sandy Hook children found alive
This
The company now admit that this picture is
Outrageous
Injections for
Rubbermaid B listen it's been a long f****** trial
And you guys have been dicks are you ready to admit that this is outrageous excuse me are you ready
To say you're full of s*** neener neener neener go f*** yourself
So apparently this is this is this is worth an objection deteriorates
What I'm saying is if there's an expert
And you better remind on
Gospel Smith School Safety shooting expert whatever it is
You're relying on it
And then
Hypothetically
That person to start saying
Absolutely crazy
And it's pretty clear they're going off The Rocker
Maybe they were even credible at one time
But suddenly they start saying a bunch of crazy things
To the company when is deciding whether to put stuff on about Sandy Hook
It needs to get it should consider whether what the things its expert Usain
Are crazy
Correct
She's the expert
To knows a lot more
On the subject that any of us
Working
It would be reasonable to believe that
Want to listen what
Information
What exactly
In Wolfgang halbig history
And expertise
Makes him an expert that you should defer to
On whether this
Picture of the Super Bowl choir
She's actually
Pictures of children who were murdered
Well that's a good question that's why I brought his bio be capitalized
Read
No
You just like you know or what
No Wyld no wild dogs
No really interesting is going on there is like Dory is essentially appealing to Authority you know like
Just was like really
You're going to you're going to tell me if the expert says crazy things
They're not crazy because this person the expert those things by being said by this person
Become credible that's
Weird Helga
So what you're telling me is that the editorial standard for Infowars
Is if somebody was an expert
We would
Believe them
Do we even qualify that for that's a good point if they claim to be an expert
So before we even get to expert if you make up credentials for yourself that I really impressive you get to just
Do whatever you want so you're telling me that the information from the
The mainstream media do a lot of backgrounds for 11 hours a day
Until 5 in the morning sometimes always researching you're telling me that you don't need to verify any that should I drop
So Mark wants to know if this person this picture of the Superbowl choir that was sent to me go
It was made by a sane person sitting here right now
This was not created
Irrational
Saying
Human being or are you going to tell this jury
That this is creative
Buy rational sane human being
I don't have an opinion
So you see this picture
And I'm trying to determine whether it was created by saying rational human being you look at it and go I have no phone
Feelings either way
Correct
I'm not a psychiatric Medical
Who's playing
That's better quite at quite a response I mean you know
Listen
Goldwater rule what you going to do if there's really no way around that from like a questioning perspectives really like
Like I guess you aren't but right
You're just trying to dodge the question of the gate that very clear if you look at this would be like
This is
Well as Mark said outrageous the problem with this little chunk right here is
We're in a situation where
The rules are such that you can't Mark can't be like a listen
You know and she can't be like
I know
But you know right and he can't be like what yeah I know I know why just level with me for a second
Everybody knows what's going on this is so infuriating to me it's because Mark knows she's full of s*** and she knows she's full
I agree I agree that that is a frustrating guide
Listen to me
That Dynamic brakes changes good in the midst of this convo
Versation about whether or not a sane person would make this Super Bowl picture and
Oh my God
You would disobey I sent you this while you were doing reporting you would thank them for it
I don't know it depends on
Okay well the circumstances
Having discipline
James Walden
Why I'm asking you what if you with this information
A picture that says at the top
10 Sandy Hook children found alive and well
End of the Super Bowl choir
From millions of people
Would you look at that and go
Personally
I would
Rather think that those kids were alive
Then
Hiding
Because I want it
Murdered
For no reason
Innocent
Children who didn't
Deserve what
That
I would
Hold out hope
To the last bit of my
Soul
Hoping
Praying the
That picture
It was
That that was something that
Possible for those kids
Pedialyte
If I saw that picture and then ask somebody question about that picture and then they gave me that response
Would throw a table through the wall I almost gasp that is f****** crazy
Such a bizarre response of the questioning over the Superbowl picture it's not even relevant to the question she was being asked
I'm tired of her own
Desire to express this okay
It's really hard to understand this mentality unless you recognize the people like Daria and I would assume most of the be
Don't ascribe to the rules of reality with things like cause-and-effect or object permanence
In her mind choosing to believe that the kids who were killed at Sandy Hook are actually secretly of the choir at the Super Bowl
Optimistic idea because the alternative is choosing
To believe that the kids are at
There's so many problems with this idea in the most obvious being that which is describing as a speculative living in a fantasy world cup
Is realities too tough
But also she seems to be ignoring how
This isn't an isolated thing like if the kids at Sandy Hook were secretly in that choir the implications of that are horrifico
And I don't I don't know if this would actually be an optimistic scenario
Just pulled off a massive they were rubbing it in
I suspect those kids would not live past halftime
These are the people who work for the literal devil they're not above that s***
I find it hard to believe that if the globalists did something like this they would just leave those loose hanging threads
Out there I mean for your response to that question to just be like you know
I choose hope
And it's just f******
So when I heard Daria say that I thought well this trip has been worth it.
You had heard something that was completely unpredictable I never expected
Good here and then it actually even goes on
So if you think about it
If you think about it
It's apparent to my clients on this picture
They should they should react positively to this
Directions
Inform
I'm not though
There is I'm looking at it as
Cider
And I would much rather and I don't know a person
Hard would rather
Think
Rather believe that the
Dad
Versus
It's might be a lot
I would say it's reasonable for a person with a heart
To have that sort of
Optimism
I'm sure Alex one
You said those kids if there was any possibility
But the kids
We're Not Dead
Then she was going to grab onto it be
Because that's a much better
Proposition
Have
Heart and mind
Then
To realize that
Alex Jones
According to
The company View
Alex Jones
Said the kids didn't really die
And they were really alive
Impart
Such a big
And a lot of Hope
Attractions
If you might not have heard it cuz the lawyer was talking but she said yes
Truly bizarre and remember this is somebody testifying at a corporate
Official capacity and still decided to take a very ill-advised
The editorial position of info
Warriors and Free Speech systems is that not only was Santa real in Miracle on 34th Street he is real
Outside of Miracle on the 34th Street
If I were Mark I would have kept pressing on this line of thought to really determine if Daria thinks that her believe somehow affects world
Like if she believes that are thinking that the kids were alive has any bearing on whether or not they are actually alive
From these comments I am not sure
I mean you know that's the weird thing that I'm getting right now I was so quick to believe her earlier
Whenever she said that she wouldn't do that stuff because I do believe that she does things
Take that if you were
I knew that you would never engage with conspiracy theorist if your if your kid dies because
It won't matter either way like that makes sense to me
She sang this with the same
Tone of of like emotional honesty and this is batshit crazy yes there are a couple Moana
Commence where you get that outside of the I don't know right like a b or c
Suzanne I didn't do anything to prepare for this moment speaker like
That I was like really stand out
And I think
This one is particularly upsetting about
Like the fact that she can't register or refuses to register that
What that
Obviously
It makes her idea look absurd of course to parents are Furious
So here's the dumb thing you said I'm going to take it to a logical endpoint
And now you're going to see that it's dumb and she's like well
I would rather die than see that it's actually much more comfortable to live in this dumb place
Congratulations if you have a heart
How
Could you not believe that I am riding a unicorn home after that we record this show you have a heart
There is there is also this focus of like having a heart
Sure we've arrested destroyed many people's lives but that's cuz we have a heart
For the good of
Hearts all of you lawyers trying to get some sort of remuneration for the Sandy Hook families that we've bad
Edgerton and horrific Lee f***** with
For the past 10 years or whatever it is
Those people call in for Cheerios cuz heart healthy heart friendly
Alright so sorry
There's more questions that you can't answer about sourcing the end up taking a break
And this is where I was like oh my God
So I think there's a recognition they like she's in trouble
She they're talking about an April 22nd 2017 video call Sandy
Vampires exposed
You understand that at the video that mr. Posner and
Delarosa baster
Summation Clement
Did you know that
When preparing for the stuff
You watch that video
I mean unless you watch that last couple hours you haven't watched
For this deposition
Familiar with the video
Did you watch it
In preparing for this deposition though
Okay
When did you watch it
Earlier today when
What's the during the break
When
It became apparent that you hadn't walked these videos you wouldn't try to watch this video
Didn't watch the whole thing
Cuz it's a 45-minute video right
Yes he didn't watch the
Pieces of this video correct
How many pieces did you watch how many minutes so did you watch it
Video
Did not count
That's a tough thing to admit to it as a corporate representative
I recognized a couple hours into this deposition that I was so it under
Water operation that I should have done beforehand
So when I came into this I was
Judging myself by Rob do standards really thought that I could do no wrong
Because I brought in Wikipedia articles and that was
Exactly
But the but now after talking to you I'm realizing that I really should have crammed for my homework
Yeah I should have done something really nice
I watch the video during the break that was I think we'll play well
Jesus Christ
So this next judge read that right somewhere along the line
Line a judge is going to go
You tried to watch it when it's mixed with an email exchange
Change between Rob do in Tampa.
So damn batondy had wanted to get clearance for some man on the streets
Question do you want to do do man-on-the-street piece
And Rob do responded no
Go to Newtown cover Sandy Hook
Okay so what we see basically here so just a pose questions to ask random people on the street right
Threatened and been in a follow-up email from Rob do he doesn't want Dan to do that right
Ryan is going to be old by the time they can Aaron
So he says go to Sandy Hook we will cover that
Intentional Choice by Mr ddr2 want to get Gambit Auntie to go to Sandy
Correct
Denature
The news
24-hour news
How was
Excuse me I'm sorry
Yeah how is Sandy Hook in the news on 77 2015
Don't have
Right
So you don't know that it had anything to do
Despite the fact
Alex
Have not mentioned
The news
Immediately
Resay purveyor
When you saying
Go to Sandy Hook we will cover that
Infowars
Is being a purveyor
You're almost almost three years after Sandy Hook
Is being a purveyor of Sandy Hook cover
Correct
No
What is that that is he saying that we're going to cover it and not air it
Your intent to put whatever Gambit on he does on the air correct
And then again
In answering this question you speculated out of thin air
That there was something going on around January 7th 2015 that put this in the news
That made it
Timely
But you that was pure speculation you have no idea what that might be
Correct
Picture of our news.
Yeah you're going to make news do you understand that
You're sending down badani there to with Wolfgang halbig
Do you know what they did there
I'd like to hear that you doesn't know if I were the corporate representative I would
Definitely know that and I would have written some a long explanation for why it's somehow okay maybe
Be some kind of rationalization at very least because it's it's bad
Aquinas would have been proud of whatever I'd written to try and get out of that b******* cuz it takes a lot
Fun because I actually walking how big was harassing people at Catholic
Actually appropriate they were probably cistercian monks so there's another email
A donde that leads to a little bit of drama in the room
All right what we have here is from truth radio 9990 at hotmail.com
End
This was something sent to Rob do at Infowars right
Okay and so we have this email here
Dan batondy stating
Someone you may want to get
In that documentary on Sandy Hook
And it says forward Dan
Alex announced that he's going to do a Sandy Hook.
Film
Sheila Matthews who you met in Hartford At A Helbig hearing
Is a friend of mine who lives in the next
Town and I'm going to guess that says
We don't know what it says after that but then it says Sheila asked me to provide you with her telephone number it gets
Right
Bright and then robson's it to you
And this is April 24th 2018
And he says if Alex wants to go to Sandy Hook route
They want to get this lady on
Correct
Okay so this is just shortly after
The company was sued
Right
That's why he wants to make this documentary right
Not sure the exact
For Alex
What is the Sandy Hook what is that
Suggesting a guest and a writing an email
Isn't that Alex is wanting to or planning to make
Documentary about Sandy Hook
In 2018 the Sandy Hook route all right now there's not a lot of beaches in Austin but there are some
I meant when you go to the beach all right there's sand everywhere and I don't know if you've heard about Saint sand is actually a bunch of crashed you know like
You could be rocket glass it could be any number of thanks and right and we were going to go fishing
Fishing there's a sand
We were going fishing
There's a whole working on a
Sort of a scene you're like sort of a a tableau decorative piece
It was Peter Pan vs Captain Hook all of the characters with cancer
Yeah that sounds like a delicious treat mat is the route
Generally speaking is that like
Maybe Alex would want to have on the show as a gas right understanding that much
Now she's just trying to evade answering a recognizing that there was at least some
I'm kind of in internally discussed plan that I was wanted to make a documentary about Sandy Hook
In 2018
And the damper dondi was sending
Sources the question about the funding sources
This is where things that go off the rails
If Rob do was sending
To you
A source from Dan Vaden
The truth Warrior
We can be fairly certain
But that guest
Was going to support the idea that Sandy Hook was
Assumption
Don't answer that question
Why not because that's extremely misleading
That's not a proper basis to objective had been added into the rule
Can you read my question back
So it's pretty clear that the reason that this was a question that if you can pull off
Are you don't want to your client answer you don't need to know about that
To be suggesting of gas but for him to send Gaston the subject of Sandy Hook reference
I meant for Rob to forward that on to Dari at that indicate that there was internal action being taken on batondy suggestion
It wasn't just something that they ignored like they want to pretend they always do with Stanford
Get 10000 emails a day obligation is clearly that there was an interest in interviewing guests who would support
Did the Sandy Hook was a hoax narrative
After Alex got sued
In the case and that's why Brad the lawyer is saying don't answer that question
Sandy Hook
Have her answer the question removed
I will I will move to composite answer that if you're having or not answer that question
It's very clear what you're trying to hide
I wanted a divorce
I don't appreciate the
That's where I'm at is a threat and I don't really appreciate it
You know what
Look at where we are in this case
Go ahead and if you know the answer to question proceed with answering the question
I get sent a lot of guests
Daily basis
There's no way
For me to know this
Would be
Pro
Sandy Hook
No idea
I don't think that's that's a reliable answer
Fine it'll just look that just looks like obfuscation
What Brad's up to I mean maybe Brad's just like I got to make it look like a
Working because
If I was Brad I'm just looking at H man
I think he gets the implication of answering that question and if you can if you can pull off and
Objection there
You might want to totally crucial again
You're going to be fired in like a month or two if past is Prelude Alex's lawyers
Not long on the job
Come on man
We both know what's going on here
So
This leads to an assessment
Of how badonde what is he up to
You know what Danville. He believes about Sandy Hook don't you
You personally d'arrigo Provo
You don't know
No as an Infowars producer here to testify his behalf of the company you also didn't do anything to prepare to know what Dan Vuitton
Right that's not part of the topics you were asked to talk about today
I know David
You
You were testifying here right now
Damn it. He's a good reporter
Insofar as him trying to
What happened
You seen any videos of Damage Done in Connecticut and what he did
You're watching
You might not be the best person to qualify to talk about whether dammit. He was a good reporter in Utah
Objection forms not what she said
That's what I'm asking her a question bro
I'm asking you
You may not be the best qualified person
To talk about what Dan to Donnie did in Newton
Correct
You'd arika Provo
My definition
So you don't you can do but you can admit to me right now you don't know what them. Need it in Utah
Do you know about Saint Rose of Lima Catholic School in Newtown for debit on the other Wolfgang hybrid there
Casa Catholic School in question Priceless almost like
The corporate representative being unaware of
What damper. He did but also saying that
She's great reporter reporter
Cuz you can just play he's a great reporter and then show the footage of him yelling at people
Newtown I mean I assume they think that's what a great reporter does I think so persistent
Yeah they're very very shallow people
So one of the questions in this case is regarding whether or not
The
Sandy Hook
What kind of materials were used strategically in terms of marketing
Absolutely not
Has Infowars when making its editorial discussions and decisions
About the Sandy Hook cover
Has it ever attempted to use at Sandy Hook
Story
Videos
In a strategic way
To attract viewers
The idea that we would
Make some video uploads about Sandy hookers
Strategic measure
That's not something that
Would be a
Would be a part of Infowars editorialist
Never
Never okay
All right so I'm a quarterback in the pocket
I'm starting to feel pressure all the sudden I'm starting to see the defensive end running straight towards my
The question is not a common happy question that is going to end with your answer be accepted is okay it's a
You don't have a football and all the rules have been lifted
There is no offensive line get your ass kicked
Crusader marked as exhibit 15
Can you tell me who the top here it will actually make sure that the bottom
At the bottom corner you see this Mark says ffs
T-Rex
Dash 07
60-69
No can you tell me first let's just look at the top of the email who is Darren
Danny McBride
Through his title in 2015 do you know
Editor
Okay and Rob do we talked about correct
Louis we talked about right
Okay the next other person that's on here is Travis Knight
You know that person is
I'm going to end you know what their job position is
And then
This
Emails being sent from Lewes to Travis Knight Rob do and Darren
And the subject
Is video files for Facebook upload
On September 24th 2015
That's correct
Yes
He asked them
Can I get these video files for future strategic Facebook upload correct
One of the files that he is asking for is why people think Sandy Hooks is a hoax correct
So we can tell from this email
Denton and Darren follows up and says any luck finding
Correct
Yes we can agree from this email that editor Darren and Louie s
We're attempting to use
A video about Sandy Hook being a hoax
As a future strategic Facebook upload
Correct
It's one of the video
Videos out of 8 videos
Sure so it is one of the videos being used for a future strategic Facebook upload correct
Objection form
Yes
But won't you consider that it wasn't just a second was a stripper
Well I mean like I think obviously you ask the question with the word strategic and
Yeah cuz you know that
Preparing well I would I just would never have expected
Them to really have used the right I think that at a certain point there probably wasn't a cancer
Now they just didn't give a f*** amazing
Of Wolfgang halbig
Cuz obviously he's a source for a lot of the stuff
It's probably just how big stuff that you brought
Word for word let's go on to talk about Wolfgang halbig would you mind opening up your blue folder for me
You see that article on top
Destiny brought today and you were talking about how much you were talking about like you wanted to read it
Today right
To talk about Wolfgang's qualifications
So this article that you brought
Is what you believe you is
Let me ask you this
Is that something that Infowars had before you went look for it for your deposition or is that something that you got for your deposition to help
Buick
The ladder
Okay
So before this deposition Infowars did not have this document in its corporate
Correct the files that I looked
Throughout
Search for
Bayou
As well as
Stephen memory hold on
Article
Archive
What
I'm sorry what
He listed his bio
Did you go try to search Wolfgang, Google did you do that
Okay and so when you say good memory hold I take it you're ignoring the dozens of mainstream articles about
You don't want to use the mainstream articles
Specifically
Bionicle
Okay there are mainstream articles that talk about Wolfgang's
Credentials or
Is electrode intros right
Did you see any of those
I've looked at many of them and I did not
See an actual
Biography
His accomplishment
Okay
Instead this exhibit 1f
Written by dr. Pol
You know who that is
I did not I didn't bring it for the author I brought it for the
Bio-data
So now if you're sitting there you have brought this
Yeah and if
Do you know the name dr. Yuan for example is pretty
Detailed look at small detail of this thing that's being brought up you probably should maybe recognize
It's for real no I would be like hold on can I have that document real quick and then shred it
Absolutely
You can't prove s*** man cuz there's bad news about this
Do you have any face
Sitting here today that the information contained in that article is accurate
Yes because even the people
Who disagree with Wolfgang
Can how big
Admit
That he has a lengthy
Who said that
I've read it
Indifferent
I thought you said his body was the memory
Acknowledged
Antibiotics
That violet
Cupboard
But I could not find the app
Natural biotic
Accurate mean to you think it's covered accurately there
That's what you think
Okay and the person who wrote that doctor you in do you know who that is
Don't have a last name right
The person who wrote
Go back and look at the first page
Understand the article was supposed
Bye
Said Doctor
Did you win
The Bayou
That's been
You started here at 7 type 2
Screenshot
From where
A boy
I do not have the source
Exact Source where was
Printed from
You have no idea where that came from
People who disagree with how they can who criticizes admit that his
Biotin
I am still waiting to see that do you have any information you can point me to that
Anybody you say who's an opponent of albuq who admits that he has an impressive bio
Those documents
That's what I
Thought I needed for you but
Instead faction I did the research
Into my satisfaction
Does bio
Text out let's talk about what's currently a screenshot that you cannot identify where it came
From printed an article by dr. Aon
Who did you who first what that's
Did you know that the doctor that you Uber
Into here
Is only good for my case wrote a chapter of Jim Panthers book
You want to be more closely associated with Jim Fetzer
The more trouble for yourself by bringing this biome has
Double-decker of deposition the yeah
So I'm going to skip a couple of Clips here because they're long and they actually achieve
In all of these and that is a
If you'd known that how big was a bad Source right would you have acted on it early
Bruno and then of course bark produces an email from March 2014
This is no good and then a Don Salazar responding to the guy
There's there's interaction with this person who clearly bringing up before
They stopped having him on the show that he appears to be full of s*** right and then they did nothing they took no action on
Nitrite didn't double-check his credentials or like whether he was a reliable source
I mean it looks bad but it's
Kind of a bunch happen in these depositions feels like
And this is what is getting into my head
It feels like
Neither Alex nor endless space it does not understand that when they are in a day
Deposition
The plaintiff is not asking them questions
For fun
This is not because they know the answers
The deposition is for you to say something dumb bulshit
And you're doing that yes and oh my God oh my God
Emails from Wolfgang that were harassing Sandy Hook
Alex responded to them
Mel lipsey
Daria does
This first one is about the 30 school email daughter go to school
Here's Daria steak on it
Okay so first of all
How do you how does the company feel about this email
Inform what's your objective
Vague
How come you feel
Feelings
Good work friends
Asking
Seems to be
Concerned
Wellbeing list
Child
Thank you Moscato
Actually I want to read this email to the records we can talk about it okay
Mr Hamid rights Michelle
How can you and your husband as responsible parent even allow your precious child Josephine to attend that
Filthy and deplorable looking school on December 14th 2012
The marker even afterwards because she was responding to having read it to herself she was like silently reading it
That was wild is all the way through
Amex only become clear if they're being asked about the same documents
You know it's it's it's really weird
Where how big is harassing his parabatai filthy the school was is
It sounds like a person who's concerned about the well-being of the child
It's just so great to know that someone cares while Alex reads it is Invictus custard
There's a couple things that I can think of that might explain these different responses
The first is that they may have prepared for the depositions differently so Alex might have been slightly more prepared
2nd to the possibility that Alex has at least a modicum of emotional intelligence and CapTel
But he's supposed to not make excuses for an email like that wears darya's Justin like cover-your-ass and deflect mode
I was thinking about this or as I call it researching in my mind I think they came up another possibility
This feels like maybe it's connected to Dara's bizarre comments about it being a function of optimism to promote
Call the idea that the children from Sandy Hook was still alive
No one with a heart would want to believe that Wolfgang halbig was an almost Cartoon Level assholes that is free time Horizon
Anyone with a heart would want to believe that he's just very concerned about the janitorial staff at the school
Yet another option I considered as that it's really difficult as an emotional thing to confront near to see
The actions in the real world of a person who you were an active participant in promoting
When you see that he was harassing and stalking these parents and you know that you're not working all your co-workers were whitewashing his
Patience raising money for him and effectively enabling his behavior that's got to be a bit of a gut punch
I can kind of see why you might want to pretend it's not real
Here's my take on
Cuz I I see where you're coming from
And I'm going to be far less generous
Lives are roles
I I see it
More like
In order to be the host
Write in order to be on screen
In order to attract an audience
People have to be able to make an emotional connection
They have to
So
Whether or not you are a true psychopath or whatever it is you want to say at the very least you have
To have the emotional ability to evoke emotion with Alex all the time with faking crying and
And I would save it
To work
With Alex
It would require a an abdication of
General human
Sympathy and empathy entirely that would kind of make sense why Dari has never been an on-air personality
I mean the one I think about it the more I think about people like you know listening to Dari is deposition I think about
F****** Tucker Carlson
You know like
Tucker Carlson can go on his show and if he didn't have editorial people
Stopping him
He could
Easily
Easily do all the same Alex s*** he's just got a bigger network with people reining him in
And those people
AR
Psychos like it's the only way that you can work with a f***** like Tucker Carlson
And not kill yourself
So I think Daria is just a stone-cold f****** psychopath you can say that and you mean like
Obviously you're violating the Goldwater rule
I think that some of these answers and you know this trend that you see of like
Kind of
Hey what if we pretend everything is good
I think that it's it's a bizarre way to engage with the world
And
It does kind of at least speak to that difference that that dynamic
Alex knows what is expected of him
Right to appear normal
Doesn't care
I should be out a job she will be out of a job that was going to happen anyway probably
So now we get her response to the email about the stocking where how big showed up at these people's house
And was talking about talking to their neighbors right I wonder what her responses
3 million creepy
You personally
Done preview out to have Wolfgang halbig showing up these peoples houses and describing a three-car garage and all that stuff
Accusing them of being people or not
Actually aren't that doesn't Ellen Avenue
Yami strong feelings one way or another.
Jackson storm
Are you asking
Yeah your personal opinion
Strike me the passion man who
Who's doing investigation something to eat
Don Hardin
Capella
That's a bike down
Lowe's give to f****** Congress are willing to watch the humanity
We don't give a f*** response thank you
Almost like you can tell the to containing of elation can't believe you said something that's going to be so
So damaged
Refusing to see like these negative things how big did
The other email was concerned about the cleanliness of the school on this one
Rationalize that I think it probably feels like good spin at the moment but this is a huge mistake
Cuz it a deposition setting you need to be considering that your words are going to be played for a jury
You should account for them having basic human emotions
Anyone in the jury who reads or hears that email is going to be disgusted by how big's actions because
Clearly man stalking grieving families and when they see you making excuses for it or characterizing it as just
Passionate investigator
That's going to look really bad for you
Is it gives the strong impression that you're either lying to cover something up or maybe
You actually don't think that how big stocking these families was that bad a thing for him to have done
Suspicion that Alex is smart enough to realize that Dynamic which could help explain why he had the responses to this email
Mel's it's congruent with how you would want the jury to see you and and how you know the jury is going to respond to them
And I don't even necessarily know where like
That's a conscious decision but it might just be like Alex gets fat
I love the way that Mark set up easy emails because you could have
You could have set it up in a different in a different fashion and made some different points but I just love the fact that it's
It's like a limbo bar for empathy that he keeps raising you know like that first one if you don't see that
That is monstrous you know
Wow you just smacked the f****** limbo bar then raises the limbo bar 5015
True monsters behavior and she's like I bet I can hit that barb is really just asking
Yes hey you know if somebody were lit on fire that would be a bad thing right
You agree with that damn so there's a bunch of questions that come up about 3
The size of the audience metrics and and traffic
Basically boils down to Daria having like I didn't do anything to figure out
Great
We're hours into this deposition
This question is damning
You understand the company produced documents
From its own corporate file
Okay and you understand that some of those document request ask for documents about
Mypoints
Can you name
My forklift you know there
It's on the notice I know yummy from memory you don't
You got to pull this
Corporate representative
You don't know the names of the people suing you
Board games
Do you know why we're here
It's rank disrespect to not even take this seriously enough to know like even if you don't want to know their name
Names as people be aware of the names of the cases right
You know I mean
This is one of those things
It's it's easy to laugh
At how terrible they are in these depositions you know it is very easy
Cuz they're garbage and they're they're just dumb on a on an astronomical scale but when you do hear that
It just it reminds me all over again like
That's why it's fine for them that's why they don't care
Is cuz I never cared
That's why they will always go find another Sandy Hook cuz I don't care what the names are of the people who are going to
Bankrupt their f****** business didn't even bother to know because most of the time they won't spend a bankruptcy business
That's what I'm saying that's why I have to be a bankruptcy I see I see where you're coming
Couple more clips left and one of the things that was really mysterious and the Alex
Deposition is the questions about
The giant background check of Leonard hofstadter
The document
The single document
That was recently produced to me
You've never seen
And this is a single.
You see where it says FSX TX
Dash 8
You don't know what this is do what is this you couldn't tell me
Background information
I mean I can figure that out right like we can look at the top at the table of contents right here
And it says for license investigator purposes only do you see where it says that
And then you see where it says Lynyrd Posner comprehensive report
You see what has all these entries about all this information about Linda Posner
This is a w
Of knowledge
That the company has in its possession
Concerning menopause
You'd agree with that
Okay
In some of the information that the company has about menopause and its knowledge include is possible relatives right you see that
The bottom of the list
Impossible likely Associates impossible Associates right
Okay if we go to DC versus page 66 for possible relatives
Can you play put the page 66 in that document for me
There's a bunch of people's personal information in there
Yes you can tell me why the company has this can you
I don't know
No one has any idea
Listen to these and I just wonder like
Who could answer that question we believe them when they say they have no idea why they have it
I would suspect that
I mean I don't have any reason to believe that they are lying about that
It's who knows who does not take who knows I mean who knows I will tell you who knows
Rob
You know who it is
David
Joan let's get him in
Is that is no longer HR it might not be that crazy that he was HR to begin with because he
He did some human resources for the dental company that he was apart of
Actually somebody
Either way
So this last clip is not where the actual deposition ends but I would say it's where it's kind of spiritually and
And that is an exchange
Where
So I had a little bit of a context I guess this in the Connecticut cases
Got us clanka who's basically the partner of Wolfgang halbig
An associate and some of the nonsense he was into
And so part of the request for production of documents
In these cases in Texas involved anything involving Corey Sanka
That's hard that is hard to find
So
They obviously would know
That there are documented off maybe these a co-defendant in the case
In Connecticut they would know that yes these orders would know
But there is something that would be responded in that request for documents
But of course nothing came up and nothing was delivered
Answer this is this is where I think
You can tell through out this but there is a sense of growing frustration with
Dealing with this deposition
This is
What are we even doing
You know Corey spank is right
Courselink has an associate of Wolfgang halbig was a co-defendant
Does that refresh your memory on Nucor stock is now
You would admit being a co-defendant with Corey Funk on the laughing
The company possesses documents
Correct
Protection form
Nothing to do with the Texas cases
Discovery request
Which you would know if you ever answer
Okay
I'm bread Marcus is the most disrespectful and deposition I've ever been and I don't we been into deposition for you presented the same
And now for you to come in
The topics about
Reason responsible case
I need to get up to speed
First of all
I'm objecting on the faces of you asking about the Connecticut litigation
I'm not asking I'm not saying you have any not ejecting to ask any questions about
Your Discovery request
Second of all
No one is trying to be disrespectful here she's doing her best job and I don't care whether you think she is in there not
Don't know care what your personal opinions are on or not if you have a problem with it with I'm sure you you obviously Duke you're going to
Try to do something about it
And and I and I want you to maintain for the record
Everyone here has been working as hard as they can to actually get you answers that you want and I'm sorry that at the house
100000 pages of documents
That you're asked about specific ones that she doesn't have the exact answer
Okay man you know what I'm not I don't answer Discovery bread I would like you to show me the
Responded to
Which ones you saying have not been responded to
Have you ever been compelled by a court order to actually respond to those documents cuz I got the faulted
But I haven't actually seen the most
I understand that
But I'm
I'm I'm unclear
Awning from defaulted on it and I'm unclear the obligation to taxes supplement it but if you if you want to ask
Ask me to do that that I'll do that for you I don't know I'm asking her
Directly
But they haven't produced me documents to my Discovery weekly
And I want them to admit they refused
And you kept interrupting me about I'm sorry I didn't mean to interrupt you I apologize that's not why I sent and I will
Go ahead and answer the question today since you can please
Wow it was not hard to make that teenage boy fall down
That was really a bit
Obviously the boiling over frustration of like dealing with his nonsense
The responsive Brad being like
Yeah everyone's doing the best I can I'm sorry I'm sorry
Such a perfect button to end on kind of of these of these
Is not doing the best Brad Brad Brad
Brad
Is there a lawyer you can't but you can't be a f****** lawyer
For a god day of corporate representatives and come at me with what my mom would say if I got a C
My dad was pissed
He's doing his best shut the fuk up
Unreal
I think we were almost probably including
Probably about that unsurprising
So I think one of the one of the unfortunate things about this is that obviously
There is three hours long at the Dari once like 5 hours long
Things that we just copies we couldn't cover everything I write a little other tidbits that
That are obviously for someone like me
It's like
Everything is is catnip
Yeah there's a ton of stuff that I would for 12 hours and talk to you about if
Felt like it was acceptable
I think your patients would wear thin about 4 hours and 2 minutes
That's about where
I find I found these really Illuminating them anyways I think
I think that obviously
The
Battaglia wine as a corporate representative is
It's not as funny as do maybe I've been at
Yeah I mean he he he was much more scared and he also had kind of an almost
Laissez-faire attitude about it to of like
Hey if I know something I'll tell you but if I don't know something I'm just going to say I don't know man I guess fear and confusion made it
Funny where is Dario's like a preparation is clearly demonstrated in the deposition
It didn't have the same humor and the things that were interesting about it we're upsetting
Deeply deeply upset that's
Wow
You know that okay it's like that psychopath
Test thing you know better I'm sorry to bring up John twice
But
It is like that story of you know like all of this this psychopath goes to a funeral meet somebody cool and they like how do you
You meet him again in the psychopathic saw you kill somebody that you only meet them at funerals
That is exactly what I felt whenever
Daria heard the email about Wolfgang f****** stocking people and she was like
Personal somebody cares about you and your like whether you are
Terrified committed were terrified
Yeah it it's a disaster incredibly bizarre I think that
Certainly something that I wasn't as aware of before is the content of some of those emails
All that are just deeply upsetting f***** up and
That the relationship between the times that like
When these emails are getting sad when the Rasmus being done when
There's
Pretty strong indications of negligence and just ignoring what they're doing
Doing and who they're promoting
It just it just looks really bad now it does not look good God's not
So glad to be on the other side of this I'm glad that I we can you know it's out in the open
Little bit of a weight off my shoulders
Dino not tipping the hand at all
It was almost 2 months now so
For not tipping the hand but more proud of you for doing it and all that stuff I'm not going to accomplish
So I guess that brings us to the end of this but I think we may have another
So that sort of deposition Asian
We look forward to that but until then
We aren't fighting I go to bed Jordan
The sex robot