Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Nick.com
The author of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
June
The King of the South to clean South not the Dirty South
The Dirty South
Who's that
Oh okay
Is he from New York
Master P is the Court Jester of the Dirty South by do not appreciate that at all
The ice cream man's going to f*** you up
I'm just making a weird all right. You're just like a Pete Holmes
Oh yeah it'll be fun
Quick question for you
Whatsyourprice
Bag breaks Twitter just as weird
Starting to record this episode
That apparently the Mighty Mighty Bosstones have broken up after many many years
Are there 20 years after I remember them last years and years.
Plaid
They've decided to hang up the old
Skanking shoes
Well do I mean it's obviously on the one hand I am big fan
I have been
Course it's my my childhood although I will say I have not listened to most of their new album
I am a big fan of the earlier catalog certainly
It's bittersweet a little bit but I didn't get to see
Stop witches
I guess it when it's better that then like to hear this news I guess I'll never
Hey there are union to be able to see him at 5 p.m. at a casino someday Dan
And you're to be okay
Midas in Everett
But like yeah it is it it at least my my childhood self got to have that like
Experian
Invalidate fasting
Thanks thanks Bosstones I have a similar experience in the reverse
I could have seen James Brown
It's my college girlfriend at the time
She's different
But
But for some reason I decided not to go I can't remember the exact
Pacific time
Week later he was dead
Yeah right
A bummer is that that is a bummer
Oh no, crime
Sherlock Holmes hat
Figure out this mystery
Absolutely I was going to be the return of saga
Which is the first one
It's about time for that day it's a really really great graphic novel
By Brian K Vaughan who's a really good writer
But the artwork is done by Fiona Staples and she is
Beyond great
It was going to be that open
Tuesday night the heat died
In my replace okay and I don't know if you recall it was about -8 degrees outside
Ballpark
1 in the afternoon
So bye-bye
Right spot is having heat again amazingly good
Pillow forts blanket Saturday
This is one of the downsides like I texted you when you were going
This is part of the bad part about to homeownership
The condo and like
Now you just look at the yellow the landlord
If I know
And I was alone whenever the repair guy came and he was like
Do you know how old this thing is and I was like No And he was like 8
Still mad at Reagan
This is not good but also Don't lecture me about it
Monday of this week
This past week of January 24th
2022 22nd
I doubt it
So this is an episode where Alex
Of course
You talked about how do you talk to the January 6th
Text committee
Everybody was pretty interested to hearing how that went
We'll figure it out
But before we do
What say hello doesn't do
The first Nick wallbank
Jen and Steve escapees of Ocala Florida thank you so much here and I'll probably walk
Blackjack
You're busted oh I get it thank you so much and I apologize
I did it wasn't part of the name
Like I got it that you busted but I guess I didn't realize that when I wrote down the name
Clever
X-Files
Thank you very much
How old is my spirit animal
I have
Risen above
My enemies
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe that I should almost broke
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Apologized
To the crew in the Lesner Chester
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
He may be I have no beef
Thoroughly with the help. If you want to explain
You're very scandalous comments
Surprised
This is like this is a good thing for a lot of people wow
Yeah that's right coming hard and Pete Holmes
Wow
Okay videos of Jordan do not necessarily reflect the ozone
Knowledge fight LLC
Like I said today 24th at the beginning of this week news broke that Alex
Did Matt virtually with the 36
Committee and the buzz that was going around was that he plead the Fifth
About a hundred times
When I first saw the news going around my first question that I had was like what information is being used backup this
Reporting
I looked around I read some articles in the mainstream media about the story and all of them just relied on comments that Alex made on
His own show
A source familiar with the investigation confirmed the meeting to CNN but that really just means that the meeting
Happened the other ways that Alex characterized the meeting where a cure
The CNN article in particular just seems like a partial transcription of Alex's show
And all the other articles are the same thing you just rely on Alex's show in the claims that he made on it
I guess there's not really any other information they could be going off of since I don't think that these interviews are public particula.
How about this whole
Still ongoing
I'm going to cover this episode but I do with the largest grain of salt any human has ever imagined
Taking his word about everything he says
Concerning a meeting with the house committee that he thinks is trying to overthrow the country
What are the biggest problems is it I don't actually trust Alex's ability to comprehend information he receives or questions he's asked
So that calls into question his telling of the thing
I'm most interested in knowing about this meeting with the committee which is
What they asked
Knowing what they asked would help gives
Some sense of what direction they're heading in and what Alex should be worried about
Having a solid sense of that will have to wait I guess the best we've got for now is Alex's. What happened
So that's what we're going to go with reading some of those because
You know normally we
F****** everywhere and I couldn't avoid it even the headlines were showing up
Read every one of them
And everyone of them might as well have been like
We're taking noted liar at face value
I do
F****** stupid I don't know if it's stupid because I think like if you're going to
Get write a story about this
Roberta's newsworthy
That's what you have to do but I do think a better job could have been done to really highlight
All this could be bulshit absolutely
Especially the day after we do deposition episode and we've done plenty of deposition episodes of the past I think we know
Know how Alex talks whenever the shitz
Real now you know that's a good point but I also think that we do need to be careful because
The depositions are civil depositions
About a case
Clearly not concerned or or have any respect for
The way he might respond to talking
To a congressional committee
Where he could be in legal Jeopardy
I think it might behave differently
Currently I'm not ready to make the assumption that he would behave exactly the same but he might
Exactly the same but
His bombastic retelling of how he behaves
Is
100%
True true
I guess that is really the point is that we don't know
We don't know
That that should be
Gov Captain mind as we as we go over the stuff
So we're going to start here on the 24th
Boo from the jump
My friends on this Monday January 24th 2022 transmission
I just had a very
Pants experience
Interrogate
Lawyers
Air flight
But they were
Very seriously
I know that
Chef is a
Caught
Making emails
Misquoting President Trump
He is ordering
The presidential train here's a transcript
President
Crane
Parody version of
Scraped up a call between Trump and Ukrainian president zelensky
At the time my position like when
Drifted that my position was it was a bit dramatic on his part and a really bad Optical move
Easy would be to attack him just the way Alex has
Think that it's fair to say that he's trying to pass off what you were saying is an actual transcript
That's kind of dumb
Yeah it's really clear that
I bet that was not the intention to pretend that it was
Misunderstanding that on purpose
So they can text you
For being a forger instead of just being a bit dramatic
Is really dumb but it does provide me
Excuse for why Alex
The very innocent person should be afraid of testifying for the committee
He's so innocent but that doesn't matter cuz she's just going to create fake document
He did was Trump
Truly fascinating that's a Alex
Constantly goes on about wanting his day in court where he can be Vindicated in the establishment will have to recognize that he's been right all
How long in power will tremble before
But every time he has the opportunity there's some kind of excuse for why you just withstand dozen
Improve anything
All the Sandy Hook depositions would have been ideal time for him to stand behind his claims
And it's very least demonstrate that even though we
We know them to be wrong now
He had reason to believe that these claims were correct when he said them
And every time he was mumbled
I don't know we're trying to change the subject rambling about how he's a Vic
Now here he is testifying in front of
Congressional committee and wealth
He could tell the big truth to power and stand up like a man in the arena like he always calls himself
Prince's fake story about Adam Schiff that's got him too worried to talk
It's such b******* this entire character he puts on his a fraud come on everybody knows cuz we've we've seen this
History in the past you know
Truth-tellers have gone up against
Kangaroo court so many times
Because they're going up against kangaroo courts
All they really do is quit and give up because what's the point of fighting back you know there's nothing more Nova
Then giving in
The powers-that-be
Yeah I think the folks
That I I think
I respect moral principles would be like well
I'm going to go in there I'm going to speak my peace I'm going to tell the truth and whatever,
Consequences May calm sure
Do you know what the
Political consequence of me telling the truth
Because they believe that what the government's doing
Is rozzi's IV Wars
And things like that bright day off
End up having consequences and they have consequences
Activism
And then you have people vertex protesters like Alex's friend
Who do the opposite
That's kind of how I feel about Alex's
Posture towards
You know testify
It's The Stolen Valor Valor
Unlike
The Stolen Valor of wearing army medals and b******* when you have endured that b the The Valor of
Somebody who's actually fighting Power and
They're not doing
Like I said it's characters
Completely so Alex
He's learned over the course of his career last episode proves that is not true
My name is Adele
Personally
Radio Beverly
That's what power to have
And I was
Really for the right reasons but I still made mistakes
And the process
Trying to be good
Careful with the power I wield
Not the normal
Process
When the type of people that actually shipped
I'm already on TV so they can be
Famous
They could get a job in Hollywood
Jobs Hollywood
Star-Lord
Because I genuinely wanted to be with the people in the common populace
My own process of learning
No I've been wrong
Help Me Grow Up
Really see what's wrong
What's the people that are
Arrogant
Hateful
Disconnect from God
Just ridiculous
Wow just really describe himself right there so hateful
Disconnected from God
Engagement Alex my understanding of him through periods of his career
I think one of the more offensive things you can say in terms of like just
Blatant disregard
For the truth is I've learned thing
The end I learn
. is alive
Categorically not
Yeah I am and also disrespectful is the notion that like
I did things that hurt people but I was trying to be good in the service of good
That's such s***
I mean you know it's
It's fun
It's fun whenever he described
I I've learned I've changed and I've grown and
It's been my mistakes that have allowed me to
Realize what's wrong with the people in power despite the fact that he said the exact same thing about them
Since he was 11 years old register is John bush
John Birch Society book
No but I think that
This is what
People
Who have learned things say and so he sort of parroting because it makes
It seem like he's actually had the experiences that he wants the audience
To feel like he's had right knee is not
He's at the opposite
Maybe he just has forgotten
How to start every sentence with
You know like maybe he actually is a parrot maybe he will
Those pages is like a parent something
Florida's office
So look
I was not looking forward to
To a whole episode of lesson
Alex
I've had enough
Basically
4 hour episodes
Listening I didn't want to jump rope
Much like the people of Nineveh
As outfit he gave me a reprieve
Huge show lined up for you today
Four-year-old daughter
Camping for munch
Couple days off
30 minutes
I think his daughter wanted to go to an amusement park but that trip got cancelled because Alex's financial information was reported in The Hobbit
Suppose we wanted to make a couple million dollars out of spite
I guess you wants to go camping now
Anyway Alex has been out of the studio for the last couple days after this episode and Owens been hosting which is a mess
Owens got on his plate
He's hosting Alex's show that has to do his show afterwards that's like 6 hours of talking
Was just one hour of a break in between we're in this
Gerald Celente
The 4th hour
There's no one on earth with 6 hours of interesting things to say in a day and is there is a person it's not Owen
Sleeves half an hour into the show which gives us like
Do therefore the first hour
A means to be there for half an hour
And then he's out of here he's got senioritis
Today
So Alex
Comes back from break
He reiterates that he has just got done talking to these committee lawyer
Testimony via
Cisco
Systems
Zoomer Skype
A connection
An interview
With the
January 6th
Committee
Is it is newsworthy an important and I move on the other big-nosed and I would Troyer
Come in and take over because I again
Taking mine
4/2
Heading to the woods
Oh it's great time to go run to the great time to get to the woods and this also brings up
When are episode drops
If there is any kind of response from Alex
So he had some time I would be building a Pueblo if I were him I would be I would be
The Border building a redoubt
Meeting Andy decided
Going to bleed
The fifth his reasons and his understanding
King of the cops
Constitution seem a little bit weird here
My lawyer told me almost a hundred times today
During interrogation
Advice of counsel
I am starting my Fifth Amendment right to remain silent
And the media tells you
Because you're guilty
Because you're going to criminate
Also just because you could be used
To try to incriminate you
Twist
Something
Against you
Adam Schiff
Famous for
Conversation
Oh I wonder if he brought that up to Adam Schiff in the in the testimony
Answering these questions because you're a known for juror
That's my daughter to make sure that this was a collegial atmosphere
If you wants to relate
You get take things seriously deal with the reality
That boy so we're discuss the fifth amendment in a recent episode where Alex is threatening
But this is a very inaccurate interpretation of what that amendment allows
The fifth amendment allows Alex to not answer questions that he has a reasonable belief
Could be used against him in another potential case
For instance if you were testifying about a murder you witnessed while you were in the
Middle of committing a robbery
You could plead the fifth about details of why you were there where you were Wendy Witten
Misty's Burger
But you could still answer questions about seeing the murder
Is against themselves
If Alex's interpretation of the Fifth Amendment were applied across the board the legal system in this country would collapse
And they're just wouldn't never be any reason to call any Witnesses
To be opposed to the goal of the investigation
People who had information about deeply illegal things would never have any concern about so
Subpoenas because
They just bleed the fifth everything instead of risking the lying to Congress
If the standard for being allowed to use the 5th was that you were vaguely concerned about someone misusing your words
It's because of
Something as flimsy as a dumb misrepresentation of a years old right-wing talkin
There would be no reason to have anybody testify ever again
The people who get subpoenaed will have to show up
To say I plead the
The fifth and not answering either question
It makes everything so much more important
This is a child's interpretation of the Fifth Amendment more likely to cause him
Referred for
Contempt charges
Because it's just not reasonable to assume that he had a legitimate concern
That answering any of those 100 questions would lead him providing evidence against himself
In a different
Potential process
It's just
A bizarre misuse of the
How long have you known Stewart roast
An alternative is that Alex has an almost cartoonishly sprawling crime Empire and answering any questions
Anything in his life and business work
Would lead to proof of a crime
I would guess you'd rather not that not be the impression that he sending but it's not a totally unfair reading of the accident that he's
There's an I've never met any of the people who work for
Wonders at a flaky legitimately did plead the fifth to all these things
I think it's a possibility I think it's an abuse of the amendment and take you'll probably end up
I don't think we'll get arrested or anything for it
But I do think that he could run into some kind of a fine
Traffic movie
But like the alternative is I do see it is entirely possible that he didn't
The 5th because I don't think his lawyers would tell him to
But I mean if you have bad lawyers
Still I don't I don't think that they would be like hey
Here's here's how this thing works
The contribution but it actually doesn't work this
I'd say that if I were a lie
And I had close relationships with a lot of militia
I would not want to go on my show and say
I told the Congressional committee everything that I know
I told them names I gave them where they live I gave them how many guns they bought
From me I snitch
Car motherfuker
Yeah I mean
Play the figured want to say I don't know I mean it
I guess because we don't
I have any word from any Source other than Alex
I'm not totally convinced that is actually what
Totally and at the same time
If I knew a bunch of militia members I wouldn't be surprised if giving away information to the Congressional committee
Eventually wound up being a crime on my part of some sort
I know too much
Yeah
I mean
Disrespect
That he has
Farming basically all legal proceedings that are things he doesn't like
You can't walk in
Something like that
People like that
I don't know if they're good people
They can always polite nice
In the background
Moray eel in the Rocks ready to come out and eat you
Then there's no reason to even
Because it's
You can see here I'll Alex operate
Any case that's inconvenient for him or that is illustrating the negative space that he lives in will always be determined to not be
Illegitimate
There's so many stupid conspiracies and right-wing talking points Alex
Can fall back on so anytime he's looking down the barrel of consequences
He couldn't pull out one of these and try to save face to the audience for the way he coward instead of engaging with the process
You got this made-up story about Adam Schiff so this comedian this committee's illegitimate
He's decided in his head that he followed all the discovery processes in the Sandy Hook case so that default judgment is it legit
None of these cases are illegitimate at all what they actually already threatening
Dalek so he needs to delegitimize them to his listeners
Leslie realize the scam
Some studies running
Right and that's
That's the how the
Kelly the Cabbage trial that Alex
See his legitimate is Benghazi hearing aids
He was charged with being
Too much of a hero
Right
The most hero anybody's ever been and they were like that
Crime scene
You're safe too many lies
Our Stars people their questions are
Stop
The questions were
Pretty reasonable
I wanted to answer.
But it's
It's a good thing I didn't because
Making them cry to climb to that perjury
Cuz about half the questions
Planning things
From memory
Namek is describing with how he answers questions he doesn't actually know anything about that Rings true to me
Deposition appearances Weaver
It's not even trying to be helpful though it's an attempt to Spin A Yarn that explains everything even if that requires make
Things up
It's what he does on his show it so it's not
Surprising that you carry that over into legal settings as well
You've never
Respect for any case where he possibly accused of wrongdoing it.
Fixies above-the-law so
Why would you give a s*** about answering questions accurately
Accuracy is not important
Utility is
And making up stories that
I guess
Kind of explain what people are asking about
Call utility
I have some questions about whether or not Alex had seen the emails he's referencing here
Without knowing what the emails are it's hard to tell if they're things that he could have missed but
I get the sense that Alex claiming to not use email personally is a strategic
Position so you can always claim ignorance
If he's ever asked about it drives you that email
LOL
Want to come
Winky face
So Alex has their question
Guess
It's not a good idea
To read the questions questions
For sure
Fix that might be not
Cool
But I don't know
Because of
Oh my God
Dysentery
That work
I if you define things like this I can't imagine a corporate feeding that Alex couldn't claim was too risky for him to answer
Jensen
If it wasn't a fake concern about Shane if it would be another Congress
Person who had some kind of conspiracy about them
It's not a real concern it's a cookie cutter fill-in-the-blank excuse for why Alex isn't standing up and taking on the system
Even though he insists he's totally innocent you being set up and he has all the truth on his side
This is kind of like how children rationalize situation
Threatening to there
It feels like a kid who thinks that they're really good at basketball
Explain that they didn't even try out for the team because the coach doesn't like their dad
It's an excuse to not have to confront the reality that metaphorically
Alex isn't good at basketball
That's the vibe
Yeah it would really make him look
Lesser than in the eyes
His his
Inferiors sec
This is assuming that he actually did plead the right
So are you telling me that he is going to read these questions
And then give the answers that he would have loved not really not real okay he will get around to like address
Sing a couple of them go down the list which is unfortunate I would have liked that
Information
The couple will get to those when he does
Before that Jesus
This
Tumi
If true
Is bad news.
That word
They have everything that's already on my phone since
Thanks cuz I saw my text
Messages
Caroline ran and Cindy Shaffer
If you wanted some of the event organizer
And they already know I didn't do anything that wasn't playing any violence
Was even talking about
Nearby should be peaceful
If they have that that you got to assume maybe they have even more
You know Alex they don't they don't have to give you everything they know yet
In the in a trial right
They will have to give you a call Discovery you've heard of it I mean you haven't really heard of it honestly is heard
He's perfectly familiar with the concept yeah I think that
It would be tough for me to believe that there aren't at least
A couple of
Weird
Messages between Hammond like Ali Alexander Stewart
You know I don't
Obviously I wouldn't know what's in that
Crossover
Stephanie Mills
I'd love to get my hands on that
I would really assume
And again we've we've talked too much about Alex's legal proceedings but I would really assume that they are key
Keeping things away from Alex's knowledge
In the early going
Yeah I mean I think you're a good strategy with him is
Absolutely not making clear what you know
Maybe he'll be able to do his thing where he comes up with a fake explanation for why everything is fine
Haha but he's going to do that anyway so if you let him do that with a
False or incomplete understanding of the information that you know you can set a trap for him
Maybe he would like to repeat that for everything because
His behaviors are self
Doubt self
Yeah
I mean I feel like if I was
If I was those lawyers I
Just flattered the s*** out of Alex
Jason just be like man
If you had full power over all of these people I'm sure you would have directed them to stop and none of this would have ever happened
Since you didn't have full power over them
Which you should have
Because you're
So
Great butts
Since you did just let me know what you did do you know because I know I'm telling you it was all good I'm sure it was all good
Cuz you're the best in the spire.
And tell me what you were doing and what Stewart roses doing
So there's one particular thing that apparently they asked Alex about
That actually fine
Fascinating
And that is
Full segment on his
December 31st 2020 show
I did not know a lot of the questions I asked
Fiend
And II
Once they sent me the subpoena a few months ago
I was shocked by
Because I never seen Matt Bracken
Recall for things like that he was always
Opposite
Look out for federal
Plants
6 days before January 6th
He's basically
Call
But he wasn't there that day he was up to.
Washington Monument give you if you believe
Whether he's
Or whether he just got
Hell no I don't support that
Weather
I guess I guess it turns out Matt Bracken was
Afbi plant
Wow Infowars Heap cover
Provocateur this whole thing
For the last eight years 30 years at least all of those things that I
Alex loves so much
Was a desire to overthrow the government
Figure out what it is
Has been a longtime consistent fourth our host on Alex's show
At least 2016 entries but was almost like David night even
Before that
June 17th
His appearance is just
Why
Bracken was also a publisher as a blogger on the website America
Can partisan with bylines going back to 2020
And then he has no more post
After July 2021
Watershed he's not dead which I can assume based on his consistent posting on Gap up until even today
What happened
Here's a guy with an a
Accomplish resume and Alex clearly trusted enough.
Close out the last show of 2020
You just disappear
I don't want to get to
Conspiratorial at this but it does come to mind that the January 6th committee was formed on July 1st
2021 resolution to form it was introduced in the house
On June 28th 2021
I would think hey
What's going on hey here's a guy who's been on your show for years and hears
He said I hate everyone
Storm the capitol on December 31st
Show and then he
When's committee came around
He's gone you I haven't bought any more
I don't know if there's any relationship with that but I would ask him about it just
In case it made him feel weird
So I thought of going camping episode
Bracken actually said
December 31st 2020 episode of Alex
He's hosting the 4th hour and
I honestly think it's a fairly standard my bracket appear
It's a lot of blustery talk about a revolution
Whatever is the Hot Topic in extreme right-wing circles at the time
That's kind of his thing and what he always does on Infowars
If the main issue was something about racial Injustice he'll insist that a race war is right around the corner
If it's gone paranoia narratives that are on top of insist they're about to take your guns and you need to be ready to kill
People to stop the rise up
If it's an election conspiracy that's getting the most traffic he'll do a video as he did in 2021
Where do you says it's either the ballot box or the Bullet
And if it's a big Patriot theme protest that he wants to amplify it's not a surprise that he will be using extremely irresponsible
Audible an inflammatory line
Excuses to Infowars Alex
Knows that
It's
Just at the s*** he's fear-mongering about the past hasn't come true and unfortunately this time
He straight-up looks like a prophet
But the wrong kind of profit for Infowars
The kind that makes it look like they were really excited about it promoted the idea that if things didn't go their way on January 6th the right-wing would need
Need to take over the capitol
Anyway let's dive in here
With other man himself
Matt Bracken actually it the beginning of this report he explains why he's wearing no
You know I'm I'm
Where in the Infowars
Shirt right there today
I'm not a member of the Infowars
Of the Infowars team in any kind of a
Financial sense
Never been paid
Doing this for my home in Florida
I'm wearing
Because
I'm proud to stand with Alex
And the Infowars family
Michigan pulling into a new year
You know we're going to do this stuff is
Fuel rally next week and we don't know how it's going to turn out
But there's a real serious
Biden and Harris are going to be
President
Vice president
Obama will be
Excuse me a mile or so away
In his basement of his
Washington Mansion
Feeding therapy
Scripts to them as he is said to
Set on TV
He'll be happy to just be the guy putting the words into the earpieces
So we know what's coming
The brackens wearing the shirt out of solidarity with with him
They should unionize the store that our Host this is why you get money
Okay
You make sure you get money
Don't respect you unless you try and grip back
He's selling his books
And stuff like that
Much wider audience I need have access to otherwise
You want a financial relationship
That can be on the record without her
Cuz then you're more likely to get protection he's doing this for exposure though
I'm actually not a hundred percent sure that there is
Financial relationship
Without any kind of evidence I have no idea what that
The idea that Alex would like people
Host an hour of his show without some kind of involvement
But yeah so we've we've got this explained
Prada shirt
It's not suspicious he's not a antifa false flag actor
I'm so he he talked a little bit about what his hopes are
Before the March
Deeply ironic
I'm going to Washington next week
I hope it's such a big rally that it's impossible to find anybody that
You know that'll be a cfp
People that's my hope
That's my goal
But
All of the anonymous anklebiters
Bet that.
You know what
Hack away at Alex
Let me tell you the man has been
A fearless leader now for many years
And he hasn't
When it would have been easy
It would have been so easy at various points in the last
Couple of years
You know what I've had it
I'm just going to
I've done my part
I've done more than my
I'm going to exit
Stage left
Just live a quiet life
He didn't do it
Just like Donald Trump didn't do it
A couple months early on that
Alley Boy
Recently
Talk a lot about Clinic
Yes we want to see you people
Just fine I'm still in the ballpark of like I just want a big protest and I would like to not be identified at that
A protester I'd like everybody to be able to blend I would like this
Two features zero Waldo
So next week
On January 5th and
What we have to do is show
Who's really a
Control
Social media
We don't have all of these
Oregon Zoo
Power
We don't control the Department of Justice we can't
Decide
What criminals
Will go uncharged
And what innocent
People will be arrested in the middle of the night
We don't
Control that
But we can overwhelm them with
Sear number
And that's why
It's going to be our week
Next week
You know we weren't around for Valley Forge we weren't around
Ordering any of Americas
Darkest Days
And now we're so comfortable it's so easy
Sit on the couch
Play sitting on the couch is bad
Acting like that our ancestors at Valley Forge
Good
Oh man
It's starting to get a little iffy
This is the kind of language he uses
This is it I mean you can even hear him being like a little blase about it like hey what yes obvious
We're going to take the country back
Save-A-Lot blase effect is kind of also Matt Bracken
He's not super
Excitable
Right
Man
I I would just find it so funny
If there was somebody who is just
Completely unaware of what was going to take place on the 5th and 6th
Doing a regular ass broadcast
Saying this exact s***
Having no idea what's going to happen and then watching it on TV just been like
Oh no
That he may have so
This is
Navigate a little bit worse
You get enough
Turn up trumps
Enough stop
Bastille rally
The park on the bridges
You can bring washing
DC tour complete
Stop
If they try to
Prevent this
Peaceful assembly
I keeping people away from
The capital
Then the people are just going to do other
And one the other side
Sprague
Talk some more about that but
I can't emphasize
Is this is
Our Moment
No we have
Never been
In our lives
Like we are about to
We haven't fought a war
American soil Hellboy
Since
We have been blessed
Star Wars have been fought over sea
In other
Territory
Blessing yeah that's a blessing
Couches
Breakaway out of
Free Adam
You know
Peaceful
Easy Living
And show that this
Country is not going to be
Stolen
By these Democrat
Socialist
Communist global
We're just now
Not going to permit it
And next week is when we're going to show it
We're not going to Granada allow this election to go down if we're going to show it
And I just want to let anybody who's listening to this no
I am associated with this iwantmyname and Alex Jones has to be at the Forefront
This exact thing that I am saying for posterity
You're already
Suggesting things like we could put a blockade around
If they don't let us near the Capital One nearby other thing here
To do we should have caches of weapons
Nearby don't bring them directly into d.c. that's a far greater federal crime that it would be if they were outside of the city again
Be clear that I don't think of this is out of the ordinary for Bracken at all they sometimes on the show
Close to normal it's just that unfortunately
You have to do other things that was the problem.
Obviously has to do with the audience
And the people who are there have been whipped into such a frenzy
With these
Consistent arguments that the election have been stolen
It's proven
And all that and so
Bracken brings
Some of that up any as an interesting source that I'm not sure I've heard Alex use
There's no question that
That
Pens
Thousands
The balance in the states
For counterfeit
They were they were mask
Produced ahead of
But you look at some of these these guys like
This witness on the screen right now
Jovan Pulitzer
It got 200
You know involved with the
Human machine interface like
QR codes
He's a he's an expert on this and he says all he needs
The sea is the paper ballot
Javon Pulitzer didn't come up with her QR codes
He came up with a handheld Barcode Scanner called cuecat
Right back into your 2000
The Wayward was the people would put barcodes in the newspaper like an advertisement said that this handheld device with
Scan the barcode
And take people to their website
Naturally because of how Tech worked at the time that meant you had to have this cute cat
Plugged into your computer and then it just wasn't convenient
People did not care for it
In 2006
PCWorld put out a list of the 25 worst Tech products of all time
IQ cat was number 20
Part of the reason for that was that it sucks
But the other part was there because there was a
Huge security vulnerability that ended up being exploited and 140,000 users had their personal information still
Out of here
Damn
After that
Future went on to run a bunch of other scams like selling crystals
Have you featured in The History Channel show as a treasure hunter
The 2020 election was the flame that attracted all the grift moths opiates are showed up and now he's a forensic ballot
What expert
And because these dumb dumbs like Bracken do care who sang something if they like with being said
He was accepted as an expert
Advocates
The capitol because the Alexa
Was stolen
I think it's funny to see that
That progression of like
He makes
An invention that
Makalapa
Suitability
Which not high
I understand
However
A legitimate invention
Barcode reader computer in 2000s pretty good
Bright
I guess your next move is treasure hunter that's a long dropped out that the crystals were after that then
I don't know.
The lucrative Market
Selfer quite a bit
So look the elections been stolen
Pulitzer sold us this we all know it
And if you allow that to stand
There's any consequences in the future
Folks
You let
Happen
Bet it's on you
Future generation
Things will say
You just didn't
Really give a damn
They stole the
Not even hiding it
So you have to act
Now our time is the six
If you don't
Future generations and posterity will know you as a person who didn't give a s*** about Liberty
So tired high-stakes I'm interested in this question
If you like and were stolen
Is he right
You know I'm saying
What are bigger issues that the election wasn't actually stolen
I mean that's obviously a very large
Biggest issue the terminology election being stolen is way to Vega to even real
What does it mean if there is like an actual installing of a person
I'm sure then
No I still
I don't know then it becomes murky about whether or not
Application for those action
It would have been Justified
Greg area of
Even though you could make a linguistic
And actually like
Fairly decent argument
That bush
Was put in office by the Supreme Court
I don't know if that if that justifies trying to overthrow the government
The Supreme Court
Possibly
Making some
Pretty
Sirius overhauls
Make sure these kinds of situations
Don't happen again
I think you raise an interesting question that I don't really have a full answer
That I think that people
Open Puzzle over that
You do is it like there's a part of me that is
Not in admiration for bye
By any stretch
But of of that like
They
Follow through
You know like if if
What he's saying is true and this is what he thinks is the correct response to that
Then they did it
Which is a
A different thing from so many other people who are like
Here's the biggest problem and this is what we should do about it and I'm going to
You know sure there's a difference there that I I recognized and I don't necessarily think his
Good price
I think what you're talking about is a fairly abstract
I want to bring it back down to the ground to tiny bit because
Is provided for why they think the election is stolen is so flimsy as to
Very
Clearly
Indicate that
There isn't a conviction that there is
Is it true that the election was stolen
It's a conviction that they didn't get the outcome they wanted and so any explanation for why it is stolen
Enough for them to be like I can look at that
Imagining the alternative scenario we're like
But let's imagine
Evidence that Trump stole the
Do you think that they would be doing this
Do you like
Trumpet stolen the election
They were not present
They would use the opportunity to make sure all elections were stolen from then on out right now it's it's
How come was not what they wanted to flimsy evidence like this Crystal weirdo
Treasure hunter astronaut created one of the worst Tech Adventures of all time
This is good enough to be listed as part of the evidence that the electric was absolutely stolen
Truth is a sort of
I hunt it
So now that we have this all this this groundwork of
If you don't act future Generations will
Condemned it'll be damned to the the history
Tommy Bracco just really sucks up
You were knocked
Be saved by anybody above us
We're going to only be
Be saved
Buy million
American
Moving to washing
Occupying the entire area
Necessary
Storming right in
The capital
No there
We know the rules
Engagement
If you have enough
People
You can push
Euro wall
Oh that's not good
What if not enough paper
Patriots show up
Then we're just going to watch
Our freedom
Down the drain
It is a little shocking at Hughes
Is the term storming
Good
Not good
I would I would not want to be in front of the Congressional committee and have them play that for me to be like
Now that's taken out of context
Nord Network
I didn't know it happened to people people call for stormy the capital on your network and you're not even aware of
Never even listen to Infowars it by Terry life
I got to go
For 30 years
You have to stop
Desertification of the elect
No matter what
Spheal and Alexa
Right in front of
1 videos
With hundreds of thousands
Bella's
Counterfeit ballet
Fake names
People that don't exist
And we can
Stop it
You really
Think we'll ever have another
Free election in this country
Do you think they'll give us a
The chance to come back and
2 years and push the
The Democrats out
Next week is a
The pivot in
In American history
Next week
We are going to stand up and
Free America
Or we are just going to
Pretty back to wear sofa
Watch our country turn into
To Ameri Zoella
Lose our freedom
Wow I like that
Amerizon wailer
Brutal the mixture between America and
Really have all of the
Serta pieces in place to really be like you have to do this
You know something
Sometimes I think part of why they get so amped up
Is because they would much rather have an enemy that
Actually seems to be fighting back
You know like the Democrats
Open more masturbating at the thought of getting kicked out in 2 years
They were like all we won't have to do anything
There's an interesting Dynamic that Bracken also brings got a clip of his butt
Talks about the Republicans in office and being the Washington generals
Store like happy to just lose all the time for a Globetrotter that are the Democrat
Squirrels Nancy Pelosi Meadowlark
You talking about Democrats
Are not doing ball trick
Study on people
They're they're throwing water at people ridiculous
So I think that we have a whole lot here in terms of establishing like
Call to action
Specific things like blocking Washington
Storming the capital is being things that you need to do if you don't get your way in terms of blocking
The certification of the election right
A January 6th is the opportunity
And the only
Chance we have
Stop.
Is a mess
Mobilization
Next week
If we don't
See a million
People in wash
Washington
Oh no
Not enough America
You scared
Freedom just didn't matter that
As long as they had
Flix
Anaphora
Refrigerator and
Cozy sofa
They really
Didn't give a damn about
Freedom
What's the case
Then we deserve
Everything that comes out
I think it'd be great if
All Americans were able to have a full refrigerator
That's probably what we should be revolting about discuss those material Comforts that people
Cuz we don't have the full refrigerator
Yeah
I really think he's laid out a call to Arms
Depressing outro to this report
I'm going to wash
I'm staying for the duration
If there are debate
Staying till the end
I don't care I've heard all about
The hotel situation in
Antifa and black lives matter
I don't care I'm going
And I hope I see you there I hope I see millions of Youth
End
Hope I see you again on Infowars
Thanks for listening
Happy New Year
Boo
You know I mean I think he's got a great
Defense though
In front of the committee
Here's what he can
Cuz they can play that and he'll be like
You guys realize though I'm at bracket
Can and no one listens
To me right
0 people listen to me I'm Matt Bracken
You could you could I mean
You could argue that his views are left
I do still think
Like like hey hey buddy
You're also a noted weirdo
That's true you're talking about these plants like
These ideas and I don't know if you'd want to call them plans but certainly like
Seems like you've thought about this a little bit before you ask me
I was also pretty blustery stuff and honestly
Just wanted it to
Everything he was saying needed to be done was done and the only problem is that the coup wasn't success
Tons of people showed up open today at the stopping certification
And when that didn't work we will storm the capital is bracken
Clearly identified as one of the necessary steps
You could escalate to
I'm sure that on January 6th
If you had footage of bracken he would have been more excited than Harrison Smith
Sing the capitol it fall into the Patriot
Skip
This doesn't look
When you're cool fails in your life in the position where you publicly advocated for all the things that went into the failed coup
You probably need to Pivot a little bit
And unsurprisingly
That's exactly what he did after this I will lyrics
So it's pretty clear to me
Q was
Turned into some
Something that would be used as a weapon
A lot of wailmer
When do the capital
Ashley Babbitt
Underwater manga
And I don't think they
Johnny Quinn
Ashley bad
Herself
Ground
The double doors
Are the glass
Stores
Wandering around
Windfinder cell
Outside of lawn for
At least half of the
The people on that Landing
Stairs by the glass
Stores
At least half of the
This was a
Pure empty
Operation
I think that
But these guys
I'm talking about at
Glassdoor
Ashley
Was shot
I think that these guys
Spothero
The outside
Extremely motivated
Patriotic
And thought here we here
The kind of a
Covid-19
Dupe
Can use as a weapon
This is ranked cowardice on Brackenridge Park
F****** distasteful so bad he acknowledged publicly advocated for the things that
Light to Ashley Babbitt to be in the position she was in
Taking the action she was taken
When she was killed
And because
Admitting that is too difficult for him
Raconteurs creative fantasy story about it
With no proof other than his imagination he's decided that he
It seemed a bit outside
Patriotic
Patsy
So they'll order to the doors where I guess they somehow
Forester to try to break through them
This is so pathetic
It's one thing to be a fair-weather fan of a sports team
Fairweather revolutionary
To indicate such a lack of Spine and Pain
Conviction it's just on except
Matt wanted people to storm the capital he said it was a good thing to do and people did and a predictable result
Got2b at antifa
Lodi
This is very precise example of the strategy that Alex uses
Bonita Alex doesn't on a grander scale
Terrorism
He engages an intense and emotionally manipulative displays of incitement
And then when someone does what he obviously is saying they should do
That becomes an example of someone tried to false-flag Patriots to make them look the
Alex is usually just smart enough to not actually say storm.
The capital of the part where he's trying to incite people
Cuz that's how the business
Continue
I think understand is that this strategy has two big payoffs
The first is the obvious one that it allows Alex
Some folks
Captivate having to take responsibility for the consequences of their rhetoric when it actually
Comes down to
The second is that they're able to pretend that their underlying cause was so Justified it's so important
The globalist needed to use a false-flag to try to
Invalidated
In this case the election was so clearly stolen that the only way to divert attention from that
Was that this false flag which they could then blame on the people were saying the election was stolen which is
Because their claims were so legit
It's sad.
It's very stupid
It's so Universal with these dick
It's one of the weirder things
I mean
You know it's not weird
Entirety of
The Republican
Party is
So f*****
In terms of their heads
Man if I really was convinced
By all of these dumb dumb
That the election of
Installing
And that it was in
Important
To do what happened on the 6th
Then to hear them do this
Which feel like the biggest
Betrayal like about that before
Gave a s*** about the government again which is already been stolen
Like at that point
It's get rid of these f***
And cowards
They're the ones who stopped us from winning
Like that's that's such a f****** like if you're one of the Oath Keepers who's being charged
Absolutely
He's got to be
B like it calls into question what their their motives are
They were presenting to you as being hot
There won't be any shirts of Alex like they're worth of Shay
I remember Zapata coming out and being like hey man I think I think this was actually somebody else's fault they I think this is
Completely
I do wonder if like during those revolutionary times in the past and places
Were there people trying to capitalize on it like Alex
Were there
Like some kind of media grifters
Engaging in the same way I wonder
Pink Sober
Because the ad think the right-wing I think the traditional way of the Griff goes the right-wing does this s*** and then
Whenever the left wing
Does the fighting
Then the the media and everybody goes
Hey this is
This is wrong and you guys have to
To stop and everybody police's the left
Sensitive
Announce be maybe I'm not entirely sure I'd like to do if somebody had a
Play paper on that
So this is why
I just wanted to make a reason
The relevant thing it's not just some kind of astray
I don't think there's anything really two different than the norm
For my bracket reason to be aware of
The sort of rhetoric I can use it
When Alex interview the Q Shaman afterwards
Raccoon with his Coho
He was on with him trying to create this Narrative of false flag
So f*** all that we say that all the time
That's not going to work any of the other time movie
We've been trying to make this happen for years
We've been infected with a question that they asked if this is about the pictures and video
Video of him at the Georgia state capitol with Nick Fuentes
Ali Alexander
Station calling for the best
Do you want to go in
We get our speech outside
I do my show
But
Olly Alexander and Jones
Peaceful
Oh man
When we left
So that was our goal
To organize that a new plan that
Going on in
Georgia
Bandsaw
The best I can remember we just went
Is Vernon Jones
Ever heard
Really nice
Smart guy never heard
Also spoke on January 2nd
They asked me if we were with
Proud boys are we leave we were with
Okay /
Hooters
Having guy almost family
Around my shoulder
What we never met
I don't know if Alex recognizes this or not
But they're not asking about the Georgia thing for the sake of any violence or anything like that
This is a question about ali Alexander
Who organized this
Bastille
And all of the things that Ali was doing
Leading up to
I don't know if Alex recognizes that
Or is being intentionally obtuse
I do think that this is
This is definitely one of those lines of quest
Anywhere you could see Alex
Feeling relieved
Eli call thanks
This isn't about
Sure I'll tell you whatever you want to hear about this George when I didn't do anything wrong there this will never come back to bite me in the ass
Yes but he probably still plugged
So they also asked
The very important question of whether he had proud boy knows keepersecurity on the sea
And we know that Rodger did
Keeper security
It's on the other hand he's not
He's not one of these poor people who accept free security
They kept you asking me do I use all keepers
Eu's
Cowboys' security
Professional Security on not putting these people down
But
Crowds at me
Bus
Ticketstorm the capital
12 or 14 security people for all those
Mega Man
Because when you're in the middle
People you need that
Just to be able to
Maryland police
Well-known private security company
Here in Austin
That responded works for
People that work
You know
People in the world
Hillary Clinton made Gardens
You know Joe Biden that guarded Michael Bloomberg I'll just say the name
Off-duty with us
Insurrection
By the way
What what
Like an exterminator
I mean I do like in a what am I poor I'm not Rodger I still have a job
Also
I'm going with black people
What what
I want a guard made a I won't have never had any problem with black people serving underneath me it seems weird that
You would think that that would be a problem
I don't
No
At what point it comes up at Alex
Keepers around still
Social Security
If they're like
Following you around
Clearlake keepers are like chips at a party just cuz you don't need them doesn't mean that they don't have to be there
Weird
And he almost bailed on going to the Capitol
To do that I just want to go
Asma loves cheeseburgers
Victor
Amy was going to really happen
We were just at a hoot
Just about
Leave when my wife was freezing
The hotel a drink coffee
Take a hot shower
And not even be part of the cow
Cuz
The Running Man
Liaison with in the White House
Caroline Rhea
One Security guy
Outside
And
Pictures
Maybe we just won't do this
Cuz they're like
Then all the sudden
They come over there
Through
We go back
Let me get let out
Oh my God
The midstream
Seeing people
Control
Moana.
I do feel like
Pleading the fifth
Might be counterproductive to him at any of this is true
Like if any of this is true then he could be like I just doing what these people told me to death
If I have somebody from the Trump campaign saying
Hey you should go
I'll leave these people took Capital right
I think you could maybe kick the ball down the road you know I might be smart
Might be smart committee to be like ask them they told me to do that
Of the conspiracy you understand I was used
It is always fun whenever I see somebody who purports
To be a leader
Really sang I've never seen any of this or had any responsibility for any of this stuff at all
I want to take a shower
No I mean like okay so we had the speech at the ellipse
Spam Trump was like we're going to go to the capital has the biggest
Protests that have been planned forever the stop the steel shed
He said Owen on a f****** Caravan across the
Country earlier. The steel rally
But patents
About to speak
My wife really wants to go so I'm going to get out of here guys anyway
Good luck with Alex's like during the Revolutionary War
Lexington and Concord sounds fun but
Auto apps
Some stew
I could use some egg whites right about now
Hey you guys do what you need to do
L so
Alex Alex is trying to rationalize like why you don't
Engage with these
Committees man
I can tell you what happened here
I just give me the bay
You make one little mistake
Talkin to that committee
About what
Obvious
That would convicted newborn baby and put it
Sabrina
Eat that baby
You said you can't go into something
Baby
Deal with something at that level of corruption I'm sorry
You put one rat
It's no good
No
Like that
But also I would love that if like
Young Billy
You have been accused of
She has no remorse
Penalty
Exactly
Baby out here anymore so ridiculous but still
Yeah so dumb
As we've already
Kind of got the vibe of
Seems like Alec
Text thinks that he's making his statement to the committee on his show
Yeah where they can't prosecute
To finish up my
To the
January 6th to me cuz I can't stand under oath
Because if I said
Behind me
They would say well actually there's some black
It's not really purple you lied
Present
5 years
I really wonder if there's an ability
Because Alex is saying they're so like he's making
The statement
On his show
Use his show
As
Who's Satan
Why not
He wasn't sworn in and you can't say that they are true but
If you do know any information you can say well we know this and this
And how he presented it
And also guess what we recorded these f******
Depositions or whatever
Become under oath then
If you think I'm making my statement
Can you do that now
I don't know if it's some sort of magical transitive property
Guess but I think
Is nrcc
Society for some reason cuz we live in pretend world is legally but
Tumi
That's what he's trying to convey to the audio
He's like business as good as on the road I just don't trust them to be under oath for them
Exactly it's just a facade it's it's
Yeah I mean I already asked if you were going to say that you
Didn't say anything to the
Committee
And then say these are the answers that I would have given
To the six committee
I'm only doing it on my show
Then that does not suggest to me that you didn't say anything to the committee
That says you said something
Completely
And you don't want that information
Baby baby
I don't know it's really hard to read it is
So I wanted to know is if Alex at heard any Rumblings of violence
Alex said
Alex was Rumblings about his stomach was rumbling what's up with the BIOS
He just thinks it was from
Did I hear about violence and the answer is
Yeah
Family
New York Times writers Washington Post writers
Kill Trump supporters
Shooting Trump
Supporters
All of the countries
Courthouse
Ivy
Vice-presidential candidate
Congress houses
Breaking windows
And so yeah that raise the temperature a lot
No one around me
Call
I was doing
Logan
Conservative TV and radio
Civil War
Time of the second amendment that was a
But you always hear that in politics in America
You always here
F****** Howard
God that's pathetic I do like the the notion that like the background noise on conservatorship
Second Amendment
The right-wing is always we always do that
Your show
It wasn't on
Conservative radio that you heard
Your ship doesn't listen
I don't know about bracket
I'm saying
Just on his show
We heard it
What if I f****** hate these people what a bunch of frustrating
So lucky doesn't want war
Unless
Once
Snow
It is an information
Let's get something clear for the committee
Want a Civil War in this country
Wallace's by anybody
If you want to fight
In the infowar
Breakfast and up
And say I don't know how this is going to end but if you want to fight
You better believe you've got one
Ian
Leanne
Infowar means we fight
With information
We fight with the truth
Is this a non
Violent War
Alex Jones.
Fine it's an information
What's the information
We will wear now people think that what we
We did was bad information man the information is that
The government is killing us they're going to destroy the Second Amendment and we should overthrow
Why in this war that's all about information does Alex around with a lot of people who seem to be
Involved in physical warlike Tommy Robinson or Gavin McInnes
Girlfriend based Stickman most of whom don't have any information whatsoever
Is the fight that you're bringing in the information War like what does that mean
It doesn't mean anything we're propaganda to try and empty Temple
So this was a shocking thing that I heard neck
We did it
Take the weed out of it
And
Replace that with Stewart
No s***
Obviously
People followed us around
Every different type
And every different group
Oscars
He was a general
Turns out you're wrong
But I saw a lot of it is
High stakes
Took a lot to burning cities and try to help businesses and that's not why
For most of its
Operation
52 taking somen
Or something
Support or something I want
Show me
Biography
Testimony
You've just been hit by a bus as a big ol 12
Stupidest f****** a****** in the world
This dude has been a guest on his show for 13 years he was working a kickoff a civil war
When it didn't work out Alex had them on the show repeatedly to run cover for me
Create the narrative
Didn't do anything wrong it was all set up by the left
Assume that either Alex is the most in
Competent
Goebel was idiotic person in broadcasting
Or he's feigning this ignorance on the show because he knows he can't say any of the show Underoath about looking
Like a big ass liar
If I'm Stewart
If I'm Stewart Road
And I have known Alex for how long I have made all of my
Exceedingly clear
Very
I mean
Like with bullet
Clear
Maybe yeah I think that
If you listen
Stuart Rhodes is appearance on the show he's very blunt about like
We need Trump to just f******
Mancos
Now
If I heard Alex say that
Throughout all that time
Get real with it
He thought I was LARPing
I would be furious
Yes that would be the most
Are you telling me that you've known me this long and you not
Once took me seriously not one well I know because we have to actually parse this out a little bit
On the 60 was LARP explain soldier in the sandbox
But apparently he wasn't LARPing
Are playing
Soldier in the sandbox whenever they would go
Hey try and intimidate people at Social.
That was knocked out
Very serious very serious big strong men doing the right thing
On the 6th whenever they start the capital and planned
Conspiracy tour
You only bring several thousand dollars worth of guns to multiple different places around d.c.
The LARP it was a goof it was a fun time they were all made of
Cardboard and foam
Yeah I think I look better hope that Stewart stays in prison
Cuz otherwise
Lipstick
He doesn't find a way to bring Alex into the same
We got one more clip here and
I think this is really revealing about the inner conversations that were happening about the sick
Within Infowars
You know
I was screaming at the crew and just frothing matter what a disaster it was
Fit
We are going to make this the end of the world
Martial law
I never shut up about this
That clip is so revealing
Screw except extreme
His buddies had done the storming but Alex was furiously rejecting that idea
But it wasn't because he actually knew that they had
It's because he was afraid
Consequences of accepting that they had
Opposition to the notion that the Patriots store in the capital wasn't based on fact or evidence
It was routed only
Fear that if everyone realize that they had done it
It would lead to negative consequences for people associated with that community of right-wing extremist
That's cute understand
Alex needed to make up a story to evade responsibility and try to provide cover for right wing
Extremism
Then that's his goal in the information War he wants to lie
Try to escape consequences what don't you understand about being the tip of the spear
I've been I've a lot to learn trailer
Is a good idea better turn around and then leave
The tip of the spear pokes people in money flows out
That's about right
Beer blames another sphere
Is that Halbert over there
I really think
Halberd halberd halberd
The medieval axe
Wordplay so
Clippers jersey
So
Indicative of how his mind works
It's it's not about we didn't do this it was about the consequences of recognizing that if we
We have
Yep Bergen ever going to stop talking about this help so we cannot possibly accept
Is being a conclusion
That people are allowed to hear and except
And we have to muddy The Narrative soon enough
That it
It can never be taken away concrete
Metaphor is very much in play will never be taken away
We will always
Always always believe that it had they had nothing to do with
I didn't see that in the immediate reaction after the 6 the way that it was a
Mad Dash to invalidate blame everything always angry with blacklivesmatter goons dressed up
Buddy but they're dressed up like Trump supporters and that's why it looks like Trump supporters are doing that's why you can see people like Matt
I can immediately and validate everything that he had been talked about for your believe in order to
Just aggressively get in place this narrative
Because otherwise
Their worldview is f***
If we get the consequences of their rhetoric becomes too obvious totally too many people and just like
After the Oklahoma City bombing
People start to take this s*** seriously again
I don't know who it was you who made this point is like
For a long time it was
More
Convenient and easier to just ignore these assholes
We learn over and over again in society that like
All right it is no longer
The Tipping Point has been reached is no longer expedient to ignore them
There is a danger that this present
I think that Alex and always
Dickhole friends recognize that
After this evil allowed to be seen for what it was that point would be reached
And they'd fight against that in the information War
I guess
No no no never going to get away with it I don't know if I call Stuart low-level
I mean I mean low-level in the sense of like ground troops
You know what I'm saying sure the media figures that's the way this is
Starting to look
I don't know if Alex is going to get in any kind of like serious legal trouble but I think that
From the sense I'm getting some of these questions that they're asking of
Appear to be like
Pretty good
Yeah no they do I think
I think
That really xxxx
Excavating
The connections between The Oath Keepers who are hanging out with everybody right now that you have that indictment in place
The security that they were providing for people and how's that interact with
The planning of the stop the steel folks
I think
I think you got
You got something weird people
People are something to be worried about more than I thought
Yeah we'll see we'll see
This
Episode
I take not seriously at all except for the ways in which
Alex is revealing Houck
Cooperative
I don't think that I
Know for sure whether he plead the Fifth
I don't know whether
Turkey
And we'll learn more as more information comes out it's still relevant
Direct knives away
He covers things up the way he makes
Excuses for himself
A 10
I am if I didn't answer any questions it's totally justified has an illegitimate committee run by a Forger
It's nonsense
He's a coward
That's so f***** up to me because it's like
I almost want to be like
With right-wing people are going to be like hey before we even talk about being right wing
Whatever you believe
F******
You're entitled to it but
This guy's a giant Howard just don't follow him
You know like follow
Follow another piece of s*** s*** let me clarify let me qualify that
Don't go with a knot
I don't want any of that s*** anywhere near me
Articulate what you're saying
Recognize the ways in which this guy's a coward and using false information in order to enable his cowardice and his business
Learning experience for you
Anybody else you're considering following
Debuts that kind of thing screwed me about what they're up to know if you can see if you can
Define better sources of information
I mean it's just that
That like listen
It could not get
Any more clear
They will incite you they will lie to you they will try and get you to commit the worst crimes they will have you on
On your
And then they will let you die
And tell people that it was
Nothing to do with them they will let you go to prison they'll say they never
I heard of that type of behavior rear end you will be abandoned
In a heartbeat if it is
Expedient for them
That's what I want no leader
And I think
I'm interested to learn more but I don't think I know anything at this
Website.com
That's we're also on Twitter or fighting I go to bed
But until then
The sex robot
Alex
Birthstone colors