Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
MoneyGram
Acknowledge
Dot-com
Text jono indeed we are
Yes
Pandora
I have a quick question what's up
Is a little bit complicated
I guess it's a bit my cat's okay
Ethylene is okay
Out there listening
It's been a weird weekend
Celine has been having some
Coughs
And it would appear to be difficulty breathing
And so I took
32in emerging
Conceived that on Thursday right after we got done recording
Episode and I was there
Nice people
At the emergency
It's about I will say that
Tip my hat to
Remember they were very comforting a friend
Butt x-ray is done and it turns out that
Celine has asthma
Just like the Nerdist School
And so on the one hand is
Inconvenient a little bit
But you know whatever it is what it is
We got to take care of your cat
But on the other hand
The huge relief
Because
What
What other possibilities could there have been in liquid is manageable and
See ya
I don't know I guess it's
Absence of a real
Dark spot whenever whenever Fanny we give her eye drops three times a day and she needed look
He was starting to go blind
You know so we're we were panicking before we ever did that and then you find out all three eye drops
Today
Sure I'll do all day
Jitter that kind of
I showed you the inhaler
And the mask that I'm supposed to use to get Albuterol
She's having an attack
I made it to nightmare there's no way she's
You can put up with this
Quite a tiny bullhorn but it's
She's a headstrong cat she doesn't take kindly to
Do I ask my Mac
We'll see what happens
Yes yes very isolated case
Yeah well you know there's a there's a vegan restaurant
Butterfly
Okay
I saw that he had that one
They reached 21 Majors first
Definition row
Notes
Yeah and it's
It's very funny he came back
From down two sets to love in the final
Against the best the best
Hardcore player alive right now
Maybe and wound up winning it
Crazy is awesome
And the more you think about it the more you realize that
The number one reason baby
You know cuz he's
He had to defeat the best players in the world
Sure
But maybe the number one reason that he
Djokovic 221
Is because Djokovic has an idiot
Take the vaccine sure ends
Lost
History forever
Isn't that very funny
Yeah it is pretty funny it's kind of funny it wasn't an injury demands just an idiot
Who was choice
Go to brain injury
Of being an enable to just get a f****** backfeed and make history forever
And it said Rafa did it
History of inovatech
I'm glad you had a good time and that's your boy
Great I hope I got to bed at 8 a.m. this morning
Only 5 hours and a half
So Jordan today
This is Alex
Back in studio he's gone to the woods with his child news returns
This this episode
It's interesting
I think he got renewed by the being in the forest that outdoor hair
I think he's lost
His desire to quit
Maybe he's revitalized
We would have
Half the time we are sentence
Eternal death everytime if he'd just gone to the woods that week
I think it's pretty obvious that
Remind applies to a lot of people in a lot of professions
You know getting burned out
Yeah you didn't burn out and it's affecting your performance and for Alex that burnout just
Manifest
I am saying that everyone deserves to die maybe you want to leave and never come back
DC go to the woods for a day or two
Same difference
Best weapons in the woods
So we can get that business on this but first hello just
The first policy
Text Brad
Respect for America thank you so much
Thank you very much
Skidoos thank you so much
Thank you very much and finally we
Text Jordan
The person who baby making fun of
The year of the Seltzer thank you so much
You're not with
I have
Risen above
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
Got to hear tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Apologize
Was legitimately having right now
You better go to the wood go to the woods
I'm so glad we start off today
It's beginning of this episode Alex
Is real
Pumped
Yeah. Some goings-on in Canada
Scoresby trucker Convoy culminated in a protest
And Otto odd this Saturday
Sure
Alex plays a Sizzle reel of this over we are not going to take it
No longest Convoy ever recorded in Canadian history
Mouthwash million Truckers
What more people are joining the peaceful civil disobedience
This is how you doing
That's a
That's a bad sing along
It's going down weather over the weekend in Ottowa there was a convoy
Truckers that were form
We're making our way to the prom
Protest information
In the days leading up to this a whole lot of misinformation was spreading about the size and impact of the Convoy
Regardless of the truth
It seems like pretending it's the most important thing in the world is exactly what Alex needed
Resume Black Underwood
To distract himself from the rest
Everything in his life
Essentially collapsing around
The Convoy itself originated in Vancouver and then
Join in as a tour Canada
But estimates of the number of participants
Over the place
Alex's singer maybe a million truckers which is
Absurd
There's just no way to even close to Accurate there that
Number sets as of 20
18th there only approximately 302000 truckers in the entire
Country of Canada
That does seem like a
Big Ups
Difficult to get into a milli
It strains credulity that some others Convoy would attract / 3
Three times as many truckers as are contained in the entire Trucking Workforce in Canada
But that whatever
The length
So the Convoy Alex is saying it's the longest in Canadian history at 50 something miles long
Pitcher the spokesperson for the Convoy told the
Toronto Sun that was over seventy kilometers long
Would you be about 43 MI
The song
Careful to point out that none of that had been in
Independently verified
Staff
The estimation that are flying around a bit excessive and what are the ones that's caught on as the main talking point that's being spread
Comes from a former NHL player
Theo Fleury
Who are the guests on Laura Ingraham show on Fox
I was at there was 50,000 truck
In the Convoy
Has been repeated all over the place
50000 trucks
That number is pretty outrageous to imagine but if there were 50,000 trucks on the Convoy that would be a big
The problem is that other folks
Put
But much lower
Kingston Police in Ontario tweeted out account
Convoy departed on the morning of January
Quote 17 full track
After trailers 104 tractors with no trailers
424 passenger vehicles
76 RV
There's a chance of this isn't the full scope of the Convoy and it's
It's really hard to tell
Some folks are claiming that there are multiple convoys that are meant to convergent Auto or not they're going other state electron
Yeah
It's hard to know what is
The full picture ever
This little 7
I don't know I got no idea
Okay
The point is that it's really hard to get an actual count of what kind anywhere near as big as what
Being promoted by the organizers
NHL players
Or Alex
Because here's the thing
This whole Convoy is just a very very anti-vax operation
Banana political spec
It began as a protest against vaccine mandates
For truckers crossing the border
It's really sprawled out from that point to become a Flashpoint
Where the exact issue it's meant to protest has become a bit
Clear
Baby today talked to a woman named Dolores
Who said the Convoy is quote also about an us-versus-them mentality
The chi believes applies to the vaccinated and unvaccinated
Fascinated
That is vague
We're here we're not sure why and we're really mad about it
There's absolutely no chance of this Convoy has widespread support
A larger Canadian Trucking industry
There's a few facts
Consult to help you understand that
The first is that the vast majority of truckers are
The second is that the Canadian Trucking Alliance
MC group that represents most of the truck
Providers in the country
Be sure to stay on January 22nd denouncing and strongly
Discouraging the Convoy
It wasn't even really about the political
Statement it was actually about the boat that was being used
The protest
Quote the Canadian Trucking Alliance does not
Support and strongly disapproves of any protest on public roadways highways and bridges
CTA believe such actions
Especially those that interfere with pump
Public Safety are not have disagreements with government policy should be
Expressed
Members of the trucking industry who want to publicly Express displeasure over government policies
Can choose to hold an organized lawful event on Parliament Hill or
Contact their local MP
What is not acceptable is disrupting the motor
Current public on highways
And commerce at the board
Another consideration is that the Convoy doesn't really have the will of the people of Canada behind
An ipsos poll that came out this week found it
67% of respondents
Quote walk the government to impose
Further measures
On the unvax
Canadian population
There is a strong sense of
Almost everybody else
There's a charade that's going on here is being played out by really well
Call by right-wing media figures to make it look like this is a
Countries population rising up again
The oppression of covid
I could have sworn that like a week ago Alex
Declared Victory because
The countries all of them in the world
Including Canada it simultaneously announced they're dropping their covid restrictions
Talkingshit
Things up
Here here's what's up
Krypton boy was organized by a woman named Tamara liquor
She's the secretary of the Maverick party
A right-wing political party that was founded in 20
When it began it was called Alexa
Because their original point was having me Western provinces separate
From Canada
They have no representatives in the senate or the House of Commons
Because their views are largely unpopular
Because the idea of Western secession is
Starter generally in terms of electoral politics
And because of that they change the name for the Maverick party
Right because they wanted
To be associated with Mel Gibbs
Spinosaurus
On their Twitter page you can clearly see that the Maverick party is using this Convoy organized by their secretary to recruit
People into their party
I've generally it
It's not so much that they're using a position to covid measures to do that it's largely just attacking Justin Trudeau
Their leader the merry party leader jhil tweeted quote
If a convoy does nothing more than convinced all Canadians Trudeau is up
Prophetic leader it's done a good job
So I guess the goal for them is less at the raising of covid restrictions that are supposed to be hurting Truckers
Politically hurt
Trudeau and of course rave party membership
Hopefully bringing donations this is weird misspelled Canadian
No he spelled it like a
Can't argue with that
It is a Roka spelling
This is essentially been a political pageant for jayhil and his party
The entirety of what
This Convoy and all this is right there is an element of this
They're piggybacking and trying to use it as a coming out
The secretaries of party organized
It's it's 8
Subtle Buzz Marketing
Website
January 25th the leader of the Western Standard
Who voiced support for the Convoy saying quote Maverick Sports
Canadians right to participate in peaceful protest when they feel compelled
To draw their government's attention to important issues
And even told them that
The party isn't directly involved in the trucker protest
Neglecting the party secretaries one of the main organizers of it
Another co-organizer
Has deep ties
The party
This is a very dumb shell game that these people are trying to play where they pretended his giant spectacle that was organized by a member there
The party leadership and is being used
Recruit people to the party
Hopefully it's nothing
Things to do with the party itself
Just a weird coincidence
Go into that
To the tribute cause freaking
Concern and that is the Dynamics of the GoFundMe campaign
And that was set up for the Convoy
It a very short. Of time the campaign had raised over six million dollar
Warriors and the bulk of the donors
Anonymous
Using aliases
It's not too weird to donate to things anonymously I think that's a pretty normal human impulse but
The concern
A number of the berry high-dollar donations are also from
Completely unknown sources
Donation of $25,000
Usher Yeah Yeah
She becomes a Merc
At this point
It's essentially impossible to tell how much of this donation pool was given by legitimate
Canadian citizen
The businesses
Concerned about covid restrictions
How much may have
Been donated by people from other countries who are just interested in funding something that they see is an opportunity
The Creator Flashpoint against public health mandate
The possibility that there's funding from abroad weather be from 11
D-backs proponents here in the United
It raises serious questions about how organic this whole thing is
A what
The money
Where's it going
Need for accountability
Beyond that point where's the money go where's the pizza place
Particularly considering
The chief organizers of the convoys in the leadership of a Canadian political party that does semen port
It's all very messy and I don't
Get the sense that everything here is aboveboard but I also probably
I don't think
I don't think all of the suspicious things are necessarily all worse case
Yeah I mean I imagine that
No I don't know anything about carrying it is
Campaign Finance laws
Or whether or not they even have any but I assume you can't just like
Grifter bunch of money and then be like I hi this is mine it's a campaign Finance
Now
Yeah I don't have no idea
Yeah I don't know I mean maybe it's fine
Google began supposedly of the protest against truckers needed to be vaccinated across the border this has now become a
Symbol of all opposition to Cub covid Public Health measures
And people who are extremists
The my direction are going to be drawn to this thing
There are legitimate dangerous
Is it considered like the fact
Even if the actual group of the Convoy art up
Anything violent
This does seem like a really Prime opportunity for someone
Use it as cover
Rumblings of a desire to have a repeat of what happened
The United States on January 6th
Which is cause for concern
The convoys organizers
So that's good
Like I guess
Circumstances he or something that a bad actor could exploit
Fairly easily
Is there a bunch
Two truckers heading to Auto on planning to essentially clog all the
Streets around the capitol
There's a danger that should something go bad it would be difficult for emergency responders to arrive on the scene
Whether or not that comes to pass the possibility the Clark Street
Could lead to an inability on the part of police or fire Crews or medical team
To get to where they're going is one of the reasons that most people don't recommend protest
Like that
They can easily have
Rippling unintended
The clients is that
That are just
This Convoy is not as large as Alex
The political message that
Designed has been diluted a hijack to the point where it's essentially
Does a proton
Are the roots and organization of adderal incredibly suspicious and the whole thing may just be Buzz Marketing
For Western secessionist political party
Ultimately this weekend
Will be
Urban points words with a little bit of
10th Street
Disaster
But I don't
Know if this is going to go anywhere
Like
Like itself
Right
Protest itself
I'm not sure
Tucker covered it
So it's most important this is absolutely nothing like
50 party in 2008 at all
There's another thing we need to dress really quick and that is
Protest itself
What's going on in Ottawa
The Convoy was organized by this person
The Maverick party
The protestors actually
Separate
Connected but separate
That one was organized by a group called
Canada unity and they're a bit more
Released a memorandum of understanding that's my
Express the goals of their protests which they're hoping to get the Senate
And governor-general to sign on to
This would require all the members of the Canadian government
To stop all covid public safety measures or immediately resign
It's a big ass
Essentially they're making an outrageous demand
And the alternative of it is to overthrow the government
This is dumb
Yeah this is Adam
That's designed to be
Ignored or reject
Which will then be used
Is proof that the government is evil and
Corrupting at these protesters did everything in their power
To get their way peacefully you to no end
Ultimately baby Extreme Measures are Justified
This is crafted essentially to be rationalized later
When
People take
Extreme Action
This was the lay of the land before the actual rally on Saturday then Saturday happen
A lot of what transpired so far
As far as I can
Intel's been fairly predictable
A ton of people showed up in Ottawa which
I'm saying that there's not 50,000 trucks and there's not a million Truckers
But I'm not saying that
There's nobody
Usher
The Fairly large turnout
Confederate flags
Even more unsavory regalia
The Shepherds of Good Hope shelter reported being harassed by protesters Amanda
Make food that was meant for people experiencing homelessness
We will set up various blockades around the country for instance one
On the border crossing between Woodstock New Brunswick
And Houlton Maine
As of the time I prepare this episode this looks to be a completely disorganized massive that definitely could lead to some trouble
Down the road who knows
The demands have long ago spun out of control and there's no satisfactory resolution
For this protest
In terms of what they are
Yeah what are they what are they going to win
Even if they do get
To the negotiating table. Ask is everyone go away forever unless you do everything I want you
Public Health measures
At all
Also in a completely undemocratic process
Actually holding the entire nation I said yes
Play make some of the people they're claiming that they're going to stay until Trudeau resigns or public health measures are
Call drop
I'm neither of those things are going to happen
Especially not the as a result of
Strongarm demands
Also I dare you to
Stay there as long as you
Get out of here a little bit
Did the ludicrousness of
This proposition
Even the demand of dropping the vaccination requirements across the border
Is silly
Because it would still then require
Oster do the same
Yeah
Need to be pressuring
The Canadian government and ask for them to
Somehow change American law
You would literally be
In the full need of a nuclear warhead in order to try and get near the level of power
Are you need to negotiate that it's a bizarre
Decentralisation of this protest
With multiple convoys apparently spring up and
In the fantasy world objectives
They combined to create an environment that could easily get out of
Control
I'm fully ready to believe that there's some folks say in the protest and Convoy were well-meaning truckers who work for Independent.
Union operation
You're concerned about their livelihood
But the reality is that the way that this protest in Convoy have been organized and run
Are literally creating the ideal environment
Extremist
The insulate themselves within the protest and use that as cover to do some pads
Recording this on Sunday and no I don't think
Anything to
Bad
As far as I can tell
I don't know that it's
But the situation has resolved
Who knows if it's going to be ongoing
And I hope it
Get to resolve this with matter and no one gets hurt and nothing ends up
Happening
On the off-chance of things
Things do go bad let's
Let's not forget the people like Jordan Peterson and Joe Rogan Alex Jones
I were super aggressively promoting this whole thing
Really pushed for it
Yeah yeah
Without any awareness of how
Clearly disorganized this whole thing is
Then and how
A reckless
And didn't just
Just thoughtless
Play just like I mean so
Instantly just like oh
These guys are against the thing that I'm again so I'm just going to say yeah that go for it
Even if even if somebody is on
Somebody has
Mainly the same
Is this base
I'm still like
What the f*** are you about
I don't know what's going on with you yet you know like that kind of thinking these guys are like
Haven't heard of them f****** ye wait wait this seems to be drawing a lot of attention
I love it it's great. Was this a pro forest-fire I don't know k
What are the reasons that I
Kind of landed on having absolutely zero faith
This is actually ever was about Truckers
The Border CBC article
It had to do with the copious amount of regulations with truckers are already subject to lie
Like brake inspections load limits
Truckers are even subject
Physical exam
I'm sure that they're healthy enough to make their trip so
It only makes sense that this would just be another aspect of that regulate
In order to be a licensed trucker in Canada you need to possess a DOT medical certificate and that requires vision and hearing test
Submitting to your analysis and the running
Neurological and cardiovascular screenings
To make sure that you don't have a high risk
Procedures are heart problems that can impair you on the road
Need to re-up that medical card every two years
Throughout things that are required by the DOT physical
You'd be just as much
Medical tyranny of the vaccine requirements
So what's a little
The actual problem they have is the imposition
None of this new
It's me public-facing position that is
Kernel of respectability to it
The tithing what was
Really that's just
TJ Maxx
Nonsense a government to as being about these
The Draconian restrictions
Philly and I mean it's there it's there
Great recruiting tool
Cross
Cross-pollinating tool
Get somebody who is a f******
Gwyneth Paltrow goop head anti-vaxxer to turn into somebody who's like
Yeah we should overthrow the f****** government
Cuz if you have it
Rally for like maybe Blitz not wear masks for a while it's somebody's like this what white nationalist
Let me let me also be clear
Don't think that like the whole thing is AstroTurf
Or anything like that just
Because the organizers
What main organizers happens we from this political party
And such
At 8 there's seems to be running
A little bit of a weird a PR campaign
Grover norquist
Consulted on or something
That doesn't mean it's like it's all a charade or anyting
Like Alex might say with antifa
Exit one I drifted
That territory
So Alex is thrilled about this Canada business
He reiterates his client
A a million
Well Canada is now the epicenter of human
Wakeling and human resistance
Millions
100000 and a million truck
The capital
All of the once-great nation of Canada
Now under Davos group
Command
Calendar Bilderberg Group command brags on TV
But he has
Canada and now has
The cabinet under his control
Yeah class Rob is from a conversation that he had in 2017 at the
Harvard Kennedy School
The Institute of politics
Conversation about the world economic forum's global leaders program
He did say that they penetrate countries cabinets with
With Canada being one of the examples he brings up
Who's at the one-minute clip that
It's been passed around right way
When Twitter cut out of context
Not scary
World economic Forum young Global leader program was all about
Drugs that Angela Merkel and
Had both been apart of it which
Really doesn't make sense I mean
What
It doesn't make sense in the context of this clip because
History is pretty clear
And this whole young at this young global leaders things
Didn't start until 2004
At that point Merkel was already the leader of the Christian Democratic Union party
And Putin was four years into his first sent
Is President of Russia
I'm guessing that maybe this might be a stretch
Yeah
Marco Island
Spoke to the
Nova leader
Young leader program
I don't believe
I mean unless they were in a very weird
A hotel Ballroom one
Time wearing odd uniforms
Babe with the rest
Group
I guess
I'm trying to think of like
Possibilities
Precursor organization to this but even then food was like in the KGB
Like going to a
Economic program
Wally's in the middle of assassinating sub
So you can go to the y g l
You can learn about their alarms and what they were working on when they were in the program
Princeton
Sarah couple entries from the 26
16 class
Hiro Nakamura and despeinada discool
Collaborate
To bring simple life changing Technologies to rural communities and reduce poverty and
Do clean-energy Prada
Another one
Dave Hanley and Shalini
Pucha Polly
Launched an Indian LED movement to prevent female infanticide and girls with tools to overcome
Systemic gender-based
Discrimination ohmygod they're still
These are the sorts of projects that are being done by these young leaders in the program which
Support their goals
Program did contact people in various fields
They could help them out along the way
It's unsurprising that people who are taking programs like this would end up continuing their careers pretty successfully
Be that in government or an NGO the
The deals with an issue that they're passionate about
That doesn't mean that the people who
We're in this program are
In the future and forever
Secret plant
From the world economic Forum has control over
You don't know what would be the point of teaching young people anything if you're not also implanting them with a chip that you can later
Control directions
Right right
I think
I think it's a little a little much
Yeah that might be a little bit of a stretch
Yeah but you know
You can you can kind of assume
There anybody who would be in this program is already self-selected to be really really motivated
Probably high-achieving person
Somebody's already invented a way to help people somewhere else by the time they were 12 is all of a sudden like oh yeah
Then let's go do it
Does opens up networking possibilities
Great on a resume in politics in a cabinet somewhere
Parts robbed
Discussion at the Kennedy School
And talk about being proud of people who went through that program
And then it's
Turned into Vase by glycerol Bragg
It's just annoying is annoying
Alex
He's
He's a
I think it must have been the forest error or something but he is
He's pretty big on
Declaring a bit of Victor
It is a very surreal thing
Chanel
The true talkingpoi
Coming out of
Congressman
Podcast
Fox shows everywhere
We have done it
Infowars
And this whole family
Have successfully launched a worldwide resistance of the globalist by being aware of them and understanding
That should make sure their program his death
Resistance in the program is like
Alex Jones here I've saved the world
Now
Haha
Okay and I'm taking
Complete ownership over creating a global movement
Fighting the
Globulus right
A global
International movement
Sure
I don't know if I would want to be associated with the one that brings Nazis
That's just me though
And it seems like all of his
Awakened movements
Have Nazi flag.
Confederate flags in Canada
Yeah
It's a little strange you know I mean
Play Twinkle mad at people
Coming from Mexico
To our Southern border
I mean the Confederate flag in Canadian Southern border that's just out of
Control right
Did you say Canadian while I mean if your if you got the Confederate flag you don't live in Canada
Not sure
The thing that the real talk
Greenpoint's getting out
Not so much of
Victory of the talking point
Is it is an erosion of who's doing
The talking
The people who are
Are in office
And
Rogan
Upright horror writer
What's there not
Necessarily the most
Critical
Finally the brains of the powerful have been melted enough that they do what I say
Power now
That's where we are damning indictment
So Alex
A little bit of his story
About what happened
On January
I don't believe this
But it does
Year later
He's finally really getting the
This probably is not relevant to court
Okay it's more relevant a psychic powers
Obviously we walked into a trap
January 6th
Obvious
We had minutes
I already got to stop at maybe Stewart Roads and they both Keepers did that s*** I have no idea what you're talking about
They was a complete trap
Nobody had any tranches of weapons we are back and forth
All over the place
On the show 20
Because you can't possibly actually know what the belief is
What is real every single day
Now
Always it was the other
Side literally
Warriors
B-big hand
Hundreds of thousands
A million people
Weeks before January 6th
And I just feel
That's not true
The Caravan
Where they at tho with Owen
Ironix9 the Caravan
There's no violence at those cuz no one gave a s***
Medicate
You couldn't have a fight at them or in the parking lot
I was like
This is going to be okay
Publican speeches and then
Beach hat on
I had a horrible foreboding feeling I thought
Quit being paranoid
Maybe you're just
Coming down with something
Picking up what was about to happen if we're being led into a trap in the
Truliant
They could have actually
Potentially
Millions of dead out of that
Maybe Alex just had covid 1/3 time
So Alex is talking s***
Premonitions about a false flag or some nonsense on the six
This is just him trying
To get ahead of any potential violence at the trucker Convoy and rally
Alex knows enough to know that
This kind of situation creates the kind of environment
It's ripe for exploitation
You know it's like how the thousands of people being around the capital and all that chaos created the exact kind of environment
The capital of
Didn't like
There's a nonzero chance of trouble from the truckers rally
All things being
Equal I already stole food from the
Swell
I think
That's awful
Spiritually in the world is bad
That's true matter of scale
I will give you the
No someone using the rally as cover for some kind of an attack
Streetzlan
Ambulances and fire trucks can't get to people who need their services
Could lead to death
Whatever the potential trouble that could come out of it Alex nose
But it's important to get ahead of it and preemptively declared a false flag so that's what he's doing
It's very inconsistent
It looks like there's a potential for it to go bad
Even though we're recording this on Sunday and we know that nothing really bad has happened
Yeah it
Alex's recording this on Friday
He's very clearly
Well the rain tomorrow
Let's hope something bad
Probably if it does
Rise of false flag no matter what
He's talking about
This premonition that he had on the 6th
Because it's really just to lead into talking about
The first trucks
Beside our arriving at
Beautiful neo-gothic
That is an extremely beautiful building by the way what
Something right out of Harry Potter
I was still beautiful
Stoneworks
Unicorns car
Lions
Everything
My point is
Make sure do look good
Make this look viola
And you know they're going to try to provoke
Keturah G
Occupy
Department
So weird cuz
If you think about it Alex insisting that it's definitely false
The message you could come away with his that you should do something
Yeah cuz then it would make them look like
False flag
There's no space
Ultimately you would
Probably be helping
The conspiracy cause if
There's a built-in pre-placed narrative the no matter what nothing bad can be blamed on the far-right demonstrator so you're not going to
Because someone does do something violent than that's going to be at the club
Esther all about that they had to do
I'm not saying this is the same thing as Alex encouraging people to go do something violent but informant function it serves no other purpose
Then to make it
Strictly beneficial
For the conspiracy narrative if something
Bad happened
That's so weird I mean it's almost like there
Priming someone
Tube
Actually Act
As though they were the false
Flag
Plant
Even though they're actually not the fault
You know like there's somebody new
To go there almost like somebody
Having a weird
But was just like
What if I did
Instead I did it but then I'm also a false
There's so many weird incentives
I do weird s*** whenever this is your plan here looking at this through too many
Ping pong table
So there's that there's trouble in Canada all around
Also one sec
A million
Theoretical
Right
Because it's not a million
It's not a million trap no sir
That would be
The length of
LeConte
Yeah
It would be a lot bigger
A million trucks
End in Canada
A million truckers 2 is
Is absurd
There's only like
Three and a half million truckers in the United States right now
Like I said 300,000 to Canada
So I mean
You're not going to get that kind of turnout
Or maybe even
I even 1,000 trucker
Is like
10 MI
Yeah I did I saw someone who did the math but I can't remember exactly what it is but there
It's absurd
Good morning things that the real problem is the people have a real inability
You to look at
Crowds
Sorel distances of things
Kids things do look
Bigger than they generally are and
I think you can see pictures of the crowd and I'm not diminishing them there still large crowds
But you can look at them
It's going to be like at 100,000 people
Baby 15000
You know it's
Iftar
Yeah I've never gotten the the guess the right number of gumballs in the in the jars
I'm not even going to
Come close to I've got it right every time yeah it's my superpower
Honestly that's kind of
Maybe the best-case scenario for
Superpowers
Spell clarify
I can't deal with Gumball
Cuz I can only do with jelly
Well I mean Jelly Bean
How dare you
Not just
Trucking related
Walmart's install
Customers
So the same things happening Australia
New Zealand it's our big stores
Grocery stores
There's a little bit of a weird situation that
A bit on the fence
On the one hand obviously I think at Walmart
Can set its own rules
Decide that a vaccine
Required for entry in the middle of a pan
Spine people complaining about it or not going to get my simple
Almost all of these stores allow people to purchase things and
Pick them up at the front door because as much as they want to follow Health guidance
They're more interested in making money
On the other hand
Evax Polk
Books of start of the camp
Painting Canada to boycott Walmart
Join up with him on this
I would say it if the end result
This is just going to be
Hurting Walmart's bottom line
I don't really care
How old is rules specifically doesn't apply to stores that sell primarily Foods
Every stores
Alright the grocery stores are exempt
From the back seat requirement
Alex has no idea what the actual policies are the tea
You complaining about
Works better for them.
Pretend that it applies
Universally
I mean
That's
We can
We can afford to
To put
Automated
Vaccine passport scanners
In places
Be harder to pay peep
Stay Holman
Nobita
Canadian Walmart might be
Be facing a
Boycott
From the unvax
Tomato
Walmart's install
Call vaccine
Tusk
Customers
Did you ever want to know what the Antichrist system would look like
The self-checkout machine
Did you ever want to know
What it would be like
When Walmart's become the FEMA camps
And there you go
See this is funny because back in 2015 during the whole Jade Helm Panic on Alex's show
What are the beacons
Pharisees was that FEMA was using
Close down Walmart
But they will take
Dissidents they rounded up
Like Alex and I remember
Stupid and never happened but the vaguest memory of that being something out
Addicted still exist in the audience is mine
Exploit that to use for his career
Also based on the story about what's going on with Canadian Walmart that seems like they're the opposite of FEMA camps
I want this whole thing is that going to Roundup unvaccinated people to put them into camps unless you're vaccinated
Far away from the Walmart
Contradict
Stupid
How do I
We're about to get into a section to show that I would say is
Transphobic
It starts
Slow with Alex
Getting into the ACT
Of the
Green Eminem Eminem
It's not about the great David Minnie Mouse is also getting rid of the dress
Right
Yep
Everyone mad
Everyone in my last moments is that what may
Make sense of this I don't know what's find out okay
Why do they
Biological males in women's sports
Dominate ever
Because of You lyrics every level
Ass backwards
Snow White
Female characters will not wear dresses
Ever
Women
Their culture and what they like and
Which I will tell them what it is
Flower Beauty
Appropriation
Call my God
Why is one species of bird
Colorful another species
This is Who We Are
This is what we do organic
No
You can't do that
Women will be like men and men will be like women
And that's what they done
Because it's an enemy of the people
Cheese
Alex implying that bees and flowers are the same species just different genders
Different Sexes of bees that is beyond the capability of both flowers and
Does he think that bees are drawn to
The flowers cuz they're pretty
But I believe
Flowers are beautiful
And that is why I am attract
It's about right
As opposed to a completely profen
Practical transaction
Exchange of power
But you can see here
I was looking
It up I don't know if I saw the Disney Princesses I think it's just about Minnie Mouse
Yeah but I really also only think that Alex is using that even talked about it because
You know other people like Tucker the most important person in the world
About this.
I think what he's doing is like
I got to get in on it also
Got to be really hate
I got to have a Twist on it
Wreck transphobia
Horrible men and women are different now it's got to be transphobic
Right
And Angie was tired talking points Sports
Yeah and now
Get the E pivots from talking about into talking about a story
That
To do with
A trans person
Who committed a crime
Against the child
Is going
Okay
And of the system work
Well this is an interesting case because
Did this person
They committed the crime
Years ago or so like around that time
When they were a minor
And so the courts decided
To send them to juvenile detention
Instead of going to adult
Which is a little bit strange
But also is something that
All of the like
The prosecution
Had no problem with
So there maybe someday
Details to this case we aren't aware of all right make this make more sense
Sure
I think it's an in
Interesting case and I think that there is a conversation
If someone probably could have about it
If you want to talk about it as a news story illegal decision that is maybe a little bit off
The beaten path
Right talk about why this could happen
But Alex doesn't do that
It is all just
Transgender woman man
Now 26 has been ordered to serve just two years in juvenile detention center for sexually assaulting a 10-year old girl
Adult
Formerly known as
Guilty
Young girl
In 2040
In Los Angeles
And be tried as an adult
The DEA declined to file a motion
Remove the case out of juvenile court
Creature in the child
What
Children
This isn't discussion of a news story or even analysis of a legal opinion this is just a person
Spewing hate
There's nothing in that clip Norton Antivirus
Conversation about the story that the discussion or leads anyone to any conclusion other than to hate trans people
They class
Of people
It's abhorrent
Halifax Alex actually wanted to express displeasure with the decision to place this person in the juvenile detention
Do that without any of the extraneous hate
30 throws input
I really wouldn't do it
For his audience
What are they realize it or not that
Kind of stuff is what makes the show exciting for them
The hate is the spirit that animates Alex's content and without it there is no show and there is no audience
Hit the displays like this there really should drive home how infrequently Alex
The contact is actually about what it's pretend
Nothing to be about
All the surface this is supposed to be about a Transit L2
Sentence to juvenile detention center for a crime they committed when a minor
Hope it's actually just an opportunity for Alex
The dehumanized
People using the story as a prop
I think this is a case
You could have it
Decent conversation about the story and not all parties acting
Good faith with
Necessarily agree whether or not it's appropriate to send an adult to a juvenile detention center for a crime that they committed as
And I don't think
To do with that conversation
You can see if this is the only aspect Alex
Latches
Spreading that kind of hate
Is his goal
Not discussing this as
Illegal
Decision yeah I'm struggling to see where trans comes in at all
Right
I mean other than I supposed I mean the sentencing question would be like
Stupid
The women's prison
I mean that seems like the obvious
Question
There's not a lot
To even talk about in terms of Alex's response to it other than to rebuke
His is bigger
Yeah I mean you you said it
You're done
You said it and you said
Within the rest of the episode that I did not
Include
Empty do I
I think I included this not necessarily to even
Talk about
The case because
Is
Response
Do it does not really
Require
No
But I do like I do include this cuz I are often
Include necessarily just
No just outright
Bigot nonsense
It's important every now and again remind people to like the content to
And it's
It's a homerun
That's what he's
Yep
Rodger Stone is coming back on
Sure
And
I need money or is he going back to jail
I mentioned on the last episode that he was on
30 Super Bee slurring a little bit more
Amy was a little bit in the character of it in the feel of it was
It was weird
He's back
Oh he's back to full strength he's Rodger ready to throw stones
Sweetheart vintage Rodger and part of that is that
He is promoting
Oh no his appearance
2 hours
Snow for he gets on the show
Better or his telegram or
What is
I'm at Rogers.
Set me this message
It's right here
And it says
I join Alex Jones today at 1:30 p.m.
Eastern Time
Endorsements and what is really happening in the world
And then he
This message he says this will be
The most significant broadcast
The 2006
Get ready
The most
Important
Person
In the world
Right now
Eggs
Rodger Stone
Send his appearances
What kind of a****** would
Said that to me
Let me tell you this
I'm never texting you at
Weep
Spoiler
This is not the most I have no doubt in my fires
At all on my mind
So we heard earlier that Alex is thrilled that
The dino the politicians and Joe Rogan
Brain tumor
The end times
All the time
This is the
Labeled New World Order world government and
All the pieces
And the training wheels for it
You hear nothing about this
Instead they ask you to check your qr-code make sure you got your vaccine pass
They're nothing but
Should insist
DentalWorks Cedars
To the belly of the Beast churches are working for the devil except for Alex's
Weird version of Christianity
System
I am real
Done with them it's a little tiring
I mean you can read the book
Says what's going to happen but also also the
The end times
By definition requires an ant
Keeps on going
And the Beast has so far been the same mark
Ingest many different ways
Dates for the past 20 years
No it's been a hundred different things it's been a different form of barcode or a QR code
Glorificate
Award for the vaccine
Theodore it's the same s*** it's just anything that you have today
Look
You got to get right with God
I know that you have
Whatever complaints you have butt
Sure together
God
Time for us to fight the hardest we ever had to spread the word and
No
What is going on
Show
We don't need to be running on empty
We need to go strong into the future
With as much Capital as we have
Top-rated best we can
The last chance you ever get
To get these supplements
Oh yeah baby I feel like it's a little sacrilegious
All churches are
Feeders to the belly of the Beast
Big-time got to get right With God all they want
Supplement
You got only one way to get right with God
So look
People Like Us
Alex probably think
Facts about the Lost
Where's supplement
Free
True unless
I mean there was a little bit of time where I was taking like
Ginkgo biloba
I don't know
So look we're lost cause
What does it mean
That the Convoy Isabelle so great
You're on the winning team you're fool
Throw your Birthright out the window you've destroyed yourself
And there's still time for you to turn back
But I'm not going to talk to people to serve evil
What's going on at
He did get your head straight
Focusing
And decide what you're going to do
Play spiritual
Cannot go along with this and not comply
The million people descending on Auto in Canada
50 60 70 miles long
Major directions
Opposing the great reset
Exposing the New World Order
Exposing WhatsApp
Infowarsstore.com in Highwood
Get these products and I would buy extra to have a
We were in the Sail by Monday vitamin
11 hundred percent of your vitamin
Are those rose hips
Why they jump
Isn't 100% the correct
Catamount
What's the point of having more than 100% of hundred percent
Anything more than that is too much
I think you see that on on vitamin bottles a lot multivitamins have like two thousand percent of
It doesn't you don't get to keep it
20 days of vitamin C valve
I just peed out the next day
Picture
I got no answer for you I don't know why is that happen but it does
What's going on here
Mourad Piva
We definitely need money
But you know doesn't Rodger
Rogersbase
And what's going on right now
Is a systematic
Fur by Mitch McConnell
Party
Control of the Republican Party
Now there are times when the president seems to understand this for example
Only weeks ago it was.
Who is aghast
AV by Congressman Chris
For Smith
New Jersey four
Joe Biden's bill.
Better trillion
Bonanza
Open self went on social media to call
A primary challenge to this rhino
Porsche
Speed Hoosier broadcast
Right side Broadcasting
Listen to District
I'll take you tomorrow
And now this rhinos in deep trouble
No he's not
Rogers
Disappearances mostly about how he's mad at the people that Trump is elected or site
He was mad about last time to ya
Rodger is
Going hard on the midterms and like trying to primary
Non Trump
Loyola right at least
That's pretty a
I mean I would say that's probably his best shot at getting relevant in
Politics
Probably
Making some of these bottles
Yeah I'm making some of these people beholding to him there is no
There is no president to sort of
Attach yourself to this election cycle really work on trying to get some weirdos into
And the Rhino is not going to hire me or listen to me or take my text messages
My crispy dude hell yeah hell yeah well completely
Congressional primary candidate getting thrown into the mix Iran Infowars and it's
Dumdum broadcaster from right side
Pedia has a profile on crispy and apparently a couple
His top issues are quote election integrity
And quote eliminating mandate
It's pretty easy to see that it's
Obviously attractive to the right-wing base
What is the stolen election narratives
Which is just basically
Re litigating 2020
Text bulshit
I wouldn't be surprised
Cuz if it was a lot of the conversation
Get on rounds
It's going to be annoying
What are the areas of public
What policy the crispy said he's
Passionate about personally is quote
Which is insane
I can't imagine how little you would have to engage with reality for that to be one of the issues you're most passionate about person
Unless you're racist
Well it's 20:22 there's a pandemic
Global International relationships are fuc
Crumbling in front of our eyes
Imagine if children knew that we were slave owners once
I'm personally passionate about this
Anyway good luck to this ding dong
He's up against Chris Smith in the primary who's been in office
In 2020 who won the Republican primary with 94.8% of the vote
And if all the candidates running
Stick around of the primary it seems
Completely unfathomable that he will lose
Against four other candidates who have a high likelihood of splitting the weirdo vote
Amongst themselves
Spell all get one
Dave Berg is running in their primary
Candidate who's prioritizing quote
Eradicating the race Theory
It only has one book listed in response to the question of what his favorite book is
You think it's a vibe
Oh no
It's not no iron Rand it's Molly Hemingway's book rig
Which is about the 2020 election being stolen
Bergen crispier essentially going to be fighting each other over the weirdos scrap
And Chris Smith is
Easily went
Counting Mike
Blasi be veteran
Also America First candidates in the primary
Who recently tweeted in favor of requiring IDs to vote
And also posted a meme with a fake Martin Luther King
Quote
The hottest place in hell is reserved for those who remain neutral in times of great moral conflict
But isn't the Martin Luther King quote it's
Actually just a poor paraphrasing of a line from Dante's
Stanford out to various sources including Hellfire preachers and
I'm later JFK
Anyway this guy wants to bring back Jim Crow laws and his post
Fake MLK quote
Memes on Martin Luther King jr. day he's also going to be splitting the particular voting block with Bergen crispy
When is this is Christmas
Race to lose
I'm really waiting for the next Republican candidate to take it another another notch
Can just be like a Merica
Das
White people first
There we go now you're uniting the base right there that's what they really look
Looking for
Mrs. Rogers first
Salvo
Crispy
If you start with a losing effort and see what
Give God you know the second one is actually a little bit more plausible but also is a huge loser
Who said that he was open to a third impeachment over Donald Trump
Regarding January 6th
This guy is the number-one rhino in the country
He's a certain
A a hard-charging
Fishman
Who is Bilton extraordinary
Grassroots campaign
Beginning
Jackson Longmire is probably not going to win this primary but is a perfect in Infowars typed
Today because
He's a f****** con man
You made headlines in late 2021 because he was offering to provide his signature for people to use to get religious exemptions
Remind me vaccine requirements
But in order to get one you had to donate to his church
This is really fun because not only is it him selling his religious beliefs not selling it
It's also a complete
He's running on the scared
Is appealing to giving to the Lord
Every state has different rules about exemption
But there's almost no situation where you would be required of a note from your pastor in order to get one
This is babyshit like imagining that vaccine exemptions are like getting your parents
The sinus lift it says you don't
Go to gym class is this a stubblebine original laminating cards
Say you don't have to hurt me mad
Exploiting the ignorance of people he's marketing
Himself to specifically using the appearance of his religion
Disposition for profit
That makes me real piece of s*** and just
The sort of person that Alex and Rodger would want it off
Office
In this case again there are five candidates in the GOP Primary but the extra little bit different
James Lankford is the incumbent but he has two people with actual political experience running against him in the primary
That's less weirdos to split the weirdo vote and more actual politicians who could end up safe
V
I still doubt that Laumeier is going anywhere but he's got a better shot than crispy in terms of
Just a folk story
Primary actual politicians dropout
Before the primary.
If that doesn't happen then beat they could end up
Splitting
De nada
This is going to be one of the funnier Republican primary election that will not be funny
Baby funny for me just because it's going to
Constantly be that Futurama joke
Book of the
3% titanium
Is it go too far enough
I think you're 3% titanium text goes too far you know like
They're all saying the same s*** America first
Anti-vax they're all saying the same s*** at each other
Right it's bananas right and I really want to set themselves apart
They're going to have to go even more
That's the only way to differentiate how do you pull away from the pack
In Crazy Town
You got to go crazy
You can't go saying you can't be like hey I'm the guy who thinks we should compromise nothing about you man
The real quick
So Rogers got another
Cuz candidate
I think we should reach across the aisle
Is Rogers at another candidate
This made me really sad
What about Laura Loomer
He's running an incredibly hard charging race against
Webster didn't even bother to show up
To vote against impeachment
And he didn't even bother to send
Or loomer's not going anywhere
That's his face is just
Rough the Specter of Laura Loomer becoming a congressperson
Not very scary
Not worried about it
Not at all
Didn't go well
Even though she was
Way ahead in the
The poles she was ahead by 6
Billions and billions and billions of dollars in it
More money than she had like 80% of the vote
All the money and then it was stolen drummer
Okay
Good luck
So we got a scam epreacher we got a right side broadcasting weirdo
Cool
This is why
Galaxies politician
Repeating his talking points
Yeah you know I
Worried
That the intellectual Powerhouse
Rodger
Gaston
Alex Jones
And Laura Loomer
I don't know if we can defeat them
Yeah
It's daunting
Keysmart
It's a game of four-dimensional chess
Alex even put Laura Loomer name on a video
In a f****** support her on a ballot
The f*** out of here
That's a good boy
So Rogers got some big election2020 news
Haha
By the way today
Where the Pennsylvania
Mail-in ballots used in the last election
Unconstitutional
Clear to most of us but
Publican State Legislature
Riverside
And legalize mail-in ballot
Now it will go to the Supreme Court
Pennsylvania
Which leans left
If the next election
Is held in Pennsylvania under the old rules
You're not going to elect a republican governor
I appreciate your
Conviction
Yeah so this is about a law that Pennsylvania passed that allowed
No excuse mail-in ballot
So does that to do with the entire issue
Mail-in ballot
Specific
Circumstance cuz of the pandemic
Silky folks challenge the concert
Douching ality of that law and lower court
It's comprised of
Three Republicans into Democrats vote
There was against the Constitution
Oh yeah which way which way did it go exactly how you
Appeal to the state supreme court struck down in
Global stand
It's not just because that's a green portal e52 Democrat
Like majority
Even if the Supreme Court did
Throw this out
Like they've Struck it down
It wouldn't have any effect on the 2020
No I'm pretty sure we have to go back in time
Now
So what really demonstrates how much of a cold the GOP is become is the fact that 11 of the GOP lawmakers hooray
This challenge to the court actually voted
For the bill to become law
Open controlled legislature
Alex love to misuse 1984 references but this might be actually a good spot
How to deploy that
One of those
Yeah I think it's a little
Yeah that's a little CC
Dolittle
Stop like these 11
These 11
We
We passed it unconscious
Tie-dye chest
I just don't even know that we voted
Open favorite hits it's insane
It's insane
It really is
Insane
Is it safe
You just have them all walk out and go
And that would be the same thing
You mean like a
People do to Alex Alex at the grocery store just do that because it doesn't matter what you
You say all of your words mean nothing
Speaking of which
Alex heard a clip of trump saying that he's going to be the 45th and 47th president
Here's Alex's response to that
Ridenour to play this clip of a
Rodger
Gonna run
Was the final deal
But he will be the 40
President that is got a scare the hell out of the left I thought Alex
Heated Trump now mean
These these these folks especially like Alex
I have a base
So much
Of their ability to engage with the world
Trump
Sycophant
Nonsense
They can't go away for
Like they'll get mad
Nml come back even though
I don't know does Trump change his position on vaccines
Certainly didn't get unboosted
I mean the thing about it that's really interesting
First thing is that they are beholding
Into fake Trump
Forever
Trapped in this world of like
Oh we made this fake 12 real
Yeah cuz the real one
Is nothing like the fake one
Yeah I made talks about that even like he's our Peach
The symbol this
Signet
Yeah I mean
The thing about making a flag your symbolism
Set the flag can't contradict you
You make a dude your symbol he's going to be disappointed
And then you got to throw a fit
And then you got to get back in life
Recognize this dynamic
Really clearly by Donald
About making something by would you care about for a little while then you'll recognize
I'm the only means you haven't ever getting Empower ever again
Angel f*** your
At this point Trump is going to pull a Grover Cleveland become the president and a Supreme Court Justice who f****** cares
Could happen so
January 6th Ashley Babbitt got shot
And
Obviously sad
She was not actual
We got a
Everything surrounding it
And then there's a
Unarmed
Who is she manison
Really
But she was freaking out
Military
So this new version of the Ashley Babbitt
What story comes from a Zero Hedge article
And it relies on footage that was shot by John Sullivan
It's not full of footage that wasn't available Alex
On January
One of his employees was standing next to John's elevator in the foyer
They are and ask
Tim to buy his footage from a
You see that on tape
Anyway it's a it's this footage and an interpretation that's provided by Taylor
Who course was the guy who burned a black lives matter flag with Owen Shroyer on the evening of January 10th
Talk about Ashley Babb it literally sent the exit at the Capitol Building cuz
Gaston Infowars of that
It's not the story that he's been telling up to this
This point in time to really think about how they wished it had gone that can really ride
Write it out new footage
It's not a new revelation
It's just new spin that the same right-wing s******* posing as independent journalist
We're trying to self take some
The heat off of fact their buddies got arrested for sedition
Just conspiracy
And it's
Boring
Boo
Man
It's
It's been awhile
Yeah you know the election
How's a few years ago
How's the whole year ago
You know like
You can't rewrite these things now
They're trying
That is a problem
How does a problem really give a stick
So I don't think not for a long time
Maybe just for long enough yeah
You know there'll be a little bit of a flash up
Little bit of a
Do you get a little bit of a charge out of it
She'll be gone by next week
Maui
So Rodger was there
In d.c.
Yeah and he gave a speech on the 5th
Some have said
Now granted some are rock
That it was a perfect
I don't know if anybody has said that
Yeah I gave us
Speech on the
January
Put it up on YouTube
It's gone
Because it was his.
Perfect
Swai
I didn't Advocate Lawless
Navigate
I did not Advocate that anyone
Anyone
About my
Between dark and Light
The Godly and the Godless by the way
Oh my God
Timer right to say that but they want to
You're right to say that
Why I'm spending all my money all my time
Raising money to pay lawyers I'm so sick
Lawyers
Normal life
Go to the store and buy a product
People don't understand the importance of Infowars as a beacon
A freedom and Truth over the last
5 years they don't understand it then Alex got to be pissed that Rodger said over the last 5 years
Ever since I showed up
Specifically a beacon of light and Truth
Before that who knows
I just never listen
You gave a great speech
Bigotry to
Calamities a weirdo
That is we were recalled from his last appearance
That was the most
Just like a child I've heard Rodger Stone sounds like in a long time just like
I did a great job
Admittedly
I did say that it was a struggle between good and evil but you know what that's not x-rayed advocating a fight
That's great that you're hurt your inside I Christian that's what it is
Yeah
My guy will say that the Rodger
Karaoke version of him that carries religion as a shield
Is not a fun Rodger
Rodger is a weirdo
The Libertines
That's a bit more of a fun Rodger
Who carries a shield of I'm so strange you can't really help
What are you what are you going to do I had an orgy the other night when am I going to be mad I'm a swinger and
No liar
Good luck making me care how can I see Nixon on my back
Morning I wake up while I'm brushing my teeth I'd take a look and I go well at least I'm not that far
This is like that's so much more of an interesting fun Rodger this is just sad
Post
F****** got caught
Fraud
But you should know that
Alex
Rodger
In the world
That's really why
I'm pretty sure Rodger was convicted of fraud
Billet retailers and that's why everybody is
Just trying to take them down
Why do they want to lock us up
Why do they want
Stone and Jones up because
Because the truth
He's always threatening to the no one is as hated as a truth-teller
Fun.com make a contribution
Go to the store right now and buy one of the great products
You can make a donation there's a donation but
I'm sick of being called
A grifter
Don't act like this.
Donate
Donate to store
The store I don't know why people call me a crypt
Yeah I mean like
I sympathize
I empathize
It sucks probably being called a group or booty call
Like one
People will call
Yeah I think it's just a result of action
Supposed to
I don't like it when people look at me accurately I would prefer to be shrouded in a Web of Lies
He has as I had for the majority
Yeah this Alex interviews a lawyer who's like against
Mandates
Seeing mandates
The and he pops up and promotes the interview General Flynn
But this is about where I emotionally
And yell about
Loser ass candidates
Make a bunch of
Give me body of a truth-teller
I'll even bring up Play-Doh
There's just nothing funnier than that like
String of give me money give me money
Chris
It's so unfair
The presumption that there's something like and giving him money that will make him
Not be called the grifters the future
Just the idea
That the last time I hear you come on
You are telling me that you need people to donate to your legal fun
So you can sue every
Everybody everybody everyone
Disappearance
Maybe is for the offense also
Call baby one way or the other but
Tonight he's not a grifter
Okay
Just cuz the story changes from moment to moment based upon what he thinks will mostly manipulate you enough into giving it money
He's trying to trick you into like believing
But he's going to get loser f****** candidates into office
You
As if you donating to Rodger
He's just as good as donating to their campaign
Because Rogers going to use it to help them
Zillow
He's at these candidates are getting
Exposure
So we come to the end of this and I don't know I think
I think this was
Strange episode because
Trying to prepare it while the rally and the Convoy were
Sort of ongoing was a little bit of a difficult thing cuz you didn't really know where anything was going to land in
You know it even as a recording this I still love like I said not
Not entirely sure
If things have ramped up when things will wrap up
FL escalator sldf
People are going to actually
Stay true to their word of
I'm going to stay here until Trudeau resign I mean if roughly 700,000 Canadians are suddenly going to
To become
Truckers in order to meet
The million required
I mean
I don't know if the the Licensing Bureau could handle it
Getting those. Physicals is going to be a bastard
Do you know that
That's what I'm telling you that's not even considering the neurological tests
They need to schedule
So I think we will see what happens but I will check back in
But this is this is where we're at
Booty back
Until then
Website
Sprite.com
Barrel run
And now here comes
Alex