Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them
Knowledge
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Exit
Alex Jones
Cindy we are Damned
My bright spot is
YouTube the
The Creator Temple
New video
That is a Bad sequel
Can part of a series about Tim pool
Australian
I think
Australia
Recommendation
Drop something on a giant piece of toast
See what happens
Create
These are really good that in depth
Analyses of like somebody's Minifigures I think what is really great about it is
Do we spend our time talking about Alex Jones
I have a peripheral awareness of people like Tim pool
And obviously we've looked
But not not with Eli granular detail
Videos that are about
Like Tim pool
Dave Rubin the three-part series on TV
I know I brought the
Couldn't remember which video it was that I
I think it was B project Veritas one
That I brought up in
In the past but this
This new one just came out
It's really good
It's very insightful about ivey-soto rhetorical technique
The temple uses to
What is really remarkable
This is pretty clear demonstration that a lot of it is
Essentially passing along Infowars narratives
Just with a
Rhetorical Style
That makes it more purchasable tattoo different audience
It's really good
How about you what's your braids
You know I've been taking this yoga class for a couple months now right
And my favorite part of it is
How
It's mainly like
Between 3 and 6 people
Every class
And it's usually the same people
Familiarity breeds contempt
And there's nothing I love you more prizes
Then s******* all over the
These other people in the yoga class and my partner done we walk out there
There's this one guy who is a
Suck up and a teacher's pet and it is
Hilarious to look at it
Adult man
I can do that it's so funny vines that hating on us Pacific
Person in the class makes you
More motivated to like
Do the class well
It's fun for me because I'm clearly the worst
There's ever been sure that yoga like I've got all these football and baseball injuries I sound like
Walking anchor tool
It's not
Yelling and yoga or not
Powerball
Yeah I found to be like one of the things I love the most
Austin College to like whenever I would
Free ClassDojo to someone to hate
It was just be like you f****** dick
The only way I could stay engaged glasses that really Cristobal
I will not be bested
It's going to be February 2nd 2022
20 days from the real
Triangle 2222 and then like several hundred years away from a Mitch Hedberg
Yes
So this episode
Little bit of a discussion of
Content warning
About it in a moment before
Just some new folks
Very much
Plebiscite
You know Steve
He's such an ass
Your apology
There's nothing left to burn you have to set yourself on fire
Thank you so much as?
The Woks of policy
Very much.
In order of the Ponyboy
Are you very much not going to like this
But
Thank you so much to Jordan's dislike of Pete Holmes is the range of caliban seeing his own face in the glass die
Thank you so much
You're now it's like
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
So take a little break now
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe the next few moments
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologize to the crew in the Lester Chester
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
So the effects of Alex's trip to the woods
I have worn off and he is no longer can do a bad mood
I mean not the same kind of bad mood
If there's going to be a bit
Disgusting and
You know just to give a Content warning in advance
There is a bit of
Discussion about Alex's
Feelings
Visa vie
Child abuse and I think some of the content
Some of the eclipse
In that portion
Yeah I may be difficult
Dear. Cuz they suck
This I have
Try to limit
Really the amount that we're going to actually listen
Listen to
In the interest of not just sort of like
Rolling it out of mud
But I do think that some of it is germane to the conversation that we need to have
About the episode as a whole
And honestly this is not an episode that
I just say forget it because
Spoiler alert Marjorie Taylor Greene
Of course this is
Something that people are very curious
But how that went down you have a sitting US Congress
This person
Text junk show
And you're also being very exploited about child abuse
It should carry with her as well
Yeah it's
It is a paint a larger picture that I think is important
Recognize
I would say
It's mostly the first hour of his show
That is this
Deterioration
Yeah
You know
There's going to be a bit of this
Episode
Most of the rest of it is
Not really
Let's eat our vegetables in get
Get this out of the way this is not eating vegetables
But we do have another context drop
Innocent
Play the song foxes Eagles
Apparently one
What language music
So if I understand correctly
If you get
Foxes
Eagle
Any kind of parrot
Kind of parrot
What is an oddly specific Trio
Brings to mind
Like a cartoon of Alex
Play The Mamas & the Papas it's like a cartoon with with Mickey Mouse
Steamboat
Yeah
Also I don't think he
What should
Don't look into The Mamas & the Papas
So here's our first clip and to actually it's covering some covid related news
So it's just
Fellowship
What a Time
To be alive
The wheels are absolutely coming off
Everything they're doing
John Hopkins
Group
What
And is the preeminent
Planner
We've all been under
And the subsequent
Verizon fraud
It's not covering its ass
By the very
Working group
It was heavily involved with Bill gay
Explaining all this
Coming out the 60 plus
Report
Add
The economic destruction of it is going to starve
What are first things to do everything Alex
Completely made up
None of that means anything
Including characterization of Johns Hopkins is equal to diverse scientific
Pick group
I've no idea what he's thinking it's a research University
The study is something that does exist but Alex is misreporting what it is
It's a meta-analysis that was carried out by researchers
At the Johns Hopkins Institute for Applied economics
Global health study of business Enterprise
That is to say that it wasn't producing any new information but was looking at a broad swath of
Of already existing
Studies
The vast majority of these studies they looked at weird people in the field of economics
As opposed to Public Health which is a little bit of a Cause
For concern
The reason I say that is because the goal is to look at the relationship
Between non-pharmaceutical interventions also
Referred to in the study as Lockdown
I Princeton
By closing businesses
That kind of thing and that
Kinship to the covid-19
And because these are economic
It's lost by researchers who approached that data from that perspective
Of Economics as opposed to
Epidemiology
A strict look at the numbers
This could show and approximately like
2% reduction in deaths
Front that they lockdown measures as is estimated in
Some of this study
These numbers just can't capture
Pans
Epidemiological studies may be able
Go to encapsulate some of their
Sure sure sure
It's because this meta-analysis is only looking at covid mortality
They can't say anything about the effect
These non-pharmaceutical in
Interventions
Reducing the spread of covid
Which would then have a trickle-down
Perfect
Even so there's a difference
Finding
Because it relates to
Did the studies that they included in this analysis
One area where there's a bit of complication was in looking
Effectiveness of specific
3 studies out of six
But include information about
The effective bar and restaurant closures
Reflected a reduction of over
28% in mortality
The numbers were 28.6
31 points
50.2
In those three study that is absurdly high
Now
The other three studies out of the six
It looked at these
Specifics of Bard street closures
Showed essentially no offense
Well that's absurd
But there is a reason why
A error is
All 20 turf
The same is true of the Dynamics of school closure studies with one of them showing a 58% reduction
I meant three other one
I'm showing no effect
So one of our big problems
2B it's really hard to even know how to begin measuring what it is we're looking
Looking for the answer to our question
There's some other points that I would bring up that I don't
Outfielder really addressed in this meta-analysis
Just do that I think they're kind of relevant
The first is that at least as it relates to the us we never really had a effect
Active lockdowns
Someplace and even went some businesses had to be closed for a brief window a lot of them
Stayed open anyway
There's a whole lot of people who are like
Gatherings of people were still happening even when
Ostensibly Gatherings were banned from public health concern
But of course
Happy mask assholes refusing to wear masks
Some yelling at folks waiting on them in public
The reality is that you
If you try to assess the effectiveness of any non-pharmaceutical interventions in terms
The pandemic
Your data is going to reflect essentially Aiden on application of lockdown measures
If the effective lockdown measures in the United States
Is actually only a small difference
Princeton what you'd expect
Without them
That might be because the measures themselves
We're only a small.
A lot of people took things very seriously and made real changes to how they went about their lives with respect
Public Health
Childish
But they felt the need to reflect
Sibley acted opposition to any public health guidance
Just because Defiance feels good to
There were really no consequences or any meaningful
Enforcement of lockdowns that would have changed
The second thing I would bring up is it different states in the United States responded with different Public Health measures
And these differences have an effect on others
Not like the borders have any real
Intrinsic meaning
Guns at the borders
There wasn't like interstate
Travel bans
That were in place order in Northern Ireland between Illinois and Indiana
This meta-analysis is largely concerned with data that was gathered regarding the first wave
Tenderly 2020
Bunch of states that didn't have any stay-at-home orders or lockdown orders at all
Arkansas iowa-nebraska
Dakota South Dakota Utah and Wyoming all didn't pass
Any order like
On the federal level
Trump didn't do anything that you would call a lockdown like his administration passed
Travel bans
They close government buildings in the CDC
A recommendation
Things are governors
To do yeah.
Yeah you know looking back on it
I don't think he did a good job. Really I'm going to go out on a limb and say that
All-in-all I think this analysis that's in this paper is useful
And it brings up some
Interesting points but I don't believe that it
It's ultimately can
Inclusive
Shows that non-pharmaceutical interventions were altogether in effect
Regardless of any of my feelings about the study
It's absolutely true that Alex is
Just lying about what it says
It almost certainly has
Reddit
He deceived the headline that sounds like something these
Now he's into being put out by a source that he's already established as evil in his storylines
Singapore tourism covering their asses by admitting that everything he's been saying has been true all along
Whole suicide point
If Alex is going to take this study is Gospel he's going to need to change his position on Mass
Set the study of the studies that they reviewed show date
21.2% reduction in deaths
In places where mask-wearing was mandated
Thankfully for Alexandra thinks he doesn't even know he has to pretend
Did not know that
I think probably the most effective
Steve non-farm
Pharmaceutical intervention
When was the
Billions of dollars of
Fox News propaganda that got us all killed
I would I'm not sure exactly MPI
I don't know if they will have the ability to capture that in their their their variables
DeWalt people covering their asses right now
The diverse group of scientists
Or whatever Reuters
Zillow
Reuters has come out and endorsed
Credible antiviral properties
Covering your dirty a hovering Reuters
Dirty asses that b*******
This was a headline in Reuters that was
Corrected
Because the original version was inaccurate
Additionally the headline was quote Japan
How us is an effective against Omicron in Phase 3 trial
This was incorrect and Reuters editor is definitely whiffed on this one because by the time the headline was fixed
Joe Rogan it already tweeted about it
Sienna
Vindication for his ex bulshit
Animated is it taken hold that Reuters was admitting
After all that Ivermectin works
Do it
You can tell here though if you're listening to Alex's realize the controversy
Be here and he's trying to claim victory using the corrected headline
Which is quote Ivermectin shows antiviral effects against covid Japan knees couple
But he says
This isn't news really
And it's not proof that Ivermectin
Ben works at all against
Covid in humans
If I'm being perfectly honest I don't even think this story is something that should have been posted by Reuters because
Not ready to go
From the article quotes
The company which has been working with Tokyo's
Otto University
I'm testing the drug is a potential treatment for covid-19
Did not provide further details
Provided about this company
Kawa and their Research into Ivermectin
But there's an unspecified antiviral effect
And I did they didn't say anything
That's not news worth
Maybe the prime opportunity to make an unforced error that can be
Exploited by aunt
Assholes
Which is exactly what happened with the
Is bad headline
There's a misleading nature about engaging with his story on a surface level as Alex does with every
It's entirely possible that did a study
And found that Ivermectin has an antiviral effective
Against covid in a test tube
These scientists have demonstrated that before with Ivermectin and even hydroxychloroquine
Many things can show affection a test tube that they do not have
In the human body
A lot of the times that we've seen these anti-vax people pretending not to be anti-vax get over invested in
Claiming the very
Various things are like covid treatments
It's usually because something shodhan
Defect in an in vitro study
And that may pretend that this effect must naturally apply to in VivoCity
Reuters completely f***** up here for no reason but the underlying reality is that Alex
The totally wrong about the
The story and Reuters is not trying to cover their dirty asses by coming out in favor of ivermectin
I just completely detached from reality and it's nothing more
When's of Alex's imagination.
Piggyback Joe Rogan
That is very frustrating
For real news are high
It's not like any
Single mistake
Could result in
Still further cementing of the pointlessness of mainstream media for Soma
Many people yeah
No big deal
I wonder
About like I said the necessity of even
Putting this article out in the
If it doesn't really seem like it
Even if
With the corrected headline I'm not certain
Cast of the public
Know if your editor is your editor reads
The main subject of the article did not provide further details
Then you have kill the story or make the article about how they did not provide further details and they f******
Right
You know the only thing that I can kind of see his like again it's a rig
Game because your report the story and then people like Alex adikavi say Ivermectin
Why aren't you reporting on this story about how Ivermectin
Proof of a cover-up
Just a just a dumb game these assholes black
You just don't need to make your own goals you know sure sure
Why is covering some dirty ass has some not so dirty asses
CNN
Is anybody cover in there
Queen Christine asses that's not specified
Getting in the ass cover
Jeff Zucker
Google
The America hating
AT&T
Yeah that sounds
Now resigned and they always use the phone
Cuz he was having
A relationship that was inappropriate
With somebody that works there
The other big crime it's men and women having sex and
It wasn't lying it wasn't
Overseeing the purse
This is interesting
We're seeing at the beginning of his shows Alex trying to do a Round-Up of news stories that he's used to paint a picture of that the enemies are in
Retreat
Johns Hopkins admit
Lockdowns are fraud writers is trying to get down with Ivermectin
Has fired Jeff sucker because
Alex got
Kicked off Twitter
The thought process is stupid but you can clearly see the feeling that he wants
The cell to the audience
I don't know exactly what's going on with this situation but even if you take the public-facing story of God
Gospel hits
For him to step
Chris Cuomo was fired recently and because the termination involved unethical Behavior there was an investigation
In the course of that investigation that came out that sucker had been having
An undisclosed romantic relationship
What's CNN's Executive Vice President and
And chief marketing
Dessert
The impropriety of that
He resigned
If the rate of the relationship is As on the up-and-up is zuker claims
The fact that he didn't disclose it is something that is
Outside with appropriate terms of business ethics
The president of a company being in a secret relationship with Executive Vice President and chief marketing officer
Is not
Best practices
There's a further air of ethical problems gear and it's something
You can see
Conspiracy theorists
Shooting out
And that is
Prior to being at CNN the woman whose sucker was in an under
Disclose relationship
Buy with Allison Gloucester
Was a communication
Director for Andrew Cuomo
Chris Cuomo's brother
Honestly mean nothing
But the appearance of it raises some questions
Disclosure of the relationship more disconcerting
Ultimately however it
Should be pointed out if you're going to talk about that kind of thing
Go ask was only with the Cuomo Administration for 4 months
A 2013
Nbcuniversal for over 15 years
Which incidentally was where sucker was
Prior to him heading to CNS
Clearly goes back a long distance
In terms of its
Professional level
And being being
Contemporary
It's a deep beat
Pass into the Cuomo Administration is more of a
But it does create in a few do I understand I'm just saying that it is a writer needs to add more character
Okay it seems kind of silly that there's only like 5 people in New York City and everybody works with the Cuomo's
I'm sick of this
There are more characters in this story
Yeah
Cuz I'm not sure exactly what's up here but I feel like the Cuomo connection is a bit too
Speculative to put
Too much stock
But it does obviously right question
Oh and the reported version of the story on its own is enough to Merit his resignation
Alex wants to make this about CNN punishing men and women for having sex
It's really more about breaches of professional app
Yeah I'm sure the tienen doesn't much care who has sex
Anybody else
As long as it's all above board
Serious liability and comp
Collective interest it does seem like this is very much alike
More like what are we doing
Like this is that that to me that's
My story that's what I'm reading here is like what were you guys
Get out of here
Stop this
That's it like it's not even I'm not even mad at them it's just like
No this is wrong get out of here
Sweet I want to get the broom and sweep them out of CNN yeah
Anything necessarily wrong with the president of a company
And Executive Vice President having a relationship
Considering they have work
Worked closely together for 20 years
We're both divorced
I don't see
Think there's anything wrong as long as you're upfront about it
Is that you should just be up for
Write about how you have to report those kinds of things
2hr if you're in middle management
And you're dating an employee or something or even
You're dating somebody who's on the same level as you and write company flowchart
You still need to report these things to HR
Because of
Pretend
Potential problems that they could real
It's it's
Very basic
Business ethics don't feel like you need that extra element I like I know I get the salacious
Elements of like they were f****** and also she worked for the Cuomo
Campaign
It's like there
F****** Chris is a media guy he's a media executive
Go to the same party
You know she have a history and Communications
Not if it's not that's why I'm saying that
Connection is too speculative
Right really put
Too much stock into if you ignore it it's
Feels like ignoring
Something that looks weird I'm just saying all these all these rich assholes in in New York
Politics all go to the same f****** parties they don't need like
A relationship with a whooping
Superior whatever you do
When
Something as obvious as like you need to report
These kinds of things
2hr trip when those things aren't followed
Create the appearance that they weren't followed for a reason exact and then people try to look for that reason
And that's why you follow them
In the first place
All these stories
And like
It's just like
Deleting up to you like a man the Whole New World Order
Falling apart
Wheels are coming off
The House of Cards is collapsing
The new world order is in
Deep
Trouble
They knew their system was going now
I knew it was a Ponzi scheme
Wanted to pose as the saviors
When their Ponzi scheme
So they wouldn't go to jail like Bernie Madoff
But instead
World leaders are standing up
In government
The clergy
What is common people on the street
City Council
School board meetings
Are calling
It out
The public is
Getting up to speed on the great reset the New World Order
Ric Flair
This clip
I see the note is in a we're totally winning type mood today which is fun is that means you high energy needs
Going to mope around like he doesn't mean we're already Dead episode not already
Yeah I'm not in the mood for that
Declaring that the New World Order is falling apart is a stupid move
For Alex because it makes it
Order for him to then claim their huge threat later on like a year or two down the road
That's not really a concern for our acceptances audiences
Completely forgotten and ignored how he's been telling them to New World Order is on the brink of collapse for like 20 years
Free
Who cares about people complaining at city council meeting
We already know from Alex's on reporting that the new world order as a
The plan B that they
Carry out a things look like their plans are falling apart
Which is releasing super bio weapons to kill everyone off
Based on houses on broadcast
There is no winning especially not by yelling
City Council meetings about the new world orders evil plans
If anything
That would seem like a good way to make them
Tympanic and release those super bio-weapon
Honestly if Alex believe a single word that came out of his own mouth
Van every moment he spent on air that wasn't about to
Keeping the audience at a grow their own food
And collect rainwater is
Is a f****** waste of time
Anyway Patriots are winning now which is a mood that I'm sure will pass before too long
Now it's go back to pretending that he never said that the new world order was crumbling their real serious threat
This means anything it's just the equivalent of a play-by-play guy on the radio describing at the
Sports game but he's a magic
Yeah I mean it does seem like if you know your enemies plan bees kill every
Then your most important
Job is to
Tired but you know that until you can neutralize the Kill Everybody
It's impossible to neutralized
The kill everyone strategy telling everybody about it what you got to do is lay low and
Very very aggressively
Try to promote
Two like-minded people
Ways in which they can create community
And the possibility of
Mitigating the damage
It's done
By the kill often that is inevitable
That would make sense
Right right
Or
Now cuz here's my here's my problem with
How do I go
I think you should interview Marjorie Taylor Greene
Obviously we know that
Plan B
Is the super violent
However there are winter storm
Slither going through
Texas and
Most of the South
Bad so that means that it's time
To really lay into
The prediction of a Cyber attack
Let me give you
The Big Kahuna am I talk about this
Getting chills up now
My spine
Because
My spirit
Klaus Schwab
5.0
What
Where's where's
Gideon
Genuine
How does
Going to be a giant
Terrorist
Covid look like
They're going to Cyber attack
Gosh
I can get away with it
And I think you're stupid
Maybe next week
Because why
The federal police forces
Have every major Western
I don't know what that is
I don't know
Prediction of next week is a meaningless predict
It's like death
An aneurysm
The rapture
They're all at any moment in time
Years back yeah friend
Convinced me to go see like a palm reader
Alright I remember the palm reader being like
Someone in your family will get sick
No
Dial.
I think so I assumed service
I don't know
I don't know what's customary
Get a haircut with the little bit different I paid
Because you know I agreed to it
Well another prediction with someone will die but they're old
Do you know Dan I can
Can see you
Just from your ear the way you're holding yourself right now that you're a closed-off person
But sometimes you're very good
Gregarious
Man
Has bats in Casey's winter storms that are heading to Austin and the surrounding air
Where is knockout the power like they did last year
Or in case another winter storm does the same in another city
He's pre-loading a
Conspiracy so we can make a narrative out of that predicted a false flag attack
Play guess what the bad guys are doing
Their power outages
All the time
From inclement weather
When I lived in Missouri they were like bad thunderstorms
The power go out periodically
Just this past week
Hundreds of thousands of people lost power in the Northeast due to winter storm Keenan
And to it y'all in advance
Storms coming to Texas governor Abbott is
Come out and said that power outages may happen
There's no shortage of things that Alex could try to portray as a cyber-attack should
You want to
Which is why this particular in
Sensitive to create a preemptive
Conspiracy narrative
Comes off as desk
Really train
No good
Yeah governor in charge of thing sorry dudes nothing we can do
So Alex gets to reading the headline of his own show
The live feed broadcast
Fascinated by this because
It's essentially all lies
Put on screen awake and alive show feed headline for today
Wheelchair because you are
The equation you are the resistance when you decide to share the broadcast it overrides the sensors
Get past big tackle
Get past
Wednesday live Reuters endorses Ivermectin
CNN Zucker resigns as World awakens
Fraud and murder
Marjorie Taylor Greene
He'll be joining Alex Jones live
On air
Don't mess
The most censored
Cast in the world
Atlantic continues on
Dealing with
Globalist
Look up to and how the world is away
Hopkins
Add confirm we already knew
Massive starvation to death
Suicide
From the virus
And I
Here for you today
The only thing like in the headline that I have
Woodsy is like
Being true is that Marjorie Taylor Greene is coming up
Time to tell me
That
75 million people died in the lockdown while I wasn't paying attention though he's saying that
Like a lot of those deaths are secretly
October
Alternative
That you're describing is
Pretty absurd
Yeah I guess the rest is all bulshit
Guest ahead
Live time
I hate putting her name in the
Show description
And the title of the broadcast
I think is a pretty
Clear piece of evidence that he's trying to troll for a
Yeah I think I think that is
It's very clearly part of his
Agenda I mean a sitting congressperson music
Definitely
If he's got a gut
We're going to know about it
It's something that you want to put out there on
Street right and then also you hope
The people will cover it
In order
Thoroughly
Signal booster
Right you let the my pillow guy paid a lie and bitching about things that didn't happen and now you got Marjorie tail
Taylor green you're going to talk about it
You know what if I respected Mike Lindell
This would
Actually do it but
I would respect him a little bit more if he forced Alex to let him
Do limericks that would be great
He was a fan like an old-school to antibiotics has a new kind of power classic
Classic throwback to the soap guy
I don't think you should do limericks he's got to come up with his own thing
Maybe haikus
I would make it
Mike Lindell
Enable.
Delivered love it
So here we go
We're about to get into the
Messi
Section of this
Where Alex
Gets into a story about a
.
Professor at the University of Fredonia
Who has made some
I would say
Troubling
Awful comments
And so here we go
You know this story just broke on
Twitter last night
And
Hipsters
Send me stuff
Watson Road about it
Early this morning
I see you're right Joe Rogan
And he sent me this
Our watching videos of the sky
They're six hours ahead of a show
678 hours later
Messages
Something
Complete
YouTube
I am.
Show me professor
It's a mistake
About pedophilia is being wrong
So
As we go through this
This is inspired by
Influence of Rogan
I mean if the circle is complete then somebody cut Alex Jones and half with a lights
Okay if we're going to complete the circle that f******
Hinduism the boomerang effect to Alex's misinformation
Theoretically radicalizing information
Analyze
And cover
So this is actually a rare instance where Alex has a narrative about pedophilia that
Actually not based on
The totally bizarre grotesque imaginary thing
Thanks right this is about the Suny Fredonia philosophy Professor Stephen Kirchner
Some comments that were
Definitely not great in a video that were making the rounds online
And the other night
I didn't watch the whole video but the
The clip that was posted all over
The place we see the pedophilia is good
You suggesting that it's quote
Not obvious to him why sex with a minor is wrong
This is splitting hairs on my part and I think it's very fair to say that the realm of conversation that he was getting in
Into was not appropriate
F***** up
I got a really heavy libertarian vibe off this guy
Singularly since one of the things he was talking about
A lot was the
The age of consent
Aspect
You hear a lot
From libertarian
Surprised to learn the kirchners on the editorial board of the journal reason paper
Which purports to be free of intellectual or philosophic
Contradiction
But also posts a whole lot of articles about weird libertarian concern
Like in the fall 2011
Issue with your personal wrote
Pieces for
There's an article titled quote
Howell libertarian might oppose same-sex marriage
What are the articles that he wrote
That issue
One of the articles that he wrote in that issue was titled quote
Extremely harsh treatment
Which was a Libertarian defensive
Torture hey great to get around the obvious philosophical objection
That someone would have as a Libertarian
None of this is an
Anyway to
Excuse kirshner's recent,
It's just to say that this is kind of standard behavior for libertarian
You can find plenty of memes online that are based just on the broad awareness that Libertarians are really weird
What about age of consent issues
If you look a little further into this guy's publishing
Career you'll find a 2007 paper he wrote for the lawn philosophy Journal titled quote
For discrimination against women
Where you might be able to guess that he argued
In favor of
Discrimination against women
Specifically in the context of admission
Medical and Business Schools
Probably going to hurt their brains
In 2020 he published another papers
Specifically arguing that coat
Philosophy departments at state universities may discount women's application
All those big Concepts like
It's okay to f*** children
In 2018 he took the time to write a whole ass paper on house
Specifically being attracted to Asian people quote
Is not wrong because it does not infringe on someone's moral right
How do you say this guy is just writing weird things about himself to the rest of us
And then Heidegger
Behind
Philosophy
In 2000
3 he wrote an article titled quote a liberal argument for slavery
The abstract of which starts like this
The slavery contract is not a rights violation since the right not to be enslaved and the right not to give out
How to benefit our waiverable
Conjunction of their voluntary waiver is not itself a rights violation
The case for the contract being put
Pejoratively exploitative
Is not clear
You are
Ruining
Words for me sir they're bad when they come out of your mouth this guy is a super annoying libertarian philosophy professor
Public publishing history closely
You'll even find that in 2001 he wrote a paper titled quote the moral status of harmless adult child sex
Wherein he argues about what you might guess from
The title
This is a position he posited for a while
Which doesn't mean the people shouldn't be offended or push back against it
It's just that he's a Libertarian if people not philosophical tradition have this conversation a lot
Yeah
He's been doing it
For twenty years sucks because this seems like one of those classic
You went
Viral for s*** that
People just didn't know was regularly comment in that
Rinat world
Like if you walked into any
If you want
How to do any shity bar where there was a Libertarian conversation happening
After three or four drinks eventually someone's going to be like
You know what I don't understand and then it's all s*** from there on out
I was looking at the issue of his journal
That techno that you wrote These articles in
Other reason papers and there was an article in it that was written by Walter block
Who's another libertarian professor
If you'd like
Fairly enjoyable
You can hear a couple of debates that he did with Sam Cedar
On the majority report
And this is you just come up with madterbate to of course it does they just
Can't get away from it it's weird cuz it's
Because
It's the most
Easily like attention-grabbing
And so when they do that they're like haha now you're forced
Engaged
In an emotional space
And your phone
Cuz they're stupid
The New York Post there's an article about this video
Pierce
To come from his appearance on this podcast called
The unregistered party
Which is hosted by
Which is actually incorrect but it's hard to tell that immediately
So I ended up looking into the unregistered podcast because I took
The New York Post
Assassin
A b word
That's the kind of
Right-leaning podcast of the most recent episode was
The evils of CR
With James Lindsay who was actually recently against on Rogan's podcast
Cast which is cool
Yeah you know if you want
Ncert it would make it a lot easier to get to slavery
Hey that's an interesting thought experiment
This interview with Kirchner on the unregistered podcast
What is from December 2020 and in the episode description
The most Renegade academic I've found
I went I tried to listen to this podcast to see if maybe the comments were taken out of context
And let me tell you they were not
If this was actually where was from
If anything the you know the short clips are a generous portrayal of this guy is views
More f***** up stuff in that full interview
But I'm not even going to play here to make
The point
Here's the thing that I wasn't
Listen to the spot
The Host
Thaddeus Russell is absolutely 100% in agreement with Kirchner
The two of them are lamenting how much grief they take from people because they insist on arguing
I've been having sex with minors as maybe actually a good thing
What's weird is
Is there are tons of tweet
It's an articles on right-wing blogs
For kershner's firing and turning him into a villain
Not that many you talking about Russell
And how the entire interview
To attempt it sound like
Veterans of the battle against
Consent laws shooting the ship telling War Stories
That's real weird
Some people are actually making that connection
He tweeted out
But he's not going to be teaching a CRT class with Russell now this is come out
The connection
It's so weird like
All of the outrage
About
This
Clip
Of course
Has been attached
This interview that he did on the unregistered podcast
But if you go listen to my podcast
He is talking
Very in-depth about the same issue real
Bad so yeah it's all a mess
Even weirder is that just be
Before the conversation
This stuff on their podcast
Russell is doing a breeds for headspace
Nsibidi sponsor
An article in The Daily Beast in 2009 about how baby Roman Polanski wasn't so wrong
Do headspace on the CBD company want to throw their support
Anyway also the you're going to hate this but one of his
First guest was Conor friedersdorf
I I mean
You know I hate I love
I love
How
These guys are such Renegade professors
Who have been saying the same b******* about
F***** up the age of consent laws exist
4:30 twenty-odd years or whatever has been on this beat since 2001 at least from his publishing history this
This guy wrote about the plants Keisha 2009 time are they like
Did you know that some innocent ass
English Professor somewhere was like
Israel's probably an apartheid state and then was fired for no reason
So I went
Down this path look at their unread
Broadcast because that's where
New York Post had led me to believe this was wrong
Turns out that is inaccurate
The actual source
Yeah
Natural source for this interview with a video on a YouTube channel called brain of that which as of the time of preparing the
Episode
That video itself has under 3700 reviews
And this is an outlier
In terms of it being a very high number of views videos on this channel
Brain in a vat
It'd be very difficult to
Stumble across
Whereas
The interview like the unregistered podcast is a much more
Popular
And So within easier Google search
Yeah it's a
Very strange and I don't understand
Foley
How
This
Outrage cycle happened
Why almost nobody
Watch this video to be different
Care
What is this
Shouldn't be a big deal for us
Right now
You know what I'm saying it's a big deal because Alex is making it a big deal
Comments are f***** up and went bad
I also think
That there with
In the realm of what you hear from
Libertarians
Watch the whole thing mostly because Kirchner was just saying the same stuff he said in the other end of
Review that I did waste my time listening to
The host of this one
The seeming to be as enthusiastic in their agreement with him
Or even necessarily
Showing agreement with him
From the stuff I saw but I don't I don't know if
At some point they do
Anyway there's a Libertarian philosophy Professor doing stuff it's not
MC libertarian philosophy
Professor getting in
Even though he published an article on this topic
Chicken 2001
It seems like a bit of a pattern of being willing to expound on the issues on podcast
Public appearances
They published
The whole book about in 2015
Apparently Suny Fredonia had no I
Idea about his opinion
And released a statement that his views are reprehensible and they quote the matter is under review
It's fine that the matter is under review but if
If you're going to enact any punishment on Kirchner about this
Probably also do some real serious fact-finding about how you could have missed this
Very often
Bsview that he has
A debt has been making extremely public for the last 20 years
I've had him on the year the payroll at this is reprehensible to you
Yeah it does seem like you guys really dropped the ball on that one
Considering it
Supposedly your job
To make sure that
They continued
You publishing
Yo
Yes it's really
It's really strange
Like the comments
Are obviously
Bad
And there are
Knock knock
Yeah
Acceptable relay
I don't think
And if he's a philosophy
Professor
Think it's stopping short of encouraging
Or saying these things are good
But I'm guessing he does a lot of Greek philosophy and
Glass
I think you'd appreciate the Socratic method
From what I understand
It's really
Springleaf
Locked up
Time Alex
Does not deal with this
In terms of the reality of these combat
He takes it in a completely other direction
And actually even misrepresents
The
Nature of what is being said
Say that again
Sex with one-year-olds
He's good
Yes it's good
I need a bunch of other professors agree with him
They all look
He looks like one
Else can't deal with these kind of
Objects with any kind of
Seriousness
I'm not going to get too deep into the weeds and I'm not investing any energy in defending kirchner's comments but Alex's mystery
Representing
Christian was talking about alleged reports in quote
Some cultures
News of grandmother is fellating children
Calm them down when they're calling
He says that he doesn't know if these reports are true or if it's an effective treatment but
If those things
Were true
He doesn't understand what would be wrong about that ax
Messed up
I don't agree with Kirchner I think it's a bad line of inquiry to go down
But also
Alex is not dealing with what he's actually saying it's
Yeah a mess
Yeah yeah I mean here's here's what I would
Say
To that art
Why and go away
Just just
Why why are you not busy
You got something else to do that other than make that argument
You know you could
Put together phone
I think that there is a strain of contrarian this within the libertarian philosophy
An obsession with these rigid ideas about self ownership and what have you and
I think that they are a bad combination
It would be nice if there was a strain of birdhouse building
In libertarian
Do you know like instead of this contrarian ISM that makes everybody pissed off and annoyed
Go build a birdhouse
OB good use of time
Topix
His feelings
About
Abuse towards
And
That's partially because
He doesn't actually know what the
The story is
Brock Lesnar
Look into it all
He can't really
Talk about it with any
Dap
That's so he needs to just use it as a launching pad for him
To do his normal bulshit
Right
Here here is something that is fairly innocuous in terms of
Not being disgusting sure
Most the people you see now you notice they don't have children that you you had because the majority of you you
Victimizers
So the eu's executive branch is known as the European Commission
Which includes 27 members
The current president is Ursula Von der leyen who has seven children
There are three Executive Vice President
France has four children
Marcus has three children
Haley third of all this
Doberman
Therefore vice-presidents
Marcos
Seth Kovach
Has three children
Vera's Jehovah has to
Dubravka suica has one
And margaritas shooting a size 2
So almost all of these people have kids
Is just completely made up from his imagination
It would make
You leadership wouldn't have children if they were intent on breaking up the family and destroying everything
And that's it must
We proved that they don't have kids
Even if almost all of them
No no
What you do is you have a
Predetermined conclusion and then work back
From the bike by making things up
Because of the reality doesn't
Gofit the predetermined conclusion and it feels better if you're right
Overly generous Alex and pretend that he met the heads of
The countries that are members of the EU
But even then things go
Get dumb really fast
27 member states of the EU and here's a rapid-fire of the country and the number of kids
Austria to kids
Belgium to kids Bulgaria to kids
Croatia to kids Cypress
Czech Republic to kids
I'm not liking this
Finland three kids
No kids
Grease one kid
For kids
That's the present
But if you want to talk about the Prime Minister Viktor Orban
Yeah
Ireland
For kids
Italy three kids
Latvia to kids little kids
Luxembourg
No kids
But they have their head of state is gay and needs
Just got married in 2015
Multa three kids
Netherlands
None
One more example
Poland
Kid Portugal
Romania no kids
Oh my God
Slovakia
Two kids Slovenia one kid
Did Sweden
That was excessive and I apologize for putting you through that but I did
Decide to not
No shot there I think it's important detail to really
Make sure that the picture
Is clear that there is no basis for the things that Alex says
He just makes up things that make his narrative see more persuasive or feel right to him in the moment and then he asserts the
Summit facts
And not just packed but actually proof of a larger
Conspiracy that he's trying to sell his audience
It's important to understand this dynamic because it's not a behavior that uses sparingly
And it was already
Approached his claims of even
Basic level of scrutiny a lot of them would clap
Apps haven't been shown to just be stuff that he's making up
And he's engaging with a topic
Is sensitive and serious is child sexual abuse with the level of disrespect in a responsibility these showing here
Which it really disqualify him
As a person need to take seriously about it
Yeah and it shouldn't even take you
U2 seconds
To be like will that do
Doesn't make any sense
Look at our presidents look at our f****** elect
Good leaders.
Most of them
The vast majority of them and absurd majority of them
Children in the RN a nuclear and style family
Because we associate that right or wrong
With a more
Stable thought process
That's what we've always done
That's how it goes of course in
Other Nation right
They would do the same
Here's what's going on I'm going to give you a let you in on a secret
Alex's just imagining Emmanuel macron
And then he's universalizing the fact that macron it doesn't have any kids
Come out everybody
I would like basically what's going on how many members
Not I'm not going to ask for
Cuz that would there's no chance there
How many heads of state
Cody name
In the EU
Like honestly
Let me look at this list as number one answer would be Boris Johnson
And they're not in the fuc
Can eat you
I think
He could go for a macaron
Haha
Probably Orban
Maybe well he would
I mean he's that's his
That's his only friend
In the EU even know if he would remember his name though too I like that guy at hungry who hates Soros
The guy who's strong and powerful I'm looking at this list
And I don't think I've heard Alexei any of these other names may be a Duda in Poland
Yes the white nationalism Association
I don't know that I don't think he knows his name either and it's hard to remember it's dude
Dude I do that
So Alex
He takes
Some
Sidetracks
In terms of talking about
This
Larger story
About abuse against children
And two other things like
I don't know
Covid vaccine
Main and I program confirmed
Hundred percent increase in heart attacks
Multi thousand percent increases in
Neurological disorders
It just goes on and on
Months ago
With the first
We talked about it yes
Saturday
White from the hospital
And of course that's exactly what the FDA new and the CDC back
October 2020 before the single injection was given
They knew exactly what it
Screen
CNN
The other pedophile
Pieces
Did you discredited disinformation
Never show you
What
Talking about like
They lie to you they're lying about Alex lying we tell you what this information we're giving you
From Senator Ron Johnson recent panel on covid
Singing side effects
What are the reports has presented chodes
Surprisingly High rates of serious side effects
This at this was presented by an attorney named Thomas rent
Who's claiming that he got this information
In from defense
Medical epi
MattyB ology database
Which was provided him by three alleged whistleblower
The thrust of this data was the conditions like cancer miscarriages and neurological issues were
Wayup compared the data from years prior
The vaccine being rolled out
The problem however was it rented
Release date
Into a thorough job
The lead stories reached out to.
Comment and their spokesperson major Charlie beats said that they run a review on their database
And found that the database covering the years of 2000
Team to 2020
Quote represented only a small fraction of the actual medical diagnosis for those gears
In contrast the 2021 total number of medical diagnosis were up
Seems like we got a lot of information from major.
Sdib
Got2b
I got you
I feel like at this point I'm doing that because that's fun
Like like strong-arming you like
I feel like I'm leaning into that and it's
Ruth b still enjoy it
They were able to determine
This
Differentiation
I have the the the only being a small fraction
End of the actual diagnosis
Because they are able to compare data sets from the defense medical epidemiology database
And the defense
What's medical surveillance
It turns out that the latter has full information
But Thomas rims
This guy got numbers from the prior
So he happy incomplete data set
Who created the appearance
That there were Sharp
Increases this year
When that's actually just the result of the dataset being a
Incomplete
Anyway Alex is lying about this and the thing about him them knowing about side effects prior to the next rolling I was just for PowerPoint
My presentation is made up a story about
I think In that clip though what's valuable is he can see an important dynamic
Alex says that this comes from. Numbers and specifically says that it's
It's not from there
He constantly reports on bulshit that
Steve purses paddling from misusing
A data
But now that Alex feels like he's got a stronger source to use
He builds up that Source biking
Comparing it favorably to Vance
Yeah he traded up
It's me that Alex has at least a
Something of a keen awareness of the stuff based on numbers
Was always bulshit
But he used
Because it was the only option he had in order to make his narratives work
Work and sensationalize
I feel like this is a very similar Dynamic that Alex has to Wendy report stories and says
It's in the mainstream news
There's an unspoken second part of that sentence
Which he speaks in the case of this clip hear about fairs
But if it's too close to home in the case of the mainstream news thing
Because
Full fought there is actually
It's in the mainstream news
Not on our dumb site that no one should take seriously
Which
Disease is more reliable and parentheses
Yeah it's not in actual paper
Parentheses
A little bit
So he mentioned vampire
Psychic
Well yeah I supposed to ones that are nailed into their home
He doesn't get into the Chinese covid-19 virus
But he's started
Think about psychics
Vampires
Time.
F****** call this professor a Renfield
There we go
Call disguiser Winfield type
Royalty from the Carpathian Mountains
If they all knew that
Romanian Hungarian
Alex is trying to suggest I guess the Bram Stoker
Ahsoka wrote the Dracula about the saxe-coburg-gotha
So here's the problem
British royalty being connect
To the saxe-coburg-gotha line didn't begin until Edwards
The 7th
Who is the son of Queen Victoria and Prince Albert of the saxe-coburg
Bird family
Would begin his time as monarch
In 1901
Conversely Dracula the Bram Stoker book
Was published in 1897
And had been a project you've been working on for the better part of
A decade
Largely because his study of Transylvanian folklore that in
Informed the novel
Romanian cultural feature of a creature called the
Stoker's version of Dracula is based
Likely with a bit of loud the Impaler thrown in for good measure
As many have speculated
Again this is an instance of Alex just making up a story about the little pieces of trivia that he thinks are connected
Really
Except for his imagination
He's a liar who can
Stop himself from just making things up if that's
Easier for him
In terms of being able to present himself like he knows every
Also Alex ends up going on a Meandering
Interpretation of the plot of the movie Dracula
Instead of getting
I think the 1992
I don't know I haven't seen all of the Dracula Canon
But I would assume it's that way
I don't think it's Nosferatu
Although that one would be fun
The point about the presser cuz he doesn't want to cover that story
I think it's because he doesn't have anything to say about the story except to connect
The ramblings about
Renfield's and Dracula's
Do y'all about it
His birthday
Tickler picadillos
Yeah there's only one Dracula and that's Leslie Nielsen
Sure
I was going to say bubba hotel has more Mommy
So anyway here is where we get
That I would actually say are particularly
Just got f*****
So skip ahead if you don't want to hear
2 clip
Suppressed 30 seconds
It might be a little more than that but
This ain't this ain't good
He's just talking about how it's good for a man
Shut up
Schools are teaching kids America sucks and the schools are teaching kids that can be another gender
Is a war on Humanity
.
I have no idea of Kirchner have kids or is married and neither does Alex
This clip is disgusting but it also has fairly Illuminating in terms of one of Alex's more Insidious rhetoric
Tactics
He gets all worked up yelling about this one story that he's a very shallow grass pond
Eddie's building up this energy
He pivots to
Completely unrelated set of topics
And he carries that same energy
Dover
Which is meant to allow the audience
Needs to make an emotion
No connection between these unrelated narratives
He builds up his anger and hatred for Kirchner and anger it is extremely nationalism
He's very bigoted views about trans people
This is an intentional move on his part because
He wants the audience to associate that feeling
He's trying to create them about the Christmas Story 2
Do all of his perceived enemies
His strategy is one part emotional manipulation and one part that he really can't
Do anything else
He's not capable of covering any story with any real depth so
There isn't really another option for him than renting wildly and
Pretending everything he's talking about his connect
But of course there's another thing he's trying
To use this energy
Before and you can
See it in this also very disgusting clip
It comes just after the last one we heard
He's off
Until they all go to prison
Major Payne
Repeat itself again and these people coming after me cuz they know I know who they are that's why we need money to fight
These monsters
Rodger
Dot-com
Arizona sales going on
Over there
You can see the way that this
This strategy
It works
I'm take
Money away from
People who fight PETA
There is
A conversation that somebody could
Could very easily have
About
The dis
Taste
Amanda
Approval
Of the comments
The cursed mermaid in that
Energy
I don't disagree with Alex taking issue with them
I do take issue with his inability to engage
With
The actual story
His clear not awareness
Surrounding it except
For that he's supposed to
Get mad about it cuz Joe Rogan told him about it the night before
And Hughes
Use of it
Specifically only
To create passion surrounding his other issues that he's either really
Really invested in
+ 2
Make it
Compelling emotional argument for people to give him money
Yeah I think that this is just disgusting
I mean it
It's it's
888sport
Because
If you
Saw somebody setting up like a f****** 8
Charity
And saying please donate so I can fight
Horrific disease of AIDS
And then you found out that all they did
What's f*** all and make their own f****** radio show better
BBC Aureus with that person
He is saying that he's doing something
A couple years back when that there was that episode with Craig saw man Sawyer
Yeah that was even more direct
Ali-A
Fraud
Yeah
Maybe the
More distasteful
Clips
I have passed
Unless of course you consider listening to Marjorie Taylor Greene
Specifically the states.
I meant there's still a Content warning in at waist
Here's just another clip of Alex's sales pitch
Before we get to her
We can build our war chest to build our infrastructure
Prayer and your word of mouth
Never Back Down
That's so fake
It's a really interesting way to do an abusive that
Alex is basically saying that he fails it's only because the audience
Didn't support him a topic give him enough money
It's a perfect way for a narcissist to relate to the world nothing can be his fault
Just gross
Man gets even worse you realize that he's saying that he's fighting
Pedophiles
And then he's going to take that money and use it
To avoid giving the parents of Sandy Hook
Victims money
You know like
This is f***** up
When I get now you're working out to Cypress Creek calling pigs evil
Morally bankrupt Auto in a in a way
That would really
F****** up
For the rest of my life if I did one thing
In this chain of events
I would spend the rest of my life like a confession
Well Alex
I guess he has a much closer relations
Chip tha God than you do in Auto forgive probably true
My phone had one of those
Is auto forgive
This is this segment is over and now Alex
Welcoming Marjorie Taylor Greene to the show
And
The introduction and I think is a little bit self-serving
On Alex's bar
A lot of new people have gotten into Congress
Republic of them the most informative and interesting and brave
It's got to be Marjorie Taylor Greene
I really appreciate it
Because you know
CNN MSNBC
People should interview her
She should be banned and she has been
Oh you shouldn't talk to Alex Jones either we should all
Be scared of each other as Nationalist and as Pop
We're not
CNN on average has 100,000 viewers Joe Rogan
More than 20
They're a joke the people have spoke
They want freedom
I thought you were trying to introduce your
Weird
I mean
Then why are you mad
Why are you mad that
CNN won't have you on they've only got 100,000 potatoes
Talk at all about what CNN's says instead of
Constantly harping about how it's the worst thing that ever happened to you
Like I've heard this from some of our listeners before and I kind of feel similarly
If it weren't for Alex I have no idea who Brian stelter wife
These elevated these people
It's a yeah it's a strange strategy
It kind of makes me think of
Things are true
So Marjorie comes in and
Bad off
Thanks so much for having me on Alexander to be here
I'm a big fan of yours as well
Where do you want start
Maybe the state of the country
Things are going
That's a bad start that she's a big fan of Alex
Wow I've never heard her speak before I've off
I never heard Trump talk for like 3 years ago
Awful
Who voted for
Stop it some people in Georgia apparently
She's she's pretty adept
Using the buzzwords and what have you and primary season
Some thoughts on that
It's the Republican rhinos who walk in talking
Till I guess
And then they do different things behind closed doors that went the way they vote and legislate
And the people they take money from
And unfortunately does Republicans have joined with the Democrats and
That's been happening for a really long time
They serve the globalist agenda and as a matter of fact today I'm waiting to have to go a boat here in just a little bit
Against
Compete
And that's what Nancy Pelosi is bringing to the house floor today she's working on getting that done
Amendments
Republican amendments to change it in This Is Us
So-called bill that supposed to go against China
And helped America to compete
The all honesty the truth is that serves the climate changed
Radical agenda and served
China first in America last
And it's all build back better and green new deal just Rewritten
Something that she lies and calls
America competes
So it's the Same Song & Dance
But it's Mitch McConnell and
And the Lindsey Graham's and many Republicans here that have allowed these things to happen to our country
And this is my primary season
This is why
Everyone needs to get involved and we have to make sure that we send the right people to Congress
People like me people who are willing to fight
Because we have to
Save our country and
It's in a bad place right now
Melange of meaningless words
Primary season
I think she should be worried
She won the GOP Primary in 2020 in a runoff election
Then against the person who came in second in the original vote John Cowan
Interesting Lee in the runoff
Marjorie Taylor Greene got almost the eggs
Exact same number of votes
I bet she did in the original
She got the crazy
In the election
Other runoff she got 43,000
13 votes
In the original like
She got 43,000
Russia lost
89 or 79 rotors what did you do to piss them off
Meanwhile John Cowan earned just over a 10,000 additional votes in the runoff
Which strongly suggests that Marjorie Taylor Greene has a very firm ceiling to her popularity at least as it relates
The primary
As for the general election she was probably going to win that no matter what
Georgia 14th District is a republican Plus
27th District
But she was also essentially running unopposed after the Democratic candidate Kevin
Vanoss adult
Are officially withdrew from the race fire
The election
The fact that it's a district that swings heavily to the GOP
Actually know it might be helpful in the general but it's
Snow good for greeting in the primary
She's facing for challengers in the GOP Primary this year
A couple of them stand possibly draw votes Away by appealing to the public as a person who has the same kind of America first
Politics
But without the baggage of greens past associations with qanon and some of the liabilities
She has to be taken seriously like
Going on f****** Infowars
That one would be a big
There's another potential problem
But you has though
And that's that's a registered Democrats
Vote in the GOP Primary in Georgia
If enough Democratic voters decided to
The Pont on the Democratic primary and instead vote in the GOP Primary
They can essentially sink breathe
Candidacy
I don't have much faith that anyone would be able to pull off this sort of organization or anything but
If public sentiment were strongly opposed to her enough
The Democratic Party
Could essentially choose between GOP Primary candidates
Inevitably end up winning in
The General
GOP plus 2017 has almost no chance that the Democratic candidate
It is going to win the general
And Marjorie Taylor Greene is akam
Leave lunatic
Take a poster
The threat to having a
Functioning government
So it might not be the worst electoral strategy
GT use the votes
The do exist to make sure the
But she can't make it
Get to the general for fucksake based on her previous actions in Congress she's a danger to the lives of
Other Congress people
I I feel like you might be mixing her and Lauren boebert
She's gone right up into people's faces you don't have prior to being in Congress she did say that Nancy Pelosi should be
There was there was that
She has made it very clear that she would prefer the deaths of her colleagues to I guess
Regular Legends
Yeah I see
Think that there could be a really interesting movement that Democrats in Georgia could attempt
Yeah I think that it would be highly controversial
Hilarious
Sure they would be real mad
What are the inherent problems of it would have to be that everyone would have to
Probably get
Behind the same GOP candidate
Right and I think that could be
Have fun with it
No Big Ten Network that she might still win
How many
Candidates are there
There's she has four competitors competitors and automakers
With a total of
What like
Less than 100,000 votes
Obvious
Yammy primary voting is usually lower
I think they could probably get just about anybody they wanted in
And then they would waste leave Georgia legislators time having to go back and be like fine
We can't allow Democrats to vote in primaries
Open primary
It's the same sort of thing because nothing in the rules that says the horse can't play football
Absolutely an air bugs
Situation
So apparently
Green
Kick-off Twitter recently what she is
F****** pumped
Devout
What is about you
Business woman that you've been successful that you're loyal the country
Yes absolutely but I don't
And I refused doing and saying the things that I'm doing
Just kicks
Joining you and so many others that have been kicked
That hateful evil left
Verizon and basically controls politics
Messaging in the media
And I'm so happy I got kicked
You really are the greatest Americans
Again just trying to
Pretend Vape to
Self-imposed
Yahara persecution complex
Does the same thing as
Virtue
Is an empty psychopath this is a terrifying
She can wear like getting kicked off Twitter as a badge of honor because Twitter such a gross Dan of
Leftist garbage or whatever
Really raises the question of why she was ever there in the first place
That's kind of obvious it
Because it's the biggest platform of its kind
Choose able to post
Inflammatory things there to raise donations and
Data retention
She never left
Because walking
Just up to the line of getting kicked off Twitter
Is in the central part of her business
This plan
And now that it's half of the only real move for her in order to maintain her brand is to do exactly this
Steph you actually hated Twitter
You're proud to be kicked off that's the ticket
Their lesson with Laura Loomer about what happens when you complain about getting
Ticked off if you look
You look real weak
Yeah and they don't like that trying to the Handcuff yourself to Twitter's door and like
You need to you need to have this defiant attitude as opposed to like
Walk like it's finally time they got me they got rid of it you know like that hole
Be thankful for the time but you were able to
Griffin attention that donation has the friends you made along the way
Don't be sad because dog be happy because you had that time on Twitter
Soolantra
So green has some interesting thoughts
And by that I mean
Does not interest
Thoughts but similar thoughts to Alex
About that covid
Pure evil in and what's even worse is
How the FDA has said that you
People can't doctors can't prescribe
Ivermectin
Now they're saying monoclonal antibodies can't be used
Against covid-19 because they're saying it doesn't work against
An indoor forcing math children an acrostic in on people across the world I mean this is truly mental ill
Wearing a mask today after two years of this Chinese virus that is in
This man-made Chinese virus at dr. fauci
People still wearing mask I mean it's truly mentally ill we know the masks don't work
And the vaccines.
She's in Congress
Also I study that Alex reported on earlier disagrees with her statement that Matt's
Is that the show
Guess who's in Congress
Wow
Just
Just wow
An absolute raving nut
Imagine
This is the thing that blows my my
Sometimes whenever I stop
To back off about how this is
Is the culture war and how everybody just
Digs in for no f****** reason on s*** why is everybody standing Ivermectin so
Hard
I get the Trump did it so you don't want him to look bad but we're past it that's because it's go away.
No because it's an essential argument
Of why the vaccine is unnecessary
Painting a chemical guy
Well here's the thing the argument goes
Basically like this
There is no reason
To have given emerge
The authorization
To this vaccine
And they have to hold onto the idea that Ivermectin worked or else your argument Falls
The part that there was actually caused
Do the bikes
I am so in order to not have to let that domino fall and their entire anti-vax argument
Starts to crumble around it
I have to hold onto this
Nonsense long past it
Expiration
I suppose
So a sweet Navaira make
Green likes it
And handsome
Dangerous ideas
But I think that people really have blood on their hands
Stop.
The prescriptions of ivermectin refuse people who have had
Family members in the hospital not being able to take Ivermectin
Or any other kind of life
Play Saving treatment
I mean I truly think that we need to investigate all these people are investigating the deaths that are reported on the bear system
And hold people accountable
Because it's
Dr. fauci and anyone at the CDC or anyone involved
Life-saving treatments and Therapies
Can people died why think they're guilty of murder
You're absolutely right
This is a really dangerous line for green to be suggesting and for Alex to be agreeing with
And I don't mean that it's societally dangerous I mean standards for them
Her belief is that people who stopped life-saving therapy
Tribute chart
With murder but
If that's carried to its logical conclusion she better hope
Let no one ever proved that the vaccine is a life-saving
Unfortunately that's been overwhelmingly documented whereas the proof of
Yeah her b******* about Ivermectin
Wow so we've got all of Infowars
Fox News and Joe Rogan all of them on the hook for murder
Murder one at least using her logic it would be
Very easy to construct an argument that if people who refuse the vaccine because their elected leaders or demagogues like Alex
Told them it was dangerous and blocked
Kill everyone
They died of covid then
Alex our green should be charged with murder
It's premeditated and it's for money that's
Man these people are serial killers were bounty
It's not like fauci was physically slapping Ivermectin out of people's hands it was just recommendations that the CDC gay
You can still get Ivermectin there's a little industry that popped up of doctors online who prescribed it for you and Alex's
I have them on his gas
Similarly alexandrine Ark forcing anyone to not get the vax
There's giving medical advice
I am puking
Straight to this medical advice contributed to someone dying from covid by their own standards
They should be charged with murder
I guess all they would take is finding someone who died and was a fan of Alex
There's one guy named Doug
Kuzma
The Conspiracy Theory podcast who died of covid in early January
After likely catching it at the reawakened America rally in Dallas in mid-December which Alex actually spoke
His Facebook is
Look anymore but I wouldn't be too surprised to see some Infowars repost
Alex narratives by covid flying around
Wow examples but I really care to pursue this any further
It's just relevant to recognize that the standard that these people like alexandrine or setting about their imaginary complaints about fauci
If apply to themselves would lead to them
Being sent to jail for a very long time
They're f****** stupid
All right I think
Made it very clear
That's
You and I need to stop recording right now and go perform a citizen's arrest on Alex Jones for the crime of murder
Knock knock
If I did do that I would arrest him in his voice I would have to do that
To make him even more Angry on the right to remain silent talk to me like that
So
Alice is interviewing.
Little bit of tension
But you might have to go give a vote
It could be again
She's in Concord
That's real real bummer.
So she discusses this vote that she's going to have to take
Asthmatic
Conversation
Phyllis compete Bill she was telling me ears
The whole leftist agenda
Better
Well this is the bill that Nancy Pelosi is pushing to the floor and I'm going to show you guys
Can be hard for you to say but this is the bill
It's approximately 3,000 pages
And it's
It's unbelievable they gave it to us on Monday as if we're supposed to be able to read it
And then vote on it likely
Possibly today maybe tomorrow
And it shouldn't operate this way it's filled with complete garbage
Everything in there totally it hurts our country
Aoc's climate change Green New Deal agenda
Billion dollars for climate change
It gets billions of dollars to the UN it gets all of this money away but does nothing for our Chi
And get this
It only mentions the word
Sentinelone
From the CCP is what's killing our young people every single day at work
Nancy Pelosi for you
For one thing it is difficult to read long bills but like you scream
That's part of the job
It's why you representative
If I can help out with that and honestly she sounds like someone who's like you gave me too much homework
The possible to read this book
In this case it shouldn't be that big of an ask because this isn't really a new bill
A version of it passed the Senate last July by a 68-32 vote which means
Support
This is something that is some kind of like a socialist
What's the fantasy Bill like she seems to be pretending
It's really weird that Bernie Sanders voted against
But I guess Marjorie probably no
Yeah yeah
Bernie complained about not being able to read it
No I'm pretty sure he was like I can't vote for this because I've never worked in government before a lot of points
She's making or just stupid
The premise that spending money on various places and investing in things like the UN does nothing for our country
I just think that's obviously incorrect.
You don't even need to
That's not a narc
The Senate version of this bill
Also
It had sent it said fentanyl 17 times they removed 16 mentions of Fentanyl
Maybe maybe when the bills are Rekha
Cancel that number I'll get bumped up a little bit
Also in the interest of like this
Just complete fairness
Steve version of the bill in the
The house that came out of the rules committee
Use the word Fentanyl
10 *
According to
To dream all right here's what I'm saying
They have to put
Fentanyl 8 times
Into the reconciled Bill Plus
Just kneel
One point
Play + 8.5
And a paragraph about how great Alex's character Fentanyl
I like that one
But in reality this bill seeks to do a lot of things
Things that that in terms of lip service Alex's in favor of
Like supporting Manufacturing in the United States
Particularly in the area of
Ultimately though its government spending
And the leader is he seems to respect if somehow crafted very strong opinions on the bill without reading it
So it's got to be evil and must be stopped
This is baby politics
Yeah this is
This is really really sad is really sad
It's odd it would be nice to live in like the
Early 1800s
You know
Before you knew how to read
You couldn't pay attention you didn't know what
The government was doing so you couldn't immediately be like oh well obviously
I with my third grade education
I'm more qualified to work in
Can the government than most of the people there
But here you and I
I've almost got it I've almost got a college degree and that lady
Should be out of Congress by Fred
It's troubling
So like I said
Earlier in the episode
I felt like
This is obviously trolling
On a certain level green on
Not necessarily the entire interview but there were going to be parts
That were trouble
And I think that this is one of the
Do you know I like to see you as this
Speaker of the House
Really scared about
Election fraud
I am too I'm very concerned about it and actually most Republican voters are concerned about it
And I've been very upset that publicans up here on the hill
Haven't taken it serious but we should take it serious because the stolen presidential election
Is the most serious thing that could happen in our country and we've seen the outcome
Becoming our president
It's been horrific and we've been suffering ever since
When the last congressional election
Oh I want I want huge but I have a strong Republican districts
Even
They can't question my election
Who's asking that part about the record margin because it's one of his
Just made it up or saw it in a meme
Please open the solidifier
With her every bit nice if she was like it doesn't have to be true Marjorie
I applaud her for not just going along with it cuz it
Would feel good in the moment
I don't applaud her how everything that the 2020 election was stolen
That sucks
Good news here is that there's no chance
Even if the GOP take back the house big green will be the
She wasn't even in the House GOP leadership right now
Never be able to Rally the kind of
Support you would need to get in
Into the speaker
With almost
Zero doubt if the house flipped Kevin McCarthy would be the speed
And maybe if you wanted to get real weird you might
Macy's Steve scalise be able to
To put together the kind of sport
We need from his position as the minority whip I was going to say I
That be interesting
It would undoubtedly be able to make a lot of noise
And get people to yell about how she's
You should be the speaker
Maybe
But in terms of that meeting anything to the Congressional process
It's just
And that's one of the reasons why I think that I was just trying to gather
Headlights
To get people
Go to follow through with it
Alex wants Margarita claim that their make
It's a claim that Alex knows is ridiculous and and
For all her inability to
Exist as an actual legislator
Gino's of
It's not
January 6th
A little bit
You're what people want
Amazing power
Beautiful woman
Promoting freedom
Democrats in Congress
For January 6th
Violence
And we really appreciate
You gone and then tried to
I suspected Alex's mostly bring up January 6th we can leave together his own personal victimhood and get green to talk
About them being in that struggle together
Yeah Dumbo partially because greens record on the 6th
This is not good
Wanting her actions leading up to the six
Explicitly fan the Flames with
Conspiracies
Is it light up to the storm again
The capital
Just before it
Perhaps more Daisy was the Revelation that one of her Close Associates Anthony Aguero was one of the people who
The capital
Pretty weird conflict-of-interest when it comes to her positions on the folks
Involved that day you came to look to her as
Any kind of impartial voice on the matter
Man I would I would argue that to you
Close enough to a Coke
Conspirator
Also no one's afraid of green because she believes in Freedom and is so strong and powerful
She's completely insane and is now in a position of power which
Easily abused
In 2017 she called
Qanon quote
A once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to take this globe
Global cabal of Satan worshipping pedophiles
Shero blog post about the unite the right rally being an inside job
The pizzagate conspiracy
And wrote on Facebook and Nancy Pelosi get committed
Executed
She wrote about her beliefs a job podesta had Seth Rich killed for releasing the Wikileaks emails
Which proved that pizzagate was real
Was trying to bring about white genocide
Her life and work is demonstrated
The clear pattern summer
Can't access information topic
Bentley
Nowhere near the level levers of power
She believes complete
Bullshittin
Beliefs motivator to act
In ways that could be
Be seriously Danger
As illustrated by
Her bulshit believes around the 2020 election letter to act in a way that encourage the storming of the capitol
This is pure and simple why people are afraid of
Not because she's too into freedom
It's because
She's really scare
And she
Write your name
Well that's just because the guardian 100 letter have a pencil she could hurt
Self right now
She chose to have her Congressional office in Vacaville
If you would stop smearing your s*** all over the walls
So
Some theories about January 6th
This is dumb antifa
People like real
Who were telling people to go into the Capitol in people to go in the capitol
Like the capital
And all these horrible things that Rahab said
And I didn't see Ray Addison the DC jail Alex
That's what I went in there
When I saw these pretrial January 6th
Descendants
Being held
In solitary confinement roughly twenty-two to twenty-three hours a day
C Reyes in there
And so we need to do these investigations when Republicans take
The house if we're able to take
But the house after this election cycle
But we need to go in there and we need to find out what
What's going on because Ray Epps
Is the one question that no one can answer
Then the fact that Adam kinzinger Liz Cheney and the rest of the day
Testing January 6th committee
Finding this guy
Just shows you and exposes all of their lives
I can't dare come after someone like you Alex or innocent people that got legal
Rally permit for people that work for trumpet Trump Administration
And so on
They shouldn't come after any of you and they're going to stand there and let Reyes off the hook because we know what he did
He is clearly guilty
More than anyone
The only evidence has Ding Dongs have it all that Reyes was somehow involved
Been plotting to storm the capital is it tonight
Around outside
Is that the people should go into the capitol the next day when talking to a random person was video recording
For January 6th I would guess that upwards of
Tens of people had seen that video
Characters of the standard the green is going to use
Scientist determines guilt
Associate Matt Bracken should be far higher on her list of people to arrest
He was on air on Infowars
About a week prior to the 6 thing
Barber in phatic Lee than abscess did the capital
Even use the word storm
Hermes we cover
It's points like this that really highlight how the whole thing with Rahab CinemaSins to your argument being put forth by green and her ilk
He's an active trying to create a scapegoat to obscure the larger picture of how the
The information space that she's a major participant in
Led directly to what happened on the six
And if we ever grappled with that realistically
She be in serious trouble
It's imperative for green to just push whatever the current right-wing distraction
The Narrative is
Yeah I mean
It's just
It's just so f****** annoying
Because it's like
You could give them re-up
You can even if even if the government was like Payless
We know he's not guilty
But just to shut you assholes up
We're going to charge it with the rest of you guys and then he'll get off on and not guilty charge
They still be like oh well it's somebody else somebody else over they threw the case in order to let him off
Exactly it's just there
Problem is they did it
They won't own up to it
Problem
Want to see this though there were some
I'm concerned about some of the inmates being put in solitary confined
But this is not a unique problem for these January 6th
It's been a long-standing complaint
The prison reform activists have been raising in regards
City Fairfax County Jail
Absolutely should be
Respected but it
It's a bit telling of these prison Dynamics
Really top priority for the right-wing until there is
Insurrectionist buddies were the one
Ones in jail wait a second it's happening to me will now I'm mad
They ended up creating a wing in the DC Correctional treatment
Facility
For January 6th us back
Had apparently it's such a
The f*****-up place that Thomas
I do despise
Charges about
Requested that he be put in solitary confinement rather than half
Exist in that environment
What you describe is toxic and cult-like
Didn't they already have a clan wing of the
Anyway he ultimately was released to home
Confinement instead of
Solitary to get away from these weirdos
I like them
I just leave me alone
This isn't like minimized
Concerns about inhumane incarceration
Shut off but I
Continue to see this as a larger systemic problem and needs
It's be dressed as opposed to Anish concerned that only applies narrowly
Today's January 6th arrest he's like Alex and Marjorie or pretend
Yeah it's just they're not dealing with the real issue they're only dealing with
Their intersection
It would have been so great and it would have been like a really good moment for them to reach out
Across the aisle if they just said that so you know like yeah
You're right
Solitary
Confinement is torture
The left has been arguing this for a long time maybe we have some agreement
Nah
You just bothered our friends so we're going to overthrow the country
I am.
Maybe they should overthrow the country
According to Marjorie Taylor Greene
What's a Dalek because you know these these weirdos
Sure
Republicans
Others of not wanting more
Finding peace party
Liberals
Come to the new Republican
Populist
America first
That's right well you know I think Americans really are there
It's the people here in this town people on the hill
And a bunch of egotistical arrogant
Politicians and the
Andy's
Brandi's poles that really don't answer right
They just haven't caught up with the people
Or maybe they were never with
The people cuz look at what has happened over these decades
This is a party that produced Bush that
Barack Obama
And now here we are at 3
30 trillion dollars in debt
And
It just like it's so bad it's so disgusting you can hardly wrap your head around it
But this is where the American people have always been we've always been
Populist we've always been nationalist
Profoundly stupid for a number
The first being that the Trump movement within the conservative world
Absolutely not happy
Peace movement
Beyond the fact
Cathay insulate and Run cover for internal to mess
The terror threats like the proud boys enough Keepers they also very troubling connections to
Even more dangerous groups within the larger International fascist landscape
Leaving that aside
Trump may never have to
Declared war but his administration was insanely murderess
8 years in office Obama oversaw 1878 drone strike
Compared to 2200
In the first two years of Trumps
We actually only no fur
For sure the number the first two years because
Executive order over
Returning an Obama administration rules
The drone strikes outside of needed to be reported in
Only ramped up the Drone attacks severely he also made its
Significantly harder to quantify
Exactly how much bombing his administration was actually doing
In addition to this Trump ramped-up bombings in areas like Afghanistan and Yemen and Somalia something
Experts attribute to his quote
Loosening of the Rules of Engagement
2017 Newsweek was reporting the trumpet already killed more civilians in his fight against Isis
Then Obama hadn't isn't
Entire time in office
Just remember that time the Trump book drop to the mother of all bombs and Alex declare that he shoved Isis up his dirty ass hoe
The claim that Trump and his movement is a peace movement isn't offensively
And Alex knows that
This is just rhetoric that has the tendency to be effective in terms of
Gaslighting disaffected liberals
Into thinking that there's something
To be gained by aligning with the extreme right
In the name of fighting against War imperialism
Tascam matter further legitimize
Extreme right figures like Alex
And to get people to fall fall for it to whitewash
His beliefs to their Auto
I think it's effective 22 some folks who are paying attention
At the Greenspoint we have not always been popular store nationalist especially not in the way that she defined
The term
Her understanding what those words mean
And of
Understanding of American History is
Very suspect her understanding of words
Is very
I have not heard her say anything that wasn't
Like
Straight out of central
Just mad libs script
Things that conservatives
They don't like she doesn't
Just nonsense
Pointless
Vapid
Empty bottles like repetition of
Very
Clearly
False
And
Outrageous
Right-wing talk
Extreme right Alex Jones You Talk
Yep so Alex
Troll the little bit with like you should be the speaker
But I think he really wants to make sure the people take the bait
It's going to hit a couple
Swings for the fences
The threat
Marjorie Taylor Greene MTG a president one day
President
You're one of the few people
Green DeSantis
I don't know what's going to happen
But in the future world will definitely see what happens I'll see what the people think about something like
So this is obvious
Pretty clearly
You can tell
I think what's really more interesting about that clip is that
Like even in this
Clearly
False conversation they're having
Marjorie Taylor Greene needs to reinforce her loyalty
Yeah Saturday
What if he's listening
What if he's listening Daddy
Sauron
Is his eye is always watching that's the problem with creating a fictional figurehead for
For your b******* movement you don't realize that the actual figurehead
Does not care at all
You could say that Trump shelves
Isis upper 30s
Less of fear of trump himself listening and more getting backlash from listeners
Who
Swear fealty
I don't know if she should keep up though
But that vaccine thing
I'm so people aren't so hot on it anymore
Change in 6 months
Craigslist musicians like this is obviously like
Just trying to
The fish forehead
Skip ahead
Now to later in the show
This is
Do you have a pipe quiz
At the question I have do you think there's also an element of flattery in
I know you don't think so you don't think he's trying to flatter Marjorie Taylor Greene at all
Alex's the victim of flattery not the purveyor of it
I think he wants her back on the show
Probably understand
That's a good point
I would think you would think I think
Mostly just
Kind of a
Attention thing
It's always nice when a plan comes together
Amazon few hours ago
Believe that
Reality
But as they are now
Discovery
Are you or murder of our innocent children
Will be repaid
1 trillion
You will be
For all of eternity
Own energy
Yorkshire
Defender fauci been
Joseph
Weather tomorrow
But it's always good
Let's go ahead and do your phone calls tomorrow it's pretty
No I mean it's very I was reading a headline that was that
Came out immediately after
Really that simple
It was that easy
Like the
Attempt
Getting attention
Pays off
In the same episode
Kalisto cycle
We we what are you guys do what do they do I do I don't also think that Alex
Was like
We are sitting at a whiteboard
Bob with a explicit plot
I just think that he has
An innate awareness of like ways that he can
Trick people into
Honestly I don't know what you would do otherwise
Guys like the idea that
Babysitting congressperson
Is on Infowars and it's
Maybe one of the nuttiest
People in Congress
Like it is something there
You can't really ignore
Yeah it's relevant
It is
Samsung
I understand why people would have lines about it
And it's not really falling into Alex's trap
If you
Correct
Actually
I don't fully understand correctly would be
I guess
Like
Dumbest radio host and dumbest Congressman get together to say dumb s***
I also like
I think that possibly a better angle on it then like
They talk about fauci or like
It's she's Alex's you should run for president or whatever
Because I was with a lot of stuff is going around on Twitter
I had to do with
Baby
Stronger approach to it would have very little to do with the focus being on Alex
It being on
Marjorie Taylor Greene
And that she appeared on a show
The 10 minutes before she was on
Was the screaming disgusting nonsense about pedophilia
I think that I like
Forcing her into that box
Facts of like
You
O-net PL
Cuz there's no consequences
Publicity
Where is negative publicity right around the times of
Primary
Preseason
Could be something that might be motivating
For Marjorie Taylor Greene special
She doesn't have her Twitter account anymore
Yeah I mean it's it just it
Suck so hard
Because
The
They could do a better job
They could absolutely do a better job of not falling
Into this kind of
Shity trap
But
The reason that they fall into that trap is because it's also good for them they get more clicks
From their b*******
System that both
Profit off of witches
Is the problem
But I think there's an element of that you know
I like I think that often times
Much like I feel about the Reuters article
Like I think a lot of times
Stuff just isn't even worth it
You shouldn't even
Why cover it not yet
Yep
Kind of irrelevant
Albatross owner
It should be hanging from her neck
Like a sad sad thing
But it's it's it's it's something that these other outlets whether or not their click Drive-In
Can't really not
Say something
That's true
So we have one last clip here of green
This is bad on her front
But it's also really interesting
What it says about Alex
Can you speak to the great reset and your views on this and you agree with me that
To expose the Real Enemy
Call Schwab
And the Bilderberg Group
Publix
Absolutely think they're the enemy you know what you know what makes
You and me
Is when we don't take people at their word
I don't really care about any of this conversation is the person in the house who believes that the
The same complete nonsense that Alex does
The point of view and Klaus Schwab is this Generations
The equivalent of Hitler
It's entirely unacceptable to public service is eroded
This boy
However
I think the more important
7.4 Mi is that Alex is lying
Marjorie here
I wasn't the countless hours of our two shown I can tell you one thing with certain
Alex doesn't believe that Hitler was the bad guy in World War II
Did Bad Thing
But he was being controlled by the globalist
Behind the scenes
Hitler was set up another real globalist or financing all sides of the war
Alex believes that when it's
Convenient
He says that Hitler was the bad guy
And you can see how in this conversation
Is consistently expressed belief that Hitler was set up run
That's very counter
I'm trying to Brand class Schwab is the new hit
And it's a it's a belief of
Search
Childish
Contrarian bulshit that you could
Compared to a Libertarian argument about the age of consent
Oh boy
22 and
He's very well-established belief that Hitler was set up
Isn't going to play
There
Also good luck getting a
Sitting representative to agree with you on a recorded radio show
And we've all been given Hitler a raw deal
Hey what are you going to do when Alex is
Running solo or trying to blow Eddie Bravo's mind but the midterm primary election coming up with nobody
Dipping tobacco
How does opinions
These are inconsistent
And they vary depending on his mood
It's more troubling that is factual claims and understanding of history is
Is just as malleable
What is listeners
Brush grapple with foot
Instead they just ignore it
I mean yeah yeah
It is if
Marjorie Taylor Greene did become president you half expect her to try and bomb
Fictional place
I'm sick of both Chutes and Ladders we have good intelligence that Lord licorice is testing the borders
We can't I can't have this incursion
Into
Whatever though
Where the
Peanut brittle Lake
It got hired the brothers from Double Dragon to take down
Just f******
Bulshit
So within the third hour or so the first hour was largely that disgusting
Display about the
Professor from
SUNY and then largely
Marjorie Taylor
Do you do the third hour
Edgewild
Make this comment I've been looking over the Calypso's whereas we're recording this
Decided that I'm even not going to play
Some of the clip
Given a warning about the beginning going through this I realize that they're not as Jermaine as I thought they
A would-be even might be a bit
But I want to stress the point
That the actual episode
Is one of the more unacceptable things that I've ever listened to
In my time doing Alex yeah
Copper Ridge
Incessant
Multiple times where I was listen to episode
And I audibly reacted to him
Like go fuc yourself
It was it was very difficult to list
We were talking about it it's just like
We can portray him as the idiotic
Goofball monster as much as we want but it's
Important to remind people
He's a true
Monstercat
M22 the
Except that it was relevant in terms of covering this story recognizing
Fat Joe Rogan
When is feeding him recognizing
Fuses
The enthusiasm and energy that he builds around these stories not to cover the actual stories
But to subvert
Is that energy toward
Marketing
And towards his bigoted narratives
I think that there is a value in playing some of that
This is
This isn't
There's nothing that's added by it it would just be like hey look how f*****-up Alex Shelley
That you can go listen to it yourself
It's not necessarily relevant
Not in the third hour Alex
I was going to go to calls
And then instead
Soros is the Antichrist
Revelation open earlier books is always foreshadows that
Thousand-year-old
People will marble and look at him
Hologram in the pit in his cell
In that black hole
And say that's the creature
The funniest reaction
It's a short for
Michael wanger
Battling
George Soros
Paylocity
He's a horrible person
That's the thing that did all this to us
See everything
Foreshadowing
The final event
Is there any devil
What
One final personification of it
But it's one spirit
It is that's the thing within this to us
Yeah this is this is
Dumb
He's going to get the calls
I would
So I guess
I mean guys are going to go to college for a while
That's why it's fine for us to
Continue saying that
That guy's the Antichrist
Cuz there's like a million
And I'll tell you right now the Book of Revelation
Sounds like everybody's the f****** Antichrist man
Use with this person
Another person
Book of exploitation is what it's called
A little bit
Here we are here we are
Maternity
Okay
And then you realize there is no Edge maternity already Uncharted
What
You already are totally complete
Just have to reach out
I need
I have been
Tasted
Completion
Beyond fullness
Beyond ecstasy
Beyond timeless
Absolute
Total completion
Beyond the Stevens Inn
I want you have
Trapped into that
Eternity
Fraternities
You will then finally transcend what's happened on the
Planet
I think Alex might have gotten high
I'm going to listen to that s*** was on Alex
That's fine
Congratulation musee was doing the evil maniacal laugh
To the beginning of the fourth hour for that
What about later
These esoteric
Maternity
Then you've really broken
There is obviously
At home chain
The Tempest here but also there's something
Visceral
That feels different
Like I needed it does feel almost poisoned post-coital
There's also a silent almost
That's behind I don't know how to describe it
Are of like
Manet The Silence
Alex
Behind him somehow
Here we are
It Feels Like Everything has stopped
It does
It does have that moment of like a record scratch voice over all the sudden
How did we get here later
Gentlemen first
We're going to have to cut to three weeks earlier about a bunch of bulshit for an hour interview
For an hour and now I'm going to f******
Tell you about eternity and how I've tasted
Uber like the end of the Mister Rogers show except for you know with Alex
This neighborhood
Alex
Have some bad news
For the Hindus out but I don't have a lot of Neighbors in this neighborhood I'll tell you that I do
This clip is weird
This is going to be
Pretty good no no
But unlike what some of the Hindus and others teach
They say well you know what the process is
People are dumb and they're losing their souls destroyed
That's a process I am an owner of holy book
So don't feel bad
Just be glad you're awake
Deception
Am I picking
Fights with
Windows and people like
I just read
What they saying
Pikachu
Jimmy the Bhagavad Gita
But you're not reincarnated
From the same thing
You're already turn
What
So
Closet
Ears are spirits
Collective creation on this
Planet
Project
So that we can build
Closet
Of ourselves
Together in communion
Just as God created us
Archimedean weather
Yes the genetic line of humans
Is a composite of
Multi-dimensional
Energy forces
Sing on this planet
I'm in building an organized
According to
I defy you to explain with Alex my by any of that
Translated into coherent understandable language
Scattershot Awards Alex's it
Bring some profound in the s*** together into rambling sentence
I have to write out the last part
Yeah really want to party
The genetic line of humans
Composite of our Bolt
Dimensional energy forces hold on manifesting on this planet right they're building an organized structure according
Slowly
The genetic line of human DNA
Four important in a Haji adenine guanine time I got it
Okay
Check is a
Positive are multi-dimensional energy force
Alright now this is where we got to stop real quick
DNA is made up of a combination of multidimensional energy
This is where we're going to have to
What are
Which which dimension
Spanish
What forces
Energy
David Arquette
Yeah so it's a composite of that
Haha
Note that means
Are they manifesting anywhere else
I mean it has to be manifesting in the other also
In order to
I am building an org
Organized structure according
To our time-space vision
You got
So
If I'm going to understand this here's what I'm trying to put together
Here's what I'm trying to put together here
What he is saying
Is that
Who We Are
Actually
A breakover energy from
Other dimensions that manifesting itself in this dimension
And
That manifestation is controlled according to our will
Or our vision of our self
That is held Within
I think that's a bad is generous
Can see what you're saying I don't think that's what he say
Curse.
I don't know
I don't really
All I'm hearing all I'm hearing is him being like
Okay so the Hindu say that the flash is faster than Superman put the Christian say Superman is faster than the Flash
It's strange
That's it
Also I don't know about this I'm not trying to pick a fight with the Hindus let me says that their beliefs are alive
What are we doing
What are we doing I'm not trying to pick a fight with a hinders I'm just saying everything that they believe is b*******
Sometimes you hear criticism of Jordan
Peterson you know Lake
Speakeasy
Dumb person's version of what a smart person looks like
I think it's kind of the same dynamic
Alex is a dumb person's version of what a profound
I think her looks like
Thanks that I would say something
Cul-de-sac
This is this is just
Weird esoteric Bible
This next clip
Person says 10 $5 words and it's not a PhD thesis get the f*** out of
Libertarian
The next clip which is immediately after this I have not cut out
This is just sort of like
Rolling
Pink the start
To make a little bit more sense okay
It's still weird
Colony entity
Is individual and is Transcendence
And is a connection to our higher selves
It itself
Is lower creation from Who We Are
Rediscovered books
This stuff is what
Good idea
I haven't been there
But if you realize this it's game over them
Sure double helix
Because when you go
Although
Of your Kindred Spirits the energy God created of other Souls
Going to be here with you
Just like you love your children and they love you and you love your grandparents I love you and you have this feeling that
There with you
That's not a ghost
Walking through walls
That is
Reflection
Their genetics
That resonates
Going onto the airplane
Papi
Since with you as your Shield
Blankets
Your Refuge just like God gave us the planet that's a beautiful goddess
Choking up a little bit there at the end
Yeah that means Hey look
When you're when you're really grappling with Concepts this powerful
Bacon cause you know
Understand
A couple times in overtime parse this
Your human body is
Is it exist in our dimension
Colony entity
Which contains some kind of a
Copy of a bunch of
Consciousnesses of our ancestors
The game
Before it help us
Difficult times ever get stressed out
Jeff but that isn't yours higher true self something that I guess
You become when you die
Point your Consciousness is copied into your offspring
Or something
This is fine as far as like a fun esoteric belief system for Alex
The spout off about but honestly I'm having
Really bad whiplash
Flash from this episode
He spent most of the time screaming absolute
Dusting s*** that was inspired in his mind from a 1-minute
A clip of Steven kirschner that he saw
How many spainhour interviewed Marjorie Taylor Greene and now in the third hour he's
He's ranting about Soros being the Antichrist
And how we roll Colony beings were
For transdimensional ancestors
Want to remind us not to walk down dark alleys
I probably say
Insane people have legitimately no idea about the content that actually contain
It's bananas
So this
Esoteric nonsense
Is weird
It made me feel weird
I thought I fell
That like
Scared
Fuel
Like I feel right
I feel gross
Because when I was a kid and I hate
Doing this I hate having to do the when I was
The kid thing cuz it's not about like a different era or anything like that it's just like when I was
Was growing up and going to all of these different churches
If
Christian
I sent
Sibley said some s*** like that
My entire
Family would breakdown of like
This is why that
Blasphemous this is why you're not following the Bible you remember that book were supposed to give a f*** about all of that
That you don't like
Where in the Bible does it talk about with made-up holiday a transdimensional
Colony do you want something else
Just f****** this weird read from Matthew and shut the fuk up
Yeah
But ultimately I think you can tell
For this next clip
Alex's
Concerns in the Physical Realm
B supersede those
Of his bizarre esoteric nonsense
12 years old
What is years old
Because
Free will
But God
Doesn't leave us alone
The
Conscience
To know what's right
What God Says listen
And not give you the sink
I'm going to give you everything you need
I love you
I created you
Because I care about you
I love this
It's not that earpiece I hate the group
It's the clip
He does not get back to his finishes thought because he gets distracted
Oh my God
I am trying to teach people about the secret of the universe as revealed to me by God and this earpiece
It's just so annoying that that's what you're all going to hell now guess what I actually don't have a way to come
Wheat this talk at your piece really sucks
Convenient OfferUp
Alex Costa calls final
Okay
How many calls does
I don't know like
Maybe 5 or so 5 is a big number
One of them is just a lady
Sayings that God is with the truckers
And Ottawa
I don't that I don't know I think that's great
Included
2 calls
Wild Oak
The first one
Can I give you can I give you a word of encouragement
Can I can I give you a hug
Noah was asked
To build an ark
And you know the Bible scholar said it was
55 + 70
Took him to build a tar
And I know that in the past
Recent past you've been talkin about
You could just give it up and and what
Listen
You're building an ark man
Your Bill Maher
Keep it up
I will brother
I just get angry and
Frustrated
Sometimes
Call Josh I'm not one of those biblical Scholars
Is this guy is talking about but I don't remember the part
The story where like
Noah got in a bad mood cuz he couldn't see the new Spider-Man movie and then he launched into a childish outbursts about how everyone deserve to die
Talk to you peace
Rental deserve to come on the ark
Noah did
Edith Neighbors
And then like you came back a couple minutes later and apologized
To the crew really sorry at all these listen
I know I kicked with unicorns off
I'm really sorry about that I was in a bad mood
I thought we were all going to die
Yeah
6:30
Piano
Characteristic difference
Between Noah
And
Cycad man I can't imagine
Having
Never build a boat
Argue with God that like
Do you have guns
Right right...
Right but can you imagine calling into UVA like
Name name a baby and you're not going to call into the majority report be like Sam
I just I just want you to know
You should keep at it bad your dad that's not how you should interact with a broadcast
I know
You shouldn't have drawers to your liking Noah
You would expect
Pick somebody who got that from a caller would make fun of them back
Somehow like
Reject
That you're totally right there I am exactly like this hero from the Bible who saved the human race Doodle God
Intervention
Yeah that's that's exactly like me
It's really bizarre that Alex allows this kind of conversation cuz it's
Disgusting
Like seamster
Need this kind of support
From the collective
Buzzard
Reaffirmation
Yeah I know you can hear me like listen brother you know I've never actually going to quit
And I like that whole thing
Sad
Kind of codependent
Yes I kind of don't feel comfortable watching it
Cuz it's two person
So let's let's wash our hands of that
And get just like
The Funko
Is Gene & georgetti
Fan
Operation fishbowl
Fishbo
It's been going on since
Days Inn
Glass ceiling
People trying to get back
To heaven
They've already been cast to the Earth
Come on this brother Alex you know that
Oh boy
So operation Fishbowl Buzz a series of 11 high-altitude nuclear test
What went on in the 60s right I guess I was secretly about the globalist
Pierce
The Dome that's above Earth in order to get back together
Hillary's talking about the glass ceiling that was about specifically
The power
Breaking back into heaven
The glass ceiling that is the do-over
There were part of operation Fishbowl we're about 10 km above the surface which is
A bit lower than the moon
In order for this guy like what he saying to mean anything not believe that's
Space is real
And honestly what he's doing
You putting forth
Some ideas that are pretty common in
Flat Earth
Yeah it does
Seemed a little bit very much like a well you know what they were closed
Like that
That's the worry I have is him
Not telling me this like is missing trysting but him telling me this almost as if like
Listen if we let them go any further
They're going to do it right they're going to break into heaven man is that what you want I understand the story of the Tower of Babel
Is that
That is trying to get back to that
That was the point of that
Where was a piece of that store
Hillary's comments
The pieces of information he's bringing in
To support this promised
AR
Very very
Here's what I'm saying though it does makes a mix
Boursin
If you believe that Hillary is a demon that she would
Ticket to Heaven Tower climb
To be fair
Conceptually
This caller is saying makes more sense than with Alex with absolutely no I can visualize what he's trying to vent mean
This is bulshit is bulshit but at least I can understand his point
It's pretty
It's pretty conceptually clear I appreciate
Miss Georgia
Fallout 4
Coming through man
Sudan to this episode
Galaxy shows
I want to talk to this
See this is a problem this guy is his race so many more questions for me
Are you telling me that in the intervening time. Between the Tower of Babel
They were like man the next thing we got to do is we got to find a way to invent nukes right that's our only hope
We're going to go from the Tower of Babel Smash. 2 1960
We got it
Yeah
Or did they try before with a mustache
Arrow
Is that the guy is that the original
Yeah probably probably I think that
The Wright brothers probably right there demons
Probably that guy from that October Sky movie
Definitely
How do you think she disappeared
Huh
Exactly where is d.b. Cooper
He accidentally went
Jazzman
Are you going to say that this is far-fetched
Are you is that what you're going to tell me
I guess
But for the sake of fun
I hate
I hate I hated this
I think
That there is
Uno
I think that Marjorie Taylor Greene
Just general existence in Congress
Is really upsetting
On a day-to-day basis it's
Not good
Existing in Infowars land
And her and Alex
Basically being on the same page about
Not so much
It really brings into sharp Focus
Just how
Problematic it is
Yeah I mean the thing about that though is if you do study a lot of American History eventually you'll get to the
Is the realization that any given point in time
Probably between 5 and 10% of all
Congress's have been
You know like you just been nut bags from
Start to finish
Maybe you should
Struggle with this little bit more is that like
Ron Paul was in Congress for like 20 years
I think
The difference between it is Ron Paul's oh his political beliefs were
Just as bad
Anyways
The things that he advocated for
I don't know if
He felt as
Disconnect
Dude from reality
As there is a lot of
The things
Marjorie Taylor Greene
Espouses
Like I don't think of it Ron Paul would be
Be spreading pizzagate
He came up with bad solution
To real problem
Supposed to pass solutions to fake problems that don't exist
Yeah yeah or misinterpretations of things perhaps right
Yeah I don't know I feels different
I was just it just be nicer if she was one of The Crazy Ones or just never win
You know like
American history is littered with congressmen who are like this is actually dumb
And just never went
Great you and you get paid you don't do any work just stay home Marjorie I think that the best-case scenario
For her probably is losing
The 2022 race
I think she could have
A pretty decent
Niche in that test Facebook
Hidden promise she's just bad
So yeah this is this
I wash my hands of this episode
And I will be back on Monday
Through
Imma be working on it
I think it's a good idea now that we've got our own Duke
Here's what I suggest
No it's a fox
Okay
Also on Twitter
Until then I'm New York
And now here comes
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color