Damn important items swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
The altar of Celine and talk a little bit about the past present
Future of Alex I like in A Christmas Carol
Rango chains dangling
Yeah sure
I guess I have very little proof that I'm alive
Hey Jordan
I will
Whatsyourprice
My bright spot
Just before the show Dynasty Warriors
I had no idea that they were Dynasty Warriors games available for the switch but
I found one
I've not played a Dynasty Warriors game since
Since
The PS2 era I believe
That it's been quite a while
Maybe a decade or so
And sorry I started playing a little bit of Dynasty Warriors 8
And
It's
Good job
That's wonderful
My bright spot is
So about 30 years ago
Godspeed You black Emperor
Recorded
The demo tape
Of which
33 copies were made believe is the number
Couple of days ago
The first time
It was put onto YouTube
First time in thirty years
Nobody even thought this
This thing even existed anymore
And we have a full hour
Wow
That was only put on 33 cassette tapes
That's pretty wild
Yeah it's crazy
Do they want it to be out it's not their business
I think
It did very interesting thing is like a document
The demo tape
I don't know
Yeah I really meant for public consumption
That was it was released as a demo
I'm 33 copies of play was for the exact
Get a record deal like not put it out I don't know LOL
It's really good and especially cuz it's a 1990 f******
For whatever and you listen to it now and they are they're not fully formed is godspeed yet but your
It's just blowing you away just like what
This is 94
Still as relevant today as it was I don't know you tell me
Do you have that too
To enjoy
Today we are going to put Alex in timeout
Good last episode that was
2000 enough for a while his casting monster might be relevant
Midterms coming up that's true
Take a look at something from the midterms
In 2040
See where Alex's had was at during that.
Free Trump right so happens if he will
It doesn't happen
The day
Oh
The election the midterm election November 4th
How much is gas
Is the most important person in the world Tucker Carlson
Really
Goddamn
So I thought it would be interesting to look at
The Dynamics of the midterm
In 2014 and also see how Alex related to the most important person in the world
Before he was the most
This is a camo Modern Warfare
Disseminate
But first Jordan that say hello to
That's great idea
Do first
Tony from Akron is a Cryptid Shaman thank you so much
Call Anna castles in space thank you so much you're no policy want
Cooking
I hope my neighbors enjoy hearing Jordan's laugh as much as I do because I play this podcast on my Bluetooth Soundbar
Your nail polish
Much but also this podcast should be something you listen to in private headphones
Noise cancelling
Next to MIT Mount weird who prepped more for that deposition then Dario thank you so much you are now policy
Physically murdered or stopped up. Either
Thank you so much you want an apology walk
Thank you so much you and I were technocrat
I have
Risen above
Miami
So take a little break now
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Nostradamus
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Belle walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
Who knows about tomorrow but let's see if Alex
Who's better in the past
He wasn't sure isn't
Today Show
Just a little bit what
Does the tiny bit of identity theft
Did you know that a lot of people call themselves Alex that's a tiny bit of identity theft
I never really thought about identity theft is like a thing of an amount
Yeah it was just kind of thought like wild people have got your private information.
Pics of my social security numbers I'm real
Playing with tonight's now if you look it's less of like a little bit of identity theft and they did a little bit with it
Yriv
Yeah they bought gas one time
So are we start here on the
4th and
No
You can see a little bit of the same sort of conversation that Alex has around a lot of Alexa
It's always the most important thing and it's a political realignment to every single time this political realignment have
I like the sort of who gives a s*** level
It's accurate
Yeah but he's trying to over grandiose things a little bit
Actually probably something
In a both parties are a little bit guilty of
You here are you here
It's okay
Before it's
It's sensible to say that every election is
The most important one
Because it's the one you can
10 impact
Past elections there might have been more important
Like things on the on the Alexa about it now
You can in the present one
What's the point of me
Being developed hate then
Look this isn't the most
An election the most important election
What's 18/6
That helps you write
Put things in perspective
This empowers you a little bit because
Most important action should be the one which you have an ability to impact
So I'm just kind of trite but
It's sitting in an election both parties have been like man
Not much going on this you want to see
So Alex is destroyed Obama
Basically his buddies have
Taking them down if you want to go.
Presidential election
Barack Obama
Secret Life
Yep that you can track to every election right
Throw this out there
Where I mean
You know that's actually something that's almost been kind of nice about the 2020 rewriting
Narrative been illegal immigrants
Deb Wright
Is the right Boogeyman this time
Summer
Well it is all of us but that is also the elite
Quote immigrants part of the storyline
Really that's true that you get from Alex's
Especially was before the soda narrative solidified a little bit more
You can see this is all this is
Really boilerplate
Now this episode gets races
That's really fast
How quick you might have
Smelled a little bit of it's coming in with the illegal voting
But man I was not ready I came into this just look
Looking for election coverage at Tucker Carlson
I did not expect for Alex to go
So hard so fast that clip of Joe Rogan saying the n word a bunch
Little version
Organizing
Walgreens
Earworm
I feel like that's a really good encapsulation of Alex's delusional position about integration
He pretends to be as a no problem with non-white people existing in the spaces around him but at the same time if he sees a few minor
Doherty's in a store
Besides without any proof that they're all here illegally and it's part of an effort to flood the country
Overwhelming to see more than one non-white person anywhere
Crazy
This feature of Alex's racism of Muslim women
Pool supply shop
Alex he's not white people or people of other cultures that he's hostile to
Living in spaces that he's decided are
R4 White
People in it bother
You can hear this being expressed in the way you saying that they were just
Too many minorities at this Walgreens that he went to is it to imply that
He's a good tolerate white person who put up with one non-white person being at the pharmacy
But there's a line
If there were three.
People at the same time that's evidence of a f****** Invasion obviously has literally zero information about
These people that he sees at
Other than that he can tell that they're not white
And maybe he can hear them speaking in languages other than English
From that he determines that they're not supposed to be in the country and that their presence
As part of the conspiracy against white people in my
That's sick s*** and it's something that I was perfect
Play comfortable expressing
Is it fact he's making legitimate point about some
Political position that he has
It's sincere
He has no information about the citizenship status of any of these
He has no information about whether or not they're immigrants
He has no information about whether or not they even
The only information he's operating on is that they're not white
And being around multiple non-white people makes Alex's white identity
And the power that he feels
Entitled
Because of that identity
Yul Brynner
Honestly Alex has a way worse person now than he seemed to be in 2014 but this articulation
What is deeply entrenched racism is
It's probably more explicit than he
He gets into today
Yeah you know it is nice that the one
Single ideal of America that is unimpeachably grape
The idea that anyone can come here
And make themselves alive
Is the thing that they hate more than anything else
They'll hold onto the image
What makes us so great
But also if there are a bunch of minorities around non-white people
That I
Victor something up
I think it's a conspiracy okay
Here is fine
Fine here's my new rule
No Walgreens can have anything less than an exactly demographic
A representation
Of America
If there are more than 60% white people
Walgreens closes down
What about CVS
They're racing
I feel like implementing of your system would be incredibly challenging and I imagine
If there would be a lot more non-white people in his Walgreens that's for sure this guy sucks
This was weird to hear
So fast
Looks
The story is so
Trite
Like its
It's it means nothing
His experience
Is
Just that
You think there was no fight there was no like
Conflict or anything it was just he's experiencing
Of what he determined to be too many non-white people existing into space
That he thought there should be more wipes
Man
I can't believe that
Because I've you just go there and you see it but that's what I would
This will blow my mind is like seeing that all of those people from everywhere in the f****** world in the same place
Knowing that if I
Flu anywhere
If I flew to any country in the world I would see an infinitely more homogenous place
In that Walgreens then I would hear
That's the amazing thing
We're obviously a great Melting Pot that is Walgreens
Absolutely.
Yeah anyway
Alex Williams from this into
Maybe
White supremacist talking points
Forgot
I'm not speaking hyperbolically when I say that this is some Stormfront s*** yeah
Boards and
It relies on the same underpinnings as the great replacement kit
Conspiracy theories that inspired Mass murderers like Brenda
Parrots in the Patrick crusius
This is 2014 Alex long. Any connection to the community and
How above the left-right paradigm
The game was always to present yourself as being against both parties
To trick people into thinking that you're in the middle while
In reality you're just trying to
Suspecting politically disillusion people towards the extreme right
And opinions like this
This is bad this is the game maybe we've gotten it wrong
Maybe he has always been above
The left
The left-right Paradigm interesting slip-of-the-tongue there
Yeah
Yeah I mean I guess I guess you could
Say that he is above the left-right Paradigm in as much as
Pisces
Nowhere near it
Sepulveda politics whenever all I really want to deal with is how racist I am
To really have a lot of power behind
You to say that I'm really again I'm way off of it I would like to use its power to inflict harm
Small government
Until it can be used in
Enforce my white nationalist ideology
I want small boots
Exactly
Listen to this November 4th episode and I got really really curious around this point cuz
Alex
Alex's insisting that the media
He's done him dirty
Right
There's a story in an rawstory
Issue with the headline
Really got my ears up
No you're not
Wait
What
Okay okay
I'm Wild
Confused I think that I just have to leave a bit of that rambling to the side
There are people in all group
Who like to beat up
People in other groups
Predator ass baby
Chat whatever
I am more interested in this rawstory headline and seeing
Just how accurate or inaccurate it is
Because I am always curious about like
Alex
Being misinterpreted or people covering him in the wrong way
I was just mad about this article in Raw Story which allows me to figure out
What episode the actual comments
That they're covering our Maiden so I can go back and I can
Figure out and see if Alex
Is right or wrong
Did this headline actually mischaracterize Alex's words or is he just engaging in the stupid racist backpedaling spin
Justify is bigotry in Moline anybody who would say
Call it out
This has to do with stuff that Alex and apparently
According to Raw Story on the previous day's episode
And here's what we will need
Need to assess specific
Alex has taken issue with the rawstory headline quote
Alex Jones Obama put out a green light for groups of black youths
Kidnap white with
In the headline to put put out a green light and the black youth are the things that are in
Jason marks
Contention that this headline is somehow
Frankenstein mishmash of his words being used mischaracterize what he said
So this was saying
But it was on Monday's episode 3 episodes on Tuesday
So Gordon Raw Story
We go back to Monday
Can we check it out
We can find out
So Alex doesn't get into this or commentary immediately so I was like what
Might as well
Pull some clips of things that are interesting along the way here's one that's really stupid
Real
Man enough to roast Alex I can just sit back and let his pants size do it myself on fire
Listen to him say that I can't do it
Hurts me physically
Have to hear him say the things that I would
Very casually say
Yeah it's like
If I got
But I brought your past self
I can't count the number of times he's yelling about I like
The world leaders listen to him
Cuz is the most important
Analysis of world issues
Hey Brian stelter is no viewers of Cl that is fatal I called
So there's one Hallmark of being a loser and then I made the other big Hallmark of a loser is like you know you
You do something
And then you lie directly to people
Faces that you didn't do that right
Refuse to take responsibility
I like let's just think about how he hold on one second
What
Are you telling me that
This clip is of him saying that
People
Lie
Rather than engage with the thing that they did
Okay
And then
Young tomorrow's episode
He's going to engage with the story
About a thing
Maybe
We don't know we don't know yeah I'm telling you that I'm going through
Assess whether or not The Raw Story headlines
Is accurate
Even take medicine
Like the way he lied to Rogan's face but what he said about Sandy Hook a classic Hallmark of a loser
Department
I'm being truthful and taking responsibility didn't go well it's remarkable 22
We hear things that I think are actually fairly
Acura
I think it is a loser is behavior to self aggrandize and minimize your enemies
Go to Fantasy World
Behavior
Kind of loser ish to not own up to past mistakes
And deal with yourself
Physically as well
Totally
It's just it's just that
Alex likes himself could not be more and indictment of yourself Center
To coherently put forth an argument
That you are a loser
Calls November 3rd
Bird show
Interesting idea
If you listen to this
You can tell that like Alex
Love
And respect
The institution of vote
Yes like
Heat sensitivity sacred Act
Or a race where
By the latest poll it's like over 3% one person over another
How about people riding something that's
Middle finger to the system Tennessee
Alex wants to use
Voting as a publicity stunt
God
Goddamn
That's just
That's
Advertising you just can't buy
No you can't buy that you can
You can destroy a country with it
Yeah
That's ridiculous
Another call from a guy if this actually was
So this caller is discussing how he
Works at an apartment complex
And Arizona and
They apparently I've somehow
Somehow
Are part of an intentional plot to bring in refugees and immigrants from Lake Liberia
Because they want to spread Ebola
Complex
Arizona complex ownership ownership group
Trying to bring in seriously bring in people from Liberia and other countries in Africa
Aunt Deborah this is
Lutera
Apartment complex
Brought in
Cheer in the office
Liberia Africa
Their own name on their own
Everything
Call Biltmore property
Chandler Village
Seems like a lawsuit
Kind of behaviors that Alex is in trouble
Sandy Hook
Is this is the same behavior it applies
I mean
Bureau of
Acting in such a way that would lead to harassment of
People whether it's the people who live in the
Apartment complexes Refugee or otherwise
Or the people who run these apartment complexes you're putting people
At a risk
The ethical implications of having this guy
Say the name of the apartment complex I mean on the air is
Is staggering.
It's so immoral
That
On this show
That all of these people are
Immigrants
You've said that the owners of your apartment complex
Are assisting them to do nefarious thing whether it's to stealthily bring a bowl
American Horror
And then you gave me a
Yes and we're going to send some people
I don't know if I've ever seen Alex do this kind of thing before
For always
Relevant and worthwhile to point out something
Behavior
Whether he's intentionally cause intimidation or harassment towards these people who
He feels our Act
Magic in ways that
He disagrees with right
Or if it's just a lack of
Concern
For the well-being of people who will be targeted and harassed
I'll buy it either way it's the results
Are awful
I am creating it as a pattern
Also makes it
A feedback loop where the more you
Tell people to go send we're going to send people out there
The more people are going to call in and say
I'm at Bubba Bubba
Send people out here.
Exactly exactly
Of his own
Accord say the name of the place
Pacifically asked
Yep
She really was interested in the ad
Or wanted to investigate this further
You would have kept that off air
Speed the
The possibility of something happening
From that
Is is
Most
Journalistic Outlets
Risk no I didn't Raymond just
F****** the idea of me living in an apartment complex
Happily
Just fine
And not having any idea that somebody f****** 34 hallways down the way is
Calling Alex Jones to give them my address
To put a bounty
Yeah that's not good
The comment
What's that Alex made
About
Black folks
Getting a green light to attack white piece
Better alleged
Avance Raw Story article
They are in response to Ben Stein
He went on
Fox News and said that Obama was the most racist president in history
Yeah that was an interesting question on Wednesday been sent money to who's the most race
President history and then
Sarah Silverman
Oh I don't remember that Jimmy Kimmel after
Got number of Seasons yet
I think Cousin Sal
Butterfield's
Sure why not was just thinking about this I saw that clip of Adam Carolla on Sean Hannity
So staggering
The different directions
The Kimmel in Corolla truck
Could not be more like
The the dichotomy of our our future like when I was growing up
The idea that if somebody just sat me down while I was
Watching the man showed been like
One of these will be good for you and wanting
Will be boys
These guys will host a late-night show and
Have some socially responsible positions that he puts out and isn't the day
Brightly
The other one
Will be an annoying monster
Just a real tragedy of a of a
Void where Humanity once was
Both would have gone that route
Yeah that's what I'm saying
We're all fought the men should be allowed in Stanhope took it over
Stanhope was
Fun
One thing comes full circle baby
Firestone away benstein maybe
These comments and that's what
Precipitated Alex's allege
Commentary
EXO
Episode
Alex brings up and Stein
But it doesn't say the things that rawstory was saying
So I listened to this whole episode
I got all the way through I realize The Raw Story had done Meador
Oh no it wasn't the right
Patches of it
Twice
Explicitly
These things on Monday
So I found the show from Monday
What they actually meant is that Alex
Video on YouTube on Monday
But it was from his Sunday show
So now we got to start over we got to play this again from the top I feel like I'm deeply committed
Weather. Rostory contact
Isabella when I listen to the Sunday show episodes in the past
Did you can't even like email somebody to complain about it anymore
Yeah I don't need to issue a correction for house tour
Today we go to the Sunday episode
I think that word like we're a little bit more in the
Okay
Call the day before
What
Do we have Alex
Instead of saying like I don't know if I agree with him but whatever
I think his argument here is really dumb
You can just leave that aside though like even if slavery was fine in the United States because everyone else was doing it we still
You should talk about it and try and undo the societal impact that it had
On black people in America
You should have blame is irrelevant and it's a distraction at this point it
It's really a matter of recognizing degeneration
Degeneration
Denied access to many parts of
The market in the economy
How these things have affected communities do this
And what we can do to address these problems
Moving forward
Make a more Equitable Society
Alex keep the conversation on the level of slavery wasn't that bad if you look at the world
Set the time because it keeps people distracted from the real reason that many of these conversations
Linger into the present and that is these generational
Deprivation
And I
But I mean that f****** f*** you
F*** you not you not you
Just because I got the episode wrong
Both ways
Yes
People were saying slavery was bad back
People have been slavery saying slavery is bad
Since we had slavery sure that we are that we are living in a world where it's fine for Alex
You just put that out there
And then for us
To just be like well it was socially accepted at the time as opposed to our rewriting our entire understanding of History to be like
I think I think you make a good point and I'm glad you brought that up because I
Definitely true
Still is
But yeah it definitely
It's
I mean I mean
If there's a reason he makes this kind of an argument so absolutely and there's a reason that we still have
It is really scared of seeing multiple by the store and that's part of why our history is built
Around the idea that
It was fine at the
You know like everybody agreed it was fine
The time so we don't need to focus on the
People who said it was
You could say baby putting us more accurately
There wasn't
These societal capital or the political will to do something about how wrong it was
About how it was
Perfectly evil right
Yeah if
If people
And this is the simplest way to do it
Took Pages out
Two of their Bible
Give to Slaves so the slaves didn't understand that the Bible said it was cool
To kill your slave masters you knew it was wrong
There's
It implies intent
Men's Raya is there there
So Alex doesn't just talk race nonsense on this episode he also gets into
One of his favorite sources
Cuz I thought it was just
Dumb
So hardcore ladies and gentlemen
What's going on
Turning around
Dynasty Warriors
This is really fascinating because it's the way Alex is trying to rationalize that like I don't come up here and say crazy stuff
Bill Joy wired article is available online
New listeners just
The brief version of this is
That there is a passage in that article where Bill Joy is quoting the Unabomber
If this is the stuff that Alex has taken to be the
The consensus of billionaires
The Unabomber isn't
Is accurate to what hours
Text me announcement
That the global Elites have decided that they kill everybody off
So stupid
So now we get back to the over
Racism and Jubilee
About the downtown Austin
Apparently
19 wipers
Ben's Austin a number of times like I've mentioned my parents live there
And I've been
Downtown 6th Street
I think
Maybe it's more annoying
Then anything else like
It's pretty loud
There's a lot people partying
Weekends in particular
Themed gangs of different races attacking white people like the Warriors arrows
A bunch of people dressed up in like baseball
All I wanted was a Voodoo Doughnut in the sky
There is so many goddamn roller skaters attacking base
The weird guy with bottles on his fingers
The case of this episode
Anthony gucciardi, anyway
Western Star train
What
You will deal
Coronavirus
Okay
That we just heard a lot of anal parasite talking
You know it's always fun whatever Alex tries to like insisted he's not being racist in the middle of
Committing a rhetorical hate crime
Yes I'm in the same situation as describing
Not necessarily things that I would describe his
Is hate crimes
Per se
I think the real
Issue is that Alex just is he shouldn't live in a city
I don't think he's able to engage with and navigate
The things
They come with living in a city which is
You don't fortune that there is some
Structural shortcomings
People are
Panhandling
Yeah
If you take any time someone comes up and asks for a bunny is like an attempt
To mug you
I think that you're going
You should just live on a phone
Yeah or or you
You could go Hog Wild
And really get a lot of Groundswell behind the idea of taking money away from the
Cops and
And giving it to the people
Who are pants
I get out giving it to people who need social safety nets housing if you'd be good
There are two ways to solve it
Kill everyone
Or help
Live in the country
Stop living in Austin city
Dynamics and things that happen when you live in a city is a race-baiting globalist superville
So yeah you can't live in the city
Stories are a little bit
Vague for me to really operate on
Man
The rash of gangs
Going around downtown
What
Okay
I guess I'm glad that Alex
Didn't pack heat
Might have
Committed murder I'm glad I didn't hear about the knockout
Oh yeah sure
Freddy's 4, taters
In 2022 it seems like it's almost like they just make these things up when they're
Kamchatka
What column which is
Alex had this experience
Babe
Dickies overdramatizing
Just a little bit
Anthony gucciardi one of his employees
He's one of these guys who exist in the space of like
Helping
Dr. group
Sell his supplements
Vibe space
Oud totally showed up fairly recently
In 2014 and his tenure was not very long
He's he's not around the Infowars parts anymore
But apparently he
Some folks downtown
To kidnap his girlfriend
You're wonderful
That is
Outrageous so we still don't know where gucciardi girlfriend is in this story
The story necessarily
Gucci already
I don't know if you Charities lying to Alex's house is lying about it I don't know
It does raise some questions
What is
That his girlfriend
Should have been kidnapped then right I think she's I think she's still gone beyond
The choice was
Give us your girlfriend or we will stab you didn't get stabbed and not okay you all are right
Imply that they took his
Girlfriend that seems like a story that I was with lead with
I mean that
Probably the biggest story that I could think of for for his purposes
Girlfriend
It seems to me that this story is nonsense
Because of the non kidnapping and Dawn stabbing
I don't know maybe Anthony Gutierrez got into a fight that's the type of s*** that happens in movies
What what what do you talk
What are you talkin about six men come up to you with one knife
Right
There's six of them making beat you to death in a heartbeat true if that's what they want to do don't need a knife
The ad
Well it's interesting that you say if they're sick
Is that number might be a little bit fluid kind of what I was thinking he was saying
And everytime it
Yeah
Alright I've satisfied my curiosity.
Rednecks
Never mind. Never
So I think the rawstory headline is absolutely accurate
Alex
Little mama green
Encourage this kind of s***
The headline itself has to do with a kidnapped
Thing in the story about Anthony Gucci Artis girlfriend was 100% And attempted kidnapping based on the way that Alex tells the story
SA
One thing
Put out
Total fairness
It's super super clear that I was just trying to drum up feelings of fear about black man in his overwhelmingly white audience
If you go like
Super strictly on details there's one way he can still make a point Against The Raw Story
Article
Their headline is quote Alex Jones Obama put out a green light
The kidnap white women
And if you listen to his telling of the situation with gucciardi
There isn't any reason to conclude that his girlfriend is white
How better headline was encapsulated
Very over racism but not
Not specified
The unspecified
Oguchi Artis girlfriend
From Alex's story all we know is that she's very attractive
But we don't know that
But she's white
Haven't gone through all this
I'm going to say that the rawstory headlines actually overly fair to Alex
These comments are racist as hell and the placement of quotation marks don't really have anything
What to do with anything
But I'm satisfied now to November 4th
Election day and what's the number of people in this gucciardi story
Was a little bit
Fluid
This is from November 4th
Grabbing a girlfriend
Is absurd and it's not meant to make sense
Alex's Weebly
The story about Anthony gucciardi but also pay really close attention to the comparison
And he's making about racial issue
On the one hand he has some guy coming up to him and maybe aggressively asking for money and then walking off with
No real need for aggression or violence right
I was just didn't respond and he says the guy stopped off
How does imagine that this
Was done because the guy was black
Can Alex's white but there's no proof of this outside of Alex's imagination
It's very possible and perhaps even likely that this guy aggressively asked a black person for money that same night
There's nothing except for Alex's imagination that makes this a racially-motivated thing and I'm not entirely sure what the
Reality with the Gucci already story is cuz it's
Second hand in the details kipana changes by the
Fellowship of the Rings
This is being compared to racist
Dragging a black man
The death behind there
Alex's referring to the 1998 murderer or you could call it even a lynching by truck of James
James Byrd Jr
Who carried out the attacks William Williams
Lawrence Russell Brewer and Shawn Allen Berry
Over three miles behind their truck
Before the killing they defecated and urinated
A killer
When does Man want the most
Disgusting and horrific ways possible they left
Does body in front of the cemetery of a black church
Cookout
The killers were members and Associates of white
Supremacist groups were abundantly clear
I had like
Nazi tattoos and chip
Got the death penalty and have been executed the third got life in prison
For cooperating with the investigation
In 2011 when one of them was on the eve of his execution he told the news as far as any regrets
No I have no regrets
No I do it all over again
To tell you the truth
Even through all that the victim's family tried to spare
The death penalty
This is what Alex is comparing his
Experience to
Some guy yelled at Alex that he wanted money and then Alex stood there and the guy left
That's as much of a violation to Alex's what happened to James
James Byrd Jr
I guess booty already stories more severe with the threats about kidnapping but
Noticed that even though Gucci already was
Super outnumbered he didn't get sad when his girlfriend wasn't kidnapped
If that story happened at all
There's absolutely no doubt that burns murder was racially mode
That was an active
Is very clear
The stories Alex's tell they may be real if I'm being generous but there's no indication that they were racially motivated
Black person bugs a white person that wasn't necessarily done because of racial animus but went three white supremacist
Because he's black
And then they say that's why they did it
It's a racially-motivated crime
The blurring of his line is an important part of Alex's
The political project which is rooted in white identity
He's a flake
Races that deserves if anything far more s*** then he gets on that front
There is something very specifically intentional about this train
Compare
Horrific
Very clearly racially motivated crimes again
Black people
Do something like what Alex experience
Not necessarily racially-motivated because the equivocation
Is
Leah Fenton
Absolute and giving
Bring the audience to equate the two
Is
And embedding of racism in their mind
The dual purpose of
Inflating his victim status
Sun
Deflating the victim status
The victims of his ilk
In elf
Yeah it's it's
I'm so flipping
That comparison is something B
Just something how he understands these days
It's terrified absolutely no wrestling with the reality of being dragged behind a car
Or
Why are who
Yeah
Well
Congratulations I think if anything's took you out of context
End of the opposite direction that you're claiming to me how often he seems to be f****** handled
With kid gloves Buy
Locations that should f******
Both barrels Adams
I think I think a large part of that is its
Really
Unpleasant to listen to his show and I think that most people would rather not do it
You know I think another part of it I was just thinking about
This recently
I think another part of it is
When I was thinking about.
Describing
Like
Oh this is what Alex said on his show if I
Really put that into like a headline
I'm something that we talked about on a daily basis that's totally normal to us
It would sound Faker s***
Every time
I think that's part of the like
I don't know if it was fully intentional but that's part of the reason that like our episodes are just a date
Yeah is the title and the description of the episode is never really all that now.
Like a blade out all the details
I don't know why
With that that
That possibility
I mean what are you going to Alex famous
Christian Zealot says that we are energy beings vibrating between multiple dimensions
And that is how we'll accelerate our growth to the next
Play
What who's going to
Don't break that
I don't know if anyone should
Exactly
Alex's disgusting raises
Remember cuz I accidentally listen to Monday's episode.
We remember that Alex was doing that coverage of the apartment
Listen to
He has on Tuesday
Obama
Mortar
Apartment complex
He doesn't have anything to back that up on its own
Just clearly a reference
Call that he got from the day before that he's integrated now
Into his
Factual based report
Bat
I would bet pretty confident
Play bet the United States has imprinted 60 million green cards in at 6
That's an interesting question
Maybe yeah
I don't know but I'm ready to go right now
I was crazy how that worked out to
Yeah
Idea about you know you bring in all these these immigrants
And then they will all vote for a Democrat
Stuff on its face
Even leggings
It's a dumb
Dumb way to engage
With 30 Dynamic right
There's no reason to assume that immigrants who come in will automatically vote
Other than if you are assuming that your own party would never help
The real assumption there is
We're never going to do any
Looking for immigrants there's a projection of that
Do you know he he believes that
You're going to end up in
The situation where there's actually just
Direct
And when you have democracy
51b voting to murder 49
His racist ideas about what'll happen to our voting
He ends up talking about Greek democracy unfortunately ends up working my side
Europe
What
Milkies
Olive Garden
There are white rocks
Look like in the air he's talkin
I'm about
Caveat Greece at the time was a bunch of different city-states
Too many of them operate
Differently it's what I'm going to get into isn't a representation of the picture of actual like
Panhellenic politics
Also just to leave the side this thing
You just talkin about ass
Also if there's also an important factor
Women and enslaved persons couldn't vote
And sometimes the ability to vote will be passed on generationally and sometimes inability to vote had to do with
Tyranny of the majority take this with a grain of salt
Alex is just talking about
Do you have any idea about anything else that was going on now your city-state
You can tell this because of the use of some specific words that he's using the very clear indicators of the ideas
The sentence of being thrown off a cliff or drinking poison remains of capital punishment because I was using the term Havelock
You can kind of get the picture
That's where that's where the knowledge begins in it
Democracy was rooted in the system of largely independent entity
There was the Boule which was a kind of it was a body that included Representatives
From all the tribes in Athens
Then there was the Ecclesia which was kind of like our Senate infected they argued laws
Maybe the House of Representatives
Bad analogy
You know I got you a sort of like a legal arguing body and then there was
Stereo which was the Judiciary
In addition to this tripartite executive branch
Apps with three archons Farm in the council that presided over the city-state
There was the pulley Marcos who was in charge of the military issues of the state
The eponymous archon who is the chief legal figure
In the zoo did B of the religious
These positions were not democratically elected as we understand them as they were always members of the aristocracy
And there was there wasn't like a legitimate vote to put anyone into
Position of being archon
If I what you were talking about elections of archons as being something that was really just a function of the In Crowd in the oligarchy
That would be fair but that's not really true the broader popular votes
It would take place within
There were many things that all male non-slave not indebted Athenians
Could vote on
Then just the way that Alex
Describing with colored rocks
Or often broken pieces of pottery called ostrich
It is true that there are a lot of things like proposed laws that if Union were allowed to vote on
But the specific stuff that Alex is talking about
Public votes
Like he's very
Clearly talking about Socrates and his Kyle was carried out by the dikasteria
Like Socrates stood accused
Crimes against the state
So his trial was a little bit more serious but there were often votes related to ostrich
Like where someone could end up getting banned
Stream the city-state by a vote
That's
Resume comes from
Africa the broken pieces of pottery
This is a process though that was initiated by the appliance guy and then voted on by all voting-eligible public
So that might be what Alex's conflating
Ability to ostracize someone from the city-state is being conflated with
Soccer
Ortiz's trial
Where he was sentenced
I'm being a little bit pedantic but the point is that Alex is using this very flawed understanding of Athenian democracy to uphold his stupid
Racist ideas about modern voting
Immigration
But I think it makes it important to talk about a little bit
If there's someone with an actual background in something from history that implicates
Current day issues it's usually a good idea to
Consider what they're saying
And that's the very thing that I was just trying to hijack
He's trying to pretend that he knows things about history that give him a better understanding of things happening
Present
But everything is talking about is really surface-level at best and wrong it worse
Yeah it seems like
He's learned literally everything
Scene from a movie
Yeah or just maybe someone telling him a story about soccer team
It's basically like
You know the kind of told him the story about Socrates like I did read the Republic tonight
Yeah or the apology would be the one about the trial
Lakeview
It's kind of like the level of knowledge that you get
From
That broke
Absolutely
I got high I was talking
And then I decided to remember that for the rest of my life has been
Yeah I think I think there is
Just a just a bad
Grasp
History that I was using to apply to his ears
How many just conceived
More messy in terms of History
Alarm
It's absolutely of them
True most ancient Greece
Alex's just talking about Socrates and pretending that he has a larger understanding
Greek socialpilot
In college ancient Greek was one of my miners
One semester was just translating Play-Doh
Apology in English before like in high school and I understood the broad Strokes of it but translating the original text was pretty
I opening
Experience
For one thing in English translations it doesn't come across fully how much are they how much Socrates was absolutely
Baking them
The Killer
He was suicidal.
Just that he was too cocky assholes that he was showing as much respect
Process
Has Alex does to the depositions we've heard him in
Literally most of it if I recall correctly was them being like
Please just go away or shut up and he's like you'll have to kill me
They're like no we don't want to
The notably one of these
Somebody has her punishment is like you guys feed me for the rest of my life
One of the other things that really stood out was
Exactly what Dynamics
Existed that we're leaving to his trial in the first
One of them was obviously the charge of corrupting the minds of the youth by way of questioning the official religion
Just use of estate
However there were other
Princeton Socrates was super opposed to democracy feeling instead that the ones who knew best deserve to rule
That he was carried out his people
Republic
In terms of
What Alex
Since talking about like the opposition to the state
Opposition.
I was going to say Socrates was more like the philosopher king
Style
The pain of Play-Doh
We get that
Political aspect of the trial of a group of oligarchs called the 30 Tyra
These dudes were pieces of s*** and they presided over
The killing of between 5 to 10% of the Athenian population
In a very short ruled they had there was less than a year
There was an uprising that took them out of power in 403 b c and 4 years later is when Socrates
I was tried and sentenced to drink a block
One of the 30 tyrants was kriti
Yes and associated
Socrates
Who is this such a friend of his there's one of them
Socrates his dialogues is named after him
Eddie appears in at least two others
Whether deserved or not the public was not hot on people who are friends with
4:30 after their ouster
And that may have played some part in the targeting of Socrates
The trial
Even so according
The apology and the later dialogue
Credo Socrates could totally is
Not Benedict at trial and been given the lighters
Or he could have escaped to Exile
A very willing
Do not go away
Just go away
Most Greek philosophers weren't killed by the
Plato and Aristotle both died of natural causes
Epicurus died of a urinary Stone and heraclitus died
From dropsy
This is an example of Alex's one of his favorite tricks
Adversity takes a little piece
Trivia that he knows about one thing
How many pretends it applies to a broader context of any presents that is true
I'm sure it's fun for him to kind of probably feels like
Like improv but
It's just lying
Who were philosophies who were thinkers
Am in Athens is not
Not really
Held up by Lake
Some of the more notable enlarger philosophers of the time I was surprised to read that they
Shots
Epic
50 this out of a trebuchet into the sun
That was a surprise
He was a scientific experiment
Could be.
That's not to say that throughout history there have been people who were like revolutionary thinker is that where Moline
Before the Revolutionary thought
But the way that I was trying to present this as it relates to philosophers
Rain in the city-state of Athens
Is not fair
He's just making sure. Because he knows a little bit about soccer
Which I think is
Anyway
Let's get back to Alex be racist
Mirador
Earwig
Star Wars
Water
Wow minorities around it's like the MOs Eisley Cantina
First off that was a that was a
Bar is great
The most wretched of scum and villainy
Somebody lost an arm but that's fine that's exact just a good bar that characterization of it is it's
Awful
It's
Yeah but that's from that's from Obi-Wan point of view he was a real stick-in-the-mud fair enough
I like that Alex went for the second stanza of
You didn't stop there
Wow rare that swinging jazz music dammit he's f***** up
I just looked up
How is the same person is like this Walgreens reminds me of the MOs Eisley Cantina
How many non-whites are
It'll come back up again of your thinking about going to see Planet of the Apes a hood
The Tower of Babel you're a witch
Who am I
Yeah we just talked about the town not on this episode on our previous episode of remember how you get into space
Oh yeah you're breaking into a world we live in
Facebook
Break my glass ceiling
This is this is f*****
That's insane
That's just insane
Especially because
Again I have never Associated ball-sized lie with any kind of racial component I was just like
It's what is it at all so that's the cool part of space
Turn the entryway purple aliens
Everywhere that's what I got excited about what I was a kid not according to Alex
To meet all these aliens
It seems like you're leaving that aside I don't disagree with you but
Largely expressing support for ethnostate
Strictly a I am not a white
Supremacist I'm a white nationalist and the black Nationalist and
Because race is not a
Constructed every group every race should have their own State and that because if you have to
I don't understand how you can defend himself against
These accusations is like you are awake
You want you got scared because they were too many non-white
Play really interesting to is the distinction
Between this like
The pool supply shop
He doesn't like to see indications that Muslim people can actually engaging
In culture normally just like everybody else
That was threatening to him
In terms of that
Function of
Integration
This is a little different
Even inasmuch as it's like
It's not about seeing
A lot
Of one group
Seeing
A lot of
See ya
Of different groups
Congregating together that's that's wrong
Really weird about it is
The
The number of different groups
It's something that any of itself is weird and threatened again
No this would be like bizarre this would be legitimately if like
In Star Wars
Luke walks into the MOs Eisley Cantina is like segregation now segregation forever like what
Are you doing
The Alex get to call about voter ID laws
Shorts
Fairly interesting
I should say that a large portion of the show that a sedative
Duck lips
Kind of Edibles bores me as a position that Alex has
Yes but it's very much in support of voter ID laws
Very much like he's ever going to get rid of voter fraud
This this called
Struck me as bizarre
Voter today
Florida
And when I went in there
Defiance against voter ID laws is being encouraged
This is weird
Well
I mean think about it this
Really the Walgreens example it's so so f******
Metallic
Because here's another thing that you could have in the Walgreens right
All white people
Okay don't white people in the Walgreens
But
There's one person from Ireland who doesn't speak English he only speaks Gaelic
There's one person from Sweden who doesn't speak English
Because they all look white and if they are not talking Alex will go in there and be like at all
And in the same way the voter ID laws
You just look at his face is white
You don't need you don't need an ID
Right
I think the assumption
Is that Alex believes himself to be talking
Come to a white collar
And so it's not such a big deal
That this person needs to be subjective
It's weird 100% the case
It's so glaring
But most of the show has been so in support of voter ID laws
And then this
Where this guy is saying like you have to show me the law where it says I have to show my ID or whatever
It's it's it's
Yeah it's disorienting you're just in
But
Unsurprisingly
Immediately after this
Experience with this collar
Deeply racist
I bet the jaw-dropping Lee racist
That is like
Here you go
I'm going to have you
Vote on this
Notebook
A special value Cannon real special ballot and you just have to go to the center of the ocean
Oh my god wow
Hot Springs
Saying that out loud isn't totally normal on Alex's show
It's not something that causes him to be like
Did you say something did he say how dare you
Condemn no
Mail-in voting comes up which we know that Alex believes as the scourge of of our electoral system
Seems like too much of a problem with it
I was calling about the
The balance in the mail
Everywhere
Well Fiore's already want no kind of taken over with the Priceless game
Animal Welfare
New weird I don't know if he is disputing with this guy is saying about mail-in voting but he definitely does
Doesn't have the same sort of
Passion behind
No that's a function of
The it's not a
Huge talking point
In 2014 it's not the right wing
Last Salvo
Had to prove that they like it was stolen
It's so funny to me how often he's telling on himself and then he would just that like
Wealthy they get all the compassionate and helpful people
And you like you realize what you just said right
The inverse of that is you
Do you realize that you said they get all the compassionate and helpful people
Beyond the GOP you attract the
Maligning and Evil
Misanthropic
So Alex gets another call and it's a guy who sells iodine
Just like Alex
And I thought this was a really boring call until it picks up
Really really fast
Obama
Naturopathic doctor in Virginia
Say that your ex to
DNA Force we've been having amazing
Detoxing the body
Just
Amazing
Actually repair
Whoa
So apparently this nature pathic doctor
Calling into Alex's show tunes
Mega dosing on x2
Has
Reverse homosexuality
I'm having
I'm having some problems
Can you prescribe me something well Alex Jones recommends this
It's not a prescription
Great great
Great great great
This is this is s***
Alex's
Supplements can reverse
Homosexuality
Now here's my question
What's the Texas
What's my month stand
I don't know what in the chemical needs
To take
It requires 6 to 9 months what part of the iodine or the zinc
Choir 6
29 months to activate I feel like I was just playing this
Clip guys at the altitude needs to be
Discus thrower picked apart I think it speaks for itself quite frankly
Real
Realshit
So here's another clip
Where Alex
Is it again
Condemning his future self
It has to do with a headline that he has kept reading over the course
A comment from an
Annex Nixon Aid
Shahu thanks
The GOP would be unwise to deal with
The Tea Party
No it's not Rodger
God dammit
Yeah but
Alex does end up saying something about the people who work with Nixon
Please stop
County Antoine
Republican
I talked all these people to work
Lead my Showdown a bizarre Direction
Is a
Nixon will also turn into an indictment of you bitching about what's Obama going to do with his pardon power
Oh true
Enjoy
Your you're
Looking at his past episodes
Just makes everything so stupid so stupid
Make the whole world really
Yeah I mean
The most important man in the world
Is about to show up
I can't believe I forgotten that he was going to be a article
This is
For drudge was a bad guy family or maybe I'm not sure
Transformed into the
Traitorous traitor
Yeah fight Hillary
What events I find really fascinating about this
This interview
Between Alex
Some Tucker is that
Tucker says some
In the wrong way
This first clip is is biting
Looking back
Can't really argue with it
There is a lot of movement
American Pie
Wrong again
Really hard to argue with that
People are going to politically moved
Go to places that they never imagined they would be
Yeah that's that's that's a very
Correct assessment of what happened with Alex
Joshua
That's also one of my big problems
With Tucker Carlson is
He could not be more aware of how he
Sure you know
Check with Alex we can always walk that stupid be evil Continuum in Tucker is
Clearly
A brilliant psychopath
There's that interviewed with Dave Rubin
He was talking about how he lies
Prescient
Another indication of
Use awareness of what keys
He's doing in the present
No idea what is
Dairy Queen
Willing to use rates
Motivated
Trade-in motivate
Beyond
Oh really Tucker
I refused his business model
Ignition of
Being aware of the consequences of engaging that way
Is pretty damning
Yeah but also recognizing the that he knows this is an effective way I mean just that
Send racial politics that's going to be using it cut
Now I'm going to do a three-part series on George Soros will not be answers America at all
I'm going to use
A video that says selectively edited shot by Harrison Smith to argue that white people can't get
Monoclonal antibody mean
Chest
Just so f******
It really is
Amazing
When you when you stop and do like
Tucker Carlson step back
And you think
I am shocked that human beings behave like
Like I can
It's almost like
What why
What are we doing
What are we doing that you can be aware that you're destroying the world where it where they're not like
Real consequences to people's lives
I think it would be
Academically
Incredibly interesting to see what
What is why do you do this what is it
Killing everyone
You're murdering millions of people I can't get any point
I've been set for the rest of his life
So it's
Really bizarre to imagine that the primary motivation would be money
I believe
Through the course of this and other interviews that he's done
In the past
I think it's piece of piece of s***
He's actually a really bad person
Cyclades expressing now
Actually things that he believed
Dismiss white nationalist nonsense
That's what he does on his show
I do believe that there's an opportunistic aspect of it that is like
Hey
It's okay to do this show
But I'd ever became such that it wasn't appropriate
He would change to something else
Do you like you would go
Neocon supporting the Iraq War
Absolutely we're not socially acceptable
And I think you would do that but
At the same time
I think deep down he's
Israel racist a******
Yeah man
That's another thing like
Why is s***
Like Jon Stewart
Just came out new like LED you need to engage with people
Thought I have his old like you famously engagement Tucker Carlson
And everybody was like all you destroyed him you kicked his ass
You're going to view he'll never work out got cancelled
And how did that work out
Well I think that there's another
Where's
Examples of
Score
Take his advice about that or his comments about that about Rogan aren't necessarily like
The dumbest
Nothing I just think it's a little bit later
Really help
Hey are you remember the Third
November 3rd we heard a description of what losers do I do remember
See if you think this sounds like a loser
It's almost like I went to the Hallmarks of being a loser is saying that pretending they're all your shifts going sky-high
Buddy else is falling apart
So I noticed something and it's really boring
This interview
Seems to be shiting on the media
About it
Very large piece of it
Really feels weird Elizabeth as interview with these dudes are just talk about how awful the mainstream media is well they
Pretend that they don't both have almost
Comically large conflicts of interest on the subject
Alex is someone who will never be invited back on any show because he
We can't control himself and start screaming at people whenever he's allowed on any TV show
He's a hostile abusive a****** who wraps up his intensity in order to turn it interview
Every time
It's a tacky and desk
Caught onto that Dynamic so Alex has a real chip on his shoulder about the media
Help no one wants him around
On the other side Tucker seems to be pretending that he was
Let Go by both CNN and MSNBC prior to his time at Fox
I feel like you brought up this disastrous Crossfire interview with Jon Stewart led to the show being cancelled Tucker
Publicly humiliated and then CNN decided not to renew his contract
His MSNBC show got cancelled for having low ratings I got replaced by Rachel Maddow
Hey look
Tucker is a f****** thirsty a****** in terms of public approval and attention
After MSNBC before Fox
He went on Dancing With the Stars which isn't something that a person is illegitimate
Be some concern that the stain for the big
Big media companies
Dancing with the Stars
Also use me for celebrity kicked off that season
There's an unspoken reason that these two guys shouldn't necessarily be considered the most unbiased sources on the media
Considering that they're both people
Financial incentive
Demonize the media
How to show only really as a reason Pig
Exist if the media sucks
Tucker's Daily Caller also benefits from people becoming disillusioned with
Actual journalist
Overall though I was pretty surprised to find this interview was so much about just bashing the media
Like it's supposed to be election day coverage but instead of hypothetical coverage but how the media is going to cover thing
I bet they're going to really that stupid
Compelling radio
I find it to be
A dud
This is how the Democrats
They're going to lie
A made-up thing that I said and you know what tomorrow I'm a
A little bit of election talk
But it also is a little bit
Composition of the
Holyshit
So here we see even more Proto great research replacement to conspiracy talking points
Casually thrown out by Alex and Tucker
It's much much as it's important to recognize how much of a piece of s*** Alex's and that
The people are shelmore Les Tucker is more than onboard with this whole thing that immigrants voting away is precious white free
I have for California being a one-party State it's fair to say that the state generally swings to the left
Just a few years prior to this the governor of the state was Arnold Schwarzenegger who's a Republican
The state is considered a safe bet for Democrats in the general presidential election but that wasn't the case in fairly recent history
Republicans carried the state and every Alexa
Send from 1968 to 1990
Elected representatives are mostly Democrats are still plenty of Republicans
State Assembly as well as the state senate
They're even 10 members of the House of Representatives in California are Republican
Including the minority leader Kevin McCarthy
Logic
Just doesn't work
Work to make this about immigration either because
Big juicy in California where most officials are Democrats
But there are number of Republicans in there too
Sintex
Most elected officials are Republican but there are some Democrats
It just like the California
It borders Mexico just like
California with a bunch of immigrants
Yeah
Grievance Obsession being treated as if his actual politics
Something to Tucker's been on board with an arguing in favor of since before Trump was around before he
I still think stalkers a fraud
The lot of this races
List
I do think that
Yeah I would like
Was not able became unacceptable to do his wife Power Hour show that he does now
He would go away for a little while and he'd repackage like a like a wrestler
Justin
Decided it isn't going to work anymore let's try a new character for you
But underneath I do think that I racist she would still exist
I mean it would be it would be even more
Depression
And nice
For both alexson and Tucker to a just been like
Inhaler
What I believe doesn't matter I'll say whatever and how crazy is the media they're just going to keep hiring me
Just a name
Are going to hire for no reason
I don't have any ability and I'm a terrifying psychopath recently Tucker Carlson
Most known as a pie
Punchline wore a bow tie and got humiliated by John Stewart
I don't understand why he has purchased
In any kind of job market well I mean
Traditionally white aristocrats
Oh good morning pretty well
Yeah I guess so
So Alex play the clip of Obama
I think pretty witty
I believe this is Obama telling people
You'll get out there and folk multiple times
Y'all get out there
Bota bota
Voter ID laws
Sorry
So Tucker isn't that stupid as to think that the only reason you could oppose voter ID laws is what you want to allow voter fraud to take place
Not that dumb
Cover for his actual position which is from the right to vote
There been many studies about hair discrimination is baked into many of the various voter ID requirements
Estates of implemented
One of the main ways this was achieved was by making seemingly arbitrary decisions about what forms of ID would be
Considered valid for voting
What states like North Carolina allowing various types of ID that were disproportionately held by white voters
And not allowing ones that were disproportionately held by non-white voters
Studies Amidon they're also shown that voter ID laws are not apply universally in Highwood discriminatory bias
How they're enforced
There was a Caltech MIT study done about the application of voting laws in New Mexico
Hispanic voters were asked for ID more frequently than white voter
Tucker understands all this s*** but in order to make his position socially acceptable to hold
He has to pretend that he doesn't understand any of this
Voter ID requirements are perfectly Fair
Perfectly effective as a means of stopping in-person voter fraud
And also at which also basically doesn't ever happen
In real world
According to the ACLU between
2020-17 quote
There were only 31 credible allegations of voter impersonation
The only type of fraud that photo IDs could prevent
During the. Of time in which over 1 billion ballots were cast
Have you been these credible allegations are often just
Honest mistakes people made as opposed to attempt
That's actually illegal to vote
Nonexistent problem
On the Tucker and Alex are trying to solve
Because the solution they're advocating actually served their real agenda
Which is disenfranchising the voting rights of non-white America
The whole song
It's it's
Like
Truly
Dumb
Or running
Informed on issues
But I might believe that they
Heard somebody
We say there's no reason to oppose voter ID laws except for if you want a bet
Voter fraud so let me explain that to you and we can have a conversation Tucker is not that person.
You know
I know exactly why we're people with
Disagree with voter ID laws
And what they don't know is
I'm actually
We just erase it they have no idea that what I'm saying
Is it true and I don't believe
Myacura Secret
I am a racist
Yeah
It's a little bit transparent
They make a big mistake
Alex and Tucker
And the first call that they get
I think it's a really
Interesting perspective
Get brought up and Alex
Is
Not happy about it
In Pennsylvania
Alex
Tucker Carlson
And I just wanted to say that
Pelicula website is really an aberration and conservative media in terms of
Disrespect
Short women that it hasn't website
Over-sexualized
Well Alex is really fast and aggressive trying to run cover for Tucker
Read about the strawman to protect him from this colors criticism
It's really fascinating as a thing to see the offensive Alex God and how quickly it went down
This color has a question about the Sexes with the Daily Caller in an order to protect
Feelings and to make sure the audience doesn't take the scholars Point seriously
Alex tries to immediately find a way to distort her Point into being so how about how the
The existence of man has sex
This obviously isn't what you saying but the goal Alex is shooting for his
The bait and respond to this dummy argument instead of sticking to our initial point
Which is threatening to Alex and Tucker
Her self-image
You see this kind of thing with Alex all the time because his actual positions are mostly
Indefensible
If you wanted to argue about like Refugee or immigration issues with him he just yelled back at you something like
So you support illegal immigrants coming here and telling US citizens
Where he feels more secure
Secured and where there is no real chance of anything productive
Devine discuss
The reality is that the Daily Caller is a long and pretty noted sexism problem
What example of this was in 2013
This episode
When Ashley Judd was
Considering running
For the headline
Ashley Judd potential US Senate candidate sure has done a lot of on-screen nudity
In an attempt to preemptively delegitimize her as a potential candidate they used Mister skim as a resource
The document the times that she's been nude in movies
To the pretty shity wait for someone
Pretending to be a new site
No I mean there's nothing
It's about that sure they do it for all the mail a
Actors who've tried
How many times has
Arnold Schwarzenegger bench
Shirtless in a movie
Whatever Central roast of presidential candidate
Plenty more examples of ism The Daily Caller but I think the actual larger problem
The lead writer for
Tucker's fox show but to resign effort came out today
Posting file racist
Alexis schitt online for years
Little boy prolific writer at the Daily Caller having almost 2,000 articles
Zombicide with his byline
One of them that was particularly shity was from October 2016
It's described in a Media Matters article like this
Quote best describes a driver running over a group of Native Americans protest in Columbus
Conquest of America
The article ran with a sub headline that read quote white man overruns indigenous peoples with Superior technology
Daily Caller is a pile of s*** publication that produces the exact kind of racist
Austin Texas contact that Alex wants
See the world
And also has the Veneer Wood
Bi-Rite we bring some of this stuff up
Then it's his job to run interference and create strawman argument
Try to get this collar off balance
You'll notice that sucker didn't say anything
That was all just Alex feeling the need to
Defend Tucker
Leslie both end up looking bad
Yeah
Really
You know how you know how in
In trials and s*** whenever it turns out like
Like 10 years later that the
The cop
Who is the witness at your trial was a f******
Coke dealing corrupt piece of s*** you know and then everybody who
Who was involved with that cop
Has the chance to relive everything reopen
If your
Writer turned out to be a massive racist like you have to go back through every article he's ever written
Put a new headline up there that says massive racist wrote that
All I get asked to be like a whole system
I think you do have to do some pretty hard soul-searching
If you have somebody who is a flagrant races
Posting horrible s*** online
Anu it turns out he's been writing for you for years
He's our lead writer on your TV show
And he has over 2000 articles on your website
Should open the box
Locks up
And see how
How
Much.
Acted his coverage how much it impacted your show and he was leader
You don't do that because that was part of why he works there
No no I mean I'm telling on themselves again it's awful that we had to let him go because we agree with everything that he's written huh
Yeah it what these meddling Libs
Good news is
We have
No reason to believe the Tucker Carlson has agreed with any of his thoughts
Except for a lot of
So unfortunately I have bad news actually has a different point
Then the real argument about sexism
Actually she has more of a puritanical
This with
Read article
Sexy girls
3 years and has three daughters
Trying to sell products
Prosecuted
Quite
Tell if this was her Point going off track because of Alex's lancerpoint
Either way I don't think this is
The really good way for the point to be made about Daily Caller sexism
Which is unfortunate because it is a legitimate point.
Could be brought up in is
At least sort of raised by this caller
Rivers goes off track Amanda Alex and Tucker
Alright
Yeah they're they're shown to be
The innocent I do think this was her original point
Because before she was cut off
She started talking about how
That this
Contribute as much as the
Left the bottom I think she is trying to say that
I'm tired of
Both the right and the left
Six update good with whatever
I mean I don't know
I guess
Alex has decided that because
The Scholar was critical
Probably was a false
Show on the women of the IDF
Hilarious
Very light-hearted way
Serious or creepy bad at all
Maxim
I mean
I don't know look
Look at these sexy apartheid enforcers
It's very weird
So Tucker
Has a guy in the Senate that he's a fan of
Strom Thurmond
Surprisingly
Stan has a record of consistently opposed invivo tonight sac
And has open hostility towards
He's such an anti-venom right a****** that when he was nominated for a federal judgeship by Reagan in 1986
He was rejected due to concerns about his comments on race
ACP the southern Christian leadership conference Operation Push in the National Council
Churches were all on American organization teaching anti-American values
He also said that organizations like the n-double-acp quote
For civil rights down the throats of people
Or courses
Mixing irohazaka geisendorfer.
But the clan okay until I learn to smoke pot
Sure gestations isn't honest and principled
Manners
Very honest and principled about his racism in opposition to voting rights for non-white people
It tracks the Tucker would like to see him as the most popular member of Congress
Subway
Fun it is going to be an uphill battle for that one I'll tell you I'll tell you that right now
Yeah
So this interview was was bizarre because
There isn't like a
A ton of obsequious nationality
There's no indication that this person
Possibly be the most
Person in the world someday
It's really just shiting on the media
Yeah it does seem to be that they're on relatively equal power footing
At this point
Time above
Yeah it's a contributor on Fox but I have his
Interesting dynamic
Outrageous amount of racism
Those flying around prior to Tucker coming on
The man even while he's there he's engaging with it
Yeah with Alex
Hello
I found this to be a little bit of an underwhelming episode from the standpoint of like
Learning about the midterms
I am seeing some kind of alike
Good dynamic
Between him and Tucker the might tell us something
About the future
I think the only thing that you could take away from this
As it relates to what you would expect
These guys do have a bit
The philosophical alarm
Visa vie
Non-white people should
I guess that is the Bedrock of their relation
Jeff you can kind of see it that way
One last clip
Here and Alex's another conspiracy theory about that collar
I was critical of the Daily Caller
What time
Great great stuff
You know it it sucks
Sucks
Really hard because
It is like
God damn it if people were
Taking this as seriously as
F****** was
Cuz this isn't
This wasn't new in 2014 it wasn't new in 2008
It wasn't new
It what it was new and Reagan
You like this is s*** that should have been Stamped Out
And instead every f******
10 years we just go
Well they haven't killed anybody for a while so let's just let it
Ride
Yeah I am not talking about the control
The ideological patience
That
People see
Seem to have
With a lot of these incredibly intolerant ideas
Necessarily lead to
The things that we see happening
It's absurd it is it is strange
Is there today patience
Exist
Yep that's crazy
I mean I don't I don't
I don't know why that exists in a larger sense I think with Alex
What I said earlier
Kind of is relevant that is it
Most people who aren't
Like me
You don't want to listen to a whole episode of
It speaks to something wrong with me
I get that
Most people want to live their lives and just have a normal existence share
Where is I want to play Dynasty alert about that
So I get it
I think that wreck
Recognizing exactly what is being conversed
About
Behind
The flimsy arguments about like well we really should have voter ID because it'll make things more secure
Is
Behind that is a guy who's
Saying that
Too many minorities at Walgreens is Mos Eisley Cantina
And that girlfriend was almost kidnapped
Bad because his Austin downtown is a war zone of a roaming black gangs
Yeah I mean maybe the simplest
The simplest explanation for why it were so tolerant is because
Everybody
Treats
The
Right wing
As though
They're speaking
Honestly
I mean
Really go back
And look at like a presidential debate
Without being like Oh you
You you just lied
And nobody said
You're a f****** liar you're a liar who's lying right now you can't say that to take it back
Stop lying
I'm not lying prove I'm lying
Public trust is eroded
It's so much that there's not even the extra
Vacation
The death of an unspoken
Brutal
Yeah I don't know
I think it sucks
But we learned when we put Alex on timeout
Welearn
We reaffirm
This s*** runs deep we got to put Alex on the timeout he's a monster in a certain way would go see him be a monster in a different way
I forgot to put Alex in the past on timeout
Maybe maybe reset Wars reset water
Maybe that'll be coming up
But until then Jordan we have one
We do have a website at telecharge.com
Antonio and Leon bvx clerk up there
And now here comes
Lukas X robe