Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge right now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
June
We are damn door.
Tweets about Joe Rogan
Play the Mario Party
My buddy Nikki gift
History of playing Mario Party
Together back in the days
He's back in the Columbia day
We would do what we do is we would play 50
Who's this
I'm one of the GameCube version
The Mario party that was Pagoda Peak
The star never moves
You just go up
This mountain and then you start back at the bottom
And we would
Just get really high
And like have a long playlist of music and just a call to Mario Party
The
The worst
That's like
A great day
Superstars or whatever
The f****** dog
Another of the capability of
If playing remote games
It's going to be living different cities and such
Of course you do like all the time
You're an absurd person
No no that's not true I'm really bad at many games
I was really expecting I was going to end up lose
But I think
I think what happened was I got to have winning because Nick ended up like randomly losing a star
On
The second-to-last her landed on a Bowser space
So great thank you technology for
Catching up you got one in the positive several thousand in the negative but you got one in the positive tab
My bright spot is the flowers that I ordered for my partner were delivered
For today
Tweet about that yesterday
Maybe today is today Valentine's Day
Add was if you recall we had the truck
Chocolate strawberry
I ordered both of them on the wrong day so this year I was like
I'll make a joke off of that
And I'll order the flowers to be delivered a week early and it'll be like a you know it'll be a reference we'll all have a giggle and they'll be
Flowers at the end of it
I was going to be a surprise for she's going to hit you over the head with a bouquet of flowers
How to be a surprise
And then they didn't show up last night
So so all the sudden surprise over in advance
Why she didn't know they were coming that's what I realized today your Grande didn't show up I was like I could have just said nothing
Ono said what I got her with sadness
The Joker doesn't work if it's 6 days early as opposed to Second
I just said it was just it was just a massive
Screw up on my part
Could have gotten away with it
But alas they still didn't show up in the Great
That impulse
This is very strange
The need to explain the lack of a surprise
To somebody
There's no expectation that I was carrying that I just couldn't handle anymore
To deal with it
Alright Jordan today speaking of needing emotional support we will need a little bit of a crutch
Get through this Alex Jones I don't know
That was a transition on my part I'm usually fairly good but that was
It was a bee
So we'll be talking about all right
February
And one reasons I decided to do this episode
Do the episode and Alex
The beginning that he's hosting off
4 hours
On Sunday
Usually he does 2 hours
And then Owen comes in for around a mile I live
Justice funny
It is but there's no sketches there's no characters which is unfortunate
Characters come into
The Weekend Update
But
Pete Davidson
Totally cool with Infowars
She's ready for Primetime baby
Look good like
Maybe a Burt Reynolds
I would just say
Jason Schwartzman from Rushmore
And that's it
I think you can pull it off Sunday Night Live as well and so like I was like
Okay I'm going to
Treat this like it's a full-on episode but then
Sunday Night Live episode isn't posted on Alex unbanned on video and I can't find it and so
Anyway to this episode
But not at all
If you're looking for an in-depth
Like
Important episode
Might not be alright
Where's screw this is gross.
Does Emily wants dirty
Unscramble
Apocalypse
Scallops
You're doing the best you can and that's all anyone can ask of you love Mike
You and I hope all is well
Lego
Bill Cooper's tax returns thank you so much
Thank you very much
Color dress
Spell journal
Thank you very much
First
Steve G from Gilberts
Thank you so much for an hour
Or how I learned to stop worrying and love the siop
Thank you so much
What's your name
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Go take a little break you down
For me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the
Was legitimately having break
I'll be better tomorrow
I'm not sure if he is better but this is a this is a real just Infowars ass episode
Bread-and-butter there's not there's not outbursts
Please not morose
You just ate just put his hat on clocked in and he got through the day it's just a show
Actually honestly tonight
It's just going to be okay we have to do it even if we don't have a wonderful Dover you tonight
That's Alex starting his Sunday Night Live monologue
What are contractually obligated
Here's where he starts with the headline
And a little bit of fairness here
First off
You all know what happened
And that is Bloomberg put out the headline that
Russia attacks Ukraine
For what then supposedly
Unfolded
Just before the last two Iraq Wars as well
Today
But the
Russian
The new name
I absolutely agree
That might have lost something in translation
Really get too much into this
Psyop
Bloomberg did this
To do that now but if this sucks
That someone actually within the organization to Bloomberg actually got fired
Mistake
Tube long short of what happened is that Bloomberg as well as many other internet-based media organizations
Create dummy pages with headlines many possible outcomes and headlines
Is it could happen
In any given
7 day or week in order to get a jump on things
Text because there's a perverse incentive in that mediaspace be the first
With something to report
Because of this obsession with immediacy they don't have pages that are about things that haven't happened yet or may never happen
I'm in this case somebody accidentally published that draft
Page of Russia invading
This is not an unheard-of situation
Like one of the times has been a topic
The conversation online was in terms
Prepared obituary Pages for a number of celebrities who are still alive
But we're out there folks that might die and it would be big news if they did
Then again in 2020 Radio France Internationale had about 100 draft obituaries for celebrities
That accidentally got published
And in the process they falsely announce the deaths
Soccer Legend
Yoko Ono and Jimmy Carter among others
Correction they went and killed all of those people at home
Our stake situations
Makes this Bloomberg
Situation here a larger f******
Visit geopolitical Minefield so they should be overly careful but
Even so
Doesn't seem like it's anything more than them
Mistake
If you ever track breaking news on large media sites like cnnr Bloomberg
You'll know that often the pages for these breaking stories are little more than a headline and a brief synopsis of what information is available
Available
Just been updated as new details come out
Again
Because of these businesses
The model that they have the so highly values who got the story out first
It makes total sense that these organizations would look for whatever strategies they could use to shave a minute
Off their time to press
Unless Alex
Demonstrate otherwise this is a mistake that
Shouldn't have been made but doesn't
To be an instance of
Conversely
Everything Alex does everyday and basically every headline on Infowars is a malicious and intentional attempt
July so I'm not going to take
You can play for this 12 series
Yeah there was one of those just today I
From like The Hollywood Reporter about how Spider-Man in no way home with snow
Oh yeah yeah
And once again that little pre-written
Blur but once again
Academy is snubbed Marvel and instead nominated XXX
, XXX
, exactly like all you wrote that yesterday and I didn't think they would do that
Marvel movies are not going to get nominated for Best Picture
Someone is going to want to read that story
That's the worst-case scenario is it does get nominated and then you throw out the draft
There is no downside to it
Unless you accidentally published another country
That is a dunce
Bloomberg to do an internal audit
Do things baby they can fire somebody
I don't know
Also I would say the maybe it's
Not a great idea for the media to operate in the state where they're busy
This model relies on living with the possibility that someone could accidentally post a headline that leads to a war
Maybe they should readjust those those priority
How is it
Is it possible to write that to pre-write the
War started story
Without
Losing your f****** my
Right
Like that
Requires some sort of ability to go to a different place to pre-write like
Millions of people are about to die in a blink
You know like that's crazy I'm crazy
Yeah
Yeah I don't know I mean how do you write any headline
What's the question
You need to go back to the elementary
So Alex has some ideas about Russia's various
Adventures
Wednesday on their border
I got up one morning
Desktop
There was a headline on
Drudge
The shower real quick
By the time I got to work in about
Clock
Others they were actually well directions
Contagious
That they came in
That was all true
What's 3
Some of the areas
Border and
Contingently
In southern Ukraine
That's really interesting Club because I think it tells you two things immediately
Play that are weird
The first is that Alex is somehow okay with Russia's invasion of Ukraine back in 2014 because he thinks they did it first
40 degrees
I guess if that's the standard needed to justify invasions I can't imagine oh Alex
Scooby a post of literally any military action
Can ever
Invade
Texas score
To get their oil reserves for crisis
Interested
Big fat Justified
Sissy Dadeland you just got
You learned is that Alex believes in a completely false version of what happened
Between Russia and Georgia in 2008
How to story just isn't
True the picture of what led up to that 5-day Wars
Is very complicated involves things like NATO's Bucharest Summit Decker declaration which
With plans to have Georgia and Ukraine join the organization
An act that was a hard line for Russia
It involves things like the Georgian president Mikhail Saakashvili I haven't Ambitions to reintegrate the regions of
South ossetia
Anaplasia in
Into the larger state
Movie where territorially within Georgia Sovereign borders they operated is essentially Breakaway States
And Saakashvili made it to political priority to be the one that reunited the country
Which naturally was
Also a hard line for Russia
Who felt like they were actually in charge of those reach
The pictures what happened to 2008 isn't really a subject of some Grand can
Conspiracy
No interest in Alex's real take on it
Except
As much as
This is a clearly part of continuing to establish his pre-emptive narrative
But if anything happens in Russia and Ukraine Russia is
Blameless
And it's going to be a globalist
Just out here
Get through the day
Right
Putin
Is an honest
Hard-working gentlemen he wakes up at 6:30 he put
His shoes on
He puts his pants on after that cuz it's a little bit different in Russia
But it goes to work like the rest
Okay goodnight
You can talk to
Bury it it's strange
Because I think that Alex
Just
Buys
Any anything that comes out
From that mediaspace and I think it's I think it's largely
They just built on
A steadfast oppositional defiance
To Western news
Despite the Russia being somehow a beacon of the West
Also
Well then it's the beacon of the West
In his understanding
White masculinity
Yeah
Yeah it is it is strange
I'm Amazed by anybody who can't
Have more of a clear-eyed picture of geopolitics
It's just like a
I don't think there's any good guy
You know
And it's
It's kind of rare that there is a like
A demonic bad guy
And I would never like
Come to the defense of cell
Military action
No no it's totally okay cool cool for Russia to blow this week no
No it's not.
I think it in addition to what you're saying like there's not really necessarily quote-unquote good guys
There's also does not like
Clear and on complex
Situation
That lead to these guys
Yeah. Like Crystal Clear like yes
The globalist
Wants to do this and so they will
Fake something in order
I don't know children's story books about like
How these things happen
It's annoying
Lie down play
The amount of just
Opera opportunism that is involved in global politics
Something happens
And then somebody just seized the opportunity to jump
Like I don't think Russia is I don't think Putin is trying to invade Ukraine
If there isn't a massive dip in
Trust in the United States
Ability of the UN to the backup at statement the worst stuff is also dudakov you don't like or
Meeting in January that reaffirmed Ukraine's desire to join NATO like there
There's
There are reasons that are pictures to this that just
The other thing too
There's a real
Agency that Alex describes
To himself and people like Trump
And then there is a lack of agency
And like the individual desires people have
As world leaders
It just seems to be absent everything is just like weird pieces on a board
Except for
Or maybe Ron Paul
There's the players and then there's Ron Paul and then everybody else is the game like the Georgia situation and
Particular was one
Where you know president Saakashvili
Was
Driven
To reunite the country
Based on what he felt was the Mandate when he came into power in
And so like
Being able to bring in one of the territories as he was
Did not work
That was
And for as much as Alex
Cares about Sovereign borders
Is it seems like they can be awfully fungible
Wow when it's on Russia
It's strange it's
It's real it's real weird I don't think it's a
Fuel teacher Russia or anything
Speed of an opposition to the
Existing International order
That he views as
Yeah
Anyway he's just really really invested in trying to build up this pre-emptive narrative
But if anything happens
Volkswagen
So you can profit off
Right
That's what they're getting ready
It's incredibly dangerous
Incredibly bad
Carlson on Friday.
Job
Atlantis all outside normally are
His whole
Monologue
But we're going to do it
Today because
Because you didn't
Such a great job
Let me be clear
It's often entire Tucker Carlson monologue
If this is not something that he rarely does
Give you a lot Checker do about 15
Pretty pretty regularly on his show like Hill
The first six minutes of the show is like
Not broadcast on what radio stations
Centennial play
Like John bound and Gregory's reports
During that time and he'll also sometimes just
Play Tucker Carlson
Monologue
Yeah
It's
It's like he's in the folder Special Report
But I don't think he can Center
No but also at the same time what's he going to do
Suum
You know like 08 if Tucker Sue's Alex Jones great for copyright
Give it to me or it to me now is Fox news's property
It sucker sucker to go to them and be like hey I I think you should let him play mellow out
So Alex has some other things
About various
Russian related War
Matters
He seems to be having some weird positions on
Globalist anti-American new Allure
Did you take my word for it
It's true
Movie production
Production was the white helmets in the blue helmet
Wm.com
Along with a bunch of the Islamic
Insurance agent
Sade
Which later came out
And worth
And a little boy
Dying for the nerve gas he went on
Take a note
From the kids
I mean all of that
What the globalist
Sounds very wrong about the larger picture of chemical attacks carried out by Assad in Syria but
He has
Possibly because a lot of the people he talks
Do about geopolitics are Putin and Assad apologist right
And propagandists
But you get to the larger subject of the attacks probably be too broad of a subject to get into right now
Really make specific claims better
Anything so
It's really hard to nail things down
Button
He did use
Specific discuss that a little bit
Balance brings up this Syrian boy who was videotaping Street treated for
Exposure to a chemical attack in
Duma in April 28th
He says that he later came out and said that this was all fake and that he was paid
To be in the video
Somebody claims Alex is making here are actually true
But it's critically important to us
Understand the context of what he saying
Because in that light
It becomes clear that these things he's correct about
Just revealed how wrong Alex is about they larger
So the question is eleven-year-old Hassan diab who's seen on video having his eyes washed
After a chemical attack
In the video that this is video that made the rounds really quickly because
It was
Or something where everything that was going into the city people couldn't get out
Should I eat this footage
Getting out was
You're very
So this obviously was very threatening as an image
Looks like a sodden
His backers like Russia
Campaign that launched
To discredit this video and use it as proof that the humanitarian groups are actually propagandist Liars
Who are the u.s.
Hey to attacking
Syria
The way they set up to do this
Was to release an interview on the state-owned Russia 24 Channel
Where the album is interviewed and says
That there was
Attack
And he didn't know why people were putting water on
I didn't say that he got paid
To say these things
You got food
From the
These are my parent
There's a video that Alex has seen and is the basis for his contention the people were faking being the victim
Chemical weapon
Send a text but I would strongly suggest that Alex should look a little bit deeper into the reality of that video
It's full of red flag
Video of shot Russian military took over to Alma and then refuse to let in
Inspectors from the organization
For the prohibition of chemical weapons in
Until 2 weeks after that point
At least partially due to possibly legitimate
Concerned about their safety to unexploded munitions
Some part of it that was
Illegitimate
Concerned but it also has a little bit sketchy
Conclusive
In the meantime this video with Diablo shot not in DOMA
But in Damascus
Guess which is about
Half hour drive away
Initially the reporter for russia24 was evasive about the context
The interview that they did
But eventually came out that it was done at the Syrian Army Officers Club
A location that was generally full of Russian military and
You know it's it's like how whenever you want
To have an interrogation you know you want
To have the if I'm being interrogated I want to have
Like 30 police officers all pointing guns at my head while I asked
But Isaac
The journalist
Been down there but the intercept
Reported on
An exhaustive crowdsourced search for images of the ex
Exterior of the building and its staff
Definitely there
Three uniformed military guys in the background for part of the report something that doesn't scream of this is above board
Put up any quote insisted they were merely on their way to a local cafe
The reality is that it's just not possible to take this interview at face value there's just
Far too many places where intimidation could
Be present
And it seems sketchy
And things that are being said about
The context of the video are shown to not be accurate
Knightcite
It should be allowed
And in fact
I think
Required by law
To throw a handful of flour into the face of any military person saying
They were on their way to a cafe
Go fuc
Dare use a baguette
Dare you send flower farm
Do you want to try that again
Another was right in the face
So then there's another really serious problem with a video which is at the end they purport to be interviewing a former militant
Claims that he made stage Victor
Adam videos
Stalking Zee news report shows images of a group of people creating stage shots of victims
Clearly implying that this is corroborating with the interviews of the
Talking about inner actually shots of him and his crew creating fake videos.
The demonizer sauce instead they were lifetime Recreations that were the video is very clearly trying to make the
That point however
These are still images from the shooting of a dramatic
Film directed by who mom who sorry
A Syrian filmmaker
He's making a movie where the plot revolves around a dramatized version of a previous chemical attack that he lived
Through in
The intent to mislead
Is very clear here and these
It is very real concern
All existing in
A couple minute long
Video it's
Very very hard to trust
Yeah then in 2019 the organisation for the prohibition
Chemical weapons
But at their final report about the attack in douma
Their conclusion was quote
Regarding the alleged use of toxic chemicals as a weapon on the 7th of April 2018 at Doma the Syrian Arab Republic
The evaluation and Analysis of all the information gathered by the FSM
Witnesses testimonies environmental and biomedical samples analysis results of Toxicology and Ballistic analysis
Expert additional digital
Information from Witnesses
Provide reasonable ground
That the use of toxic
Chemical as a weapon
This toxic chemical
Contained reactive
Corian
Chemical was likely molecular chlorine
Anyway the point here is that I'll do the chemical weapon attack denier and he accepted that
Very dubious video is being real
Because of the firm the conclusion he's already
Decided to believe
Namewee that Russia and everyone they're aligned with are actually always in the right
Because they are
Poised
Against
The international
Community vet
He thinks
Right right
So in so doing
He is Twisted himself into a place
Where did
Defending people who cover up
Horrific atrocities
Because of
Strategic
I guess so yeah I had to admit that
These attacks are real
Like
There's a part of him that seems like they had to do that while you're fighting the devil
I understand that we don't
Do these rules
Civil War stuff but
You know what when you're fighting an enemy this bad anything's okay see it's really strange I think it's
Abhorrent and they find it
To be the sort of thing that
Doesn't get maybe enough attention
In terms of some of his positions
But I think in hindsight
It's something that
Maybe Morella
Yeah
That I think should haunt
Should linger so many things should be haunting people
So many things
So Alex gets into talking about China and the Olympics
Not really the Olympics
Sort of the Olympics
Thereabouts or someone who was at the Olympics
I was trying to do a live remote shot
The Chinese authorities got in the leg
A few days ago
Speaker of the House
Do not criticize anything when you're in China
Are you get dishes
Appeared
Reporter TV
Videos posted up on Infowars
Cam
Hold off by
Myccp
During Olympics
Live report
Because they didn't like
What he had to say you see the red armband
Of the five
Policeman
2A
Police rosselli reportedly will be
Deported
Davey's Locker
It disappeared
So to be clear the way of the Chinese beliefs shut down those that reporter's live shot at the Olympics
Just kind of chilling
It's not acceptable really
Alex is a bit out of line sing the guy was
Beard
When someone disappear is disappeared they disappear
In this case the reporter wasn't even dragged off to a facility to be deported like Alex
Just claiming
He was accosted by the police but no one was hurt and then like a minute later he was able to reset in
Start broadcast
Bowser's making up all this
There's a lot of issues of press freedom in China and it's a scary incident but
Literally making
Yeah
It's not true what happened
Again
You do not need to do
With China
Well if you would like an example
Sensor disappeared
It's not hard to find one you don't need to make it up
Right but it would require you to do a little bit of work
Yeah that's true
Where is the alternative is
You can watch a video that you saw on Twitter and that make up a story about it man that sounds so much easier
I'd rather do that
I would say to our athletes
You're there too
Do not risk
Incurring the anger of the Chinese government because they are roof
Honestly if Alex were the speaker of the house I imagined is stable be like something
Similar play to be way more Sensational and angry
Anyways disagree with Pelosi
CNA sport any athletes
They feel the need to protest witches
Confusing because
These people like Pelosi a globalist
Blob working towards the same goal
So doesn't compute how they have disagreements like this about a geopolitik
Weird all of them possibly be true
Somewhat stupid
And you as well
Going to go out on a limb and say it's probably bad if if you're the Speaker of the House
Just be like
Shut up
The government
F****** kill you that's that might be a little bit aggressive it's certainly untactful
Bissell Little hunt text
I would
If I were her maybe
Express things lightly
I like maybe I see what I weigh weigh has to think about you know he was there for the last time
China hosted the Olympics and he has bad thoughts about it I'll buy you that right now didn't go well for him and then the White House
Express things better than like smoke them if you got them Let your freak flag fly
What is it Anyway
I thought when we voting for Democrats the idea was
Veridian
Little bit more adult they don't time where is much I guess
Self-control which comes with age
Look
This is
Weird Alex decides I don't know exactly why
But besides that he needs
Layout with
The world powers are
Although that's a bad idea for him
Yeah it's a little strange I found this to be really dumb
Competing tyranny
To the globalist
And there are competing powers
The European Union
Those are the major power structures of the government
Combine
There is
Parsley
The Communist Chinese and there's a Russian
Above that is the day Bose group
NAU an
Animals
Decorations
The New World Order
And an Ender
Military arm that is the UK
Why do you ask
And a commonwealth Nation
Quasi
Commonwealth
Chanel on every channel they celebrated the Queens
70th year of rain today
British intelligence
U.s. government
By what they've all written books
Denied
A PhD level
Your classes
Georgetown
But you are in the Queen's service
Do that part of the end there about how this isn't tonight at the PHD level
Talk to be under the
Just Alex Griffin about things he has made up about Carol Quickly's book tragedy and Hope
You can tell because he reference Georgetown and that's a dead giveaway
Also my dad got his PhD from Harvard and he claims that they never mentioned
Being under the
So Department
Suspicious benefit dead
When I was a kid he was a big fan of things like fault
L h i x
You're taking notes and I appreciate that because
This power structure is sloppy
You can see my notes
Camaros
So there are four base
Music governmental powers
Which is the US
Also known as the anglo-american established
The EU
Russia and China
This seems wildly simplistic considering that it means that there's literally no power structures that matter in South America Central America
Africa the Middle East
Southeast Asia
Matthew's nut
Weather got their own stuff going on
So then there's the Davos group and the UN by which Alex actually made the world economic
Look for him at the UN
Who make up a new world order along with some other ngos Alex doesn't want to specify
They rule over the
The four other powers or three depending on if you want to pretend that the anglo-american group in the EU
About there a little bit in cuz I'm a little late correctly he said that they were a little bit a lot
Yes scaccia
Apparently the top-level has full control over the anglo-americans of the
EU but not China and Russia which is why we have articles online about the queen
I really don't know what to say about this other than to say that I think it's a stupid it serves as a
Simplify be incredibly complex picture of geopolitical
Most of the world isn't even at
And Alex's
Conception of things which is weird
They're ton of examples of this whole thing into question
Brexit
Like the EU
UK wasn't be used as part of the Anglo America
Can group
EU group
Then wanted to leave the EU which
Most of the EU and the US were not in favor of right
Make any sense
If Alex's Grand portrait actually reflected reality
Notes app now they eat the UK is now the EU Patriots
Like how the Patriots in the United States are the Patriots
Of the United
Alright
UK's the Tennessee of
Ubu I guess is what I'm saying
I don't know how that tracks you but
Speakeasy here is Alex giving it really shallow assessment of world relations based mostly on members from
Book written in the 70s
Did you didn't actually read but instead just understands
They were published by W Cleon skousen
How it's kind of realizes there isn't much
Fremitus
He's kind of Retreats that Queen impression
And rambling about how they teach you at the high levels of Ivy League education that we received
Currently under the British Monarchy
It's
It's silly
So tell me more about these lines that you have drawn here to figure out is who's on who's
Eastside / who's Under and Over
So the UN and such was under was over
I thought they also encounter
China underneath there
Control what I did all of the all of them is under the UN
Russia's fighting against the Tyranny right Russia's a member of the um
Fighting against the tyranny of the UN It's Not underneath the globalist
No right under the evils they are
Well
Unfortunately they are
The UN and
The world economic forum and these are governmental organizations are on top of everything
Guess I've just called the globalist yet
They are on top of everything everything is underneath that
Okay they have
Total control
Over the anglo-american Apu group
Right less control over China and Russia
Right and needs it but who are the two tyrannies the two tyrannies are China and the global
But they
But the China's underneath the globalist on top of that
Heating system of care
You know sometimes words could just be
Whatever you want
Kind of gay
What Alex wants to save year or what he's trying to say
But I don't think it makes any sense
Snow
He sang of the globalist are in charge of everything and
You know they did the UK the EU the the United
Midstate
Vero Lake
Inanna
And they're cool with it
Where is China
Was cool with it either fighting
Against it
Sure I'm an Russia is that always
Are there like the
The defense
Against
Overarching
Little dump
So
Alex Gibson
There's just more geopolitical conversations this stupid
China Wok
The New World Order
Shut up by this entire
Our system and now what did Gigi pink start doing the Last 5 Years
He said no
I'm going to be going straight to
Control the world
Materials
Do you like me
Shrink control the world that way
The West Wall of the military
China course double-crossed
Didn't follow that
Take over the United States
When they're spies
Double cross
Help us
They were so busy trying to
Cut ourselves penises off literally
That now the Tricom double-cross
Austin Pain on Hollywood everything else
And a Rollin
Spy
Only because
What
That's where all this is
Going
Chinese military at about 2.7 million members
In 1995
4.1 million enlisted
In contrast the US has about 1.3 million Act
Super snouts
Numbers aren't really the most
Important thing
Necessarily in terms of
Building up the army
In terms of spending even though China has boosted its defense budget in recent years
They're still only spending about a third of what we do
Well it is true that the gross number of dollars
The China is spending on defense
Going up steadily in the past 20 to 25 years
Not the Last 5 Years
The percent of GDP that's being spent on defense is actually gone down
In 1990 there were spending approximately 2.5% of GDP on it
Compare 21.8
Percent in 2019
Yeah relatively
There's nothing is going down
Right
And it's not a phenomenon that's been going all over the last 5 years at 10
Consistent thing
For for a while
I like I like the idea that
Like that
It was like we
You can pause
Simple for us to really keep it in perspective
That that America spend
40 f***
18% of its budget
On
The military
No reason
Other than
You know money for that
Really
It's crowd
That's
So but then they're like
Hey hey hey
You can increase your Builders baby
From 5
To $12
I can't I can't handle that s***
Trillion dollars how about that
You shouldn't have spent 12
Conspiracy theory that there was a deal struck
The United States military might for the New World Order China would have control over rometty Rios manufacturer
Has the city of London will be the center of banking did Eisenhower
No word yet on any of the rest of the world
But I'm sure it's in the fine print of this conspiracy
Contract Alex's imagining everyone sign
Honestly I don't know what to say to something like this other than it
It's dumb and a bizarre over-simplification
Of world events and his
I've never heard Alex actually back this up this claim with anything meaningful
She did say that it was like that movie Rollerball
So I guess you must be on
Yeah that does make sense
Which one James Conner original
This is just for Alex to explain away how Soros has been
Some critical of China lately and call Ga
Threat to open Societies in the world
Alex is yours yelling about how soros's want to be heads of the globalist tours in League with Islam and China to take out the noble ameri
So now that Sarah's is making some high-profile comment
That are critical to China's leadership
He needs to have a story to allow his audience
I take it that news without questioning Alex
His previous narrative
The problem is though that you can fight instances of Soros criticized in China in the past
Particularly
SunPass
In 2019 he said of the US and China quote the reality is that we were in a cold war that threatened
Things to turn into a hot
In 2020 he said quote
There are a lot of people who say that we should be working very closely with China
But I'm not in favor of doing
We must protect our Democratic open Society
At the same time we must find a way to
Cooperate on fighting climate change in the novel Coronavirus
That won't be
I guess what
In 2019 he also said quote
China is not the only authoritarian regime in the world but it is the wealthiest strongest
And technologically most advanced
This makes G Jinping
The most dangerous opponent to open
Open Society
Sure
There's a lot of optimism
And a lot of sources comments prior to around this point
We have to understand one of the main reasons the things
In earlier times that look like China's government was opening up to the world in the progress is being made on that front but then
In 2018 she abolish
Term limits and essentially made himself into a dictator and this
Definitely
How the situation look to Soros
Someone interested in open Society
What if you just abolished
Term limits
You're still have to
To win the election
The last one
Yeah but
It's email yes to win the next one it's it's
Totally fine that
You did that
And is not him declaring that he's a dictator for life it's basically an alley-oop
To the next person who am I mean that's why you're the John Stockton of Decatur
The service has been pretty clear about this stuff in his comments and speeches in the past Alex hides all that information from his audience because
It doesn't really fit with the narrative
How's this thing about Soros is making some headlines for the audience
The fun tale of intrigue
Is betraying the evil global
Plans
As best as I can tell it
But Alex is writing
And if you
You can remind people
Especially you are an idiot
That they are coming for your children
Right they are just demons
Need
Peanut
What is things that I found really remarkable about this episode is that like their horse
Statues of things
That are just
All naat
True like Alex various things
Form that I'm just not true not true things
Program
Is about
Suppression of information
When they make
They're big
Biomedical tyranny takeover move
What is an operation
What is an opera
Operation lockstep
That is an operation of
The 201 and many others
Finest detail
Virus
Release the virus
And then
And then forcibly inject
Therapy
And then give us
A world ID
Through the vaccine pass
The phone
The track-and-trace
Everywhere we go
Control
Weed
All of that is made of
None of that is connected in any way to reality
I was looking for something
Pretty hard
It's really an all of those operations
It's not in all of them
No it's at all
There was a real operation that was a training exercise
Smallpox many years ago
Operation lockstep
Operation Operation role-playing exercise
Operation of it
I love that operation so f***
Real thing
All these things
Added up to prove that this is all
Covid stuff is all the shenanigans
Thankfully there's a ray of Hope in the world
Are some
From a very important event
Place in Germany
Event 202
Where they are having an international
Criminal court hearing with
Top judges
Lawyers scientist
And I have handed down the findings
I've recommended in.
One of the things
Going back to
Said it wasn't
Freedom
That is important
The first have
People's Court
When prestigious people
What
Congress
And then you
The public sees it
Committees of Correspondence grew in
Choosy
Continental
Congress
In July 4th
198 ways
For simple Disobedience and nonviolent resistance one of the main one is
Mock trials in mock jury
What
Something I was put out by the Pentagon 3198 Waze
Resist
That's nonviolent resistance
It was a guy named Gene sharp who is a political scientist and Nobel Prize nominee who wrote on Brazil
Dictatorship
Weirdly holding
Fake trials isn't actually on that list
Giving out Makawao
Prison holding Maca like
Since those are on the way
Just claimed that holding box trials is something that is a main entry on this list
It's just him making s*** up to overhype a bunch of idiots
Germany pretending to do courts
I'm not sure that mock trials are such an important
Piece of American legal tradition
Really matches up with the story of the Continental Congress either
All right I mean
Judge Judy Judge Joe Brown
These are all my trials really
Good for education purposes Soto
This is really a mock trial either as much as I do
It was the uniting of delegates from the colonies to make actual demands of Brit
At all very real these people in Germany are not going to be reaching the same kind of outcome
But the actual demand advised like indictments and okay
You guys have fun
You're so powerful
Group in Germany's called itself The People's Court of public opinion and they're not as Alex is claiming top
Judges lawyers in science
Conspiracy lunatics presenting their conspiracy nonsense in front of little Mike's wear while wearing suits
So it looks more official then
If the same things are being yelled by Alex
Like usual
For instance the legal representative for the United States as a woman named Deanna sack
On January 24th Deanna spoke about her involvement in this trial in an interview with Jim Fetzer
The guy who wrote the book no one died at Sandy Hook who Alex is
Is desperate not to be associated with
The rest of her Twitter feed is mostly just anti-vax blog posts and retweets of Robert Kennedy Jr
The other rep for the United States is Nancy and a Garner who was almost section recently by the
City courts of in Albuquerque
After she wrote the judge a letter that was quote
Truly shocking
Roman article
From an article about the incident
Import of the letter she called masks face diaper and then went on and compared mandate enforcement to Nazi Germany
Call the governor Michelle Lujan Grisham
A quote phony
And said vaccines are experimental gene therapy
This wasn't a case
I swear she was representing a restaurant that was trying to get damages against the city for needed to be shut down during covid
I guess she thought that letter was going to be useful for the case
Mr Smith Goes to Washington
I just wanted to show them you want to play
Daddy said by people who are never playing I wanted it to be shocking and yes I liberally
Used a couple of square word
As the judge said I think I insulted every branch of government
That's what I withdraw and I did with drive but I meant every word of it
Just lawyer that I like that I like this is Betty lawyers that I've liked
Results of imagining what
Goal is served by this letter.
Just feeling
Feeling good
That's prestigious
I would take that as Christie
I feel like this
Probably like
Malpractice
Didn't want her to do this I feel like they might be able to sue her
Yeah I'm going to be I'm going to throw this out there I think bull would kick her out of the people's Night Court
A meaningless exercise of repeating the same old
Conspiracy anti-vax
Do dangle red meat out in front of people like Alex
Cool get really excited
Didn't sell it to his audience
This is the move.
Finally going to bring about a worldwide recognition that you listener
You have been right about being anti-vax all this time
All this time everyone said that you were an a****** in prolonging
No
Absolute weirdos in Germany during and they're going to vindicate everything you've ever done
There's nothing meaningful about this at all it's basically just the international version of Jacob walls
Front porch
Publicity stunt
Just thinking to is like a lot of people in Alex's orbit do do this stuff
Reverend Manning
Up in New York held that weird
Another pumping held a mock trial man this goes way back
But that wasn't recently
That's true pet Benedict did not pick up another phone that's
I feel like
These folks
Really value the
Attention Gathering
Having a mock
Because also you give the appearance of having any kind of legal
Amend
The people who take in your content
You'll understand it that way too and disseminate it
Pusher
To further its
It's so just a dumb publicity game just think of all the out-of-work actors who would give anything to go
Go to Germany and put on a play for a couple of weeks
Makes you know
There's no
Principal first
You need a law degree
You need to write a judge a weird letter
I could probably pull that one out to look we got these weirdos in Germany
We got ran Paula saying that the Republicans take over
In the in the Congress
They're going after facts
But that's not all
Well
Guess what
Congress
Has now started
And if
And game
Function
So that's very very poor
I go through
We're Congress announces in the committee
Control
Investigation
Of the will
Virus origin
Gain-of-function
For some reason I just
And cannot
Cannot find it
Stop story can't find it
Smaller
Have a different Works load paper in front of you
Clearly not effective
Not going to help
So this is just a story about the Republicans in the oversight and reform committee James Comer Steve scalise and Jim Jordan
Calling in 7 scientist to testify they believe were pressured by people like fauci
The claim that the virus wasn't likely to have come from the lab in Wuhan
The issue they have is that some of them like the UK's Jeremy Farrar hit made statements
He was 50
50/50 on the liability covers his natural origin
Confer
Call on February 1st 2020
We're fauci was involved
How to use part of that conference
After that point he was aleska
It's by the Light
Theory
This naturally proves the fauci
Put the squeeze on him and got him involved in a
A cover-up
As opposed to the possibility that a bunch of information it's science was discussed in the car which made for our change
Tour doing the lab leak Theory
As less likely
How do I does just another grandstanding publicity stop by the
These folks in the GOP horizontally creating names and bank accounts for themselves
By attacking public-health officials
If there's some evidence that there's actually a cover-up in Gray
Come out with it but I think the game played
So many times already and I know this is going to be a zero
It's just going to be
You like Rand Paul yelling Itachi
Like it's just going to be that
Again no I mean it's
It's like
I mean it's like three cavemen trying to ask aliens how to fly
Like
But they're smart enough to know that they can get
Millions of dollars
I know what you talking about
It's just like you don't know any you have no
Contacts for anything that they could try and
Explain to you
Yeah and the problem to is the hostility of the questioning will disallow any kind of actual like
Cuz I'm sure there's a lot of times
These scientists would be willing to
Explain be happy
Me to explain
Treated as hostile Witnesses and badgered into a bunch of cavemen with clubs about the bright lights in the sky
It's counterproductive
It's not good
Speaking of
Counterproductive
Rodger Stone
Is back
Great
Got to do all four hours
Rodger will be on later book
Breaking news
Spell with Raj
Rodger Stone
Joining us
I should have
My mind going on
Because he's been on fire lately he's always
Informative
Involved
With the massive cam
Florida
Friday
And they have found
30 40%
Other voters are
Of course
Huge number
None of it is skewed towards Republicans there is
Some of that butt
Percent
Skewed towards
So they showed people's houses
And I do know we've lived here 5 years
And that person never lived here
Bought this house from
In some of the cases I go yeah that guy moved out six months
Horses
Chase's
It totally fine
The people are voting
Alex and Rodger going into reruns this is a story Rodger tried to push last October but it
Nowhere's I guess he's trying to breathe some new life into it
Try to push donations or something maybe
Maybe you need the money in order to make sure that this canvassing gets into the right hands and it's got a
Yeah
I don't know
It's crazy that it's all on the devil
I totally I swear if you really start getting into what Alex State like
If you believe everything Alex says
You have to think there's like 50 Democrats in the United States
He is waiting
That's what he wants them to think we're the massive majority
I think about the Dynamics of a lot of people that are listening to his show
What is it a lot of his stalwart audience are people who are in more disconnected area
There are plus-26 districts
If you will
Semi-rural
And I think
At one of the things that is advantageous about that for Alex
Is that he's able to create portrait
The play on the
Fears
And Prejudice is the people have
Urban areas who don't live in them
If so I think
That we do you can play paint this picture of like crime everywhere
Last episode of downtown Austin isn't safe for anybody
To wander through whatever
And living in a city
Bright or big city
I think the same thing is true of like presented the demographics of democrat
That's like it is believable if you live in an area where everyone around you
Is is Republican
It is probably truth it
There's only 50
Democrats even like that bias
Does exist on the other side
Cloistered and
The insulated in
Just hanging out with him
And experiencing Democrat
Sure they can think that it's impossible that anybody
Would be on the right
But but I think that I was plays into that easy
It serves his purposes very well
Yeah yeah does
It is a it is always smart to
If you are
Dealing with p
People who don't expose themselves
Two other things
Frequently
It is a lot easier to tell them that other things
You should not expose
Lose Yourself to expose yourself to them and let me tell you about him
Bono
Alex's
Can I introduce Rodger hair but
Adverse
They have gone to Grand Jury
Phelan Phelan slick
Forest
Yeah you might just you know see me in jail
Gaylord add Willy people
Was Russia
I want to sit there and
Please do you how serious this is why it's going off here in six months cuz of Finance
Please
How serious is vice listen to country
I want to be
Peaceful
Democrat Republican
Come together
Read say no to the multinational corporation
New World Order
Heather playing us all against each other
Republican Democrat
Little Canada live in Mexico desert
The New World Order
Good for you
Where are the masks
But you're only engaged in the Stockholm syndrome
Rodger myself
Car finance
Watching
Down
Target products
Put the money in. 6 weeks
Before I get
I'm having to put it on
Because of that we don't have the cash
Need
What would be good for him because recent Wars wouldn't have any kind of shipping issues or any kind
Supply chain is no just be pure profit
For him so be good
Also I don't think
It makes sense
That things that he ordered 20 weeks
To go are now coming in if this is a new thing
Move Supply chains are all that he needs
Ex post facto
Dad
Also I mean if you're out of supplies
You need to order things that'll come in at 6
Six months you're f*****
That is absolutely not
A real depiction of his situations that's nonsense
I go to a
Bank and tell them that's your situation that you need an extension on your loans and see how they treat their
But I guess you are foreclosed upon now
Yeah
Alex wants to drive people to reset Wars
Because
It's just
I think people might have noticed that I have maybe become a little bit less concerned with reset Wars and maybe
The drive to cover it has been last
Hey what are the reasons for that I actually couldn't talk about it
Until after the deposition
Came out because
If there was a question about it in the deposition
A what Alex said about reset Wars
Risa Ward
No that is
That is somebody else's
That that
It's not like
It's very clear that Alex isn't
Really you just get the
The recent Wars has a company isn't even Infowars it's not
Alex it's not free speech systems it's Jake Ducey
And is hypnotism b******* and he got Alex
To be the frontman for these videos
Dorothy
And so
This is my most important work I've ever done
After you kind of get the sense of like he's
He's willing to
Just back at somebody else's s***
Yeah
Took it took a little bit of the interest off at 4
Yeah when you when you see like
Brad Pitt
Hawk and some product in an old Japanese ad in here like that's clearly you just
You know what you don't even care you're just doing a commercial
For the cash that's great good for you whatever f*** off
But that's cuz he's not built a career out of
Sebring like he
He gave a s*** about the news
I can't believe that you would
Seriously say out loud on your show
When you are not even
Close to thinking that it's even a little bit of work
That you try
Or even something you're willing to take
Any direct ownership of
It's not really even your project at someone else's company promotion
Real it's
It's a little bit illustrates disingenuousness on his part
Let's think about you would we know people comedians who have done like
Corporate gig
Kind of things worth
Like maybe they do a video for a corporate internal use
The host of the
Match Game
Dating Sim dating show used to watch
No
You'll get elimidate
Love it
Something like that
Rodger Lodge
Hosted the training video
For it
Do stuff like that fuel corporate gigs
Rodger Lodge was Troy McClure
Some people do that
What Alex has done is that
This is a quart
Great gig for him he's
The face of
Are the the recent Wars material that is
From Jake Ducey
And it's just pathetic for Alex because of the most important work is over.
Being quiet I don't know what else you've done in his career
Like I'm so proud of this hoodrich theaters
Promotional video the internal training
It's the best work I've ever done
That makes it
Slightly less interested in like Rush
But we're still going to get to it eventually
So sad it's so
Raven and an awful
Because I want
Cover his most important work
I don't want to cover
Him doing a gig
Again you have had that football pulled out from beneath your feet
And again you go flying
360 in the air
So look Rodger got a plug
Alley Cats of course
Alex's Azan plug
Rogers got to plug
This plug
Is
Is is why
You can go to Stone.
Unfortunately
You do still
Need to help
Patriots and a warrior
Community
You forgot
You have
You have the Capitol Police suing you for running January 6th I mean you weren't nothing to do with it
They come at you with
Georgetown University and the CIA are suing
Okay
Admittedly run the law clinic
The Virginian lawsuit against
Weirdest
We just got a
The old process
They local constables
And literally take
Lights off
4 years in the corps
All this just to stay on the air
Blasting
At the New World Order
By complaining about my own
Righteous battle against all the f******
Comfortable
That looks
I think of some more though
What that means
I think I read it I think this is I think that he's talking about the fact that I I think I read somewhere that Rodger
Can't afford to fix his car
Is it a half a car that's broken or is it a car that's Halfway Broken
Can it work sometime
Who cares
I mean Beyond
Beyond Rodger
I mean like
I don't know every car that I've ever had has been half-broken
But he can't afford to fix it is what the character exactly
That's that's fine but that's what Alex is talking about with a half broken car
I mean let's go back to when I worked at that movie theater where Rodger lodged at the training video
I never felt entitled that someone else should
Fix my car no I don't know why Rodger Stone that's something that's relevant to his his legal
I think because he would like everyone else to pay for his arrest
After his life
Yeah I would think so
The way he goes about it
Trying to get everyone to pay for all this s***
Little tacky
Little tacky hear it
White tacky
No
Damn serious we are going to back down
We are going to give up
We could get out Rodger
Rodger Stone did nothing wrong shirt how they get your boy
How do I find Rodger
Paraphernalia is the left called
Again you can go to stone-cold truth.
Go to the shop
You can get your
Wrong t-shirt
Or you get one of my famous
Rodger
Stones paper weigh
Sorry what if you just want to help me in the legal battle and I need that
Bingo.
Stone defense
Please this Shopkins.
I would understand
Rogers stones
A little dumb
No that's great Rodger Stone
Chabad
You can't not-so-little Uncle Joke
Kind of universal it's a little bit on that scale of
Come on man come on
But selling
Signed pardon
That is
That is a maze
That breeze that is
Absolutely
One of the more waggle your dick
At the law
I mean
Goddamn
Signed
Copies
Of his
Presidential
Yeah
God damn I'm going to have to look this up I didn't look in advance how much does it cost for a signed copy
We of the presidential pardon of Rodger stone for crimes that he 100% committed
Wow okay so 4
10 bucks
Yeah you can get a small autograph
Okay for 20 bucks you can get a in engraved
It appears signature
On a larger stuff
Score
For $25
You can get a shirt
Is a syringe with a
Line through it
And it says
What happened to my body my choice
Too long
Rodger Stone
Still did nothing wrong with a fedora over at that hat $25 also
Brookstone still did nothing wrong
15 bucks
That's an expensive mug
Probably too too much you can get a
Picture of Rodger Stone getting arrested
Seriously
They have a Rodger Stone arrest photo for sale
8 21/50 why this motherfuker can get away with this s*** is because that is such a great
Dick wag I can't I mean they told impeachable
Description of the picture
A riveting piece of history and a huge mistake for special counsel Robert Mueller
The stunning pre-dawn raid of Rodger Stones home to arrest him for politically-motivated
Fabricated first-time non-violent crimes shock the nation and mobilize the Baga Bass
In America to support Rodger Stone in his Epic
Struggle for justice
CNN just happened to be there to live broadcast the entire Cirque
Didn't get a photo that signed by Rodger for twenty bucks
Wow where where would you hang up
In the fireplace
Picture is not stew because we
You guys have talked about a cow
Do they they came when they raided me he's wearing a shirt that says Rodger Stone did nothing wrong
Dick
Goddamn personally hand-signed presidential part right how much do you think it cost
I'm going to have to go he's going for broke on that when I bet he's charging 100
So on December 23rd 2020
President Donald J Trump granted an unconditional presidential party
Pardon and active both mercy and Justice capital
Jake just
Capital j
Has the president determined that stone had been framed by Robert Mueller's now discredited political witch-hunt
Wrote it in the corruption trial in Washington DC
20 bucks
Oh man he's really blowing that one
I feel like you need to charge a s*** ton for that that's Prestige price
You know you can
You got your Goldilocks items you got your you got your shirt for twenty bucks
You got drugs
You got your expensive items you got your mugs
And then you got to go For Broke with some
Well I'm going to tell you this right now
Supply is unlimited believe so is low
I don't think he could get away with charging that much cuz no one wants it
The flagship product
He is about selling it because
Youwantmati
Clearly broken car what kind of conversation the if you buy one of those
You expect
Somebody to be like hey what's that and then you say
That's my
Signed copy of
Rodger Stone
Presidential pardon
It would be so funny if you go into your doctor's office and they have their diploma
Just as a prank that would be very funny
That would be very funny either be the best doctor ever or unit for Rock
I would have loved to be there for the conversation of deciding to do that
That's just amazing that's the kind of thing you come up with when you're like cigarette high with your buddies
Kind of an idea
No that's the idea so Rodger stones
Same Session 5 Seconds
Great Neck
45 minutes is f******
Terrible ideas
What about Stones Rogers
No that's stupid
I've been finally we get to
Oh my god I've got
The perfect
Yancey I think a normal person would respond to someone suggesting they should
Should sell autographed pardons if you like I don't know I think I would look bad
YouTube
Is
Bespoke product
That it only Rodger Stone
I'm certainly not flying off the shelves
Alex get to talk to Rodger about the situation in Russia is really really strong
And he's got a lot
From his research in his contacts
Stration
He really thinks it's happening
With this Russia crisis
Lighter say sorry fake headlines
Are we seeing the
Bathroom shelves
We said give us proof they said that is the proof
We've already gone over the Bloomberg story but I really think about the claims that by individuals
Made that Russia was going to carry out a false flag.
Very strange
I'm not going to defend the administration's claims or necessarily how they're presented not but the last person who should be attacking this
Is Al
If his complaint is it somebody's coming out predicting a false flag and then the only proof they can provide to back up their claims
Trust me
There's a situation where Alex has indicted himself
Far more than
Anybody in the Bible
How much is career is 1 long
String of in predicting false flags that never happened no evidence
Or something
Intuition or maybe a dreamy add
Resume headline he misread
If I were Alex I wouldn't
Take this approach to attacking the official because
It has the
Cancel to make any
Engaged listeners question what evidence Alex ever has
Her to offer it is with his predictions
The false Flags
Anyone who seriously question and it listened to enough of his show
Reach the inevitable conclusion that Alex is just regularly
Making up at 10
When's predictions of imminent false flag
Then when they don't come to passing moves on and acts like a never did
Let's just
I I think it was
It's dumb to accuse people of baselessly predicting false flag
When that's your business model
Yeah I was kind of expecting as a cuz I heard the I heard by them and all of them say that and I was like
Oh well
Great we're having a great time
And I assumed Alex's going to be like a Hi-C
This is the false flag
They are going to do it
And then release the video
So they're just getting you ready for the false-flag they're going to commit
And then they're claiming that the Russians committed that false flag when in fact it was the United
The committee that makes the most sense to me
For an Alex things
Sure. For him to be like
Declaring a false flag is a bad idea like what are you f****** talk
Talking about being like if
You predict a false flag you must show
Absolutely
Now that's
He can't live up to
Infuriated
It's a strange take
I guess what you going to do
Is audience doesn't demand much you know that's true there is not a lot of demand
I have some interesting ideas about what Putin wants
Visa Vie Ukraine
Exactly like the Cuban Missile
Interesting
And install a
Puppet government
So that he can restore the faith
Glory of the Great
Soviet Union like he's dead
Afford that
Secondarily
Let us listen
Do you say
Over and over and over again
He doesn't want
Ukraine to join NATO
Why do you saying is
Western Metals
Border
President
John F Kennedy said 1962
Russian
90 miles off
Assure
Straits
This is all about that
Over and over again
Extrapolate
To take over Ukraine
I don't believe so
If
Ukraine would merely agree
Not to put missiles on
On the border of Russia
This entire thing
Could be
Averted
I I think
Thought experiment here might be useful
What is
Can you imagine a situation where Ukraine agreed
No muscles on the border but we're joining NATO
It would be a huge problem
Interpreting the only problem being
Missiles
Nautica
The problem is the missiles within the mind
I'm the one in May.
There's a possibility that Putin doesn't want to take over Ukraine in the sense of actually occupying the country but just like in the case of George
2008 use military action or the threat thereof
To serve as a veto to a state wanting to join NATO
Turning to other states in the region that might want to join up as well
A part of it maybe missile related but it's also an attempt to keep states in the neighboring region within Russia's sphere of influence
You're not allowing them to make other strategic partnership
Rogers tennis sugarcoating this
Make Russia the unimpeachably good party in this which is
Alex's agenda as well
Again I don't think this is an indication of any kind of like
Fealty to Russia the way that some people might suspect
Secret of the international order
Like if Trump were at office they probably be insisting that he needs to send troops to help flush
Russia fight off Mater
Probably would be
Right but it would be motivated from the same place of opposition to
World body Issaquah operation
Things that are seen as globalism
Yeah as opposed to necessarily support of Russia
Yeah I mean
If I were
Pardon
Specifically
For courting Russian influence in our election
I think I would go
So hard the other direction when I got out the other side of the part and I'll be like
Russia's bad
If I'm going to continue to say that
I still didn't do it. Here's what the great is it Rodger believed that his part in that that he could never be dry
Double jeopardy
Text me
Yep
I just think it's a little bit
So Alex
Gets into
Weird consistency
Theme of his here
You know we get new crew in here
Whoever and people will ask
Your office
For now are you came out or are you using drugs
How the hell did you get so excited once you're on here but you're not
When you come in here
Vinaigrette
The world's excite
And exciting things are going on
And we could all die but that's exciting
Wow
He seems to have consistently people around him asking if he's on coke
Okay that's
A little sister
Here's a common things that happen
You
Low energy
Bright
Go into a room by yourself
Come out high-energy
This
If it happened
Once
This is a regular occurrence, just excited that we might die
It seems like
Might be excited in private without anybody seeing what gets you so excited whether or not this actually is
To him on a regular basis he does seem to feel
Need to bring it up on Arrow La particularly strange about this
He's not even like
Crazy high energy on this Epic
No this isn't one where he would need to
To give that caveat
I mean unless he walked in like literally asleep
Just practically sleepwalking me like there's no way Alex is going to be able to handle it if you did a bunch of blow
And he is just super high energy like maybe he was
Projecting
I don't know it's very strange
And I will
A would-be
I would be curious why he seems to need to bring this up over and over again
So
I'm glad you wrote down that diagram earlier about the world powers
Are we going to have more to relist the world feel like we're going to have
Thank God
I'm seeing it everywhere
The Scotts
Lawyers
Tucker Carlson
And Joe Rogan
All these other people
The great reset
A corporate cabal
It's the other power
Russia
European Union
But what's bigger than all that
Get together the big
Above-the-law
Think about being conquered by them
Reset it so please
Go to reset
Wards.com today
It said heavily promoted
It's becoming an issue Maybe
He can't get anything in stock for 25 weeks
Write the list
The powers which is strange
He forgot it when he was in the middle of his lecture seems like they are the ones that he hates the most States seems like he's just make
Making s*** up whatever feels right in the moment
This is not this is like the the Bill Gates's of Council of twelve or possibly middle management
Who knows this is this is bulshit also I would say
If these
Big corporations
Are the problem
Maybe we should do something about corporate
Galaxy politics
They should be allowed to
But they should not walk
Exactly that's what it's about it's about freedom of
Choice Dan
The freedom to kill people only means that if
You don't you're a better person
I think that if
Out of control
Rampage Incorporation
Are really one of them
Largest issues that we Face an even Alex
Recognizes that
It seems like some kind of state power is basically necessary in order to reel in those Corporation
See you I don't see what other alternative there is in terms of
A communal solution the alternative is to keep people
Shoplifting to make sure that the corporations have more money
Don't feel like that gets us where we need to go but that's cuz you're not going to get there you're going to be
Sing the shoplifting is the answer but stopping at Circle
Well that's not a problem
Okay
Well I'm convinced
So Rodger gets the plugin
Again
Do you need money or you needs money
We don't have George Soros paying our bills
Again the best websites
Rodger stone for folks
To I build support you then
Fun.com there it is
Stone Fence fun.com
I still got to fight
6 completely baseless
Harassment lawsuit
George Soros
Case by the biking
Apartment
Civil suit
Business Insider
Said last week
They're baseless
But if you don't go fight
Like them to get a judgement against you
Pretty lost
Enough
Back on my feet
I got pulled over by the
The Chinese virus
I did
Ultimately
Make a comeback then
Ivermectin
But in the meantime research
And your iodine product
X3
Crucial in terms of rebuilding your immunity
Anybody wondering
No I'm not paid
Bunsold yeah
I believe it that's all that is being genuine well listen
I would never believe that
Rodger Stone was lying to
Especially if he says I'm telling you the truth Beacon of Truth
I think that he might be getting paid to say it
Specifically because he was in the middle of a plug
Maybe Miami his brain connected it to plugging the iodine
Seems Seems like maybe those are in similar
Departments in his brain seems like he's supposed
To be there to get everybody
Even do a plug without going into another plug
His plug for his legal defense got interrupted with a
A story about how sick he was so you can plug iodine to be racist
I'm going to continue to plug Ivermectin and hydrochloric win for no fee
And then I'm going to plug one of Ali
Plexus products
That I definitely am not required to do as part of this appearance
So I'll Alex talk a bit about January 6th
How they were all cool
It's a bit defensive about it
Because people wanted to shut up about January 13th
Pansexual
Polza research the number show
Did you want your sex
Republican
This is just crazy
There's no there there
Just tired of hearing about this
Hey Alex
Benghazi
You know he keeps things alive
Quite a while
Crazy it is crazy
It is so crazy
They could have killed a congressperson
Like I just could have killed one more than one
On
National TV
Live stream
And I
Camp
Help but think
That a year later we would still be in the same place where they like that's legitimate political murder though that's
That's totally fine
They're just good honest God-fearing folk honestly don't think so crazy
Vets
The line would have been crossed
In a much more serious way if
Number of conch
Murdered
I understand you're shaking your head
That's a level of disillusionment jadedness that I
I pray for you so don't have faith that whatever response would have happened to that hypothetical situation
I don't I don't say that it would have been
Necessarily super-effective
Or maybe the right response
But I think I'm more serious response wouldn't
We'll see
Maybe
It especially because they have people like Rodger running cover for it that's kind of part of the problem here
Next
Fucken cliff
Schmear against that Great America
Good Patriot
General Michael
Flynn
It is alleged
Is there was a draft
Cast of a memo
They talked about seizing
The machine
A draft draft
There's never Act
Fact is I understand that General Flynn's react
Needs to run
By the lawyers
Illegal
I mean if I
Born about murdering someone
Then I don't murder
Of course not
Now you're being fresh
Crime
Let's be clear
Recommend martial law
General Flynn
Recommend the Instagram
General Flynn did not recommend this evening
The machine
Recommended those things on Alex's shoe literally all of them
Yes Direct
So we don't even need to talk about any drafted executive orders
Chicken dumpling here like in December 2020 he spoke to Newsmax and he said quote
He is
Trump here
He could immediately on his order sees every single one of these machines around the country on his order
He could also order within the swing
States if he wanted to he could take military capabilities and he could place them in those States
And basically rerun an election in each of those States
It's not unprecedented
These people out here talking about martial law like it's something we've never done
That's what he was saying right after the other
Quizlet really clear about how he wanted Trump to respond
Rogers just lying about
It is now because it looks really f****** bad that he wasn't
Just talkingshit
Is also coordinating with Trump about the possibilities
Of doing these things
Right so
So like yeah
It's so if you think about committing a murder and then you don't commit a murder
Not a crime
But if you get like
75% of the way to committing a murder
That's called
That's true
You I don't know
Conspiring with people to commit a murder and I take a bunch of steps
Towards committed that murder but I never actually follow through
Especially if
Murder plans
Indirectly led to the murder of somebody else
Like if you hire somebody to
Kill
Somebody
Right right
You still in trouble
It's Alex
Rattling off
A bunch of things that aren't true
I would say almost everything in this clip is not true it's get it
Trump will be removed
Insurrection.act she said will have martial law even be Wednesday election we're not going to accept
Inauguration
They said
Is the temperature
Billions of dollars of buildings
Police
You know
The device
President
Murderers and criminals out of jail
And then
Sure that's why
Fight the police a few thousand wave in the building and they arrest those that peacefully went in
This is a fraud
Refuse Trump's request
A month before
It's on them
Because they created the condition
Rodger Stone
Yeah go ahead down the list there
Pelosi didn't say that if Trump won they wouldn't
Accept it and Alex's making things up a sauna wargame beating the people had to discuss the possible
Responses that could be taken
If Trump lost
And refused
Leave office
The burning of these buildings in such protest that has nothing to do with what
How to talk about
Thanks 3, Harris didn't bail out murderers or anyting she retweeted a link to the Minnesota freedom
Find which is helping to bail out people arrested in
Did the George Floyd
This has been spawned by people like Alex into reaching the form you here
6 narrative seems to be ignoring the roads in The Oath Keepers totally planned
To do what they did
What you hear there is Alex going back to the old narrative
He used to say even though that it shows talking points have been update
But he's not even in
NSYNC with his own
Lights
Five federal government in Russia was Trump's request
The National Guard
There's at least five like really discreet problems with
With that
Only 50 seconds long
Here's it's complete bulshit here's what I'm saying
Okay we don't need to f*** with
The First Amendment at all
Alright
We don't need to
Limit people's speech
What we need to do
Is just get like a litmus test like this
This clip right here if you have enough lies in a short enough. Of time
You're off the air well it's like Comics will do the last per minute
Read measure lies for men
Sabermetrics for bullshitters what's your lies above replacement post
I think it'll be tough to find somebody who would be able to replace it
Is the
I can't think of the best baseball player in the world in the best baseball player in the world
Who was the best
Open till in history was Barry Bonds
Ohio Tony another 10 years and he might be there that's how good he
One of the top 20 Pujols
Pujols top 20
Maybe even that I would say I would put
Ken Griffey at
Holes probably around 17
Down there that's pzo
Number 6 Mark Sioux Falls
I'm just naming the Cardinals that are part of SeaWorld teeth married
My buddy is all
The s*** out of that.
Yeah this is a bit like this episode in terms of
Like meaningfulness over replacement not gray
Bright Now Dental very bad I'm going on here cuz I think that in some ways Alex is in the middle of a holding pattern
He's made this
Prediction of
The Giant cyber-attack
These preemptively made that narrative
In case something happen
The storms didn't seem to do it
So maybe this is going to be pushed down the road
Scan down until maybe
There is some kind of a Cyber attack
Simultaneously he's waiting
For something to happen in Ukraine
He's built up this pre-emptive Narrative of being a false flag
That's globalstar pulling against Russia no matter what right
The rest of this is just
I don't know
Weird b******* about history
Rodger really needs money
I mean I will say I take I take some schadenfreude and that I would like to
To see Rodger Stone
Tiny listen walking everywhere for the rest of his life I think that be
Quite enjoyable I mean he could be a certainly could be out there asking
But what
He would make you a hat that is true
Panhandler
I don't know I don't take
Joyin
I like his impoverishment or anything
I do think it's funny though the way that they're doing
Dislike
Promotional basically
Like
Excessive
And I got to get one of those got to get run of Rodger Stone
No
Got to get in Grave 2
Nopalitos paperweights
To put it on your stacking
How many say this right now
I'm worried that someone is going to as a joke
Bye
Give Rodger Stone a f*** I told you I want to see him penniless walking everywhere for the rest of his as a joke by
His assignment
Noah pardon
Just take joy in knowing that it exists and someone probably isn't one
Has gotten if you beat them
Maybe take it for
Run Runaway
On another episode more impact on this
But
We aren't worried that knowledge underscore fighting I go to bed Jordan
Rhombus
Lukas X robe
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work