Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
Joan
King of the Road
How you doing
Better than you
You need it
My bright spot is last night I went to cysk
Would you are an alumnus
Sure you ask me to Meredith
I hosted a couple times
Redefined what it means to debut at zysk
Regenerist Recovery album by Drake
I think that's just cuz I ran the light accidentally by like
Twilight 3 minutes
I got to see Marty DeRosa the aforementioned hehehe
Don't stand up in a long time
First time up in forever and I
Can't believe how Hardy Crush days great was ridiculous Kristen to me
Since I started comedy years ago
Amazing I love her she was
Awesome
It's just
Great to see him
Fun my car got towed
And I walked around
Downtown Chicago until about 1 a.m.
Just got on
The trade-in what
Yeah that's fine but there's no resolution
We're awesome when your car gets towed you stumble around trying to
Get out of lockup and I give up
And then I was like I'm not going to do this tonight
Not going to happen that does suck I know that like it's
It's not good
Experience Xavier car towed anywhere
But I think in Chicago with a particularly miserable.
No it's the worst
I've never had a car while they lift yourself never had to suffer this but I've been around
A number of people who have that fate has befallen them
And yes
Bad news the first time I lived in Chicago when I was 19 I had my car towed and
It was about 1 a.m. my cousin had already gone to sleep I'd walked about two miles to his
Consciously
So I had to walk another three-and-a-half miles back
Back to my place
Is Not Great there's a bad night
Is bad night sounds pretty bad
Don't don't
Get your car towed in Chicago
Anyways with your wife
Stuff I can't really get into yet by project
Be kind of stuff maybe coming down the road but I feel like that's teasing and not appropriate
My bright spot is my car didn't get towed
Just having a little fun
2022 extreme
Zuppardi's very scared
About that stuff and that it really blows up in his face
I'm excited to get into it
Let's take a little over to say hello.
Somebody walks that's great idea
Do first
Tallest purple
Knowledge fight for 50% off at my pillow.
Is Mike Lindell really did want to f*** with us that would be a good way for him to do it
There's actually a dad
We don't own two words X's the books that burn podcast currently reading River of
Teeth by Sarah Gailey thank you so much you're now about
Thank you very much I had to do that
Is the otherwise it wouldn't
Currently
That's true
We got to take Amtrak to the mixture
Never realize how to Alex's
Technocrat
I have
Risen above
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
And all your s***
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Back here again
Apologized
To the crew in the western Chester
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
He may be better he may not be
I appreciate
One thing about that
Drop more than any other witches
Is Dan you have broken
Both mine
And every other policy wonks brain
Because I cannot get away from
Take a little break a little break easy
Breakout video
I'll take a little break
Vomiting
Brutal
Your drops have
Broken the brains of many of many of of walk I'm just doing my part
Appreciate it
Alex
Has a overarching narrative on this show
And this is before Alex's actual show bumper starts
He's just muttering over
So here's how we begin
Ladies and gentlemen this is a Maxima Red Alert
Worldwide thermonuclear war
Meadowlark maximum alert TuneIn now for the word Infowars the most banned Network
In the world
So that's the sting and then it goes into his bumper and he starts the show so that is that how you know this is
Sirius total thermonuclear war
Infowars
Either worsens there were some comments that Putin made after his press conference races in the Press
After his meeting with Emmanuel macron recently
Some talk of moving to missiles and what have you
This may be interpreted as a direct
Threat of nuclear war in escalation but
You know either way
It's not great
I think Alex might be a little
The Buckwild on this
It's important to understand
Any kind of threat
That Russia may be making Visa V discussing their nuclear capabilities
In the context of political history
Does Putin that his administration do this
A lot
Them to exist
2014 foreign minister Sergei lavrov
I'm against Ukraine if they tried to take back for me yet
In 2007 they warn Poland of the Czech Republic that they could
Still nuke them even with Western anti-missile defenses
Attempt to dissuade the countries from letting the US
In their country
This happens a lot
And there's a pretty simple
It's one of the very few pieces of Leverage that Putin in Russia actually have at their disposal to
To use
And because of that it's become a state policy to use threats of nuclear war in order to
Deescalate situation
It couldn't be the acolyte D escalated otherwise
So I came to power in 2000
And shortly after that that April he put in place a new military Doctrine which replaced
The previous doctor and they did have been put in
Ian 1993
What are the main
Pieces that's relevant to us now is that in the original version nuclear arms could only be used
Quote in case
Of a threat to the existence of the Russia
Confederation
The new version
Expanded this tool a further use quote in response to large-scale aggression
Utilizing
Conventional Weapons
In situations critical to the National Security of the Russia
Confederation
They opened it up a little bit
Which is what you want from nuclear
Consolidation
The former head of Poland's National Security Bureau status
In practice
An article from Politico Europe
The numerous events of Russian nuclear blackmailing add up to the Russian strategy of information
Warfare which aims to intimidate the West
Enable Russia to reconstructed
Soviet Union
ER Tech
Right and also its
A bluff
But
It's not one that you ever want to risk
Calling all the fun
Don't f*** with that Bluffs
Speak on the matter of you this as a propaganda
Because ultimately this nuclear deterrence also exists within the nuclear deterrence that many NATO countries
Also have
Nuclear capability
Goes both ways
And Russian knows that if they were to actually use those nukes at their posturing like they're going to
The responsible Swift
Devastating
For all part
Their ultimate goal of protecting the Russian Federation
Confirm
Reserved
Provide the Russian Federation getting
The goal can be served by threatening to use on that threat being enough to intimidate
And change the behaviors of NATO
And the countries in the region that wish to join it
Situation
But it's important to recognize a little Alex engages with any of this s***
Pumas Ebony's going to move some missiles
Perhaps
Alex starts his Joe do this grotesque movie trailer voice
Thermonuclear war
When you recognize that
These threats the Putin is
Is deploying or part of his information Warfare strategy
You have to realize that all Alex's doing it either wittingly or unwittingly amplifying and playing right now
Into that strata
The more of this thread is hyped the greater the chance of forcing an 80d escalation and
Capitulation
To Putin's demands
Then again the world
Completely insane
2022 and many things that would have been
By conventional wisdom of the past 20 years as being to being a possible
Anymore
So I don't want
Entirely downplay this
Situation
The point I want to make is just that if Alex were half the geopolitical
He pretends to be
He wouldn't engage with this
Piece of news this way
Right
Are you going to get really extreme with
I mean I think it's
Probably a bad idea
That's just because I've never seen total nuclear war before so maybe there are some positives that I
I haven't considered you know I've lived through one
Yeah
I think that Alex really likes to use the Specter of that possibility as like a way to
Excite people
Come on baby let's get it up
So Alex has this
Story about poop
And he has a sorcerer
Actually isn't
Bratz
The source
Isn't
The Daily Mail art
Okay
That's worried start
Brown's it's so much more digging on this thing man
We'll see
All right here we are on the edge of thermonuclear war
This this morning
Daily Mail
I had trouble believing it
So I went and searched
Some of the quotes
Nowhere else can the Western news
Spend some time
Found it in Russian
Translated and indeed we found a version that has subtitles
Vladimir
President of Russia has threatened nuclear war
And said within the blinking of an eye
He says you won't have time to Blink
Your eye
You've NATO continues its Article 5 takeover I got the clothes right here on the video
Proxy war
You're going to
Basically
Stop
But basically is in there
So Alex is trying to pretend that he did all this leg work
In the crew dug up and found until about this Putin speech
Spoiler alert
That's all bulshit
Eventually Alex plays this translation that they supposedly came up with
That's just a literally the video that's embedded in the Daily Mail article
Even has the Daily Mail logo on
You know they got it from Russia
Alex's is reading the subtitles to veteran that discount
What a
What a dick
He's pretending to work on this story because he wants to create the impression that he has access to information that the rest of the world
The media doesn't have access to or
Choosing not
What to talk about
Exactly you can really easily find it English translation of this entire speech to the Putin gave us
The kremlin's website
Announces version is
Is just the daily male version
It
Really match the claims even that he's making
It still doesn't match up
I just like hearing that the
Kremlin has a website
Isn't that kind of silly like in your brain
I think most
Government pository
I don't know
I don't I don't know
Sure at least it's not like a blogs
Traveling. Substack
Because there's a new shut-off
Isn't really accurate to the transcript provided by the Kremlin
There is a reference
Do something happened
Speedily in this case in the heartbeat
Instead of a blank
But it's not necessarily about nukes
It's about how if
Ukraine goes into NATO
And Russia attacks Chromeo which they interpret
As a defendant Premier cuz Russia
Abused it as their own
Then cook in a heartbeat
All of the NATO countries would be drawn into a war with Russia
Because of the rules of Article 5 which state that if one country is attacked
In the group everyone comes to their tooth
That's right
There are slight differences but these are the Fingerprints of a lack of exploration that Alex did on the topic
But he seems to like
You want to make it look like he's taking this very seriously and did a lot of digging into it
And he's missing like
The actual Contours and context
Of what is being talkative
That right
Kind of irresponsible special
The topic is
Impending nuclear war
Yeah
So Alex is coverings
Like he is done
Intensity
And
That he's he's really gotten to the bottom of this thing in a way that no one else has
And he feels like no one else no other media Outlet
Covering it the way that Infowars is
Russia makes a fool of macron Biden
That's not what the headline really should stay
Infowars
Quotient
Vladimir Putin warns a nuclear war
Breakout
If Ukraine joins NATO
Headline that Alex has of like humiliating macron The Daily Mail headline
Of 1
Their articles
The other article is
Putin threatens
Nuclear war
So they have two articles one of which is essentially the same headline as the one that he is arguing
Right
Synchrony just didn't look
Look for anything or he's lying about what Outlets used as their headlights
Metro
Muse's dire threat of nuclear war in Europe is he doesn't get his way
The Daily Beast
Nuclear war over Ukraine
Vaden
Saying for Stuff
Newsweek at quote Ukraine crisis could lead to nuclear war under new strategy
Before this the financial times
Us believes Russia plants nuclear exercise to Warren West over Ukraine
Untraditional used by Putin
Alex isn't discussing any exclusive
Snooze plenty of other outlets are running with the same lead as him and more importantly
Single unit of effort into this reporting
Says it's just him riffing on a Daily Mail article
While pretending to the speech and translated it
This is just a performance of trying
Mets Braves
It is phrase
Nobody really thinks you did that
About research man
It's funny to imagine that
This is
Altru is the result of all of his digging
What book did it's like let's play a fun game
This Daily Mail article that's like I don't know I can't take this I can't seriously
Searching can't find anything else on the internet so all of his people finally find it in Russian
And they translate it and they dig even deeper
Find a find a video that has subtitles happens to be the same video that's in the Daily Mail article
I'm going to go even further down the stupid Rabbit Hole I'm going to say they went to The Daily Beast article and then
I would like there's no way this can be true
So they went to Daily Beast. Are you we met
And got it in Russian
Had diarrhea Translate
Back into English sheet that's that
That thing that makes any kind of Rush
And translation seem believable because Dario
Ability still doesn't
Make any of this make sense
Do any of this work now but anytime we talk about anything address
He's going to have to be like we had somebody who I had a crack team translate again
So we get to this Daily Mail
The subtitle
I over it and there's some very slight differences
Between this
Had me Kremlin transcript that I want to discuss cuz I think it does actually change some of the meaning
Video app
Licorice root
Match one
You to finally hear me
Deliberate
To your audience
TV online
Email video matches the Kremlin transcript pretty closely where there's is quote
I want to reiterate I've said this before and I would really like you to hear me this time and convey this mess
Switch to your readers viewers
And internet users
Contacts
It's missing however because this is just where the Daily Mail video begins Alex has no idea of what happened right
Play before this
The question that Putin is answering a squad
Is mr. macron your only dialogue partner in Europe
You said you was a good conversationalist
Do you consider him as an
Intermediary to convey your message
Which two European
Try very good question
So this is something that will matter later as it relates
To the larger point of Putin
He saying
Would you get you here in a moment.
That gives
Got some
Idea of why do you say
Has a response to that question
So here here's where we get a little bit more
Right immediately after this is all straight through
Convenience later this week she totally silly Dilly.
Play my Julius to do you understand
It or not
Ukraine's going tonight
Military memes
The European countries will be automatically
So this is really the point of Putin's answer
If Ukraine joins NATO Russia is not going to respect you
Ukraine's claim to Chromeo which will lead to
Conflict
And because Ukraine will be then a member of NATO all the other native
Countries will have to defend them
Which puts them immediately in pecans
Conflict with Russia
This is important to understand that
The context of the question because
It has to do with the message that he's helping
To send to these leaders of European
In countries that would be affected by this and suck
Into that war
It's essentially an attempt to Blackmail the European countries do not support Ukraine joining NATO because if they do
The questioner Cormier will become their problem
Signaling in advance that he's not going to budge on it
That's
Did Messi leave listen I'm not saying that anybody is going to do any harm for you if you join NATO I'm just saying
And the other things that are already in place could be a problem for you I'm just saying don't join
And all I'm saying is we'll see what f****** happened
It's less even a message to Ukraine to not join NATO it's like
I don't support their during this is going to be on you
Plus now you're in a fight with
Or you want that France for NATO and Germany
Well we are going to let Russia take from
Then there's no point in maitopia will spoiler alert there have been a number of times in the face
Everybody come to the aid of the party is not necessarily happen
So the the clip goes on
Unity skis
To my stitches keyboard
Can you sniff
Of course in Russia
Potentials are incomparable
Abby Newman
Understand
Companion
Perform
Is a subtle hint
But it's not really a direct
This is expressing that he's well aware that NATO's
Combined military strength
Outweighs his butt
He has a nuclear deterrent so pure military strength isn't the only determining Factor
This doesn't read to me to be a strong threat to use a nuke
Because you have to remember the
Context
This is about chromia and the Dominos that will fall
If Ukraine joins NATO and Russia does
Don't give up their claims
To the area
This will lead to war but
That doesn't necessarily mean that it's going to lead to a nuclear war because
That would kind of be counterproductive towards settling what's essentially a regional territorial.
Spirit
I'm not saying that I couldn't
Spiral out of
Control
You're what would they do
Nuke Premiere that's not in their interest no no
Look Crimea is
Part of the Russian Federation
And that's why we
We have to Nuke all of Europe
Does that not make sense to everybody
It makes perfect sense
It's
I understand how did the fear
The anxieties around
Regional conflict
Getting out of control too
To the point where they absorb absorb the entire world
Anxiety
I understand
It was a problem last time
The same rhetoric was flying around in the advance of the 2008 war with Georgia and the 2014
Hostilities and Cormier
And even though there was active
Happening
Nukes used because
That Weaponry didn't match
The goal of that
These
These coming to these making kind of read the same way
It's too much that released to me they do is it
He's going to Nuke anyone over the conflict
But that the rest of the world shouldn't get involved
Because you wouldn't want to be at war with a nuclear power
No matter what
North Korea
Fight and then we'll get this s*** out of the way
Nobody's doing
This is kind of how this nuclear comment
Reads to me but an entirely different way
I think a fair amount of it too is just
Getting out of
Hand man
Alex has taken listen directions that it does
Does not need to go
Winners
So just
Hypersonic
Chris vessels and
Ballistic missiles
Both
Horse the United States has he would stop
Secret
The point is is that
It doesn't matter which nuclear weapon
Russian suicide Soldiers with suitcase
Party in Yoruba
Does it matter
Space space system shoot
Levothyroxine
Ballistic missiles or submarine launched
Doesn't matter
The nukes are all over the place
The point where Alex
Start freestyling his own doomsday narratives
I barely somewhere in this transcript that he's translated there's information to Putin is embedded
Suicide agents with suit at 2
Suitcase nukes
All over Europe
That's definitely not a James Bond plot
Right
I don't know about you but leaving aside the important point that I don't believe any of that
How can Alex
Possibly ever think that someone would have
Sleeper
Suicide suitcase nuke agents all over foreign countries
Scooby anything less than a f******
Supervillain honestly think that Putin is some kind of force
A good bringing back the west but he's also creating elaborate high-tech situations like this
It would essentially allow him to hold the entire world hostage again like you said like a f****** Bond villain
Possibly think
Stop
So tell me
None of these cuts
Trees have any idea
That
Putin of all people is just having people carrying around suitcase nukes wherever they go
Or all the countries are like well there's nothing we can really do
If you want to carry a suitcase nuke
In f******
Nebraska
Go to town man
How can you tell the difference between a suitcase in a suitcase
Change the risk possible possible to tell
Havasu
Suitcase ching
It's an achievable goal
Very easy to do you can do it
Just need a
Suitcase in handcuffs
Oh
So look
This is silly
I don't I don't really think
That this it I think this is a
Real real serious escalation in
Consensus sensationalization of the topic that Alex is covering and I think it's a little bit
Disrespectful to the actual series
Of the situation.
What's going on in Ukraine
And it goes on Putin clip
And you will be pulled into this conflict against your will
Who's pitching
We won't even have time to Blink
Your eye when you execute article
So here's where there's a slight difference in the translation I think in this context
The Daily Mail
Seems less Act
Info on Alex's reading
Certain The Daily Mail want you won't even have time to Blink your eye when you execute Article 5
Where is the transcript from the Kremlin says quote you will be fulfilling Article 5 in a heart
Be even before you know it
Brothers around a context that makes more sense the boot movie saying that if Ukraine joins NATO these European countries would have
Invoke Article 5
And come to Ukraine's Aid involving chromia in a heart
That conflict
Existing it isn't going away so if Ukraine is involved in the collective Alliance of mutual protection
The secondly join all of these governments will have to enact article
Conversely The Daily Mail translation makes it sounds like
Something else that will happen
After Article 5 is invoke Article 5
Nukes are on their way to your house
Then kind of what the Daily Mail
When you execute Article 5
Heavily implies that
Was that day after tomorrow thing
A second
Suitcase nukes you guys you guys sign the papers everybody's taking the picture and nukes are on their way to your
Quite match
How the train
Scraped itself reads
Larger picture
Itself kind of more is
Realpolitik
Idea of like this in this is
How it is
Are we the aggressors
No one can say really what is aggression
I just saying that Alex is not dealing with this Acura
Yeah that be weird if
All the sudden we're Putin apology
I will be strain
Here's another clip as it goes along
President macron course
Doesn't want that
And I don't want
Brimstone
And I don't want it
Which is why
He is here
Was Maine
4/6 straight hours
Alchemist read the subtitles are
He didn't say that macron have been touring with him Putin said the macron
I had caught been tormenting me for 6 hours now with a
His questions guarantees and solution
Email translation
Ring instead of Torment
This is where Alex is understanding
Comet's begins and ends
It's because all he has to go on his that Daily Mail video and that's where the video cuts off
Immediately after this clip in Boonton
Set of macrons
The Diplomatic visit
Quotes I believe his is a lofty mission
For our part we will do our best to find compromises that suit everyone
There's not a single point that we consider unachievable in the proposals we sent to Nato and wash
Seems like somebody who has
You know that least
Rhetorically
Uninterested
Keeping negotiations open
Yeah yeah yeah that mean altimate Lee listen
Here's how we want to get you
Because it costs a lot of money to actually fight a war
Maybe I threatened you with nukes you guys will be just like
You can have you
You know it's really expensive
Getting nuked I mean imagine you're in Moscow
Right and you're just going along your day and then you're getting nukes that's like at least 50 to $60 to rebuild
Definitely
Baby drop
The contact
Threatening nuclear war
That's what Alex is doing
Do you read the full transcript that doesn't
Bill Acura
That feels
Like a bit of
Maybe some clickbait nonsense
Alex just trying to make everyone afraid
Which is a smart idea if you're helping Putin
Do you want to drive traffic I think people like in a state of
Impotent
Fearly Alex
Have you ever
Well I mean if you practice
Does ducking and covering lately
You have a desktop
Is there bars on my side so I don't have any ducting
Car flip over the air
Nobody got to go to Freestyle sometimes
Tell Alex he's doing his little breakdown of the Daily Mail video that he intend to get some product of
Deep freezer
Andy comes back from break
Why don't you think this misreporting
Vladimir Putin officially threatened to use nuclear weapons against Europe Ukraine
An official press
Warren the last V Article 5
Within a blink of an eye shed the West will see
A massive military response
Russia
Which invention
Nuclear weapons
And that you will strike
Western Europe
Breakdown the timetable on this if this starts
Listen to
This isn't accurate based on the actual press conference
Even accurate to the Daily Mail video that Alex is using as a source
And there's two really critical things
Things that
I need to talk about
The first is that Alec doesn't
You seem to even understand
Conceptually what he's talkin about
The way he's talking about Article 5 shows that he thinks something to absorb into the group
But that is not correct at all
Articles
State score
The parties agree that an armed attack against one or more of them in Europe or North America shall be considered an attack
Attack against them all
And consequently they agree that if such an attack occurs
Each of them
An exercise of the right of individual or Collective self-defense recognized by article 51
Of the charter of the United Nations
Will assist the party or parties so attack
By taking
Forthwith
Individually and in concert with other parties
Such action as a deems necessary
Including the use of Armed Force
To restore and maintain the security
Of the North Atlantic area
It's the rule that natak on one member state is an attack on all member
Perseids not a mechanism by which an 80 can absorb countries into itself like it
The Blob
This was a part of NATO
Core cause
And it's been in place since 1949 but it's only
It was never in Polkton
Until 9:11
To tell you this is not a universal thing that happen
All the time
Not a ton of people are stoked about getting into Wars
Not usually
The fact that Alex doesn't seem to
Grasp this conceptually like what article 5 is
Really makes it difficult to trust that he has any understanding
The conversation the boutin was
He's covering
And that leads me to my second point
This is a serious story one that involves
The Safety and Security of a ton of people in Ukraine and Russia
In particular
But it could have ramifications
People outside the region
As well
According to Alex himself this is a story that I
Potential consequences in the neighborhood of a worldwide thermonuclear war
He can't be bothered to know the basics of what he's talking
This is something that's at the center of a lot of Alex's
Contact
Intense and terrifying sensationalization
And decided not to look at
Is embarrassing and it serves to give the audience
It's not an absent event
Information but actually
Bad information that they
I think is good
They think their information
That everyone's about to
Is more accurate
Then the information
Maybe everyone's about to die
It's like he's not
Not not having food is having food that will make you sick
It's just
When it's around this kind of
Subject that is
Conceivably very serious
Like I am not
Convinced that this is going to lead to nuclear war but Alex seems to be
That's the way he presented the story and he
Even
Get himself
MultiCare passed
His normal routine of finding a headline
Lying about what he's done
Prepare the store and then ripping about his own
Paranoid and terrifying fantasy
Yeah and I I mean
You know the more you think about it
Galaxy
With love
Thermonuclear war that would be a great button on his career
Well you still working on that bunker
I need to get out that would get him out of a lot of s*** if all of a sudden nukes were dropping everywhere
He be like I mean obviously my Skin's going to melt off but
I'm out of these lawsuits
It would probably put a delay on on those
Yeah little bit
Alex
Alex takes this misreporting these doing of this
This, and he just turns it into like just
Bucking terrifying story
Breakdown the timetable on this
If this starts
When the Russians get overwhelmed by the NATO forces arrayed
Heavy weapon
The forces
10 minutes
The orders will go out
Cruise missiles
Sonic Russian military
What's the Russians make the decision to use
Cruise missiles ready their icbm's ready
And the minute
Weather radar satellite
Missile launchers they will have a total commitment release
Other weapons or submarines
All of
Directions cities will be
Verizon's well
Western Europe will be vaporized
Here's onto like really lay out this like I won't even have time to go find my daughter like
Really highly dramatic okay really
Aiming to scare
You know okay
Suitcase nukes you can conceivably say that it's
Easier to get a single person with a nuclear bomb
Device in a suitcase around
Then
Having a f****** nuclear submarine off the coast of New York City
You know what I honestly don't know
What Harbor
Near New York City
But they allowed rushing to get what what world are there people walking around with
Suitcase a little bit more noticeable
Probably probably
13B like elaborate masking technology that the aliens
If you know what I had not considered the aliens
I agree it's a little far-fetched but I
Not sure it's more farfetch
Text Ed suitcase with suicide bombers
I don't know which that'll be tough contest
Cast
But like Alex
Houses just like
Really trying to drive home the sphere
Maybe the cikaracak f***
Most of us will just get
Knock-down
May the roof caved in on you but when you come outside we breathing all that
Delicious radiation
Give me when you get up again
Won't be coming back on
4 years if you're lucky
That's where we are and where the evil decadence satanic Society
I mean really
What yeah okay
Maybe it started I didn't expect that turned you know what I was thinking I was just thinking
I think everybody
Time to die
Maybe we should all
You know what go find a spike
Just f****** do it man I believe in humanity
What is this
Maybe it's time for all of us to die
You know what weird mood
Yeah I don't I don't really know how to read this
Other than like
I guess he's depressed
No
You'd have to be a little depressed
To be very blase about the extinction of the human race there's some financial news
That will be discussed later that my plan for this
Okay I might have something to do with his head
Nolet's
Actor from the past makes it appear in ham
All right for that
Alex's discussing
Like maybe we all deserve to die from nukes
He starts rambling around
He drops
Drops a bomb of his own
That's
A little bit unbelievable okay
The CIA
Georgetown University
Literally has sick an army
5 / 10000 Muslims
Run through the school and given degrees
Intelligence badges
What games are Muslims
Okay
They've got list of judges that got list of people
Captains
We're a lot more trouble than you know okay
So I guess it's a we're all going to die episode
Yeah it's not a
So this mood his is flipped
That's pretty clear
This is really dumb
We've done this narrative already
But it was a year-and-a-half ago but
Instead of a brigade of Muslims
While the Patriots and we're going to go door-to-door taking them out
And now I guess enough time has passed that Alex to be sure that his audience
Forgotten that he said that s***
We don't need to worry about the migrant Caravan anymore
Becoming brigades or even when Alex was saying that was a way to get Ebola
Yes yeah it's all there
You know that old adage
The best way to keep a secret it between more than
2 people is
Just to kill the other two or whatever
You know what I'm saying
I'm going to go with
Having entire Brigade
Forced to keep their own participation
In secret
I might be
That might be tough to do man who is to give them badges to easily identify
Bouquet
Why would you leave 10,000 of them to take out Alex
I mean if you got a secret army
Part of the reason that you have it apart of
The best
Having a secret armies
You know
Cuz it's Secret
Right
I like specialized unit to maybe usually
People who
Solve the problem and then are gone
I need a tech guy absolutely Nations person
10000 mobile drive to get Alex
That's very weird I love it with a religion
Together Alex sub another subject
Text Gabby
The Capitol Police share
They're out of control
Social media
Meet with lawmakers
You read the article it says yeah they also didn't respond
But now the documents are coming out being released by Congress
Any
Investigation of the
Spectre General
Michelle
Are the Capitol Police
Unbelievable
Members of Congress has
Offices at night
The plumbers
Nixon dead
Having
Gordon Liddy and others break into the psychiatrist
To find out about him
Pictures of Capitol Police breaking in people's officers
Closing is capital repair
Photographing and stealing material
There's a tough narrative route to be dipping into because it might clip there within one minute he's essentially gotten into trouble with two
With his friends
Rodger work for Nixon and Watergate didn't go down like that
Now based on Alex's reporting
Then Alex's describing what these folks in the Capitol Police allegedly did going into offices dressed up like maintenance people
And that's exactly what James O'Keefe got arrested
Super doing to Louisiana Senator Mary Landrieu
Play Wild how many friends Alex has
Who do the precise evil shanty
He's so mad at his enemies for
Supposedly doing
The only way to your enemies are doing evil ship
Is to be the p
People who do that either
Sure
That makes sense to me article it's a disturbing Revelation that the Capitol Police
Been doing some digging into the social media and other public
Information
That's available for people who meet with members of Congress
And I'm not into it
But Alex is lying about what this article covers
There's nothing in the article that's buying in plain clothes that's just Alex adding to the recipe for
Buy more flavor
Also it's Alex referring to allegations made by representative Troy meals
Who claimed that the police were caught snooping in his office
Capitol Police released a statement saying that no one was snooping
But someone did a his office to secure it
Because he left his office door open when nobody was in it
When that happened
It's protocol for the Capitol Police
Security office
And close the door for him
It's not safe
The Capitol Police has come out with a statement this dude's a big dumb dumb
Close your f****** door. Maybe we won't have to show up
Also Alex can't possibly read the inspector General's
Report that he's claimed
Going to have on the Capitol Police looking
Get folks social media
Investigation cuz that just began this week and there's no info that's come out about it yet
He may be confusing with this with the IG report about the Capitol Police regarding January
Text but I'm also sure he
Read that right
I don't know
It just
This is
Ridiculous
I think I've only interested in nightclub
Because it's funny that this guy just didn't close his door turned into a conspiracy theory
And then the second thing is
So how much Alex's friends
Are implicated in the same Act
Evil
But it is it is somewhat of that that like
I know they must be doing it because we are
It is kind of that Vibe of like
Well obviously I know what the
The evil people are doing
My buddies are doing the same thing
That would be fine
If there wasn't
Also the denial of what his buddies are doing doing the evil s*** that they I say the other guys are doing
My buddies are doing the single shape
Haha now that I'm telling you that I
Think they didn't do it you won't get mad at me
It's it's convoluted
Alex gets back into the Caravan
A little bit
The trucker is up in Ottawa
Popular novel
A good time
Population of aw not having a great time
It's like the Brooks Brothers Riot with
Trucks
Awful and longer and longer
So my heart goes out to the folks that I have to put up with this
Alex has a guy on to talk about how great
The the Caravan is and how how how awesome
They're getting free to everybody
Jeremy Mackenzie
And he
Is joining us
Here on air
Popular podcasts
He's joining us to talk about
The latest incredible developments in
I don't really want to get more in-depth
We already have
The trucker Caravan if my position has changed
On it since the last time we talked about
But it's interesting to Alex's got busy to talk about the news from the front lines
Alex called in this guy named Jeremy Mackenzie
Wouldn't you know it
He's not the trucker he's
Actually a piece of s***
I'm not totally sure that McKenzie has a podcast but he definitely is a livestream that I was able to find
Interesting comments that he made on stream
Thanks to their being collected by anti-racist Canada
Here's one of them that is
Not good
Like that you watch that movie like Schindler's List actually is based on
Fictional book
Oh my God
Wright's really
Oskar Schindler was a
Black the movie
Was based on a
Digital Book
But they presented as though
This is what happened 10 Dark 30
Make it very
Jessica Berry
So you're learning about a
Something new for the first time
Now you're seeing this visual fuc
Sprayed in there
This becomes memory like this
What happened
It's like you're watching
You're watching a
Production either actors in costumes and if none of this is real
Now you believe that that would That's History when that's not what
Place
It's f****** crazy like yours that you're the great example there's a movie there's a guy
I need to call in a revisionist nnn all all of the
Things you can do
The guy's a historian it is David Irving
From the UK
Oh boy I just want to know
So he went over to Germany and winter any interviewed all kinds of people didn't
Like a c
Elektra
Any road
Schwarzenegger
Yep stuff from people you never ever hear about otherwise
Jerry
Is based on the non-fiction novel Schindler's Ark
The events of the story are true it's just that some of the dialogues been dramatized
Really weird the way this guy's calling it a story of fiction
It also seems to have trouble understanding the people know
That there are actors in movies
Scariest movies ever
I mean it is so much like a you can hear it when they talk or you're like oh
Of course
You think other people think movies are real you think
Think movies are real sir
Not what David Irving did
No that's
This guy is very wrong
David Irving is a
A full-on holocaust
Austin IR
Famous in the world
He tried to sue journalistew called him a holocaust denier for defamation Auntie loss
He very publicly argued that there were no gas Chambers at all schwitz which landed him in jail in Austria
He's been banned from entering multiple countries because of his anti-Semitism in Holocaust denial
He's associated with the Neo-Nazi group
The National Alliance
Enemy here since like 1990
His entire public Persona has been
Open pro-hitler anti Jews
And denying of the Holocaust
You look is Mackenzie guys who are neo-nazis jorian
Neo-Nazi
Generous as possible he's
Idiot who seems to be drawn like a boss
The flame towards any.
Information that makes these look good
To act
Honestly
He is not an illness
He's just a regular Nazi
That's just
Out of time
It's like he time traveled from 1939
There's any way there's an issue of semantics
6 against to get into but
Flabbergasted
Delete plenty more interviews of him pal around with white nationalist folks like the host of Red Ice
Stevie
I was doing interviews about how the protocols of the Elders of Zion are actually real with the anti-semetic ahdoot
Could have chose
To come speak out about the trucker's in Autobot given update
The guy you find we got to find the most Nazi
C10 most likely travel and similar ideological circles as they do if you know a lot of
Nazis and you been a lot of Nazis know you and they like you and you like them
I'm going to throw this out there
Maybe you are also an
Hey there could be a part of the interview where he's like
They said there were Nazi flag there was one guy with a knife
It is
Listen to too much about
Interview
Really
Care and I don't think he brings a lot to the table or any interesting information
Really funny thing that keeps happen
Have italics
Keeps saying this guy's Special Forces
And he has to keep correct
And because he doesn't want to engage in Stolen Valor
Right right cuz he wasn't
Very short. Of time where he was in a special forces
Does unit or something along those lines
But Alex will not stop getting it wrong
Has it he's had to correct him and I believe this is the second
Gametime Alex
F****** loser
Mike's after this
Yeah I saw that that was one of the aspects of the I can brief you when it was a Special Forces Unit
You're in my bed be right now
You got
God help me
I'm just telling people who you are
Can you tell me don't say I'm this and then you say don't say that
Let's just say you're in
Each other
Man-in-the-middle
But like
No no.
This is
Deadly serious if you know what is it what is it with you guys and you don't like me lying about what it is you did in the military
I think it's probably because a lot of people that Alex knows get accused of lying about their military history because they are
I think that's probably why he's hypersensitive about this point
Like him for any other reason but this
Mackenzie guy seems like
Like that
That's the right thing to do
Senior military service
You probably don't want to be seen
Playing along with that less
Everybody else think that you're also inflating
Flying rice
Your service absolutely which is why Alex hates military guys because the real ones actually do that
He likes non-military guys who claim they're in the military because when you say they're in special forces that like
Like f*** yeah I was exactly
I was all over the Special Forces they come on man improvised with me don't
Don't downplay this I need to present you as the greatest
Best possible source of information
Therefore you started the Special Forces took down an entire Brigade of muscle
They were in Austin
I was busy
See you at that's
That was just a little bit of fun
After this
Alex
As a familiar face
Come around, around
It's not author
Then the the former gold salesman
Henderson spend some time on
Who he is what he's doing
He was a sponsor of mine
In 1997
A year later he started the gcn radio network
Pictures already sent he was already
Financing a bunch of shows he already had a production
Popular on AM FM shortwave
He already set up as Network
Two years before was getting it ready
I was already doing another show on everyday
9 years ago 10 years ago in a gold bar
Anymore
Parted ways with Chad but said you can still carry my show
Educated
Crustaceans
And
Any more side to go out
Michelle Morin and try to get money in
Stop being able to pay Alex because a gold market took a dip
Lily's nuts there's no indication
It seems like it was because he got sued for the fraud and customers Minnesota took away his license
Sell precious metals
Also we've been over this at length but
Their relationship
Some good buddy is just trying to help each other out
Alex Azar
Shameless gold salesman for large stretches of his career
Mysteriously
Begin blast gung-ho about
I want desperately needed to buy gold
More recent career
That's after Ted stop selling gold
It's crazy how
Quickly went from gold will save your life and protect you from all diseases
Zinc will save your life
Protect you all from diseases it seems like the focus has shifted and it's like
It's you know I also like whenever
The relationship
Of money changes with Alex or it's like
Ted Anderson when he's giving money
Is the greatest
Person
That ever lived
Incredible when he's not getting money
This guy I remember him he couldn't pay me anymore
That's how broke this guy was this guy couldn't pay me me but I'm such a good guy
Exactly he's going with them
So guess what
He got wrapped up in
The Sandy Hook
It's not working out well for him
Pikachu
4 years ago
The Shandy
And
Nothing to what I said on-air did and I was already off
He was only a satellite provider
I don't care about that
And now we know now.
Plus
I just want to get this out now
What's 700 + affiliates
100 shows on it
But we talk radio in
For couple years it's been losing money but because it's a
Project he started
He's losing hundreds of thousands a year and that number is going up
And so they say that's fine
Just give us your whole network
Eucerin
Syncing directory off the air which it would be a crippling blow
Surrender surrender
In the Connecticut Sandy Hook case
And that simply because he was disseminating and profiting off of Alex
Defamatory content
Did targeted harassment
I'm not positive that Alex's Shady business
Miss practices are going to salvage this case
It's because I feel like
You know if they have an existing syndication agreement
I meant I can't afford to pay Alex and Alex's why don't you just
Keep on doing it not pay me
That seems likely agreement is
Phelan Place Alex has just agreed to forgo payment
I'll just leave that just means the Ted's making even more money off Alex's lies about Sandy Hook families
Need to cut Alex in for a taste
He's essentially gotten rid of his overhead for lies
Stocks to beat a drug test
It's it's
It's interesting I mean like
I guess maybe
Do you know his his radio network is a
I asked that they could be
Beamed
Possible something you need to sell for whatever damage
Bankruptcy they're going to take them ass up
Yeah and I thought it was really strange
Because Alex is like he's going to fight
This case but like
Part a day even like I don't know this to be true because I I don't have a whole lot of understanding of the inner work
Kings of the Connecticut case
They say that he got the
Defaulted along with them
Like
Like Alex says that he's already lost the case
He just would be fighting the damages portion I guess
I don't know that's not the case.
What ink
The name are they doing
Crazy
Absolute lunacy
Alex
He wants to build Ted up as a
The hero right
Why does
Money
All the people
And then they come to him
Thomas for a while
You know what screw this I'm not going to shut down
But because they're trying to shut him down and because they're trying to silence those other Rose
Sometime you had you down the road I know.
What other places
Better than ever
He's here with us today ladies and gentlemen
Talk about that
Appreciate
Kids already spent
300-plus thousand dollars
About to go to trial and vitamins going to cost him a half million dollars
He's already losing hundreds of thousands of dollars a year
I'm getting judgments on him you know he's totally innocent
Give the shopping but he's in America because the first amendment believes he's going to do it but he needs your help
This is sad
Do the last person who's come around begging
On this shows
You literally the guy selling them gold for the last few decades
This is where he's got to like this makes me really distrustful of precious metals investment
Deeply involved in Golden
Silver
Iceman
I mean it's hard to hear Alex say anything other than
Ted Anderson is a really bad busy
Businessman
Who is also kind of a fraud
And f***** up by allowing me to say whatever you want
Give him
Free market capitalist
This guy is losing hundreds of thousands of dollars of year a year running a business
You should do
Is give it to you to fail
With no review duration
Just bail them out
He's a great businessman to promote this this website save gci.com
Which is actually just a redirect to give send go campaign
Right
But like
The
B wildbuddies Oz
He's going to put commercials on all of his shows on the gcn network or people to go to that website and have to work
Yeah but like
He was already doing
Sort of
But he was like
Selling space
Marshalls on TV commercials for buying ads
On gcn
Basically like
That is give me money but then you get something out of it get mad
This is just like
Donate donate to keep my business afloat right
If there was
Potential for this business
Need to do this because people would be buying that at
And I would be getting him
Yeah I mean I can understand these people being scammed by like
Religious
People you know the the gospel
The Prosperity Gospel people
Cuz they don't have an actual business
No you can always just be like all I'm giving it to God
Not like I'm giving it to a failed business man who lied
History of broad
To pay my rent but goddamn this man's failing business needs me to
Give it money
I keep chat on the air
Important for democracy
Elephant in the room
And that is that Alex
Could just give Dad money
Then dude you don't get rich by giving money away
URL backup
They're saved ccn.com
Gcn.com one word
Don't make a donation
1500 2000 dollar
Depending on
Because you don't
Money
Do you want to try to help me or what
Turn the network
He needs money
So basically if you take this version
Of the story
I need $300,000 in Alex's like
Let's get the audience pay for it
You got it
Yep
And I wouldn't be too surprised
If it wasn't a situation with the behind-the-scenes conversation was more like Ted being like
Hey Alex
You f****** a******
You got me into this trouble
Like you
I'm on the hook for this because of
Love you
I buy syndicated you're so I made your f****** career right I know so much about you
You're going
To find a way to
To pay my legal fees here because
It's your fault you better
I wouldn't be too surprised if there was something along those lines
NSAID
Man you know I don't know I would imagine that he does
Didn't get to talk to Alex like that anymore
Well I mean Alex has that you know when they're when it's 10 Anderson and Alex you can't really say oh well reveal
Information about you because the answer to that is
I'll reveal information about you I mean we're both
Scamming Liars
He been through true Court
What is fraud
I'm not seriously suggesting that I really had to have been some kind of
Tractor reveal information
But I would be very surprised if there was
The conversation surrounded
This is your fault Alex
You're going to do something to help me to do something yet
And if it
All it is is giving me an hour to beg your audience for money
Then I guess that's what I'll take
These aren't used to give
Ted money and Alex Wood
He doesn't have any money
And that means you should give him money same person gives a millionaire money
That's why we have shave
Infowars.com
It also takes you to give shimko
Amazing it's a plug to support
We can't cuz he don't have any money so you got to give him money to
Right so save gcn
Save Infowars
Rodger Stones legal defense
We got pills
Who is Scott
People can buy a lot of Revenue
Streams that involve
No one getting anything for anything
Weird coin of are selling
Didn't work out surprised
I'm shocked
Step
So Alex got to break
Viking news
Here
Where is Sturgis
Hey I got some
So Alex got some but some breaking news
But it isn't
I just received information in the last 10 minutes
This is all coming out of wire
That leaves us I'm going to bring the shop
Weather
Joel skousen but it's a
And I was reading the.
Biden DHHS declares terrorism threat
Due to fall some asleep
Document
Ascension speech
Is Terrorism
Sanctioned means authorized by the government
The bulletin that the DHS put out the day before this episode
Resume doesn't say that unsane
Can speech is now a legal
That it would be surprised
I think Alex is just surprising for the DHHS
I think Alex is just misreading the word unsubstantiated
Like unsubstantiated narratives
It's
Yeah yeah
I think it would have
Pantry
This is just a bulletin expressing the awareness that there are Terror threats
That are growing out of the covid in Iowa Community the 2020 election fraud community
And some other communities that are largely driven by rampant online misinformation
This is not a controversial statement and soon as long as it remains a threat assessment
And not a call for the DHHS
The police the internet for misinformation
This story is a zero
It's kind of sad too
See this
And be like
Wow
If this was 2009 you could turn this into a mayak.
Totally
You just don't have the chops anymore you're going to forget about this in a we know
You just doesn't have it
Man
The last people I would want policing
Anything on the internet rdhs
Yeah yeah
But
Recognize
Spheres and communities are
Places
Is where
Their potential Terror threats are developing
I think of that
Rio within what they're meant to do
True absolutely
Just like okay why are you
Putting out a press release saying water is wet
Alex gets back into the
Open story
Because he's got Joel skousen
Coming up
Hear this you read that Daily Mail article and he was like
Get me Scalzo leave that man has my expert on these matters
But also Alex Tidwell
Obviously
We already played this several times the first shower but
If Calvin once we can reread this on air
My interpretation of it is
He said
NATO
Claire's Article 5 in baseball
Retakes in Ukraine
800 overwhelms us were going to use nuclear weapons
And I said
Very very chilling
And
The video when I saw it
I wouldn't actually found the video of Putin indeed saying that
There's such an agenda that Alex has to create the appearance that he didn't do nothing
It's it's
Kind of
Understandable because I think he is self-conscious about how
Little he does
Yeah yeah how much he wants to have the appearance of somebody who takes the shitz and
Enterprise
I mean I get it
It's sad because he didn't
City.
No
No I mean but if you're the emperor and you're not wearing any clothes
It's really smart
How to tell people that
You totally are
You're totally I'm wearing so many f****** clothes
This morning
Tried on a million different clothes
And I'm wearing all of them right now
I didn't just trust that Daily Mail are dug around I found the video that was embedded in
The Daily Mail article from to Elmore Leonard gumshoes
So 1000 comes in
Immediately
Just punctures
This entire bubble
The whole narrative goes away okay
Charles and thank you for joining us
What in the world is really going on with this Russia situation
There's a lot of posturing going on especially by Putin and in that particular
Understatement
He knows that the United States is not going to invade by does already said it's off
The tables are going to be no troops coming into Ukraine
When it's attack they're going to let us know they're going to wring her hands are going to do sanctions
You don't handle their future gas needs but
I'm still
This is going to lead
Two nuclear war because the US will not go to war with Russia
For Ukraine
So 1000 comes in with whether or not any assessments are correct or anything
Voice of authority cuz Alex's build him up as the one of the best geopolitical expert
Just contradict Alex
Across-the-board
Alex spent like
10 minutes doing it
Bizarre fantasy about how quickly nukes will kill us all
I'm in Skyland company like that it's not good as his posture and did you not listen to the early part of the show
Corsicana
Thousand
Said
That we all deserve to die
And now you're telling me we're not going to
It's deflating XXX weather
Word of God
I think the scouts and can tell
That maybe Alex is a little bit disappointed
Big news
Skim something
Take the wrong collapse in 1990
Orders due
It'll let the Wall come down let the riots go forward
They even gave orders for the Communist dictators to step down
Chow chesko ever met anyone who
Refused Indians wife
Wow sothi the fall of the Soviet Union flag
When I heard that is like don't tell Steve
Cuz he took down
This is a man this is a complicated mythology that is occurring
Out-and-out in
Violent conflict with itself right
Possible that Steve pieczenik was then in on the false flag
Felling of the Soviet Union Audi killed Aldo Moro so he probably faked
I think that this is this indicates a
Lack of seriousness
Well I mean
Full marks
You're saying we're not going to go
To Total nuclear war
And didn't even say that we deserve to die in a true nuclear war
Going to have
Give him an asphalt in the Russia false-flag two-tone collapse
So you can give him another little bit of a Mark here and that is the 10,000
For what other all the problems that he has
Does not trust poop
And Rec
Noises certain
That are clearly propaganda
Pro Christian talk
People to have children
Sushiman on TV
Why do you say
George Soros coming out
And really dabbling
China was before
Why are they admitting it now
Answer the question
This is Matt
To deceive
This is a major
Conservatives
In the United States into
Is our savior and I get emails all the time.
Wilshire is against the New World Order
Exposing at least partially
The globalist in their support of Isis in Syria Center bombing those convoys
But the whole thing about building churches
And the support of Christianity is a total fraud
This is
Don't listen to the show anymore
You've got too much going on
You really run
Ginger when you have been on for years
For you to take them seriously to take them as actual experts because
This isn't
Just like some
Some assholes saying this
You lying about the
Does religiosity
Conspiracy second-generation conspiracy absolutely
Alex is not happy
I think you so unhappy that he just
Basically like I'm done with this in it
Where can I pick up seats in the House
And will retain control of the Senate
Complete
Air Forces
Going to make a very sophisticated and get prepared to make sure that we don't win
The presidency again in 2020
What else should we watch
Back to eating lunch
During interview
Bulshit people
God damn it I can't be mad at you
I can eat
My feelings
So we've got this guy's I'm coming in
Just destroying the fear of nuclear war narratives
Putin's not a good dude calling out that
PR
Propaganda campaign that Alex has fallen for a man
Oh no scales and just to make the
Hat trick
Has to
If you makes a point to bring
Basalt
Because he he doesn't like that these are these
Conservative Outlets
Conspiracy sites
Have been promoting
That weirdo G giant giant do it no no no no no you can't do that man
Hellboy
Let me throw this out cuz I
I cover the Saturday and Sunday
Gathered that they were doing a
People's grand jury
198 waves Pentagon talks about
Civil disobedience
Put the song to the show grand juries
In other bodies the blueprints
Are you saying
That that you saw area for wasn't in Clearwater or what's happening
The entire internet is alive
Impression that he's actually filed students
And I want to make sure people understand that isn't true
Cute as a model for other grand jury so then
Yeah but you can't do that and it's not a model there never will be a grand jury in the first place
Should be filing a civil suit where you don't need a grand jury
They just common citizens
And the prosecutors
Grand jury to really discuss the conspiratorial evidence
Then you got a house conspiratorial proof
Which none of that open
You don't have Sansa transcripts
A collusion between fauci and the vaccine manufacturers and you can't prove they're lying excetera
First of all there is a logistical reality that skousen recognizes that Alex doesn't which I think is really funny
But
And a little bit too much at the a witch
You can't really do this in a grand jury cuz you don't have proof
Reduce conspiratorial proof what's going on what happened to skousen did he get hit in the head
Maybe somebody hit him in the head with a pan like a cartoon and he just woke up one day was like
Maybe I should tell people that they don't have proof
That's that's what's fascinating about his tone
He's recognizing there is no proof proof
But he also seems to be of the mind that
Quote on quote
Conspiratorial proof
Is good enough away shyn
Belief
Yeah I mean his literal point is
You can't take this to a place where a grand jury is required who have to go to a different
Court you have to go to a civil court
So a grand jury has nothing
To do with it
I think you didn't have trouble in a civil court but I think you have a lot of trouble as it'll go
Too much of an awareness
That there's no proof for the thing
They believe him
I have not heard him really just start saying throwing around we don't have proof
Well we know that fauci did all this stuff
Movie Cabaret
We'll see that's a problem because you say you can prove how we know if we feel it
Feels right I agree
Again
Okay
Wait what
Prove okay well then prove it
So this dirt bikes
This interview with the skeleton was a little
For Alex
And
I feel like he got a little delayed
You said that though
You've got the
The Alex
Signal
Waylon Richardson
For some reason I'm sure it's important
I'm going to be on the 1st
Alongside
I'm coming up
So is Ben like we need to Alec we got it
I'm hosting the fourth hour but
Bombshells
Too big to not have AJ
Right there big news is that he is a interview Trump
And so he's got to
Big Newman hot guy
This is about how I believe
The trumps
Be the Speaker of the House
And I'm sorry what hold on okay
Not only does
Wayne Allyn root believe this
Other people ascribe the idea to someone else
People say that Steve Bannon came up with that idea it's my idea
Dammit
I want to take credit for the warts ideas
Well
It's debatable if there was a worse idea of
Speaker the house
Which I was the first kind of country
Never bring that idea
CB speaker the house
A lot of people give me credit all the media every time they talking
They say when root asked him about it
But they say Steve Bannon is the one
First
Not true
She better brought up in
In February of 2021
I wrote about it
Nationally syndicated column
In January
A 2021
And I said
Trump should become Speaker of the House
At lead
Open LED
Applications
Criminal investigations against
Everything is about
How to do
That we know will destroy this country
Be speaker of the house I put my
Lightfoot
Again
Will you
Be willing to be Speaker of the House
He didn't say no
Which is very interesting
I hope we don't need that we shouldn't need that
House CD where he wants to do it and then and then they would vote him at his finger
That would be amazing
I don't think it would happen but also Wayne Allyn root
Here's two things
Things that are f***** up if you want
Trump to come in and investigate the guy who beat him in an election
Weirdly healthy conflict
Very healthy for political system
The second thing is that he wants him to investigate Biden
For future crimes
Crimes that he we know he will
Commit
That's really messed up
Now I'll tell you this
Has a problem
If I take the results of that Invicta investigation to a grand jury
They are not going to believe it's due probably not
If not really
Future crime
Proof.
So Alex looks like
Trump can get this house eat and then he'll become the Speaker of the House
Wayne
Believes that there's a quicker route
Oh my God tell me about it this is where Alex I think even is just like
I sent it to surrounded by idiots
Anybody could be Speaker of the House
After we win
After the Republicans control the house
No message
You can vote in
You can dominate that
But but it's clear to me he doesn't want to do that
I'd rather make an easy form now
All you have to do instead of running
Is be nominated for Speaker of the House
And if the new house election
I don't believe so but that doesn't mean
Anything can happen in this world
If you have enough momentum anything can happen
Yeah man
How to speaker wasn't from the house you can be elected even if you're not in the house
That's
Never going to happen
This is a wacky can-do spirit that isn't body and go
That is something he's got he's got ID
Bad idea
Google
Tons of jobs that
The speaker takes on from an administrative and party leadership position
The GOP would be interested in having
Trump be
HR jobs
Leaving it alone the fact I'd like Trump doesn't want that much work
Also
View motherfuker
Like Alex and Wayne
Did they can agitate all they want about how their leadership in congress is weak and ineffective
But in the real world
The greatest
GIF they could give the Democrats
It's somehow throwing out Mitch McConnell
Hey Kevin McCarthy and replacing them with some inapt
Diplomatic lightweight who wouldn't be able to Rally the caucus
StarTalk amazement that I have four
Conservatives who are like
Mitch McConnell's got to go are like
Have you guys not been around Mitch McConnell
Has successfully kicked the entire ass of the United States for 30 years
He's very effective my world
That's something
Higher higher value for the used vehicles
GOP he stole the Supreme Court seats
And then successfully got two more
He is destroyed the entirety of the Supreme Court for the rest of the United States history
Not a real court anymore
That cannot be achieved
With a lesser
Party leader
Have the ability to negotiate with various
Parts of the caucus
And get everybody on the same page it just
Would not have work
And
I don't think that
People like Alex necessarily
Care about that or recognize me important
Cancel that
F****** Matt gaetz in there and we'll run
Your party fracture
Get people to come on board as idea
That Trump is this big super strong man who we need to have leave
The country B
Well because he doesn't say that he want to do it I'm going to make it easy
For a big strong man to not have to work hard
At all and I hate Mitch
McConnell
Who is successfully steered this
Entire country
I hate that
That guy give me the lazy ass hoe
Also
Just from a
Odds
Perspective
Like we already talked about this when Marjorie Taylor Greene was on the talk about her becoming the Speaker of the House
There's no way you'd rally the kind of vote
So you need
The cheese in the house
Buick Rallye indicado votes necessary to like
Get Trump
Out-of-office
Tubi
Riverhouse former president
It's just
Possible there's no way
I mean Irish
I like
The acknowledgement
That Trump
Shouldn't
And couldn't have become president unless we live in a topsy-turvy world and anything can happen
But I'm going to go out on a limb here and I'm going to save this
Is one of the few things that absolutely cannot happen
Crazy world
I still think this is
Not going to happen
And I recognize also chocolate Speaker of the House in McConnell's in the Senate and all that but
The point still stands
In terms of
At the rally.
McCarthyism
But
The impact of trying
To unseat
These people who are
Very effective
Party leaders is
Stupid it is it's amazing
It is amazing like
Genuinely if the Democrats had somebody like Mitch McConnell it would have been
And instead we with Nancy Pelosi has a hundred million dollars
So that's nice
Yeah so we come to the end of this and I feel like this episode had a fun Ark
A bit much is Alex's
Obsessed with the the
Nuclear war and then skousen ruins at the end
Sky Zone kicked him a couple more time
Just a
A little kid
Holding birthday balloons
As skousen goes up with a pen and just
No no
Pop Anthony looks at him
Alex is a goddamn Nazi on to talk about the the truckers
Anti
Wild stupid
How is this a ship
Pretty funny very buddy
Jordan
Weekly back will
I hear tell that we have website
It's knowledge buy.com
And I'm new I know you I'm busy
Gunbarrel rundus
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color