Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge but I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guy
Stripe.com
A little bit about
Alex Jordan
My bright spot today is kind of hypothetical but it's
It's still in the in the ballpark
Sweatpants cool sweatpants
The concept
For later I might
Tiring to like sweatpants
And I think it's time I took great around the house maybe maybe like
Lovett or something
Getting into leisure
I'm huge sweatpants and I mean that literally I have
Gigantic sweatpants
It's way too big for me and I just
Can't get rid of them find myself like
Always
Generally wearing a hoodie
I feel like what is
What is sweatpants
But the hoodie
I'm excited about that
Is this movie new movie
Maybe I can remember it's called red rocket
And it is about it's one of those Classic Slice of Life
The decline of America movies you know
Pornstar
Can't hack it in LA anymore has to go back to his Small Town Texas
Fairies
Unsaddle Trump
Comparisons very unsubtle everything
Very interesting movie
They have to go back to the struggling Texas p*** industry and try and rebuild
Sounds fun I thought you were forever
Movie theater in Novi
So Jordan today we have an interesting episode to go over we're going to be talking
Thing about Peoria
Is Friday last week Friday
Very very exciting little
Sort of Arc we have over the course of this episode
And I'm excited to get them business on April 1st
Hello doesn't do walks
So first
Lauren B also sorry about this we should have got to this maybe a week ago or so now we're a little bit late
Play on wishing you a happy first day as a policy officer
I owe you an apology walk
Congratulations
Next passholder
Thank you very much
I got fixed a little drinking for me thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Tiger butt
Lego
Jordan active listening to Alex and clips and given him credulous feedback is always my bright spot thank you so much
Ewok
Thank you very much
Valentine's Day messages for sidewalks out there so far
Valentine's Day
Next Happy Valentine's Day to DJ
1 * 1
Thank you very much
Have a little Mikey
A little Blake
So thank you very much
Alex Ross you know which one we mean
We're listening.
I have
Risen above
Miami
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe later on West Broad
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the crew in The Westerns yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
I'm not sure if he's better on the on this episode but he certainly gets weird towards the end
That's always nice
On Friday yeah Alex was deciding to take most of his time
Talking about
How the globalist have been defeat
Already
Bow Wow
It's a Triumph for Alex Mark in your calendar
You can officially mark your calendars
February 11th 20
Biomedical power grab
Great reset
Officially
OverWatch
Really from day one they launched it two plus years ago
Does our own documents our own arrogance
Launch this live
Began to wobble and
Collapse
Slow motion
Free fall
Prosecute
Psychological warfare
Biological warfare
French Revolution
For prosecution
There's a little bit of a tone that you're going to get over the course of this episode I
Think that is
That there's that there's a tunnel chain
There's a mood change from now it is time
Do put on war crimes trials for all of our vag guy out of
Alex is a little bit high on the truckers
Inaudible
All right that's the explanation for everything I think he thinks
So this is all
All the problems of
Trudeau step down
We just got to prosecute him for war crimes the whole
Everything is getting wrapped up thanks to the brave truckers who have
Right
Cuz I will be honest what he just said does not make any sense
It certainly doesn't know
I think even if you just look at it
Conceptually you take it outside of the prism of reality
You look at it from a okay so we got a house of cards
The second they launched this operation to Oculus go
Wobble wobble
But now it is
Completely collapse
But that's not how House of Cards
But it's collapse
And hark the day that it finished collapsing
The die was cast
You know it's already destined to fail so theoretically it already has fail
I don't think there's a lot of saving a wobbly house car very delicate
They're very much.
Yeah and also you'll notice in there to the Alex has his favorite thing of
They have completely collapsed is over but also they're still good
Flathouse still going to try and do it that's not how it works
Got the cards are going to shuffle I'm going to try to make you play Texas Holdem
Well this is difficult I thought we were playing House of car
So like I said this is mostly about the the trucker
Crybaby Auto apartheid
By the way came out and got the article instead
Crackdown on his insurrection
Children jumping on bouncy houses
Yesterday
11 hours
K12
Almost zero now in Ottowa
Absolutely just making that statistic up
There's no way he's looked into relative crime rates from before the truck Convoy arrived in Ottawa compared to
I'm pretty much certain he wouldn't know how to look into that even if you want
Alex is very much wrong
There be plenty of crimes of people have been arrested for in Ottawa specifically at the Convoy either
Over 100 of the tickets and citations that have been given out of a relatively minor crimes like having booze out in public
You're not wearing a seatbelt
Multiple people arrested for
Destruction of property in regards to damaging
The property of local businesses
According to a statement put out by the Ottawa Police Department
There are over sixty criminal investigation so far related to the demonstration
They're primarily for Mischief theft
Hate crimes and property damage
This is outdated information there been more investigations instead of opnsense
That statement was really rare
It's it's no it's good PR that is image of the bouncy houses 2.2
That is all that was going on but
Let's just meant to run cover for the actual really f***** up things that are happy
It's like how Alex uses the image of people Milling about at the Capitol you know like walking through the Velvet Rope
That's all the event was as opposed to the reality that
Friends trying to overthrow the government
In this case one of the things that the image of the bouncy houses
Discovering up is there seems to be a lot of hate crimes happening
The Ottawa Police Department put out a press release on February 10th
It revealed that their hate-motivated crime hotline
It received over 413 calls
They were needing
To be followed up on
Resume context in 2019 Auto ahead only 116 reports of hate-motivated crimes
And 182 in 2020
Write the. Of time where the Convoy occupation is gone on his leg doing over doubling of reporting of hate-motivated cry
Compared with the city usually season a year
That's been going on for like 2 weeks
Right so when rich people in America pay for stuff
Generally speaking at increase the number of hate crimes in other
Suicide effects
Themes
So this is just something that Alex does really
Consistently
Everything is related to extreme right-wing causes that he supports involves absolutely no viola
The mere presence of these Patriot Heroes has the effect of eliminating
The crime that existed there before
He does this with right-wing protest all the time and now apparently an occupation of a city by people pretending to care about vaccine man
For truckers
Conversely every event that involves people on the other side of the political aisle is reported by Alex is essentially being a bloodbath
If he was there he would have had to fight his way out of wherever it was
If you wasn't there he'll find some weirdo to claim that Auntie who was beating up Grandma's
Well the police cheered them on
It's a nonsense
This is asked for him and the reality of a particular situation does not matter
The goal of his show is to advance this very extreme right-wing politics and he does that but using narratives
It's not necessary for those narratives
The connector reality
If they work
That is true enough
Skateboards worth of course Biden wants Trudeau to use more Force to help the situation
These assholes are blocking border crossings that are essential for transporting goods between the countries
You should expect that to piss off the heads of those state
Real quick
Okay if you say to me
See now after these Convoy guys got there
There's no more crime what does that tell you
Does that tell me that we should have a convoy shut down every major city in the United States in order to end the crime
I think
Are you dispute the statistics
Obviously the statistic
Assuming it's
I would look
For other possible explanations for it like
The police have gone on holiday
Responsibility whatsoever right there is no crimes getting reported right or something
As opposed to their actually not being any
So that's one way to solve the crime problem
Completely shut down the ability of anything to function whatsoever
Then you can't report any
That's one way who you can report
Ghostbusters Zach
So look this
This protest is
Is non-violence
It is
Hey is just
Like civil disobedience
Quorum million truckers from the tip of
South America to the top
This is the kind of
Stuff that Viva sort of Legends of nonviolent
I love it I would love that
And then they wanted to soften us up
And feminized man
And now they're surprised
The people understand they want violence understand they think they can beat us
Violence
Politically
Culturally
Peacefully with very light civil disobedience
Walking Bridges lights.
That's what
And you're going to try to call that violent
What Supply chains breaking down because of the two years a lockdown to the third world where we get our supplies from that mainly
Because of a couple weeks
A trucker saying hey
You attacked us for the blockade
We're going to hit you right back
Show you
BoBoiBoy
Yeah I don't think any of these people have the kind of discipline
Gandhi or Martin Luther King jr.
Might have had
It also I
Pink
From my understanding
Certipath
Actions
People like
King or Gandhi
The point that was pretty clear
Yeah it's very clear cuz I think that the nebulousness of what this
Truck and it's the laws
If you got it
Getting a criminal trial for fauci
Is there everywhere
Baby bear everywhere
There is a non-uniformity of what is the point of this that I think
Kind of hurts the
Desert of Civil Disobedience halfback.
A poorly organized from that standpoint
If your
If you're real
Point
Is
We want to make enough chaos we're smarter people than us can like sneak into the halls of
Power while everybody focus on us being assholes
Then you can't really say that your idea
I don't think that's
Nonviolent with running a distraction
I also like really like supply chain issues that Alex is bringing up
Like there's going to be some impact on it from the blockades on
The bridges that
Because there are a lot of trade goods are transported But ultimately
How much is missing most of the point
The conversation led to people that are having largely isn't a bad like the larger supply chain
Totally being impacted right specific ones that are getting hit hard
This is mostly about the automotive in to
Mystery you know car manufacturers
Rely heavily on that Ambassador Bridge
The truckers are blocking
I have been blocked
The blockade is Led too slow to Simply lines and some
People just shutting down
This seems like something I would should really care a lot about
Considering how much you talked about how evil it is that the globalist wanted the industrialized the United States
It seems like if he's blockades continue and he's already struggling auto manufacturers in the United States can't do business like
Like this there's going to stop making cars is that what they're going to do
They're going to raise prices
Manufacturing somewhere else
Where it's more convenient to that which is Oz supposed to be super against and what you're forgetting is that if they
I have a pretext
They're going to do all three at the same time and you're giving a great pretext
There you go
Alex has a friend of the worker
Anyway
This is working out really well
The
The Blockheads
It's gone
It's come down
But also they might rebuild that house of cards
I cannot express enough
You
Talk about that
The next hour
The positive things
Across the world from Asia
To the Middle East
Africa to Europe
Russia
North America Central America South America
Except The Usual Suspects
God bless
What
Aquestive resistance
Enforcement in the military
In the system
Realizes
Destroying their own future
Going along with this either you work with the system
People now know the New World Order stinks stinks
Stinks I don't know who the Jon Lovitz before him Alex Jones has decried something for stinky
In the catchphrase I don't know who The Usual Suspects
Goodnight, give me a little bit literally every
Continent except for the God bless
Luxembourg
God bless God damn look absolutely
You can see that trick their that Alex uses to keep people engaged when he's forced to announce something that's supposed to be good news for his
Team
Everyone dropping these covid restrictions so that should mean that they won
But if you let the audience think they want then they're going to get much less engaged in a
Hurry
So the best thing you could do is to make sure that every Victory comes with a reminder that this isn't actually a victory
There's trouble right around the corner so you need to stay scared
And relied on Alex to be the tip of the spear or whatever
Everything you restrictions being dropped I thought we already did this narrative like a month ago with sure we were done with this what
Multi
I don't know if this is really disoriented because
Alex claimed Victory and said that everyone is dropping their covid restrictions back when Boris Johnson said England was going to which was
For the trucker Convoy
Because the Convoy was really exciting people
If you launched
Never happened
Italy fee was reporting that was true then you know that everyone is dropping the covid restrictions
That would undercut the supposed reason that these truckers were in the right to do what they were doing it
It's more like a soft opening
You know like a big restaurant you're not sure you got a hammer out all the all the Kinks first then they were hurtful
Exactly
Like capturing a probably a wise decision
The momentum that comes from this whole situation and Ottowa in whatever Direction things end up going there
That's way more profitable than
Bland storyline is going to grow out of Boris Johnson's announcement
No way no good
Different places have
Context for how the pandemic is going
So their responses are going to be different
Sweden is easing restrictions
Cantwell Hong Kong is tightening up
Significantly
Alex has a habit of generalizing very complex things down to single variable storyline
They're easy for him to explain an easier for the audience
The Digest
There aren't a ton of different governments making decisions based on different variables and different philosophy surrounding Public Health
There's just one overarching evil cabal is make
Everyone put covid restrictions in place
And they're so scared by the trucker Convoy that they've decided to have everyone withdraw the restrictions at once
It's childish but the impulse to engage with news that way makes total sense
Huntsville
It's actually had to explain the things he's talking about
Detail his worldview and
Conspiracy wouldn't make any sense
Like a house of cards
That was wobbly from fetty WAP
Yeah it's
It's
Brinkmanship is so it's not brinksmanship that that that like
It's it's always on the knife's edge
Victory or failure but
Never know
Like it's literally him screaming like Hey listen
We played a great basketball game
Only 10 seconds left we're up by 50
Key points we don't need to worry about it that said their last shot
Counts for 51 points in it's a layup so you got to be terrified at all the time or play rocking jock
There's that silver basket even realize
Yeah it's
It's a it's a cheap trick
Text to try and create
Attention and
Continue detention
It's
It's stupid.
Alex has some other news from from the world about victories Visa V covid
Greenpath
They're all scrapping everything
In Phase 1
AccuWeather
That is a problem
A soft kill weapon tends to be a problem I haven't heard.
The soft kill weapon is the problem
Israel's decided to do away with its greenpath system but it's not Universal
And its application
They're still going to be events that require vaccinations
One with Coke significantly greater risk of
Infection such as weddings and parties
According to an article in Harrah
It's not really good news though because their reasoning was largely that the program hadn't had an effect on encouraging
Holdouts to get bags native
Felt like the pass program was quoted becoming obsolete with the ramp
Put spread of the Omicron variant that is changed the way governments are approaching the pandemic
It's tough to see how this is a victory for Alex unless he's been cheering for the virus all this time
I just not told us
Yeah I mean it does seem like his response
There is a little bit like
Everybody's kind of
Gone from trying to stop things to more covering their own ass and trying to
Keep their jobs so
Yes we're open again
Doesn't this destroy one of the
Giant conspiracy theory pillars that like
Once a government gets a power they're never going to give it up never going to take us passes away cuz the passes are than my right
Absolutely anything once they have do they have them in your hands
You're gay you're done you're never going back to how it was before
Mercury is reporting the Third
They're going back to how it was before
That would be a great part of the Book of Revelations 2 missed out is it at Subway
The the Antichrist could just be like you know what guys
I'm going to take these marks of the Beast back
I'm just going to take him back right now
By ourselves unless a bunch of truckers honk honk for a couple of days to get freaked out
No more Market minimum of sustained civil disobedience
Soon
Elements to do this
Reporting
Pales in comparison to Alex
Doing this
Yes next
God clip
Is
So
It is next level stupid next level
This is this would be almost
I think this would be embarrassing if I heard this on Project Camelot
Biomedical charity in the mentally ill
Hypochondriac
Kingdom
And trying to fill them full of deadly poisons that are made out of the HIV virus
Every organ in the body
And turn off
Your white blood cells
So you get cash
I understand
Record heart attacks blood
Implied
Carditis
And of course cancer
He never gets to those
Articles does leave that aside
And
It doesn't matter
Suddenly the Smithsonian
And science
And Physicians world
Credible news
What's in the Pfizer in moderna shot the graphene oxide
Preacher
Perfect biomedical sensor
And now they're going to be able to read everybody they say with machines it's a byproduct of what you took.
So I don't think this needs to be said but this is not in the news
Not in the news
Also are we just back on the Bigfoot
Computer chips in the I mean it's the same basic difference in
Instead of a computer chip it's a
Graphene
Scanner thing will make a chip within you or something
Mane so icy
Think that one essential piece that we need to
Just really deal with isn't there isn't graphene oxide
In vaccines
Which kind of makes Alex's argument collapse much like a house of cards
Yes and I was really confused because
Iodide
No idea what the f*** he was talking about
I couldn't find anything
About what he was
He said he did not find
Nor hair of this
It's mainstream news
Graphing biosensor will drive new Innovations in brain-controlled robots
Exact
It's just a
Funny byproduct
People that have a shot
Medical diagnosis
Wow and those who don't will just inject you with it and now you can
So this is
Nothing to do with
The article an article from physicsworld
To do with the brain machine interface
Says they can be mad
Robotic arm
Future applications
WeatherTech
Technology can go
Until recently scientist had a problem which was that graphene-based biosensors are really effective but they are also free
Quote corroding upon
Contact with sweat
That level of
How's life
Fragility
This wasn't
About implanting
These Hunters into the brain either this one does not like internal sensors it would be like EEG
Would it be called
Electrode on the surface of your skin
To work really well for these sensors but they had that durability drawback and then on top of that they quote
Xzibit High skin contact
Impedance
That a lie detection of signals from the brain
So this article in physics world is about the development of a new sensor using
Epitaxial graphene
Which is
Quote grown on a silicon carbide on silicone Subs
You know like you do
This creates a material that is as effective as graphene but without the other limitation
We mentioned earlier
The researchers who developed this new better sensor believe that it'll have a lot of applications in emerging
Technologies
Like being able to
Have like
A sensor that will be able to move it your arm or something
You know that's what this article is about you can see how about this is
Wheatley made up
Yeah he's making up
Literally everything about it
The two pillars of his b*******
Applying for a scientific article Heat
Read those graphene oxide of the covid vaccine
Has a Superbowl level bulge
Yeah that is that is a lot of stuff
Pulled from Whole cloth
By being just just
With nothing
With nothing behind it it sounds amazing
Well I mean you had conspiracy theories running around about Heather's graphene oxide in invex
Vaccine
I meant Alex
I guess someone showed him a headline that said that there is
Biosensors
Using graphene
Anyways like
Done they're the exact same.
Two they're injecting you with a vaccine that has it and then you'll have EEG electrodes
Growing inside you
Or something
This is ridiculous
Yeah you know it is that like
Weird combination of the fact that we both live 100% in a future beyond our
And also live in f***
Can caveman times tables
Simultaneous
You know like Alex can
Straight up be like there's
You know the God will if you pray right you'll
Getting you know and then at the same time a scientist like
Yeah we know how to grow substrate
Big deal we can grow
Sing
How how old is Jake live in that same
There was that there's a story to David somebody got stoned
Like what
Growing substrate and
Stoning people in the same day I don't know did you ever like grow salt crystals when you were a kid and like science class
I think it might be close
Yeah it's a little disoriented
Between state that you live in today
So that's why we were treated to listening to Alex and bewildered
That's where we live
So Alex has heard someone is not happy
About the
The trucker
And this is a person who's like an undersecretary
Something something
Apartment I don't remember I don't even remember who this person is quite frankly
This lady got on
CNN
A pleated also about how you
Flash their tires
Edit move the trucks
Alex's is
Really upset about these comments cuz he's super into this
This this Convoy he wants to make it his own
His complaint
About this woman
Seems to be largely centered around the idea
That if you slash the tires then you can't move the trucks
It seems to be him complaining about how this woman this woman doesn't know about truck
Just a bad boy. It's very bizarre
Former deputy had
Homeland Security
Coming out
Mom singing in in
Oxymoronic
Arrest the drivers
A professor and CNN analyst calls for violence against Freedom Conway
But if you slashed the tires
But even you can't move the trucks
But she doesn't seem to understand that
Harvard professor CNN analyst former Obama administration under Secretary of Homeland Security
Violence and vandalism
Convoy protesters
On the bridge that connects Detroit Michigan
The Windsor Ontario
28% of annual trade movement
For the u.s. and Canada
She tweeted
Slash the tires
Drivers and move the trucks
And in that order
Dakine heli Pro
Freedom
Security issue now
28%
Cast
The truck start over
Drivers move the truck
Cuz you don't know anything about
Rashad run your ugly tile
Delta sweetheart
So weird why
It's so weird hats
I mean there's a misogyny in there sugar
No no
They seemed so hung up on the idea of the truck
Sure it seems to be how he's taking like the masculine High Ground
Only a man would know how to move trucks
Is kind of what I'm getting out of this not like it's wrong to slash the tires in
Kind of his is larger position I think yeah there's also the sort of classic or the classes
Chisholm aspect of it this Harvard person doesn't know about tires
So stupid
Everybody's response to the convoys
Is somewhat stupid because we're only trained to deal with protesters the way protests are dealt with with
Violence that is always
F******
Spray people with a hose
With these idiots just
Dress somebody up like Hillary Clinton with a big sign and milk Chaser out of the goddamn place
Kindergarten driveway they'll be like
I just had a great plan what's that
Is CW McCall still alive
How to get of God
Have him
Just drive past college buddy rubber duck to get them to follow
This is not a violent situation this is an outsmart the Dum Dums come on Legends of Convoy
Viscira Stitch
Maybe get to Burt Reynolds ultimate Heroes
Remote problem
If somebody just ran through Auto on Yelling that they wouldn't got to Smoke's coming
Maybe it doesn't get everybody maybe some people are like this is a trick
But they're got there going to be a lot of people who go
And you know it yeah you know it 90 in Dayton OH it's a numbers game
So
Alex bedtime
Scott order of
Slashing tires
Moving truck
And unfortunately that means that he did not have time to get to his actual point in that site
I will
Want to go out with you really got a big problem on their hands
They needed to be able to have a Total Takeover by now
Spencer everybody plant down
In the future when
They can cover it up instead
What is a right
It's funny because he got too distracted by his confusing complaints
About tires
Here's the thing though Alex's Point makes no sense
He's already said that the globalist have a plan B so because I listen to Alex and I remember what he said I know that if it
Globalist plans are really as screwed as Alex's
Pretending they are
Then they're just going to release a super bio weapon to kill everyone world that they would have preferred to have an orderly kill off
You can't always get what you want as I've learned from watching house
Play play that song.
I feel it I feel like ideas like this on the way Alex began to show talking about how it's time to shift into
The prosecution
Denotes
The B of A troubling possible
I wouldn't be too surprised if the goal is to move
The town in two more calls for violence against these imaginary enemies
And he'll use any deaths that end up happening
If you will that call
Obviously there isn't going to be a mass dying off but you've seen how folks like Alex
Responded to celebrity deaths
Recently
Every elderly celebrity that dies must have been killed by the vaccines
Male trying to hijack whatever emotional connection you might have with the celebrity
Android turn that into anger against the globalist
For killing them
I suspect that you're going to see a lot of Alex doing a lot of
The
The opening part
With him saying that we weave
Declared Victory now it's time for tribunals and all that s***
Tumi
Anytime these this kind of
Conversation on the far right happens at like
Now it's time for trials
That is a that's a week-long countdown to trials and never work at the office
0 time
It's a countdown to like
We have realized that
AR
It is absurd
Joel skousen is come around and reminded us that we only have conspiracy evidence right
Things
So we might as well get a shoot
Stupid
It's troubling
So Alex
Decides
Call an audible
On this episode he was going to have some Gaston
I've no idea who they are but they got bumped
I just canceled yes we've got
The Great Gatsby
Remove the Guess Who
Suicide
And we're going to take
In the
Angela Fourth hours a day
And I'm sure.
Joining us and I want to talk
The first round of callers
Two truckers in Canada
And people there on the bridge are people there
At the Capitol
Australian
Function France Belgium people in New Zealand it's the truckers
Leading the fight here
Hell yeah let's get some truckers on the line
Got to get some truckers on the line
So we'll see we'll see if this pans out apologies to whoever you know plan to be on Alex's show getting your
Message out did not did not end up happening
I guess I worked anybody
So what are the things that Alex is really great at is
He's always right
He's never wrong
Because
You just forget about the
Thousands of predict
He makes that he just
Pretends he doesn't make he is psychic here's one that didn't come true
Probably
The early morning hours I would say
Saturday evening
Sunday morning
Divided yes
DVD attack
As well
Imaginal Car Bomb small car bomb
Too much for their cop
Police are going to
Get it car bomb
Or something
And
Course I mean I do it because I just
What I would do
That's what I do
Operation
Call flag
Okay okay
What is on Sundays
Well I mean the the cop
Ask them
Politely to go
And then most of them went
Yeah and that didn't clear things out now early now
No false flag car bomb
No I do like how he's insulting Canada like you guys couldn't pull off Oklahoma City
Bomb daycares are cowards
Cano globalist arm or whatever
Do they pull up Oklahoma City that's big-time.
Look if you want to turn Ottowa into the
Northern Ireland border
Circa teams 95
Bye
Fly
But you don't have the guts
Did you okay
Casey
That's
The frame
So Alex Goes break
Comes back
And we got a special report from John bowne
We're not going to listen to much of it but that
Just the beginning of it caught my ear and I was like
F*** you man
Tool of the cult of the left
What kind of rice the song called
Keep On Rocking
The Free World
And proceeds to be
Dell'Osso
Of the song
Hey John that song a little tongue
Antique
Wow man
Abandons her child on the streets to go get drugs
She hates her life and what you
She's done to it
There's one more kid that'll never go to school never get to fall in love never get to be cool
Yeah keep on rocking
I'm starting to get the feeling
That
For most of the things that
It's conservatives get very very angry about they have not been
Close reading on
Was almost like John bowne is responding to this song b title like Alex
But it's particles in the headlines
Is it really is
Is focus there
Just like how born in the u.s.a. is about how great it is
It's to be born in the u.s.a.
That's what it's about
Cuz it's the title
I would guess that there is somewhere a John bowne report about
Yeah about spring green sprout in the USA
Springsteen was a target of influence for a little while commercial
My God what is wrong when it's Super Bowl commercial
I'm sure John Brown did a video and he's like
How could somebody who made bored in the USA
How Could You Raul Garcia
So Alex has got some more news
He's he's pretty worried about
I have
Chance to read
The emergency by the
Globalist
New World Order alumnus
I'm Klaus Schwab over the state
Province of Ontario Canada that Auto with the capital Geographic
Martial law
Hundred-thousand-dollar sign a year in prison
And the way it's sold
Is all of you block a bridge but actually says
Then ambulance might be trying to go down
You're going to go to jail
Even if everything Alex were saying we're truth that's not martial law
But you look very
Why is that right rollers like
The left block the road you can hit him with your car
He was pretty into that yeah
Yep he's not really all that important that I agree with your sentiment
But this isn't Marshall Auto matter what
Might be like a tight clampdown on protesters but it doesn't even come close
The definition of Martha
Martial law
For Alex in the audience
Because it Infowars land
Martial law is a term that describes a Feeling
Is a feeling of whenever government does something you don't like
I don't feel like I can do whatever I want right now and probably
The government declared
They're going on here
The first is that Ottawa mayor Jim Watson
Declared a state of emergency
Conceived in the city on February
Then on Friday the 11th Ontario Premier Doug
Ford also declared a state of emergency
The province
Because we were setting up the blockades at the border crossing
Things that are outside Ottawa
Alex didn't read any statement or merge
Regency order pretty probably watch Doug Ford short speech race of this
Quote
Today I'm using my authority as premier of Ontario to declare a state of emergency
And our Province and I will
Convene cabinets to use legal authorities to urgently and orders
That will make crystal clear it is illegal and punishable to block and impede the movements
Good's people
And services
Along critical in
Infrastructure
This will include protecting international border crossings
400 series highways
Airports
Porto Airport
Sports Bridges and railways
It will also include protecting the safe movement of ambulatory and Medical Services
Public transit Municipal and provincial
As well as pedestrian walkways
Fines for non-compliance will be severe with a maximum penalty of $100,000 and up to a year in prison
Will also provide additional authority to consider taking away personal
And Commercial licenses of anyone who doesn't comply with these order
So this is a temporary
I order
But also I don't I don't do without interpretation but I
Don't say I think this is a bad idea
I I don't agree with this this
This move
Cuz you don't really need to have any further laws
It's illegal to block traffic already
Yeah
Please get a ticket
No no no it's important to do this now so whenever somebody who is
Non-white a person of color does something like this
You can put them in jail for a year and find them $100,000
I think
And then the Ottawa Convoy will
Get along very nicely I think you run the race
That potential of being president
It's used against other protesters
Always work tonight
I think that it's unnecessary. We don't have a problem of lack of laws
I have a problem of
This isn't being a
Or just like you go for too long and now it's too big of a problem for you to handle
Understand that I'm in control of the government
A bunch of idiots
Block the Convoy and there's just nothing we can do what are we supposed to do
I don't know
So Alex I'm going to skip this clip cuz it just Alex
Suggesting that the
The protest should shift to being about
Trying
Klaus Schwab and of course executing him
I can I can imagine
Big swing for a pro for a single protest to do
Definitely and ice
Again this this exacerbates the problem of there being really no coherent through line but about what this is about
Yeah
Murder the head of the world economic forum is this really the right
Place 2B rabble-rousing
Attack Clash Royale
You know what I'm saying like where is cloth swab
Currently
Probably
Probably somewhere in Europe
And he's usually in Europe
So
I don't
I could be wrong
But I don't think a few hundred people
Causing problems at the border of Ottawa in the United States
Are really going to have a big effect on how Europe feels about
Malenkov swabs
Bodied
What if
The auto manufacturers get really desperate have to kidnap Cloud swab
General Motors
Mujica is anyone could go in and get you a foul odor
He's got the the fighting force behind them
Vets
It's it is the exact audience you would want to sell
This to the vets
It seems like these folks have
They're they're all
Onboard
Great reset nonsense totally
Today are the kind of people you could get to actually like
Cheer let's get Chihuahua
Everybody's embraced absurdity to the point where yeah why not have a bunch of people in ottawa's chanting kill
Clothes swap
So Alex is going to take some calls and he's called for the truck
Her folks to call in
There's a little bit of a problem
It matters too many non Truckers
I'm not trying to be mean here in the letters I love you to death
I normally all the phones up it's just a free-for-all
But when I specifically
Want to
People
Geographic area or particular
Group are on the ground sing something
We need everybody not to be calling in
Because the call screener
Call
When I want it on a
Particular topic
And we're unable to get Truckers
To get through
Because the phone lines are all maxed out
With people that are not
In Canada
Or truckers in the US
Australia
Truckers. That are
Part of this or your view on it
And I want to get your take on the situation because
Hey Doug Ford
I believe it is like
Thousands of call Lyons now
The board's babies at the scale back
But yeah your response that is very similar to my nose like the sounds like nobody called in
Nobody from the Convoy is called
I felt that way he doesn't getting couple self-identified Truckers
One of them was there
One of them was there but then he had to leave cuz he had to work
He's like going back and forth like doing s***
That guy seemed
Cool
I don't remember anything about him actually foot
Alex has two calls that he has to get to
That's because they were on the line with the show ended yes
Alex took their number and he's called them back okay I was assuming they were still on the line
I wouldn't I wouldn't be surprised some of these weirdos
So here's the first one this guy's got it this was worth calling back in about
Something everybody can do
Active
Rusty wife
Glad you called elaborate on this yes
Now is the time in your small town or your big city
Put on the bathroom wall
How to put a sticker on your car
Banner hangs over Highway
And it will be a chain-reaction beautifully said
How fun is this
It's good marker
Here's the thing I love first
Not a fresh idea
Instant pudding banners over the highway
I mean
I mean I've seen people put Styrofoam cups in the fences but that
That's minor leagues to another level
This is not not to setting the World on Fire Within
Also this is something to tempt
To get out of hand and people end up putting really offensive should almost liners
My love
Is it to bathroom graffiti
He was really willing to start from the bottom
He was like you know what I don't know if we're ready for bed or is he a good time go to ban Todd video
Even have a message to put on a banner
That's expensive
Get yourself a Sharpie
Practice
Bathroom
Refine your message
The first few are going to be good they're not going to have it in there probably can be too long I absolutely
Your timing right here you want to come back and make sure people haven't giving you notes
Who's walking around with the red Barker giving you little paragraph breaks
So this color is Alex's pretty excited about easy enjoy this discussion of
Obviously free promotion
Convert about everything
That's what we learned at something that we have
Been tracking
For the better part of
3 years
He's finally about to happen
Brother that's why I love taking calls why should take more calls on my very soon we're going to start
At least two nights a week and once on the weekend on top of the Sunday show
A commercial-free
Podcast that's live
So everybody can call and we'll just hear from all of you amazing people
God bless you Chris
Finally going to get that caller show telling you I'm telling you right now
I don't think it's going to have
Well if past is Prelude we're going to hear about how it's about to start about six months
The week at any moment to start a live podcast
Where people can
Can call it
Can't wait anymore
So Alex believes that
Everyone thinks he's a hero
Bright because
Keith standing
For the people who are standing up
In Canada
He's standing with the people who are against
Fauci in the vaccines and what have you all over the world
But he's not a hero
No
Robin obviously
Is saying that he's not a hero
Oh okay
See if you can track this cuz this is like
I found this to be incredibly convoluted
Wow you're so nice you care about us
Car swap with your country
I'm not doing this cuz I'm a hero
I'm not doing this
Call the self-preservation
Going to put me out
Okay
Self-preservation
Like if a takedown Canada Texas is Max
Right obviously this is just a preamble for a sales pitch and it does end up coming immediately after this
But it's also Justin consist
Alex compares the situation to how he would put out someone who was on fire because that's what he
He would want someone to do for him
Which is a completely different motivation than cellpro self-preservation
Putting someone else because you would want them to put you out if you were on fire is actually pretty
Fairly heroic Act
You might want to impugn your own motives and say your act
Unselfishly
Cuz you think you'll get something out of it but you're saving someone solely because you believe people should help each other
Backflip legitimately would only make sense if Alex was saying that he would put someone out because
You know he was afraid that they might catch him on fire
Preservation
As it stands is just a muddled mess
I'm back with that is meaning
Yeah yeah I mean
In Alex's World though any kind of
Sting
Could happen to somebody else
Somebody is
Planning
To make happen
You know
Like vids somebody just in the abstract being lit on fire
Has this moment immediately afterwards like
And the globalist want to light me on fire horse
Exactly like that
So I'm going to save that guy because what if the globalist light me on fire which they're going to do
My feeling about it is more than he's like
Alright
I do think I'm a hero
Got to make sure that people don't think I think I'm a hero cuz this is
Leading to a sales pitch all I'm trying to say I was going to do what Heroes do
I'm going to say some incoherent inconsistent s*** about how I'm not here okay
It's self-preservation and also I would want someone to put me out if I was on fire
Alright
Give me money
So look
I think that the language
Is shifting
On this episode
I sent this a little bit
More there is a strain of
We have one
And now it is time for Venge
Right and that is trouble
Beautifully said but I want to be clear they started this war
Cost Millions to commit suicide or died drug overdose
What are peacefully doing this
False flag
We know we didn't do it
We're not apologizing for whatever happen
Cuz they started this
Apologies
Not by me
I know buddy I pledged to you no more apologies
Nope
I'm with your brother
That's troubling
No more Impala
No more apologies
And they started it right this imaginary villain cabal that Alex is up again
Committed all these horrific
Obvious war crimes crimes against humanity against us
Hey man if you know
They get attacked or something it's a false flag so we know we did
Do it so we have the moral Authority no matter what happens we will not apologize
This is all just
Very
I mean it's it's kind of stuff that could be taken
In a particular way I mean
It seems odd
Considering his earlier comments
Suggest that
He obviously would like people to apologize to him when they are in the wrong so it
Teams
Only reasonable that he would apologize to other people when he's in the wrong no more apologies well then I don't think he's
Title to any apologies any further
Might be influenced by Rogan
Bob putting out there
All the time
Yeah I think I might be having a tough time with that
The way he's dealing with it
Some people might have seen that been a little bit disillusioned maybe some people have been disappointed in jail
Alex
Seems to want
Do some counterproductive
ER for Rogan
You know how great it is aroga says the n-word all the time
JoJo came out
A Secret show
Sunday night
The secret
Comedy show
He did another one
He said I am not to apologize
Was taken off the air just as her jealous
Because if you watch that attitude
That is not an apology that is a clarification
D'usse
I'm sorry if you're legitimately your feelings are
Cuz if you do watch it it's a little
3 minutes of the n-word over and over again
Yes
That is exorbitant
Class of people
Alex doesn't like words that hurt a class of people
I mean
Blurt laughed at that when I was little
Words that hurt a class of people
A large grouping of people with a certain
Let me tell you identify and characteristics if I if I made Supercut
The times that Alex's used words that are meant to her classes of people to be a lot longer than 3 minutes
Weird I mean
Just leaving aside the fact
Joe is absolutely apologizing
Whether or not it was a good apology or not is another question
But if it was a little long
I mean the way Alex characterized it he is right that is not an apology
To say I am sorry if you were offended by something I said
That is
You made a
You made a mistake
No I'm not
I'm happy
I am not here to decide whether or not his apology was sufficient to her or
Heartfelt
Not
Decision
Here to make
He did
Express that
This word was something that I didn't realize how inappropriate it was for me to say
In the context that I set it in
I was at
Talking to my friends talking about rich
Pryor albums
Or whatever and then being like I now realize
That that is absolutely not okay in context or out of contact
Not okay at all
Has understanding then and I do now
It is an apology
Whether or not it's good cuz there's also some
Problems with a little bit of dumbness
No Doubt
But yeah it's not what Alex's
Expressing
When I was growing up
He's at the n-word all the time
No no he never said he's never heard it
Lockout
East Texas vs the South
People usually get more
Questions
And trashing
Well I'm not trying to put down
Common people
People need to take it back and use it
UFC fighter
Black Yoshi father
Because she understands
Yeah
Alex's
Wellington
Reclaim the n word you know
You know I've always thought
Not my first thought about people whenever I've heard the n-word haha
Trashy that is
I prefer a more high-class form of racism thank you very much it was a strange way for a
Alex to claim that he
Never heard this word used
Cuz he was Christian
Yep
That's tragic
Strange I don't believe anymore
Look
Text when he was younger
He wore a suit like a silly shirt maybe a shirt
Did I had colors that led to
Kids to mock him
Said haha haha
If so much of his career attached
This has to do with Joe somehow
Okay
I remember being like
Go to public school first few years I would private school teachers ever coming back
Sixth grade to public school
Making fun of my shirt
Blackpink
Green
Kind of plaid
Shirt my mama give me a
Clockwork Orange
There was a look at his look at his
White remember laughing at him
I started laughing too
I am I don't mind
Cousin
But the same time
You're feeling
That's okay
But
Ruby rhod
Okay this is weird like
Alexandra going out of his way to make a point that Rogan didn't apologize for saying the n-word over and over again on his show
That's strange because Joe
Did
Right he did release a 6-minute video where is unequivocal about how he sorry
It doesn't matter if using the word
Is in context or out of context
It's bad no matter what
Here is like the end of his apology
It look I can't go back
I wish I could obviously.
But I do hope
This can be a t
Teachable moment
It doesn't realize
Offensive
That word
In contacts
Sporadic
My sincere
And
Humble Pie
I wish there was more that I could say
Just me talk
Hopefully
At least
Some of you
Will accept
Sincere deep
It is at my apologies and I had to up it
Serious
Yeah
I think there's some problems with his biology mostly because it's not accurate to help Joe actually use the word on his show
He claims he never wanted to be a friend to for entertainment value but I don't think that accurately holds up
If you consider some of the times he uses like
Fairly offensive language
Clearly
Shaka defensiveness
Sometimes there's just a note asking and saying transgressive words and he does not really deal with that
In that apology
And then of course there's a very confusing explanation for his racist Planet of the Apes story
But that's another matter and we talked about that clip back when Alex was using it against him during the Sneaky Snake.
Amazing Alex
Alex's pretending to be really offended by Jose Planet of the Apes story
Gazelle all the stuff is a game.
Alex's comments leave me with two possible
Conclusions
Oz making up Joe telling him that he didn't apologize and this is Alex trying to save face with his racist flash free
Free Speech obsessed audience
Rogan is his means of presenting himself as relevant to the mainstream
Broken becomes irrelevant Alex's audience if he backs down to pressure like this and does
Stand up for racism / free speech
How to protect from the backlash that reality would cause
Was in his heart
Second possibility
Joe did actually tell Alex this stuff and his apology videos just b******* that he didn't mean
Use a trying to protect the brand and not lose the Spotify deal so he did what he had to do
Animated boilerplate apology video all well reassuring Alex behind the scenes that he totally defends racism flash freeze
It's hard for me to see a third explanation for Alex's steadfast insistence that Joe definitely didn't apologize
What he totally did
Yeah that is
I mean
Listen
Semantically
That isn't Apollo
That's just how words
Unfortunately
So you can't really argue
So that is an apology
Is there is there is there is an appearance of giving some thought to it like more than some
Apologies you hear there is a 2B
A wrestling with some
Some of it it does seem again more like we're living in different time periods you know like
He's coming at us from 1950s men being like
If you did not know this
The N word can be used in a hurtful manner now
All of my friends and I we have never heard of this before
But I have suddenly discovered so I hope this can be a teachable moment for all of you out there
Who had no clue
But using the n-word
Could be
I do think that there are some people who may need to have that teachable lesson and if Rogan's going to deliver it maybe that's a way that
Could get through to that that's what I'm saying. That's cuz they're living in the 1950s
I do I don't know what it is but it just feels like Alec
Text trying to
Control Jose narrative
For him
In a way
And I don't
No why you do that
I mean I think
Because
You want it both ways
You know you want
You want Joe to have his Spotify deal you want him to continue to be in the mainstream and if he is in the
The mainstream he has
Do apologize
There's no way for him to continue but if he apologizes and it's clear to your audience
Then
Exactly
You have to say that his apology is not an apology and you have to say that johri and Joe will say that his apology isn't apology
And everybody is happy because the status quo is restored
And we can do this all again in 3 or 4 months
It's great everybody wins the media Alex Jones
And the only people who lose are everyone on the fuc
Planet Alex feels the need to go back on Joe show-and-tell want he'll use the
Do it all the time
Alex did get a couple calls from truckers
They were uneventful
He also
Is going to need to preempt
These trucks
There's not much on my show that can preempt
Awesome truck drivers an activist
Face jail time
And a huge fines to stand up for all of our medical rides
But I like to get to your next check with this Trump nuclear war Trump
The highest
Is nuclear war
You got I guess
The
Clubs
What happened to all the colors that are holding Shea in Ohio
Josh and Canada
And Sass and Andy
Clayton and David in the order that they received
But I got to go ahead and get this this is already in my stack
Can we are
Joe Biden already said quote
There today
That's a World War
America.
Shoots down reports evaluation in Azure in a war Russia
That's pretty Sensational but he has a lot of trouble talking
Silex isn't taking this commented by Maiden contact we don't think
Send troops into Ukraine to rescue Americans left there if they chose to stay in the country
Because quote
That's what World War when Americans and Russia start shooting at one another
The rhetoric lying around from the government seems a bit over-the-top and honestly I'm not sure what the exact strategy is here but it
It's critical to understand the world war
That was being used as an explanation for why he wasn't going to do something
I do I do love that malicious level of Minnesota is just like listen
We're not going to do this dumb thing if we did something that stupid that's a World War
That's the world
Jesus man
Wow completely Miss reporting
This comment because he's just seeing the headline
Biden said that's a World War
Do you have no contact with the comments he's telling his audience that Biden has come out and said we're at war with Russia
I meant Alex has the nerve to claim that bite
, was Sensational when
Most of the sensationalism is coming from Alex's unwillingness to read
Ridiculous leave Ukraine that might be
I was thinking it's more like what I moved the moon hits your eye
That's it that's the world
I couldn't come up with the second one
We maybe could ever count
If you want if you
You come up with a better line please
Write it on your nearest bathroom stall indeed absolutely somebody go round Kenosha
Timer
So look they're starting this world war
World War Z
It isn't Alex believe that it's kind of because the trucker Convoy was too successful
But one Big Slice of the
What equation is so bad
So horrible
Haven at Main
You think they're just going to let us be them on this whole
They're going to start
Turn on believer this cars
Oh my God
So
So real
Surrealism ocean
Smoldering this does throw him into chaos for the rest of
The show
He is f***** up threatening show
I don't know what happened but he gets
Real weird
It's been a fairly normal Alex a show so far there's the
The ambition to talk to truckers the call problem with
Getting truckers on the line on Maddox come out a couple of them and then we're going to preempt them because of this breaking news
Or that's a war
Yeah yeah
So Alex is like I knew this was coming course I told you guys
Back in August literally Psych
What did I tell you back in
That wasn't
Whole story but
Multiple
Redskin
The military
Corporate world
They were told
Cuz all the big guy
Congress is involved in insider trading
Paylater
Okay
That's where we are
The Russians attack
And then
Pictures of default Airline no do you inject yourself
We should not just believe the Russians we should want to see proof
We should have international observers there
Whew now Alex wants international Observer we're all very interested in the UN sounds like you getting in
Get the f*** out
Throw baseball at
I don't believe that Alex has any of these high-level Source actually wouldn't
Be too surprised if someone told him at the beginning of fall last year that there might be trouble with Russia in early 2020
Me too
The reason for that is that last June they do have the Brussels something
Where was reiterated that Ukraine was on the path to joining
And if there wasn't anything that Russia could do to block that process from
Like an internal perspective
I could see this news reaching Alex
By about August through one of his associates
Maybe they would look back
2008 when the Bucharest Summit happened and then Georgia was affirmed as being on the pasta NATO membership
And then a few months later war broke out
It wouldn't be a terribly hard predict
Come to make though I'm not a hundred percent sure it's a predictable end up being correct
The history of the Sun
You could see some aggression coming from
Russian the face of one of these NATO Summit they've explicitly said they cannot
Not join NATO is affirmed as joint
No I don't
It's weird because I don't actually believe that that's impossible for someone to have told Alex
August of last year
Yeah I think it's possible
A lot of the times I don't believe anything you say I think he might have
Possibly hurt that he would
In 2000 it wasn't like anybody had never been like hey I think Osama Bin Laden is probably trying to do something
Well yeah cuz he already did and he's going to eat that he's that type of guy
He's not a quitter
You know
Their patterns you can see it
So
I'm going to skip over it
That's my eulogy for a soffit mud
Wasn't a quitter quitter quitter quitter
I want to skip over an interview with someone from the rebel Lady by the name of Sheila Gunn Reid
Yeah Gunn
Little man
She born for this
She's not she is basically a press spokesperson for the
It's it's not
More
Though
Alex
Does more calls
And this guy might
Broken Alex's brain
He supports
The convoys
Because of God
We don't wrestle against flesh and blood but
All these against
Hours
Against the rulers of the darkness
The sage no
I get arrested
On Saturday so I'm doing this
I don't care at all
You're right and everybody's been calling in with
That quote on how to make a t-shirt that says
We wrestle not against flesh and blood but against
Principalities
Powers against the rulers of Darkness of this world
Nnnnn
Ephesians and above
The join the resistance infowars.com because
This is a spiritual fighting
None of this makes sense Until you realize
People serving that's are literally demonically inspired
Michigan
She looks like a freaking Jacqueline
She doesn't
That is a demon
I got to say I kind of agree with Alex that none of this makes sense
Unless
You've taken all that other stuff
Ye are safe I mystical novel
I asked back to reality
That is just made up as Alex goes along as he sees fit
Yeah none of it doesn't make sense without
Spell I mean I hate
I hate it but like if that's what that guy's really all about if he's out here fighting for freedom
Then
Do that
Where a fight for Freedom needs to happen
As opposed to wear some
A****** has lied you into believing that freedom is being fought right now
Like what are we doing
Either you either you're a giant monster racist or your
Fighting For Freedom you know whatever I think it's easy to
You know make make a wrong choice on what Pro tattoo might go to
I'll beat somebody up too hard for it but I do want to say
If you do go to any protest
Bad to assume that the people you're there protesting against
Are literal demons
Right
Right don't think that's going to be a productive
Protest
Magna health
This is just labeled Alex is a lunatic
Josh
Yeah you know that the truckers are heroes
And everything but
Something price
God bless you all
It's real they hate
Who's going to oppose our mark of the beast world
Not according to the Bible
Woodwind
Chess
Interdimensional
The full spectrum of reality
And and they're they're here
There's God
Maybe universe
And then there's
They want to hurt people
They see you as an anime
They're an enemy military
That Hacienda dimensionally get you to kill yourself or hurt yourself
Troy
What
Boys and girls
That it's all about hurting our children because they see that
We don't like something the Creator
Conscious colorful or older
Twisters person this spirit
So I may hear Clips like that and it really makes you think about like I was on. I was scrolling
Around Twitter and I saw somebody posted a clip of
And he was talking about how Alex Jones is
Just as good of a reporter is anybody on CNN he's
Yeah he's been right about all kinds of stuff he's on the ball and like
Interdimensional at least I
Just
Want people to own
This
Like if you're going to vouch for Alex
Know what his
F****** show is
Hey I know that what you're doing
His backing
A lunatic
Fundamentalist I dare not
Even call him a Christian Fundamentalist
Absolutely wears a hat that says Christian with actual belief system is
A Bazaar
What we're looking at here
People to have a better understanding
Of like
I know it's fun and edgy and you feel like you're countercultural in some way to say like
No actually Alex is really good at
His job
But you know people people give him a bad Shake because of
XYZ you know do know he gives himself a bad shape
It's not as it isn't laundry ball
Yeah I know I mean nobody does Alex
More of a favor
Then everybody who reports on Alex and is just like
I mean I can't work
You know let's do the thing that's relevant to today
Let's pull from his show with relevant
Today
So it looks like the entire TV show is relevant to today as opposed to Let's
Pull from the show that's relevant and then let's pull from
Him decrying how interdimensional demons
Going to take over Governor Whitman mersal
Because she looks like what
And the other thing is that like
I do think that none of these people actually have watch
People like a Tim pool character
Like it if not actually engaged with the material that he
He's putting out
Or spent the time to listen to this dogshit show
They see the clips that
Like maybe get posted by rightwingwatch or something
Only come up with a way to make an explanation for why it's not as crazy as it sounds
Or maybe it's politically
Similar to something they believe about how Trump is great right or something
You know he what he was
You was all like Trump was right about Russia stuff and like
Hey listen listen to his actual show
Before you get it because it's
It's totally unacceptable I think
Are you here
Stuff like this
As people are
Yeah I mean
It's the same thing that they do with Trump
Is you create a fictional version of this person in order to serve your own purpose
Nobody's nobody on the far right is like listen
I understand the Trump
Has some problem
Princeton
He steals a bunch of money from everybody who's ever worked
He steals a bunch of money from everybody who hasn't worked well
He takes a bunch of money from people who are murdering other people
He's an evil guy
But
You know he was on TV for a while he's pretty good
It's true
You got to see it I think you could have a very similar breakdown for a
Without watching his show you're not aware of all of those things that are like the real
The real things that you're you're really
You're really promoting in your coat is cozying up to and
Sort of selling to your audience
What's in a deceitful bag
And I find that to be repulsive
Yep anyway
Globalists are losing
We're getting it back to spirituality here in a minute
But
Go-Buster losing
Well I mean we are ahead by 50 but again
Last shot is worth 51 point
And
They have like
50 different balls look at you into that basket
Got a bunch of those
Just know this we're winning
Things aren't going well for the globalist
They had some contingency plan
We resist but they are
Crap in the riches
Crap and they're bitching get all confident on me yet
Because
You know the
But as long as we know what
Blackouts
Wars
Field goal
Currency collapses
Waste Wars
As long as we know what dirty trading ball trick
After sleeve
Basic human rights
Super tricks they have up their sleeve are just about
Anything
I mean
Listen
They are all wearing carnations
Do not go smell
I will tell you right now it is connected
To a little pump Ono spray water right
Your face her Dietrich
Currency collapse
Dirty dirty tricks area
Take a little bit of the power out of
Claiming to understand the enemy's Playbook when they took they could do a lot of dirty tricks
Now I will tell you
Having studied them for my entire life they can do literally anything all of their powers are on blast at all times
And there's nothing any of us can do to stop it
We are winning
They have a lot of tricks
Everything
So dumb and I know what they're going to do everything
So it starts waxing poetic
A little bit here I think he got into the spirit there a little bit earlier talking about how there's the angels
And all the demons had a fight
He starts thinking about how like my whole career
It was God
God did the whole thing God didn't do this he did it
Here we are
God
Did every bit of this
Kitty God and the devil did every bit of it on the other side
That's not how it works
God and the devil are just as real as night and day
Well actually
God they're really created by
There's a chief
He's got a lot of other
Change
That Motley Crue
That goes along with his plan
And his plan is not God's plan
God's plan
Freewheel
Beauty
Help
Henry generation
Honor and just
Goodness and Discovery and end
Creation
So good
Not according
Total
Just
Definitely
A few times conscious Anaconda
Sleeping table
Go with him
In the presence of God
Believably status
The Holy Spirit
What gods or a butt
To be in God
Realpresence
Is like
Complete
Completion
This goes on forever
This is eternity this is timelessness
Oh I can do everything now
Just want to go all God I love you
Oh man
What a what a journalist
What what a great
Grass
Of One's Own belief system the book that it isn't
Entirely based
Sure
Truly an astonishing level of under
Understanding responding two different things
More
The
I've been
Gods
Crescent Shores literally multiple times
I mean
Who Among Us
Had not felt God's touch at least once
I think that would Alex
Describing a little more than
That he may have had a dream but I get a drink I think he may have had a couple of drinks
Maybe he did some hallucinogenic
1 * possible
I heard it crack on that beat
When he was in high school
You know as it as a Bipolar person
I had a manic episode once when I was much younger
And hallucinated the s*** out of everything and I to met Jesus
Now
Later on when I was no longer in that manic episode
I said to myself
That was not actually Jesus
And there we go it was me
Had I gone it was me
When there was only one set of footsteps in the lies it was you caring me Dad
I think
If you if you had just
Sort of I got to run back in a run with Wildwood
Chemistry can make
Certain experiences much more
Memorable attic
Extreme
And I think that's
What year experience
Figure with Alex nuts
Yeah he's absolutely nuts
Because it doesn't matter if he believes
What he say
Know if you don't believe what you're saying
You're so nuts for saying that
And if you believe what you're saying
Both of those things are equally nuts
So he's not
Man good reporter though really cute
Basically just like
I don't know
Stelzer or Brian stelter
I remember Jake Tapper going into his guttural voice
I am calling upon the ancient gods of sumaira to Smite his enemies
It was just like a weird day for her
Yeah you know like a regular experience
Fullness Lenny
Closest most of the shows these days we just accept it
No this is Alex's particular brand of insanity
About to his religious belief reporting on his religion
Just believe and I think he's reporting that
God created humans to destroy Satan
I think
That's what he said you're okay I may be wrong
Can you imagine the people that
Had the opportunity to be with that
And decided to break with
Saw that is slavery
Build whatever you want to do whatever you wanted know whatever you wanted
Buddy wouldn't God
Isn't.
Nest app
Oh by the way
I'm creating all these new tent
Entities
Freewheel just like I did
Little tiny versions of myself
Go ahead and have that app
Let's see
If you can even
Beat
My babies
Okay there comes the argument is
I just lonely
What
Communion
And so God
I did this
Okay
Alright so God's lonely
Or he wanted
To watch us beat up
Yeah
So I'm just going to throw this out there
For people who are Christian and who listen to Alec
Alex Jones
I just a reminder
Every bit of suffering and Terror and death Unleashed upon this world is purely because it's
Creator
Was real lonely
So I everything that you've done or ever have or whatever will do is pointless useless and is only there to make
A weird sadist
Well Alexander
It's not sadism
I think this is just sort of like a twisted and childish understanding of like that idea
Yeah those like if there is A1
Solitary unit Unity of God to be in
Then it would want to experience itself in
You know that's how you do fractions of it
Become other consciousnesses
I think that's kind of
What is the thread
Pulling on
With that I guess but I feel like he's pulling on it more as though God we're Superman and Missy and Satan was Lexi
I don't disagree
But also
I'd wanted
Babies
So God created the judge
Alright is not normal for Alex's show
That's troubling true
Alex
Understands God's plan
Mm2 script
Ends in a very jarring way
And then there comes the argument
Whatever exists
God
Lonely
God wanted communion with us
And so God
Did this
Forgot the choice
Consciousness
Weather
Preciate it
I totally
God is perfect
And the perfect spot
How to do this
The Satanist will always argue
Why is your god allowed
Why is your God allow all this
Why your God cuz we got free will
Cuz he was lonely
Universe
Texted here on Earth
Given
Cleveland
That you're willing to get hurt for doing the right thing
Nothing good
The song called apologize
Those are all the longest coming
Preaching here today
Boy wow
That's wow I thought that we had given up on the trucker protest
Cuz we had moved on to that deep
Deep philosophical Quest
Lessons about the
Meaning of life but the nature of Angels and Demons
Gods
Supposed plans nope now
Nobody
Can pull off
I mean I don't think Alex did
Don't get me wrong I think no one
Literally
Can pull off that kind of a transition
No no no no no you have to be tested to give you
It's hot man
Dubstep clunky as Hell by satanists are always at all why is there suffering
Oh man why didn't God just make a best friend
You guys could have had such great times
You're the best friends just holding hands walking across the infinite nuts
Epicness of the universe
That would have been an option
Great way to go yeah but you know
It's not good enough just have 14
Community
And then once you have a community
Doll f***
Jasmine Evelyn ship Lego
Anyway we have we have One Last Cry
Jordan
And this is Alex describing how
Keep fighting
Got it
The trucks
Big fan of the truck
Totally Trucks
Are going well they're defeating globulus
All the covid-19 sense
It behind us but
It's going to come back
And also the globalists have 100 different Drake
Right of anything
Any disaster or horrible thing phrase in the car
And the only way to stop it is bathroom Goofy
Treaty of good
There's some other things you could do but you probably almost everybody
But yeah you just got to keep fighting
Got to go get dissolution
Give me some money
Things are not going the way they wanted them to so this is
And we got to go reconstituted we are we going to rebuild our infrastructure
We got to know that we're waking up to the fight were in
This was just one battle that were barely winning
Barely wake is going to get much more serious
More
And the more we wake up
Fear
We care about our children and our future we don't care about what the globalist
Say about us
Stronger we get
God doesn't give you anything
Enemy Step Up
You're going to be one of the people that helps take down the New World Order
This broadcast is the temp
Shell command Monday
Got it
Shop
Be right now
You can't even get a reaction out of you
From that anymore help
No
Nothing there wasn't even like an eyebrow rise
You could give me somebody was just there and I'm bleeding out of his
His voice is the severe call to action if you can be a part of the actual taking down to the new world order book
Is really about the
The sale
But he's got going on at infowars.com with all these
Great pills and what have you
It's a it's a disguise call to action
I observed
Become
Little bit
To do recruiters
How it how is it that so many people get
Tricked into believing
That
The real way to defeat the New World Order is Commerce
And it's not
Biden
Design exactly
Part of the New World Order
At least in Alex's case I think it's
Because the exact same things like why do people think
XYZ is martial law
Yeah
That's right the feeling of fighting against the New World Order that Satisfied by
Supporting
Him little man
Yeah that's that's the marketing
Yeah and it's and it's a good sale because it doesn't feel like Commerce motivated to do it
Out of the fight
And it feels really good cuz you don't have to do anything and if you actually did go into the fight dude that is
Not feel good most of the time
It goes downhill pretty real quick
Real quick
There's blood you know nobody is like this $25
Kill me
I think
In a little bit of a little bit it's hard for me to tell because
Little sleep and so I am I'm kind of a little frazzled
It was a weird ride
Yeah the the
The way with which Alex's is reporting on this the Caravan
Amstaff
Clearly nonspecifically for the most part.
Selling the feeling of it being
Successful intake
Walking down the covid Sharon over whatever
Is it strange cuz I don't
I think it's a long-term solution to his problem
I think this is a Band-Aid right
I think it's going to fall off right
Before too long
But then the way that the rhetoric is also shifting within that conversation
He's really really scary
And then his bizarre religious like
Swing
It didn't last like
40 minutes of his show
Just upsetting and strain
Yeah
I feel like here's what here's what I'm feeling disoriented
Weis
Like I feel like I just watched somebody
You trying to scam me with a three-card Monte game you know
And they were moving the car then I got out of the first one was I got that
And then they just kept doing it not at a high level
But four of long
Just switching the cards around just switching the cards around until I'm just like I did
I don't know
I don't know man
What are we doing
Go to follow the car but I got bored a long time ago that I
Whitney by the person doing the car now.
I got you
Exactly
Cuz I just got to you
K
I guess
Do we still have a web we do I was going to try and come up with something clever sort of we have a house of cards
Woven Alex's devil demon
But I couldn't come up with one on the fly in a certain Dimension you could say that our website is called now that right
That is true interdimensional available on the world wide web
Absolutely
We will never go on Twitter and another really got kicked off 48 Twitter
No it was that was censorship
We f***** with time Cancel culture
Until then
Emilio Emilio on PCs
Clerk I'm Daryl rhombus
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work