Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Sit around
Alex
Damn quick update
Yeah
Going strong
And good morning I will say though
You mentioned I think you said you had big
Sweatpants
I got two big
I think it's better than the alternative obviously than I had to anticipated
I went with an extra large
Because I'm
It's barely a bigger guy and I figured
Yo let's play it safe
Relatively hirsute you know what your
Bikini line to show Absolutely that is that is a consideration with sweatpants
Yeah I was pretty surprised and maybe feel like sleep pretty good
I'm telling you bad the evil
Until you break a bin after after their 2 years old
Oh that's
The s*** yeah
You got to get old sweatpants that's the rule distressing
Distressed
For Valentine's Day or actually yesterday during the day I made a big smile
I was trying to figure I was thinking of what is
Is the last thing that she would possibly expect me to do
And big cupcakes flowers on time
Man
All of that s*** is in the past that my favorite show is is a feet British people making bread
Baking cupcakes
I may even a strawberry
Also
Secret
I didn't know until now
Milk get rid of your water get rid of your 2% oatmilk
Is the way to go definitely see that I have shifted over to mostly an oat milk at 8
For like cereal
I think it's solid milk
Replacements
That's good to know
And put it in that.
Smart move so Jordan Valentine's Day and I kind of
Because today we're going over the Valentine's Day episode of Alex Jones
His broadcast
Is the February 14th
2022 episode
Of his love is in the air
I don't know
Man I really wish you did have a few
Valentine's Day what
Beamwood Alex Jones
Valentine's Day
I'd like to talk about my love
Fighting the New World Order
Weird Valentine's date of violets New World Order how I love to hate you let me count the ways
Actual Valentine's Day content
In a second
Exposed first Chevy leave
Truckers Michael Keaton and a kitten with mitten
From Rogers Park
Okay Paka ministers
Vtrans
I'm sure you know who you are there's too many of these
But in that were bigger policy walk
I'm a policy wonk Tucker Jones love triangle is better than Twilight thank you so much
Journal about
Thank you very much do you think is a Jacobin who's Edward
Mario
Alexis the werewolf
Okay and he's whining
So he's he's Jacob right now set Edward who's
I don't know which is which
Which is which which ones
Screen for Note
Reason
Okay so obviously Tucker Carlson
So Jones is werewolf and vampire
Falling in love with ancient be
I could see that cuz Rogan his kind of caught in the middle vying for his
What is
Yeah
Is effervescent like force have we solved
I think we have
Jordans
I have
Risen above
Miami
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words
For you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe that I should almost broke
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Apologized
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
No time for break because it's Valentine's Day
Jeff is Love of the Game lover the correct
So here's an out-of-context dropped from Today Show
It's on
Like
Donkey Kong
Hell yeah alright well if we're talking Valentine's Day
What is beyond like Diddy Kong
Seekonk okay
Which one flies the helicopter
The knuckle
Cuz he has airplane right that's alright
How about this
What are the
Which ones
K rool is the leader of them
I just arrived there a problem
Is there beginning the show and we get into a particular
Really distasteful narrative that runs throughout this show
There is a a through-line that Alex
Who's going to have
About the vaccine causing HIV
Okay
And we'll deal with this
As it goes but
All the major problem
Play face are run by the
Our weakness
But we know exact
What's happening in Eastern Europe
On the borders of Russia
Delete delete
We know exactly
What is going on
Web spy
We know
Exactly what's going on with the deadly shot
Now confirm with Mainline stuff
Scientist
System
And give you
Beige
Vade
Autoimmune
Disorder
Oh my
God
Unprecedented Hy-Vee
Cases worldwide
Sexuals including from saliva
Does a good job of allowing Alex
To become a parody of
Themself
All the news ties together and there's just this one solitary story in the world
Everything that's happening is connected in each thing regardless of where
It's happening and who's involved
Globalist who are willing to destroy the world because they are so afraid
Did Alex and he's with his weirdo friends or Brittany
Embarrassingly childish level of analysis
Described as a dangerous way
Partially because of how it gives the audience permission to
To deal with information in their own lives this same way he's modeling that
Behavior is like an appropriate thing to do
Maybe it's not covid in Ukraine all being
Connected but you
You can see how Alex's behavior is really just
Kind of grandiose version of like a person
You think they got a parking ticket and that's part of a larger conspiracy against the
Everything is connected
Did get towed the night after I went to a stand-up comedy show when I was thinking maybe I want to do stand-up
And then obviously that was part of a conspiracy inside the Chicago
To keep me from getting back on stage that they do they read your mind
Actually now because you texted me about think about getting back into comedy so I could have
You've told them.
Comments I think he's just referring to an op-ed in the guardian that came out last week about how hiv-infected
Intersexual people
I'm gay and bisexual men for the first time ever
These numbers were specific just
England but the reason for this isn't because Hy-Vee is now more dangerous or straight people
It's because there's a large number of gay and bisexual men who take prep
Which wasn't an option in the past
It's always Ivy rates
Have gone down drastic
The article itself in points
Without
This isn't about it
Huge spike in HIV diagnosis among heterosexual
Instead is primarily the result of a sharps
Systane drop-in diagnosis among gay and bisexual
With a 71%
Fall scents 24
Amazing there may be some small increases and HIV numbers this year and possibly last year within the
Isn't because the vaccine is giving it
The people that's because there's a disruption of normal Medical Services
The pandemic
Just Cause 2
Could could see a slight increase
In a lot of
Conditions as a as a side effect of fat
And I'm guessing that's why everything is just something out with
I would assume so I don't know where the
That well from his glands
Well that's life
You thought about the enchiladas which we know he loves them going
So Alex
He called
This whole thing about vax
Steve's giving you HIV
That I recall
He called it early
Figured out
We were able to
Put the pieces together two years ago and
Those reports are posted
Predictions
Section
Again going back to
January February March
Weapons laws and World laws
It gives you a new type of
Autoimmune deficiency
Disorder that's much worse
Buccaneers
Pick 6
What how would you know
That there are
I'd like condition
And it's almost
Completely
Pfizer and Merck
Wait for it
Eminem
NRA
HIV
Vaccine
Only mitigate the
A little
As well
So suffice it to say just about everything in the eclipse
Is made up or both
Bananas
Set said scientists are working on an mRNA HIV
Fixing but that's not really news
Moderna was working on a promising candidate over a year ago and Alex's just mentioning it now because
There was some news that it's entering the phase one human trial
I mean after work
You've seen the f
Fricassee of the MRNA
Covid vaccine
On such a large I would be surprised
As if there's literally an mRNA vaccine being developed
For everything but as we speak cholo application
They're pretty high
Yeah yeah
Because time and dormancy is a subject that Alex is talking about Visa V this vaccine
Hy-Vee
I can be fairly certain that what happened here is that Alex saw a headline about how researchers identified a new variant of HIV
In the Netherlands and he's making up a scary story about it from his imagine
This Newberry to seem to develop into AIDS quicker than other variants
But also the existing treatments appear to be equally effective
If against it
Honestly it seems like even more of a reason to work on that mRNA vaccine
Yeah
It's tough to tell how much of this is Alex just pulling things from his imagination and how much of it is take
King from sites like natural news
Which have been pushing the evade
Xydia
It's not based on any science or studies or papers though
It's just rooted in comments made by members of the anti-vax lunatic
The group America's Frontline doctors
This is in case you forgotten the group it included Stella Immanuel and also they had a website where you can pay a doctor to prescribe u i
Ivermectin are Hydrox
Chloroquine
Also that website that they did that through was run by Jerome corsi
So I did like that reminder though
Alex has a section on his website
Predictions that he's gotten right eye I can't believe that
Metro
Tonight's good time to
Check in on what's on my page
Call boy
I can't imagine it like we've gotten a few things that have been like oh weirdly similar
Joking about accidentally
Maybe seeming fairly accurate
I can't imagine
What kind of
Dork I would have to be to be like
Check out the damn freezing I mean you're the one who's going to have to edit it I don't remember what you
You predicted today
Alex's
Call Alec
Alex Jones told you everything about Chemtrails in 29 2009
I don't I'm not sure how correct that prediction is on his part
That's weird
Here's another one
Alex Jones at Alan watt discuss mind control via
EMF waves
I didn't know that wanted to
Is that a prediction
If you just
Even his prediction is just
We discussed some
Control I mean I guess if you predicted that you were going to
To chat with him about that then
A good prediction
This list of predictions is completely f*****
One of them is quote
Fake alien invasion
False flag exposed in 2008
We experienced a fake Alien Invasion full flag is I feel like that would need to happen
For Alex to clean but he got the
You would need to
Experience.
Yes
But have you considered that it
It did and you just don't know about
Or he made the prediction that because of the predicted being made it didn't happen
How fun
A buddy some of these are just too vague
Do you really know what they mean but then there's things like
He's only gotten right if you
Except Alex as the sole source
About whether or not he's been right
Princeton's quote Alex Jones
Coronavirus engineered bioweapon
Proven correct but Alex's information
Space treats it as if it's been proven
Tickets to pretend
Look at seems like
That is that is cheating
That's brutal
There's ones that is our true at all
Infowars predicted door-to-door vaccination
Maybe some vaccines are offered
People in their home so I guess I'm going to like the availability of on-demand vaccination could be seen as an accurate prediction
But the video image says quote Forrest inoculations are here so this one's bulshit is
With guns going holthaus
You or shooting you a heads-up
One-armed I'm biking back makeup
Yeah
This page is full of s*** but mysteriously absent are
Thousands of prediction
Very specific
Entirely wrong
Just this week he predicted A Car Bomb false flag of the Ottawa Convoy on Sunday morning
Sure that was
Incorrect I can't count the number of times
Predicted an imminent nuking of u.s. City often
Chicago and here I sit
On nuked City
Embarrassing attempt to log reputation in history
Probably get more in
Into exactly what it
Steph
You said butt
We've done 650 episodes about it already
I see now that
The type of page that we would do
Which is an obsessive chronicling of literally every single prediction we've ever made along with weather
Whether or not it turned out
The way that we predicted it
Usher our percentage will be
Incredibly low
But that's how accurate we are we want to make sure you know
TriStar Productions
There was a part
Has me that wanted
Until like haha I'm going to go through all of Alex's prediction
I can't
No we do not have a team of 300 researchers with the next 2 weeks on their hands
Might be fun to create an alternate page like all of these things that he's predicted to have not come true
Dialects with guns
Top of the list
So Alex shift over from this
This medical narrative into talking about
Ukraine Chelan
Oh man
8 years ago
And brag
5 billion dollars
Okay so Alex's referring to a 2014 interview
The George Soros day with fries acharya aunt
You can look it up
And you'll find that he doesn't brag about overthrowing
He's worried about Putin's efforts to destabilize Ukraine and here's the
Exchange that Alec
Mischaracterizing
Zakaria asks
Quotev
First on Ukraine
Things that many people recognized about you was that you do during the Revolutions of 1989
Funded a lot of dissident activities
Civil Society groups in
Eastern Europe in Poland to the check
Republic are you doing similar things in Ukraine
Soros replies quote
Well I set up a foundation in Ukraine before Ukraine became independent of Russia
And the foundation has been sunk
Thingiverse
Who played an important part in events now
The term dissident activities here refers to activities that are opposing and authoritarian government
Things like Free Press organization
There was just saying that the
The foundation he set up in
Ukraine is that an impact on the transition from being under Soviet rule
The present-day where it's at
Independent
It's not a matter of interpretation Alex's just
Lying about this club in soros's
It's just
I'm sorry
Could you read that one more time
I heard you say
So proud
Hahaha but I
Thinking back
Final a billion-dollar real gaslighting
I remember anything about it
Alex
Planet
Haha
I don't think Alex would be at scatterblast
Movie Into The Rat box
Yes
So look
Alex is gout
Some interesting feeling
About the situation in Ukraine and Russia
His analysis is stupid and I don't really care too much about it
There's something
The underlying
Some of these comments
That I found
Really weird
In coming days and push back
Why are you saying
Because it's poking the Russians over and over again while they accelerate the attack
Russian controlled areas in the east of Ukraine
Is a proxy war
Indoor Regional War
Into a World War
Rates I think he responded exactly the part that I felt a little bit strange.
Find the Russian control portions of another sovereign country
Yeah
Confused as to what we're doing here
Are our borders that has been in
Encroach by another country
That's weird
Keep send stuff like that multiple times and it's just normal
But I don't think
You said if it was a different country that rocks
Look just because
The UK has
I don't know anywhere between 10:00 and 15 colonies
In the United States that any s*** I already wrote the bed
Nevermind
Mexico was like occupying
Well you know what he going to do
Where we're going to start a World War over this
Is it worth it
Can you take some Michigan
Whatever
Not
This is the whole issue right this isn't the problem is occupied
You get the fundamental problem here I feel like you're just on the Russians
Yeah that's what you're saying
Blue Lake
Here's another clip of him just casually throwing away that like
Hey Russia is taken part of Ukraine
Russia is
Russia
Ukraine
Russia now says that us and NATO are building up weapons
AR
Swai fish
Why
Arapaima
Just blown away
I don't understand
Mohican
Because I don't think that this is consistent with his earlier positions that I've heard him Express
Just
Just say you want to give Miami to Cuba
The Cuban
There's enough Cubans in Miami
They get it now okay is that how it works fine
I don't know or I mean like just come out with it and say that you believe that Russia has the right to invade
If they believe that very
Just extrapolate that out and
Say UALR into the Soviet Bloc returning
Soviet Bloc was
Really stoked about trying to be more than
How big it was
So you might as well say that
I think
The politburo should rule the world
We may be like slippery slope and get here a little bit
It's not like
It's not totally disc
Connect it
It's not really a slippery slope if somebody stated objectives
AR
What you think
Slippery
Slippery slope
Alex
Agrees with it that
The kernel of it is kind of
Give the same
There is a wreck
Nation on Alex's bar
In 2014 took part of
Ukraine
If that's fine
Was
Well it wasn't but now it
Is that kind of what he's doing is kind of doing just like this wave wave like
Look if you wanted me mad rush about taking over Ukraine
You had 2014 and you did nothing about it so they get it all help because I I know that I've heard
Alex in the past David
Isn't what happened
And that Russia is like
Like the Crimea is actually
No it's actually part of Russia
Call Great Knoll a crate
Most of the people there speak Russian
And like
The wave
He's talking about it now he's
Is different than the way he's talked about this
Situation of the past
Recognizing
Budweiser came in
And whenever
Samaria whenever we do this again in a couple of years our lesson
China's take
Can Taiwan back
Whose side is Alex going to be on
You know I think
I know but he hates the Chinese but he also is against
Clearly it's
If it's wearing a similar situation
It's not Russia he doesn't
But you can invite
That's fair
Because Putin so Christian except for
Fraud
So this is this is this is a strange
The gullibility and the cheapest of the public
Brought these
The wolves
Not your fault
Me and I even describe.
Incredible future
We've got to get
These satanic forces
We can do unlimited things together
Is unlimited
Potential Unlimited
You need cuddles
You will have total victory
If you want
You can't see the devil you can't see.
The formulation if you can't see the devil you can't see God is a very bizarre theological stance
Actually makes total sense in the context of Alex's stupid brain and his oppositional nature
His
Underlying premise that must be true for the statement to be true
And that is the only path to seeing God is to first see the devil
This implies that the only path to Christianity is aleksandr is through the devil
You encounter the devil then you see God in
In contrast
God in this understanding appreciates on its own
God is really only understood in opposition
To the devil
This actually makes a lot of sense for Alex
Because it's essentially how he operates enforcement matters to
Everything is defined
Solely by opposition
Which is to say
Defined as good because it is against the thing Alex has decided he's bad so this we can put into
Do we can put this on another in the column of things that would suggest Alex himself as a
Satan worshiper
Because Satan would obviously assume God only exists
In relation to himself
So I'm going to go ahead and say yet again
Alex is a saint
Let me think about it like in politics
It's only really are rooted out of
Fear and pain
12 discovering
Nonsense about the global
Write the evil and the good in opposition to the evil
That is in the world
Because it has to
To stop the
Right of which we all are
Simultaneous hit it's really strange but like
A b kind of
Take me to make sense
Narcissistic
Yeah but it's also stupid
Yes
Which is how most nurse
Psychopaths
You're not wrong
Too much
Further in
To the the vaccine HIV thing because it's nonsense
And there's not really a whole lot to even break down
Skip ahead to where Alex does a really long Dracula impression
How about George Soros
Do they found the club
Alive right now but
Ukraine
War with Russia prachi by George Soros
Turn on the front of that we posted
Blah blah
Crowley rituals what do we do
What is happening
Prince Charles
George Soros
Really a good sign
Impression or whatever when you have to say I am blank in the middle of it started out as
Is Dracula Edmund slowly tilted towards
Like all this that has like
Hey Ridgeview we got to get up
Prince Charles where to get a picnic basket
I didn't know that Sarah's work
Looking for
Charles event that seems like news
She at
I think Alex was thinking of Prince Philip but he's also dead
Weather
I don't think Soros needs to work
Royalty
Hold on I have to take a step back I think it's a reference
Expect Prince Charles
Is descended from dragon
From Pennsylvania probably what that was
British royalty is somehow dragged
Keep a keeper blind
So speaker
Thanks for the inline
Where am I
Another appearance
Rodger Stone
Since becoming around a lot really really needs money
Is Rodger Stone
But we came up for air lap
Never really brought back to Fox like he was
4 years ago in 2017
He came out and said Trump was being spied on and seconded us
He was marked for Destruction
I've been through hell
Warriors thinking you battle-scarred and punished
The fourth leg of the Russia hoax
War with Russia
Well Alex, it's great to be back with you
Well said
Alex and Rodger doing a Victory lap
Because they're just parroting the right-wing media has erroneous claims about this new filing from
Special counsel John Durham
Regarding accusation
Sunset Michael Sussman a Cypress
Security lawyer
Had lied to the FBI in an interview about the Trump campaign
Potential Rush
Spintires
It's very complicated but it's all about you.
The Durham filing wasn't reporting any new information and the coverage evident right with medians
Been totally inaccurate
To create this perception
That it proves that Hillary was spying on Trump
It doesn't prove any such thing and
I think that Alex
Rodger
Like to use it to get
But I mean
They were right all along
Everything
Absolument up for air lap
I do I've never I mean I've watched
Some professional swimming Olympics
Swimming
In the last Olympics
And they were swept by Katie Ledecky
Not one lap.
Did she just
A whole lot
That's hard
Do do let's just do a quick take a breather lap
Via the thing
The thing here is that
Alex
Is
Heal
Always refers to this
This globe luster holding me underwater and then you get away and get my breath
You got to get a big breath in order to
Sustain yourself next time you get there.
Yes yeah and so like that
So Rodger is an interest
Thought that actually I was like
Wow you're right
That is not
I'm the only person you know
Who was actually investigated during Watergate
And also investigate enduring russiagate
I went
At age 19
Before the Watergate
Grand jury
Then as now
I did nothing wrong
Wild you are the only person who's mixed up in Watergate and the Russia investigation
Really are the f****** Forrest Gump of
You know what
You can have a couple other things so that last like the Brooks Brothers riot
Stop the steel effort to the 2016 elections the latter which
Who's connected to the event January
I think Rodger selling himself short of his lobbying for evil governments over the years I mean this is a
This is a man who if you have murdered more than 100,000 people
You know Rodger Stone into
Connecting thread through a lot more than just Watergate and the Russia investigation
Conover
Man
That's such a weird
Sometimes you see those like pathway through history and
You just see some a****** like Rodger Stone pop-up
I need to be more characters in reality I'm sick of it
How is it possible
Somebody stop him how old is nobody it's like oh it's like when you see the Joker get out of Arkham Asylum again
Do you like Jesus Christ
Put it somewhere darker
In that case it's like
Narrative ksenia
Reality shouldn't require Zach
Joe Rogers
Some stuff to say about this Durham filing
It's not really not really
This is the greatest single
Political scandal
In American history
This is the greatest show
Single no
Abuse of power
That we have ever seen
Let's just find it
If we met
Barack Obama
And Hillary
With the approval of Vice President Joe Biden
Who was in the room when this was all approved
Use
Authority of the United States government
And the extraordinary capability of our intelligence agencies
To spy on
And there and thus
Launch an investigation
To remove
A duly elected
President of the United States
Donald Trump
Against the people against the Republic
So none of its proven in the Durham silent
This is a bit complicated so I'm just going to read this
From a New York Times article that explains the information in the filing
Concise manner
The filing was ostensibly about potential conflict
But it also recounted a meeting at which Mr sauceman
Presented other suspicions
When's to the government
In February 2017 Mr susman told the
The CIA about internet data suggest
Thing that someone using a russian-made smartphone
May have been
Connecting to networks at Trump Tower and the White House
Among other places
Mr. Sussman I had obtained the information
A client a technology executive named Rodney Jones
Another paragraph in the court filing said that Mr Joss company newstar
Had to help maintain
Internet-related servers for the White House
And that he and his associates quote
Exploited this arrangement
By mining certain records to gather derogatory information
About mr. Trump
Gotcha
They're a couple of very important clarifications that are missed
Spivey
Reporting on this filing
The first is that there was a
Spying on Trump in the white
And that's not even with this is referring to
The DNS logs from the White House that are used in the analysis
The Obama
After the Russian hacking happened
Began an investigation into possible malware in the White House
In particular russian-made phone device
Yotaphone
Connecting
Genetworx
As they were researching this matter they
The data from NuStar to attempt
How to find other potential breaches of security
In terms of yotaphone
Connect
That works
And in the process they found indication
Their Communications with you.
The servers and Russia coming
From networks in the White House Trump Tower
And Mr Trump's Central Park West
This was where the information came from not from any spying on trump it was from researching
Dental relief
Compromise networks in the wake of the
What is the Rogers
Is this making s*** up
Which is
Who's cutting his bread-and-butter
Yeah yeah I mean it's way better than saying
No no I was totally convicted
Did for a reasonable and logical reasons
Frankly I got off light
The actual should I did if I told you
Boy you ready
Sounds like buddy you don't even f******
You thought I found religion this time
Find if you guys
Accused me of my real cry
Strong
So you talked about lying about his case
Actually comes up
We do know that
Former Director of National toast
1000 pages of evidence
Which implicate
Not only John Brennan
But also the former CIA director
But also former FBI director Comey another words
Both of them were informed
Did Trump was being surveilled
Both of them
Chose to use the
The falls
Narrative of Russian collusion
Open investigations and a smear
The president
When I tried to say this during my own trial
I was gagged
When I tried
Expert testimony forensic evidence
I was barred
That defense
I don't know what evidence has or hasn't been turned over and neither does Rodger so we'll see what happens on that front
The beginning of that clip
Justice
His trial is b*******
He was gagged because he was posting threatening s*** online about the judge in the
In the case of every opportunity to call witnesses or any kind of Defense you wanted to be
Chose
Not too
That was some
He specifically chose not
To do
There's a Brazen no rewriting this
It's exactly what you
Yeah it's like
It's like he's f****** I mean
It's weird this
Tortured
Simile but it is a little bit like he's Kirby
From Kirby's Dream Land
He just sucks it inside of a man transforms in a newbie
About it like your trial head
What are you talkative they wouldn't let me
They wouldn't let me introduce evidence
Saying that you did everything you responded everything I'd really turned over every type of railroad
Guinness down I mean obviously I spent a lot of money on lawyers and then
I think that their argument really Falls
The part
Look at it
Like
They don't present themselves
As blameless
And everybody else's
Screwing them over it becomes
Only too obvious that they are up to no good
Yeah
What is already too obvious they're up to no good
Not as they are
Future is blameless
So more stuff
And I don't know it's just a bunch of dots
I don't really care
Sonic skip ahead to where Alex talks about
The tomorrow about the Durham report
Existing
For the ones that
On the payroll
And so important such a big deal
Doesn't want
What's the news
But you're not want the news out right now
Filed from
Groups
Candida servers and do all that
To the news
National Security
Going so
It's always the top lawyer isn't it
It's always
Just about
Prestigious lawyer in the world about the matter of Clinton
Things are the actual
Point of the Durham filing
It's not actually an issue at all
If Michael Sussman had been
Billing decline
One campaign for research he was doing
What's the reality is that Sussman work for a Perkins coie
Who's contracted for a flat
Retainer by the Clinton campaign
There's no evidence that Sussman himself actually was
In contact with the campaign
That's
The issues
That Durham is a representation
Shouldn't be allowed to be his legal counsel
Because he claims they have a conflict of interest having represented other folks
In terms of the Russia investigation
In the course of
Also claimed
To the FBI when he said that he didn't have any clients when he met with them
And provided information about the yotaphone matter
But for what it's worth
Sussman's lawyer
He never claimed to have no class
Right so
We will see what happens here but there made
Not even be
Would be a little bit unwell
I would be surprised if a lawyer
Claims to have no clue
Don't be a little surprising right
Yeah really
Not doing anything right now guys I'm not trying to sell you on ship
Because nobody's hiring
Anyways I'll work for you
Oz just responding to right-wing headlines about this filing and then
Connecting Woody imagines they say to other narratives he's working on
Hey it's just completely detached
From reality
So Rodger takes off
Farewell Rodger Rodger Stone legal defense
They did do some
Other plugging
But we don't need to belabor the point
Alex goes back from break
With the the cell Teresa ultrasound
Car horns
Freedom worldwide
Martial law Krusty the peaceful truckers who don't want to be forcibly context
MRNA
So so good
Back we heard Alex the interview a guy named Jeremy Mackenzie about the
The Ottowa Convoy and we discussed
But I wanted to loop back to this because I've learned some new information about Mackenzie since that episode
He's a Nazi
Defacto leader of a group called The Plaid Army
Who have been described as I felt bad already about about already bad
Well I always I hear they like that I'm kind of like well you know the Bosstones
Call bad in plaid
Lizard neo-fascist
We believe in the creation of a cup
Country called
Diya Gollum
This country would include the Canadian provinces of Alberta Saskatchewan the Northern Territories
And the Yukon
But also would extend down and diagonally through the United States
It would also include Alaska Idaho Montana Wyoming
The Dakotas Iowa Missouri
Nebraska Oklahoma Utah Colorado
Alabama Louisiana Texas tennessee-kentucky the Carolinas Georgia-Florida
Mississippi
And Kansas
What don't they get
Would it just be the Northeast the West Coast
In case this needs to be stressed Alex was endorsing and piling around or the guy who believes that about half of the US states should leave the
The union informal weird diagonal country across
Northern
North America
Yeah so this group is also notably accelerationist and that poses a really
Serious concern that they might be the exact sort of folks who would see these protests
Flashpoint
The escalate into outright violence they view as necessary to create the world that they want to see
With a weird diagonal country across North America
Guess you're really not going to be able to negotiate
I don't think so
This makes it really troubling that even prior to his appearance of Alex
Mckenzie was arrested for possession of
5 restrict
Firearms
Prohibited magazines body armor and ammunition
On top of that on Monday at 13 people were arrested at
Coats
Border crossing
Where are there were protests
What's happening
And in the process a cache of guns and armor with c
You sure
There was a patch on the body armor that was seized that said
Diego Luna
Which might be construed to imply that MacKenzie's GroupMe of that at least partial ownership of this weapon
Since cashcrates is really f****** scared
Being a pseudo Nazi it looks like MacKenzie
That socialist countries
It's right next door to the Convoy
I was hoping you were going to say that you did
Discovered he was an aspiring country star
No he's not
I don't know it and
Listen
I don't think that
The punishment bureaucracy
And I don't even think you should be put in prison
Having a bunch of
Illegal
But I don't think you should be allowed to have any weapons after that
0 weapons
After you get caught
With a lot of illegal weapon
I believe that there are I think part of his like parole or whatever does involved he can't have
At least
Yeah but if you're a terrorist
With a lot of weapons
And they get it
Skip
So I look
That was a bad guest
Alex's Park
Add note that the future will make it look
Like a great book
Don't know
But I would say that this next book
Maybe worse
This guy
Holyshit
I expected nothing out of this interview cuz it's just another one of these like hydroxychloroquine Ivermectin doctors
Marble
I think I've heard him on the show
Before because he he made a website called like my
A free doctor
Where he'll prescribe ivermectin for people
And stop the very hot
Industry
Sounds great Blown Away
This interview is
While
Okay this guy is
Doctor marble
He's lost his f***
That's what I would say
Man
Is the
Travis president
I would drop a bomb on the world economic Forum in Davos the next time they meet
In the plandemic
Yeah they're the enemy
Gates of Hell George Soros
All all those leaders
Marxist Mark Zuckerberg
Etc etc
Put on the world
This is really letting this dude talk
Yeah he wants to
Bomb of the world economic forum
I mean who Among Us has not thought
They're all there
This is this is a little bit more extreme and some of the language that usually get
Gets thrown around
Politically
He says I were president I would bomb the world economic
I don't think it would
Get the results
He thinks it
I know I think it would be satisfying
A very short. Of time but then the problems that would arise from it might be
Might be an issue I would assume so
Also those dorky ass names
Videos for everybody like that's one of the real sort of
I mean it's a minor problem but it's really annoying
The lineage of the assertive
The legacy of Troy
Giving people
Nicknames
Derisive
I mean is it you made it really popular like the right
Legacy of Nick Cannon's Wild n Out
Look
Obviously roast culture number on this in the right-wing in particular I think Trump
Calling people like Little Marco and stuff
That's what they are
Trying to recreate the excitement of
Of that
They thought it was funny
See the thing that made it funny was that it was Trump doing it and he is an inherently
Cartoonish
Right. George Soros
You're just an idiot
And you sound stupid you sound like a child
Mark
Yeah
He has somehow managed
Mr. Magoo as a child his way through life
Consider his contacts
Marco Rubio Little Marco like on stage
In a debate
Or something is
An entirely inappropriate setting for that kind of why
It's notable
Is you talking s*** on a podcast
Alex isn't really really all that like
Edgy
And I think it's
Mainly Edge
Because they
Especially for
Trump's way of doing it it's cuz it's directed at people who are so thin-skinned they can't help
But be like Jerry called me Little Marco and are definitely not used to that
Everybody agrees to be professional
So
This dude
Are marbles
Ben marble
Has
An interesting theory about what
Really made this
This pandemic
Not enough bombs on the world economic
Certainly that is probably part of it
But he has a theory that it's
Political correct
This is a bioterrorism
Program no-doubt-about-it in the
Single
I would also
The globalist a Davos
Is the Great Big Sea depth.
Oh you know what your five-year-old to be talked about transgenderism you're racist
Paper tiger
It's like The Wizard of Oz
It's a hoax
Yep did this fear of being called a racist everybody will go to extreme lengths to avoid being called a racist
Political correctness
Killed around the world
Say go in for do you know 1946 they made it illegal to be a Nazi
Well when this war is over
Wow
While this guy is stupid
What a really really dumb things
One thing I wanted to ask you about I'm sorry I interrupted you.
What
How do you do that
How would you ban political correct
Well
I mean I think ultimately the undercurrent of what he saying is that
If you don't allow me to say the n word
Everybody else is going to die
Yeah there's a little bit
I get
A strong feeling that this guy's really sensitive about people calling for AC
Why is it that I can't say the n-word and not be called a race
What are the other
These are the kind of conversations that I would love to have in a different setting than on Alex's show because like
If this guy said this anywhere else
Sorry like
How
Do you propose we go about banning political correct
I mean if you said that allowed in a place where there's
Four more people expect
Everyone to stop what they're doing and turning
Stare in your eyes and be like
Stop it
What policy positions do you advocate
4tube and political correctness
If I say something that makes you feel bad
F*** you
If you say something to make me feel bad
You're going to die
Is it
Here's the other thing
Situation where political correctness is me saying that what you said is racist or is it political
Preakness anybody
Stopping them
So therefore it would be illegal to not be racing
Your point is good but I think you're skipping over Al
A lot
Which is first
What is it that you're trying to ban
When you say you're trying
YouTube and pull it
Pickle correctness
People saying with
Things are racist
8 is that it that's the feeling I get legal for
For people to say that things are race
Let me mess with the whole ant icrt thing
A different word
Because you can't legislate Concepts
That's a very dumb things
If you can do well I mean out of basic level that is true but I just
Yes
This guy
So concerned about free speech
And
He's advocating for something they would necessarily
Require a
Drastic
Limitation on
And a massive surveillance industry to enforce
You bet
So he's dumb
Anyway I might be is about Soros
Or I'm sorry
Sore ass
And he's
And I'm doing great job as president
Bill Gates
Fauci in a few others
Minimum they need to be arrested in on
Protect
Oh man this guy seems like he's he's a little bit
Here's the problem
Here's I swear to God here's my f****** problem who in
Presidential election after this win the campaign on the right is just going to be
Here's who I'm going to kill
Here's my here's my list
For me for this list
And that guy is going to pick a different list of people to kill and that's it
I love you be like
I like most of this list
But I mean Skylander mines on there
Every any other let anybody their name would have been great hardship
And then
Two years after that they can be like politicians are all liars even kill anybody on these lists
Going to be a whole new handle
Seems to be
Clearly preoccupied with the idea of
10 executive
Feeling erratic
Not a great sign for his idea of politics
Not a great sign for his ideas
Democracy or how
Our system work
Kill people
As a doctor
The way I want to solve problem
Is murder
But other people doing it cuz I need to preserve life
He is a big fan of those German
Fake trial
Mock trial
Good stuff so if you miss the episode where Joel skousen was on he already explained to Alex how these are stupid and they are
We are going anywhere
But Alex is back to believing in because Gavin isn't on and someone who believes in them
You know Rider full Mitch he's a lawyer in Germany
Mock trial
July 4th
Everything that's going on in
But we really need is some of the
No the police that the upper level
Military to start arresting these evil people that need to be arrested and imprisoned
And then we can hold trials
I'm actually in favor of
What time of War
It's interesting to me how one of Alex's like
Big thing
And all of his early earlier career was Posse Comitatus
He was out yet shirts that he sold with it
Any idea that this guy is on here suggesting that the military should be arresting
People
Legitimately be
Hypothetical to anything Alex
Could listen to
Hi I mean
He should be furious about that ID
This man
Is
What is the most incoherent raving lunatics that I've heard in a long
And it's not because
And it's not because he's saying like oh aliens are coming
It's literally he's just saying
Varian same s***
That should
Everything I've said is about how much I want to kill today all I want to do is murder I want blood lining the street behind
Find me I think it's wrong
I think the death penalty
I want of a Bomb drink
Like if you take away the the military arresting people problem
You still have like
What he wants is the police
Without warrant
Seems
Yes this is dicey understanding these people have
The government is essentially maybe what if we were all 25 people living in a small town in WoW
Wild West Exodus
Can stop the one Thief that came through in the last 20 years we all hang them and then we're like
Seems to be
Pretty consistent with our obsession with
Understand
You think dr. marbles doesn't understand govern
You're about to be proven wrong
So we have a completely corrupt Supreme Court majority of Congress that has taken the poison so we haven't
Stop Congress
Global leaders by Justin Trudeau
Why is that
I mean
This is ridiculous
So how would take
Backpack
Sir Alex has to take a long breath there
How do IRAs
Identify even even appear
Consider this
Wow I walking through mud 11
What do what do I buy
Asking myself that question the world economic Forum or should I
Not being
Should I
Weird that I'm against that or should I just let it
It seems so hyperbolic
You can't be serious
But also
Hundred percent means it and we should not allow him anywhere near any powerful position a or a microphone
The Supreme Court
Most people in Congress leaders have all been vacs
Weather in on this remote
Conspiracy therefore we have to
Overthrow all the government
Right
Then I guess it's like get rid of all the Supreme Court Justice
I mean he does realize that he's
Is it accidentally 100% accidentally poke
A massive hole in Alex's whole story
All of our Supreme Court is vaccinated
Most of Congress is vaccinated
Why even f******
Bother with a revolution
They're all going to be dead
That's a good point
There's a designated Survivor though and you know that guy's not vaccinated
Admittedly it be real bad if your designated Survivor died of covid
True
Yeah that is a good point no need for revolution if you believe your pictures away
Yours anyways just hang back hang loose guys you have a barbecue just chill out
Yeah just chill out so try to overthrow
Governments are already done
REI
I find this
S2b
Abusing a little bit but also like this guy seems
Unwell
Oh no he needs
Yeah the word territory unless like
Two-spotted more like somebody
Peet's intervene
There needs to be a professional involved it feels a little bit that way
Alex
60 people are getting like
Booster shots
Compulsively
Can't Stop
I think he does think that they're doing that
Call Laura
10 shots
Okay well doesn't work
Lester the grating
Miss causes insanity
The cause of this Mass formation
Psychosis
Global map
Yeah man so people are there like
This
How to take eight
I'm just going to keep taking them
And that's
Because of
Political career
I mean
We're at a point
With this dude where am I
Legitimately
How do you go to a grocery store
Because your brain is so whacked out
What could you
Would like anything in a grocery store concept
Everything is political correctness
Political correctness is people wanting to get shots
What's the name of that the driving the crazy isn't named after a racial slur so it's politically
Break bread
Little Debbie she's too small
So Alex
You know he just wishes
But all of his dumb friends were wrong
Don't we
You know.
Discovery of HIV with wrong woman
I wish that
Father was wrong doctor you. I wish that
Inventor of mRNA technology
What's wrong
Dr. Malone I wish you were but you're not wrong
Major insurance companies
10-18 256 or 18 to 64
Bigger than WWII death rating
It's probably political correctness yeah I would assume so
Is Ali Aziz weirdo friends of Alex's are wrong I hope that he can take some comfort now that we've
You know disabused him of the notion
They're onto something
The insurance company saying there's a huge increase
Is true
This is about a guy named David
Send the video of one America Insurance
And said that they are seeing a massive increase in deaths in
Upwards of 40%
I was absolutely lying about them saying it
It's not covid
This is about Coke
This include the comment Davidson made that reflected that even if something doesn't immediately app
Appear to be a death
From covid quotes
The virus could have triggered a separate illness that eventually leads to
To death
This is just
To the one that are definitively covid where there's a chance
Play the covid side effect led to a fatal condition
Alex is lying about this to make
It seemed like the insurance company said that all these debts are covid because he's a liar
The time and that's just
Standard practice
Does he run in football
Nonsense
And I mean
If that stuff
That's Tuff
You know
I just imagine being somebody
Who is so
Integral to
The Non-Stop
Stream of death
Reading a study that's like death
Sir up today and being like
Well got to go to work
Not like
I am a true f****** cancer upon all of humanity
All of these debts Rising
Are partially my fault
More so than many other
And then
About him
Well you have your pot committed
Santa
So
You know it
I think there's a lot of people to talk about
Howard
It's tough to
Get people who were in
Conspiracy communities and like
Maybe qanon
Now they believe Alex.
It's hard to get them
Out of that
D radicalization is really difficult right
And guess what
It apparently at this is
The perspective of doctor marbles to
Oh yeah but in reverse
What they believe is fake science
The PC Kobe
You can just pretend you're whatever your wallet
The woman you're just a day or
And all your enemies are Russian just cuz you don't want to go to war
Yeah and anybody who says it is sitting against that is racist and all this
Just nonsense and they're just
Crazy
Brainwashed and
It's hard to bring them
Panda
Breathe
Thousand
Renovation
Yeah I would encourage
Patience if you got sick with covid
See how that the money is
That narratives coming back I guess
World economic forum
HEB
Clash Royale battle and kill them
Hey this dude this dude
Political correct
Right right right
I mean his first hundred days in office are going to be real race
Real race to the bottom on that one
It's going to be a lot of lawyers
Shreveport we'll all be dead shirt
Yeah there's not much they could do about it
The ACLU lawyers will be
So we have one last clip here and it's Alex rambling
A little bit
About to have
Hospitals
Going to kill you
This is nice to see this narrative going back to
But you got to write this down
Your friends your family
Hospital
Apollo destroys your tissue
And then what
Froggy's is low
Ventilator was kills 94% of people
The ventilator.
Vitamin C and vitamin D
Iran
And then obviously
$53,000 / minimum value so
Dr.com
Like that
We get so many calls where do I call to get online pharmacy will call me back
Where do I call it's free
Pictures free this
Stop donations
Boost your immune system
Three all three types of iodine
I feel like it's
Really deaf
Difficult to hear a clip like that
And not think
That he is promoting his product
As a preventative
I know that he's not making
King B connection one
Yeah he's doing a little plug for weirdo doctors
Call in line
Queen of the things you got to do is load up ahead of time
On stuff for your immune system at that 8
Boost your immune system by using my products it really feels like
You would take away from this
If you were listening
Right if you are directing people towards the lodge
Conclusion
Of your
Regardless of whether or not you put a
Couple buffer set
Fences in between
If you do this
This will happen
Then you're still saying that it seems like
I mean obviously against the law
And
Warned about that by the New York attorney general
Serious problem with this
This doctor marble
Well I mean I have many
Are growing
Did he prescribe any medications other than Ivermectin and hydrochloric when not that I know of
Like button
He's been a doctor for what he didn't just start being a doctor today I would assume that he does
But I don't think
I don't
Think you would ever be able to find an article about how he prescribes other thing
Well I mean yeah
That's
All of that comes
Who's from the same medical information that we
The scene was created out of it's not like he's prescribing a completely separate
Unrelated like all of this comes from the same side
But you can't get you can't be like all these
These great
Pills and vaccines are good
But these ones are evil
The calendar made by the same Folk
Nothing's real that's a good point
I'm just so mad
The doctor Marvel
Piccalilli
I think he has it it's crazy town
I don't I don't I don't know how to respond to anything you're saying because
You just do what you have to do is
Is give up
And then it all makes sense abolished the death penalty after we've killed everyone that I would give it
YouTube
So we come to the end of this and I think it's
Surprising that Alex's
Doing this little charade about the Durham report
I think it's really gross
The way is trying to get on the
Vaccine HIV train ride
Doctor marbles
I hope we don't see more him
Wolfie sky was a bit more I really thought doctor group without their Buttman doctor marbles is
And it's bringing
If we
The past is Prelude then Duncan Barboza going to be a piss doctor
I mean it does really sound like
I mean it really does sound like
He was a day
Talking Cirque du Soleil show
Doing backflips
Having a great time and then was like.
Doctor marbles
Just called
It's the same same basic thing
Chernobyl no
I feel like maybe get a dog named doctor marbles on his like
Yeah I want I wonder
About him
So you know who
Let's not legitimate field of study
So we'll be back Jordan
We have a Twitter
Back but until then
Dzx Clark
And now here comes
What the sex role
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color