Alexandra Thurston color
We are couple of dudes like to sit around and drink novelty beverages
About Alex
Twista
You
Dan Friesen
Are you like Siri
Pretty sure most
This is already out of the store go to Petco I feed my cat
I'm not afraid of you info Warriors
I'm really afraid if you
I'm incredibly scared of intro Warriors
And you don't know anything about a goddamn the show fine
It's fun in
Discussing our relative
Perspective
What you got over there
These before this is an apple soda
More sugar in it
I love apple juice
Is it delicious
I don't mind it I love it
Are novelty beverage game has gone more towards the comfy
Icarus we flew too close to the Sun with that coconut trees.
Is not going to be a good way to go back up to really bizarre eventually but for now let's stay with the soda game
Absolute
I'd like to give a shout out
To our new donate new policy walk-in before blazing gentlemen
He's a great comedian ladies and gentlemen
Mike Riley
Thank you for donating Mike Wiley
Miley on Twitter
Hardware or good for a while.
News
Very unsupportive with a crowd the other very supportive and nobody ever showed up
What it's like to be a comedian in Chicago 90% of it is running bad
But bonding through bad show
Running Sancho's and bad roads
Nevermind
Oh yeah
Today we're going to be doing another investigation
Installment
Because I hate the present
I don't want to talk about
I was excited I was I was really hoping walking over Heroes
I do not
September 2nd 2015
Through
September
Fort
To the pretty short. There's a very interesting narrative Arc
2 plays out
We'll get to it is about
But I wanted to spend my position that I'm staying
Cardiologist
I have two things I want to talk about up a sort of General business up top
The first thing is I read an interesting article today
Distinction
Between the alt right
And the alt light
I don't know if you're aware that the stadium
The alt-right is people like the most famous 12b Richard Spence
Out-and-out nausea
Yeah white supremacist neo-Nazi
Official position of the show everybody gets
Not just one
Not
So the alt light
Is like Mike cernovich jakpus Gavin McInnes
All these people that are sort of in our
Sphere that come up on Alex's show and we talked about
And I think that is one thing I want to say
Isn't it we call those dudes alright
And there's
They make the argument that they're not alright
And they split from the alt right
Because they
Don't
Want to be associated with the whites
Soupremacy
Of the alt-right
So they're the alt-right
And they want to be treated differently
Skin color
Does that I say exactly
Rhymes doesn't mean you get to
Would not owe you if you're in a barn
The out and
They took their hood off
F*** you
I hope the barn burned down
With all of you inside
Implied version of that
Spin version of
Racism
Did you don't want to be any version of racism possible
So I don't think I don't think that's a really great defense
Weird
The healthier version
First of all
Second of all I've done enough looking into these p
People threw their appearances and the prism of Alex Jones
Call me into our natural sphere
Watch a bunch of his bulshit videos online
Ejecta sobiech I've spent a lot of time with
Mike cernovich certainly
You have just described hell you realize that
Myself which is bizarre
What I want to say we all created
The people who are listed in this
Then the alt-right
Section of it
Real f*****-up rapist
They are some
Out-and-out
You like dangerous
White supremacist Nazi type
I think their problem
I don't want to do a show about them
Very conscious
I don't want about them
I want
Am I focus on these
Alt Lite
People
Who are all right
Whatever they want to call
Indulge
Rebranding
Don't allow them
To Bellflower
Think that it's
Possibly even more important
To focus on these people
As opposed to the
Admittedly more dangerous
People in the alt right
Section
Is because
They are how people get radicalized
To the all right
They're like the
Yes
No one is going
To find the wild baby a couple people but it's a very small minority of people are going to
Find the heroin first
And go to
There's any sort of
And started doing some coke
You didn't work at that it's not
You get what I'm saying
As are we all by the old
People start with like Gavin McInnes and maybe they become a proud boy
Is it seems like a fun fraternal organization
And then as they go along to become one of the all tonight
They become part of the army version of the
Proud boys
I'm a little bit later it's not enough for them and they find ohmygod look at all these other people there
Some real s***
It is a progression
And people like Alex Jones
Everyone
Who talks about him online positive
Says like crazy
You stopped without him my eyes never would have been open
They are
The intermediaries to really f***** up radicalization online
And if you cut that off
The people who are really extreme
Will not have access to
The man like most
Okay I'm going to come
Fine
And I don't
I do agree with you though
These people
To me are far more.
Cuz because they have the air of respectability normal
Afraid of Richards
Richards
Is laughable
Because every
Can look at that
So we don't pay attention
Exact
Now they all
Right
Hide
The racism
The ones who you see
People saying
Sometimes
Right there not funneling people in
Into the
Further right
They're giving people
Cover
To indulge in there
Proclivity
Ultra
Like
Cernovich
Especially your pulse
Citgo Fox
Sprite
Which is my new favorite
Those guys
Bar
Are a way for peace
Go to argue
That they are not being
While still legitimized
Yeah that's
But they are so I'm not afraid of them putting
People towards
I'm afraid of
I'm afraid of them making the middle
The right
Do you see what I'm saying
But the guys that we are looking at
Tumi are far more days
Cuz they're not
These are the
People who are really good at internet radicalization
Yeah
Tumi
Is
It is transitional
To some extent
Into a more extreme
Headspace
I believe
For the most
I don't even know how to put this because like
Be really extreme people are a problem and that they might hurt somebody
But there
Uniform thing
F*** all of them
Do not
Allow anybody to
Polis
They are the same thing
Just like we've
Just like we've covered
Alex and David
Yeah even Alex
He has to
Publicly disagree with.
Or not
Well
Because
V if you put it to a large majority
Even people on the right
That these guys are out
Bigot
They know in their head
Approve out in
This is going to ruin
I don't care what color you are
Costco
Yeah I only talked about
Or hiding your or hiding your
Racist and bigoted views
Behind
One black Pastor who said so
Similar
Specifically
Exactly the same thing
Bright and the other thing
To keep in mind is that these Alt
People right
I'm just trying to use that
For the sake of clarity
I am in the descriptions
Spell
Still are
Super motivated by anti globalist ideas
That there
Is based on a
Semitism
And bigotry
So
Just like we
Revealed
They're big
Get tree is
Of the
Hiding behind.
Globalist
If you are
I would say 100% of the time if you
Are blaming globalist
First off
You're hiding
Let's move on
And let me
Defend myself
Again
About why I don't want to be in the bread
I listen to the show
Monday's show this week on the 17th
Complaining about robots
Got the statistic right
Sports
Baba
Then Tuesday
On the 18th
How to make this argument all the f****** time
Even recently
I've made it
In response to tweet
The people have sent me and messages when they
Send me the newest
Alex Jones meme
I've made the argument
Feels good
But you're helping him
Whenever you play into these things that make him a joke
And make him funny
You are not
Doing anybody any good
Now listen to this clip
From Tuesday's show
Really just make my argument form
Blinking lights
Germany Syrian hairdresser
Integrations flipped his female
Employers throat
Realize
More and more
Portmore I am going to
Everytime We report
Allah Akbar
From the Time Warner
Super Deluxe
Or they make it look like I'm just making stuff up
That was a real article I was reading
For the police chief
In Ohio and one in New York and then
Integration
Gmail
You can't
Play this game with Alex
He is
Really good
8 using attack
Against him
To his advantage
You just
Give him ammo
It's not good
I get it
Itsfunneh
That Bon Iver video.
Parody
Itsfunneh
In a perfect world we could all laugh at it
But unfortunately
Here's the score
Alex Jones 1
Meme 0
No one
Do you understand
I agree with you
I'm curious about
I am.
This is why because here's the deal
Sound like
Generally my Sirius
Absolutely
He has nothing in this story that he brings up
Go over other than some guy
In the neck
What are the circumstance
Delete work for her for a year
Maybe there was a dispute at work
There's all kinds of possibilities
All he knows is
Is the ethnicity of the person
And because
You know there is that
The refrain in the song
He gets to use it
You guys are making fun of me I'm right and now every time
That there is
Some incident that happened
Whitmer there's an immigrant that attack somebody
He gets in everybody's face
And it's not it's not
I think our biggest issue with
Meming Alex
Is that he is
Complete an
Can you because that's what he's doing
Every time
There is a murder
Every single time
He's going to comb through as many murders as a
Toucan
The Muslim
Celebrate that
He's right for murder
Giving him more
To do that and it's not just going to be once
Every time there's a murder over whether the show
Is model of
Story
Same story different Swift
Soap name
Congratulations
Great work
Go fuc yourself
Everybody
Legitimately
Not our listeners you guys are great
But I'm serious
We're not taking this seriously
It's it drives me up
We have
A bigot with a massive audience
And the best we can do is thousands and thousands of retweets
For this f****** video
If 10000 people retweeted that are that episode we did about Dennis Montgomery
Think about the effect that could have
If he was drunk is s***
On March 30th
Of 2017
Do you think what that have
We cast a light on this stuff and maybe it's more difficult maybe I'd certainly more difficult to take
And then
A 2-minute video
Alex Jones plays the Imp
Tire video
The entire Bon Iver video
Coming in from break
And why wouldn't the smart thing to do of course if you're like like you're mad about it
When
Especially in the present
Where is God
F****** nothing to go on
Nothing out of
He's spiraling into this
Repetitive
Bulshit
It's far more dangerous
Just like you said
Monday
Boring
Now he's got this pizza
We all had a good time but now he's
He gets in on it
I don't want him to have fun no I don't ever want him to have one.
It doesn't ruin it even have thumbs
This day I mean this has been inevitable outcome of pretty much all the time
Let you try and make these fun meme
It's it's
Keep going to take it
And use it and you are going to
And he's going to use every part of the Buffalo No Doubt
Itsfunneh
Play the clip
It's funny to get angry at people
Who's think it's actually doing a good job taking
And then it
Itsfunneh
Use it as it's
Propaganda
Every time he feels like
It is approved
Time Warner
As opposed to a funny video
David just reinforces that I want to put on it
I tweeted something about this then I didn't I didn't
I couldn't figure out how to put it the rest of it in 140-character
Alex Jones doesn't have a sense of humor
He doesn't understand how to use humor
It isn't
Incredibly potent
Tool
In terms of
Rhetoric
Being
Persuasive
Humor isn't
Incredibly important
You see it in any
Anybody who's giving a speech
If you don't have the kind of charm that elicit laughter
You're going to bore people
And Alex Jones
Can't get by on his own
In terms of humor
He needs other people to do it for him
Who is Bon Iver video
And I know it wasn't
But like
Disparities video
Does it for him
He doesn't have to be funny
You're doing the hard part for him
When you make videos
Set reminder
To go f****** fly a kite
That's it
Little pretty funny videos very funny
The smart idea is well
Computed Bon Iver has a very
Sound
If if if
Is the consequences
They were
They didn't reinforce
The
Uneven
Dan Dan
Shut up
Dad we want you to be happy
All right let's go back in time
I'll be happier in 2015
Clap their hands
Noting
Tinkerbell
SOS
Alex Jones
In 2015 September 1st to Justin out
That he was going to do a 27 hour marathon
For project
Money bomb
My conviction that this
To the opportunity
34 big money
Coming to his show
Become part of
Team Trump
That is where we left off last time
We pick up our investigation
On September 2nd
He's very weird on September 2nd
He wants to talk race
To bring that money here is the first clip you want
Talk
Murders
And they just got
Ariana homicide suspected in off-duty Texas officers death
Is home
We have another cop shot of course in Houston over the weekend
We have the TV reporter and a cameraman killed
And much of it is black on white
With yesterday
Different radio shows
Better out there
Where folks are calling for
The murder
Police officers this is tremendously important he is just tied together all of his narrative that weird
Going to be discussing today in 140 second sound bite
Black people
Black people killing white people and especially cops
Louis Farrakhan has
Come out and put out a video Alex play it later in this investigation
But just to give you a short version of it it's Louis Farrakhan saying
If we are being
Killed
And we have no redress
They what we must do is
And kill those who would kill us
Which is fair
Epic seven
That I mean
What else do you do it
Mix
And has no other
Possibility of Jessie
Like none
The system doesn't even
Pretend to work for
Frankly
People would be happier if
The cop was
Even just
If he wasn't even brought
And so if you don't have that
There is nothing else but viola
Facebook
Rioting is the voice of the unheard
Alex Jones also wants to bring in a cop was killed and it home off duty
There's no indication of that guy was killed because he was a cop there's no details that Alex Jones has about this
He's just
Narrative
To give extra
Then
He brings in these various radio shows
I want you to remember that
Cuz we're going to get to what he's talkin about a little bit down the line
Various radios various radio shows
Specific
And it's not on the radio
So
Here we go Alex wants to yell but Farrakhan a bunch
And here we go it has a really great end
I got to say
Out of being really mad
And I think you know exactly what type of cavities going to make
FBI
What you said
Maybe you are just crazy
On that subject
The loved one of the anchors
Is here with us
What's a medium
Hillary for
Hillary for prison shirts
Yes but did you notice no reality
That he's selling as opposed to it like you just
Stolen ID
Which she admitted on our last episode The back-and-forth
Very interested in is this harsh pivot from
Screaming at Louis Farrakhan payroll
To being like
I understand it was killing somebody want to kill him
Try to get it out
It's all so performative
You stupid Louis Farrakhan operation
See this is why I so much better in the past
Now he would just
He would just have spittle
Flying from his mouth week
He's not angry
He's yelling about
He's just angry about all the s*** they
It's going down in life
Choice
Somewhere in this 2015.
And he's paying for it in 2017
I've listened
To a bunch down the road
I'm still convinced that I'm right
Okay. I still don't have concrete evidence
But I'm pretty sure I'm right
And one of the reasons that I'm sure I'm right
Is that Alex
On this September 22nd
Can show is out of
He is just
Furious and grasping
Distraught
Oh I'm sorry
September 2nd
He's Furious he's just he's just an angry angry man
And doing a ton of race
So I told you to keep in mind I radio show
Come back up
Here in this neck
Tell you a little bit about what this radio show is
It is a radio show on
It's basically a app for Matt where you can put out a pot
You're here
The audio of it sounds like a guy
Recorded it through his cell phone
It sounds like an answering
I looked into the guy
His name is King Noble
He is a black supremacist
Black Supremacy
Love you has the 800
Followers on Facebook
Real real
This guy is hitting obvious
Let you know
Not not
To be a dick
We do not have
100 followers
I understand that and that's not what I'm saying
Relatively
This dude Alex Jones claims that 20 million listeners a week
He's
Scooping down that far to make an example
Not good
That means you don't have an
If you're like oh this guy on SoundCloud
What are you doing
What's the angry about nothing
How do you say
Klip2save
Wilbur
Just combing yes
Yes absolutely remember when we went over the Humvee will Lucaya situation
Breitbart
Maybe they have tipsters
To tell them about things they find
Or they're just
Trolling for race-baiting stories
Right there just
Trying to find anything
How did you
Find out about
A child on child sexual assault
It is small town in Idaho
Idaho White
Supremacist
Sent that little
Too bright
Exactly
It's always going to be the same story
That's how these things
Get traction
I mean that's it
And it's pathetic
What's what's the
What would you say
We're going to listen to Alex Jones going to give it a little bit of an introduction first
He's going to play play that super.
Xvideo it just
The time traveler
They're probably working for the feds
They got screwed over something by the cops that are some racist
I was sophisticated enough to not hate all cops are all black people
Describe a group of people
And then
Said that he experienced
That exempts
Yeah but he's evolved enough
Dinos
He knows that
It's new.
And he also said that those people work for the FBI
Is this his way of trying to subtly say that he works for the FBI
By the way I'm not saying that does not work for the FBI
Probably you think we do
Find out about it's probably going to like these guys are federales
Followers
We will be taking shower others No Doubt
I guarantee we have more listeners that much love talk radio show
You don't have listeners
And so it's really just a bunch of babies that like to play the part of victims
I think they're going to be big tough honchos
What cures for what is a real racehorse starts in this country it's not in either side
Historical lines and
Play at the game going picking people off
Go pick you off one at a time
Fluoxetine
Water buffaloes water buffaloes kill more people
That's not
I just shows disguise ignorance
He called himself for the lord it's all part of this narcissistic
Hip hop culture
T-Mobile
Black Supremacy and I want to talk about the shooting
Of the white deputy sheriff in Houston Texas
I Shot the Sheriff tell me what the Houston Texas
Brutal
Execution before the public represents to me if it's open season
Killing whites
And white police officers
And probably killing cops. It's open season
Towards the police department
Anna police
So now you got some
Black
Military
Awesome angry black man
Wok Shop
And executes
A cracker car
In broad daylight
This is real
Is open season on killing white people and cops
It's unavoidable
Escapable
Itsfunneh
Then I will move into a Time
Become the prey
Yes they said
It'll be a race war
And that we cannot win a race war we can't win
We're outnumbered
They got weapons they got drones they got this they got that
But I remind you of the Buffalo
Who outnumber the lion
They're bigger than lion
Any moving larger her but get picked off
Alliance
By one by one
Picking them off
Today we live in a time where the white man will be picked off and it's just if he can do it.
White people, can we ever have before
We see Whitney Houston
Texas shooting
And we see
Weber news reporting shooting
Virginia
It's about
To go
Down
Is open
Season of killing wife
People in crime
Gravity the black lives matter movement
We try to appeal to them
Let them know that this type of thing would comment would happen they thought they were indestructible and invincible
Because they took advantage of the weakness of black people for too long with all this police brutality and now they
Challenge
You're a grand jackasses what you are capable
I want to challenge this this guy uses real name and come on this show
Is Rihanna
Fluoride water is going on dummy
The cause a race war
Internet
So Alex
Is mad at him and the media
A few small exam
And then he uses
A very small example example
I wanted to let that play realize I felt it as we were listening to
But the reason I wanted to play it is
Alex barely interrupt
And there's a reason for that
He wants to paint
Black people
So he wants the audience
To fully hear everything
Memphis black supremacist
The saying because it feeds into the fear that he wants them to feel
So relax
It was anybody who doesn't respect as much as David Duke
He allowed David to have parameters
Any other time he has someone on who's contentious
Especially if you like we both had that episode where we played
Is Keith Olbermann analysis
Yeah.
Work
Do is make a mockery of consultant
Exactly
It serves his purposes to
You fully play this
I don't think it's like he sat down and thought about that I think it's just an intrinsic
Decision
You played this guy
Again a very small audience
On BlogTalkRadio
And conflated that
With Louis Farrakhan
Two of them are making very different state
Lose
Weed
If we have no recourse for being killed by cops
Why we should kill the cops
Kill us
Sleeping pretty specific
Think about it there's some room for interpretation or have you but I want to make it clear
That this is what's going on at the beginning of September 2nd
What route is that
For about the first 40-minute
What happens after that
Higher rest of the show
Until the 4th hour
I think it's Rob Duo
Fourth hour
But then
The next
Hour and 20 minutes or so
Is an interview with dr. group
About how people need to buy their
It becomes
We've already started
It becomes a
The straight-up infomercial
They're just talking about
Shilajit
And various other things
I've actually talked to my doctor friend doctor gums about some of their
Full of s*** most of them are
Like I want to get him on so you can break down like this
Specifics of it
But man
Meadowlands people who fall for this stuff are a real special breed
Especially cuz these bottles of pills cost
Second epoch
Various
Spencer
Nothing because those pills
Cost 30
Max and once you start taking them you feel bad when you don't take it what you may or may not be psychosomatic
No it can't really be
There's really nothing
120 % of your iodine in
Everyday
Have to adapt
To having
And so of course whenever you
Completely remove it
Instead of
You know it's just like getting rid of any Medicaid
Slowly go off in the more metal
Like when we got off the gold standard
Paper off metal
So
Coming on to talk about the biggest
Nothing to be afraid of
Not
Vaccines
Not fluoride in the water
Dr. group
The biggest thing to be worried about
Now it's nanoparticles
Nanoparticles
Very observant that's good for you
I think they're over selling it just a little bit and being very specific
Then the thing Alex is pimping
Building up as we talked about going broke
You can see it and all I want to do is try to have peace
Prosperity
But there is a force out of Evil's activate
Evils making its move that's the big event
That's right
I got out of Beyond
End tables making it smooth I mean
With this Collider
I mean we're talking about opening up another dimensional we're opening a portal
And we don't know what
That's right
Very
Check out
Could be a portal
Yeah could be a portal
Maybe we're looking
Looking for the gravitational particle
Maybe we're inviting Cthulhu into the who knows
Yeah I mean with these sort of hypothetical things
Outside possibility
Portals
But not the way they're saying
Portal what they're like what
Yes
Also I love the idea
Rosen Bridge
I loved the idea that it's just like this door is going to open up in front of your life
I need to remind everybody that doctor group
Is a chiropractor
Doctor and who else
Netflix
Right
Completely nuts
Question
I'd love to answer the question
If we've ever really
Talked about
Either chiropractor Williams
PW chiropractor does
Portals
Prosperity mean
No
Not really free market
I want Prosperity what is that actually look
You know how
Whenever Trump says America First it means whatever it means to you
It's just a nice
Sort of catchphrase
But that's what he's talking about you know
I hear it and I guess what he means is
Like how does the textbook definition Wright
I suppose
Plenty plenty
So he wants communism
No he certainly doesn't
It's not real
A free market
Lives on
Cannibalizing its poor
Absolutely
What's it wait what's your point
My tab I was just asking
What it is
That he's our weather and I could never describe his prosperity
No I just want prosperity
I think it's just a nice word
You get to bring your bag
And whatever positive things
Think it's great
Things upon everybody
Mobile
What's your own
Alexa
Do more listeners
Hello Alex
Group a sit-down
And they get down to business
Sing that song
They do not
Is Mike Pence
Start
By reading a review of one of the product
Stop
Alex starts by reading review
And then
He accidentally reveals a negative side effect of his Medicaid
Tennessee I just feel better in general
Overall sense of improved
I will
Albiery ordering so thank you for your support
Thank you for checking that out it's a process
Amnon from Jabba the Hutt level
5 years ago chicken ocean almost 70 lb
Fix my temperature but
Operation
Therapist analyzing Alex Jones
After his bigoted
His temper is his worst problem
That might actually feed into a lot of his bigotry
Those sorts of impulses
Are we
So maybe you should stop taking super female vitality
Sojourn
This goes on
Forever
Homosexual
Getting another man's
Absolutely
Unless you're a little bit light in the loafers
So
This goes on
For a long time
The doctor group interview trying to push that product real heart
Feed them to my narrative that I believe is the truth
But he is trying to make money before the fiscal year end
Texas
Episode I made it clear
It was just mentioning taxes
I should have been more clear there's a lot of reasons
To try and boost your
Your numbers before the end
Fiscal year
One of them is if you have loans
Orleans
If your credit limit is
Contingent on how much you bring in by the end of fiscal year
He could be in a situation where the bank will give him any money
Unless he gets
2 x amount of dollars
Bad financial reason
If your if your company is doing well
You don't really need
The Panic at the end of the fiscal year
If you only really need to do that if you're cooking book
Or you're in trouble
So
Any real books
I don't think
Bread
But beyond that
So I want to just make that clarification
Might not totally be tax
Cuz it could be some other credit issue something like that
But whatever it is it's
Think Financial
The time push product before this
I forgot to mention
That's
A shooting
Of a police officer
Lake Illinois
Suburb of Chicago
Yeah cuz this was only two years ago
Hahaha
So
Let me feel Joy at remember to let me ask you if you were mine
Please let me in let me ask you remember this
Do you remember when
Alex Jones Joe Biggs out to Fox Lake
Remember that
Biggs comes out
Shooting some remotes
And their atrocious
I really don't have a good camera system
So like he's on his cell phone
Giving an interview
In the it being like
I don't know I'm down here we're just going to be hunting down leave so if anybody knows anything just let us know
I am hanging out at the Starbucks
Because the guy was on the loose for a bit
SO2 Infowars tips
Let us know I'll go check things out
Not a cop
This is not
Boring interview
Guest appearance on
September 3rd
Get to now
Alex Jones
Is in a weird hats
He's always been weird
We're talking about which
Which type of
Today's episode September 3rd
Incredibly f*****-up
Never forget
He does
Some stuff that is unconscious
He says
Incredibly expensive
It did the way the show end
Is unpredictable
Oops
In one of the most wild flameouts I've ever seen in my life
It's going to be really bad
He's going to make you scream
But just know at the end of it he doesn't feel great
Is about other things
He suffers he starts the show off talking about
Alien
But
General Public
Rogers
Turn on front
Now they're cool
How they got money
All of it's just like
Colors showing off to each other
I Can See Clearly what happened
Very poor
Poorly constructed
It's just crazy town
In the beginning of a
Tired of complaining
It's a UFO
I'm not into aliens
I love the best Millions idiot
The devil I like that rationality
It's not this
Also my mom told me never
Into a UFO
Absolutely not very smart
Whenever you get a chance
Like UFO
Brett Uber
If you're going to get into a planet
You know you you want to make sure that you order the planets
Galaxy Spanish
Alright I'm about
About how you gas
So are you going to come back on the 3rd he's back already
Maybe they did get some tips
In the Infowars
Sublime that weren't good
And it's also possible
Was related to Alex Jones
But somebody saw something
Reported it
The police acted on it they jumped
And it turned out it was not the suspect
And the shooting
Joe Biggs
Is furious about this bad
So
He complains about it a bit
And then Alex Jones
Worst shoot
I think I've ever heard
And you're going to have to put your mic.
Looking for difficult
We talked to the credible threat
And the next thing you know you start getting
People calling a hater suspicious people walking to our yard
Another was just wild goose chase going on
It was all because the lady lied because she wanted attention
She wasn't looking for attention
From a family that she was working for
Through the entire State because of a lodge
Cross burning
In modern times where it wasn't people doing
Clan murders but not really crossword
Where the swastika put on it as been fake
Every time a dorm gets a swastika put on it has been fake
I mean it's almost
Is almost always a false flag
Iora black lady
There is a pension
Criminology
Most of the making stuff up
To get attention it's just bizarre look when they're all the time
The police don't believe a woman when she's crying
Because many women alive
I don't get your psychology Alex
A couple things the first thing is
That he uses
Specific instances like the Duke
Lacrosse situation
Situation
Ladies
About getting cut off
Turned out you did do it to her
There are a couple
Minority
Situation
Ben tries to generalize them to pretend
That most women are lying about being sexually assaulted
To find
The fact that it's so very rare
Never ever reported in the news that some
Anytime somebody is
Lies about being raped
It is
One reason
Never happen
Publicized
Because it never happened
Because that
Not a real argument
Why do so many women lie about being raped
Is the thing that you say before I explode
This is real f****** think this is a real f****** thing whatever the causeway Alex
Locations
First started coming out whenever there was 10 women
Women that he raped or whatever
Whatever that happen
To go
Home2 thanks
Giving
With my
Wearing my little sister
And my mom both said
You know
Maybe we believe these ladies if so many women didn't
And I was going to burn their house
I thought it would be a good idea
Right
Now I did
Because the
Giant Cross burning
Didn't go well the last
Everything every hate every hate crime
Everything purple
Perpetrated on somebody
Report on somebody Global all lies
But anytime
Yep
Hit the nail on the head my friend
One of his big pieces of evidence that he's been using a Blog Talk Radio Show
Women should kill 40% of all men
Today when we make the argument at least I don't have to deal with Trump
When we make the argument that Alex Jones
His primary objective
Is
White Christian
Bale
This is
Evidence
Saying something's are faking something
That's your
Light
That's your old white guy
Remember they're fine with
Rape and when you guys make Bon Iver memes
Remember that this guy is way worse
Then you're
He's a horrible horrible person who's leading thousand
The people
Into essentially erase
Congratulations to make him
Palatable and funny
Anyway
Now we get to go on
Stillmatic
I understand maybe this is all of our audience clapping their hands you would feel better
Never clap
I'd like to go policy won't stop right now
This next clip will get you right out of that funk monster
But
You get the call from a guy who asked
Somebody's car
To talk about
His car for about
10 minutes
Alright a selection of the end
And I want you to hear like
Victor
I'm going to give you a sign
Absolutely don't talk over there
Cuz the end
Is f****** banana
Alright I'll just
No you don't have to
Maybe
Playing with fire.
Alright
Legally sell it
For the price listed by.
I am so
Now they're coming out with more than be a lot more
But it's just a piece of Americana I kind of treated myself
But I think I might actually sell it because
For somebody like me Miss got so much riding on what I'm doing
People counting on me
So I just want to take a break there to say I mean
Two years later he saying the exact same thing
Who's playing the I got to be humble I should
Wait to get the humble points
Without actually do it making an action
So many people are relying
Me
Fake ID
I need to get rid of this help
I just need to
I just
I just get out it's like
It's like when Jesus
Kick to the money
Out of the church
Right
Then he wrote often.
Americana
But the other thing I want to point out is that Alex is so desperately like doing an hour and a half
Infomercial on yesterday's show
Doing a million-dollar Marathon a week and a half later
He's talking about just randomly buying a sports car
So I mean there is a disconnect between his personal life
Of the business
He clearly isn't
Suffering at all for his
We're suffering at all for the cause
Like most rich
People anytime there's layoffs at
Well like when they laid off
100 copy editor
At no point
Did any of the
The CEOs
High-level manager say
Pay cut
Keep 30
If you guys give
Yeah I put 40 hours a week at least
Sons of b******
I mean
Alex
Nada.
No
Can all go f*** them
Sure
F*** you
Also Alex himself or how much longer he talks about his car
A woman
The problem is
Is there a ditch absolutely mate
It doesn't look like anything's
I don't like super fancy stuff
I got love Ferraris but I even had the money I wouldn't spend it on that but
It's just too flashy
The understated stealth nature of it
And the fact that 780 horsepower
Gordon the car driver and others
So you're sitting in a 780 horsepower car
It's just sex
And it's even sexier cuz it's more than meets the eye
I really like that I really like
Does it also transport on the highway on 37
And I was coming back from the base kids with my parents
When I got to go buy 1,000 miles on it
The first two games.
Why is this Uncle Joe
I shouldn't have done
So
I'll stay there
What you doing
What the f***
He just said he was going to let like he was implying that he's letting up a smoke after
Tax write-off movies
I'd like to thank God for all his grace
Just have like a
Car radio show
Click-and-collect
We'd be so much better off as a country possibly or if he was literate and he could just become like a y a author
Or something like that
Infection like you already have
Right but
F******
Look like
There's those moments of unintentional,
TV
Pivoting to unlock
Right is going after break
There's moments like that that are like
That's how that's f****** hilarious
I just said I f***** the car
Guarantee that guy
Yeah
I'm going to go with the ladder
Also I screamed over but likes point out that Alex
You can f*** yourself for not liking fast
Furious and reference
He might have like the first ones though cuz those were
Those ones were more street racing better off
If we had a car
Paul Walker
Call Joseph
So you heard at the end
Alex Jones saying
I was in a really bad mood which we heard
Two days now
Guy calls when I can talk
Car for 10 minutes
And now I feel great
This next to it
Listen next clip is 6 minutes later
6 minutes later
Going to talk about it
I love doing this radio show and I just really enjoy it and
Elephant ears but
Some days
Gardasil shot having convulsions
I can't be on it
I just told him during the break
Don't get robbed
About the police in studio
Animaker the old fourth hour late
I think it's really just gotten to that point where the evil is so over-the-top
For a few hours and I just need to really
Get my head screwed on straight because
So Alex Jones
6 minutes earlier
He's a rapid cycler
Gears like
On top of the world
Talking talking about the car
F***** my car
Now I'm
Ladies on Gardasil
After I fed
Finished jerking off
Course
Refractory. Don't want to scream anymore
How am I supposed to be a propagandist Photoshop my wad
Cuz he doesn't
Late were
Go get me Rob do he's in the news off
For Studios
There's a bunch of office
And all of them have a gun safe
Now I'm very
Videos online you can find of Alex given a tour of the studio
Massive building
To the point where it's absurd
Considering the offer
How much renting out this Warehouse buying it would be
Utilities
Standing Lehigh
Expenses
That's why he's against government control
Taxes
Must be really high on it
Is Warehouse
They're probably
He doesn't leave at least not for the next
Half hour or so
In the next half hour
He gets a caller
That
Makes him wish
I know that I was making a pretty big point
Of this
Race war narrative
And the fact that Alex is
Conflating a Blog Talk radio host
With no listeners
Lewes Ferry
And I did so
Because
First of all it's
Manipulative and wrong
Because it leads up to this caller
The patio in South Carolina you're on the air
Questioning
With myself
How do they think they're going to get away with
George Bush Morgan a million Muslim you know
And Donald Rumsfeld
Daniel
Cocaine
The reason I called
Clearly
Police in general
I think that rhetoric
Perspective perspective
I don't think he's calling for as much as
Cobbs
But
Houston General
Are white cops
So here we go first point I'm going to make is
Daniel is awesome
You will end up saying couple
Can't handle it
Interrupt
No no no
What do you want
The all white people
I've asked you out
That's what you're bringing to the table
Because that's what you're afraid of
I could hear Louis Farrakhan say that and I don't
Think I'm
Going to be Target
I don't care black
Don't look at me like that
I get what Louis Farrakhan is saying and I'm not here to say that everything Louis Farrakhan says
Sensible or right
I am so
Really the conversation would it needs
To be unfortunately
Daniel doesn't really
Get into this
Dubious
22 clip
It's not dealing with
The Source material is bringing
Imperial
He does make some other grateful
Analysis tone
Listen to how much more deferential
He's he's very
Conciliatory
But also condescend
Well that's absolutely
Play true as well
He has conciliatory because I think he senses this guy knows
He's going
To destroy me
If I disagree with him forcefully
A knot in just a patronizing
Waited
A lot of white people treat black people
Sort of push
He's going to come back at
Alex knows that
Oh wow
He has his guard up quite a bit
I don't want to talk about it
I think I I think
Never listen to like Freeway Rick Ross talk
Gopher
For sure like
If I believe him if I don't but his story is basically
That he was getting cocaine and crack
From the government
Excelling at
Like he was the funnel through which
Scratch game
I'm not
Totally
Supposed to be impossible
It seems like it's possible
I don't know
You might as well introduce
Crack to the black
Conspiracies
I think
Possible
Maybe even likely
Did Reagan kill JFK
Totally
Liberty Global asset above-the-law
George Bush
Would be able to get away with that
Unless he's either intimidated the government
Mama
That was absolutely true
Is just
What shocking up
Put the globalist and I don't know which one it is what do you think it is
Contact in contacts
Individual
Contacts
Inconvenience
Stocks about to composition fallacies in Lake
The responsibilities of individual does upon the group that they ran in
Greece travel guide
Louis Farrakhan if you wants to be above board prove that he doesn't want a war and isn't part of the globalist
He just has to say everything I want
Music
Identity is incredibly fragile
So let's get back to the scholar who is
At this point still pretty awesome
The cops
How's the traffic
Alaska.
Even better
It makes me upset
Nauseated
Al Sharpton
When the themselves
Also these talks
Three layers of b*******
Talking about is taken while they are
Send it
The obvious right now
Local and the locals are a patchwork Department
Overall
I can see your perspective
What is your aunt
Afrika Bambaataa
Next song come out
Irish policeman
Call Max
Water is harassment because it's because
A lot of different factors
Old Customs racism things like that but also
Movement the gangster hip hop culture Push by in Longview
Which is going to get worst social engineer sir
Are manipulating
Is coming up
Told you already report
Abdul comeback
I didn't eat breakfast this morning I also got my blood sugar
That's what it sounds like when you lose an argument really hard
That's embarrassing
That's crazy
My son has been harassed
8 time this year coming back from the pool with his friend
Cuz we're black
And we live in a decent neighborhood
Fault cuz I was
The globalist
Making your son like hip-hop there's always a
White rash
Elevation for
What's weekend always black.
Tribalism racism to be like a puppet
Tomorrow
Stereotyping B on hip hop culture
It's always hip-hop
It's always
Civil rights you're all black pants
Is everybody else
Radio show guy
You're always judged
Always been like that
Since the goddamn
Black people were f******
Four years are we going to have to put up with
Not me personally
Play but I mean it affects me
Everybody
Absolutely it's on f****** believe
Which is the fakest thing in the world
It sounds like me trying to
To get out of class
That's the level of
That's like
He's in a bad mood that day earlier he's like I got to go
My boss at like 11 that I don't feel great and I might need to leave
That's laying the groundwork
Keith I want to leave later I am and here you just got
School fire collar
Who has
Point and personal experience that Alex
Does not have a good argument for
He's making these points for the hold button on
Loses the argument pretends he didn't
Alex takes the next day off
He takes Friday off
Take a long weekend
A good idea
I don't think
He had to leave I don't think you had low blood sugar
Haven't got a plane to catch
I think that's a steal this is bulshit
No no
Would be able to
I think any longer of a conversation
A little bit more so than he already
I think a lot of his listeners are probably just like yeah
Alex is right
This guy does like
Isaac
That Alex Jones
Might have gone to take
A meeting
Or something like that
I think that there's some sort of business
He's doing behind
He's gone for Friday comes back
That's what I
That's my that's my
Catch
I don't know that to be
Exactly
But that's what I that's what I feel like
You know that took a vacation
That's entirely
Either way
Pretty wild oceans
Take a lot of vacation
That's good.
Do not
Deny anybody I think we should all take more of a k
American
Where's like
I support
Even Alex Jones
Having labor right
If you agree but if he screams about like
How
He eats sleeps and breathes this
Revolution in fighting globalist
You don't have a competent team back home
You can't have anybody Gucci already hosts a whole show what he does
Friday
Disaster
I like I said that's what happens on Friday but the Thursday show that we're going over here this September 3rd
Quite done
They go to break
Studio
And Rob do
Clean up
With this collar
They've kept him over
The break
No chill
What basically what happened to his yet Rob do just have to let this guy to make a whole bunch of
Disregard
And then
Rob do loses the argue
Very
Ungrateful
He just loses it in a very boring fashion
Sort of his style is a boring man in my office
Yo-zuri Justified why he's angry
I just want to say this for a go back to him
If you start shooting more with the police it's on either side we have to defeat this
With the infowar
Using cameras
Putting this stuff out and just
Inching forward it's not going to change overnight I can tell you that
I want to be clear up top
The Infowars video on Pole
I think they're really going to help
That is hit the black
Community
Police horse videos but it's always about how
White people are being oppressed
The police aren't doing anything about it or white people are also bothered by police
Top shotta
So it's great
It's good stuff
Isn't saying
We should have a shooting war with Apple
So even in setting up going back to
Call is misrepresenting
The position of the car
After this point
Pretty sensitive
Yeah
So
That's not fair
Finished with what you were talking about
Black lives matter
BlogTalkRadio shooting probably
Are Airway Veneno millions of people here I got a question
Hell yeah
No way to get Justice
Understand
I was joking
Mainstream media
There's the only point of me to take issue with him
Media narrative
That's not good I don't appreciate
I still think I could hang out with him
Yeah we could probably
Bruno argue about that
Rationally and civilly
At least until things have a pretty good head on his shoulders in terms of
These not willfully Missy
Theater Snellville
Okay
Rally
Unconcerned
Minister Farrakhan
Completely
I understand
This
Ourselves
The same thing
Open Season
This is why we
Nihilism
What someone talk for a really long time make some good points
You're wrong
I appreciate your perspective you just don't know
Also I want to do things
King Noble
Is not necessarily associated with black lives matter
The only evidence that we have from the clip
The black lives matter what
Didn't get it done it wasn't enough
Like
The black community tried to give
Understanding a chance blacklivesmatter
Albert
Alternative to what you would like
Being deeply involved with black lives matter at all
Does using
Like that
As a conflation
Shinola
Complacent
I would argue
That ever grew
Is protest
And they're changing oink oink
Mukbang
It's possible
To be interpreted as but true cop
It's also possible
Play the cops keep shooting people
So I don't think that's necessarily
A call to violence I don't think that
Certainly
That's certainly very well within the free speech
Alex
Care-A-Lot about
Oldest stuff
Exactly how lunatic
Oh so close
I know I run to bed
Investigation
I think it was all the pretty embarrassing show
On Alex's part
You know you start with him
Building up this black narrative is white
Cops
Are going to be targeted by black people
Begets
Incredibly intelligent
Collared with a lot of fact
A lot of perspective on his side
Alex let me bail
Lisa Rob do to take the brunt of it
The guy
Make all those points on the show
But that's just because
I don't know why they
Let's very weird
I think much about the races
The caller
Probably
They would
Even they are aware of the optic
Alex Jones
Maybe or the
Re-up
I think you're probably right I think they were I think they are aware of that which is
She's why
Which is why they dismiss him at
End of every
Never engaged with what
Says just go
You know what where you're coming from
Like
Yeah I think you're probably right
His usual tactic of harassing
Erupting would be like
Yeah exactly
The other point I'd like to make at the end of this is I think we've heard a couple of things in this episode that are substantially worse
Any meme you can possibly make about Alex Jones
I think one of the big issues that I always
We have with you
Is that
It always
It's like they're always giving
They're always at like
Farrakhan shouldn't be saying those
There's a better way to say that
You should black
It doesn't look like they're reaching out
Well it looks like they're doing all of this stuff
And it's always
Is always this b*******
It's on black live
Is matter
It's always on them like black people haven't been trying it the right way
Quote-unquote right way
All of the
Smaller-scale
I blame the fact they haven't called me
I could call them
Analogy there that's
The great one but I blame the other party for not reaching out to the other one not reaching out themselves
Especially when you're
Contacts
When it is
300 f******
Always trying to reach out of
This is how you're going to get white
This is
You're going to be able to
Never actually engaged
Never saying you know what this is
Listen to you
To listen to you
But the right way
What the f****** do every time
And I don't think he I don't think even Farrakhan his things
No I don't think
Even in the context with
Within which
She said it know where Andy said
This Vista
What should
Exactly
Making the correct point
The right way
What are you saying is
We may have to
Prevent violence
To get people
To do the thing they should be doing in the first place
As much as everybody wants to say Martin Luther King Jr did everything by Nonpoint
I will be goddamned if there weren't plenty of people
Put out a real physical
Ghetto
Don't f*** with it
Revolution revolutions need two prongs
Yeah that's what the proud boys
Understand that's why they have their normal military branch
Wright Giants
Absolutely
So I want to reiterate again
I am sorry that I keep harping on this
But
These memes are ineffective in battling Alex Jones is better ways to do it
I do agree with you in that
I mean
There has to be a middle grounds over
Between a 3-hour
Investigate
Nation bright
Bon Iver
Strike
Do you think we could put out a clip of Alex Jones
That clip of Alex Jones being drunk
I put that without on YouTube
Yeah I mean would that be
I was drunk drunk on his show
We don't have Time Warner behind as it's not a hit piece by Time Warner
Text Jones drunk on air
Right
I don't know man I don't know what the answer is but at the end of the day I'm really excited and thankful that we do have
The people listening that we do that is really awesome I really appreciate people who have reached out
All that stuff does keep help me keep moving even though I have to be inundated with everybody f****** setting between
That I know a week later
You're so resentful I'm not resentful it's I'm not mad at them I get it I get the like I'm mad
The fact is that
I know from my experience Val Jones when someone treats me these means a week later they're going to be on his show in a positive
Extra
Jeff
You follow along with his narrative it just becomes
Part of it and it is neutralized amongst
His people
It's very import
I am it's not
Dislike
It's not Super Deluxe his job to I don't even know if they're really interested
Actually working against Alex jump
I'm not sure what their goal is probably just make it quick
Something that I
Would disagree
Hoosier I don't either accepted them.
It is
Because it's actually you're creating a tool that this propagandist will use
It's not Huber four humors
Be a result of it is outside
Control
You've created something that will be repurposed
By someone
Who believes that almost all rape accusations are fake
Racism is a false flag
And globalist control the world so whatever bigotry that lies in his heart is inconsequential and everybody should pay attention
Dumb veiled anti-semitism
So what you're doing is you're helping him
And I don't know if people who are making these things don't realize that ahead of time
But I wish they would
I wish people would understand
That they
The best oven temp
Since I'm sure
Are there being a tool
Their tool for Alex Jones
Although
When you when you say that though like
We can't control how
People take this up
No
Right if it's out there I'm sure there's a way
To find something
But like I said like I said in the beginning
If he wants
Clip of me saying some s*** out of context
Right
That's in his narrative
Breitbart
Cuz I'll tell you what
Play without me dad I know Jordan
You're you have it completely back
Okay because of Alex Jones.
And took you out of con
Then we get to play The Alex Jones game with him making fun of us
You understand
Your flip-flops
Okay
We are taking him in context and engaging with what he's saying
So
Any attack
Would have to be taking us out of context
Or debating the merits of what we're saying
Wichita
Right
So there isn't really a way to use this
Propaganda Stickley for him
REI
He's already called himself the meme machine
The king of memes
Really you're just reinforcing the
I know I know is aware of it
He knows that he can
Of course
And I know that I'm a crank and I don't like fun
And all that I get
I get that that's my personality
But
This is
More than just that
Sincerely I believe
It is
A moral imperative
To not help
I agree
Good
If you don't want to help him you can go to our website
Dollartree.com
Poor male vitality
Sublingual
And then
Immediately exactly calm
Although we're on Twitter at knowledge underscore fight
Look us up we still don't have a picture nope
Open Facebook I just now it's right on Facebook
Nowhere
To everybody who's become
Policy
Appreciated
So many people who have been nice
We have more and more people
Finding the show Westworld truly amazing
Started many of those what's that f****** mean though
Ambetter
Better grateful for what we have
40 million people listening to the show every week
Then why was one reason why
Cuz there's one man
Who still exist
In this world
What network is curious about this guy
I don't understand
I was trying to figure out cuz I was also trying to figure out how to
F*** you John Rappaport
Alexandra Thurston color