Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
We are the bad guys
MoneyGram
Stripe.com
A little bit about Alex
Jordans
What's up
Michael Jordan is I was hanging out with my friend Angela Lansbury
She gave me a late
Christmas present
There could be no other Bryce bothering these because
Gmail
Magic cards
Let's take a look at these and see what your see specially-designed project car
F*** out of
Pull up pictures of Eva on Twitter
But one of them is you
Yes I'm broadcasting Banshee which I will
Will take as a compliment yes
You could you do damage with her loud yelling to equal ^ + what + what counters
There's one that is that is me
Your name is way better than mine
Where at where at where legendary creatures and there's also one of Celine the feline test
Contessa of course
Tell her that these
Are all
Massively overpowered car
Well your 2021 so you don't we both are because blackjack
But yeah it was so fun together of like
Unique Magic cards
Anywhere else
I know you would never ever have imagined anything like this and it's in
Incredible 2
Appreciate it
What what
Yes very much so well that now supersedes my bright spot for being my bright spot so mine is immediately
Lee no longer bright spot but what I had before was obviously socks Ruby Bryce country
Previously on break
Horizon forbidden West
Download it tomorrow
I'm excited
I've been looking forward to Planet zero Dawn was one of my favorite that's great
Zig amazing
We've been looking forward to this for a while as well
We can't find PS5
It says
Bazaart
Commodity goods are not supposed to work that way
Does Sonic
It is funny it's it's nice you know before I would look at like a PS2 or PS3 and I would say
Playboy I want one of those cuz I cannot afford
Yeah and now I'm like who I'm in a better place in my life I can get me one of the can't have it no dammit
Reality and the world will not allow it
Jordan today we got episode to do
Just to kill some time before you can play Horizon
This is all just waiting game for me
I kind of thought about it
We would talk about the prez
Too damn much
Ben concert
Rodger Stone okay
It's been a lot of 2022 episodes
In a
I need a break so I decided to
Poke around see what I can
Vines
Does boarding Jim Bakker no good
So I went
2003 fortunately there's a string of episodes
That are
So boring
Nothing is happening
And it's just a disaster
And so we end up having to skip
To July 17th
The 11th
Yes to the 17th 2003 before we can find anything
It is worth going over but
It is so worth going over okay and I feel
Excited
I feel delighted
To have the this episode has fun
There's meaty stories
There's Alex being an idiot
Accidentally relates to the present day and ways that I did
Back right cuz you're a witch
Right
Which by the way is part of my my legendary creature human witch
According to as magic.
Business on this nonsense
Before we do
Hello
Stephanie UK thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Bikers ocools thank you so much
2022 busted
Eik
Good spelling of average
I don't know how else you would spell ever
I know what your policy want
Guantanamo Bay but it's
Bae bae
I'm a policy wonk and also I could have gone I could have seen it being Bay
Which would have been a very different type of
It's true it's true
Alex Snowden... No relation thank you so much
What's fun about that is it could be no relation to Edward Snowden could be no relation to Alex
Cuz people are sometimes related by first
Fatty's
I've heard him say that Ivan definitely heard them say that
So we we sewed
Play Chalisa.
The jump we kind of have something that relates
The present day
And that is
An insistence
That's theirs
False Flags,
We'll go off
And
Military
20 years ago prediction
Black North Korea nuke in a US city in World War 3
Which of course all happen
Yeah just because Alex talked about it and stop the evil globulus plant
Well I mean it was good
Because
What I've seen is that the yuppies have not yet all woken up so soon
Alex to stop that
And protect the yuppies from the you know that the real
Blinding reality TV is bent towards coddling the yuppies so why would we allow them to
You make a good point.
So I would lay aside their there's a real stretch of boring shitt
In 2003 in July
Cuz it's fun
To wave through the pass
But
I heard Alex talk about the World War 3
Nuking of cities and I got
Take that boring to I could leave that aside
But
Join
Degree
This is a story that is strange that its existing on Alex Jones Show
Eddie's liko there's got to be something here you know whatever details that we are giving currently cannot
Not be the entirety of this store who's got to be more I'd be lying if I didn't say this
Spoke to me as somebody who like
Yeah I dropped out of high school sure you know there's there's this educational
Used to stuff by in my history
There's a bit alike who lets the dog out here who had a better chance of graduating college if I escaped High School I wouldn't be
I would be surprised about that obviously if she's
This person is taking college classes in high school it does require
Getting a GED or dropping out in Subway
GDP that makes this
This something that
The Deep In Me Speak deep in the story
I'm excited to hear about this
But first Alex has to dwell on how
This is a person who's too smart of the system. I'll come down details
Harrison Bergeron
Why
Nationwide
And from geography bee
Wasn't
Vicious
I don't know what kind of local spelling bees Alex
That that's bulshit
Can do is discuss the big National one
The largest spelling bee in the one they've seen televised is the Scripps National Spelling Bee
The one that the venue in the movie Akeelah and the Bee of course the documentary spelled out
Be started in 1927 and the first home-schooled winner was Rebecca sealfon
In 1997
After her George Stampy. I remember her I'll tell you why because I'm sorry this is
Response
The other thing that the spelling bee is great for is
It was all of the best episodes of cheap seats starring the sklar brothers and she had a
Just a fantastic
Stick appisode she was great on the show she was Graeter's amazing she was the first home-schooled winner
Well congratulations 70 years after school are the be started
Almost after her George Stampy and Sean Connolly both want is homeschoolers in 2000-2001
Then six years later in 2007 Evinrude or anyone homeschooled winners in 82 years
If Alex wants to talk about whoever really dominating the spelling bee game
He's talked about students
From India
The most
Consistent winners modern time
The script
Homeschool children of beating kids to go to public school and all these glass decapitations ism
True it's just the centerpiece of homeschool propaganda
Had to be clear I don't think there's something inherently wrong with making the decision to homeschool your child but
I do think it's unhealthy for
It's motivated from the sort of place that Alex
Who's coming from where it's like
The schools are evil and indoctrinated your kids into globalism and multi
Culturalism
I don't think of the healthy impulse
Or instinct
I understand some people at
More
Rational reasons for homeschooling a PhD in pedagogy
You would be like
Maybe I'm better than this Elementary School
I honestly think that might be unhealthy to cuz it's super on head of kale with your narcissism
Are like a PhD in therapy you should also be your own child
But that seems that makes sense to me what is it is not a healthy reason to home
Old school I just know that some
Arnot
So he's got this incredible knows he's got an interview this this way
Kid but first I mean there's just important
Other things
That must be discussed
Every week
And that
Well
Come on
Come get me you know where I live
The lack of enthusiasm that Alex has about someone threatened
I need to kill him
Not the first
It's strange that he feels the need to bring this up like really at the top of the show
But also the lack of
Conviction and passion
Is a glaring
I think I want
I'm with Al-Qaeda on a shirt
A hand pointing
To the person
That's what I really want to go through
Don't put that up armored absolutely and I'm going through airport security tomorrow where that
Just to see what kind of stuff I can take out
Also Alex
List of a bunch of nonsense evidence
That's at the globalist have been trying to dumb down the population for the last
Forever
I am at the proof of it
Is this Angela lipsman
Wizkid
Detroit
Call Angela
Which one
Is lying about the situation with Angela and her diploma
I was nonsense
He was getting into it
These documents and UNESCO
Talked about a lot of that the Passover
Is this
Angela has been taking college courses through the borough of Manhattan Community College for the past 3 years
This point since she was 11
Hey cheater earned enough credits to get in
Associate's
Apparently some interest from Vassar to have her come
Continue her education there but
Can't because the Community College
Can't give her
Associate
This is because you can't get a higher-level degree without some form of primary degree
You can graduate high school and get a diploma or you can get
Equivalence like a GED and that work
But Most states have rules in place that you can't get a GED until the age you would be when you would graduate high school
Angela's case in New York you have to be 17
Is rules in place for a number of reasons but it's primarily because socially a 14 or 15 year old
Is it ready
Need to be in a college setting
Generally
Even if you're intellectually able to handle the classroom material
It can be dicey
We've seen the results of
The baron
Brutal the bare minimum for the laces generally 16 years old
CED
Issuing
State that's the minimum wage in most States
You can Dropout of high school.
Do you be allowed to do that
It's generally seen as a preferred pass for student
To skip a grade
Is there overachieving because the Alternatives don't really
Seem to be super-healthy
Before a child Broadway
Plus when children overachieve this aggressively it's often a sign that they might be
Experiencing some unhealthy influence from parent
Like equivalent of an academic States parent
And that's something that you don't necessarily want to
Facilitate
Do you want to have kind of some some guardrails in place
Sure sure there are tons of stories you can find a people like Angela who
Studied college-level courses
And gotten
Credits
Prior to graduating
From high school but typically you won't be
You won't be awarded your
Degree
Even if you earn all the credits for it until you have an equivalent of high school
It's just
Pretty consistently across
The board
To go
I got in trouble almost every High School also allow has
Advance place
My class is like AP classes that you can
Translate to college credit
Yeah what happened
The do the test after work but it happened was I finished all of the
Until I had a huge chunk of my schedule that was a
So I convinced them to let me go to the Community College and take courses
Is there
But I hated those so I found out that you could
Test out of those classes and get credit for them so like
Instead of going to collapse like a game-high I just kept taking all these tests and getting grades
Good grades of these glasses but I never went so
Eventually they found out that I was spending half of my day outside of school doing f*** off and they got real bad
So I wasn't allowed to keep doing
Yeah
If it's not beneficial to
To facilitate that looks the Eric however we bought a Frazee
No I was immediately going to push back on you is like they shouldn't be doing that and I remember my start as life
There's also more to Angela story in this whole thing then Alex is letting on and
We'll get into that as
As we go along
So when we start off we get this interview going
Alex is interviewing
Her dad
Lips
AMC times in a couple times
Hobbit it seems like
It's mostly this dude
Please play
Right off the bat
No real red flag
And then he starts
Stalking
And I got
I got some
Love's problems
Which Curry to purchase
Each requiring
High School
Irrelevant
Orion
The guy went to the Lord
The Bill of Rights
Navigate to Megaplex
Please clearly reading off a script
Like a diatribe
Really interesting to me the way Alex
Try to interject
That he just steamrolled I don't know if I've ever heard Alex like
Just take a pic and I'll like that yeah and then they started the break music started playing
Very shortly after that
Yeah till I I kind of felt weird about that I've never I've never really
See that kind of behavior from someone who's a gastric no calling in
Look at the totality of evidence I have in front of me and all the information I've been able
Find care much for this Daniel lipsman character
It's one thing to support your very intelligent child pursuit of appropriate education but it's another thing entirely to do what he
He seems to be involved
One thing the whole studying at College at age 11 thing it appears to have been Daniels idea
In a 2011 profile on Angela in the borough of Manhattan
Community College
Just website describes how she got started
Quote my dad admit
Makia McDonald who was then assistant to the vice president for student affairs
And broached the idea of enrolling Me In Summer courses
This was just after she graduated 5th
Grade and I don't know how that story doesn't include
I told my dad I really wanted to go to college over the summer so he contacted Miss McDonough
Phrase make it makes it really seemed like this was something that he was motivated
My dad said I was going to Community College
It's
Yeah
I don't I don't
See as much agency of her in the way that
She tells the story in that in that profile it does sound like
My dad went behind my back talk
Go to this muckety-muck
Broach the idea and then the next thing I knew he said I've enrolled you in summer courses at the community college
Everybody I don't think that you necessarily get the sense that she's
Super opposed to it or anything
But it does seem like
The Caboose
It sounds like if you were give a few were asking me that question about swimming lessons I'd be like well my parents
I saw an ad in the paper and then the next thing I knew I was at swimming
So when you read this profile that you get a sense that she is an amazingly capable and driven person but also
The level of stress and responsibilities that was being put on her at that age
I think is wildly inappropriate
From the profile quote
I went to school everyday like everyone else
She says the two evenings a week I took the Subway downtown to Chambers Street to attend classes at BMCC
When she got home she
First tackle her 6th grade homework
That was the most challenging part she admits
But somehow I was able to get enough sleep and wake up refreshed the next day ready to do it all over again
Pounds
Not great
Oh man
This would make me a bit weary but the reality is that this isn't even the first time that Daniel lipsman has used his child to try
Try to bring legal action
Against the school
Hey 1999 lipsman sue the New York City Board of Education because he felt their uniform policy quote
Violated their rights
Free Speech equal protection privacy and Liberty under the first knife
In 14th
The judge found this case to have no merit so lipsman ask acting
Sing as the lawyer for himself in the case
Did you need to say that
Technically
He waved all the
The clams and the judge gave the school board summary judgment
Maidenform lips mandated
If you didn't get an actual lawyer for the case it would be.
He felt like he should be able to represent his daughter pro se but it's established law that you can't appear prosafe for someone else
You can only do that if you're representing yourself
So he was in the wrong here couldn't do it
Violate the everybody's entitled to an attorney
And the if you're not a lawyer and you're
Insisting on representing your child
Driving them yeah
The lipsman didn't get a lawyer and then decided to appeal the
Case arguing that quote
The District Court
The dismissal of Angela's claims on the ground that he lacked an attorney deprived her of her to write to a day in court
Wow
Big swinger
Affirm
That this is right around the time that Angela was graduating 5th grade in starting college courses
Taken together I can't help but get a little bit of a picture of someone not acting from a place of trying to do what's best for his child
But actually more someone who's acting out and using their child as a prop
Otherwise it's hard to understand how he wouldn't get a lawyer
To try the case about uniforms
If that was actually aware this was about like he's underlying claims as opposed to like getting a chance to grandstand in front of a car
There is a little seeming of you know oh well you won't let me do this cuz of the dress code fine then I'll put
Put my kid into Community College that'll show you I can't wait you know I can't
Ozarks
Seems there
Daniel's issues go back even further than that of course
I was able to find a New York Times article from 1993 about how New York schools were delaying in opening
That's who you are because there was a fear about his best
They're doing a thorough
Navigation for letting kids in
Angela was about to begin
Kindergarten
To this article Daniel and take him to school board to court
To try to force them to open the schools on September 9th
Ultimately losing that
You can look at this as having previously been really into schools and then a few years later going
180°
I actually think that this Behavior track
Perfectly with his later actions
He seems to like to sue people
But particularly the school board
I would guess he is a fairly libertarian-leaning set of politics
So I guess you probably be super opposed to spending money to inspect
SchoolsFirst
Absolute money in bureaucracy what the free market should choose whether or not
Asbestos kills my child
Stream 93 of him repeatedly suing the school
Things that
You seem a little weird imagine this is a guy who has a card ready and waiting at a security checkpoint just like you do
Don't have the right to search my car sir thank you very much
Hangover the diploma issue
Is not the first time
Betty's tried to
To tangle with the school board
On his
Presumably on his daughter's behalf
Troubling
Pattern
Yeah I mean you know
I imagine
Every single person involved when he walks in the door when this guy
So that's not a good place to be
I don't want to be that way
Also two pieces of information about Daniel lipsman that I found shocking
One of them I can prove and the other one is a little bit unclear
The uncleared Dead the whole time
The one that's unclear is that
Think he wrote a book in 1972 titled
The Jewish connection
There's a listing for that book being written by Daniel Jean lipsman
In the library of congress's catalog of copyright entries
But I can't find the actual book and I can't 100%
Confirm that this is the same person
Person
That is definitely his middle name though is it
Pretty good
My experience if you title the book The Jewish connection the my eyebrows go up
If you are a person multiple suing the school multiple times for Ticketek stuff
You are the type of bush it person who wrote the Jewish
I think it's obviously we don't have any access to
The book will be making undue assumptions about it I have no idea
Possible but it's train
Take a present look back
The finger like a roofing is that in 2020 lips
Smith received exactly one vote in the race for the 13th
House seat in New York
It seems like not too far-fetched to assume that he voted for himself it's a little ghost to vote for
Which means that he ended up time with such luminaries as Eugene vdubs almost
Keith Sweat
And a misspelling of
Katt Williams
So Eugene Debs was dead the whole time maybe he's dead the whole time
The 2nd
Accidentally misspelled his own name on his boat
Keith Sweat
Tied with
TV's John Stewart aboveboard
There's a part of me the field
Bad for Angela
No one under eighteen should have
Literally any exposure to Infowars particularly not being interviewed on it and being used
Create a public school propaganda
Yeah the wave this
Is being
Done, Tri-City
Every part of this sucks for her only
Yeah he was boring so we're not going to look into too much but this
Incredibly f*****-up thing
Did end up happening that just baffled
That's good instincts on Angela's Park
I can't imagine how Alex couldn't realize the giving out the contact information for a fourteen-year-old on his show
Might be a
Super inappropriate thing for him to do
But not to be outdone by Alex's completely insane action
Daniel popson and says this
Blew my
F****** mind
Well if folks want to get ahold of you
4420 4420
Yes we have them giving out their home address
Complete with apartment number
That's just not f****** cool at all
Wow
Wow I don't know what I don't know what
Kind of like
Nobody's listening to this show ass feeling they must have had to be able to like this is safe
I mean
Cheesy
Jesus Christ
I feel like he's got a
Copy of Catcher in the Rye on him at all times
Stackhouse
I can't imagine dodging the bullet of like we almost gave out a child's email address
Let her real address
Yeah
Oh my God she doesn't share that with
Two other little girl this whole thing got resolved on Angela turns 16 and went to New Jersey where she
She could get a GED at
16 as opposed to waiting until she was 17 in New York
You got her degrees and ended up pursuing a path in law
Unfortunately
Unfortunately this fingerprint
And still remain so this episode of Alex Jones a show where this story was told
I am glad that she landed on her feet though and see
Seems to be alright is
Absolutely Dynamite at two truths and a lie
Her
Her two truths and a lie game must be out of this world
It's just three things better dad to the school board for unwanted made up
Nuts
Just like really
Come on
Come on wait until you get a 17-16 to get a GED if nonsense
Bernard Malone
Yeah that's not true
Because he feels like Texas is a common sense
Freedom state that you can't
Dgd whatever you want feels like you're free or in Texas
Then you are in other states yeah but your 360
So you're not at 3
It was really interesting and obviously I really enjoy
Digging and I'm trying to figure out what the real story is
You clearly had a great time with
Obviously offer a lot more variety terms of those things
Usually
I'm not blessed with
Multiple
Instances of this in one episode her dad was one
Story and Alex has another guest
Would like holyshit this sound
This sounds like it's going to be amazing
Track
Crime books
Find out with
That's fascinating
Yeah I feel like we're in you can buy gas spot territory
What are selling your book or the like
So this guy he didn't name himself after race Bannon from Jonny Quest
Can confirm that
He's written a book called race against
Steve-O
And you got a little bit of breast Interpol agent
Has a really
Really extreme story
About going around Europe in killing
People who were involved
Denis human trafficking and child exploitation
Drinks and Alex is a little bit ambivalent about this because he believes that Interpol is actually engaging in
And so he's having a difficult time squaring this but
He's going to interview race Bannon
And
This is this thing no one is ready for this I'll tell you that right now
He's got to go to some calls
There's a theme
And these calls
In California in Northern California
I just wanted to congratulate you on your excellent
Interview again Coulter last week
Counting down of America that you're
New York
Yes and I mean I just wanted
Air hockey
Run over by a
Attract
Yeah this is there's a real Trend most of the calls that he gets about how he destroyed
I don't recall that I don't either but I don't recall her slapping and honking like a goose
Her laughing at how stupid
Yes
Nice laugh but
Perhaps that stop me
Yes we get another call and guess what it's not the same thing
Alex
Agree with the last caller there
Are you doing
Tremendous job on Tannerite
Standard
He really thinks he's something
It did a job
That's not what she said
But ya didn't either on who showed or in the book
Real interesting
Misogyny
April absolutely one-hundred-percent misogynist
Your calls of like
Resentment towards this woman who thinks she knows things
It's strange but I it's not too unexpected
I think one of the things that you really notice about this is it
Culture is legit stream relevant
Answer there's a preoccupation with
And like an obsession with
Continuing the conversation about her
Long after that interview happened right
And like soda
Secrets of aftershocks of attention of the earthquake of the original
Boulder and reshape it into like this heroic story that Alex
Vanquish Medusa or whatever
It would not surprise me to discover that most of the time when Alex
Is easily dismantled by a woman
A group of men get around him to gather and say that he's so great and he's he won he's the best at
Well woman would ever defeat any of us
It was so amazing how you yelled cupcake
Drunkenly if that woman is a woman
Men are better
So Alex gets to introducing dr. David race Bannon
The excerpt
Or like the little blurb of his book
Cersei
Could not sound more bored
And the darkest
Deny
Deliver
Beyond the reach
Notorious
Criminal
I even Ian to the middle of that
This is a sleepy board
That's high in tree I mean it it sounds
Blackamoor
So I imagine it's probably not as true as we would like it too
Who knows this guy Jonny Quest characters
You being recruited at 19 after being caught at a South Korean Riot that one raises
Sure
That story is actually fairly interesting he was at
South Korea
Student uprising
And
He got stabbed
By some guy
To kill him
I am aha Interpol recruited him right they were really impressed with
At 19 Interpol is like 10 that's a good murder their scouting
Okay
Riots now I'm going to say that sounds far-fetched but now that I hear it
I think he'll tell a little bit more of the details of that story
Later so we'll get to that
We got recruited in became part of this
Unit
Call Dark Angel
Brought that goes around Atlanta
Deals with these human trafficking
Interpol was the good guy
However
Certainly
Subdirectory
Wish I were
Dark Angel
Do identify those
Dubai in
Children
Across International
National wines
Having said that
You mentioned
Foremost listener
It's difficult
The rapper brain
This type
Prime
Do you see their him being like
Different Alex
This point is going to be like hey
I'm dope
That's a good way to placate Alex's
Concede to his main point right right out of the gate
Right right
What are things that I'd like to do a Xanax
Experiment
No I want you to experience this information and see
What you think about it
Other red flag
Write Spanish
Yeah but we're going to begin the story at the beginning and we're going to go through all the way to the
And we're going to go
Piece-by-piece to see what is true and what's not true
Well I mean we don't we can't really know that
But I just want you to have your instinct
Gacha life
What what do you what do you ask somebody who
Takes in information and assesses it how do you feel now this guy sounds like
Got cold
Let It Go
Alex's
He's really trying to nail this part down that is like
Sure
Traffic
King and what-have-you every time I look into it
My enemies who are doing
Exactly correct
Meijer's with Interpol
When we were assigned
Crackers individual
Many times
We would find with any network
The slavery ring
Their individual
Jules highly-placed
Either religious
Store political
Leaders are
People
Old man
Very seldom
Those
Targets in
Instead we would Target
People lowered
That is correct
Well
Problem number one is very simple
If you are in control of your story why are you agreeing with absolutely random and saying things Alex to say
I mean if your story was true would you say true things
Instead of being like Alex
You got it ask
Exactly right unless that is part of his true story to say that
Piano
Alex bring this up
Is forcing a change
The story you haven't read his book actually be part of
This is a sad is life story
Construction though of
This guy is an Insider haha
In this agency
AR games
Any kid
Experience
The Interpol is essentially just a cover-up operation
Protecting these really rich
Powerful people
While taking out lower-level folks
No he didn't
That's exactly right
That I have a problem
I don't think I have it from the Fuller interviews I don't think
If you would
Not say
Say that
What
Wouldn't he say well you would say that he's
Killed a lot of people
Do believe that there are a lot of P
Interpol who wanted this
Terrible traffic
Stop and we're doing everything
To stop it
But I also know that
Frequently
We were
Not assign
The cases
Where it was
Was very clear and
Individual
Significant
Influence
Was either by
Selling child
We are actually in
Involved in
The services
Unbelievable
Now
You would have stopped
The teams with arcane
Angel known as
The cleaners were innocent
We want to talk about this
When we get back
Mormon missionary
In South Korea
Call thing
Okay alright
How you feeling
Genesee Bloodsport
You know how that's wrapped Frank Dux
I hope that you know how that's a true story
I'm getting a lot of blood from this right now Houma today
The military had to let me go fight in this underground tournament because I was
Too good
For them
Get in the way of
Had to keep tabs on me because I'm too good what if I fight against old cover
Well
Yeah there's this interesting of those wipes
It's totally understandable because it's story
Is wild
Assassination team haha I think that there is a strange Trend in some of these gas
But Alex has that they
Like to
Portray themselves as hitmen
Larry Nichols his claim that he killed people for the Clippers
Yep.
Yeah I don't understand why these folks just insist on
Play Murder credentials
I don't know whether true or not cuz you know Larry's case was bulshit he admitted that he lied about that
Bouquets still might have been an actual cleaner
I don't know too many people who
Yeah I don't know
Too many people who killed anybody
Why
Do people look up to you if you kill a lot of people and I think it's
Machismo thing
Big menacing scaring people as part of their masculinity
And no know who has killed anybody though has been like
Killing people is not something to ever say ever kill people
Soldiers
Call Cami my grandfather
It's much more sense
What it was like
Yay I got medals in
Both of them were very much like
Not something to brag about I think that you hear that typically and interviews and stuff with people who have
The Story begins
Rooms for him in South Korea in this riot
He'll discuss that here a little
Started as a Mormon missionary in
South Korea
What time is very war-torn
Country
Students were killed during that riot
And I was required
Use lethal Force
Myself
Myakka
Who came to the attention of an Interpol recruiter and it was
Just convenient
For him to have somebody
Who had Korean Lang
Training
Malleable
To their propaganda
He says many
Fundamentalist
Kosher in
College campuses are without doubt the
Primary
Recruitment
A most intelligent age
The reason being
If you have someone young and naive
Who will equate
Service to God
With service
You can get them to do anything
Call man that whole thing about marrying fundamental a service to God with a form of patriotism
Probably feel like that is heavy residents with Alex's present-day career anything about that
Exactly what he does
Instead of getting people to
Do things in service of the country to take them to buy pills
I mean the mentality is pretty much the same describing
Yeah Alex's did really Auto
I am getting feeling like
If
He weren't
Recruited by Interpol
He would have been recruited by the secret space program
Said that I'm getting like that all of the recruiters for a very lot of Camelot
For various places we're all at that particular riots
They were kind of looking around and he just got nabbed by Interpol first he was about to be a super soldier and he doesn't even know how
How much you missed out all of these groups like this is a good space program
Globalist
All of them were there for like
A convention
And the right itself was actually just like
A recruitment thing watching with binoculars
Squid game until people became soldiers
That makes sense
So Alex wants to ask about like how
How many people have you killed
Like you're talking about the bearded assassin
How many people you've killed
We were then given
The dossier on this
Individual
And assigned either
The team or singly
2 Traxxas
Individual
Extract
As much information
Responsible
From them
Either through undercover work
Or
Sometimes
True torture and then Ulta
Play Eliminator
Answer this the head of arcane
Angel commissioner
The fair
With Interpol
Told me that I love you
250R
Archangel cleaners
Surah fath
Most of them or respond
Beaufort into
Two three digit
Yessir
Sure
Don Cornelius
The women and children
How big
It is amazing
Of huge
Global proportions
The money that is
Regenerated is
Listen to the billion
Dollars
So you killed
The hundreds of into the hundreds of people
That's the type of thing that where somebody's like
See this is so crazy they'll have to
There's no way anyone would believe that I would lie about that
It's too obvious that I'm lying I'm good that's why they'll buy it I'm getting a strong sense that you've
Attractive
You've marked this is bulshit pretty close to saying definitively
This is complete
Sweet bulshit
CBC you have
All of the cleaners
For the Interpol 258 or so of them have
Killed a lot of people
So you're telling me that these people are important enough to be assassinated but not important enough for anybody to notice
Thousands of them are going missing at all the all the
Do you have
You know just the basic
Gist of the story is already giving you massive
Red flags
The
South Korean Riot that leads to being
Recruited by Interpol
Becoming part of that program called Archangel where he's killed
Into the hundreds of people
Write it just
To eat
It's a little fantastic
I'm getting
Close to what is going to be my favorite part of the story
Which is the part where they have to explain why their evil organization that is directed them to murder thousand
The people
Will absolutely not harm them whatsoever after leaving and revealing all of those
And I'm looking for it already is unspoken
Won't say that you actually was an agent
Of course they wouldn't
Why would they
Why they never reveal that. No
No further
So
What are the big things that Alex wants to really nail down interview this interview is that they're ignoring
The upper level
People like the globalist who are they get a pass from Interpol
But that space
Basically the vibe that I'm getting from him
When he says old money
That's what happened
What is Italy
Ultimately it comes down to
Money as almost all of
Is pernicious rings
Do
The producers
Themselves
When we were able to extract
Information from the producer
Frequently they would name
More powerful
People who work
Funding their activities
Much of the material as well as
The children themselves
Some of the names
We were given we would
Deliver to
Our commissioner
And never here
They were names
The people that are info
In the world for their
Peter political
What are their name Siri or religious
Wow
Yeah that's
Wow this is exactly
What I've
Made up stories about for a long time and now you're
Telling me that all of its
True this is
Overwhelming Alex is not doing the work to sell
But he's also not doing the work of the sort of
I don't know critical analysis
Serious
It really feels like he's just trying to get this guy to finish
His story and then get him off the air like you just going consoles just like
Wow that's amazing is on for the rest of the show
Thrilled by this because it it feeds into the narratives that Alex already has in place
Namely that they're going around there finding these people is under using
Interpol as a way to cover up
Rise rich and powerful people find people are being blackmailed
In order to do exactly what the globalist want
M2
We've been wearing
Anchorage to infiltrate
The network
Just basically doing
Standard undercover work we were developed
Complete legend or covers
Story
Information
As possible before we also
Definitely eliminated our Target
Sometimes you think
Torturing
Why we were doing this we off
Futon cover
Many names within the network
They were not known
Low-level producers again all across
The world and
Immediately recognizable
Or upon further research we could
He was highly placed Within
Within a religious organization
Haitian divorce
Some major Global Corporation
Gyro
Just talkin around
The warehouse where we
Betraying that Archangel talking
Sing with some of our supervisors
Xcetera
We do know that they were occasionally
Times when these individuals were blackmailed
The information
Uncovered
To suit
Current agenda
Who's all works perfectly for our
Right
I get it
Come on
Are you telling me that Interpol
Is in the business of blackmailing
World leaders
Why
Why is INTERPOL doing
Right is that our first question ultimately at the end of the day Interpol does not like exercise a lot of power
In the global structure know that's the first question
A question it's not really even a relevant question for this interview haha
More about those assassination kill those people
God dammit
Assassination
Team
Cleaners usually with
3 or 4
Individual sometimes we are sent out
Singly or in
Teams
The team pad
Their Own Strength
Weaknesses
My particular for table
I was watching on his
Close sweat work
That is
Close quarter combat
Hands are bladed
Yes
Yes yes absolutely
The message that we used were design
To eliminate
Quickly
There were other methods
Used of course
Mercenary
Enough
The master and knives I was proficient in the size
Other people in my group had
Of course nunchuck guy there was another guy but he was a little bit out there
You know what on those long road trips he would keep us laughing he was a good guy
Dad I had to murder him yeah so he's not like
It's like a knife out of it you got like The Dirty Dozen f****** a******
Got the you got the guy is a sharpshooter nice guy probably explosion
Of course you can get into narrow syndrome
His story may be more believable for Alex
Is
This
Next clip
Talking about these sort of
It's not exciting to kill people kind of
Is counter to what you would expect
Somebody telling the story
To say
Little bit more credibility isn't it sort of off
Expectation
Lido
Throbbing
Sing another person's life
Find of using
Torture Tech
Extract information of course
Plays heavily
On one soul
Is very difficult
To deal with
Frequently these individuals we would either catch
Four-wheeler
Catch them
Surrounded by video or
Photograph
Images of
Abusing children
Seeing those images it was not
Then to
Use the method
In which hour
I was trained to extract
Information
Throbbing horror supposed to Annex
Flash
April right situation
No
I mean
You should be a f*****-up interview no matter what really
Like
Where are you at in your own brain
That you can hear somebody in such a banal way just be like I executed
Hundred
With
No legal justification beyond what it was we saw
An archangel named
Exactly why I'm listening to this person and
I am an Alex
This place going
Instead of you're a f****** terrifying psychopath and you need to be stopped at
It all costs that Alex does have some misgivings about this emotionally
Will killing people
He does think that this sets kind of a bad president
Can a can
So I appreciate him at least giving voice to that
Alex has some tough stuff
But we gotta face it
The truth but David race Bannon everything he said on the shows
Complete lie
2006 Bannon whose previous name was David dillie but he had actually legally changed the name of the band that does sound cool
He was arrested in, Colorado on a number of charges
Criminal impersonation that'll do it crime and attempted
Will get into the details on this but the short version is that he just made up his entire story about working for Interpol
Us authorities were essentially fine with letting it go but it became a huge problem when they realized he was using these fake credentials
Quote
Solicit fees in excess of $3,000 for a two-day training course on human trafficking
At that point he was actively profiting off of his criminal impersonation so they decided it was time
Go on to take
Plea deal where he admitted to the criminal impersonation
And the other computer crime and theft charges were dropped
He got five years probation
It was ordered to undergo Mental Health
Open substance abuse treatment as well as performing 100 hours of community service
Presumably
Not as a secret assassin
There's a chance that he actually could have done prison time for this but the prosecution
Specifically decided not to
Pursue it and the fact that he had to undergo mental health and substance abuse treatment right there was something
Irrelevant to that
That made it so like me
We think that he's
Got a problem I mean it gets back to the point of saying something like this which is if you
Did all the
All of these things in your saying it
You are
Absolutely out of your f****** mind
And if you didn't do all of these things in your saying it
You're absolutely out of your f****** mind
There's something going wrong
So the bottom line here is that this guy's a complete fraud in the stories he's telling based on personal experience that he's at
Add are all lies
All the stuff about how he knew that Interpol was ignoring some reports powerful people involved
Golden child trafficking
The stuff about torturing and killing and killing child pornographers that was from his imagination
The stuff about the riot in South Korea where you had to kill a man and I've got recruited into
Interpol at the complete fiction
The Charlotte Observer is a really good article about this where they rely on statements from Interpol itself as well as an interview with Bannon
Ex-wife
Pretty clear how much of a fraud do you
Cheap planes that during the period of time he claims he was out there killing human traffickers
He was actually quote
Teaching computer classes at a community college in Raleigh
Is it North North Carolina not North Korea
Assessment
Think David is well
You wanted to be a hero and wanted to be a writer so he created a relic backstory in a book with kind of solved both problems
The way you jump
Is actually pretty
He wants to be special but he doesn't want to put into work
Hilariously whatever
You're right that is devastating
Hilariously one of the sources that did some of the really good work deconstructing his fraudulent backstory
Is a website called Bushido. Net
It's dedicated to exposing people who lie about their martial arts back
That's great unfortunately to be a third-degree black belt in hapkido
And this got some of the folks at
Bushido poking around
No
Yeah my friend
They poked around
Figured out
Pretty much clearly lying about their belt and what led to pulling some
Threads
Their post that originally started on how he was lying about his martial arts skills ended up expanding at we Savage takedown
Facebook
And if their description of the plot is accurate at all this is one of the most ambitious lies I've seen
On the show
There's so much International Intrigue and murder
Even as to kill a friend and lover named
When he finds out the truth on North Korean spies
Premier things just
Deteriorate into an exercising
Fact-checking it's almost breathtaking
They show that based on the year he claimed it happened that South Korean Riot he says he was in could not have
Actually even happened at all right
They had somebody in France go to investigate whether or not a French
French Secret Service member that he claims to be engaged to
But died in the line of duty
Was a real person or not boil alert chichiwawa
It was all made up
They even contacted the Korean school he claims to have a PhD from and they have no records of him getting a degree at all
Great it's amazing stuff and it really helps make sense of why the Charlotte Observer article about him is titled
The man who lied about everything
Pretty much nailed it
I think this entire interview with Alex really highlights
Two problems with his show that exists
System 2003
Annie's guns
0 work
What's the remedy
The first is that he's the most
Gullible Mark who's ever hosted a show of this size
Just about anyone can come in and tell him made up stories about something he wants to believe and Alex will buy it wholesale
And pass it on to the audience's truth
This guy or Steve pieczenik say the stuff that Alex wants
To hear and things that make his narrative easier
Create a perception that
Geopolitical significance
Presumably historic heroic people
They think that I was just shows an important place to make an appear
That validating of Alex's narcissism is just something he can't resist taking part in
Regardless of how clear a liar you haven't developed for in order to get his fix
The second problem is actually a bit more serious
And that's because of how irresponsibly handles this stuff
He's actively disrespecting the very issues he's pretending
To take seriously
Uncritically interviewing is Doctor race Bannon is an affront
The people who take the fight against human trafficking seriously
Instead of dealing with the issue soberly as it exists in the real world
Retreats into his own
And in the process helps this guy promote
In profit off
Creating a fake life story
The exploitation of children as an intriguing plot point
Essentially it's a
Propped his story yet
How should be really ashamed of his participation in this but obviously race Bannon should get to the Lion's Share of the flag
The notion that he created this entirely fake career and Interpol and was using it to run seminars on human trafficking is
Terrifying
It's unknown all the organizations that he sold the seminars to but when he was arrested
It came about in the aftermath of one of his speaking engagements on a college campus in Colorado
After he took that gig the Colorado police caught wind of him and contacted him to see if he would do a training session for the police
He quoted
Bryce and that was plenty to fill out the warrant
When is Hughes willing to lie to students about the reality that is a very serious issue of human trafficking
He was willing to lie to police in a training setting
He probably had in the past
Yeah
This is more than a charlatan
Is a person who made his living disrespecting victims
Human traffic
It's just amazing to Alex
Can't or will not see through this very clear fantasy story
Of murders and spy novel tropes
Just because it works
To help him demonize the people that he wants to demonize it's a shortcut
Taking the shortcut cuz he doesn't want to do the work
The thing that I really want to
Sharp focus on
As much as like
Obviously this guy's the real problem
His appearance in the way Oz gauging with it
Really does
Has a connective line to the present
Yahoo's show sucked in
Similar ways back then
And he never learned
He never
You never fix these holes in the boat
Or whatever it's
It's just know he learned but he learned that the holes in the boat or what keeps him floating
Oddly enough
Yeah yeah yeah that that that may be true the paradox
Maybe
Maybe maybe I could or maybe he realizes it's in his
At best interest to sync the post and so the holes are actually good I can breathe underwater what the f***
Yep
It's
I mean if you don't give if you don't get caught
Consequences for your actions Beyond being rewarded for that you're not going to change your behavior
It's it's
All too often this is a little bit
Skinner isn't with Alex
Except just Direct
If you reward him for this Behavior he continues
To do it
You know
It's very simple
He does seem to have no
Ability to experience negative
Feedback
Like
But there's no
Constructive criticism at his world really that ever seems to exist
And so there is no negative feedback at positive feedback negative feedback is just proof positive
That you are on the right track
Until what was trying to f*** with you that's just positive feedback baby
Is it makes for a devastating Loop
Brutal so there's another thing that they have a conversation about
That I think is a little troubling
And they seem to want Alex and race Bannon
They both
Seem to want to invade Thailand
Wow be the US should invade Thailand because of human trafficking
Concerns
Which I think is geopolitical e weird
I'm in.
Not even saying
It amazes me
The things that we seem to worry about enough
That's over
And yet here are literally
And I've been in Thailand
Land on a number of
Assignments and we saw parents
Children
2 years old
To sell them
The slavery
Is this
Should not be allowed by any
I'm not denying the exploitation of human trafficking does exist
At all but
These dudes
Are having a
A fraudulent conversation here
Surrounding a fake lived experience
The this guy is is describing
It's being used
Call Ford
Geopolitical things like
Invading Thailand starting award
I thought I was an idiot
Can guys really against War
I mean
Iodized
I just
I just don't
I mean
Yeah yeah
It really going out there and saying that
People can hear it
Should start a war Wild
Some calls I mean just really some assholes said that there's a lot of human trafficking going on in Thailand so
You know what
Let's invade at least
For either
I don't know
But we can take the calls
We cannot ignore it.
Rob
Qveen Herby
Individuals
And tell me how
Amazing
Call
Basically hero kill people I feel like they don't
Stephen even f****** do
Much
Write a couple albums
Well I mean turn on the bright lights was their best what I didn't get better after that let's be let's be real
Pretty good don't know enough Interpol songs or albums to make this drug work
Call you when I deliver this is a risk that ass
Yeah I don't know I don't know the extent to which Interpol is going on
Assassination Squad
It's embarrassing the way that Alex has now accepted the story and is reporting
As opposed to being like
I'm talking to somebody who claims that he was
That would maybe be responsible way to interview this guy with a little bit of pushback
I am like
Let him are the claims but make it clear that you as the person the audience Trust
Have some misgivings right about the store
This f****** guy rules
What hero
Bucking get into it
It is very much so
And my PhD is in Asia
In history from Soul Man
National University by the way and
While
Throughout Asian history as well as Western
History
The elite
Pursue this
Task and dark fetish
Attract
Anything else will
4:30
Thank you will
And I mean
What's a grim added detail for me
Like the fact that the audience at requested Alex interview at every opportunity
Are preparing for the interview in anyway so we will just get duped by a con man into making a mockery of child exploitation
The act of not preparing for this interview I want to be very clear about this
Is a choice
And I suspect this one that I would routinely makes because if he prepared
He wouldn't be able to justify interview in these really ambitious Liars who helped him create profitable narratives and validated
His own inflated sense of self
Real guess
Wouldn't do that
At forum and if you treated the comment interviews like they deserve to be treated
They wouldn't provide him with what he needs
It's kind of like an unspoken mutually beneficial Arrangement between Liars we get a plausible deniability
Get a platform to say we are both
And then maybe you get hired by another cop agency to teach them about an f******
Human traffic
Will be completely useless as a training exercise
Let's be clear
Counterproductive it might actually impiantare ability to deal with is real and serious
F*** these people
So your way other talk about his book
Against evil get it cuz of name is race
Now that I got last week
New Horizon
Compressed air
Penguin
Wow
Right
Didn't write any old book you want
Unfortunately
Maiara
It's not
So I am actually not entirely even sure that New Horizon is an imprint
Good lucks
Take me to the list
On the website included which wasn't a good sign off
The job yeah and then in 2021 they decided to close up shop and in a post announcing
By the end of operations of new Verizon
They discuss the history of the publishing company and they don't mention Penguin at all
Which is another bad sign I don't believe it actually was artifact worth
An imprint of anger
Probably
Being a partner throughout enough
I don't believe that but Alex is using that part of his life
In order to establish that they would have done fact-checking
So therefore this guy stories must be true
I think that's
Justice
Super duplicitous
What you think they would just let you make a movie out of Ally
You check up on it they wouldn't be like
What is the kubotan why is this guy there they wouldn't
They wouldn't do any of that it can't be true Dan
So we get some
Interesting stories here at this point
Maybe this
Banning characters
Maybe feeling a little bit more like I was just saying all this stuff is true
Live Let It Go
I actually spent
Sometime in the North Korean labor camp
Get it
North Korea ID
Idea I
Myself
Was imprisoned
In North Korea
When I was captured
My PhD is
Is an Asian history from
University so
I like 10 I know a lot about this
I can assure temp
North Korea has been working
Construction programs biologic
Chemical weapons
Big boat
Call it is
It is it's a huge everyone on the inside
Has known that
It may be that is now just more politically
Convenience
House
Hang out there
That is correct
There are
Horrendous
Involved
I was only there for
A little under a week
Until I was
Traded
To South Korea in
Play swap that is
Is there was a known
Mole
South Korean
Secret Service
He was actually an hour
Green double agent
He has been
It was traded back
For me
Yeah they also got
Cash considerations and a spy to be named later
Unprotected for the next 22
Yeah
You can get the sense to that one of the ways that this guy really is able to get people like Alex
To go along with
That stuff is very soft-spoken
He seems nice
And then also
Clearly has some just
Like ingrained or in a
Improv skills
Like he's able to say yes to just about everything and then move it over to something else
Like
Talking about them serving dead
Human meat
I was like yes
And also there's a bunch of torture methods
Shift away from having to be talked about the cannibalism
The redirect
How is it that you know so much Alex and I'll tell you also about what's going on now
Check that I think Steve do it a little bit
How does my
Later though cuz he was
More than willing to be like no now he directed the shows
Improv
Evolved far away
Haha
So I we learn the sex clip
About to his fiance that he had he had his French Secret Service
Terrorism
Lady Hahaha he was his fiance into Ascension
Different guy
I was involved
Operation with Interpol
Counter-terror
French
Dfta
Agency
Where are we
Approached
North Korea
Terrorists who were used
Child pronography
Thunder activity
Including a bomb
Of the Paris
During that confer
Temptation my
Fiance
Today revealed who was
Hey
EST
Was killed protecting
The lives of others
Buy a North
Terrorist
And that's what old
Add to my
Willingly
Embracing
Sing the roll
Replay.
Eliminating these
Lockout
The moment I just want
2 minutes before she died
Dammit
Come on
Incredible
Answer problems
Problems
Frigidaire terrorism unit
We're fighting again
North Korean terrorist in France
And that his fiance got shot and killed died in his arms
This is a little much
What are you doing
I don't even need this in my life
I think any responsible person having this interview would have to be like what the f*** are you talked out of here
Go away Siri
That is
Absolute bulshit
At the moment of her passing then lower your head and then dramatic
Play raise it up where did scream
No at God himself as a rain down upon your faces
The next chapter
Seem to have an understanding of what's going on in this interview and that is like worth
Going to be able to use each other pretty well
Alex much alike
He did with the interview and the whole conversation
About Angela lips
A whiz kid
CPS
Because he hates the child protective service
Gordon's O'Bannon is a willing
Participate
Not involved in this
The number one group when I read the news
Counselor
Don't
Power
Children
Very much
Alex
The profile
Well said Alec
Everyone in child
Protective Services is indeed running a front for human trafficking
Great work
I am truant
CRST officers
It doesn't get more North Koreans terrorist than true Public School teachers probably in the mix.
Why not today is there around kids
So you asked an interesting question at the beginning of this and that was the idea of how he still alive
I told you we would get to that damned.
Here's the explanation there
Question
A list of
People
Incorporation High government or high religious areas
Finance
Globally
It were involved
He was probably too
An excellent question
Repeatedly
If I may say this
Account
But that is
Part of
The largest
Documentation
Secret
Insurance policy
Before myself in
Family
Release it to 100 torque
I understand
Around
So this how Liars like this guy lie
Like you can't produce a list of names
Because that's his insurance policy to stay alive
Impulse would not exist
The absence of proof as proof itself which generally speaking as the mark of someone you should
Shouldn't take seriously
However more
Interesting lead the way Alex and gauges here it is fascinating
Is it releasing these names
Because it doesn't ruin policy to stay alive and he's got to do that
Calling 100 places in
But then Alex remembers that he's normal talking point
Is it not that
Tecumseh
It consistently
Position that you're in danger only if you sit on information
The only way to act
It would be safest to live wide out in the open
What Alex should be doing if he was serious is to
Eejit insisted Banton release
All the information that he has immediately
Cuz did not do so according to
All the things Alex usually says
That's a threat to his life to not release all of it
I suspect Alex doesn't do this cuz on some level he knows Bannon is making
Stopping there is no less
Press the issue
The only way really through this interview is playing along
Even if you have to contradict long-held position
I mean I think the simplest thing
This one
Let's take it at face value
Is that true
Is it true that you are withholding the names
Of the very
Traffickers that you
Theoretically are 100% against
To protect
Just you
What Acura you're willing to kill in the triple digits
Annie
Possible harm comes to you oh my God yeah I got to protect the bees
Billionaires and millionaires who are financing
The ongoing human trafficking spit still happening that I'm not doing anything about what you were saying now is that you were
Willing to invalidate everything you've ever done
Meaning that every murder
Committed is 100-percent worthless and on your black shirt
Kingsoul
And then if you
F*** you selfish desire for safety comes at the cost
Of presumably
The lives of
Countless children
Individuals you guys want to play your masculine I've killed so many people bulshit
If you want to talk about courage
Kill zero people and die to get that information
Right
Pharmore drugs
So Alex is going to take a few more calls but he realizes like s***
Let's talk about World War 3
That is so serious
Is been right on the cusp
Bro long time
Matt is right now too
Detroit
Alex really seems to before
For this whole thing and he wants to know more about these these killing
Seems to be a point of fascination
A Alex
How you executed
What's with a knife
Primarily
Expertise was
With bladed weapons
General
We did either I would work
Problem
Individual and I can say that there are many occasions
Square thank God I was
Team because
Some of these scumbags
Very tough
We'd like to thank
Them all being coward
But they weren't
Are there were groveling
As well however
Alrighty
My goodness indeed
So your visitor view comes to a close with a whimper but
This whole thing was
Outrageous
Start so f*****
Yeah what's up
I was I was like
I was very surprised because like I said this stretching 2003 that I've been listening to has been really boring
Not worth
Even discussing really
And then I get
I get sucked in by the story of a
Genius
High School
And then it turns into an episode
Perhaps one of the most brazen
Sociopath
His show might be an exaggeration
Particular lies that this guy is is selling art
The nature of them
Much sicker than a lot of the other people
Are they coming to Alex's orbit the personal interaction with the
Stories
What they're about
It just gross
Yeah I mean it's it is that kind of like
I feel like the Batman
Conundrum for for these dumb
You know like
You want to all the superheroes the guy who goes out
Killing human trafficking knives up killing people
And just like Batman goes and takes care of crime
You're like yeah but you're not doing
F*** all but
Masturbating basic
You could be doing
You could be helping people
If Batman spent a f****** Dollar on helping human beings instead of building a goddamn
Batboat
Then maybe we'd be in a different situation this or dealt with the actual problem instead of the symptoms of a problem
This guy's doing that same thing of like I'm willing to hold onto these names because
That's heroic it's me living
I'm a vigilante totally
Taking on sort of the lower levels of things while intentionally
Protecting the powerful and wealthy
You have just
Told the most heroic story of yourself Subway's when they looked at it in that light it's almost
Good that this is fake
No it's incredibly good that this is fake otherwise there talking to somebody who is literally running interference for
All of the most powerful people in the world so they can continue child exploitation
Yeah so we wouldn't last clip here and it's Alex Soto realizing that he didn't
Get the most of the news
Acquainted
Underground
Armaldo
Daughter
I think listening back to these old episodes I understand how the strategy of Never Getting
The actual stories develop
Back then 2003 in particular around this time
It was super important for Alex to get people who are listening to go to his website because that was where they had a better chance of getting in
Integrated into the revenue stream
The best way to get people to
To go to the website was too hype up huge bombshell news that never actually gets covered on the show
Totally proven
And documented on the website that where you got to go to find it
Understanding you can kind of see how his show might evolve to essentially be a promotional tool for the website
Where Alex is insinuations about the news stories he should
Really it should be really seen as a sales tactic right people to take action without the website
Go to the website is a call to action
Not going to the news is it called action for highlight right absolutely not
His best interest
Discuss the stories on air because
If he did so the audience the impression that they've covered the relevant topics and there's no real need for them to go to
The site to see that coverage repeat it
Suspicion that this was an intentional strategy that also conveniently made it to Alex didn't have to do any work
And let's just continue to the present day that's
The training that he gave him
Also as it relates to that last part of the clip where Alex is being all snarky about banning bears
Bears are bad
You can't own a bear
A bad example
He's actually making a solid argument for band
Because
The danger
So let's ban guns cuz of the danger that is what I want if you want
Students be allowed to live in the woods
Official data stream or whatever
Everybody can have guns but they
Can't interact with human society have them in your home you can have free range gun
Yeah something like that
Old people driving that's also a really bad example because we
Required licensing to drive
I guess I was wants to compare the relative dangers of old people driving and guns that's great let's just
Then treat them similarly and require licenses and Universal background checks for gun ownership
His arguments are dumb even these arguments that he thinks he's making that are like
Slam dunks his best argument
Are the ones he makes
In a sarcastic sounding voice
Because if you if you attack your actual
Rebuttal with a washer
Let's band Bears the actual point you want to make is that everybody should have unlicensed
Unregulated Thomas Jefferson had a bear than everybody should have a bear
Actually that one does make sense pretty.
This episode was fun it was fun
Heavenly knowledge fight contact
Upset
Terrifier
Big Sur so much more interesting
Stuff to dig into
Nair then a lot of the present day
It's really nice to have that to that little break
It's going to
It's going to kill us all that little break-ins will I will
Pikalox
Need to shape up 19 years overdue he's got some time is he can figure it
Also will be back on Monday Jordan with probably check back in on the present who knows but until then
We do acknowledge right. Com
Omniome Leo MDX Clark on marbles
What the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color