Important
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Fix it and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
What's up
My bright spot today is playing this game
A little bit called the sinking City
Typo
Ambiance
Kind of game
Aquarius
The bright spot of it is
The city didn't sink
Pretty underwater there's a big flood going on because of the the Deep one
Alright
The esoteric order of Dagon is involved somehow
Did the specific Brightspot is there are little little
Monsters in
Stop the epic fail sometime
And the smallest one
That you killed make a sound
That I swear
Is stolen
From Eternal Darkness like I swear that that is a sound that is directly
Taken
Brahma turtle
Exactly the same
It triggers memories and me Darkness version of The Wilhelm scream
It feels like it and I've tried to look into it I Googled it
I can't find anybody that can confirm it
Convince me otherwise the makers of the game reach out to me and tell me it is now
Not from Eternal Darkness
I won't believe them
I will think it's a conspiracy with a little bit of delight
A real tragedy according to me
Because I I love that camera
The madness gauge and stuff like that we have such a fun innovation
Ruq Mega game that gradually makes itself unplayable
Azure
You should have played me better assholes
That's how I like it
I think that's some of that was a little bit over sold
You know
Once you know the things are not really experience is really
Is immersive but if you're like me
And we're 1718 when I came out and
High all the time
Close my f****** mind
I used to love
My buddy Nikki gif
Suelda play games like that and
Resident Evil
But he is also like
Really really kind of scared dude
Butte playing behind the scream just gets startled by every great times
Bring back video games
By the bright spot last episode was
Spoilers
No spoilers at all but
Great man so good
It's so great yeah I am excited to play it eventually but
Do you know what I I realize I was playing it and I hadn't played the original in like
Forever
Back into the things that I love the most about playing that game which is basically creating
A series of Rube Goldberg machines to get one machine to trip into a trap and then knocked
Sound like 30 different ones
It's just so much fun but you're good at your place
I'm glad you're enjoying it
In the most insist no spoilers
Oh my God
You have no idea
February 8th
Great
Top marks
What are the best episodes he's ever done I think there's some problem
Okay
Things going on in the world certainly and when
There's World intensity
That's when Alex is at his worst
I will check it out a little bit
Hello
Zombie walk
First sugarbear.
Rhode Island skeleton
I'm a policy wonk
Steve nowicki
The tiny cardboard Alex Jones says the bone broth is loaded with vitamin R thank you so much
Next big daddy crust
Muppet chimp says the new Technic ride drop
Gigsalad bright spot I think it's about you and I
It is very special
A technocrat shout-out going out to wish
To Alexis and Jared
Many more moons going around Earth go around the Sun what is it
Strawberry Moon
This is the last time you guys many more moons and Jared happy anniversary
Y'alls technocrat
I'm a policy wonk I have
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe the next few moments
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Real walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I apologize to the
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
We better tomorrow
He is If today is tomorrow he's not better
Baltimore
So he starts off as a sort of the tradition
Yeah sort of the more recent episodes
Declaring that
Is upon us
Okay and it's not Russia's fall
I hate to say it again we called what was happening they chose
Black forces in water
I see into eastern Ukraine and Russia and other areas
They Russian
Episode population aeromax
When's mount
And this is
But attempt to
Get the
Come into the race
And start a major
On
Believable
Not to be believed I mean 8
That's that's
That's
Gremlin
That's Kremlin there have you check their website
What narrative
Yes believe that s***
We've seen this repeatedly in recent days like Alex is offering analysis
Situation Ukraine
It's over the top
But like
He claims that rushes The
The victim
But there's an attack on the Russian held areas in a sovereign country
Which is weird
What that that there's a disconnect there
I think if somebody were to attack New Orleans
France would have course be like how dare you attack our French held territory in the United States right now
Strange
I honestly don't think Alex's position is something he can seriously argue because essentially no one in the International Community
Formally recognize recognize areas
Like her me or the Dumbo sorry Jaden is being legitimately part of Russian territory
He's calling me Russian held territories and for him to say those words he has to understand that they're holding
That without the right to do so
Also I want to point out that I don't just trying to soft sell the idea of
These areas are rightfully Russia
Who population in these areas are like
98% Russia
The argument here is that the people are essentially Russian
I'm so bored
Hear it really should be part of Russia they're all Russian
That's what struggling
The most recent census in Ukraine was done in 2001 although attempts have been made to do one sense but they've all been po
Postponed
But don't boss region is made up of 20 blast the luhansk
And donuts
In the most recent
Scientist depopulation of donuts was
56.9% Ukrainian
And 38.2% Rush
Russia practically 92%
Approximately the same ratio exist
Aloha.
With a 58% Ukrainian at 39% Russian
For some comparison to population of Texas is 39.3% Hispanic or Latino so for Alex
Argue that these areas of Ukraine or actually Russian
He's going to have to get himself in a weird position does Mexico ever decide they want to occupy two
Fortunately think again my head
Hey beat this is exactly like what if
There's a massive number of Mexicans who lived in Texas and they just said
Well Texas is ours now
Alex will be real bad about that and then the numbers are exactly the same there's an exact percentage
Well
Alex Wood look
No
What's going on here is that Alex has misremembering one of his talking points from 2014 when he was
For Russia to Annex
XtraMath
Peninsula is 58.3% Russian a 24.3% Ukrainian
So when the annexation was happening the pro-russia talking point was the premiere was base
Physically Russian
So they should be able to claim the territory
Alex is conflating
This argument with
The statistics that were thrown around regarding the status of South ossetia and abkhazia
I was just make
The Georgian territories that Russia
The leaves are there
Both are within Georgia's recognize borders but South ossetia population is only about 7% Georgia
With most of the rest being our session
Similarly the population of abkhazia is over half abkhazian with a minority being at the mcgeorge's
Because these
Ravens had these demographic profiles books like Alex argued that they weren't really part of Georgia is a wanted to be part of
You should be
That was part of the talking points justifying things
It made sense then
Make spice
Texas much sense now
Alex doesn't actually know what's going on in the world right now but he knows that he's invest
Didn't create a party in this conflict
In opposition to the evil global
And it shows in the way he's just recycling talking
Complaints that weren't accurate to begin with
And wouldn't even be relevant to the current situation Eva
Even if they were
Another thing that's important to bring up here is the numbers of Russian people compared to Ukrainian people in the Don Bosco region
It's pretty difficult to assess
Partially because of intentional actions taken by Putin
The government of Russia is carried out a policy of passport ization as it relates to the residence of Don Bosco
Whereby the issue passports
The people unmasked
This is a couple of
Particularly dicey side effects
Probably the chief among them
Is it allows Russia to artificially inflate the number of citizens they have in the region
And the protection of those citizens would likely be a major piece of any argument that was made
If they want to talk
Occupy oradix the territory
The real-world situation is complicated and I would be lying if I said that I understood everything that's going on than most of it but
But I can tell you with absolute certainty
Is it Alex's
Wheatley winging this coverage
I'm making s*** up based on things he remember saying and past shows
When he was rationalizing crushes Act
Their neighbors
Etienne has the fingerprint is there it's
Very clear
Talking Tom
Is old
Wrong and arela
Weird it's weird that you would bring it I mean obviously it's
For him it's not like any you know
God bless Russia and more just like
I have no skills
And I remember this thing so I'm just going to do them just to read redo that one
This is bad
This is pretty bad
This is bad I mean it's a propaganda is bad it's not they're not even trying that hard
It's bad
Yeah yeah
Sloppy
I'm not being the tip of the spear
It really boils down to is like
Less
Necessarily intrinsic support of Russia and
Weird worldview that Alex's
Created for himself where Russia is an enemy of his imaginary enemies
And therefore he supports
Them
And so any conflict
Like that what's going on in Ukraine any kind of
Possible conflict
Is attention
Between Alex's enemies and on the other hand
Russia who are
Against Alex's animes and therefore he'll always side with Russia
It's very it's very
Confusing
I'm stupid
This one's
This one's a little
I'm going to have to call this floppy work on everybody's part
I think it's sloppy work on Putin fart
Dreading NATO's doing sloppy s***
The news
Alex
Everybody the only people not doing right now
Are everybody else who is confused as to why these assholes are fighting a war
Yeah
If i m
You know you can only do such a good job when you're
When the whole point is I got confused
Yeah apparently
Unbelievable
False flag
Kindergarten
Text for this and now here we are
Hillary Clinton the people representer
We president now
It's a Roundtable
Clinton crime syndicate
Obama's
Soros's crime syndicate the roller lock
That are
What in the world are biomedical martial law
So here's what I'm supposed to believe
I'm supposed to believe that a combination of Hillary Obama and Soros is individual crime syndicate have come together in there
Spiralizer
Control into a World War that'll probably be nuclear in nature
But they can't take out Alex
How could they
Like you supposed to be the most dangerous guy in the world to them because he has their number
And they tried to recruit him because he's so damn good
Let us go let him live when they have the ability and willingness big actions will cause the deaths of millions or billions of people
It seems f****** dumb and honestly they could kill Alex so easily
He's so unhealthy that any kind of heart attacker was open.
Do the toxicology they be like oh my God I'm sure he died just because he's
Is Alex be less suspicious than Breitbart having a heart attack
It really would be
Yeah I don't know I will say they're probably waiting for the right moment big anime
They want to do is they want to see everything he's built laidlow you know
And then really step his nose in it
Everything has to have sort of a dramatic Arc
Cotuit Alex's world
Circle
I say we defeated you Alex where's your God now
Probably
Anyway also Alex has no evidence that the bombing he's discussing here was a false flag
Kindergarten
Do the kindergarten in the Levant region in Ukraine which was shelled reportedly by pro-russia
Separatists
Attacking from the East
According to Ukrainian soldiers
Who said they did not return fire
Russia put out a statement claiming the Ukrainian stage the whole thing which is
We are now in a position where folks like Boris Johnson or saying these acts or false flag being done by the Russians and their folks like Alex
A false flag
Being done to the Russians and there's no way to move forward
It's just
Alright I look okay
I know
The
The warrant
But has Boris Johnson sent
It's Putin a box
Chocolate or flowers or anything to to thank him for
Not
You know allowing the news cycle to last long enough for Boris have to resign
Yeah probably
I was trying to think of what the UK version
KB
A crumpet I could be it could be
It's it's very
Complicated to like this idea of everybody saying everything is a false flag
I think it's awful
And I think that it's really dangerous in terms of
The president could say
In terms of people understanding what's happening in the world
Like if you allow for everybody to do
Presume that things are false flags and nothing means any
What's 1
Once Biden came out before a false flag or attack at all happened and said
We think they're going to do a false flag at that moment reality cease to matter I kind of agree with you now
But I do think there's one stipulation that I would make
And that is that there is a possibility that there was
Intelligence that there was going to be a false flag is that the case
Calling it out he's something
That would be awesome
Strategic relevance
The issue that I have
Is that if this happens more
It's all over
Alex says everything is a Volkswagen that's her dad
Just do record
You understand this is how he's information works
The idea of this
The government
Would also date to get into that game is a little bit
It's not good
If it's not an actual at example of something that they had solid evidence
Or intelligence
It becomes
Like wild nothing means anything anymore
I mean
From my understanding of how that would go
Alright
In order for Biden
To come out and say with the backing of the
In community
We know they're going to do a false flag
That essentially has to me neither
We know that the Russians
I have been communicating got a false flag attack is going to happen so we're telling them week
You can hear them right
Or
It is we're making this b******* up
And so we're telling them that we're lying about this stuff but they can't say out loud that were lying about it cuz it's going to look like
They're lying about
Like this
Once we get into a situation where now we're in an infinite Loop of well if I do this it's going to look like they do this and I do
It looks like that we don't know what don't know what the
Phuc yea
It's Fox
But if it's
The first option then you kind of understand
The the
The tactic being used although it's
Weird but I don't enjoy it
I don't I don't like to hear those words coming out of anybody's mouth or a historian
Did anybody stopped Atkins
Consult us like we've spent the last 5-6 years talking about false Flags almost non-stop I wouldn't
Anything to add
Have to think
Giving recommendations
Is no false flag
Volkswagen should only exist in the fictional area of Alex Jones's world
So we have a situation in Ukraine obviously
Plates
Sure he's also got a situation in Canada that's getting out of control
Arresting
Without bail
Peaceful protesters
You know it wouldn't just be in
Situation
The capital of Ottawa
Arrest
People in jail
We don't tell you why they arrested
We have the Sean of
Blocky the preacher
Who is now facing
Prison is a terrorist
Calling him a terrorist for praying
Alex is language is really bad there cuz it makes it sound like the guy's son got arrested but is actually just
Article on Pulaski
Arrested
Covering
What would a
To be a large story here but you got to really look at
The details is offering and you can put together
Pieces
He's talking about
To hear the Essential Elements of the story
1 people are being arrested
Not in Ottawa
Two people are being held without bail
And 3rd pawlowski as been arrested
And there's some mention of his son
Story is that there are massive numbers of arrest for no reason
Who are then being denied bail
That's the impression he's Sunday
In reality this is just about one person order pawlowski
An article about him Alex's read on Rebel meme
Is it just came out on February 16th that pawlowski had been
Denied bail and relationship took place
Kouts Alberta away from the Ottawa situation
Valesky's
In Rebel
Alex is lying about what happened
The Dow and the all of the
For one thing
I was just claiming one of the Border Blockheads but it did
The border crossing from Kouts into Montana was being blocked and Pulaski was arrested
At that
Arrested is home but had to do with actions that he took
In relation
To the bi being at the couch walking
Right right
The second lies that he was arrested for prank
With the truckers
That's absolutely not true
Early in February in agreement have been
Construct between the lawyers for the truck blockade and the RCMP
That would allow for a couple Lanes of traffic
To be open
Allowed
Have some flow of goods over
Over the Border
These later Pulaski was recorded on video giving a speech at a place called The Smugglers Saloon
Where you passionately arguing that
The protesters should go back on their deal
And that they needed to be willing to sacrifice their lives
For the cause of
I guess getting rid of Public Health measures
This constitutes excitement inside the protesters to go against an agreement they'd already made with the police
So he got arrested
Ultimately the fact that he keeps going around wherever he stands to get a bunch of attention and desperately tries to
To get arrested
Made the courts
Beside baby
Stood a really strong chance of reoffending if he was released
Also decided that his defense
Could not assert free-speech ground since
What's Canada's Charter doesn't Protect free speech
That would incite other people to commit criminal activity that's trouble
Shouldn't have done it in the wrong country buddy stay on this border should have gone to Montana
Incidentally the couch border-crossing was where the RCMP and covered a large cache of weapons
Sand a little while after Pulaski gave you the passion speech
To never give up and called the blockade their Alamo
Four of the people arrested at the blockade were charged with
Conspiracy to murder RCMP member
That's going around
Like over the weekend Hospital in Ottawa
Close at the campus due to a bomb threat
A woman was arrested for making a bomb threat against the mayor of Windsor
A twenty-year-old
Ohio is likely facing felony charges
We're trying to call in a bomb threat to the Ottawa Sheriff's Department
I think he tried to because he was real idiot and
You trying to reach Canada but I accidentally called the city in Ohio called Ottowa
There's apparently an Ottawa Ohio
A bomb threat referencing Public Health measures then called back
Kentucky been shot but when he said where he was pleased.
Confused because it didn't match any location in town
This whole thing was busted and he admitted he was lying and just trying to waste public resources responding to a fake report of someone being shot
Great because he was mad about public
Health measures in another
It's just
The creativity
And the problem-solving on display
From these people
Is just
I mean
You don't think of
Convoys as being hotbeds of ingenuity
But the way they're going about
Getting the
Stated directive that they have which is to obtain
I don't get a lot of
Overthrowing the world's government right
Ottawa
And nothing's really been at
Lake Pulaski
Comes of it there's going to be a lot of really G
People who might start to think their last allegedly peaceful solution
Has been a failure
And I like it
Blackpilled as they say
You can see here in this case study a great example of how Alex lies
To build narrative
The actual story is just one guy who got arrested
Stood for inciting people to violate an agreement that they made with the police who is denied bail because of a documented pattern of behavior
Alex reports that is people getting arrested all over Canada not being told why they're getting arrested because of the emergency act and then being denied
It's b*******
Yeah but at the very least
It is
Aimed at getting people who are already notoriously violent and on a Harris
At knife's Edge
20 no no this is terrifying
Yeah probably
He's discussing the arrests that are happening
As it relates to the Ottawa protest
What appears to be several
Thousand
Man
Black ski mask in police uniforms
And they already started the arrest of the leaders
The trucker Freedom Convoy
And they are
Not charging them and singer being held without
Bale
Martial law
Infantis the police may not have been wearing black
Ski mask foot just like balaclava
Are you really cold
Super cold
You can find plenty of images of police not wearing masks or just wearing covid masks
Who's apart of Alex's branding of his enemy forces but it's also important to remember that even if everything Alex's thing there
There were true
That would still not be martial law
He definitely has no idea what that term even me
Does it matter
It does
Well I mean to you
Cuz he calls himself mr. martial law
I think that would be the first sign that he doesn't know what it means it could be
Also Alex is just lying again
The organisers who were arrested have been charged
Emerald
Was charged with counselling to commit mischief and she still awaiting a bail hearing as of
The preparation of this episode
She may get bail she's not been denied it yet that's for sure
Chris Barber is another one of the organisers that got arrested but he was already released on bail by Friday the same day
Episode that were list
Listening to
Who was charged with counselling to commit mischief
Counseling to disobey a court order
Counseling to obstruct police and Mr that interferes with the use and enjoyment
So he has
He has been
I am so annoyed
By every
Legal system in the world that uses
The word mischief
Didn't
A crime
Simply Misti
It seems like they had a prank
You can't say the same thing
Mann packing is another Convoy organizer in l a
Lee public statements about
Is belief in white supremacy
He was arrested and charged with mistress counseling to commit the offence of mischief
Counseling to disobey a court order in counseling to abstract
Deer court appearance over the weekend but as of the timer recording this I'm not
Entirely sure if he got Bail or not but he may have any may still get it in French
I'm not I'm not certain
Just making things up because the details he's making up fit the narrative that he want
Pasta salad
He needs to sell the feeling that Gestapo blacksky
Mask-wearing shockproof surrounding up all the Convoy leadership
The staves holding them
Without charges indefinitely but none of it's true
He makes this s*** up because if he didn't
He wouldn't
Be able to create the app
Impotent
That he needs is audience to stay into
Some captive
That's that
Yeah it's a little weird
It is a little bit weird how
Hard the American far right is
Really pushing this I guess assault on Canada's
Sovereignty
Boy are they
If it is
Another country had done this type of s*** like if if the situations were reversed
Bright
Half of Canada's parliament is like
Hey y'all better go down to f****** America and really kill those guys as much as you can because their governments evil
OneAmerica do like sanctions or some s***
Why can't Trudeau be like hey guess what
Tucker Carlson if you coming to my country again you're dead
Navigate to far are being taken in
In terms of like freezing the donations that come in through like GoFundMe
Give us time to go kind of stuff I think is
Maybe the appropriate
Level up
Trying to stop
Influence
But yeah I don't I don't know it is it is really weird
Yeah where you intellectually get around that some like Alex Wood is that it's not about Canada. About their sovereignty
Protecting their sovereignty from the global crime syndicate
That is running the country right now I understand but sometimes it is about sovereignty cuz that's what you're attacking
But it's not really if you say it's not
I didn't consider the old
Husband charged
Polish immigrant
Preacher
Popular preacher
Who winning the Convoy
Jasmine arrested
And they're not even charging him and they're saying that
He's being held without bail
That is also in the news for the other individual
Two men arrested
They're saying
Will not say
Where they are what happened to him
This is martial law
They're clearly trying to start a shooting War ladies and gentlemen and
The corner where folks have no other choice
We do not
Need
To go out
And start shooting words
This point that's a really interesting perspective because you really have to ask yourself what Alex is trying to
To do here
He's a lying about the situation that all these Convoy organizers organizers in Pulaski are in in order to frame it is
Kind of a martial law scenario
His explanation for why the government is doing these things is that they're hoping to trigger a shooting War which Alex's supposedly against
I don't believe that
If I was truly opposed to the triggering of a shooting War then
He would want to report the information about the protesting the arrest
Accurately as possible
Sensationalizing things only Ally people to drawing a conclusion
Possibly taking impulsive emotional actions based
On those inaccurate conclusions if they were
The only reason you would lie like this with these dramatized
Details specifically tailored
To talk on the very specific fears and paranoia is
That you've built in your audience
Is tomato kind of impulsive action more likely
The Fingerprints of Alex's intentions are really visible in his actions here
He wants to escalate the situation with the sort of hopelessness in the audience
How about any peaceful solution
To the problems that they face
His actions really don't makes
In terms of any other contacts
Text that I can play
Well I mean
I would say if
If
My
Favorite guy was in the middle of saying hey
You guys better stop attacking Ukraine otherwise we're going to have to save everybody's life in Ukraine
And everybody's like
No
Nobody's doing that please don't do that and he's like yeah you guys are just trying to make us go into Ukrainian save everybody's life in Ukraine
Right now
Is that Mike
Make your
They're trying to search you anymore that's what they're trying to do
Kind of sea slide
Similarity
Yeah
I don't actually know if I necessarily thinking that Alex wants like shooting
Start
But I think
He's really disappointed that things seem to be
On the downslope
Climax seems to have been reached in terms of the actual protesters falling action now
And that's not really as fun for him it's not as profitable right
I think you can see the little bit of a transition over to Ukraine narratives the Convoy is no longer the most important
Take On The World
And probably still the most important person in the world
Power ranking
Is the same unless updated you would probably tell us
Baby Pulaski is the most important person in the world map
Tucker still
I know I know he's more of a future pics
So we've got to look at some other information coming out of Canada
Beliefs of the volunteered for this
Wearing balaclava black
Jordan police are resigning or saying no
They
I'll join the protest
This is fun but it's true
But wouldn't that work that is the most enjoyable moment for you though if
If the tow truck Skies
Join the protests are like haha that's backfired on you you idiots that's enough that's from a movie
That's what you want just lying about the Ottawa chief of police resigning
That's what he saw police resigning or whatever
Peter slowly resign not because he was so offended by the idea of arresting these protesters with because he was catching
Very severe criticism
For letting the situation deteriorated
To the point that it
Yeah yeah
Special units of police were brought in wearing black
Ski masks
The tons of police are resigning
He built on the foundation of
Of the police chief
Resignation
As for the tow truck drivers thing that's just made up to
You can find video of police Towing the trucks out and there are tow truck drivers
Forming a mutineer everything
Inside of a movie but it's
It's not real I am Spartacus
I am truck driver
So Newsweek had my interview with the
Video of a lion's Towing Ibrahim Nasir who said that he
But was very clear that is
Not be interpreted
To be for or against
The truckers protest
His concern seemed to mostly be a logistical one
My employees are not trained to work in that kind of an entire
The liability issues associated with that situation
They're just two Gray
Newsweek reached out to a bunch of
More companies and they all had no
Global News spoke to Mark Graves the president of the provincial Towing Association of Ontario said
The water they're sticking points was that the
Government
Give to first show it will protect
The industry from threats to safety and busy
It seems like many of the companies working
Concerned about possible retaliation from Convoy protesters if we were to participate in the removal
The trucks
What are the safety issues involved definitely forecast of snow that is a piece of it
But the other issue was A&P towing companies had been receiving death
The president of the Towing and Recovery Association of Alberta told Global News quote
I can confirm that
Three of our members had received threatening
Phone calls
What company was threatened
Just because their trucks were seen near the blockade
Couch
So as it relates to the tow truck companies
What's their joining in with the protesters as it is the fear of terrorist threats
The protesters are make
Trucks with their company identifier
Participated in Telugu
Top that's what I'm
Did not
For my Mutiny and join in with the police against the police
Want to be on record before going to tow these trucks that I am against
The Convoy
Exactly wouldn't want the right wing
Reading I would want Alex Jones reading my tow trucking companies name out on the air all the time
No that's obviously
The concern is retaliation in the safety of people
The other 12 is that
If your run
Company you will inevitably probably work with
Trucking companies
Some relation
It wasn't one of these articles even
A concern about
Even though it's a
A small amount of the
Total number of truckers in Canada
People can
Destroy your business on social media
Yeah like
Be a sex like
With that right
I guess partially it's
Again just
Out of fear of reprisal
Right right right I I like
I like that America has learned one thing
From our war on terror
Starting a war against
Terror does not work
Being a terrorist
Works eggs
Usually large number of times that they in a row
It doesn't get you the girl you want but it
It gets a gold gets it gets
Bing
It gets stung
Done
So Alex gets back to talk about Ukraine
And
Find this to be strange he seems to be
Promote this idea that
Like a man
Tried to be cool about this
Russia
Pat tried to not escalate
Couldn't have tried to play things down
What
I had just come out and said what we already know
There's a massive Western offensive
Attacking
Russian Hill area
Genocide
Take me to
No one says
Provocation
Dual
What's the weather in Childress throats
Cross the river
And I just worked
Lost a war
What happened
Attacked
Many people chosen this route
The children's throats
That will be too much
I'm actually kind of
That's f***** up
That's the second time in this episode that Alex
Is brought up the movie The Last duel so I think we know what he was doing Thursday night
What's up
Paprika movie
Getting this information from but I do not think it's accurate
What is worth much like posturing with nuclear weapons
Making accusations about genocide
Can system strategies when it comes to navigating
In the lead-up to hostilities
I don't
These kind of
Allegation
Sirius and
Be thrown around and want to minimize them
But
This is something that he doesn't.
He recently claimed it was going on in dunbar's looked a lot like the genocide of Rock
In 2014 for your antics and Crimea he said that Russians were being the subject of ethnic cleansing
In 22008 Medvedev was president
He to claim the Russians were being a chemically cleanse
In Georgia prior to launching a war against
What are the key justifications of Putin and the Russian government gives for taking hostile action against neighboring states
Is it an obligation to protect Russians who live there we're under attack
The evidence that they are specifically Undertaker's never really provided and then
To protect Russians
The region
In reality it's actually Russia who generally is engaged in these acts
Sabathani cleansing
In 2008 they rounded up Georgians in South ossetia and tortured them killed them and burned their home
The annexation of Crimea Russia is targeted Crimean tatars and attempted to reduce their numbers
In the country
Honestly this is a sick s***
Alex is so blinded by his own imaginary fight against
Buying into war propaganda put up a really dangerous power
Just because he's decided to believe that they oppose the imaginary enemies
But he has to
And not only that he uses pretend X
Geopolitics to convince his audience that they should support this stuff too
Let's grow sets
Like I said this is really like
The topic is
Very serious
And I almost could not be more C
No I mean
Radio host
Claiming somebody is committing a genocide
Recent historically has gotten a lot of people
Like this is
This is the type of
You see this
You see all the time just like hey look I don't know man
They're committing genocide I guess Russia's the hero on this one just like let's
It's it's a laziness to on Alex's part
To not recognize
The historical trends
At least over the last
20 years
15 years of
These lead UPS
To attempt
Invade areas and neighboring countries
Have
What preceded them has been largely
Surrounding new clear
Weapons
And then accusations that Russians are being
What ethnic Lee climb
Then this area
8 something
That Alex
Has every reason to understand
Is part of a pattern
He just buys
Whatever Rodger says because he believes them to be
The enemy of his enemy
You months ago
12 for the past several years Putin has been like hey if NATO expands
I'm going to be very aggressive
And then NATO's expanding or is it sits
Appearing to and he's being very aggressive
Now
To believe however somehow that in the intervening short stretch of time Ukraine was like
Now's our chance
Get these 10 guys
That would be a little bit
It would be it would be
Yeah it if you have to kind of even see
Potential
Strategic reasons
Spore
You know invading areas like a dumb boss
Them as
Russian held territory against separatist
Russian back groups
In that because
That is a check
Ukraine joining NATO
Has been pointed out by
More less
Alex has fallen for some s*** here is all above board in terms of their actions
And in the circumstances
Has fallen for some dumb s***
I mean it's just on added level of like
The f*****-up
Instigators are all around and I don't understand any of
But I do understand that it's
Pretty clear Putin's goal is to keep NATO away
Who is the only person trying to win nothing
Everybody else right now is trying to
Keep him from quitting that thing
But since it seems like a very simple game
Doesn't seem like there is a Winning State
Really call back for another few years until
That seems like that could be the case
Cities base
Geopolitical issues Visa Ozzy Ukraine and Canada
Alex is Revelations of his own past
I remember
Reading
Society
Going
Clothing
Zbigniew Brzezinski
Puppy Bowl
People like Cecil Rhodes
They indeed said they would do these
This
Is important
Because it has to be believed here then essentially all of his conspiracy theories and all of his supposed knowledge of the world is rooted in the
A society
You rather stupid magazine and then pretended to go read the books they were siding
I can guarantee 100% he never read those
He has absolutely no ability to discuss what they're about Beyond prepackaged talking points that probably came from the John Birch
Materials that tell you learned about the books from in the first place
That's all he knows about these books
Well there's no way that the John Birch Society is going to tell you about these books without severely coloring your a
Fraction of what they are going
Going to be before
That is true
Simply put
There's an argument to be made that Alex's entire career has been one long occasionally entertaining charade wear a diaper
Pretends to know stuff but really
He's just yelling about stuff you read in his dad's red-baiting magazine
Honestly this makes sense and it's what we've kind of
Suspected
Known
Painfully written in a deeply bigoted extreme right-wing publication
Alex is probably reading it on a regular basis at a time before his brain mature tube
Read them over some of the article titles from their issues from like 1994 basically read like a call sheet for all of Alex's early now
Narratives are some titles
Pushing for a world currency
Gun grabbers Global Gestapo
Bono Purple Penguin
1995 the article obsessed with OKC conspiracy theories
Play Issues the b******* kind of stuff that Alex sites all the time
They had an issue that was so virulently anti-gay including an article titled quote
6 great immigrants
Wow
That's,
That is somebody should have just been like guys
Let's just
With this is even worse
We know what we're doing being like yeah guess what we're evil
That boy
Understand to the society and their Publications
Venus conspiracy
They treated the push to end apartheid in South Africa and Rhodesia is communist conspiracy
They treat any instance of people who aren't white men demanding rights
As a communist
Conspiracy
And this is the intellectual tradition that Alex filters the world through
It's not racism it's just they don't like communism
Absolute loser
This is where it all started for him
John birdshit
It does it seems weird to me
That you can just get away with the same
Way of
Pretending not to be racist
For so long
You know like The Birches have been around being racist
Since people were allowed to just throw the n-word around 4
But I know
Because they were so
Reviled and no one like them that they disappeared for a long
Stretch
And people forgot that there
F****** idiots
Alright
Brutal brutal
So
Alex
Life is so stupid
George Orwell
Interesting
Interesting start
Real
Waze and how they plan to only hurt
Interesting start
Dominus of the Spanish Civil War
20 years of working with the comments to the highest levels
Intelligence
Uninstalling
Before WWII
Oh
Long-term plan
Call Schwalbe distillate
Frontman of
No scrub
Twin story about George Orwell but that Alex is making that s*** up
Also the Davis Group isn't the thing and class Schwab didn't just get made ahead of it
Davos is the name of the meeting of the world economic forum
Founded in 1971
Started it
Alex has just recently learned about him named Alex
Learned his name recently need a name whenever he was founding it
But now that they
They've been found
They got a name
Alex's yelled about the Davos group for
F****** ever and never appeared on his website until
Very recently
You never would talk
It's not a name of any of his villains
No such b*******
We've traveled through twenty-odd years of his past
At this point and I have yet to hear him say close Schwab is also the originator behind all of this neck
Text Bill Gates in
The world economic forum
No real
Interest in the who the people in it are specific about stuff
It's not really all that effective and people kind of geek
Confused and lost in the details but if you say something
Like Davos group your mind can go to a smoky boardroom of
Decisions
And if you name one name too many times then that person
Quit then you have 2 minutes news
They replaced
Them being
The narrative
George Orwell Story made up
Also terrible news coming out of the UK
Prince Charles
Four months ago to a worldwide war against humanity
Pretty population
Worldwide collapse
How he
Fell down
When he went up to the podium he fell
On his face
Haha
Obviously Prince Charles did not pledge himself to a war against humanity
Winifer the power of Satan helping Smite his enemies but probably not going to be king
Even if he is he won't be for long to cares
F*** around and outlive him but you know
Then again this morning
When were recording this we did learn that
The queen has covid
So kudos
Also the monarchy is mostly symbolic and ceremonial get into that one pretty hard I don't care if the
The prince says that he's going to demand a World War because again
Not actually be bad.
But like
Imagining a scenario
We're Prince Charles has called for a war against humanity
Him being king or not would have no effect on his ability to pull that off
Feel better than the British because they would have to seriously reevaluate their relationship with the monarchy
Prince Charles that much
Much lower than Elizabeth
Think that's
There was
Large
Part of the
The public will be far more interested in William
Skip
Just get rid of them
Yeah come on
See serious public pressure for him to abdicate
If if you were to assign
Even in his interest to be king for a short. Of time
Be in turmoil with people don't like him
Intuit nobody wants him to
Run the risk of losing
Which amazingly you still have
So yeah we have some more thoughts about Prince Charles here Alex's soda rambling about to how he's going to
Destroy Prince Charles in
Achoo
We were checked you
Because we hate you
We fight you because we love our children
Innocent
With God's
You will not break us
We will
Break you
Situation
With Russia
What
I'm sorry what
Hold up
So there you go they kept yelling Awards coming
Horseshit is
So this is how Alex reports the news but what actually happened is that bike came out and said that he was convinced the Putin
Decided to invade Ukraine
He never said that he was reiterating that the US was going to attack Russia and its
Almost all of this comments have been about how we're not going to do that
On Friday he even said quote make no mistake
Is Russia pursues its plans it will be responsible for a catastrophic in needless war of choice
The United States and our allies are prepared
To defend every inch of NATO territory from
Any threat to our collective security as well
We also will not send troops to fight in Ukraine
But we will continue to support the Ukrainian
He was literally saying the opposite of what Alex is reporting and to just said that he would impose sanctions
Russia decided to invade
The reason that there is a disconnect here is likely because Alex is getting all of his information
Really disreputable pro-putin Outlets
But share his outlook on the
That would make
I would think that's what's going on
And I'm I'm not like
So far outside of the media sphere that I'm unconnected
But I have not heard
Anyone
Calling for asthma
The cleansing of Russia I have just not heard it from
Anyone
So there's that
There's something going on
Here and that is that
The globalist
They want Russia back
And so here's Alex talking about that
Good kind of disgusting
Lovelace of lost Russia
I want to retake
485 years ago
The children in
Puppy monkey logic
Live torture
Now they know that
Catalyst there now they Brothers
Metro Police
Another you in
You want everywhere that go rape and murder
The c-130s landed in country
Europe
They go to the hungry arms
Schwab
Acs's lower
The worms
We are
Meat on the table
Season 4 the monsters they are
Block find God again
Preferred
I will not be
Your slave I will not
Conventional
Because we want wake up
To the facts
Medaryville
He won't take the black
Realize
Finger bad
What that app
You wake up
Tell that Alex is actually using terms like blackpill on air
Yeah that's
That's
That's just
That's if that's what the
The pillows
That's part of it
Let's the big Awakening and realize
Conversely the back
F****** nihilism
It's been that has a specific meaning and
I know that is that the world is to screw to be saved or chain
And it was particularly popular among incel community
Take the black pill for them at realizing there's no chance of their circumstance
Hopeless
Which had the effect of leading some to commit
Act of mass murder
In the political context taking the black pill is a root
To domestic Terror
That's
What is being promoted
Also a lot of especially the meat on the table stuff that Alex is doing that's just in referencing
Fake documents silent weapons
For quiet Wars
It was a hoax document that Bill Cooper published and build apparel
And Alex thinks it's real
But Alex is encouraging his audience
Is a really dangerous kind of combination
Stop yeah
It's gross
People's emotional heartstrings with these planes and take your kids
Prakash Rob 22
Dassault
It's just f***** up
I mean it is
It is like
We just watch these motherfuker
Kill
Hundreds of thousands
Through
Lies b******* and inaction and
F****** exacerbating things
With the worst action that you can do
And rather than face any consequences for that
They just get to smooth ride on over into trying to get p
People killed with guns
Instead of disease
And that's just how it's allowed to have
Cool
Alex has some fake things to say about the president
Mexico
I've heard from him in a while this is such a bizarre thing for Alex to say
Mexico's got his problems but
Likes to be its own country and sovereign
The Mexican socialist president
Along with it
We don't want the great reset here we don't
We don't want to build back better
Besides that
He's not
So this is a direct contradiction
So many narratives about immigration that Alex has spread over the years
If you're one of his listeners and you
Hear that that Mexico does its own thing it isn't involved with the globalists
That should be a cold splash of water across your face that Alex is making everything off trying to work with the global
Was to take back Texas this whole time or whatever.
In the game of 2018
Also you didn't see those things on the news that I was talking to cuz it didn't happen
Mexican president Andres Manuel Lopez obrador has been vaccinated and boosted although he has
Lockdown measures taken by other countries
But you have
Cenotes being clearly excessive
FairPoint
He's also gotten covid twice so maybe some measures might be wise
I can find no evidence that he said those things about the great reset or build back better which I don't even think things that Alex
Define with this point Nancy Pelosi stop the build back better legislation from
Headed back to college
What why are they batted what are these things like what does it mean
It's it's
Whenever everybody's at all white and then they're not
What is build back better
Really weird Alex aclib strange thoughts about to the president
He's going to say something
Things about Clash Royale
And the deputy
Prime minister
In Europe is becoming a failed system
What is Pop-Pop say
We're creating a post-industrial world
We're getting rid of the social contract we're getting rid of
We are going to build
Collapsing under cloward-piven
These are freaking statements out of
Father was
The fourth-largest
Manager
What
Christina Freeman's
Father was the director
Joseph Goebbels
Multiple
Of course she works
Klaus Schwab
You can hear the way that Alex was like grasping at things trying to pull details now
When is the Deputy Prime Minister of Canada become a bit of a target for the truck Convoy supporters
Sushi is it is getting it on the act of attack
See how Alex is remembering something trying to smear Freeland but
Quite remember what
You supposed to be mad about
So freeland's father Donald Freeland was a farmer in Alberta
Beats of Rage it seems unlikely that our father would have been old enough to be gribbles
Right hand man
Are you sure I'm positive how old is
She I don't know but that doesn't match up
Her mother was named
Hell yeah.
She was born in 1946 though so I don't think she was involved
Hitler's war effort
Her father me Kayla Chung
Was the editor-in-chief of an anti-semitic publication
Tim called Krakow Avenue
That was distributed around Nazi occupied territory
So one of the things that's really interesting about this story is that it seems like he acts descendants
I've done a lot of wrestling with what this guy did
For instance Freeman's Uncle history professor John Paul hemka
Has written published articles about his father-in-law's connection with
With the paper
Freeland has even cried it is
Assisting in one of them
A person isn't inherently responsible for the things that their parents or grandparents did particularly when they make an effort to learn from
Bad history
I don't feel like the grandchildren of Nazis need to be condemned for the action
Is there grandparents unless they're Nazis
Themselves
To suggest
Freeland
I don't think
This is going to work
Yeah
A class Rob his father worked at a plant called Usher wife
AG
Which mostly made turbine
They did Supply the Nazis during the war but they weren't their top weapons
Supplier fourth top arms whatever
All those family repatriated to Switzerland during
I mean
Yeah if you're is it at mean it's like
What are we going to be mad at like Volkswagen or something for helping the Nazis maybe the business itself with someone
I would wonder about the level of their culpability
Fled the country
During the war
Cuz they possibly they have less culpability Alex is trying to acai
For sure
Yeah it is it would be an interesting like
It like
Down the line employees
I'm not saying this is a good idea but like
1938 Ford and 1938 Volkswagen who's more anti-semetic you know what I'm saying
I'm like that's a good question
Sure it's not a good question it's a bad question but it's men
Legacy of the cereal about it
Game to exaggerate all this stuff and grasp
Put straws to attack you
Supposed
He's only doing that because the alternative is working hard
Do that
He's going to Lazy rude and he can't even get the details of the lazy route right
He's talkin about Freeland
Has grandfather got those
Words can't even remember the details of
What each one did
It's on it's worth
So weird
It's so weird because if I knew that my words and actions and deeds could
Potentially get somebody
I would be far more specific
Responsibility to I would like to know details before I just said hey
To all of my millions of murder targets
What is 1 when you're talking about stuff like these I do believe
That you have a higher level of responsibility than
Someone talking s***
Alex's
Demonstrated pretty clearly that
Keys on Russia's iodine no matter what they do is there in the right
Visa Vie Ukraine on the Dunbar
To the point of
Claiming a fictitious genocide
In 2014 he was on board with
Their annexation of Crimea
Perfectly similar reason
Browse this this was trouble
So now we know it's a western offensive in the Ukraine
Trying to elicit a response
Georgia
That seems to be a little bit
Weird
I mean
That's not good
Yeah it's it seems to be just like a really consistent thing he's just
Like if you think that Russia was the good guys
In 2008
Yeah that you're gone
I'll be missing so weird to meet like I can understand people taking the the anti-nato side
I'd have liked or you guys shouldn't have said in the 90s or whatever you're not going to try and expand and then
Now Ukraine starting to talk and then I get why Russia is it because Russia has to have a response I can't just have no root
Otherwise they basically seating any kind of power in the global stage whatsoever
But you can't be like
Russia's telling the truth
No
No no no no no nothing nothing
And Western aggression force them
Go to Warriors Georgia
It's the little we can do a lot of s*** but that is too far it's a little much yeah
So Alex pawlowski
Come on the show and talk about how
View
This this this this truck my ears is weird
And it's just amazing under the civil emergency to hold your father
Until March 11th
Without bail without bond
Perfect Crime
Godfather conscience
Black people
Say no to being told that it's in the back of the bus
Restaurant Norfolk
Window in
Get it out
I know you can't come on the bus
.
Black folks around the us at see that
There's a Man Group
Refusing to take
You can handle a four-way all the
Solve this by reminding Alex that his intellectual tradition that he belongs to and all of his Heroes were the ones fighting super aggressive
Allow businesses
Get food from those back windows
But he still forced he still fighting hard to get Banks to be fine not giving black people own
What is
Superheroes in the John Birch Society and people like Gary Allan wrote and pamphlets about how the sit-ins at lunch
Doubters where nefarious communist conspiracy
Let's overthrow the country's the fuk down with his lionizing
Civil Rights Movement
If you been around back then he would have been bull horning City into another funded by
The Rothschilds are some
All the larger level the situation with vaccinated as literally no similarity to the treatment of black people in America
The suggestion is offensive on its face
His brain and his desire to aggrandize his own imagine suffering
12 minimizing the legitimate struggle faced by people who died
Don't look like
I would encourage him to provide literally any examples of people who been arrested for not getting vaccinated and then after that he condemned
Majority of them are black
As far as I know and can tell no one has been arrested for not getting vaccinated
Some people have been arrested for refusing to
Places that require vaccinations after they've been asked to leave but
How it should be in favor of that since
Those businesses and their owners should have the right of free association
Deserve whatever customers they want
Your call Alex was super in favor of that Bakery not making
Can a gay couple of wedding cake
You've also been arrested for having Thor Distributing
Fake vaccination cards which is just
Forgery of official document
Call what fraud the crime now are we just going to say that I guess it is
But now we're going to cry
And this is actually one of the ways I think I think you can see here that Alex waste everyone's f****** time
Because he's making these declarative statements
People are getting arrested for not getting vaccinated a majority of them are black
You go and find
At the wild goose chase that you aren't going end up going on if you are expected to
Assess
The information that Alex is providing right and it's
The Trap
The time-wasting Trap and he does potentially
I'm not letting at least of which that you're not just going to blanket search
Vax unrecognized people arrested you're going to search for like
Black unvaccinated people arrested he's he's narrowed the search down so you won't even try and look for a broader
People who are arrested for not giving cash
Not
Yes no
So we're one more clip from Pulaski's son
Happened to the notion innocent until proven guilty
What happened to Dupree
Or something
He's not been convicted of
And don't let him out on bail that's that's martial law
Yeah exactly
No now so the courts in Canada are not presuming pawlowski guilty of the offense that he was arrested for
They used to pass pattern of behavior to decide that he was a person with a high likelihood
The certainty of reoffending If released that's not
That's not presuming him guilty
Forgot
Innocent
Being a consistent nuisance
To society
Until he was then convicted guilty of being a
To society and then later on whenever you get caught up again
They're like you're a consistent Newsome
We already proved it Nobel
And he's also getting his due process rights
It's like he has News full trial yet but they didn't just say no bail for you and slam the door in his face
Hearing
Don said the total b******* and saying any idea what martial law actually means
1 + 4 what about that I mean
Me I get the feeling that Alex's understanding of what martial law is coming
Mostly from like dystopian movies
The last duel
As I passed martial law
Not a dystopian movie it's a Ridley Scott his
History movie about two nights
It's dystopian inasmuch as
It's like we're both in it
Is it good
I know that cuz it looked at the Wikipedia page earlier I will be honest like most Ridley Scott historical Epic
Very long bike alien no like a kingdom of heaven
Kingdom of heaven and a half hours
Stillgoode
Actually really liked it but too long
I'm happy for you
We all like what we like
Something I don't like
Like the last duel sure I guess we'll have I have one I have I don't like that movie
I don't like is Alex's next Gaston without a hole
Only reason we're still alive on air and only reason we are millions and millions of them
Tropical watch Justin am and FM station
It's because of you
What am I told you
World governments making its move
Strengths about a weakness
Now that the
Thermonuclear war
Two Minutes to Midnight
The most prolific individual D Trailblazer
The most accurate person
Really see the
Stickers everywhere
Jones was right well
David
What's right first
The term deposits
Weather for the next day
That's honestly degrading for Alex do we sing
Complete loser putting himself second to David Icke of all peoples
I get the sense that Alex is doing this in order to
Create the false appearance that he and David Icke were on the same page early on
But that kind of winds a bit of
False credibility to the idea that they were both predicting what is happening in the world today you want a unified front or at Leon
That's absolutely not true and I even a little bit of time engaging with their material knows that
You know the thing that's absolutely pathetic about this is that
Very clear
Power imbalance that is totally clear but
Entirely unspoken
PeopleLink existir the guy who hasn't changed his core branding
The same isn't true for Alex
David Icke early in his
His career
Pretty much all of Ike's worldview in order to keep up with the rapidly escalating insanity
Findlay conspiracy community
Do you like was he turd in the punch bowl with his interdimensional lizard being
Things back in the day
To the real s*** talking about the
Banks of the UN
Alex is always know better than David Icke it's just now realizes he's not capable of maintaining a brand
Pretend that he is
Pictures of crazy as he's ever been
His brain isn't
Entirely able to take or leave Alex
He won
Hanesbrands is f****** impenetrable at this point
He's made enough of a cottage industry for himself a really really need anybody else he can help us out loud weird speaking
Can you date Alexa
Sell books
He's a little bit like a passive cult leader like he doesn't have to have those like
He doesn't tell you to go get him s*** all the time but
You'll just show up and people be like oh my God you're amazing
She made a name for himself
Bank
Completely crazy at a time when there were enough
Public crazy figures
He was early in on the game he's a grandfather yet
Famous person prior to that like
Went he went on TV and said he was the son of God
Like it was
Ridiculously
Huge
Coming from that kind of an inciting incident
Into this career in like
Lizards Walk Among Us
Like
There's a built-in thing that will allow you to have like
F*** off
Kind of money in your branch
You know he has he has his own thing and
Alex's Alex's so pathetic that you just have to be
He can't stick to his guns now because there's no money
And being like
Haha yeah
Everyone else
Is getting sucked into qanon stuff
Everyone else is getting sucked into these inter-dimensional demons and what-have-you in
I want to hold the line and tell you about how great Rand Paul's physical
Ideas are you know what we need to reduce foreign aid while we're on the subject let's get rid of
Let's let's
The FED will get people excited
Don't be lizards
So that Alex has had to
Completely sacrifice whatever are of
Like I'm better than that he want
That there that's a sort of facade
And what's left is David Icke laughing
Except he's not
Cuz I don't think they would I give
Yeah I don't know what
I don't know what
Drives that guy
That's it that's
That's something I don't want to
I think it's actually he's mentally unwell
Is that can't just be it people wouldn't
Engage in a decades-long labeling of
Oh wait no yeah they would
I don't know exactly what it is but there's something
I think
80s prom
Also is Alix lynx
Unfortunately that's basically him saying that he believes the protocols of the Elders of Zion are real because David Icke has
Push that quite a bit
So congratulations Alex
Anyway
He's into these trackers
He likes that he likes the Canadian protest
Is 2
Purchase the biggest Reservoir
The threat of a good example
If
You
Do what they done
Canadian
Pressure and oldest
They say okay well
Massive state
Show the rest of the world
People have the power
This isn't the legitimate powers of people situation
Prove that a relatively small number of people who act
Strategically can on
Unsuccessfully attempt to force their will on a much larger population who doesn't support them
If they're willing to take
Extreme Measures
Outcome of it will be annoying a ton of people and wasting everyone's time for a while
Prove the efficacy of
Terrorism
So congratulations on that
I guess
Great that's not power the people that's the opposite want to
Terrorize people
Into giving up on what they believe is right
Andover throwing this is their of their elected leader because
Right
These people are stupid
Anyway they want
It is so funny to me that the people who
Screamed at me after 9/11 about how patriotism is so important
Are f****** terrorist now
Well
To be fair
Astra Alex would not have been yelling at my patriotism in the aftermath of 9/11
Other people
Probably
These days
Alex David Icke
They I think are invested in
Trying to read
The situation in Canada
What happens if
Millions of Canadians images
Marched peacefully now
Would that finally break the will of the steering is that the answer
That's why
You know
People in Canada robot looking from the sidelines
Buffy you doing
What's your say is not just your future
Disappearing into a fascist tyranny
Silence and David want tons of people to show up and represent the solution to world
They're disappointed that the protests are getting cleared without any real major incident happening that they can profit from exploding
Alex didn't get that false flag car bomb that he was hoping for so
He's home to try to do the best you can with
Another completely false
Pretty underwhelming narrative about organizers getting arrested without charges
That's not exciting and also if anyone takes the time to look into it they just see that
Just making it up
The answer to this propaganda narrative dead-end that they're facing is the prospect of adding more fuel to the
The fire in the form of
Tons of people showing up energized
I'm convinced that
Stopping the clearing to the protest is the solution to
World tyranny being established
High probability of causing some kind of a flare-up which is what these dudes want
This isn't going to happen because I doubt there are millions of people in Canada
Support the protest
Apple came out on the 14th showing at 72% of Canadians wanted
The protesters to quote
Go home now
44% of the said the protests inclined to support measures like indoor masking
And showing proof of vaccinations at the Canada u.s. border so
Substance you could look at the protesters being counterproductive
Maybe they backfired
I don't know
And it certainly didn't achieve whatever goals they wanted to enlist
The goals were
Enrichment of some really shity grifters
The ton of attention for some
Some shady folks
Yeah I mean I think we're missing out on another huge
Which crucial ask
Aspect of this is that
This is all happening where it
Can't really affect Alex or David at all
So they get to
The pride and power of saying
You guys go shut down this whole place with knowing
Expect nothing bad will happen to them
Probably not
I mean the only real possibility
Is if those blockades wife
Rested long enough
Have a severe impact
On goods and services flow
Did the tractor supply chain in some way
If it ended up reaching the situation where
The
This artist migrated to the United States
Right and
Going to major thoroughfares in
Primetime trade route
Square block
You could see Alex getting affected but I don't think even he thinks
Said it would ever get to that point
I mean I think the queen will have to of course just take
Canada back
That'll be the first thing
The illusion
That she's not in charge
Let you know
I mean if they want to get rid of Trudeau there's only one way to do it
Not give it back to the queen
Well see but that's why Trudeau gave the queen covid
Trudeau you clever bastard I've read your book
Always one step ahead
Trudeau
So I just want to try and scare people until like you need to go and
Stop the
Stopping over primary
What we are on
Looking at now it's decision time
You know all we going to
Capitulate
Location
Ongoing future
Emoji
Which what you're saying on the screen
Is the norm
A Line in the Sand
Because
So many times
What is coming what is plan
East Falls
Extreme
In terms of the consequences of standing up now
When people say
Oh yeah but what are the consequences for me of doing this
I can tell you the consequences of not doing it
Enormously greater
Psych
I guess you should at all costs
Penzeys fruit
I mean yeah you have to be willing to give up your life
At the border of Canada and
America
And Ottawa
To get people to stop
To get
To get the thing that they want witches
To really achieve that
So he's speaking pretty passionately about how like it's nightmarish whatever is going to happen is is so much worse
Worse than you could possibly even imagine
This happens is really really funny
Why are you crying why are you crying
Well
Would you like me to write alright crazy like okay thanks for that
That's so great
Alex trying to like really like I asked
You crying what's going on here
I'll cry
Thought about you idiot for free
One of my favorite genres of Alex question
Question
To subtly and play Alex
Along the way
It's just gorgeous
What is it like
For you
Tell me what about the world what's happening currently produced you
As such an iconic person
Super iconic who is out there
Globalist
Preeminence
Can't believe it
But what is it like
Years or so you bump
Thirtysomething
Play David David
We're both you
We're both so big I love you but mimos
I like meat
And I'm bigger than you I'm just saying that the two names
Are you and me
And me as first rarefied air
With me in this rarefied air of you and me
I do love that but that's a lot of fun
That's so annoying
So you like
Just talking about Satan a Feeling
About Satan
Being fear
This Consciousness this would Tycho this
Satan
Because it's fear
Feed store
Sphere
Ice always has to
Interstates
Getting the fear
What we need to do
Easter Easter rise above that
Allowed
Ciara
To impose itself upon us
That's so dumb
The only thing we have to fear
Is the devil
And what we know about fear
The mind-killer goddamnit
Come on man I'm sorry I wasn't ready for a dune ref
Mine always be prepared
I think that's stupid
I think it's
Sweethearts built on do you like better octave
Something that is
Obviously a right but
The true point which is
Interferes
Not really a product
Good State of Mind
Need to be on right
And you know
Combat fears is always
Usually a positive exercise
That's sad
I'm in Canada and situation in Ukraine
Arnot
Just to make
David Icke scare
There that's not what this is about sure
There are other things going on that are real important
Yeah
Like
Important than whether or not David Icke is afraid
Wow that must be pretty serious
I understand this
Impulse on the part of conspiracy theorist
We are just trying to make you scared in order to keep you control then what have you
Lupine
But also the things that are happening in the world are real
I am
Good deal with that seems escapists
Boston Subway
Flip it around if this is like you know the global is Sturgis
Trying to make you scared about the situation
What are you doing
But you're also trying to make your audience scared
Well if I'm shaking a they better be
Global strategy or whatever is the game control by
Spreading fear
For that great to keep
Control if you're riding
Do I need to control my audience
Beer
I'm starting to see why you think that this is bad
Go for it
Okay
I'm scary David Icke
Is a prop
That hurts
Yeah
What comes next
Well
I have this phrase
Know the outcome
Crepe erase
Global control
Connection of human
It's not going away
Is
Oops David I just gave up the game
Wow imagine and state that he sees things going towards
Plan is to take everything that happens in the world and find ways to explain every event is being part of the planet
Advancing towards
That and State
Pretty smart in terms of how to be a really lazy profit because he
Committing to any specific things happening
Unless you're not really ever at risk people saying you're wrong unless you're in state fails to ever come into being
You can always say that the villains are still working towards that end State and their plans are behind maybe like 10 years behind
As we've heard Alexei so much
The best way to get a good profit
Is he out there is to die before it
It's fruition you're like nobody's going to be like
Dude
F****** John
There were only
5 seals you said they're going to be seven you dick
If you bought in today would like s*** you might
Hear what he saying as a reasonable response but to me that sounds like a clear admission to David Icke
Just make stuff up as he's going along
He sees world events and incorporates them into the larger narrative that he has about the world fudging details if he has to
Oversimplifying things when necessary and then just outright ignoring tons of stuff that he can't make fit the mold
The only real question
Search for me is whether he's aware of what he's doing and he's like
Conscious conman in this
Murphy's just mentally unwell to the point where this is an unconscious process and how he
Actually experiences the world
I'm not sure but I think
Really really telling
Like what's next
Let me tell you
I know the endpoint and I will
Figure it out along the way
That's not
That's like
That's aspirational prophecy
Like I know where the end is going
So
What are you talkin about if you know where the end is going method of Storytelling
Hey look you know what the
Conclusion of the story is going to be a man along the way you write how the characters get to that point
That's the problem that's too transparently what's going on
No
A back-to-front program
Whatever
I like good good stuff babe
Anyway
There's that there's a problem
With a lot of the vaccine
Conspiracies that they're going right is that they're not killing everybody
That is a big issue with the
When did supposed to kill everybody
Yeah so David thankfully has a workaround
What do you from your research No Agenda vaccine so-called
Doing it in a way
X2
Keep the levels of people
Dying suddenly in these earlier
In this area.
211 catastrophic is it is
Keep some kind of lit on it
Enormous numbers of these files
All right really just say line solution
Most of the facts
Mario
Such a b*******
F*** you. That's the way I know but there's no number
That idea of like
Well it's still catastrophic but this is
Dare you tell me
That there's a balance between catastrophic and reasonable
The point is well-taken but you also got to take a look back
And the listen to that last clip
And recognize what he's doing
He has the endpoint
But he's rich
And that is what the vaccines are going to kill everybody
And now there are events that are happening in he's had to write little detailed plans because it didn't kill every
Buddy quick enough
There or their new details that he needs to incorporate like to rewrite
Solution for most of the vaccines which is the explanation for why
It's not killing everybody in the way that
Of course I have already said my endpoint
Sure
So the endpoint
Is actually correct but most people aren't actually kidding tabaxi
Therefore I am right about an end point where you don't know how we get there
Is that you can always move that in point wherever you wanted to go or you can create a loose like
Illusions of definitions
Absolutely you can read to find things
Sunway Alex remembers
I think most vaccines are fake too
Nice
Credit I remember you
Most of this is sailing they're only targeting old people in military
And then now they had major top
Just go off the government's own data
And show that they're actually targeting conservative nationalist
When the poison shots actually were able to map it out
Gregory said a report on what you said
A long time ago
What's up Gregory's video when they put it out last month and honestly it was so dumb that I didn't even take the time to
Engage with it
I just know that I was bringing it up to the fence of dumb s*** that at that David I can say
I'll talk about it a little
January video titled
U.s. government targeted
States with deadly batches effects
This report was based on a website that a guy named
Cooper through together called how bad is my back
It's like reports
Michelle how many deaths
Some side effects are associated with
Each batch
The vaccine listed by badge number
Information was then taken and interpreted to show that to the most deadly inside
This data is all entirely told from
Not even confirmed these Adverse Events happened
The data isn't meant to be used that way so right off the bat you can't reach any of the
The conclusions that Gregory's video does
From this data set
Already it is stupid
But
Make it even more idiotic when you realize what Vera's data is
It's self-reporting of side effects that may or may not be real
All this data would actually be showing is that in red States
There are a higher incidence of self-reporting of side effects that may or may not be real
And if they are real may or may not be related to the vaccine at all
That kind of makes sense to me giving her largely empty Baxley conservative community
Becoming the last few years
I can see them having a greater tendency to over report possible side effects
Or for some people to actually be inclined to file. Reports
Used by someone like part of Cooper and then Greg reason then Alex
Some David Icke to argue the facts
Seems our deadly enemy exotic conservative areas while the rest of the world in the country gets placebos
And this is a rebuttal that even just takes for granted the data part of Cooper extracted from bears being
Accurate and it's presentation
I just decided
Stipulate that it is because I don't care whether it's accurate or not it actually makes no difference
In terms of the conclusion
Like it's it's
Ridiculous
It's a ridiculous thing that has
Potential other explanation even if was being presented as data is act
I'm starting to feel like our show is like
Black Mirror version of
Schoolhouse Rock
Like when you when you hear that song about how I'm just
Isabel ciego from nothing until
And you're like I feel like I've learned something about
Process here
Learning about the process of b******* is really what's going on
But that was only because terrorists asked me not to
This is a truly insane website
Complete with suggestions of how to cure yourself of the vaccine is able to use at the bushes dump
Conspiracies
Cherokee Elementary this is the laundering process
Are we go Schoolhouse Rock theme song
This is just a misuse of various data at its core
It's meaningless on its own but it gets misrepresented and misinterpreted on this website and it starts to take a little bit of a she
Whose website is still
Pretty inaccessible to most people
If you're not already on board.
You're going to see that you're not going to be swayed
Alright whatever
Tell Greg Reece comes in he makes
Flick video packaging the claims of this website in a form that has the ability to scare people
This videos also something that Alex can use because
The site itself is too far was for Alex to really get a grasp on there's no hold
For him to grab onto
He needs concise talking points as opposed to a sprawling website full of insane.
Reese's video provides him with those talk
He can go forward
From there
Also
Be clear
What day is 8 months ago wasn't that the vaccine wasn't real
He was saying that covid didn't exist
There was no virus
And maybe
Viruses don't exist
That was his take back that but I guess I was just want to get into that
Let's get to choose between a
Agree with that
Or bring up something that David Icke said that looks really f******
So I think you can see uvuvu
Assertive
I don't know
Channel
You still alive
The chain of evidence
We see the way that it's chiseled into something that
Canby
Usable
Yeah I know I did have its core what it is is
Still the same s*** it's just
Bears data
Being dressed up in a certain way
It's like a it's like a manufacturer
Process it's it's literally like we've got this raw material that then gets refined and unrefined and refined refined until
Do you have the diamond of b******* that Alex
My only
My only clarification I would make
Is that like
Are you looking to manufacturing process
Usually the repeat of
The same thing over and over again
Whereas in order
To make this
Usable
Propagandist usually after
Process each side
But you need to make it look different each time
Yes but that's
That's true.
We won last year and it's Alex wax
Sing poetic
But how
David
David Icke
We may never speak again
It is
Parting is such sweet sorrow this could be the last time you and I ever
Marc Broussard
Let me last time wherever on air
Today next week
Xbox in
That area where that house
Let my enemies have the enjoyment here about what
You going through some summer thing just
The attacks of
Much more
Barely on air ride
He's got cancer he said he's dead
Deal about it it's just suddenly they're gone
I love the idea that Alex is comparing himself like a family member has cancer was just on one day
Yelling about how his show could be everyone to be in last year
Yeah he's like a family member who yells at you
Constantly about Heather about to die then tries to sell you something you don't need in order to keep them alive and also
Turns out there life-threatening condition that they have
Is a cut that gave themselves will trying to stab a random person on the street
Not really.
They keep trying to sell you things to keep alive its
I'm in Noble
A person who doesn't want to burden people with my illness or whatever that that's what he's trying to Metaphor camps private Wars as
F*** are you type of person who's just there and then gone you know it doesn't make a fuss
Out of the out of like what what are you going to be my aunt died of colon cancer
You know I'm sure he would never would have complained about the
The pain she was
She was a
Hard strong woman
And I'm sure Alex is
Just like her
Such so simile
I'm out of here f*** you I want to go to the woods
Christ
You're just a child who doesn't want to take responsibility for his actions
How is that a thing that you can be at 40
Actual child who just
We have bases
Essentially all of his worldview on dumb s*** that he read when he was younger and
Hasn't updated really any of it
Do an improvised storytelling to create a worldview in
Conspiracies along the way
Who f****** nonsense
It is Aries like
Whatever this stuff happens it is a little bit like
When I was younger I love reading books when I was a kid I read read these books and there was always that line
Find that like
Everything you think you know
Is not how it
Right out and I was always
Excited by that cuz it meant that the mundane boring aspect
Facts of Life
To be transformed into
This show is like that it's like everything you thought about how the world works
It doesn't work
And I'm not excited because it's so much dumb
Then I could ever possibly thought
Level of intelligence
Required to run a school
Just on a phone
Actual level is a principal
Is far beyond anything that these people have ever consider
And there's a president of the United States or whatever the f*** it you know like everywhere we go
They're the people who actually run s*** and it's
Insane but I think
I think
Not to defend
The president of the United States let's say
But I think you're not taking into account
The
Complication
Cans of that job
20 got a bunch of other people to do inform the people are crazy
Vice-principal
Thinking more like
Yes
Alex is very
Stupid
And it is it is remarkable
It really is
But that's really goes to show
How much
A b Attalla
And
Rampant narcissism
Check and unending confidence
How much over the course of decades
Expertise
Intelligence
The facade that
Hi
And yelling a bunch
People are afraid to confront you about that
Yeah but you got to be real stupid to believe
Putin on the
Just this once
Too bad it's too dumb you got to be real dumb for this one no benefit of the doubt
No no like hey
We've all made mistakes before
No
Russia
This is that you can't do that
Just not this one
It's it seems like a tough
22 except
Unless that's been what you've been doing for your entire career
Talk to change now
So anyway Jordan will be back
Little breakey
Probably on Wednesday
Free website
We do acknowledge fight.com
World's on Twitter
Text clark.com marbles
What the sex robot
Alex
Christian color with huge fan I love your work