Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge by now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
We are the bad guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones
We are
Question
Far and Away without a doubt is a little package that we got from
I don't know
She's got to come up with her own title policy wonk whatever Katie
Board game incredible pool of inside solutely incredible sort of a take on
Monopoly rules
Are we going to play it yet excited beyond all reason to play it
Just instead of the properties there are people who have like Leo zagami you have multiple
All versions of Alex
There's a incorporation of Project Camelot stuff into it
Don't think I'm doing a good job of describing it to cuz I'm just super
It is a well-done system of jokes
Kind of incredible
You know maybe 442 assholes like us with the with comedy brains
We can be sitting on people that is very funny
Really good I have not obviously
Like a chance to our why would I just sit and read over all of the car surprised
Play have a great day
Sense of humor
Clever and witty
Thank you so much
Justin a real
A bright spot in a date spoiler alert the Restless episode 8 going to be bright
Thank you for bringing that into our lives
My partner
She's making these shirts she's an art teacher she's good to make a church bread maker
And she's making these t-shirts for other teachers in the school
Because I don't know if you know this teachers are treated well
Sure there's a quote from this one person they were all getting together all the teachers talking about how Terrible Things Are
And this one teacher was was like
Man this thing came into my room it was not a mouse it was a whole rat
Bright
And so she made a tshirt out of this right nice drawing it's classroom it's a whole rat
People have started getting them
And she made one for me and
It's very very good
This is going to be the next piece of me I hope so
If your CPS teacher look around for it's a whole rat you'll find it's a whole rat is going to go up there without
Alex's new shirt with the president's daughter
We don't have time to get into this but I encourage anyone the picture of it Alex
New shirt that he selling what has
Faces of presidents in a bit obsessed with it
For the better part of the week I'm so confused by it in there for awhile
Problems within 2 seconds and I'm still digging it's very confusing I don't have time to get into it
But it'll be on archway
Children recently time to get into it today is that yeah there's there's major world events of foot
And
Quite frankly I had planned to do an episode of the end of this week of
Tracking Alex's Behavior over the course of the week
And then I work Thursday and last night Russia and Putin invaded Ukraine
And I have to redo every
Yeah that'll change things
It's so what we're going to be doing is we're going to have a focus on today's episode 24th
February 2022
And then we're also going to have a little bit of a Prelude little bit of a
Would it would it be
Preview prologue
It's a weird looking at February 21st
February 24th
The first Bret Stephens
Next day we're going over the episode from February 21st to 24th 2022
Thank you so much you're an alcoholic
It's 22 also sliva, Antioch
Text gay frog enthusiast
Thank you very much Jordan the Heretics of Dune called shahulud
Thank you very much for calling me the devil that person that you would get it
Why do indeed I do
Walk up in the mix
Globalistatv babies
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Miami
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
5 years
Walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I never want to come back
Apologized
To the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
He has not been better this week that's not this price not a good week
Forever World particularly for the people in Ukraine
Our thoughts are with them Force
And
Ayodhya
Very confused
Dialysis
I'll behavior and is narratives over the course of this week
I told you this before we started recording
I don't know exactly what his point is that almost anything
We can track it and hopefully make sense of it
By the time we finish up
Here is the first we're going to start on the 21st
So this is Monday show
You know these will give his speech
Where he decides to recognize the
The Breakaway states of donuts
Answer
That has not happened yet
Is just the beginning of the show
Is where Alex is at
Russia
I've already been an eight-year proxy
Obelisk
And
Blacksburg animal heavy weapons
The last few years
Accelerate under Biden
Until puttanesca
A bunch of troops on the border saying you need to not
Tomato
Top heavy weapons
We need to have
Armistice
Demilitarization
Ceasefire meeting
Under there Denese
Compact
So we can just go ahead and say right off the bat Alex is taking literally everything Putin says as gospel and
He's back in Russia 100%
Keep coming back to it as we as we go through he's a Putin spam
Being a proxy war against
The globalist
That seems like an absurd concept but it's something that I was just casually toss around like a perfectly normal idea that it's stupid
The Vic anything else could possibly be going on
Alex doesn't even have a solid consistent group of people who actually makeup
The globalists have no faith
It explained this proxy war if you were forced to
Like if I had a follow-up
Inform I don't think it would make sense that the globalists
Broadband using other people
Who are also globalists
Sure to fight against Russia it's direct than isn't it
So Russia.
Has been using
Russian no yes it does seem like proxy doesn't make sense
It's a strange idea
Something was really funny of that clip those he's not rushing for a few years now.
It started under Trump so he has to immediately qualify that
Instincts to cover his ass stuff are really strong
Considering
He's already said like that guy loves vaccines
Justin said hacking forethought
Just a just a knee-jerk like I don't know if people are going to get mad at me for criticizing him about
There's no such thing as the domestic
Compact
That's an agreement that Alex is making
I think that he's trying to remember the name of the Minsk agreement
But he came up with the wrong mental file
The Minsk Agreements are two formal attempts to stop the fighting that's gone on in the dumb Bossa region which have both been on
Successful
The first was he meant protocol in 2014 followed by mints
2 + 2050
The Goldie's agreement was to put in place a ceasefire between the Ukrainian military and the russian-backed separatist groups in Tonasket
Who have been they've decided that they are their own Breakaway States
Not apart of
Disagreement or super complicated cuz he have to look at it from
The status of the parties
From each other's viewpoint
And when you do get a sense of how this was probably do a failure
According to my
Most of the world
This was essentially an agreement between Ukraine and Russia
Separatist groups in Dawn boss wouldn't be able to continue any of their actions without rushing back
It's not really necessary to say that San Francisco tonight
Need to withdraw happy heavy weapon since without Russia they wouldn't have have you ever happened
But from Russia standpoint this is a negotiation between Ukraine and the separatist Indonesian lot
Routinely taken the position that they're just observers and that they're there to mediate the process and they don't exist as a party of the
The agreement
Who deceives himself as Unbound
From the group
Itself at least partially for this reason
At the same time Ukraine
Specifically sees this as a negotiation between themselves and Russia
Ukrainian president zelensky
No intention of talking to terrorist
And it is just impossible for me in my position
His perspective on the agreement is similar to how much of the world sees it as a conversation between Ukraine and the Russian government or Fuccillo
The action
Of the separatist groups in Don Bosco the Ukrainian government
CSN truly as an insurgent
Right right right
So you can see from the perspectives of all the table be very difficult
Navigate
Based on
Perception
This is where we get
So much of that like
Space space
International Intergalactic contract law being so important is with
These types of agreements you know you have food and being able to be like
Na na na
As it's them
What are you talkin about it's on a technicality don't have my signature
Do their writing do you eat like a f****** Capone
So there was an inherent lack of agreement in this agreement and it clients almost immediately with the accusations from both sides of the other
Decided broken the ceasefire
So I don't know what the desk compact is
Alex doesn't know anything about the Minsk agreements but is making a passing reference to a justify Russia's actions
Now because he's invested in defending everything food and does
Monday Alex's built him up as the only major geopolitical force that stands against his imaginary
Get me so whenever it looks like the rubber is going to meet the road Alex is going to be on team
And he'll use whatever flimsy grasby has on history or past
Agreements to convince his audience
But they should be too
And that's kind of sucked
He's pushing the he's pushing the car
Talk to me about what you think the globalist hierarchy is right now we know the devil fliptop
Write the devil is definitely up top
Who's his second-in-command second-in-command
Pcloud Schwab
You would think that
And then since we're dealing with
I'm going to go with soros's up there
He's got to be way up there at 2
And then I mean naturally the trilateral roll
Other power is Brian stelter so I think it's those three there's a new flowchart in town
Here's the headline
The world is now in World War 4
Global
A war against humanity
Designed Apple controlled implosion of society
Do they carry out their endgame
Other destinations are gold
Eighty-two 90% depopulation of the Earth
Official documents
90%
Going back to the 60
The CFR the trilateral commission it's all the same group
They're the
Capture
Elite caps
Sure grips
Do you know of is the day most crooked Abel's crib
Is the main PR Mouse
Lord of the Rings an hour
Don't
They're on the edge of Mordor
Blackgate
Open
Marchezais
They say are you sore on the Mouth of Sauron
Mouth of Sauron
Alright
Okay
I got one
Damn is
Or the top
Larry Fink
What
And about that of course is that
Okay okay
Who is Larry Fink Larry Fink is the head of a black rock
Oh
You also on the board of Liquor World economic Forum like a bunch of
Yeah okay cool
I don't know when he got inserted his high
You second-in-command real quick
Wow now that's wild I didn't tell you
There's a wrestling storyline where Vince McMahon was the higher power that was running Undertaker
Hood that's how I imagined Larry Fink reveal yourself to Alex alright
Larry Fink cuz I haven't listened to literally every episode of
Is not one of the villains that I had to be second-in-command
Yeah
You might have got bumped up from the middle management or Council of twelve
Impressive
Yeah good for him
Stupid killing of time here and this is something that I always find very interesting and
I don't think I'll never ever ignore when it comes up
We're going into World War 4
What is economic
The psychological
That is cyber
That is radiological
That is electromagnetic
Radiolab
Covert
Silent weapons
For quiet Wars
Weapons
For quiet Wars just look these terms up
And it's what
The globalist are obsessed with and they brag
How you're dumb animals and they brag
How they're going to annihilate you
Thank you love it
While they brainwash you using pavlovian
Behavioral psychology these are the worst
Villains the Earth
Has ever
Silent weapons for quiet Wars as we've mentioned before is a fake documentary was a hoax document that got published in
Behold a Pale Horse
Duckbill Trooper wrote we went over this ingrate
Detail on episode 381 of the podcast
So if anyone wants to know why it's really pathetic that Alex is referencing this as a real thing
I'll check that up
Episode
Name
Really is a great title
Agenda 21
If it was actually something the government had produced
You should never date you don't actually maybe
I guess the fact that you know it's b******* kind of makes you able to take it until it goes through realm of fiction
A little better it does get into like
You know you like the judge in the Blood Meridian but if the judge were actually alive you be like I got to get away from the dead
Lisa Vidal
Yeah yeah you may be right
So Alex is Cena meme
And I come to realize
Probably brought this up before
A lot of Alex's reporting is just based on me
MCC
It's really shocking
I'm particularly when we're sitting here talking about you know the
The. Where tensions are really high discussion of a potential invasion
Are going on when you're reporting
Stuff that has
To do with Ukraine
Based on a meme
That's not good
It's not great it's not good
From where they were ordering people.be lot of protests
The police there just dropped
Their Shields
Send control
And technocracy
Control
And there's not
Human
The Blazer told
What's the router piece
No we'll just drop our Shields
That's the real courage
You know that all the talking about it before they did it
Then the one guy decides
They orderly just got dropped
Nepal
No we're not going to beat
People over there ever be another piece
We're not going strong
Should see
So this is a great example of the information that Alex disseminates in like a
Be trusted even when he shows a video
You show us the video of this
He's playing this video of police dropping their Shields into a pile just describing but the
The context of the situation is completely different than what he saying
Either saw this posted as a meme somewhere with a false story attached to it he saw the video and decided to make up his own plot about
Wanted to imagine this was
This was not from covid X
It's a video from 2014 that was filmed in Slovenia
City in East Ukraine
There's been skirmishes in the city between Ukrainian government forces and the pro-russian separatists
Point of the video being shot the police have detained some of the supper
The video depicts a crowd of people threatening the police the police realizing they're outnumbered and then dropping their Shields Envy
Right that's the situation not so much
Freedom fighter truck drivers
Bach
This really interesting is how much of the story Alex is telling has to do with
His own imagination and how he's come up with.
Detailed motives
For the people in the video
He sure that they talked about how they were going to do this in advance to make a statement about covid measures
It's all just
Product of him seeing the video and then deciding how he wants to make up a story about it to sell the audio
That's his deep research
It is researching his mind
Imagining nonsense has written an entire like
High school basketball movie where they're all in the locker room getting together and there's some guy giving a big speech about how I'm going to stay
Kind of s*** yeah
It's weird it's it's
They're so real
Assertive
Herbs for the dramatic
Everything has to be movie
At the same time but that scene is itself quite dramatic that video is just not in the way Alex
She wants it to be
Well I mean
Print the legend
That's true that's what they say it is or y'all Villages Alex
About to speak sometime in the next hour
We'll see what he's going to announce
Probably that
Attacks on
Hilarious
Tropical
Or perhaps
Ukraine
They will stop shipping heavy weapons into their border
Tractors
Or that he's going to invade
It's all been done
Pressure on expansion
To get to the back
Security concerns
Globalist hate God
What
They hate Russia because Russia is now having
Just like China
So you can kind of get the sense that we're heading into this
Putin speech
Seagrave
Top-level s*** that West's the aggressors for sure
Leaving the prediction he's going to say that either
These places or make an ultimatum but it's easy
He's already appearing is audience to like except guys like this is exactly what should happen
Strange
That would be if it wasn't him it would be strange
I mean Annie strange
In the context of how the world
Should work or is supposed
But man
Just
Why is everybody doing this
I'll be on the far right
On the far right I just don't understand it is
It is bizarre
Yeah I don't know I think really don't know I think obviously one piece of it is probably just an obsession
Well strongman leader
I think that's a big part of it
Being able to protect all of your
Let's say
Culture-war obsessions on the way there
Alex
Is so defined by opposition
Is meaning
Yeah opposition to sjws or like trying to own the libs and what have you
And I think they projected bit of that on the food and him as an ally against his
Vietnamese food
I think a lot of people on the right too and I think that that
It is a piece of it
Right there's got to be more somewhere but I don't know what it is exactly ultimately the only thing that I can really
Please put my
Had around
Is just
These are people
With non-stop violent fantasies
Probably a piece of a 20 and like if
I was running a country this is how we'll go bum bum bum I would just do it like I don't
With me off my borders
Yeah it's just a fantasy
In order to
Lead up to the speech of moon was giving
I noticed
How much is doing just a lot of water carrying
For the Russian government
All of the western unconfirm reports
That the lgbtq
Are going to be putting cam
What is the low
What's the length of our you put our children in
They're not arresting
Homosexual
In
But anytime
Gets arrested
Pink sweater
Purple sweater
Someone to tell Alex that it's illegal to be gay in Russia he does realize that you will be arrested
On account of it being illegal
Everybody's going to get arrested
I've been widely reported purges and arrest people who are either gay or
Suspected
Yeah 1013 the government to build stopping quote gay propaganda
Which has been used to Target activists
Speak up for the community
The first same-sex marriage recognized in Russia between two men married in Denmark was
Weekly unrecognized
And then the men fled the country
Prepare for their life
Yeah there
Over 100 tortured in chechnya in 2017 which the Russian government doesn't even theme
Worth investigating
What Alex is saying is Bolt
And he knows it
But he also knows that he can't allow the picture he paints of food into be water of someone who's harshly
Repressing People based on sexual identity orientation
Bus Alex decides to just pretend that every instance of targeting the lgbtq activists
Is secretly them detaining a CIA agent
I mean weird
You know it's wrong
You can't not know you can't not know it's wrong
If you're also lying about it
Because even this
This is like
You're already talking to the crowd you already tossed now white nationalist slogans it clearly your audience is fully on boy
Bored with all your transphobia be gone by now if they were
Exactly so it's like just say we like Putin because he arrest
And disappears
Lgbtq members
And that's what we like
But I think that Alex
I mean it's flimsy grasp as he has over history
Though he fancies himself a scholar
I think even he knows that that was
A little bit of the early Nazi purges to celebrate the
Right
And it's like
But that's what you're doing
That's amazing
Play the game that he is doing there is because
If you was going to be honest about the gay propaganda law that Russia has passed
He would need to explain it okay for the state to curtail for
Free speech to this drastic of anak
Isn't the real serious problem but I kept her Free Speech Warrior like himself protest
Consistently Crackdown on in Russia
All the things that he thinks are essential
Elements
Of course quote Western culture are not
Carried out in and respected by Putin
Yeah
He can't
Except that or like
Sell that to the audience
So you deny it
Well I mean
Just you just create a new story
Can you how can you literally
Be one of these people
And just watch
Putin literally like the moment and anti-war protest
Chester walks out onto the Street Moscow they're f****** arrested
And think to yourself well
If that's the type of leader that I want
Because I remember and I when we were protesting the war in Iraq
Especially Alex whenever he was strongly against
I'm sure you would've been stoked to have a president up f****** arrest him immediately
It was that kind of
F***** up
Is an ability among some people to
Abstractly imagine themselves
In various positions
Within Society
I think you gained a lot of empathy for people who are living
In poverty
By being able to imagine yourself
If you've lived in it and experienced it
And you can call back some of those memories
I think that Alex sees himself
As
The person who
Doing beef
Attacking protesters
He does not abstractly imagine himself as being someone who would be
Protesting the Russian government never occurs to him
These people protesting are wrong
Oh they should be
You're right that's kind of how I think of brain works only free speech if you're right
Correct and he's never right
So Putin starts his speech
I noticed
Very bizarre dynamic
Well perfect timing as we speak vitamin Putin has just take
We're going to go to this announcement by The Rush
Cheerleader
About the ongoing armed conflict
Western Europe in the proxy war
Is Ukraine
Of course my address
Is also
Aimed at our fellow
Citizens
In Ukraine
Rollhouse
2/2
And details
Conversation
The matter is very
.
It was surreal to listen to this on Infowars because the Putin speech itself was pretty f***** up but
Are much more local level it wasn't saying how Alex just plays the whole thing and doesn't interrupt except for commercial
What
His actions really indicate a very real reverence
Alex Fields towards play a video without jumping in
It went on over multiple segments
Even with Trump speeches he'd often cut into double down or say something to do damage
Control
He was just airing a straight feed from Russian TV to Infowars
And it was it was very strange holyshit
It's just
Putin speech yeah so there isn't like a lot to even
Go over he's not really saying all that.
No
Just a Luna
Do it one of the brakes
When he's
Taking a break
Putin speech gears his take on it
History
I've never heard of modern world leader me the song
We came in herds
Ukrainians
In a way
And linen David all the way to begin with it's always been part of us
When your son's talk other balls cut off
That's really what this comes down to
Cuz she's going to put your kids
With adults
Because
He wants to go back to Russia being Russian things
Things that are Caesar's
What you're not over there in Russia
Wow
Interesting take
I mean
I didn't know Alex
Hero worshipping Neville Chamberlain these days
So Alex believes incorrectly even if you just wear to
Watch that speech transcript of it
He believes it with Putin the saying is
Hey Ukraine Live and Let Live if you want to go with the West go with the West
But you seems like you're making animus boyfriend getting broken up with I mean
Very strange
Take the take is wrong
Yeah yeah yeah
I mean you could say
In a way it was a modern leader being very honest
In the sense that they were
Revealing that there a psychopathic supervillain ready to invade a country because they want
Territory
It was honest in his much as especially with the gift of hindsight that we have from a few days later
You could scare a lot of people
Arguing this even
On Monday
This was
Keeps listing of excuses for why he wouldn't
No I mean you listen to that song I listen to the speech and I was like
He's going to die
Like that's the only
Conclusion you can draw from such a f******
Crazy sweet
If it feels that way but the same time Alex is still saying this this notion of like what he's going to do
Do is probably
You know with the dawn boss those those areas
He's going to take those because that is part of Russia in
Right the wrongs of Lenin which is a great way to frame it if you're a lunatic
But that makes and very strange yeah
Cialix does
Continue that prediction
Didn't ask
Scar are going to crush
Come take them
So they're going to Annex
Eastern
Tax on it
That's a serious situation
Consequences
Soros New World Order
The West
Vault of Soros
Speed art Isaiah instigating is meddling around
Who works for Larry Fink who work for the devil
You got to keep that org chart
You know BlackRock
The devil
The devil would sit on a black rock Black Rock was the name of the ship in lost that has
The dynamite in it Wells Fargo
Episode in
Season
So this is this is where Alex is at
Anti we've heard him say what he says in his next fight before
But it's always funny just too
To remember that Alex may actually
It's a shame
48 years I've been under 20
Basketball crazy
And I knew that pretty started meeting with Shelton eats in the last
Great
But now I
Are you seeing more more
Vladimir Putin repudiating communism
Western powers
Free from this restarting exten
Can get free of this club ilysm as well
Infowars
Putin Putin loves a war just one of those
I can't imagine
To like
Listen to this show
Right right
I even
I barely can handle
I can't imagine if you're the head of a country
Making the time to like
Oh I got to check in and see what this
Drunk texting is angry about today
His day look like
He can fit in some info
Right right
Very much but it's not like after he eats dinner at an absurdly long table with whoever you know he goes
Close down and he's like
Now I'm in my man cave with a nice comfy chair ready to listen to Alex f******
King Jones listening group may be with the Lord of blocks
I got one of those look like a lost viewing party if you will European weirdos that might
Show up
Alex is a man
He loves this he loves this speech
Kick it enough
Alright
I don't see how you
Historically true
Blah blah blah what do you want to know it's coming
We don't want you with you
Please please don't go to war with us
Level is powerful
It's the truth
Is powerful
Infowars
Hell yeah
Right
We just want to do business with you Russia
It's so
So from
He listened to Bhutan
Speech
That that that
Hampden interrupt interrupt it was played in entirety on his show we know he listened to it because he probably
Smacked
At least yeah so it was probably difficult to hear for about 10 minutes cuz he's chomping
Probably
Maybe maybe soft food burrito
I think that it's real it was really difficult for me to listen to this cuz it was really jarring
The dissonance
Between Alex's interpretations of things and the things I was hearing
Yeah yeah I mean that
Stats with that fux with my head right now I can't imagine being alone
You know
I think Alex might just have had his mind blown by the notion that like
You know Putin
Doesn't like communism
I guess and the
He has distaste
For Lenin and Stalin
Wow
For one of them who is also a complete badass apparently.
Digest
If you listen to the actual speech explains really
What his problem is
Yeah so this Bisquick was really where I think I figured out one of the most
Mccentral
Problems
With Alex
Interpretation
Hard on Ukraine with a rhetoric referring to a cranes process of decolonization
You want to be communize well
We're ready to show you what real
Becoming eyes
But the Hardline
Right-wingers here
So brainwashed
Russia was our enemy
It's a secret plot they're still in bed with an O
The Larry sanction black rocks in
Global organizations
Is not
Under their control
Where is Thanksgiving autoplay
Here is the actual clip
From the speech that Alex is talking about
And as a result the Bolsheviks policy
It's obvious Ukraine was created
And we have
Every reason to say now
Ukraine
Created
By Vladimir Lenin
He's
It's crater in Arkansas
Skooly
Confirmed by the
Documents from The Archives
Also including the
Decrease
Play music Chris regarding.
Dequeen and now
Grateful
Demolishing all this
Statues old monuments
Kaladi communization
You want
Communization
Well we are quite happy with that
Don't stop halfway
We already
To show you
What would mean
Actual Dam ation for Ukraine
What Putin was saying was a threat
He was not saying that he was going to get rid of Communism which is the way Alex is reporting that comment
What are you saying is that the people of Ukraine or moving past their Soviet past and smashing statues of Lenin
But Putin says if you want to do that go all the way and revert your borders back to what they were before 1922
Would you crane join the Sophia.
Frederick scary and Brazen, that has implications for all the former Soviet member state
There's an underlying premise here that in order to actually leave the Soviet Union you need to go out exactly as you came in
And if your borders are different than when they were previously he has a right to take that land because it's actually still Russia Today
It should be pretty obvious why this mentality could be a problem for a whole host of states in the region
And Alex does not seem to be willing to understand what is being said
Highway Avenue
I mean
It's like talking
Finland's worried again that's the level of
Where we're at with this is not like a he's going to get
Crimea
This is like he is
Stated that before he dies he's going to try and reunify the Soviet Union
That's basically what that speeches
There's there's there's a lot of there's a lot of calls for
Concern
I'll say that that's for sure
So
That is I think one of the central misunderstandings that Alex has this idea that is
Rat around
Idea of becoming ization
Alex is interpreting eyes
They're going to be part of the free-market again exactly
Market
Not they're going to replace a democratically elected governor with area so we go to the next Tuesday
Here's where Alex's head is at
It was so incredible
An emergency broadcast
We take calls for 3 hours
Replaying his speech and
My mouth
Cuz I
Last night my
My mouth
Was
Hanging open
Bad Stalin was bad
Lennon was bad
You want a d, nice things we're doing
We're having kids
Free market
And we're going to fight back against the globalists in the Monopoly
And and
That the West
Corporations try to make everybody Papa
It's so weird to turn into world leader and just proof
Who's coming out
It's all true the Russians
Came into Ukraine we were bored you're really the most Russians freely
We're sorry that the Communists killed YouTube usually apologize
We want you to be free
And we're not going to take you over
Just your government needs to go it was
I do actually have your own government
You need to stop attacking eastern Ukraine
Knowing world history
Milly Rock
Hard to find pulse
LeVar Burton
Wow it's great to Russia to say you have to overthrow your government
Right not be just involving
Are the areas in Dubai government was put in by the West so you have to get rid of your entire
Overthrow the government
You'll be free
We're going to take your land
And overthrow your government cool
Reading comprehension
You can understand a book
But I like you can understand a chapter you can understand a page or paragraph or a sentence a word
He was like that
Oliver
He's written a story about a food was saying I don't know that word was a prompt
For him an essay
That's totally what it is complete rejection and abandon
The communism
Maybe part of it but it's actually a term that refers to the states that were formerly part of the Soviet Union moving away from their time as a part of that
All sometimes by way of purchase
So people who were involved in the Communist Party
The things that Alex is saying are the characters actions of what he imagines the word me
It's like having kids of being free market or fighting the global
I bring this point up for two reasons
The first is that Alex seems to be really hang his hat on that Miss interpretation
The second is that it really illustrates how much of Alex is reporting a
In geopolitical analysis is storylines based on those assumptions
It's a really unreliable method for report
When Putin discusses his dislike of Stalin and Lenin the Communist Party
He isn't saying that he doesn't like them for the same reason to Alec
What does
If you actually listen to the whole speech it's super clear that doesn't like them because he blames them for breaking up the Soviet Union
Quote
It is now that radicals are nationalist including
Primarily those in Ukraine are taking credit for having gained independence
As we can see this is absolutely wrong
The disintegration of our united country was brought about by the historic strategic mistakes on the part of the Bolshevik leaders
And the cpsu leadership
Mistakes committed at different times and State Building and in economic MSN
Mick policies
The collapse of the historical Russia known as the USSR is on their conscience
Also I think I'll be real stretch to say that he was apologizing for anything even
At the predecessor is dead
Snow
This is the state that Alex is enduring
The early week
He's fairly
Bully cheerleading on Putin
You think he's a fountain of Truth somebody can find no fault in him as a leader
How much is fully aware that Putin is most likely going to in some way or another Annex the donbass region
And Alex
Completely in support of that
He's bought this action will be taken to defend Russian speakers in the region which is
Inconsistent pretext that Putin uses
Hostile actions against his neighbors
And Alex has every reason to know that
On Wednesday night
The status quo change dramatically
And Russia declared war against
Ukraine
Security Council held an emergency
MC meeting Putin announced his intention to demilitarize and quotidian ossify Ukraine
And began a campaign against the car
The assault wasn't just limited to danfoss region but included attacks on cities far to the West
So the reader
Yeah the turn of events is not on but it's far more extreme than most people's
Even though
Yeah I'm no expert on the Regent soda
Don't take my
Word is any
Anything meaningful but from everything I've read and see and I was not expecting anything
On this scale
It's ultimately not the most important piece in all of this but because this is a show about Alex Jones it should be pointed out that Alex was also
Also entirely wrong
How about his assessment of the situation
He completely whiffed on his interpretation to Putin speech on Monday and use that misrepresentation and misinterpretation
To justify Putin subsequent actions that led to the invasion of Ukraine
As it's pretty much always the case Alex's
Painfully wrong because he created his narrative
Biking combining uncritical acceptance of hostile government propaganda
With figment of his imagination
But that leaves us to pick up the pieces on Thursday
Now that Ukraine has been invaded now it says
Attire weeks is collapsed around how is he going to proceed
And more importantly
How will he pretend that he's been right all along
That's the question we ask ourselves
Enter
The 24th
Yeah you know I mean he's wrong about everything
And the early week
But it does seem like he's cheering for like
Minimal loss of life
You know I mean he saying fine you can take care of regions and s*** and maybe it's right
And all of that stuff is good but the the endpoint is
We're not going
To start a f****** more
That's the idea
That's what that's what I'm saying that's his mindset coming into
The war he imagines
That there's a way for that
To happen
Ready for Russia to force the overthrow of Ukraine's government without there being
Civilian casualties in
Terrible consequence
He's pretending that's true but it is not it is absolutely
And I think that
Much like
Myself maybe I was naive
I don't think that Alex expected
What happened on Wednesday
I think he is caught on his back foot
And
Really have to figure out what he's going to do now we're floundering
Yawning pretty much everything
Well we don't have to come in with our own canned air raid sirens for during the Cold War
Hillary sirens
Get dropped on Military targets
Housing
Park Place of a Slavic
Peoples
Ukraine
I should jealously just not one
What's Soros
Self self
Precious
That's the reality
How much going on
I'm saying
Oh that's
He's been saying that I'm going to take it over he is he's not been anything I'm sorry you guys can run your own country
No you saying I'm going to take this land if you want to be with cirrhosis and newworldorder you do you
But you can't cuz I'm taking
And that's what I've always
This is strange that's a little bit off-putting it's a little bit of the opposite of entirely
If you're listening to Alex's show throughout the stretch of the week
Have to be like
This is not good
What's going to happen
Myrtle Beach
We interpreted Putin's words
In a way to tap this is all cool what he's doing
Great friend now there's an amazing the table today or interpreting these words in a completely different way
And even then still being positive about it
I like it's fine
Well I mean
I don't think it's good that you can take over an entire country
But Soros is taking it over so it's really taking it from Soro
Taking over turkey
Sure
So
Boy
Alex is proud of himself
For reasons that are
Unclear to me
Putin has invaded Ukraine
Is he just taking out the military targets so far but will he continue to ratchet up
That's how the US.
That's how Hitler did it
That's how you meant worm
Take over a population in war you never tell people
But you're really planning to do you're going to get the inside scoop
Sister is
YouTube ABC
Or you can tune in here and actually really understand the history of things in
About where all this is going
All hell is breaking loose
There's a few clips of yours truly
November of last year
So you just play some clips of himself talkingshit about how there's going to be a war and
And such
Any. Ms career you could come up with clips of him saying
Stampy water being any
Random month
Yeah it one of them I do remember is in the context of him talking about being out with Joe Rogan
And some other Joe's friends
About how there was going to be a war
And I was just part of the prediction is somebody's got drunk and ice
Play that is a Victory lap
Great
You have to understand. He's maligning
All sorts of other information
Cancel versus wild saying I keep tuna in here you get the real s*** like
Yeah it's not
Listen to Infowars
And you get information that leads you to
Wheatley ill-equipped
To deal with with Brett from Santa's like this
Because you've been fed a line that Putin has no fault
He is a wonderful leader and all he really wants to do
Is is
Enoteca
What you don't like unification you don't like the Communist Asian you don't like meat denazification Dan
Those are all great things
Just like Americans for progress is a great group of people who are for progress
That's how words work they always mean literally
What it is there about
Yeah you
It's just strange for him to be bragging intuitive
Pumping up his own chest when
He's living in the cops like that the aftermath of his own
Failure information
Take me to Victory lap
Yep
You can turn into the BBC in here the Putin's the new Hitler in a mean tone of voice
Are you can turn in here and hear that the new Hitler is going to keep going
You have a great time
So Alex is a this weekend is going to be a long show on Sunday and there's a reason
Special Report
Infowars.com
As it's needed
Saturday Night Live
Joanna
Sunday
6 hour live show
Other word we doing this Sunday
Going to be again
Kicking off at 4
P.m.
Central Standard Time
Until 10 at night
Because CNN is running
Every
Protect lapray
CNN is running this
Promo
Every break
The only time seeing as viewers is during election
Ordering a war so they've gone from
What was the ratings of ever had their ratings are quite high right now
And why would you be running
Promos
About Alex Jones being the devil
Every
Single braids
Every single break so I did something
Purdue
I went to Andover to seeing in this morning
The first
The devil
Mouth of the New World Order
Demonizing me
So he's the devil
I've gotten a number of questions about this CNN megaphone of conspiracy
Sure I don't know if I talk to them
I did talk to somebody
It was months back
Right I never heard back from them tell everybody what you said
Well I didn't I don't know if I would get in trouble for saying this but
One of the things I made very clear
Is it I would not be willing to be a part of any
Kisor documentary or anyting
That played up Alex as some kind of a like Mastermind are like
Big like
RaeLynn kind of thing because I
Let me know he's a bumbling idiot who has
Weird beliefs about interdimensional demons fighting against
F****** George Soros in the gang and I feel that if anything I'm going to lend
Myself to her appear in for my own sake
If nothing else
I don't want to perpetuate that image of him as
Some kind of a megaphone wielding
Write a valentine
Know if that is with a deal-breaker
Decent chance that the person talk to me like an a******
Oh you're just going to go around thinking you're some kind of special expert on Alex Jones
I think
It's possible
That
I rub the person the wrong way
I don't like the metallic we had an unpleasant conversation or everything
I just
I find myself to be unpleasant.
So yeah I'm not in that
For all the people who have been asked
Did not hear back
Again I want also be clear
When I talk to the person at CNN
They said that there were possibly multiple projects
So this might be a
Completely
Something that the person I talk to you I don't know I did not hear back
Hey
Based on this I bet I'm never going to talk to anybody else I would not be surprised by that
I've declared talking to Brian stelter my white whale
Yeah that is going to be something I need to check off the bucket
So anyway CNN doing the tape piece on Alex
And there's a reason
Hundreds of newspapers a day
Dozens of TV show today
National shows every week
Alex Jones is sick
Because they see me butler
Stream Kodi
Man who's a father
Who believes in Freedom at his rally the people
Has survived their attacks for decades
And they think if we can just
Destroy him
Building
Prison
Then we can somehow defeat
Get to you if they hate you they're your enemy
War with you
It is a b
Attacking me because I stand between you and Powerful
Toxic line for propaganda
Sears
Because it achieved
Really potent goals
The first is that it creates a centralized point that the followers need to support to the point of considering the survival
Well being of that Central Point
Is as important as their own
If not more
Yeah cuz they're not as important as the fight
If Alex Jones or Trump is all that stands between you and sir
Globalist Onslaught that it's in your best interest to do everything
Think you can to protect them
So you don't get onslaught
This hustle is perfect
Because it works no matter what because the dreaded Onslaught is imaginary
As long as you're in business and siphoning off support from your scared audience you're doing your job and holding back this imagined arm
If you go out of business or died then it doesn't matter if that Onslaught doesn't actually come because you aren't in a position to exploit
The audiences fear anymore it works coming and going it's perfect position to receive any kind of car
Consequences for doing such a business already
Scams by American tradition
You were in essentially Sidelines any legitimate criticism of this centralized
Point
Alex is a complete liar and a noted piece of s*** in just about every aspect of his life that we have any information about
But none of that really matters
If he's the only thing holding back this imaginary Army
Trump is a lifelong con man who treated the US government is as cool to exploit for his own agenda and self-interest but
If he's all that stands between you and this imaginary Army does that really matter
And hey does
He deserve it for standing in between you and not coming on site what's a little corruption honestly if I were
We're doing so much good I wouldn't be able to resist a little
Corruption this is how
Insidious 2 of manipulation and it's a direct abuse that Alex is perpetuating on his audience
People who criticized Alex for plenty of other reasons and not just because he's a strong man who has
Raz-Kids
It is Honorable and Noble
I can think of
0 of those
Reasons
And I found a come up
Manly
His ability to cry
Wine and do nothing for anyone else of any good
Just think of honorable people I think of those who refuse to take responsibility for anything
Oh yeah
For honorable
So we started
This 24th Episode and Alex some of the interpretations that he had
Obunga
Sure sure
But now he's
Narrative again
Russian flag in Ukraine as Z tank
Butcher
From the East
No tanks
From Belarus
Dinner
Deeper into the nation
Panera
Because just like the US
The Iraqi leadership
For 2
Copper Cellar generals
You see that Putin is already done
Work
What and is already paid off
Military
And that's why the rush
No they can roll right in
Call snow resistance
What
Because that's how real war
John
This is really interesting because definitely wrong and multiple way I mean so many
First it's wrong in the sense that it took
Complete contradiction of everything else was reporting and predicting earlier in the week
No point is Alex taking stock of how wrong he was and how he was supporting Putin directly in the
Lead up to this
The second way this is wrong is it making up everything about Putin paying off Ukrainian troops and there being no
Resistance
There's been a ton of fighting with a Russian air units shot down in ground
Do hotspots
Not just in Dunbar
What I just want example of this is fighting this taking place at the gospel Mel Airfield
Russian paratroopers came in and took over and they were confronted by Ukrainian troops
And as I Was preparing this episode the outcome was still on.
It's been like
Back and forth
I'm taking it back from them and so much and there is reports
Many other instrumentals
Well it is the island of the Snake Island
I saw something about that just before we started recording
Does reporting this complete fabrication because he need this to be true to emotionally disconnected self from the fact that he was poor
Are the media chorus in the United States
The cheer.
Actively promoted the lead up to an invasion that is not killing civilians
And causing widespread fighting in an invaded Sauber
Bring country
How much supported the thing his brand is all about pretending to be against
All because he's blinded by his imagination
Did Putin listens to his stupid show and it's an ally against his pretend enemies
How to extrude on something that is at
Just an attempt to overthrow a neighboring countries government
And at worst an attempt to take the whole thing over
And he doesn't want to feel bad about that
So if this is just a situation where military
It is Marching In uncontested
It's not a situation where civilians are hunkering down at Subway stations for shelter where shells are hitting
Residential areas where Russian troops are attacking
Far more than
Region
Which is the flimsy
Text that I bought from the Kremlin it's all through his body
How to draw
Majorly wrong
In order to maintain the feeling
Throng this has to be fake
It's fake
What's going on
Can't make
Can't take responsibility for a single cell
It's got to run has got to be always running
It's not even just a responsibility
It's the feeling
Oh yeah no course
Well I mean I don't have that feeling
To feel like
Save cheerleader the next Hitler
Probably probably
Nobody
There's some people will probably be thrilled to have
And it sure seems to be those people generally don't have large
Million Dollar business
Doesn't seem to be that way
Myself
Huh
Anyway this is not the only time
That people have just bought off Army
Victor French just gave up and
10 days
What Hitler
Invaded
No
He bought off the entire
French command
I know
Taylor ship of France
Headquarters
For the next five years
The attack on France didn't last 10 days
Also at a France was bought off to let Germany just come in
People die for no reason
I think what Alex is talking about is that they entered Paris unopposed
That was because the French army is already taking a gigantic hit by that point
And the French government had fled from Paris
That's one of the historical things that contributes to the whole right-wing joke about French people loving to surrender
We went through that with
Freedom fries cheese eating surrender monkeys
Groundskeeper Willie
This is not how things played out
WWII
Nor is it an accurate description of how the Vichy French came
To be I guess it's simpler for Alex just imagine
These events in history were just like a simple Financial transactions
Everybody ever
Paris whenever whenever the Vichy took over
Everybody was super cool with it cuz they were paid off
There wasn't a consistent non-stop resistance from that single moment on until the end of the war
Government-in-exile absolutely not
Anyway I guess this is simpler
It must be going away now Alex kind of Hester
Wrestle with the fur
Back to poot with lion
Can't think of any way to fold
Can you crank
He denied it they denied it
We're just going over to
Songs
We're just going to
The Nazis
Which
How's the left side under that
To look here's the thing I will tell you how sir there's nothing
Alex is saying like
Great
That's just good strategy
That wasn't saying that
Denies that
Now
Do a little soul-searching
About how
You
When on air repeatedly parotid those lies
And also said this is the most truthful person that I have ever seen
The greatest world leader in terms of
Just give him the truth
Dust fact power of honest
Sticker power
That is what
He said
Power of honest
States parody level shape
Alex
And I had done what he did
And this was the result I don't pretend
Freddie Bennett
In any serious way
That Alex is actions had a direct result
Anything like that
He's lying to his audio
Possibility
To apologize
To deal with hey look I bought that lie
And I sold it to you
Yes
Would be effective
Something to sell you
It would not be fun
And you probably would get mad at me if I were to say hey Biden might be onto something here
No one would have accepted that
Maybe the president was telling the truth the entire time and button Putin was lying which
Is an inversion of how things are supposed to work my
My home
Marketspace Academy
You f***** by that and so I went with Putin's lies cuz he's great
I sold it to you as the most honest thing in the world whether or not I actually believe that at the time
You need to do some unpacking on that something he's not he refuses to do it while at the same time accepting the Putin would lie
How about his intentions and what he was doing
What to do
It's Blitz cowardly
I mean
It is like
He is spinning
Tons of plates right
But big
Because because
Because there are no plates it doesn't matter if one of them Falls
All right because they
Don't exist
So it's like oh no this
Theoretical plate would have
Really f***** me up but
I'm just spinning a f******
Stick
Yeah yeah yeah
Or even
Like I do I don't even
I don't even know how to make a metaphor that works better than
Thanks
Want to be alive
Going to be allied with Russia
What is the Slavic
You found Russia
We want you
Because Ukraine's always been the good part of town
What is a rush
What
And they're not going to let George Soros out
Mama
And so
What's happening
Yeah so they can't Source can't have mama
I mean it's just got to feel like so much more work
On this one
To try and like
Pretzel your way through Austin something like like
You can't just be like
Holyshit
Got nuts
Changing even over the course of this episode so far cuz I don't even know where I'm at
Ouroboros of lying
So you not getting with like he's attacking military installations is it going to go farther
He's going to take the whole country of the invasion
Fake
Purchased it also nothing is actually happening every Soros literally every
Thing that you are going to see
He's a lie is what he say
Include his real interesting change of tone
Different previous days
It's not yelling about how Putin
I was so full of Truth in those straight up leader in the world who Alex can't find fault
Just wanted to protect Russians and do boss
It's taken Ukraine to Soros can't have it
And Alex doesn't seem like he is offended by that
Twitch
Is
Also Alex is full of s*** about it being 50-50 in Ukraine about joining with Russia or the way
Center for inside research poll from December 2021 asked
If Ukraine was able to enter only one international economic Union which one of the following should it be
58% said the EU compared to 21% who said quote
Customs Union with russia-belarus and cause
Another poll from 2021 reflected 64% support among ukrainians for joining NATO compared to 19 /
Opposed
Alex is trying to create the impression that the issue was split down the middle because
It lends greater credibility to the side that
It's far down in the
The polls
Which is beside Alex supports which is boot
Its climate denialism as a
Boats a lot of
It's not necessarily their fifth
50/50 exactly
Play but they're equal in strength
You know how I feel about them
Yep
So Alex continues
In the middle of this show as it goes on
To pretend that there's no fighting
Going on
And Ukraine which is just
Wild
But that's why you're not seeing any
Because it was all
Her show
The comedian Hollywood
President was a
Double
The whole time
Oh yeah
Money
Is on
Experts on Ellen I'm an expert myself
No
And so
We already won
For Ebola
That's why we're infowars.com
Tomorrow's news
This is brazen even for Alex
I mean they're going to kill zielinski
Like that's the
That's the plan
I'm sorry if my response was a
No I mean it's f***** up and he's saying that
He's a double agent
They're going to kill him
I have
Difficulty assessing what
I think is going to happen
Especially with
Circumstances as have happened over the past week
I
Don't know
Write like that as the intelligence that was given out by
By biting his that he is Target one and his family is Tiger Woods
I wouldn't be super sport
Beyond my capabilities of like Assassin
What's going to happen outside of like information that is in front
At this point
Terms of Alex like
How is tomorrow's news today when today's news is a direct contradiction of yesterday
Yeah I don't understand how that works
Today's news.
S*** up yesterday so
You're listening to him you should probably recognize that tomorrow is
Probably going to be the time when you realize who's making s*** up today
It's important to understand that this stuff
About a fake invasion into lenski being a double agent is
Rationalization
I was just worried that this conflict is going to escalate and end up turning into a wider War
And he knows that
He's been way too public in his support for food
Continue in Russia continues to a grass on their neighbors
Alex's business model can survive being a media mouthpiece for the
The enemy
His twenties talkingshit
Sounding like he knows everything
It's not good when he's getting into Lord haha or straight-up father Coughlin territory
This rationalization also helps out with pivot away from over
Putin cheerleading
Without having to accept the consequences
If things do get worse he can say that after Putin wanted to Ukraine he stopped hearing Abad at that Ukraine was a false flag
Where there wasn't even any fighting and the double agent president surrendered for money
This allows Alex to avoid feeling bad about the people who died in The Invasion which he supported and promoted
Because he's an emotional and intellectual coward
That is what's going on
Heartbreaking
Not not for him to be no the real world
Heartbreaker
So like
You read about
America in 1930
Haven't you read about how so many people were like
It was great
Taylor super cool
Book I get why you don't like him but
He's going to be calm down by the elements around him. They're going to moderate
And it's like we're just doing it again
And it's just so f******
Sad
It's really hard for me to assess what's going to happen
In the
The idea that this is going to necessarily spill into a World War
Seems to me to be
Getting ahead of ourselves a little bit
That's the only thing that I'm pushing back on
And I mean you know it's easy to say that any comparison to WWII is
In totality but I am I am just describing the the amount of
Propaganda in
Support
That is being pushed
I don't disagree with
That is very strange the
The
Seems fairly uniform among the
Assertive higher-end of the Trump
Propaganda
Being on
Is there Nazis
Weird
So I look this is all just fake
And you'll never guess who he blames
Are taking over
All nuclear power plants
And coal power plants
And gas plants
Amber taking Oliver
Billings MT Airport
It look like a bunch of young 18 year old Russian
You're there aren't even special operation
Countries around
And no one's opposing I'm just this looks fake
Well that's cuz it's all a big drill
Military
And so now
We'll see what happens
What are the Publix
End up getting hung
We'll see what goes on but this is all directly
Because it was
Baptist Western forces
Are pregnant flight suits and all of their
A complete
Joke now
It shouldn't surprise anyone that does loopback somehow to being the fault of the meddling sjws
I want to such an
Immediately so caught up in his own narratives that the literal invasion of a sovereign country has to somehow be related to
Is bigot culture-war obsession
It's really remarkable how little of substance he has to say and how much you were treats to these things he's completely making up
Like the war is fake
Muscle memory Big Al War memes that he makes money spreading
Kitsap it's
It's
Pathetic I don't know any other words
I mean Henry he should really
The boss to give him a performance review
I mean is that is that is an element that I have seen
Repeatedly
Come up that is an undercurrent of a lot of support for Russia on the
Is that like
We hate trans people too
That I mean it's deep-set
There's so many
Little arguments of you better like
And we got trans people and you're like what
Remember what what are we f****** talking about is that it is that what you mean
You need somebody to kill trans people for you
That's what you want
And it's f***** up
It is so f***** up
It is
To be fair Alex also took a swipe at CR
That one I think it is just that's just
Sabonis I don't really know how to to say anything
Other than what you're saying but it's just
It is what it is it speaks for itself it really does
Complete monster
Alex has a new conspiracy
A little bit later comes back from break and you got a new one
Where Putin is mist
Elated
Is that they're going to
Power off in areas
You can bet
Your ass on that
Okay
Default movie
Volkswagen be blamed on the Russians
Directions
That looks like taking the bait to me
I would not have done what
People
Taken from them
Started with the Ukraine
So here's the narrative up till this point
Ukrainian military to stand down thanks to some involvement from the devil Asian
President zelensky
Right I guess that Ukraine is now in on the whole thing but the international Global is 2 still don't like Putin they're going to do
Volkswagen where they cut off the power
Maybe in Ukraine or something and blame Putin
For reasons that I don't really
Yeah I don't know what the game plan is here like the rest of the stuff Alex's things to believe
I don't really know how this would be a meaningful part of the story
It's not even clear storytelling and I think Alex is just throwing whatever the wall
It does have that feeling of just like
Okay and no I got a new thought
Alright so that ignore the last
Okay here's my new pitch
Leggett it's got that writers room of like
There's just a bunch of people throwing out ideas like is this something is this a good
Suckered into this somehow but he also paid off the Ukrainian military
Preparing to buy off of Ukrainian
Military and now
Send
They're going to do false Flags
To blame him
So when the Ukrainian military fight
Back
It'll seem like they weren't paid off with Ukraine and Soros paid them off now
The false flag
Power Attack
Ukraine
I don't get what that achieve
If they're outside of Ukraine like in the United States are United Kingdom
I don't think you need to invade Ukraine to say that Russia did the
No I don't think that's necessary piece of this donated
It's I would if I were reading the screenplay
I would ask for an edit
I would ask
Just go give another pass bright money
Well I mean it does seem like
I guess what he's trying
I think I guess he's trying to go back to
The proxy ID against
Read so Putin's paid off Ukraine and they're just going to take
Price
But then
The EU doesn't want them to just take it
Thesaurus
So they are going to put Mala Flags in Ukraine
Which gives
Batman excuse to go into Ukraine
To fight Putin
Is that what he's trying to say if so that's such a long walk
That's so crazy Joe like hey man you can attack here and then go go go go
I don't know that's crazy
Anyway
Speaking of crazy
Yeah we got to guess
Except in the mix all God no it's not Steve
Who else
Steve's Steve might be too much in the in the gas if someone else
Rodger Stone
Grammar
Trump advisor
Always has been
They talked quite
Florida
And he's got a lot to say about Russia
January 6th in Rogers today
Alex is great to be back with you well as we used to say when I was a correspondent for Infowars
Tomorrow's news today
We
Predicted this
A good 10 days ago that the
Plancha war was inexorable
This was as I am
I don't know what Rodger might have been saying
Absolutely did not call
Wild
This is
Yeah that's a little bit offensive
I just don't have you know that's it say it is a little bit maybe I'm a little jealous
You know cuz I don't have that level of confidence in Psychopathic ability to just
Declare that I did see
Especially
Even if I did something
Well I'm terrible at being like
Hey man
That was all me and I would like all of the credit
It's brash
Baby Bowl
Yeah got to get it
Fortune favors
So Alec Hamilton Rodger Ukraine news
Rodger drops
A piece of information that even Alex
Has to be like wait hold on
My job for this is wild
Show all one thing that did bother me and that that was that we one of the
Show called
Where the Russians have already taken control
They're starting to force
People of the Jewish faith
To register
I don't like that
Is there a pressure point that I read this morning
Shortly before coming on I hope that it is
I think Rodger is pretty out of line here if Alex had done a very out-of-character follow-up question
I would have been allowed to Clement are as fact that Jewish
People were being forced to register in one of the parts of the Dawn boss reach
Because Alex asked if it was true which is
Again bizarre for a baby it's not true kind of Defense
Feel so conveniently doesn't say where this news report he got it from was
So it could just maybe not even
Since Rodger doesn't specify I'm left to speculate about what he's talking about in the best I can do is that in 2014
There were Flyers that people found in East Ukraine
It said Jewish people over 60 and had to register with the coma
You were terrifying obviously but also they appear to have been a hoax
With neither the Ukrainian or the pro-russian separatists I'd clearly being behind the distribution
Some believe that it was possibly an extortion racket that sums
Splinter groups of the separatist
Trying to get going
But it's hard to say for sure
That said this was news from the last invasion
But
Who's the super serious allegation that Rogers just throwing around he's going to act like that
He needs more to back it up in some random thing he may have heard that he doesn't even know if it's true or not
I can't do standards
Are too low he said he said that Russia is forcing Jewish people to Reggie
Is that what he said
Or was he saying that Ukraine know he's saying that the rush
Actions are going into a territory
And saying that Jews must
Register
Right
It's confusing
I mean if that's what he say I feel like he's justifying a war against Russia
Right
Like you can't you can't also be like and it's cool that Jews are ready
Maybe maybe it's
Is it like
Situation where he's assuming that Russia doesn't have
Like control over damask
And so maybe the ukrainians are doing
I mean yeah along with the dean ossify kind of
Idea that the rise in the just
Location for the Declaration right but I mean it wouldn't make sense
For them to do it now
After the war has
Let me tell you about
No need no need to explain further
Yeah I don't feel we get any other clarification on this because
I always ask that follow-up question Cuts Rodger off at the retreat
Because you can't
Defend this position
Absolutely
So we don't get any more information
Anyway
Putin invaded a he's going for the whole country
And
Alex again refuses to accept that he fell for this s***
Why Rodger Stones ride shotgun listen to the next Alabama have two hours of open phones at had
Call Joseph Watson
I'll be on the War Room
Also huge
Ukraine
Putting that
Amused
I should do in war and it is now moving into the whole thing
Use deception on
You
Hi
He used
Deception
You well you know what sometimes this information is necessary for enemies ahead
The deception
Really work with much of the International Community so you're saying they worked with Alex and Tucker
Alright
Now that does make sense
Yes
Get off your f****** highfalutin horse gear with this deception stuff
You have to then say
Other people got it
Well I got it wrong I'm glad you brought that up
Brn a global conflict
Helicopters
Full-scale invasion
People are broken or right twice a day
Got to give it up
Map got to give it up to the Somali Biden
So now Alex
Yeah fighting was right you know what he's now what do we do
He was wrong
What does raw well I think it's implied that if you admit Biden was right
You have apologized for being wrong
Also the whole shot down helicopters thing would seem to contradict Alex's earlier point about the Ukrainian military just being paid off by
I don't see him retracting that or correcting himself a wrestling with how he was wrong
Like I also think you should take the realization that Biden was right a little harder than he is cuz it really hurt that
Really hurts his whole thing I mean for just to be blase
If I mean banana
Jesus the devil
He's literally working flower design
Kikyo
Junior cosmology Biden is working for the literal devil way down the flow chart
Sure that's
So Rodgers appearance can go fly a kite
Quite honestly it's just the same as wants money
And we can't fight if we are unarmed Financial
Do people need to go to Stone defense fund,
Adam Schiff in the January 6th
Help me Sue Hillary Clinton and her retinue
Alex Jones
Join me in that class
We have to do it
Show defense fun.com
Books
T-shirts
And more on your other side
I'm thrilled for this not to happen
Wow so f****** Petty
Really sounds in Port
And today doesn't it
I'm going to sue Hillary, I've got a fake lawsuit
You should give me money today
So I can fake
To Hillary Clinton
Isaac Rogers taken
Do this like lawsuit Griffith a little too
Eagerly
To thirst it doesn't come off well he cannot come up desperate the moment he comes off desperate his Misty
Seek is punctured to the point where you like
Oh you're a sad Petty old man aren't you
With
A tattoo of Richard Nixon on your bag
I don't know weird
Consulting fees paid by Foreign dictators
Paying for his top hat
He can't be coming to you and asking for money for a top hat
With
Crowdfunding you got to come up with
You can't come down if you want to be a real information
I'm sorry it did it is done to the people on the lower level
The money Kongos up
That's the
The flowchart for Rogers ship
So Alex has a meme
Barbie memes
Love memes
Putting out on Twitter
G m
Everywhere in
It's going viral
I need to look it up
The world economic forum
Kris where the prime minister is a member of the world economic forum
In Western Europe
Except for Spain
What does it mean to be a member of the world economic Forum as an individual
Because it means you've gone and given a speech at one of the Davos conferences or that you've attended one
Hello bar
I don't I don't like
It's not people on the board
Alright
But every
Okay so all the people go to the world economic forum
Obviously they can
Become a member
And if you choose
About 10% of those who become members are taking to their underground brainwashing
Sentara where they are hooked into a chair
Enf on the temple w.w.
That's bad
No Electro neural what was no nevermind
It's whatever
But
So this is just b******* that was posted on Twitter by former NHL player in current
Conspiracy Peddler Theo Fleury
If you recall he was one of the people who was originally pedaling the million
Truck nonsense on Fox News in the lead-up to the Ottowa occupation
And I guess that brand was lucrative for him so he's doubling down on the world economic Forum stuff right
He posted a meme that wasn't even about Western European leaders but if people in the Canadian federal government who are quote
Listed on world economic Forum. Org people
That peaches blank
It happened and all the captures in the way-back machine go back to 2016
I'm not sure how anyone could even go about checking this list
But even assuming that all the people he has on there attended Davos
That proves nothing
And it has nothing to do with Western Europe
Also not to split hairs here neither
But
Most people who have breakdowns of world regions they consider Spain and Portugal Portugal to be in southern Europe not in West
It is a dummy metallic so I decided was groundbreaking he thought he should write a new story about it before
Reporting on it this is dumb
This is process this is what he does
Tommy
Former NFL player NHL player Theo Fleury
Are you didn't you didn't pull up the stats no
Do we have any do we have a card but here's a problem to with me
I don't know anything about hockey and so like if I looked at his card it would probably be like
Right I don't know what these stats are for a goal
Icing is whenever you skate and then your likes
And then you hit somebody in the face with some
Is it really
I don't know probably
Maybe it's not see this is how little I know about whatever you pushed to get the puck out of there so you're
Defense and the offense is like and you're like out of here if you get it
I'm a boy. So
Alex's head
What I would describe as
Internally inconsistent narratives about Ukraine
On the 24th
Fly in
Stark contrast to the nonsense he was doing
Right at the beginning of the week
Clip is where I believe he gives
We're here
Watching all this up.
Watching this
As it takes place
And then we're told
At the borders of Ukraine are the most holy thing in the world
And that the Russian should
Be there
When
The people controlling
And running our country
Sovereignty of our nation
He's being erased in from the plan
It isn't just
The Border
Set the globalist
You in
Have told the third world to come here
Here's a lockdown
Cuz then flush them up here
2B now political pawns a new permanent underclass
Globalist
Making us the third world world
Permanently
Use these masses of people they've been exploiting as an invasion
Enforce
You can see here that Alex essentially has nothing to say about the situation in Ukraine
This is very clearly an attempt to shift the
The focus into a subject matter that he's much more comfortable yelling about namely is racist great replaced
This doesn't even marry response
Because the situations he's describing art analogous and anyway
Instead
I'm playing this Calypso leap
Need to demonstrate one of the ways that Alex's coverage work
He's throwing so much s*** at the wall because he has no idea what's going on but
He's still expected to be the guy who knows every
This manifests
First of the beginning of the week as his supposed deep wisdom about Russian history
Handheld Putin
So right that there's a need to defend Russian speakers and dumb boss
Alex pouliot understand because he's an info Warrior
Free market in prosperity for the people
The kids and we can survive and thrive
Falls Park
Invade Ukraine so Alex needs a new story
This largely takes the form of Alex make it not that there's no Ukrainian resistance and then Putin paid off Ukraine including the double
President zelensky
Alex knows that this isn't going to fly and by this point in the show
I'm sure wanted is in terms of telling him that there's fighting and multiple locations around Ukraine
Russian helicopters down
That narrative isn't going to last but it was a first try to make a further conspiracy out of the situation
But he could use them
In the future
Buying time
With that failing he needs another distraction because
Without distractions
It's really too obvious that Ukraine is under attack and Alex reported
Completely false information
Tomatoes audience support the actions that led up to it
The perfect distraction here is exactly what Alex is doing
His arguments have failed his information is shown to be bulshit so the last Refugee really has has
Just a point
Racist brake replacement obsessions and say why should I care about their board or when we're not fighting to the front door border
It's essentially a white flag
The whole narrative building exercise here
And maybe a white nationalist flag will be more appropriate in terms of this but
Marvel white Hood
Alex
This indication of given up kind of even started earlier in the show where he was trying to say that acceptance of trans people in the United
They've somehow LED
Despite
This is where his resignation is really crystal clear
Maybe it was something more to say the later day or someone will feed him some information during commercial break but
At this point
This dude is done
Hear this bed is done
Yep please bake
Yeah that's
That's straight-up
Like Pat Buchanan like 9/11 happened because we allowed gay marriage or whatever it is
Does he know like it's it's
Straight up that kind of
F****** Pizza no more anchor to reality
Is a punishment for us
Caring about
People that was that was sort of earlier in the episode a little bit of lash out
Sitting here saying why do we care about Ukraine when our Southern border
There flooding an invasion force of
Third world population
That's given
Yeah that's that's
Okay guess what
All the s*** of the race of s*** that I yell about all the time
That's more important than this
Who cares
You wouldn't do that if he actually had something good to work with
It is the sign of somebody who has no f******
You got to be in text from skousen
During a break
Here is here is a interesting mirror
That I notice
Early in the episode we talked about Monday
Alex plays without interruption
Putin
He doesn't
Cut in and then say like know what actually
Anything nothing
Instead he just listens reverently
On this episode on the 24th
Alex Goes
Do a b
Listen to his behavior and how it's a little bit different
Imagine will be a little different even before it start
We are back live cellular phone calls but fighting just start
Please be patient colors I love you
Maurissa and Virginia nobody else and I get Tina Mama Collette's
Let's hear some abide that he can get his words from together
Are Dash
Sorry to keep
Even before it starts he insults
If you can get his words together grumpy old dum dum can even
Speak words right
The reverence
That he showed of the respect that he showed for Putin isn't direct contrast most honest
And
Powerful man
I've ever seen
And only saying that after you've already formally cut off
The speech you're not talking over him at all
Here is
How Alex babes
Dirt bike
This is a premeditated attack
Vladimir Putin ism
Planning this for months as I'm as we've been saying all along
More than 175,000 troops
Military coup
Blood supplies in the position he'll Hospital
Black lives matter burning all you need to know
See this is what he does what
Child was right
About
The situation that we're looking at right now I don't care about Ukraine because with more important
Is Keystone
Sure
Am I guess it's just a position to buy performative
But it also leads to like what you described as a
A bad
Stand-up wrif
But y'all know
So much
But he gets distracted until like
You know what the problem with this is get out of here
Like a bad Adam Carolla written
It's unfolding largely as we predict
Cyberattacks against Ukraine
He's so desperate to say stuff over by 10 so you can't hear him that are being brought up
Because they are threatening to because Russia is attacking with 175000 Troop
Yeah I need sign language people
Yeah you got them
Battle that's what we need to deal with it
Awesome
So
I mean
This is this is
The way he's behaving
So different
Between these two speeches
Is
It tells you all you really need to know
It's absurd
Two new show called
Republic
I'm Sovereign Ukrainian Church
Snowboarders
No USA at all
We don't have borders
Now sovereign
Territory
Which is part of Russia
4000 years
Continue wait hold on now
I'm sorry you seem to be going back on some stuff because you want to yell
Wow
Airnow instantly were like I would take over Ukraine and also
Hey hope the f****** breaks it what B was never chanting no Borders mobile.
I would give anything for a president to be like borders are bad
That'd be great
Yeah
I think that Alex in much the same way that he'll say like
George Bush was a liberal
Or something like that
He paints with such a
Targeted
Is so dumb with his definitions that he's like
Oh yeah by Nano borders people
Like right the f*** out of here
Convinces himself basically YouTube
Go back to being
Just because he gets mad just goes by
Chose this war
On your doorstep
How to say I'm going to live on your porch
Machine gun
It's actually true
If you finally walked
I mean I mean really
So you can see Alex's becoming more and more probe as siding
Speaks because I went to politics
His perspective
It is anchored to anything other than opposition
Is only coherent perspective is to be against
The positions that are expressed by his imagined enemies
Is giving a speech thing
Alex esta tonight right go on his knee jerk when even after saying
Earlier in the show that was right about this situation
That
Is taking the whole country
Simple this is an emotional outbursts on Alex's Park
He doesn't even really mean the things he's saying I don't think
It's coming out of his mouth contradict earlier in the show but it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter because the product is selling the audience
Isn't analysis it's an emotional experience
The emotional experience of pretending to yell down by
And shut him down he would liar
The emotional experience of pretending to know secret information that no one else has
The emotional experience
Being proven right even when all the things that are happening by the opposite of what you predict
This is the emotional resonance
Is enjoyable for Alex's audio
Yeah and it's
All
The facade it doesn't mean anything
Yeah I mean if what you're selling people is
Secret special knowledge that makes them smarter than everybody else
More powerful than everybody else
And
I mean
Who cares what's real
As long as you're providing
The feeling of being
Smarter than everybody else and if you feel it then it's real Advent it's that doesn't matter if you're not
Holding anything I'd say It's Magic and I think that this next clip
Biden speech
Design fucus I can't listen to this a******
Pretty quickly compared to the
Such very long time he listen to
You know isn't that such like
You know that
They'll never do it
It's never going to happen
This is so
Such a simple moment of like
You're going to listen to everything Putin says
Even though Biden's right
You're still going to side with Putin just because
Just because
Never not even this one time when I do know he's right
I've said it not even this one time can I listen
I can never do it without one
Nope never
Nope
Not even one
It's f****** w**** which you are against
Theoretically he hates intervention
Like you know everything
Supposed to do
The Clipper now
It's
Strange but not that strange
Like this like this
Healing verses
Reality,
Conflict
I think is actually really indicative of that
Alex has a little bit of a clip of Nancy Pelosi that
Pics of such a slam dunk
Where she saying a country
In a whole different area of Europe is Ukraine
Doesn't
Even know the country of
Ukraine
And she says a totally different country
I'm at leadership of
And you see hungry
And you see how it is encircled Russia
Belarus
Crimea
Batiste
Have taken over butthead
You know it's still a danger now to Ukraine
And then you see Poland and Romania and all of us
Just a budding
Oh that's a Russian influence
Hungry
Sandwiches a liar and this clip is deceptively edited to make it sound like
Pelosi thinks Ukraine is hungry
YouTube This by cutting off what she had said just
Prior to the eclipse starting
Quote
What was interesting was to see the heads of state with him we had interactions as well of countries who are newer member
Members of NATO in the concerns that they have
What's next for Putin if he were to be successful in Ukraine
I had the privilege of sitting next to the president of Latvia for most of the plenary session
And others have
Others there were very concerned about what would be next
When she mentions hungry as well as Poland in Romania
Do reference in countries that were of concern to Nato members about states that could be in trouble with Russia took over Ukraine
Alexander knows this new playing the clip deceptively or he
He never even took the time to find contacts
Is just desperate to play clip that seems to show someone he doesn't like misspeaking
Which I guess is a huge win for the info War I mean that's the feeling he wants to spread this feeling of
Nancy Pelosi doesn't even know what countries are what we got
Yassi
Look at this look at how smart you are and how stupid she is with the reality of it is
Just a lie
I mean it's not hard
To come to the conclusion that if today if Putin
Not stop
He's going
To do it again
It is a very simple thing
If he wasn't stopped
From 2008
Hey did Crimea Crimea he's does Ukraine has not stopped
Hungry's in South America it borders Ukraine absolutely
Anyway or van is worried about it the word real trouble there
So Alex interviews a guy named Patrick Lancaster who's a
We're journalists
On the sea and in done by us
And yeah
I'm catching vibes
I don't know what tone about him but I looked at them a little bit and
Must be some very serious distrust
His motives and history
One of the things that I thought was a particular red-flag is he claims to be a crowdfunded journalist
Makes $15 a month on patreon or something like that
I don't know exactly where this crowdfunding is I looked
It's a mother
ESO PS4 support
And
I don't
Okay
Just cuz you have one rich backer and a bunch of very
$1 givers does not mean it's not a
Crowded some sense
He doesn't really actually say anything that adds to real conversation
Alex
Assassin
We'll see how this all got now we have
And now you got class while we have the clip I want to go to calls
Shore Club
Last year
Exist
Jacquee's what this coming
It's what makes it covid-19 look like nothing
Power will be out
Everything we're doing is around that
Going to cut our power
Joe Biden's and clips
Last week this week
Today
Get some
Like I said I think the Russians have been let into a trap
What
That's another lead into a trap
Play possum I guess and said we're not going to attack
So I guess maybe the the whole thing
He was selling about it being fake
Invasion
Was just him talking s***
It's abusive
You know we go back to him anytime
This is abusive you've said it that it is
Is abusive
This is so
F****** abusive
Furious that this is allowed to
Even in one man
Even if he wasn't on the Arrow
Abused by the idea of somebody saying all this debate not to be around this person
Yes
It's it's that I mean like this
It makes no sense
Like included with the totality
All these coverage over the course of the week let alone the day
Yeah and it also doesn't
Obviously he plays that clip of course Rob and he's just saying that like it's
Something to be concerned about
And that if there were widespread cyber-attacks it could be something
That would be more damaging Society
Inboard disruptive then
Covid lockdown
A massive chunk of the power
And then we're all five leave alone
Like Russia doing it there's a lot of actors that could be there's a lock
Potential vulnerabilities
It interprets that is like Holly threatening to do this
Whatever that's how I was his brain operates it's stupid
Been over that a hundred times yeah
Leaving that aside
Like I mentioned earlier
You don't need
A
The Lord in invasion of Ukraine
We like hey we got to be worried Russia might have a cyber-attack plan
That is a completely unnecessary middle step
Along the way it makes no sense for the larger storyline
It's just I was trying to find ways to rationalize
It has to be
Anything other than the guy I said was the most honest guy in the world
Lied to me and then started a war that only see one
Cannot be
That the guy I say is the truth teller
Is lying and is not even a conquest her or anything like that
Just a
Plain old mass murderer
That's it he's a criminal he's not even a powerful leader
Let's not forget this
The person who fell for that lie
Was that
Alex sold at
Yeah
So
And he just doesn't want to recognize that he never wanted
It is it is so much just like
You know he lied
Do you
You know that like don't you feel offended by that a little don't you I would feel offended if the guy that I see
Think it's honest
Was lying to me the whole that I know that
Steve is told him that Putin listen to Infowars he doesn't give a f*** about you and he lied about
Never heard if you lie to you
Does not care in such a way to make you lie to your audience
You were manipulated
By somebody who absolutely does not care about
Just like you've been manipulated by Trump
I'd like you've been manipulated B
Steve
You're just a f****** moron that's what Alex is
Yep
And we can see the kind of steaks that he's willing to be a mark
About
And then after the fact try and rationalize it with these bizarre stupid
Conspiracies that he's making up
It was just one cuz even Trump was like
Hey
Love the move of overthrowing Ukraine
It wasn't like hello there's a dead excuse for why Putin my buddy is overthrow Ukraine he's just like
Phuc yea killed I just saw the headlines about that I thought he was just saying that likes in 2014 it was genius what
I don't know I didn't I didn't read the full thing
I'm not sure
But I also think happened under my watch
Because it's also inside great
Cool
Yeah
I'm interested to see
See particularly what's going to happen
When
Galaxies have taco
Yeah cuz that I think might have
Some kind of
I just feel like
Literally everybody's waiting for Tucker to tell them how to feel is like
F*** this
Putin's right
Everybody's going to be like yeah absolutely
I've died
I feel like I have no faith
That Alex is going to have his own
Like actual tape
Baseball
Based on this waffly nonsense like
I don't think he has any
He's not standing on Solid Ground
And the kind of people that he could bring in to give him
No good you passes expiration date
You have Joel skousen and he's not going to play ball
I don't know what other kind of like legitimate geopolitical experts he has in the bullpen
That could Calico Rogers no good
You can't have a legitimate political expert
It's not a possibility
Because this is so cut-and-dry
You know like this is Steve would help him
Seafood helper
You can't have Steve
Christiwood Guru
You don't know what Steve is going to help him with
Yeah Steve cannot be a helper
He's going to get you into the Hague
You're going to
Yeah
Temperature might be too high for this s*** that's too bad
Ivy
As you can
You can't
Because I'm imagining
Having fun with it
No circumstances it's disrespectful to
Hopefully
Hotmail
Jordan
I forgot to play this out of context drop
At the beginning of the shower now
Call somebody
Yeah thank you that was a good note to end
I'll let you out
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work