Damn important
I have great respect for this knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
What's up
Quick question
Horizon forbidden West
So good recording and I was really
Questioning was whether or not it would
Live up
To really high expectation
Super far into the game but so far it has
Exceeded
Expectations
Which is surprising
Oh yeah
We haven't no spoilers policies course
I'm having a great
Oh no the moment the moment you started you texted me something about it and I texted you immediately back like
I slid beneath the legs of a Tyrannosaurus Rex slow-motion fired an electrical arrow in the
Thing blew up in who's the most satisfying experience I've had
In so long they added some new mechanics teams that are like really interesting
My bright spot is yesterday I got the chance to get together with my cousin
Who I haven't seen for a while even very close and they have a new French
And it is
So goddamn cute
And you get to hold it
That's a bright spot for
Yeah I think so I'm not a dog guy but even I can appreciate
Little puppies in the crook of my arm
I get it
So Jordan today we got to
To dive into
February 25th
2022 we're going to be doing is a deep deconstruction of
The idea that Alex
Predicted this war
Oh okay
We heard him tiramisu we were going to split up into its component parts
Molecular Gastronomy Alex's bulshit
I'm so excited to get into that
The rest of the stuff
Not so much excited to get into we will deal with it all on the other side
Hello.
Thanks.
Rachel's infuriating Breaky time
Proud of you.
!
Thank you so much boy with a little bit of swagger busting it down
Sexual style is he goaded with the sauce most definitely not think
That's what your nail polish
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you
Mud
O'Reilly
I'm a policy wonk
The writers on the show have been teasing me for five damn years now when are these Dan and Jordan guys going to finally get together thank you so
I have
Risen above
Miami
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
Apologize to
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not
Yeah I'm positive
Not good
Not better from the last time we saw him
Hard to get word discussion and content in the lead-up to
Ukraine being invaded by Russia and his response
Immediately
Was that
Isn't that
So I guess no contact dropped from Today Show
Leo zagami is way underrated that dude is the real deal I'll leave it at that
I would agree with him if he's talking about Leo's music
Play underrated underrated he had a good stretch there in the early thousands
Hung out man he was
King of the underground Roman techno seed
The real deal better
So we start here at the beginning of the episode on February twenty
5th and
This is where we're going
To dive immediately
Into the discussion about Alex's predict
And here we go
All hell has broken loose
That lot of people that ask how did I know
Remember December
Told you how I
I knew that
The ice
Melt
Football game
By the end of February
And major Financial
Individuals I talked to the highest levels
Get ready
For war in February
Not just
Russia but also China and I told you that
How does he do it he must be a secret agent
Or Jones
For the last 4 months
5 months
Come
At the end of February
So what are the central pieces of Alex's coverage of the invasion of Ukraine has been about how he was going to be a war
Back in the fall to early winter
Of last year
That's become a bit of a medium and he can see people posting about Alex's remarkable prediction on Twitter another message
So I felt like a really good use of our time would be to really dig into this
And see what Alex predicted
And talk about
Hawaii keys
Full of s***
Unbranded video Alex posted a video with the title quote
Watch Alex Jones predict
War in Ukraine by February compilation
This is on his own website
But providing evidence of his prediction
So this is what I'm going to base
My discussion on it's his own evidence exactly what the title
Ukraine by February
Compilation
So it is a compilation of a number of clips from different shows
Deal with them
None of this is selectively edited to remove anything from the compilation he posted
These clips are going to be played exactly as they appear there only separated
By which show they're from
So this first clip here is from
October 21st
The smart money
Is on award show
And I don't want to war
But
We're looking at a giant Warren
February right now
Projections with the top people on the Earth
You playing
They're not with the New World Order combine
In war in February
This is the type of time but right before World War before World War II
When everything kicks off
And I hope
That doesn't happen
But
Currently
That is the tragic
Actually we're on
And there is a
Consensus
On that
And a large concern
I don't need a consensus with people that just live here in Austin
The new-made powerbomb of the country
I'm talking about
All over the world
Contacts
And
Errol Flynn things
War with China is in
He was Raising alarm 10 years ago on that that's what I got mad at
Do all the smart people I talk
Say the same thing I'm saying
So the first obvious problem with this clip is that Alex is predicting a war with China which hasn't happened
Has his own ever
Yes
So he left
The part in where he said this is going to be war with China
What is the problem
So taking nothing to do with Russia or Ukraine
The problem for me
The second thing to note here is that while Alex is talking if you watch the video they flashup b-roll the video of
Podcast witch
Doesn't make sense
Unless you know the larger context of where this clip came from
When Alex mentions this new Power Center in Austin
That's because just before this clip Alex into repeatedly and embarrassingly insist
But he wasn't just talking about Rogan
And the reason he had to do this is because these comments that he's making on the 21st
Or actually an extension of a story
He told the day before
Which is from the 20th
Probably
Avakin
This is going to end
Gigantic massive
Billions dead
I don't know
Public yet but I guess
Is coming here
Some other things to learn some really interesting things
But
I'm not ready to talk about that
Where am I from Joe
All the people he runs with
You can probably imagine
Wiethop
I am.
Elon Musk
Alex has been out with Rogan the night before having some drinks along with Lex fridman and Michael malice
The information that Alex allegedly has it comes from them
Secondhand which Alex is very clear about on the 20th
There was
Michelle's
Joe Rogan
Lex fridman
Michael malice
Quieter
Quite a group of people there
The open
We just have to discuss what is going to be like going through this
And I learned a lot of interesting Intel
Okay but I won't go
They only are
Because they all have their own little Intel
This is an instance of Alex he's in one of his regular strategy
Which is basically just a combination of escalation and obscuring
I'm a 20 if you tell the story of being out with Rogan and a couple of his weirdo friend
Andover drinks they talk about how they feel like war is come
Call the 21st Alex embellishes this story to be about all these high-level sources he's talk
In reality it's just a continuation of a story from the day prior
Which is why he needs to insist that he's not
Just talking about Rogan
Alex does this a lot
We've seen instances of him taking information that a caller gives him one day which goes on to report is coming from an unnamed High
High-level source
The next day
I guess what Alex probably wants the audience to think is that a minimum
This is something with Elon Musk has told Rogan and then Road
It doesn't really matter
The information he's providing doesn't come from any high-level source and more importantly
The prediction that he's made based on that fake Intel hasn't come true
This is about war with
China
It's not relevant
Again it's also about United States war with China which the United States is not currently at war with China
Am I correct
You are okay
So on to the next clip
Now this clip is from July 21st 2021
And you better get pumped
Because it features
A guest appearance
From the guy who took sole credit for 911
Leo zagami
Biological bacteriological virus
Next is the Cyber which they tell us in the Nexus nuclear lay that out
Yes and the cyber warfare basically is already taking place with all this
Constantly and then of course we have the nuclear now the nuclear is already starting to be announced
China threatens to Nuke
I want yesterday here's the headline Fox News going to keep going
Official jerseys daily
They said we will nuke Japan
As you can see the garage
Free phases of over this Superior that we unfortunately going to be leaving and that the
The will of course diminish
The population of deer
That is absolutely nothing to do with the current situation
It doesn't mention February 20-22 radiological weapons
Not Russia
This clip is also being taken wildly out of context in order for it to be used in this compilation
Here is the actual context of what
Alex and Leo are talking about just before this clip starts
I know you don't want to
If you don't know
Research
What's the time
Takeover how long does happen
How long we got to survive
22 2030 there's a free stages take over the fastest bacteriological Warfare the second the sidewalk
Warfare defend is nuclear warfare
Saudis
Free scenarios
Will BMV
In the next nine years
This conversation has nothing to do with Russia invading Ukraine let alone doing it
In February
It's two lunatics tacotote Imagine The Devils schedule looks like over the next decade
This clip is meaning
Yeah I mean we're still ain't even in his
We should still be in the first bacteriological phase
At least cyberwarfare we're not in full nuclear war
Will be way ahead
I don't know of any art
That exist
Set the pics of the devil as being ahead of schedule
I think there's a lack of strategic tension if the devil had downtown
The devil is like waiting at a diner for you just like sitting there like I can't believe he's like 10 literally
Literally me just sitting typing is huh
Need to be busy all the time
So this next clip is from February 17th 2021 and it's important to understand this show
Is it a game from
Was during the 2021 winter storm in Texas
Particularly grumpy about how he doesn't have his fun LED background in the
The studio and they have to run the show
On backup generator
They may even
I have Bible Stand Down
The first strike
From China
My guts
Never been wrong
Ever
Last month
The United States
Going to be hit by nuclear
Your weapons by China
Stand Down
Stay in your homes
OU
Your powers off
Approve that coming
And they're just getting us ready for the disaster
I'm going to hit the main cities
Very good chance
That they're going to either blow the entire power grid with a
Get ready for or they're going to hit us
First strike
And you're like
America
It's gone
Been awhile at the house
And I was in
Because they're going to be removed
So I just I got to be honest with you false it's all a
Okay it's all a
Military
Against this has nothing to do with Russia or Ukraine and doesn't mention February this is the u.s.
He's also not like a specific timeframe
The year ago
This clip is utterly meaningless in terms what this compilation is supposed to demonstrate
They believed it Alex predicted this war back in mid-to-late
This is s***
Here's what I
I am getting
Alex
Without
Question
Has at a certain point in time said that Russia and Ukraine will go to war
I've no doubt it
Somewhere along the way only one of these clips will sort of get into that
But that would take a lot of effort
Probably I also think
As this this next Clipper we're going to talk about sort of illustrate
Maybe some of the times you talked about it would undercut his actual argument on that point of this
Compilation
Let's get to that
This next clip is from November 16th 2021
And it's pretty short
Having a really big ones today
Ethnic Wars about
Start something
Xbox go down
That means nothing
You probably are asking why is that clipso shortened
It's compilation it seems
Weird
And that's because
This is what
He said around that clip
It's really huge and got me having butterflies right now
I'm having a really big
Start something
Xbox
Go down
My Spidey Sense
Never been this strong it's
Bonfire right
Talk about
Stomach
Yeah that is
That is some energy right there there's some
Big stuff
China threatened war with United States
CIA says righteous preparing to invade
Ukraine which I don't believe a word they say
Haha
Hahaha
Smart too smart to Clipper real sport
Where he's predicting War he says that the Russians would not invade Ukraine CIA says that
Whoever put this compilation together has to if know that that's what he says immediately after this quarter
He says all I feel like war is coming
That's useful for the compilation and they know that f****** people who see this compilation are going to ever
The time or the interest to go back and be like
Wait a minute you lie after this he said that Russia isn't going to invade
So this means that not only is his compilation entirely about the United States and China fight
Fighting game
Is not happening it is also
Moving the parts where he said
Russia won't do the thing that is happening
In order to bolster his case that he is not just
Not wrong
But precious
Yeah it's an abusive lie and it's very intentional
Well opposite of what this compilation is supposed to
So cut it out
So we can just make it look like he did
Yep
Yep it's such dogshit is like how a child would think
To the next A2 is from December 1st
And
Yeah I don't think this helps
We are not just here talkin about what they've already done.
We must ask ourselves how would they carry out
Mass extermination on
Operation
It's already killed Millions worldwide
That are soft kill binary weapon
How would
They
Get away with that
The answer is
A massive Financial collapse
A warm
So this is no specifics involved it's just Alex saying that he thinks the globalist
Start a war or collapse the economy to distract them there covid bioweapon plans he's insisted
He'll expose coming to life
Isn't meaningless and does nothing to show that Alex made any specific prediction
About Ukraine Russia or the month of February
Let alone all of them
Together
This next week later on December 8th
2021 and Willow
Where we got here
The imf's machine
Global Financial collapse
Cyber attack
Oh and imminent war with Russia
So I guess China can swoop into
Taiwan Hong Kong
South China Sea
Vietnam now
That's
How World War start with the same political cultural spiritual
Economic climate
The world was in
On the eve of World War I
And we're
In the same
Geopolitical
Economic culture
Spiritual position we were in
Right before
There are more than 50,000
Nuclear weapons
Conservatively on the plan
My problem
Most of the work
Half mile of Mi up
Destroy
Real estate and kill humans
Each win the nuclear reactor
Go offline and start melting down
And we've got
He 100-plus chernobyl's look forward to
I won't be safe in a little bunkers from themselves
China nuking us or against nuclear power plants melting down
Has nothing to do with the prediction of war between Russia and Ukraine and doesn't involve February at all
Chernobyl so I guess we're getting
Closer
I guess yeah there was one jump in there too clearly trying to make two parts of this episode mashed together
Make it look likely thoughts appear to be more directly connected
And then there's another jump-cut which steaks
Take us to the next clip
It is also from this December 8th episode
U.s. Senator won't rule out nuclear strike
Against
Well isn't that just sweet
And I got stacks of articles with them threatening
And and then already moving their weapons up to the Russian border
And the Russians are like okay you're taking over a country that
90% Russia
In the east
30%
And you your cigarette at a car
Gas pipelines in our facilities
With NATO troops we're going to stop that
And their answers will just nuke you then
I predict the Russians are going to roll in
Swollen
And there's a good chance this psychotic crazy people
Could be killing us with the shots in the bio-weapon Everly
Watch tactical nuclear weapons to Russian
And the Russians are going to respond by destroying nature
And it about
15 minutes into that
Papa and the cruise missiles get fired
Where's a good run while we had it right wheel of Satan right
Loverboy she will guess what
Y'all get ready to die
The closest we're probably going to get
Discovering an interview on Fox News
Ukraine because this conversation was already happening
December
Entrancing about other news and interviews on other news channels Alex said he thought that Russia was going to quote
Rolin
Which isn't specific enough to interpret is him being correct or incorrect
Depending on your preference
What's more important
Is that the rest of the stuff he's ranting about his
Completely off base
So at this point he also never said that it was going to happen in February
He was thinking Derby military action that's contained within the Don boss region
The only way to make this seem accurate is to be really generous which Alex doesn't deserve any even if you do he's no
Not saying February
No these are disconnected thoughts and even then he is looking
NATO as the aggressor
Right
Maybe he's like Russia is
Justified
In which roughly did which
Based on some of his other comments in
Career you shouldn't be too surprised by
I'm predicting that this war is happening you definitely weren't predicting that Russia was going
Going to be invading
The entire country
Very broad reading of uber lamp
So there's one last weapon this compilation and it's from January 5th 2022
Globalist get out of this without nuclear meltdown
The service we are becoming a little bowl in every
Every actuaries madani mother pentagon
Why are they following a path
Will
Pause math War masturbation
A nuclear meltdown because it's
A planetary ending event
Look up means nothing and is no predictive quality to it at all
When taking their totality the compilation involves Alex mostly talking about his fears about China nuking the United States and
February once
Not even in relation to Russia
This is a really A desperate attempt on Alex's part to capitalize on the tragic
Aventador
Complacent
And use them to inflate his sense of self
It really grotesque motivation he's displaying particularly considering how weak the oven in
He's presented
Is Voorhees supposed
Prediction
The reason that this works on people is because most people don't have the time to actually listen to Alex's show so they don't know what the context
His foremost these clips
Place together the way they are they given appearance that's
Dishonest
He's talking about about war
And he says Russia wants
Twice he says he thinks Russia is going to quote roll into Ukraine
Earlier in a different clip he said February
If you're not paying attention
Disconnect to these clips are you run the risk of combining them in your head
To give Alex
What's credit for a prediction absolutely didn't make
You run the risk of being the rube that he made this clip
2 and a lot of people have fallen for
In reality Alex predict War all the time
I will grant him that the vast majority of these predictions
Has gas
Make a
Kind of obsessing about Civil War or race war
The geopolitical variety does happen sometimes butter is really just insight met based on his culture War big
That's kind of
The Sweet Spot for a
Predictions Alex make slideshow historically
It's been
A lot of financial collapse type stuff that's
Certainly something he does all the time or has
But that's because
One of the big reasons and the other is because it helps him attack the Federal Reserve if he insists the collapse is just right
Around the corner
Tacitly predict that never happen
Except for
And then you get to look like that all I predicted it literally
Once then crash of 1987 happened it's been like every 10 years
You know it's just there
I'm predicting
Is something that
You're never going to
Eventually long enough scale you're going to be right eventually
And if you give yourself credit for predicting Russia invading Ukraine by yelling about
China Dukan beehive state
A bunch then
You've Won
The pointless game
That is so
Is like
Loki
Such a f******
Disgusting Psychopathic things
Look at all of this destruction and death
That makes me feel good
Cuz I was right
You know I wasn't
Edit clips
Makes me feel good still somehow
Which is really the only thing about that cares about
Also and I think it's important to point out is that Alex predict his own imminent death
Pretty frequent occasions
Haven't happened yet
And of course gives constant failed predictions about false flags that he insisted going to happen
The point here is that Alex didn't predict anything
This video he released as a disgrace and it doesn't even show him predicting what's going on in the world today
It includes the clip it had to be edited short so it would include the part where Alex says he doesn't think that Russia is going to invade Ukraine
Just not use that one
He's a piece of s*** and this is how he tries to make money
To get attention off this war
It also
How is the temperature lower people's attention away from the fact
That all through the
Beginning of last week was going on and on about how great
Honest Putin was and how
You can find no fault with him and that he should take Tonasket Lots
These comments look really bad now so in
Instead of apologizing for that
He starts this b******* campaign basically Nostradamus
Because I was a liar and a f****** coward
I feel really
I don't know I mean obviously I think
It is bread-and-butter to do detestable thing
So this is just another in the long line of them right I think that the circumstances being what they are elevate
Take this to a different level of
Shitheadra
The other thing is that this
Is
Something that is
It's a it's a luer
Much like are you using fishing
You know like this is trying to get people on the hook
You posted
This compilation on the social media and you try and trick people who wouldn't otherwise
Maybe I've been being lied to about alleger all this time I heard that he was bad and I know he got kicked off social media but
A lot of good people have been kicked off social media give him a try
There's a lot of
Possibly well-intentioned people who might
I get by this
And
I think the arguing against
Somebody posting this
Him
Difficult because you have to engage with it
Enough
To be like
That's not what he's predicting right and then
You don't know where those clips are from and it would take
A person who is
Me Providence
Probably it would drive people mad but I'm already mad
So I can I can handle doing this but
Such a
Dangerous
Propaganda tactics
I bet that is reprehensible
The irony being you or the theoretical rube that gets caught on the end of this hook
Will have gone there because they think that Alex is right about Russia starting a war
And if they stay there long enough will eventually support poop
Yes among other things
If you end up
Getting sucked in by this and then they are cloud
If Alex can predict this you must you must actually have really great information maybe I should listen to him
He's going to do it yeah you could end up believing all sorts of
Devilry
Yep sucks
Let's get back to the present day
So Alex believes
Of course I heard a little bit of that in one of his clubs
For the past but that's
Yeah this is Russia's fault
Republican and Democratic senators
Calling for more military aid to Ukraine
What got this going in the first place and weapons being shipped in
To the Russian border
Poking the bear
Grizzly bear
Dan at the zoo and wondering why I teach you
Bengal tigers
Gorillas in wonder why they get their head ripped off
What
And whatever happened
This is historic
This is an incoherent position and if you actually think about Alex's position
Begin coherent
Because the Alternatives just don't work now
If this is actually a situation where the West is regressing on Russia's Border in Alex's stated a bunch of times that he
I believe that the Don boss isn't the part of Ukraine
Then why wouldn't he support Russian Putin's action
He definitely supported them hypothetically last week
Before they became a reality disposition is no good because Putin is actually doing the thing Alex want
Did that happen and it's f****** horrific
Alex makes money in the space where he yells about things that people aren't going to do
Like Ron Paul would do he was President Trump should Outlaw the Democratic Party
It's a real problem in the things he supports end up happening it doesn't happen that often
But when it does
It usually involves a lot of people die
Right and
It doesn't want to
Make me feel bad
Yeah but look at it from the other side
And you realize Alex can't take the opposite position either
He can't see the Putin is entirely in the wrong and that he had no justice
Application for invading because that threatens the very long-standing positive coverage that enforces had regarding poop
He's been built up his
The one great hope of defeating the global is so if you take the position that he just invaded a sovereign country for no reason
You're going to men
Funny questions to answer
Plus Alex
And he knows that a whole lot of his audience loves
Putin invade
Sogo
Is going to be bad for his bottom line
And thus you get this middle-of-the-road b******* where Alex gives lip service to protect
Take me to post the invasion while simultaneously placing the blame entirely on Western powers
And thereby completely absolving Putin
The blame for the entire
Now
It is all on him
Somehow
Well he's trying I was just trying to say like whatever happens now is on him
Jesus totally reasonable
What are you doing
It's a bizarre position
I think it's entirely the West fault
Obviously Russia should it Putin should invade and now it's all Putin's fault
What
What are you talkin
You understand I really think
If you if you take the time to really focus on so I think
A number of his positions throughout his career has had to be the same kind of
Completely internally inconsistent thing because
You going either way is not going to work
I think when you see that it's
It's really the Hallmark
If somebody that you should not
The trust yeah they're up to something
That's an
So we get to you I was talking about his fears about Cyber attack
Going to be a false-flag cyberattack
Against
Well Rush is going
To be the victim of that NATO is going to run the false flag
Against Russia
In order to
Start a war
Here
Is the big escalation
All the Talking Heads saying others any type of Cyber attack
Anywhere outside of Ukraine in a NATO member
And that if so much as a stoplight
Take those out
Blamed on the Russians
Senator
Warner Brothers actually said that
Eviction
Bueno stop light going out
U.s. troops have a car wreck
Article 5 and go to war with Russia
Nicely in the world as we know it
So there's that issue
Against
Poland
Or against
Hungry
Against
Are the Czech Republic organic
Germany
You know hacker groups and you know different globalist groups
Going to try
To scar the shop and accelerate
Conversation about like a stoplight
Put out
Used in the context of like it introduces really bizarre question
Yeah
If there is a cyber-attack that Russia does against Ukraine it has the potential to affect the infrastructure
Of other countries
And
Does that
Require right kind of an article 5
It's not saying
Stop light goes out we're going to f***
Concentra it's it's more like the system is so completely and
Utterly interconnected and complex
That the idea of what is and is not a specific attack on whom is difficult now to even
I understand but also reporting this
Some kind of like mind-blowing new conversation but that's
Stupid
The NATO secretary-general Jens stoltenberg has been saying that cyber-attacks on a member country could trigger r
Article 57 at least 2019 if not earlier
It's never really fully articulated but if you read his comments it seems pretty clear that the way Article 5 would be invoked
In that situation is in terms of retaliating in the cyberspace
Not in terms of a physical War
Right so they're there interpretation would be if we trickle are trigger article 50
For this purpose and can we can meet it
At that same
Maybe that's not always
Consistent but that seems to be the way it's disgusting about cyber
Stoltenberg wrote an article in Prospect magazine in 2019 that includes
This passage
As we look ahead we must
Continue to build a strong and diverse Workforce of future cyber Defender
The UK has already started doing this with cyber first
A program aimed at supporting and preparing undergraduates for a career in cybersecurity
We must be smart smart about recruiting training and retaining highly-skilled cyber experts
They make sure their skills are kept Sharp
Through regular exercises
As we do for instance through our cyber Coalition exercises
Cyberspace is the new Battleground and making NATO cyber ready while resource well-trained and well-equipped
Is a top priority
Article 5 really just says that if a member countries attacked the other state
It's come to their defense
It doesn't require that that defense be a Landon
Anyway you can tell her that Alex is laying some groundwork to be able to claim that he predicted a false-flag cyberattack
If Richard does do something
Or there is a Cyber attack
He can be like a high do it I called it
Bright
No it's not
That's no not good
Not helpful
But at least he'd named more than six NATO state
So that's that's pretty good
I wasn't counting Republic
So
You remember in the lead-up to The Invasion there was a lot of conversation
People like
Do people like Biden
Us
State Department
We're saying that there was information
That Rush a plan to provocation false-flag pretext
Foregoing in
What do you what was Alex's response.
I believe Alex is a response to that was to say that it would not happen like false flag
Just don't happen
I couldn't get that I was like
He didn't say that
All false Flags don't happen up crazy
What you did say
Somebody like
Let It Go history never
Pretty pissed off based on his own expertise
The United States
Whoop
If you think
It's easy to Stage a false flag
State Department
Car bombs going off right as the Russian
Invade
As a pretext
Military
Military class 5 manual
Usually you don't want to kill people
Blow up
Blow up you know where I am busy building
Barracks
Pretext
It does look like some
And she it's okay to talk about
This guy calls himself the world's foremost expert on false flag
I guess Russia did a false flag after all
Looks like a state department is right and I the world's foremost expert was wrong
Alex was
Just wrong he was pissed off that anyone other than him was
Suggesting that a false flag could happen
You really got the sense that you took that personally but now I guess you realize the state department was right
But Woody's
Failed to take
Stalk of
Is that he was wrong
He'll never do that because if he acknowledges that he's wrong or that there's a decent chance he could be wrong
Keep losing a lot of hypnotic power over the audio
So much of Alex's appeal is based on his performance
Confident so if that facade cracked
He doesn't really have much to offer people other than bad impression
Leaving aside the question of whether or not there were in fact false Flags
It's weird how Alex can accept it Rush identify
False flag but not draw the natural conclusion
Putin is evil
Evil leaders do false Flags according to Alex at Infowars being honest honorable leader
False flag but here Alex seems to take the whole thing pretty lightly
Doesn't do it then you're just out of gray you're just don't even know what you're talkin about
I still don't think
Define the idea of a false-flag wanted to look like the good guy
Two car bombings to make it look like they were I guess
Alex won't take me very short very obvious step of recognizing that it said they are the bad guys
The good guys
Because they are not
The good guy
Talk about false flag
It's always been okay stop by false flag
Does it talk about false flag
He calls everything a false flag with no
He constantly rants about
Vague false flags that are coming any day now
He uses accusations are false likes to excuse their behavior with murderers who are motivated by the same
Extreme right-wing politics
The Hughes files is on a daily basis
There's a lot of space between
Response
Possibly talking about false flags and what Alec
He is full of
See you can
Damn you can talk about false flag
Alex
I think even more so then on our last episode
Yep since then Alex's
Waffly a little bit
He's not saying the Putin's bad
Right but they were right
What obvious
Putin was right
I think Alex has solidified that a little bit more on this 25th
This is being done to look strong to go in at
Disarm Ukraine
Because Russia for 20 years has left the last
Expand 805 times
Very clear
And put the shed
2 weeks ago
I'm not going to invade
Just say you're not going to
Invoke Article 5
So you're not going to bring Ukraine into NATO
And I said nope
Images of large US Transport Aircraft
Delivering
Palace
Very
Structube antiaircraft
It's got one now
Wow you just said it was right for Putin to invade
That's that's what you just
So-vi
You think Putin murdering all of these people if he looked he believes it's saying was a cell
Self Defense Act
NATO promise Russia after the fall of the Soviet Union that they wouldn't expend is taken as an absolute fact
Will do accept it as a fact but
The reality isn't so
Clear
It's definitely been the Russian government in Putin's claim forever but there's
Story that make this
Incorrect
This comes down
Go to the. Right after the Berlin Wall fell
Discussion happening about reunification
Application
What are the big issues in the negotiation involving the US state department in Baker
I am Mikhail Gorbachev was whether or not NATO troops will be stationed
East German
USSR in Russia
Did not want that to happen at all
So in the past
Pointed to a May 17th 1990 speech from the NATO secretary-general Manfred Warner
Happy Day Dental
What happened to the assurances our Western Partners made after the dissolution of the Warsaw Pact
Where are those declarations today
No one even remembers them
But I will allow myself to remind the audience
That's what was that
I would like to quote
The speech of NATO secretary-general
Mister Wok in Brussels on 17th of May 1990
He said at that time
The fact that we are ready
Not to place a NATO Army outside of Germany
German territory give the Soviet Union
Hey firm security guarantee
Where are these guarantee
The issue however is that the speech that Warner gave.
Promise not to expand member states
Of NATO right
Just promise not to station NATO troops in the former East German
Even gorbachov is that they didn't agree not to expand in a 2014 interview with Russia Beyond
The topic of NATO expansion was not discussed at all and it wasn't brought up in those years
I say this with full responsibility
Not a single Eastern European country raised the issue not even after the Warsaw Pact
Cease to exist in 1991
Western leaders didn't bring it up either
He says expansion is against the spirit of the agreement but it wasn't discussed and no promises were made
The point is that there's a gray area here where Alex just sees black and white
In the same way as Boonton
Multiple NATO States Estonia and Latvia border Russia and they joined in 2004
Multiple former Warsaw Pact countries have joined the earliest entering in 1999
Prior to Putin come into power
Bring up NATO expansion is being
The spirit of the agreement that was
Tell me about Germany
Is something that is a fine thing to do at a negotiating table
What is absolutely not a justification for an invasion which is what Alex is using it here for
He seems really desperate to make the audience think that this is the West
Asphalt and that Putin had no choice
Which is pretty f*****
I'll bet that's where he's at
It says
That's how the cow ate the cabbage
Man it's so it's so weird to me
Seeing
How many people
Are you like
Apologies
For a war
Yeah I was watching
Chicken some of the America
The first pack
Conference
Nickel
Disease getting a round of applause there is great
For Putin
Their computer
Pick some of those eight does
Believe some of that
Stop but I think that kind of line is actually
That was one hundred percent to get on
I think I think he is also a dangerous horrible Neo-Nazi as bigoted but
I think that was
Verbal shitposter that was definitely him being like
Guess what's going to be on TV 2
Even though you was
Expressing
Quite a bit of support for food
Invading Ukraine
Getting a
Round of Applause and a chance for putia
All sorts of
Folks across
The right
It's just
Really
I can't I can't think of any
I can't think of any war that I be like
Well listen
This is great
I think this is awesome I want this
It's crazy
Crazy to me
Yeah who's the who lives in that world of like
Yeah we're still cool
I didn't
So Alex
Is really caught up in this
Ukraine stuff
You know and it's so much so
He's forgotten to cover some big
I'm going to cover the
Developments in Rochester for this segment the next
But then the last second of the shower I really
Drop the ball yesterday
And this isn't just about this news it's just
Unbelievable
It had almost all the pieces of it but now we got
Madonna created
Covid-19
Reverse-engineered at the lab data
Coverstore
Cork moderna was created by Bill Gates and others just
For this event
So this story that Alex is talking about has to do with another preprint article that he's blowing out of proportion in order to weave
Conspiracy Yarns
The team of researchers who found that a 19 letter string of DNA in the coronavirus map
Bring those patented by moderna a few years back
In relation to a cancer drug
They were working on
Sure this was covered in the Daily Mail who spoke to Professor Lawrence
Young'un virologist at Warwick University you said quote
We're talking about a very very very small piece made up of 19 nucleotides so
It doesn't mean very much to
Refract
If you were to do these type of searches you can
I always find matches
Yeah it's a quirky observation but I wouldn't call it a Smoking Gun because it
It's too small
It doesn't get us any further with a debate about whether covid-19 was engineered
Also Bill Gates didn't start but he wasn't even involved in the venture
For Capital start-up for the company back in
In 2010
Even within the study that itself they suggest ways that this could have happened naturally and there
Conclusion is just that
It's something that should be looked into
That's fine
It doesn't
Justify Alex's reported on
Montessori at all
Still get back to it a little bit later but you just had to be like flakka
I forgot to cover that this is so important this thing that's not true
I got to get this out there smoking God
Open the garage
But first you know we'll get into that
Giraffe stuff we'll talk about why why your neck so long what are you hiding
What are those leaves and they better than the ones I got you will lead us giraffe
More about Russia
Globalist
Never give up
And they're really pissed it Russia or not
And so they are pushing Russia
Add
Understand
Global system of setting
War
And defeat
But
Put made a major mistake going into
Ukraine
And
Long-term
Trigger alarm
I understand that it was
And one of the choices out of list
The bad choices
And I know you putting on
Baby born
Just analyzed
Wow
Sweet kind of see here how the only way Alex could be
Anyway critical of the invasion is to put it in
Tactical terms
You have nothing to say about the targeting of civilians
Possibly bads
Strategic decision food made today
Who knows maybe I'll be a good thing in the end
Missiles
Directly into kindergarten
Hospital
All of that stuff
That is just
Bad
Strategy
Not evil
You just got to do it better there's a real
I don't I don't know how to describe it other than
Lack of Center
There is there is a little bit of that like
Oh he's watching a TV show
He's watching a TV show and he's like
If I were the head
Main character in this show I wouldn't do that
I mean he's he's like I don't go don't go in there
Don't go in there behind the door is also imagining a killer being behind
Everything's fake TV show isn't real he just staring at a big rock in a wall
Sunnyway in in case you need to speak clear
Enemy is the globalist the enemy is Hollywood the enemy is the left
Heather moralize
When are the worst
People
This planet
As ever
Yeah please make
Can clear that those are the animes the enemies of Russia
Yep
That's just
It's amazing
It is it is kind of talk about this bunch of the past but maybe not reiterated enough
Russia about the people
Of the country
Hey can be it can be easy to misconstrue
It Bears repeating
From time to time I am thoroughly anti-oil border
So
No Warner Waldo USA at all
Send but you sure have a right to defend yourself of an army
Shows up at your door
I just I guess wanted to clarify that because
Of my way of saying that like
Alex thinking that the enemy is Russia I don't mean
You have some really interesting event by that I mean dumb ideas about what's going on
How with is engaged
But you get around the average leftist they are
Hateful
Filth
And never stop attacking
Until they get control
People on the world
Russia
The left has successfully feminized America broken
Donald
Didn't happen in Russia
85 years of New World Order leftist rulership
Is that we see the response
Was an outrageous thing for Alex to be saying at least partially because it's a complete contradiction of everything he said
For the past week I mean
God damn it was initially threatening to go into the Don Bosco regionality wasn't saying that he was doing that to stand up to sjd
Do use he relied on Russian
Compliance targeted Putin should do that and it's basically already
Russia
Even after the invasion Alex said to Putin
Paid off the Ukrainian government and was going to have no resistance in his invasion
The New World Order
The effeminate men in sitcoms and commercials or whatever purple penguins are why millions of people have to
Alex suggested that the fact that the US is tolerant of lgbtq focus that made us look weak to Putin at a past episode
But this is a different Target
Alex is making now
This is an argument about Putin's motor
It's where Alex's suggested that he invaded Ukraine because it was somehow a response to how the left wants to
Control everything
And feminize men
Is a profoundly stupid thing but it's one of the only refuges Alex has to hide
The Invasion is ongoing people are dying and all of his predictions work
Complete s***
He was wrong in the lead-up to The Invasion
Eddie actually was wrong in both directions
He said the Putin was just going to take done boss
Eddie also
Was going to start a thermonuclear war with the United States
At their parties are done both extreme psyche got a 7-10 split
Yeah
In order to put
Salve on his wounds and distract people thought that stupid video about how you predicted this last year
And then he goes and he does everything he can to shroud The Narrative of the invasion in topics that he's more comfortable with
Which is to say bigotry
Is it the audience
Love those marriage just give them what they want
More to the point though this isn't analysis of
Anything
This is an emotional outbursts
The ticking to use the invasion of Ukraine to inflame people's feeling
It possibly incite them towards anti-violence
Yeah I mean it's it's just
It is it is literally like hey
We can forgive
Anyting
As long as your aim is to Stamp Out
The lgbtq community
Like that's
Spizike
Phuc yea
You have to invade otherwise NATO's going to bring the lgbtq into your f****** c***
Like that's
That's your argument
It's it's not far off from the spiritual core of what he say
Whatever you got to do man as long as we get rid of lgbtq
You get a free lunch
I am sure he would try and pretend that there are other
Elements
Central
Organizing principle
Of what he
It's it's awful
I mean it's might as well be
You know this hurricane was caused because we allow gay marriage
That's that's
It's it's just
God has to visit
Pain upon us
For our sins
So Alex gets back to this covid narrative
Even
Take
Something and use the actual bit severe
To make a conspiracy have to lie even about something
We could just work
Somebody seen this cuz the Indians I get the credit
Major Tom
University
Biogenetics
Virus scan
Completely man-made
All the parts
Play-Doh AB
They're all come together there's something
Next flight out with synthetic
No debate
One out of three million chances
They just one part
October 9th
When you put all the pieces together
It's basically impossible
Flying first of all this wasn't from India's most prestigious or top university
Researcher on it is
Who's at the University of Oregon
Can in Eugene
There's one researcher from India who works at Doctor shots charity Eye Hospital
Second Alex is just lying about what this paper is about
It's not about any other part of the genome been this strand of 19 letters so when Alex says that it says something
But outside of that
He's making that up
They do calculate the odds of this string matching the string that was patented by moderna as being 3 billion to 1
Remember that this hasn't been peer-reviewed
And even just in the comment section
Of the article like the actual
Paper itself
People that brought up some potential issues with how they calculated that probability
They also didn't say that it had to have been made in the lab that's all an extrapolation on Alex's
Is Bart there is even inside the story a or in the paper itself
There is a
Potential explanation for how
It could have occurred naturally
Abso
So yeah
Newark
It's very much not telling
He hasn't read this
He's just
Cena headline
The article that I was reading from his is from The Daily Mail and even this article includes the response today
I had from Doctor Young about how this is interesting but it doesn't mean much
It also has another quote from a microbiologist from Reading university
Interesting coincidence
This is Shirley entirely coincidental
The real version of this story as reported in the
Starting a Daily Mail article deserves their thoughts of a shrug and say how about that
What is also lying
And making up details so you can make it more scary for the listeners
And make it more of a confirmation of his bulshit Mera
So I thought this to be uncompelling
So it even then our reaction to it is more like
Who is Michael
Like when you see a double rainbow we are like well that's unusual a double rainbow
A very different response
Panda so much news
So much to hit
How many are there
Just now the full compilation
But 7 minutes
It's a pawn
Banned. Video nothing
Long
It got millions of years
On the internet right now all over the place
Billionaire
3000 there
Came out
Byerly
Incredible
Why don't I just go ahead
And
Play
A little bit more of this in context you navel-gazing f***
Oculus
It's not about we're that much news it's not about me taking a Victory lap
That's not what I want you to think that by the way it's a Victory lap based on getting a lot of attention for a compilation of deceitful
But I do want to play this uninterrupted for everyone to hear
Put a piece of s*** every second
I guess you don't have a lot of news to get to you know apparently not
Anyway he tries to salvage
A little bit
From this
After the after the compilation plays he has some interesting
Rebuttal
Sources information I saw everything going on
February
China
Moving and rice
Because if they're going to move
They're going to move together
And now China is making more and more
Allstate
But they also said that they
They like Putin.
Ukrainian president and talk about an armistice
Demilitarization
The media of censorship controls
We're neutral so that we can move against tartar
See what they say
I got it for you Alex
Probably inspired at least partially by listening to the compilation video realizing
Entirely about him predicting the China was going to Nuke the US
Annoying a maybe I should
Explain that or trying
Y'all make it not little glaring
Jack's for that one
23rd article in the washing
Two times but doesn't say what he's claiming
What he needs to repent
This is about a propaganda Outlet set of instructions
China there were allegedly leaked
First being posted on the website China digital
It's unclear from the original Source where these instructions at
Totally came from
It's entirely possible.
This was just an internal corporate memo
From the social media team at the news Outlet Horizon news
From the digital times are
In this case the author of maybe were laying specific official instructions or taking the initiative in anticipating the
The desired course of cover
Alex is a discount from the government
It's not in the underlying Source material.
News Outlet you kind of probably have a video for what
What's good and what's bad in your boss maybe so but
Still doesn't have justification to say that this one is directly from the government
So the story Alex's covering can't even solid leak
Confirm that this was something that came from the GoPro
Instructions
To be against Russia's invasion
So they could sneakily do some invading other route
This doesn't match the messaging of the instruction
Is really just making up a lot of this
Basically the instructions were to just not say anything
Negative about Russia into news around social media
I mean they've got a
Full cooperation treaty
So yeah that makes
To be clear I think it's
It's not good
If this is authentic
I don't know
It necessarily how credible
Please
The sourcing is on this if it is real but I think it could be
Jerk taco
Snow socks that Horizon news be making rules
Not post anything quote unfavorable to Russia or pro-western
And they're being told to monitor comments on their post
But this doesn't
Match with Alex's reporting it all
There's a larger issue to confront here and that is that Alex's rhetoric is directly in line with the positions being expressed by
Representatives for the CCP
From the Washington Times article that he's Alex's source
Quote
On Wednesday Chinese foreign Ministry spokeswoman Hua Shan Yin
Appeared to be following a similar propaganda script
Do one of the disclose
A to the one disclosed by Horizon news
Misua blamed the United States for the price
Criticism
Quotes lately the United States have been
I've been sending weapons to Ukraine heightening tensions
It even typing up the possibility of warfare
She told reporters
Hockey question here is what role the USB corporative current tensions around has played
Nisswa said
If someone keeps pouring oil on the flame while accusing others of not doing their best to put out the fire such kind of behavior
Clearly irresponsible and immoral
I look forward to seeing how Alex explains how his coverage of the Ukraine invasion is directly in line with what supposed to be
The result of the Chinese propaganda initiative that he's decrying
I also know damn well he's not going to deal with that at all
Now I can polish it
Which is
Really strange
No not that strange it would be but it's obvious if you think about it
Pretty strange
Just because
Your people are acting on consistent like principles
Awesome
He signed the Treaty of cooperation with China and China is now just
Giving out all this propaganda that helps Putin
So evil of China
And you like wait
What
What's happening
Yeah Alex could have given that statement that the Chinese foreign Ministry spokeswoman gay
Straight up very similar to
What a dick
Anyway Alex takes
Some calls cuz he had so much to get to
And
Yellow
This is the result
Of the kind of
Narratives that Alex puts out
The day before obviously Alex was saying that
Ukrainian
Leadership
Hey military have been paid off
There wouldn't be any resistance right now it just gets parroted back to him by a collar
I believe
You're right on that everything
I think
Ukraine
Invasion was a theater I think it
It was
Land II
Putin basically walk
True Ukraine
There was no opposition
I'm sorry
Very little
What
What do you
Did he
Does that guy think that happen
I mean how you get that from
Listening to Alex
Talking point about there being no resistance and such
That was a while back
It was a day ago based on this episode
The notion that it came to
The past that's crazy
Yeah it's just living in a bizarre
Fantasy world
Alex
Recognizes
You know what there is some fighting going on
I can't really pretend that there is not
I got to come up with an explanation for why
And here's what he's got
Clearly the military leadership
Was Bob
Before the invasion
It's a ragtag Pilots ragtag tank grapes
A ragtag militias are
Fighting anime
In the face of the Russians
Actually holding a mop and some areas
Any other border guards they didn't get the memo to children
To surrender so they got killed
And admire these
Fighting good people
Upset about being invaded by their historic
Brethren
Interesting way for Alex to try and Salvage is shity storyline about there being no Ukrainian resistance but
This is entirely pulled from his imagination
He has no evidence or even
Suggestion of evidence of the Ukrainian government has paid off to surrender as a fun thing to tell the audio
Yeah be interesting if that's what happened
Now that it's clear there's a robust Ukrainian resistance he needs to find a way to delegitimize
So he's now making up but there was a memo that went around that the military needed to give up at some border age
Scrappy Pilots didn't get the memo so they're fighting back
Scrappy Scrappy Pilots Band of Brothers
We happy few
This is absolutely pathetic
And it's really the face of Alex
He's making s*** up to help his listeners and not experience reality that he finds inconvenience
Even in the context of lying about people fighting a war against an invading country
It's just debased stuff and like
As the kids say he should probably just take the L
I move on
Do kids still say that I don't think kids do but coronavirus delts like us to
Feel like I see it on Twitter and I assume that's
Makita Twitter's the kids
Nautica
Scooters for old dum-dums like us Twitter is no longer on fleek
No
Thoroughly off fleek
Bleek is nowhere near Twitter anymore
This is a quiz about
So
Where can I deposit I love it
Did this sucks
And this is Alex's way of trying to get around
The fact that this is not
Come to pass
The the lack of resistance
How but he still wants to hold on to a lot of
The leadership stood down
Jalensky's hanging out with the fraud of frauds
Hollywood people
And and and all the rest of it because
Because
Behind the scene for my sources
Jalensky's actually a Double H
I wouldn't doubt it wow
Wow this is getting interview by Sean Penn
Clearly has not left you've essentially created a folk hero level mythology about himself
Ceramic is unwillingness to back down as a leader
What else is saying is completely out of touch with reality and it's super offences at least in part because it's just Alex baking show
Get up in order to pretend that they real-world matches is
Conspiracy world
Which is very dumb
A dumb world
Yeah this is not letting the truth and reality leave your coverage is having a predetermined conclusion and literally ignored
Ignoring the truth
And making up your own false reality
So you can protect and maintain your predetermined conclusion
It's abusive to the audience and it's pretty much all Alex can do cuz it's politics suck and he has nothing to offer in terms of
Information on here too and I don't believe that it
Necessarily
Bully what's motivating this
Zelensky
Is really doing some great PR were
And
That's a threat
Do Russia and Beyond
Yeah is there food and standing in the world
Certainly is threatened
Bye
Image of
The leadership
That is being
Exhibited by zelensky
And I do think there is a slight piece of this that is trying to
Tarnish or create like
So it's all it's all fake
Sure and I think that there is there is a part of it that is
In in in service of trying to
Retain some image of Buddha
At least
It is much as ours has invested in that is like
The champion against
I mean
There's no way
For you to continue saying that Putin is
The champion of the globalist
After he
Didn't just start a war
And try and take over a country
But also
Lost
Where is is is a loser
Well it's hard for a strong man to look strong and
Especially whenever the guy that you're going up against is
Theoretically
Just a comedian actor
The Mystique or the power behind
He's just some guy I just won't f****** give up and to be clear you know we're recording this middle of the day on
On Sunday
Anythink
Could happen it's not the same
That there is a end to
So we do not know but they're material advantage
Just so I think
That you can still say based on
Just about everybody's expectations
The notion of Russia trying to invade Ukraine
I did not working
Dim the first couple days
Is a win
In terms
Turn of events
Chef
It's supposed to like literally losing
He has not taken over the country easily
Yeah is a law it is it is
The loss of what his
Been his most powerful weapon
Open witches
He looks like
Like he's the
F****** most
Evil supervillain strong man in the world
And he does whatever he wants without anybody getting his way and he can make people disappear whenever he wants
And guess what
If you can't do that
You don't want people to find out
Yeah it is
It hurts
Almost said Charles Schwab
Charles Schwab
I've been here
Close Schwab on the other hand he wants to kill every
And I know
You want to go watch a movie you want to go play pool you and delete you
Enchiladas are steak
Want to go for a hike
What's fun around the local pool
You're not clock swap he wants to kill you
He sees you living on his land
They stole the world your fraud and they want us
And if we let them kill us we deserve it
Survival of the fittest
I don't think he's a fetish
Our species should act like
I think he's with his he's not us
What do you think
You want us to die buddy boy
Well the words of a pallet
13 no
No
No you will die
Politically
Defeat
Until your ideas
Play
Murdering cell
Wonder if that's an intentional strategy
Alex uses to incite his audience towards violence while simultaneously providing cover for himself in terms of plausible deniability
I do appreciate
I do appreciate when you see
A fiction writers hands behind
A character's motivation what are he's just like
Charles Schwab
Cars Plus I broke the dam
Call job
Thanks it's okay
If you just sit down and let him kill you
That's fine
Now I think that too
And then he only thinks it because you'd like it Alex thinks it is you don't like back then
You deserve
Because Alex thinks that
Also cause Rob as Lightning
You have to be real strong with the dark side
Boo-boo poopoo Odessa breaking news alarm
What would happen
I heard it but I thought it was the fire alarm
What is the breaking news
An article has just been posted on natural news
Cam
Yes you share it
Complete
It's by white hats
20 + in one area 30-plus in another
The kill the Spy
Myprotein
Week
And I give you a minute
Spike protein
Very sophisticated
Weighing beholder
Moderna
Come out
And Angela
Nothing like
Well I'm glad I can't wait for this great fall apart now.
This is part of his narrative future cuz it's
So dumb just never going to talk about this one again so good guys
Yeah in the
Virus
Creating community
White hats they made Alma
Macron
As a way to provide immunity for everyone
Wow with the same type of killing the spike protein
I guess that means acures the
Disease cure disease
Right
There's a vaccine disease
Curing
Disease X
But I wouldn't believe this if I hadn't heard it from the health Ranger
What kind of dumb white hat hacker
Are biologist or whatever virus creator
Alright alright
I won't reveal that the whole thing is Eve
Destabilizing
I will just make
Dramatic
Movie asked version of the disease itself bit towards the disease being a team for two people
Of them is like oh my God
I must alert the media and the other one grabbed him by the shirt collar
This is the plot of Cowboy Bebop the movie
They're nanomachines that kill people and then they're like we got to stop this so they make nanomachines
To stop the nanomachines
It's the same f****** thing
Thought maybe I was branching out
Syfy Cowboy Bebop soundtrack
So what's this point
Boudain
Made a call
For the Ukrainian military to
Performative
Yes
Swing
Sagami with level swing right there
Look at this Reuters article that's out right now
Bars at Bloomberg
Calls on Ukrainian military to seize power to better negotiate with Russia
Casinos it's a bunch of bubbles
A bunch of former presidents jockeying for control
Military which is a very smart move
Just be over in 48 hours what do you think
Wow wow
So first of all Alex's Putin going on TV and asking the Ukrainian soldiers to turn on their government and overthrow zelensky
Military coup
Secondarily though
How does he simultaneously expect this to be over in 48 hours
There's a thermonuclear war coming please known since the last year there was big move the China
We're going to make the Takeover
Seems like these two things are
Contradictory
Because they are
Alex has no attention span just gets caught up in talkingshit so when
This caller is in the contact
Loses track of the other ship that he said he starts floating stuff but I was going to end in two days right
On one hand this is the byproduct of Alex not preparing it all
And having no actual position on thing pass knee-jerk reactions
And Hyper Oppositional defiant
On the other hand it's also part of an intentional strategy to overwhelm the audience
With nonsensical
And self-contradictory position
So they can't possibly
Keep track it was actually being set on the show
Except for the feelings but Alex creates a
We've listened to the past week or so the show and I can't really tell you what Alex thinks is happening or not happening because he's been all over the place
He has no key
Consistency except in terms of the feeling that you sell it
He's selling fear
And be all bad he's selling the feeling that Putin is right and is fighting against these globalist Boogeyman that Alex's train the audience to feel
The information itself is constantly changing and being remolded with New Lies
But the emotional core is really what he
Reselling
In terms of this
Performance and you can see how excited he gets like the opportunity to riff with somebody's like oh that's a good one
48 Hours what do you think
I need to stop and be like
How does this
Fit in here would be the best
And worst person to have in a writers were absolutely
Also it's 48 hours later now in the war hasn't ended so chalk that one up on my compilation is rhymes
Predictions of totally wrong
You got a longer
It's not
600 episodes
Going to say it so long
Gaston
Royce White
Who's a farmer basketball player
He's a running for congress in Minnesota
Royce White charges for 2 seconds I really appreciate him
Coming on he just announced a few days ago
But he's running for congress and he's super smart guy
Ilhan Omar
He's a famous NBA player and
Mac guy are all that because he stood up
Everybody and against tyranny and against
The Democratic party and against
Chinese, National leaguer
Two things I need to make totally clear at the first is that Alex doesn't give a s*** about the weeders Edith pretend
Optitex Chinese government
He said on the show in the past that he doesn't care what the Chinese do them if China would just leave him alone
The second thing is Doris one of Mike lindell's pillows if it was running against Allah Tomar so I don't know
If I care
I don't think this is going to be good
For whites campaign to show up on Infowars and this interview could go severely off track
If the topic of racial Justice and White's position on George Floyd comes up
Husky and Alex
See eye-to-eye on the
They tend not to
Here's the deal
Roy's doesn't have a chance of unseating Omar as a republican which is how he's running
Minnesota's 5th District is a Democrat + 29 District so in order for Republican to win
You'd have to basically be running unopposed
Have you even though Omar gets a lot of s*** from the right-wing media she's pretty popular in the home District
You though because there's
Chaos Brewing
In the Minnesota 2022 midterms
There was a chance that we could have gotten a shot
Because there was a fight going on over rediske
Scripting been resolved in time Minnesota was talking about having to have an at-large election
Where the political parties put up a
What field they feel the Slate of candidates
I'm on the top nine vote-getters of all of the candidates woodwinds
Seats in the House
In that situation he
Could possibly have 11 of them along with Omar but
From everything I can tell the redistricting has been resolved so that process
Being done
There's no chance of the fifth district has it doesn't help the Republic
If we wanted to win
He should have ran against Omar in the Democratic primary
He has widespread name recognition as a former NBA player and those she's won her to Democratic primaries by date
Margins
Omar is a bit more vulnerable there than she is in the general like
This appears to be another Doom Congressional candidate showing up on Infowars where Alex will alter
Smelly create the impression that they're so far ahead in the polls and the only way they can lose his cheating
Remember losing Alex will forget about this game until the next election cycle where it'll repeat all over again
Yep that's fun after he loses right will never be heard from again on
No that didn't happen
Laura lubbers name can't possibly be
We ordered only by Rogers.
I'm sure roses going to have a job
He actually has far more in
To Alex's narratives than I would have hoped
That I was looking up I don't I don't know much about him but he was an advocate for mental health
Issues
It is time of the NBA and then he have some involvement with protests in the wake of
George Floyd killing
Until I kind of had this thought that like I maybe this is
Just a guy who
Don't know what he's getting into gogani pool immediately like
I was a huge 40 no
Yep
Like when we had krs-1
So a big interview itself
I don't really care about all that much
But there are a couple things said by Alex
He's trying to argue that
Needs to be
In the in the house deleted
He he he realizes that he's
Complaining about ilhan Omar and AOC
We have to start to be like I don't want no women
Flower
Mexico's a tickets out of control
And you know women are great bunch of women in Congress
And the day we need men to be men again
Do magic carpets for men
White Noise White Royce White. Us
Imagine
Why does Mad Men again
I need men
To stand up and realize it's their response
Ability to be leaders
It's a genetic
Wow
Most of the are all of the house and Congress
It's really
Let me let me ask you a question
When was the last time that there was a female majority in Congress
It wasn't it
Female majority
If it wasn't for the genetic genetics I forgot about them
Everytime I go I can't help but lead something
Every time I've been in Walgreens I've led a revolution
Music Man 76 Trombones man I got them out there
How much does a few more thoughts on this subject that are
Yeah it is
It's deeply deeply misogynistic
And women have their office and women could really want
Women want men to lead on average one
A bunch of power
And any system that sells women being in charge
Doesn't really want women in charge
You are the one who just said you wanted more women in Congress
Idea that he does what he wants to give lip service today
Don't want no women
But yeah if women are in charge that the really just some nefarious plot by another man want somebody to
Push around
Abuse based
Worldview
I bet
That's allowed
I mean that's some Cro-Magnon man s*** right there that's
Well I mean obviously I have a larger Club so I can hit you so I'm the leader it's also
Scared
Call terrified
Speed skater
That's what he's expressing what if women take over and all of the things that I'm a man about don't become important
Anymore
So interview with Royce White
He take some calls and then it's the end of
The show
That's pretty dumb
But he does have one caller that I think is actually worth
Worth bringing attention
Thank you so much for holding
Received
Arizona your first up thank you for holding
A Batman
Swear to God
What you going to do I'm not going to do anything I'm just going to enjoy it I'll be leaving to leave back
I'm going to put my mic down and I'm going to smile.
It's
It's a foregone conclusion
Anyway
Head and things on that
Call themself Mahopac
I know Mick Foley's actually a good dude right
Why did why is he showing up as mankind on Infowars
No it's just a strange dude
God
Yeah so I figured
This episode sucks in a lot of ways and traffic on 10th why not leave on a high note
Whoever whoever he was just killing
And he's revealed
Too clearly that's he is
Supporter of Putin's actions
I just didn't know that Bill Gates
It's created Moderne in order to facilitate
Putin doing weight
I really don't know
Understand what are you even trying to get
Well
Seed NaturalNews is proven right but Omicron was
Invented by
Good
Bioweapon covid-19
Would be a biome
Just because
Just cuz you believe the person who's realizing it
Thinks it's going to
Be good
Irresponsible
Something goes wrong with
Whitehat Omicron
Bio weapon that's been released his against the Geneva Convention
XX
Has there ever been a 100% effective virus
I would have made I mean like what exactly
There's no way that you can make a virus
It's like at Omicron
I'm sure even if it's to destroy other viruses
Without also eventually causing some problems
Two people
That's how
Yeah but it was
A good guy
It's a stupid stupid I really want to draw sharp Oak
I think we achieved that the
The video that you posted about his prediction is full of s***
And if you really Trace down the sources you see the the actual intentional
Misrepresentation of the things that he said in the original episode in order to create the appearance of predictive power
And now he's using that to gain
More credibility for his
Justifications
Of Putin's invasion of
And I think it's important
And something that
Should not
Be forgotten
Time goes on he's very much 100%
For Putin invading Ukraine should be Albatross ship
Around his neck so it should
So he will be back in deep
My friend oh yeah but until then
It's knowledge right.com
But until then
Emilio Emilio I'm busy X Clark I am doctor marbles
The sex robot