Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge right now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Exit for the altar of Celine talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
A Jordan is behind the bastards this week
Nice to have a nice time and sit down
What did I what did I would have liked
Grand old time to talk about the end of
I don't know I guess Christianity being nice
The beginning of something else
Something
No spoilers comes up on Thursday
It's it's a lot of us this week if you want
If you want Dan and Jordan content boy
Everyday
Ikea shudder at the thought of someone listening to me
Every day is starting out white
Overburdened our voices
Check that out enjoy Good Times
Yeah absolutely well that was going to be my pride aside so you stole that from me
But my bright spot is very stupid
But I have
Recently at the best
If no one
And without telling anyone embarked on a little comic strip adventure of my dog Jake
Series of a little situation
And I finished
Story
Again without telling anybody
And Jake is eaten by
So it is it's a tragic end
Is a mutiny that did it or no
Involved in the mutiny
Oh no she's just a grump
Maybe she'll have some Adventure suit
Go to music
But that was my bright spot
To take them where they come
Today we were talking about
7th 2022
Episode
To do Sunday and Monday
But Sunday there's too much
Talkabouttd
Oh man this is something else awfully
I'm not saying something that we've been on over the past week
This is a mess
And I will get to it
A book forwarded let's say hello to somebody walks
So first I know you're listening to this while you're working so
Keep crossing your thesis Dan and Jordan give you their full support
You're not a policy wonk
Thank you very much I refuse to let you speak for me though I don't know anything about this
Support
Continuing to meet
None dare call it charcuterie thank you so much
Thank you very much
You would think the globalist would stop writing their plans
I don't seem to be at Platt hold a hat
Text Keith
AKA
Bukavu globalist
I have
Risen above
Miami
Go take a little break you down
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe the next few moments
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Real walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Only what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
Apologize to
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
A lot better
I don't know I'll let you decide
Wow if there's there's a question
Our last episode we talked about
That video that Alex dude about his
Supposed
The prediction of the war predict beginning so much traffic with
The Alex crowd for the Auntie Alex crowd
Vivi whole like he predicted the war
They're there now saying wow he did it I think that I've seen far too many people tweeting nonsense about
I have this prediction is proof that he's a Russian
Here is getting information session intelligent
Anything with the
The
Deposition
It's the Dario could not handle being so it's not blurry
For an intelligence operation
She just got to have
I wouldn't if I were in charge of a country's like intelligence assets
I would dress her organization
No
Engage Metallica's materials off of difficult because it draws you in
People who want us
See his stupid predict
Video is proof that he works for rush hour already passed the point where Alex wants to lure them to
Because they've adopted his fundamental
Premise namely that he
He did actually predict this war
Whether you see that video and hailed him as a prophet or you accuse him of being a foreign asset either way you're playing his game
Both conclusion speeding to be his own attention economy and involve the belief that the things that Alex Azar worth
To do and not just random bulshit
He throws out so be cautious caution people
Do not fall into the opposite trap
Begin from the Occam's razor point of this man is always lying
I don't I don't I don't know if that's why is either because I
Think I could in a blind you too
I mean Alex Jones
I understand that it could blind you to me
I tried to call a taxi was applying I think it's a process though
If you can train yourself to 22
Hasty conclusion
It's just more of a if you can
Set the practice of like okay what is this
Information
I is exhausting
But it's it's
It is better
So
We start here
With Alex talking about how
You know Russia's kind of restrained
Restrained
What you're seeing is a
Massive
Conventional
WWII Style
Invasion
Of Ukraine
And I'm not lying eyes in the Russian
Enter Putin butt
Wanted
To clear out
Those areas they would
Just dropped heavy Munitions on
A cluster bomb
Because I don't want
A high civilian
Facing massive casualties
With their infantry going in
To the areas
People that
Guns after
Dave
That's Riverside
I told her being fired up
Large Russian
That's all
From what I've been seeing I would imagine
There's 20,000
Walking Dead Russian
Trips not 5,000
Like
And I would imagine they're also
Thousands of dead
Ukrainians
But your aunt never be hearing about that
I have very little patience for Alex saying that he doesn't lionize food method whole pageant last week
Alex right now is trying to moderate is insane admiration for Putin it's just an affectation
Putting on because Putin is abating
Sovereign neighbor
Things are getting a little
A little bit
Seriously
Service the moment that this conflict
Is however concludes
Alex will immediately baby icon like
Well poop got a raw deal on this her or whatever maybe before you will be will give lip service to
Just threats flying around that's the time to be
Support
Civilians are being killed
It's time to pretend to be a neutral party
So you don't end up having people
You feel bad for supporting the guy who's doing the invasion
It's entirely possible that the fatality counts are higher than what's being reported now
But pretty much every report you see on that on the number of
Casualties includes that caveat
The well hostilities are ongoing
It's really hard
To get precise number
Really take too much of an issue with Alex's insinuation that the current numbers may be low
I think it's speculation of how far off the reported numbers are might be a little loose
Morally objectionable is his claim that you'll never hear about the higher death toll
My God
Alex is so addicted
Conspiracies that he just inject them into almost every sentence that comes out of
His mouth
And being an idiot but there's an element of this that sex
Pretty clear strategic
The tactic designed to train is listeners
To be distrustful of every source of information that isn't him
Or something with Alex's indicated as one of the good ones like
Gateway pundit or NaturalNews under question until I authoritatively
Give you the belief that you should have
Yes yes it's super toxic stuff and it's just the audience in a bubble
Where they can't take seriously any reporting or information that proves the central Infowars narrative to be wrong
Alex has to spread distrust
Of all other media sources
Because he's rightly scared that if his audience actually took in a broader scope of sources for information
Phoebe Fox
And so one of his primary even subconscious behaviors is the concert
Bentley inject
Insinuation
For outright claims that you'll never know
The truth about various things
Epsom
Not good
I listen to this
And especially that
And I mean
Is something f***
Stop about
Being a part of the American
Media
Consumer base
Insofar as
Because
The United States has committed so many war crimes
Either lied about it or
To skate or tried to hide or any number of those things
Alex can say you know
When they go in there they want to Lowe's
Civilian death toll so they don't cost
Starbomb
Culture bombing a f****** city is
Warcry
I'd literally War crime you can't just block they don't want to have a high school
It's wrong fundamental level
No I agree
I agree
I think that
To the point
That there's a
Find criticism tomatoes
U.s. foreign policy a pig
The wars that we had
It doesn't really have a bearing on
Whether or not this is right and you're saying that I'm just saying how the media
Allows us to speak of it as though it's not something that should be treated as
You cannot cross that line
Not like
Oh they don't want to I mean like literally
You cannot
And the problem is it
We have and that doesn't bear own piss
But that does bear on how we talked about
Nature Institute
I have guard rails for the what
To come up in
United media
That's what I'm not like this is a both sides or anything along those
Or some people
Kind of argumentation
So Alex believes their propaganda going around
And boy is there
The level of propaganda
But the Russians and NATO and
Staggering levels
But I got to say as usual the last.
Clearly top Russia
In
Bishop going on over here
And then you got them
Demonizing
Either
As a profoundly stupid position for Alex to have it even he knows that what he saying
Is bulshit that's just a desperate attempt to justify Putin's invasion
Both sides are equally guilty argument
Talk about
So weird how this position is evolves from real bombastic yelling about Putin being great to cowardly middle-of-the-road
Bulshit about both sides having problems
This isn't a serious position Alex has you just knows that he can get his audience to tears of Justified
Journalists and protesters
To his own cancel culture narratives
But he's trained the audience to respond to
Sure the Patriots have caused some violence but
Black lives matter is called some violent protest too wide open
That's essentially the game between play dear
Uses established talking points as a crutch
To get the audience closer to being on who decide that they would be
If Alex were just reporting actual information
And it's fine I guess
I mean it was it is one of those
Propaganda effort
It's that is
Not aimed at like oh okay
We want you to be on Russia's
Steam it's more aim.
We don't want you to be on Ukraine
We want you to be on in the middle
Love like
But you know what this this just
You know whatever it is
Yeah I would say that it is less a attempt
To make
Gluten look
Good
And it is an attempt to make Putin look less bad
Keep you from condemning what puta
In the way that you should
Exactly also I think it's
Open insult to say
I think Alex accidentally insulted whatever is like as usual the US wins the propaganda War again
As usual your haircut and Putin short
He's got he's had some wins
But I think it would probably let that go though
You think I don't know him
We're going to talk to somebody who does know personally later
But also a liar
Welfare
So Alex decides that it's time to
Let's reset the narratives
Let's try and come up with a way to rewrite the story of what I've been saying
This whole time I didn't
But here is what I did today
Very clear
Hi there
I said that
Before the invasion
And I said that
Going to try to stage cyberattacks
Shelves
And that once they've done that they could really ratchet up things
With the rocks
Khalid
2A Regional
Nuclear war
And then probably a full-scale nuclear war
I'll because of you
Just a satanic
Evil running our world
I mean we're really close to that
Who is probably going to be Oz talking point moving forward that these were his positions
Incisor was related to the standoff and then the invasion of Ukraine
Of course it's all a lie
There wasn't really a consistent position Alex's have through any of this time by Q waffle.
Set up all over the place but there were some elements
It popped up more regularly and you can
Use as kind of a
A guiding through line through what he was talkin to
What about
Points on this whole thing was on February 8th
Clip posted in a Daily Mail article
Of the speech of the Putin gave any decided
The boot was on the brink
The firing nukes
To destroy all of Europe
I enjoyed that narrative quite a bit because it allowed him to
Send it too long and vivid descriptions of how nuclear war
Because of abortion or whatever
Even prior to this but escalating as the tensions Rose between Russia and Ukraine Alex's Central theory was that a false flag
I was going to be run by in order to gain support for
During the midterms or take attention away from the trucker convoys which Alex was insisting was
The key to defeat the global
This is the narrative he was selling on February 11th on the day that Biden announced that he would not send troops into Ukraine to fight
Because that would be a World War
If you put this together with all the other pieces it would take an hour to go through I'm just going to give you the answer for my view
But there's one Big Slice of the
Equation
You think they're just going to let us be them on this whole
Can go away your crazy they're going to start a damn War
Oh my gosh these people
Make me sick
Are Alex's coverage is mostly about justifying food and take military action in The Don Bosco region because
According to Oz fake version
Interview Soros did Ancien
Soros had actually overthrown
Do you want
And brag time she can just put it on screen
He parroted all food in stock
Complaints about how did NATO was attacking tamaskan look hot
I wish Alex reported as areas that shoot
Be part of Russia or were rightfully being occupied by Russia
He repeated the claims that the kindergarten was shelled false-flag pulled by Ukraine
He claimed that Western forces were going door-to-door killing people in an ethnic cleansing of the Dawn boss region
He did literally everything you could to make sure that the audience
GameStop that is violet
Did Breakout it only happened because the West was so evil
Headed for spoon to respond
He was literally saying that on February 8th
Here's the bottom line
When they launched offensives in the east
And then now in tube
Other areas of Russia
Control
When they finally attack Crimea the Russians
We'll have a Redline
And that Putin will be deposed
Hardliners in
Putin's being driven into a corner
Be induced
Which will then be called
Details here and there and things would move around
When was pretty clear into
Consistent
Any fighting was to be seen by the audience as NATO and Biden
Fault and if we did something look bad on paper
It might be a false flag and even if it's a real thing he did he only did it because the Western Powers forced him
He would have loved
Did not do it
There's nothing he wants to
Do less to do than war crimes
Soros is Madeline crime man
He was going to recognize the nest
21st and Alex was beside himself
How much you supported
What he pretended boutin was saying
He's apologizing for communism is saying that he just wants to enjoy the free market with Ukraine
Woohoo
Absolutely not bitten off more than he could chew at any point up
This is this point according to Alex in
That wasn't even Alex's dance
After the invasion
24th Alex had to deal with the fact that he
Buy Russian propaganda and they Putin was definitely planning to invade the whole country
Well thank publicly that he wasn't going to do that which Alex repeated as truth to his audience
But even at that point when Alex has shown to have been very wrong
He still wasn't saying the Putin had been off more than he could chew
Alex was very insistent that already won the war because he
Paid off Ukrainian leadership
The Russian forces would just be up against
No resistance at all
These troops raise
Russian flag in Ukraine A-Z tanks
What you come
From the East
Ando tanks
From Belarus
Dinner
Deeper into the nation
And there is
Because just like the US
The Iraqi leadership in Gulf War 1
For 2
Generals
You see that Putin is already done
Work
And is already paid off you
Ukrainian military
And that's why the rush
No they can roll
Rite Aid
Because that's how real war is done
Alex never said that Putin have bitten off more than he could chew
He was constantly expressing solidly pro-putin talking points that revolved around the idea that food needed to take over the
Dawn boss
In order to protect the Russian
Can speakers there
Even after Putin invited the entire country Alex was rationalizing his actions by pretending the whole thing was a piece of theater
Where's olinsky was a double agent in on it with Putin and there will be no Ukrainian resist
This b******* you saying I was
Attempt to whitewash his actual position
Because he doesn't want to own any of that ship moving forward
He wants his initial positions in the lead-up to The Invasion to appear far more moderate than they actually work and the reason
This pretty off
I will grant that Alex has been saying that there's going to be a cyber false-flag for a really long time even prior to this standoff
Again our last episode of play the clip from July of last year where he and Leo zagami were insisting that
False flag cyberattack was right around the corner
This isn't actually a meaningful prediction though and it's just Alex laying the groundwork so in case there ever is a cyber-attack he needs to
Pretend isn't real
You can claim that he was predicting a false-flag cyberattack at Vista
What is a f****** year-ago everyone assumes
Will happen sooner or later so it's only like that is going to happen
A lot of vulnerabilities
Is there a lot of Nefarious people who are pretty good with computer
It's not a good prediction so much as it is like this is how
Annabelle write a story in advance should ever happen in a way that's inconvenient for my narrative
So I can pin the blame on my imaginary enemy
Bingo Charles Schwab
Beautiful computer machine Charles
Deep blue it's Charles Schwab
Gotcha
Smile back to the 27th Alex talks about the headline for the show
Aaron's the world
Is on the brink
A nuclear war
As NATO Ramsey Farms
Against
Russia
Think about that ladies
Gentleman
And we have the
Video of him singing
Unlike corporate
Established
Globalist
Media
Are there Empire lies
When I tell you
The clip
This is kind of Alex's orwellian moment
Russia is invading Ukraine but the situation is really that the west and NATO are attacking Russia Vice
Supported Ukraine at loving sanction
There's no other way to really look at this other than Alex
Just hates Western Tubac
Perseus
See the International Community thrown in
The chaos
Also
You can f*** right off with this unlike the media I actually play clips bulshit
What the media who doesn't play today
Nobody's exactly
It's just a petulant lashing out against be poorly Define nebulous group everyone supposed to hate the dreaded media
Again this is just a strategy Alex used to soda
Distrusting all sources that are not himself or things he has ordained as good
He can never really miss an opportunity to take a
Swipe to remind you the listeners that he's the real journalist
Or at least eat that until he's under out the man there's a
Completely different story
Entertain also Empire of Lies
What is a quote
Upfront
Thought that Sebring use a great term
Who is
It is just like
You can't do that
We've had
We have novels we have novels where people do that and there's a bad people how can you do that and not be immediately like oh yeah
You can do it
You should just be a little bit less of a coward in on your position
Well I mean
Yeah
He wants to pretend he has this moderate distance from things
But he's
She's just acting as
Amalfi's
Citymd
That's what
You know people who are like always a Russian asset or something like that
I think he's more like them
Weirdos who are like Elon Musk
Superfan reply guy he was still on Twitter
In so many different parts of his life you know with the anti-communist
Intelligentsia
G Edward Griffin
Who are in the John Birch Society and the same thing is true of the militias
Is out over these weirdos
I do exercises with guns Underwood
Like it it's just like how he's Fanboys out over Star Wars
It's just a higher Stakes
And also he claims that he does
It's just kind of a consistent thing with these
John Birch Society ding-dongs militias into a strongman dictators
Yeah it is it is weird for him to claim that he's the tip of the spear and yet at the same time have been has been there
Perpetual follower and hanger-on
He's in that he's a retinue guy he's he's not
He's not in the lead of s***
No not the tip of the spear at all
Sunday was the day that they were supposed to play that documentary about Alex on Sienna
What time he's on air I believe the units but it already gone out that it wasn't going to happen
I was just pretending that that has not happened
That it's still going to air
And yet something
Complaints about it in a bit of a high road
CNN 4-week
Advertising every break
Purposely
Alex Jones special
Tonight 10 p.m. Eastern
9 p.m. central that I was going to watch live and comment on here
But my family is more important
World War 3 is more important
Crisis
And it's a
Feen
Foreseeing into are something like
During a time like this
NFL,
Get more viewers
I'm having small audience
And already know it's regurgitated lies they sent me
Questions on YouTube
Respond to it
The questions was a bunch of made-up malarkey
First of all malarkey
Come on let's go Alex
Second they haven't been
The press release announcing that special was on February 22nd
They've are commercials around that point
And it's really easy for Alex's I was like well I was going to go over it but my family is more important
After they've already canceled it right
Real smooth Above This
Hold me back family I wouldn't I would go hard on these people but you got to hold me back
That's a little a little sack
So Alex let's talk about Putin's speech
And he's not being clear about this because
There was
Before this the announcement that Putin was putting his nuclear deterrence on high alert
Alex is referencing
He's actually talking about is
The speech were Putin declared war
That's what I would have assumed
This is an older speech released a couple days old speech that Alex is referring to
We also
The way he talks about it is amazing
Russia hasn't it
Ethos
Invasions by the Huns
4:00 of years
Invasions by the Muslims
For over a thousand years
Zen Napoleon and Hitler
And
20 million Russians died in World War II
2 million Germans died
Russell KB
670,000 people
In World War II
Or
Something's house in Vietnam and everybody
Felt it knows it was a real war
Russia
Million
In World War II
And so it is in the Consciousness and I can
Said he said
People always try to bully us and always flipping her boards and weapon
And for the first time ever Russia is not going to wait till you attack
47 minute
Address
He also says you want to sexualize our children are a bunch of pedophiles
Hollywood
Devil worshippers
You want to destroy
The men and women of the family and we're done
You want a nuclear war
I mean it's unbelievable
Supposed to say
So that could was fascinating because it's specifically designed
Two deceptive ideas in the audience
This is mine
The first is Russia's history of being invaded makes the idea of Putin invading another country somehow more acceptable or
Understandable self-defense when you've been robbed 300 times in your past
You know the moment that somebody looks like they're going to rob you
You run them down with your truck
It makes perfect sense it's just another in a long string of Alex's very clear attempt
To justify Putin
Invasion without having to take on the intellectual and moral responsibility
I'm giving a full-throated endorsement
The 2nd
Interesting to me because Alex is doing is lying about Putin speech in order to create the image that he threatened
Nuclear war inspired by the very same thing that Alex feels
Are Central to his battle against
That's the global it's so weird
Obviously Putin didn't say though
He said he wanted to protect the first
Alex says those things haha
I'm fairly certain food would be assassinated immediately if he were to go up and give a speech about ready and nuclear weapons also
You want nuclear war the f****** go while spouting off a bunch of Alex's and Niche culture-war complaints
Bros bros
We have to take out Hollywood they worship the devil
The feelings the audience has towards
Hey Monty Putin
If you're an Infowars listener you recognize all of those talking points
Except the globalist
The pedophile trying to sexualize children
Hollywood is run by devil worshipers that the globalist want to destroy men and women in the family
They recognize that because they're things that Alex yells all the time
Time and the audience has been trained to believe that Alex
These things
Is a form of him fighting for them and their very lives
There's no way to slice this other than to say that Alex want the audience to not only admire and support Putin
They want he wants them to view him as a person is motivated by and fighting for the same things that Alex is
I'm has
Been all this time
And you know Alex is a hero right
So is Putin
You can't you can't get somebody to go from
Auntie interventionism
War is bad
To immediately be like
Absolutely has to murder all of these people in order to protect himself from the West
Do you have to have an intermediate step where you say
His grievances are real
You know I have trained you over the course of
I never born
Then the lives of any
One man or woman
Who's the f*****-up mentality but it's really not too far off from some of the ways we've seen Alex frame Putin in the past
What makes this particularly troubling is that Alex isn't playing this rhetoric in response to news that Putin has raised the alert level
Level of nuclear weapons
It's really hard to tell what's going on with Alex and what's Behind These
Completely insane things he saying this week but
It kind of feels like him getting his audience
Seether
Support the idea of using nukes or to rationalize
After the fact that
You know they may not like
Did Putin use nukes
Globalist to water destroy men and women just like him no choice I didn't have anything to do
It kind of feels like a pre-emptive getting you ready to justify it
Massive Slaughter
Whatever the case is here this was one more disturbing Clips I've heard on Alex's show in a bit
Shocking and disgusting clothes with this was psychologically worried
This involves Alex
Clearly talking about himself when discussing poop
Trying to get the audience to believe that Alex's words were coming out of boutin's mouth
I also think the laughing at the end there was Alex
Speak surprised that he went that far
I kind of suspect that he even shocked himself
With his ability to go that low
Yeah
I mean
You have to also
Consider that he has to find some way to justify to himself
That he's for Putin murdering all these
You know
Like he knows
What really happened
There's no there's no way that you cannot know and still, like this school are of some
Right bro
Vulpix
Batman
Wow how do you
You wake up and go like yeah
I'm going to be on that guy
You have to find the number of ways
Is to do that that's really key is to convince yourself
But you're not actually
On this dispersed
One of the ways you do that is pretend that you just want to stay out of it
Above The Fray
This is a Slavic
Civil war going on
And I study history I'm addicted to it
And a slob just like the Japanese hate the
Chinese and vice versa
Swampert always killing each other
And they're always doing this
Just gone for over a thousand years
And it's a Slavic Civil War
Are B you just stay
The hell out of it
Ladies and gentlemen
On the Crips and bloods shooting
Each other in
La weekly
Need to stay out of it
We have
Knock yourselves out
But make no mistake
George Soros and others I'll play the clip
We come back
B Lipton
Soros
And the New World Order responsible
Okay because Soros
Has ordered the Ono
Cuz he paid for
Because he was there
Yeah
I think that this is not
The mark of neutrality everything he did is Justified because everything they did is
Yeah yeah
I just think you have a situation where the argument is pro-russia it is much
Is it saying don't get involved
In terms of sending military aid to people who are being invaded
And that is
Explicitly
Pro
Putin
Yeah
Not
Is
Taking Rochester absolutely you can't you can't just be like oh man you know it's one of those civil wars that they
I have every so often
Uamee he's trying to also get you nothing
R-Truth
Just be like hey
You know what if they want to kill all of each other
That's none of your business
Don't give a s*** that
Putin invaded a country don't care it's just another civil war that these people have always had
Yeah it's
Trying to make where he's like I am
I'm not
Into this I'm just seeing Alside
Is so fragile
And it's really clear
But that's the impression that he's trying to give on this Sunday episode
So Alex Pei
He tries to layout why Russia has a legitimate case
Does a clip of Soros
Stop run. The car is interview CNN from how many years ago
I was eight years ago about overthrowing the government of Ukraine for money which she wasn't
Just b*******
The other piece of evidence Alex has a clip that clip of Biden saying he was threatened
To withhold Aid unless
Ukraine fired that you cry the corrupt prosecutor
That's it that's
Log the evidence Alex has
Is tobacco Putin's legitimate claim
That Ukraine is a poppet of Soros sunglass
Justify
Everything well that's the angle
From the Russian perspective right of the Ukrainian perspective perspective
He just gives this
Justification for why
Russia
What do this
Pieces of evidence that he provide just b*******
Man
We have an entire f***
18 amendments
Devoted to not letting a soldier into your f******
Can house man
That's
Real number
Alex Alex
You wouldn't fight for that one but it seems I feel like it's
Not having a soldier quartered in my f****** office 3rd Amendment absolutist
So the Russian soldier comes to my house
It's totally fine for me to fight back
So that works quarter
Oh my God I'm so relieved that is a third amendment
I got worried
I need to memorize the order of these Amendment
So Alex is he's pretending that he's going to give all side and talk about all this you know it's
Fraud
Claims act all tough
Shipping $10 of weapons
All these Russian held areas in the Russians
You're just like okay I guess we'll attack
Proxy government
Pedagogy
TV star
It was the president as the
Dad's the TV star host
And then I can stall him and do all this
And Russian went crazy
Axel F
Always doing whatever they wanted a Viking
Just a couple days ago not knowing who he is
Adversary see this
And it scares them even more but they're such a competent leaders they said well screw it
And put the shutdown
Jackson congratulation
And the podium is yours let me pull this out
But okay
Sage presence camp
So that's why
What
Okay
Today's Alex has claimed that he's going to show the Ukrainian argument and the Russian
180 side but you just played the sauros inviting Clips they're the
Conspiracy should we just talked about
Just trying to justify the argument that Russia is cool to invade
Clearly
Making more justification
I was just trying really hard to do literally everything in his power to create the feeling in his audience
This invasion was absolutely Justified
And everything bun does is good wow
Occasionally
Could do this
Just wants a plausible deniability
It probably really good strategy on his parts
The feeling that he wants in his audience and he's supporting Putin's agenda
The same time
Creating a number of Clips are you saying that he isn't in favor of this
Never needs to pretend he was against the invasion in the future
I'm going to Paper Trail
I thinks he can take out of context and put in the compilation that people be tricked by in the future
Texas is doing to trans youth right now Russia has a better argument that they should invade
It would be tough
The rest of the country would be stoked about it I don't know where Russia would start
Mexico cool Mexico's their own country as we heard of that
Cuz they're not with the globalist so I guess I have to hang out with Canada do go up to Alaska have to take Alaska
Skippers
Trudeau is weak
So this could happen but then you got to go all the way down
From that yeah that stuff
At self
Give me a long walk
Yep
Too bad there's not the Bering land bridge
So this
This is this is
Weird Alex is talking about how
People in USSR Soviet to always
Ben
Double-crossed
In the past sure
Like Hitler screwing over Stalin
Just like Hitler
Installing
In the early 1940s had a deal
Nobody should hear up amongst
And of course
Hitler then double-cross.
That's what these criminals always do
Can't believe Hitler would
And things being shipped in
And prepared
Too attractive
NBC's The immorality of the West
He talked about it
You talk about
Nobody
Going to shower
One way or another whether the whole damn speech we have
This is again making reference
Do the the speech where Putin was declaring war
Bead
This is nothing but
Justifications
It is
Sweetly like we needed to do this totally
Everything is a everything he's doing is right that is all that's going on explain to me how history
Three of Hitler betraying you
Justifies invading Ukraine
That's not the question that I asked
I give up OK Google
So Alex is you have this situation where
Ohio
There's an invasion going on Soros is instigating everywhere it's all his fault
The West
America
We had a lot of freedom
Sure and we built them up
Make a reserve
Right like the third amendment
But they're running out man or running out of freedom
And I might down for this because that leads Alex to some
Some troubling
I tried to explain.
For a long long time
So free and so open the door.
Skating don't get out much
McDaniel redbud
All of that shaved up
Freedom all that shaved
Liberty in all that saved up
Security
That we had in the bank lady
The gentleman
Is almost gone now
At a certain point there's probably no reason to talk about
I'm going to go
I'm not mad I just want to go meet my family
Enjoy yourself
I'm out here
Just can't do this
I can't pretend anymore I can
Can't go along with it
Destroy all planets
Stop
Prepare too much
Okay that's that's that's what's going on
I think you really see Alex's
In trying times
Real real Rock
I'm telling you I am starting to think
That may be the amount of effort it takes to twist your brain to a place where it's okay for
Rakuten to invade and murder of a lot of people scary cat gonna really f*** your head up yeah and especially if
If you want to try and just do it without
Doing any work yeah if you don't care at all
Just make them up on the Fly improvising rationalization for the stuff is probably pretty
Have a writers room for that level of difficulty
Yeah
Yeah but like man
Globalist
Alex is walking over it he's done maybe there's nothing you can do
I'd like SiriusXM
Action about that sure
What does Satan do
After
The planet has been destroyed
Terraform
Everything
So you can start all over again
Oh I don't know isn't it
Wasn't childhoods like at the end of the like
The aliens
Could only breathe if the like the enviromed was degraded
I would believe that they like breathe sulfuric acid or something
,
Yeah great I bet I would
Push came to shove that's what you want to do
Blow it up
Maybe maybe
Maybe maybe we should all just die right away the planet
And maybe that's the best
I mean I'm not going to blame God if
That there's big nuclear flashes and then we're all dead men
Over with
Hollywood need to be gone
I mean don't
New York
You know
And I know there's a lot of good people there
Stop.
Seriously
But you know
The children don't deserve to die song
I shouldn't even sit here in
Hypothetical you say
Are you I mean what is the point of having the Book of Revelation
If you're going to be like maybe God will just kill us this way
Should you be more relaxed
It's about nuclear warrior-like but look it's not in the f****** book so guess what no big deal
Fairly relaxed
Inasmuch as
This is just a little childish outbursts
What this is is a manifestation of him being in a bad mood
Right maybe hungover
Sure
Probably
Really wrestling with how much
There is to talk about and how little he knows about the subject that is a problem
Just lashing out
Maybe gacha
What about the children
Buckets
So Alex ends up
He's gone
How many are tape and I'm not sure.
Concern
Family
Next week
I heard that before
And just all of this is
Saturday
Because I think that's the right thing.
It's not even talk about it.
Look at it
A synonym for you
Neither Liars
For the whole world burns down
Close down there like trying to stop somebody who's trying to stop it and line
I got all these clothes smaller
Anywho
I want to know this stuff
Probably don't
Jesus
What a second loser
Who is this
Going to blow up everything maybe you don't want to hear me riff about a Gateway pundit article after
I should be with my family but I'm going to take next week off
No one else but Owen Shroyer to read Gateway pundit head well and you will miss him when there's no one else thought I would try as you will
Well I did that is true
Stupid
They just reveal how unequipped to use to
Deal with
Maybe serious material absolutely he's very capable of dealing with abstract
Nonsense
That doesn't mean anything
I think he's fine whatever they're just bees like vague things like
Palace Intrigue about the Trump Administration
It's kind of fun poisoning him
Yeah but little spy novels he's ready even to some degree the election
Conspiracies like
The audit is going according to plan
North Korea
There's there's all that kind of stuff
It kind of works for him cuz
The stakes of it aren't really real
I even he didn't think that January 6th was going to happen
Subway
It's
It's kind of like
He can do that now there's actually a country getting it invaded by a nuclear power
In a geopolitical
A pickle
Alex is dumb
Too lazy to
To possibly even engaged so you see him act like this
Yeah that is something that
Like when you when you talk
About the CNN documentary like I don't want something that's going to portray him as big
Bad Evil kind of masterminded it's like yeah
Cuz listen to this s***
This is not an evil mastermind this is a whiny teen
Yeah
This was an evil mastermind
Everyday be able to handle it
So he comes back
After the next break
Cuz he just actually
He storms off
For like the last couple minutes of this segment forgot the commercial
Low blood sugar
And the crow
But I'm not
You're not something I'm not
I really care I'm really informed really involved and I'm
With all the
Stuff going on in the world
I know the globalist nine times out of ten of the ones like
Nephews
They're endangering all of our
Lives in our children's lives
Gnarls Barkley
Please show
I wasn't crazy because I didn't know enough
If I do too much
The show
My word
Good about not blowing up on here
I don't think that's true
Did Gnarls Barkley do a Las Vegas residency for a while that I didn't know probably they have like a Celine Dion
I'm kind of style attraction going on there
What's up Miss speaking is one thing
Alex Jones has been apologizing to the crew for 24 f****** year-long
Set alarm
Everything is the globalist Fault 9 times out of town today
What even talkin about
None of this is real
I think he said something accidentally that revealed one of those classic paradox
Cuz like
Everything I tell you is a lie
You know like he's saying I'm not here to protect I'm not pretty
Pretending like I'm something I'm not
Where you like
Yes you are
But
That is who you are
So you aren't
It's one of those kind of situation could be it could also be used
Pretending
For a long time and then just is that now
You become you become the thing you pretend to
That where
Sure
Also to
This isn't
Like someone who cares too much
March
This is not the behavior of someone who cares too much
This is someone who is
Supposed to be doing their job
That's right because they're in,
Things aren't like why do I need geometry because they care too much about geometry and what about math
Samantha this is already been proven
Anyway
Alex going to start
Okay good
It's a little late from the beginning
Going to start over and I'm going to plow through the nose
You have to understand something later
There's also a great frustration
Justice stop right here
Is so horrible
And I refuse to rationalize what's going on in like not making it
Migraine
It's the Stockholm Jean
Where was I being abused I can make it
Excuses for it
And and
Can you just go along with it
Being awake
I don't have the Stockholm change
And instead with people are enslaving me and my family and enslaving you
I get extremely upset
Do you know what happened
They had three more universities with
Crispr Gene editing
The damn covid-19
But it is one
Hundred percent made the lab
100% made by Madonna
There are more universities coming out with evidence of covid-19 Aiden the lab in
That's all nonsense that's just the last episode
Mo3
Studies have come out the Tracy epidemiological history of covid
And all of them
Very strongly point to a natural origin of the virus coming from the Hunan
Seafood mark
We'll have to wait until those go through the review process but they take different approaches to looking at the question and each strongly suggests match
Florajen
And strongly point away from the idea that it came from a lab
The personalizing of this stuff that Alex is doing is really scary though
The dumb conspiracies about covid being a bioweapon
Kind of abstract enough that most listeners in the past generally see it as kind of a detective game they were playing
These evidence
Pieces together they could finally stick at
The gate
Proven 100% that they killed your family yet this on the other hand is inside
Alex is having this emotional Outburst in such a
Personal contacts didn't hit the audience permission to deal with covid like that too
A lot of people have friends or family who have died from the virus and this is modeling the sort of response that appropriate
Have about that
Screaming and yelling about how your friends were murdered by the globalists like
Clothes swap
It's a bad sign of things to come and honestly if nothing else it reflects how unhinged Alex is on this episode
He is
Losing it
Another problem though
Is it there's an intention behind
He's building up this emotion
What are the things that emotion and then uses that to
Power another machine
And you can see after building up this emotion
He uses it
To go in another Direction
And debilitating other people I care about
Hitman all they start a war with Russia I'm so sick of Bill Gates
I'm so sick
Barack Obama Hillary Clinton
Anymore
Vladimir
How does fingerprints on a bioweapon
I don't have a dog in that fight
The Russians messing with me
You know why they call me a Russian the Russian czar
Power down there crap either
The fakin way over-the-top emotional outbursts that Alex
Perform there was essentially in service of creating strong feelings
But then he could shift over to being used to justify Putin
Invasion of Ukraine
It's a tactic where he's trying to create this very strong negative feeling about these globalism
Villains that he pretends he's fighting
Which is so much stronger than any feeling the ADI
How could you come down on Putin
Make this bio-weapon how could you come down on it when these villains exist
Started the war
I hate Hillary Clinton Obama close Schwab
The people who started the war
Definitely those people the globalist
Like Obama and Hillary Clinton and Klaus Schwab
Kind of an outburst is an indication Metallica's new busy
This being on are incapable of
Responsibly discussion discuss
These sorts of very important
Misuse
I am too I think it's pathetic
Yep and it goes even further off the rails if you can believe that
He rushes The New American
The capture America
You can't have a free Open Country
Cuz everybody else might want
See what's happened
Alicia love these ran
Because I don't
Because they got
Chateau de I was going to sell to cover the news
And we're going to go through all of it the next day
Okay
Russian is the new American
Is is
Yeah that's real real real real bad
This conversation supposedly happening on this episode
Deacon
Really say anything
That would be more of a way of Alex saying Putin everything everything is the best
Your patriotism pretending to be impartial
And like
I'm not for this Invasion or whatever
But suck
Bulshit amazing thing that I find
Fascinating about that clip he's
It does appear that Alex
Can't do these Rats on it
Yeah that's true I feel like there's a physical aspect to it he seems winded unable to
Have the lung capacity
To just do that
Second
You could hear a couple points where his brain was trying to find
The next thing
To like
Where is before there would be a bit more fluidity between
I think his brain and his body aren't able to do this anymore
But he also knows that
Kind of wanted the only things that people need him
Before yeah I mean if that was
If that was that
That's the type of audition tape
That would really get your ex
You know
That's the
Quite the performance that you want to
I want to have the world C
Maybe maybe take that one a few more time
5 cm
Oh boy
You got to know your strengths
When you lost your fastball come out
Clayton Kershaw new when he lost his fastball changed his pictures got it better adjusted things yet
You know what curse I was willing
To do his work
Paris XXX
Is not high that's hard
You know if he got in shape I bet I could do rant
Again I have to correct
Myself
I said that Alex was
Willing to do work
Actually this next clip contradict
And if I have to I'll push the great I want to show your back
That it work
I can cover all this
I got ready to cover all this
And I got the
Prepared
Probably a little too much
Anytime I prepare 15 hours for show
It's the weekend
Apologize
Just prepare for a couple hours that's enough
Instead of literally
Reading
Iran
Videos
Oh my God
But you don't need me to tell you how
Oh by the way I got another video clip
Whatever. Time to get to it is your fault
Set out to do
Also I call Shenanigans
How how are you
Complaining
Tamia
That you can't get
To a video clip
That's not fair that's not fair it's not your fault is the listener
And it's so abusive
You know why I can't do my job
Cuz I work too hard over prepared for this and that's why I'm having this silly childish outbursts
You would do if you had all the
Information in my head
It's a really good way to
Cover when you haven't done any work
No idea what's going on
You also want to emotionally
Aloo your audience into sporting
I mean can you imagine something like that happen
To Alex at a f****** Starbucks
Seaburn that ship to the ground if the Barista was like hey I'm sorry I couldn't get to your coffee I was too busy
Studying coffee in the back I was caring too much about over prepared for this year
I'm sorry I will get to you tomorrow it's funny to imagine this in any other context
Imagine you show for a college
Of course and the professor just screams at you through the entire thing
How about bike
Nothing related to the subject matter
I studied too much
To prepare for this course
No to much about this subject
To yell at you about anything other than the Grievances that I made up
To be happy right now
Even just picking more middle-of-the-road down the middle news
Reader Iraq imagine that
But no one has this reaction to over preparing
You know what
I do think the possible reaction to over preparing is having
Too many bike possible non-sequiturs that's maybe
I mean a possible over prepared for a test before
And then you've got so many answers you're not sure if this is the most
Correct one
Or if there could be a more current over preparation
No I didn't
I didn't immediately go like
All these questions are wrong and lies and everybody stuck here with me and I mean I don't even want to be here.
Baby. You just let us go
Getting nuked already
So
Apologetic
To the crew
Not this time
I got really upset earlier and I can apologize anymore for it
That's what I wanted
That's acting out
Friendly God made us this way to get upset
Things are going on like
Everybody does dozen
Doing on its normal why doesn't everybody get up
None of this is normal
That's because
No one is as manly as Alex Alex is so in touch with what God wants him to be
He acts like that
The other people don't
I agree with him not about that that larger point but that was
If that's at all
Justin acting out
Also agreed I think that it makes
It worse
But he's clearly aware of that and willing to just be like
Yeah that was me putting on a show I mean that is
It's almost weird to admit
I say that out loud especially because you so unable to actually even do the acting out thing
It's kind of like
The old clown who can't do his routine you know just sad
Light on right is flower only towards water about an inch to enter to himself wet
Can only juggle 1 balls that's sad that the sad clown throwing up a ball
Juggling one ball
Yeah I mean like if you if you're going to be like I meant
To do that this is a this is a thing
Just realized his inability to even do the fake job that's that he sees
Is being a job it is a little bit watching a man disintegrate
So
Like I brought this up a couple times and it
It's because
Alex does as well
He thinks
That he can get away with
Saying that
He's looking at all sides
Looking at the NATO side look at
Is very untrue
But you eat rice play that game again
I'm going to do my best
Has to show
All the news tab
From the Ukrainian side the NATO side and the
Russian side
Bunch of clubs bunch of articles
And a bunch of thanks
To get to Butler
Start
And again this is interaction with their subtitles
40 viewers last stop
Thomasina play
It's on record so people know he said it
Play show you what I'm about to say
And then I will paraphrase
So I got to say after we seen here today I'm super confident that Alex is going to be totally fair and impartial
Give equal weight
To the Russian Ukrainian tomato position the f*** out of here
B words mean things
Right
So this Peach is the one from February 24th
Current speed
Very unclear
He's not he's not being specific enough
To give the audience really a clear understanding of which
Speeches Which rare things,
The speech were Putin
Declared war Alex is doing is he's going to be uncritically playing in endorsing
Putin's propaganda campaign
Where you trying to rationalize invading Ukraine
Going to be his
So so I think what you might be saying
Is that when Putin gave that speech
The one that
Cricket that Alex could find
No moron
Speech yeah it was the
1 prior
It was one where he was recognizing on skin
Couldn't find fault with
I would send seeing this one until probably until yesterday
Yeah so
So the speech where Putin
Lied
A lot
Non-Stop
In an effort to convince
Anybody who would listen
I think that we're not
Alex is going to just play that
Johnson Tire
Is very little because he gets bogged down
One of the problems is that Apes
Video with subtitles there's no dubbing subtitle
That's too hard
So he doesn't do much of it but
Cannot believe they gave him a video with subtitles
Do you think the last
Foreign language film he saw was
Get the f***
Catching Tiger Hidden Dragon
So here is out with his first paraphrase
He says they're using psychological warfare operations Destroyer family to rhodhiss from within
Shall we collapse
They want us to our families
And we're aware of this
So here's what that part of the speech actually sat
Properly speaking the attempts to use us in their own interests
Never really ceased until quite recently
They sought to destroy our Traditional Values and force us
Course on us there felt false values that would erode us are people from within
The attitudes they have been aggressively imposing on their countries
Attitudes that are directly leading to degradation and degeneration because they are contrary to Human Nature
Naturally this leads to Alex picking up the ball and
Translate
Support raised transphobia
Which might be a fair reading of Putin's words
He says like they've done in the countries that control
Honey they're bombing us
With fentanyl
And an LGBT PG
Eqz
They're bombing us with transgender I mean
Destroy somebody
The Russians are dumb
Look at this
Because they don't want to embrace this there the bad people
Wow so one of the things that's really interesting about this particular passage from Putin's War speech is that it could be used to appeal to
Really any variety of bigot
If you have
Trans are gay people you can hear degradation into generation isn't being about that community
Happy same time if you're a racist you could
Mute being about multiculturalism or
If you're super anti-immigrant
See it about being an attitude of openness towards refugees and asylum-seekers
If you're a misogynist you could see this buddy about feminism
If your auntie abortion you could see this being about that
This passage that Alex's playing is essentially a Rorschach test for a person's bigotry
It seems pretty clear that Alex is deeply committed to his hatred of tramp
Also if you follow the chain of logic here than what Alex is saying is the George Soros made people in Ukraine trans
And they Putin is worried that he do the same in Russia so he had to invade
This is nonsense reply when you can't just come out and say that you love dictators and what a One World Government
One that's authoritarian against people
Who you considered to be part of out-group
Write a Netherlands towards
You right and you're in group
Yeah the the language is so
5 minutes
Just f***
Nothing on except
They are bombing us
With LG
With lgbtq visit
What is a histogram
End
Putin just saw them bombing him and they're all Putin's doing is bombing back
Sure
What they're doing is saying things are okay and using words
And Putin is murdering a lot of people but bombs are bombs
It's
It's pretty disgusting
Yeah
We got because Alex has gotten what he needs out of this this is most of what he covers of pollutants
There isn't much reason to do anything other than like go back to
The beginning so I can rest more on the
And to get some other rest
But he goes on to say
This is not going to happen
You're going to fail
I mean
What do you say to that
Cuz this is an alien takeover
I don't like green men running
What is
Whatever's going on
What are the most the world is anti-human
Russia and China are rejecting
That's not what
He was saying that the US wasn't going to defeat Russia and impose the West
Model of an open
Society on the country
Things he wants to hear in this because he really likes Putin and wants him to be the hero that Trump couldn't be
And honestly it's just pathetic
It's it's
Just a disaster
You have Alex here on Sunday
Listening to the speech
From the 24th
And
Being like
This guy
Is great
He's standing up to these aliens
That's what I've that's what I want in my president I want the new American president because Russia is the new
New America
And Putin is the President of Russia between Putin is my president
He I love
It seems like a short walk honestly
Just
Nuts
Sphinx
But he's in
Anyway
Being all sides
Next time off
Just took some
Give me just go to the woods like a week or two ago
Otherwise it takes
And I will be here live
Tomorrow with the Monday show but
I have decided English major Wars going on but I'm going to take off a few days
Because
I've got to really think about
What's happening in inches
Come out disconnect
Because here's the problem
Just like I know this happen you probably
I'm thinking about this all the time
I'm dreaming about
This is all I'm doing
But I'm becoming
Very unbalanced
NASA Global is playing
The globalist plan is to make you all talk to you earlier
Performative
I don't see that as being a good plan problem is probably that Alex he's dreaming about this stuff I could
Tutors at Visions
Or research
F****** time off maybe the rest of your career take it off
I don't think
Anybody
Really
Needs
Your take on the Ukrainian
Situation
Especially when it
Into this direction
LaRosa's
Lukashenko was are always calling an idiot
And I'm moron
He doesn't know anyting
Swatch subjects ego research
And you want to watch
Our lawn
Galaxy
Michelle
And I'm not endorse
Everything he does
What he's up to there
Like what
Alexander lukashenko is a dictator and he's been in power in Belarus
Since 1994 could f****** God I'm a little more careful about finding himself relating to look at
Hey Lucas and I are two peas in the same pod and I see no problems with saying that out loud to Allah
A lot of people
What are the complaints of the International Community has with lukashenko
It's Betty really seems to like torturing political dissenters
The 2020 election where Lucas
Santa won his sixth term though most of the world in a lot of Belarusian
Believe
Strongly that election
It was not a fair election to a lot of protein
According to Human Rights Watch
At least 8712 people were detained in connection to protest
Between November 2020
October 2021
In August 2020 the government decided that there was no reason to open an investigation into 4600
44 claims
Filed by victims
The torture by the government
What usually the Fairly strong indication that they don't want to talk about all the torturing
Is Alex thinks that Luca shanko sounds like his show he probably right
But that's because Alex is yours essentially the ravings of an authoritarian wants to
The torture and imprison people he doesn't like
Also considering the Belarus has now at war with Ukraine also
It really makes it clear
Capable Alex is a
Close to impartial coverage
He's just a stand for Putin
Like the idea that you can maybe okay well
I'm going to distance myself from Putin a little bit
I don't think the war is smart
That's my problem
Not smart
He's in over his head
He bit off more than I can chew
If he said one
Then it would have been very
Now what I'm going to do is I'm going to heat preys upon
A
It was just somebody who is totally neutral in this situation
Somebody who I can say listen
Somebody who's
The only other person
F****** a******
Yep unreal sucks
They say Ukraine the quote unquote
Head on over to Belarus that's where you going to the country where Russian Troop
Please put nuclear weapons in our country that's stupid
Yikes has complained about Joy behar's comments being insensitive
And I think
That's
A little
Point Beach
I told you
You going to have a guest
And it's you
Evilly
All right folks Leo zagami is a best-selling author research
Vatican experts also an expert on Western
Happening in Russia
I'm sorry what is an expert on what sorry what now what
I mean he has spent some time in St Petersburg cuz of his like DJ
Sure
I know like
I know that I've seen videos of him like
Showing
Flyers for the event cities.in Russian stuff
At least Samba familiarity with the country but more than Alex
Elizabeth be
Like really above-board here
He is not a best-selling author
Those books are
Disaster is
They suck
Self-published
He claimed that he was in the Illuminati
He was Jesus
Well yes he was approved to the Vatican that he was Jesus and they were like whoa
Can't believe it can't believe it's blowing my mind right now.
The only Jesus would have
Yeah if you could open the padlock
All the basement of the Vatican
They have eye scanners that only record
Acknowledge Jesus as I know he is repurposed himself I guess as
Is ax word
International relations Visa V Russia
In the meeting
Moscow in 2002
At briefly end in
When he was a steal a mare in St Petersburg remember
End
Heating change Russian polish
Sure
I would I would like to just because it's fun imagine that every part of
Leo's mythology is something that he believed simultaneously as opposed to he's done a bunch
Two different grips over the years he's coming off of
Just a few months earlier at 11 for 9/11
Saw the towers go down was like I got to get out of here I'm going to head to st. Petersburg going to hang out with my buddy them
Mayor
President by 2002
All this is so dumb
Anyway after that
Intelligence services
Right now
Right that they had to frame up some folk
F****** a******
But that's it just goes to show the cravenness at the depths of the thieves
These con artists will go to
In order to come up with their new mythology
Which is it part of it is done in service
Of getting rid of that old one that
Kind of sucks
You don't want to be the guy who's Jesus
It started Matrix ism is 911 amazing might be fun for a little bit
You need a new gimmick you had a 2002
And I know everything about Russian politics
Look the the the
The world is seeing
Breaking out in Russia which is short people are pretty heart
It's nice to see people
Being that brave right
Lukashenko and Putin both are fans of torturing people who protest
You should know is actually not true
I mean
President Vladimir Putin
If some people get arrested
People I know for sure
The West
They of course get money also by George
It's not the relevant
Yeah man these protesters just paid by Soros wow irrelevant
Trying to play the I'm impartial games
Just at disaster
I.
That's really
That's really incredible
Good work
Goodworks agave
Does Christ
Yeah it's not relevance what why would all of those people care
I mean sure their money is on fire
But Lisa relevant to the work
Cooking class the man who feeds his family and his money's on fire
Not relevant irrelevant
So we went from
That that meaningful toot for our purposes
But he describes what is going to be Putin plan after this
Alex should
You should have stronger
Because they're at a time right
Is this
The Centenary of the Soviet Union crane his
Is going to go into the bath
And so basically Europe
Heading gift for peace
And so if you want we got to get you on this way
Call this amazing thank you so much
Wow okay see your your guy who's supposed Russian expert is
He's going to put together the Soviet Union again
I want to rethink some of your support
But you're throwing around here
Alex I just want to let you know
That after this
Again
Super totally fine
Both side invasion of Ukraine just really gentral
Putin will also be invading 627 other countries and I'll help
Because if the 100th anniversary of the forming of the Soviet Union
What were you just going to let Finland not celebrate with you this sounds like the new American
Doesn't get much more American than colonizing
There is something
I feel like Alex might want to take a break
A little Breaky Breaky
Take take some time off we think maybe take a big long break but I think over that time he might want to rethink
How he wants to lick position himself right terrible job right now I mean
Sincerely is doobie
I can out now Putin apologist
This goes on
I don't understand
What else
He could be setting
Myself up for
I mean
Honestly
Like we're at a point where
I'm even willing to entertain the thought of Alex being like well
Listen I'm going to be broke in America soon
But
If I'm not in America maybe I'm in Russia
They need a new Infowars they got a lot of wood they got a lot of woods out there
I told my daughter camping
I told that you called for me
Yeah I don't I don't I don't know I don't think
I don't know that's absolutely ridiculous but it is nuts
Just don't
Get I don't get what the game is
Really
It's a rare it's a rare instance where I can
Can see like little pieces of it and yeah he's doing makes sense and the
The little propaganda games
But the overarching point of it I can't really see
I don't know what the benefit of this is other than maintaining
The idea of him as a champion of these anti
Sjw
Memes and
And there it is that he has
That's the only thing that I see
Is being worth it
For him to preserve a
I mean I think the only
Maybe maybe here's what I'm
Maybe it is at a point where they're just
Pot committed with Putin
And they can
Can't admit they were wrong
They can't just say it maybe I was wrong so there is a place where they built up Putin and Trump as both being soup
Super cool dudes
Who are absolutely aboveboard and not at all line to the global community at all times it may you might be right
And if you say Putin is actually
F****** evil
Like everybody obviously knew he was
Then you also have
To say well I was wrong
Spec's humble
Yeah yeah it could
It could could be that simple
I mean I wish it were
You know there's a busy
There's an out there possibility
I am just throwing this out
You better now
Alex and his
Community
Never were more relevant than the Cold War
That's a good point world
Where there was
A big
Ominous villain
Consistent threat of nuclear war
Really really did wonders for the anti-communist community right and
Made them
Voice Within
Some of the right-wing
They gave them a boogeyman that was such a society wasn't necessarily as maligned until after
McCarthy
So I
I could see some kind of subconscious Drive
To bring back the good old days
Voorhees
Antiquated
Radical
Right in that
In that circumstance
The ironic part
Is that is that be
Because of the way that their
Pics of migrated
They're cold war buddy
Would be Russia
I don't think
Cuz right now they feel like they're in a cold war with
Every but I guess the democratic government as a at the con
I feel like a process that bridge when they got there
How it would play out
Just spitballing
I don't know it's
I find the same time
Just disgraceful
The
The way that I look
Extract position himself in
Pretend that he is
Like not just
Doing
Rationalization justification
That's all he's doing
Absolutely
The breakdown was pathetic
Even in terms of just like on a scale of
Good break down to
Bad breakdown
Very low on that
Upscale
Unreal
Will be back
But until then
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight and I go to bed Jordan
Marbles
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work