Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge
Bestbuy.com
What about Nostradamus
Little bit about
Alex Jones
We are damn Jordan
What's up
Vibrate
Weird but it's very satisfying I don't think I've ever done it before
Wow what a Man Loves a Woman
So whenever you use the microwave
Obviously you don't
Two beeps
Happened when the timer runs out
They're annoying
Yes you want to pull the door before the people
One second
But almost every time I open the door any second left on the timer
Do the first beat
Today for the first time I've ever noticed I pulled the door at exactly the point where there was no beep
And the timer with John
It felt great
I would I would love
To s*** on that as an achievement
But honestly if I'm alone and I just tossed a piece of paper into a trash can
Fuckingo Apes
I got you got like boom shakalaka you're on fire
Danielle Colby
The realreal
Satisfying tiny moment there
I'll never I'll never be able to replicate it
Celebrate they went it happens as opposed to
Wish we could just leave it as space we always open the microwave door
I think that my bright spot is I
I think I've decided to switch back
Contacts
Okay my glasses are my visions
So bad now that at this point
I'm like
Leaning into Reed s*** I'm doing the whole thing I got to stop
With the glasses Dan I got to stop I'm going to go I'm going to go contacts again my friend
Alright
Baby okay
No
I look like I'm 19 again I feel like I don't get used to it but
It'll be it'll be an adjustment
I mean like
Over the course of the pandemic you'd want the headband roof and that was that was tough at first
We got used to it I think I've looked different every five to six months
My beard length
A bit extra
And that drastically alter
Where's my my appearance
Yeah I Will Survive. I've never done contact before I forget
Add contacts
Does that have
Like do they help more with vision the glasses counter
Not well
So-so with with my eyes
Contacts are very very good for like
75% of the world you know everything from
My full arm away I can see perfectly
Play in all directions
There's this weird Middle Ground between my arm
And where I can normally
And that's
That's where I can't see what's on
So you're saying when you wear contacts
Sneak up on you and solutely
ROMs for my lights on
You know there's that it's all there for you I'm I'm essentially a helpless little boy
As long as you didn't really close
This locally penetrate
As everybody knows
Sure Thomas Jefferson
What was my glasses as you can see
Everything sucks
Hysterical
Is completely God
So I'm just blind most of the to the periphery
Yeah I got no peripheral vision
Okay easier to sneak up on you then
Which option allows for the best sneak options
Video games
We have an episode to go over it's going to be a little bit of an episode
Too much of us too much contact for several hours every
So today I was just taking a little break
He's he's gone
Husband
No stuff to go over I was thinking about like
Impression of Alec
I'm so boring
I was listening to some Harrison Smith stuff and didn't want to do that either
We had Stewart Roads back on for an interview
I've not seen that happen
Since the indictment vs Harrison
Still
Still gung-ho for him
My free speech
It's being taken away why
I mean that's a weird thing considering what was it just yesterday somebody the one of the guys played guilty to seditious conspiracy
Cersei not like
Not anything less than seditious conspiracy
That is top
And there are indications that he's cooperating that's not good
Yeah yeah
You'll see the treason and you're cooperating
Had a lot going on for you
That means that the
What it what you were looking at is a clout no chance I'm making out with making it out of this trial
I was at with an acquittal still do public hangings cuz it sounds like that's what they're going for band
This is cooperative cooperate cooperate
So we'll see how that all plays out
But I might not look so great plead guilty
Doesn't look good in retrospect
Harrison Smith story
I'm so excited to do instead of going over some of that stuff which is
Kind of like
Just
Banging
Dark Horse
Banging your head against the wall
I was I had a mixed metaphor in my head that just wasn't coming out right
And
I thought let's go back to the past
Let's do answer
Continuing that
Exploration of what the f*** was Alex doing back then
I'm into today we're talking about July 18th 2000
Free ride this episodes weird
Pinterest
And told all the little details before
So first The Silver Stallion pick him up juvenile policy walk
I'm going to steal me
Operation Horizon forbidden West thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
My older brother is convinced
Thank you very much
Rasta philosophy
Myvpro
Thank you so much
Going to apologize
I'm a policy wonk
Jordan
This is a bottle episode essentially I mean like
In 2003 alot of these have
Very little connection to
Anything that's going on certainly the present-day or even around them cuz I mean like our last episode from 2003
Alex talk to that Wizkid who couldn't get her diploma cuz she wasn't old enough to
To get equivalent to high school
Dr. David race Bannon from Interpol
You have all that
Has nothing to do with it
It's always fun
Getting just a slight bit of distance away
Being being with my memory that I have and then you tell me all of these things and I know they happen at the same time
My brain is like
There's no way those things happen
Korea being Assassin's Creed triple
I remember that happening
A fictional character obviously
Yeah the highlights of
Something is going on on this show in the past
The path
Call mireille connective tissue pieces is collars
Congratulating Alex on his Ann Coulter interview
That seems to be one of the only things that actually goes through all these episodes and makes me feel like
Yeah this definitely did happen the day after the last one that's true
Weird
Today's episode
Rhode Island
Empire
Obvious vampire vampire Mister blood
Alex
Don't get into business with mr. blood
He's from the Northeast cuz I'm sorry that one that one trick
You got me buddy
There are two
Man veritiv saw that are going throughout this episode
One of them is
Outrageously offended okay
It is
Very much Alex taking a new story
And repurposing it for his own use
As a homophobic
Attack
Good
Depravity
Reporting
Literally
Doughboy
A little shocking like
Very clearly aa8 just a child
With no information letting his imagination run wild like
Oh yeah yeah gay people I don't understand
This is before eating
It's true
This
Situation where there are like a couple of data points that Alex's
What you're saying like a child just connecting things
Just like I don't know what Rolling Stone article Alex exciting if it's
Any of that nonsense I'd really like to get a look at
Pacific time
I don't know
Scriptures
Literally just say that end with this such a blase like
You know this is just
What is it with these kids these days
Very popular among the gay community to each other and give each other AIDS
This is going to be something
It keeps coming up on this episode so we'll deal with it a little
More details later but
This is just homophobic nonsense freely and the guy Alex is talking about he didn't get arrested for saying gay
He was arrested related to
Some things that he said at a fair that were alleged to have been inciting
This dude gave a speech where he asserted that he believed the country people should have the same rights as members of minority groups
That's the version of the story has a
Appears in papers
Speed wasn't recorded at according to
BBC quote
Several people
Complain to the police about his speech
What kind of assumed that he said some other s***
This created a fake version of the story
The scientific term for whatever as everybody's known for a long time
The Spanish word for black is the scientific term used to describe human
Is Robin something
We we talked we talked about this
In detail on past episodes
He gave people forgot
So this is an interesting point to that should be remembered I think is illustrated by this clip even as far back as 2003
Alex was spreading
Legally insane and bigoted narratives about gay people like to be cannibals and give each other AIDS
So when someone suggests that he always
We are we wasn't always such a bigot
It's just not borne out by the reality
Pretty pretty nuts
But you know it when you can
When you can look at somebody's bigotry
As as like
Somebody somewhere somehow describing you know Alex wasn't his bigoted back then
Is he is now
And you're only thing you can hang your hat on right now I guess
She's like now his bigotry is full out like maybe we should just kill everybody I don't lie
But back then it was like
Everybody I don't like
Is probably a cannibal
Which is almost kind of a hero like that is big agree
That's true
It's true there is a like
Psych meds turn you into
Hers or something through the quality of
I think that I
I disagree with Alex's coverage here bro
Keeps me pretty insistent about
Can you run out of
Flash
Weird tell me more about
I knew immediately what Alex was talking about here but the way he is reporting on this is just cartoonish
Spanish in the US to go to Mexico to get your legs cut off so you can eat them when you run out of Lake
Kill you in order for you to be
So this is based on just
The few stories that have come out of people who want to have their healthy limbs amputated sure there's a pretty poorly understood phenomenon
That's been labeled body Integrity identity
Adidas order and cases
Pretty low but it's
It's very difficult to get a precise number
Hannah people who experiences
It's definitely not always connected to sexual feelings of those sometimes people do
I have a sexual relationship with
I am feeling faint wanting to get their limbs amputated so they can
That's not typically the presentation
Alex is writing a grotesque
Story about something that he knows nothing about it
Uno's
But it's not in this financial interest to know anything
Think about if he learns things but he can't do these cannibals Walk Among Us Marantz to scare the audience so they can pick the game
Gay people should be seen as less than human
A big
Fetish to go to bed
Cookout
You know you'll get off
Double Chestnut
Okay
Alright
So
It look okay
You can you can sell you can tell me like there's this fetish for going and getting your legs chopped off in
So people can eat
He didn't tell you that
My problem
Really
Is the follow-up
Where he's like
And they say I'm crazy
You are actually I think that by the end of episode I will lay out what
I believe that strategy
Cuz I do think that's an intentional strategy extreme criticizing
Abs
On our way to finding this
Conclusion we need to learn more about this
There's some more cannibalism to be discussed a demographic
Breakdown we have
Isaac Moore large people with larger legs who are chopping their legs off
And I'm going to like crack
You know I'm going to gain some weight before I go down there
Substantial to really chew on you know but that might actually not be how you get the best
That's a good point
I don't I don't know no there is no discussion of this
But it turns out that there is a case
Ava cannibal 2003
Hannibal
Charged with murder
Manscape
I'm coming in
Spell lackadaisical throw to a mammoth clone a story about a third of all men in San Francisco 1
I get AIDS and die and I guess mammoths around next time news I didn't track that down
But I don't know what he's talking about and I don't notice Rolling Stone article is
Accountable this is Armin Muse
Suicide German dude who ate a guy who'd volunteer to do it after meeting Armon on a message board called the cannibal Cafe
There may have been like 450 people on that message board like Alex think it's a group of 450 right
But I'm going to guess that a vast majority of them were just people at a vorarephilia can't
Which is the erotic desire to eat some on orbi
Like the Cannibal Cop from years ago
But not a not quite but everyone on that message board was on there to roll place
Something
But not something they actually wanted to do which is
Probably a big part of why our men had multiple people agreed to let him eat them but then they ultimately backed out
I would guess that that was because they realize he was serious about eating them which was a deal-breaker
No
They wanted to jerk off to the thought
Not actually
Probably
Initially this was a mess from a court perspective because as the BBC put it quote
Cannibalism is not a recognized defense under German law and the defense will argue that since the victim volunteered this was
Was no murder
That's trouble
A bad day in court for everyone involved
Oh s*** we forgot to make this illegal
So in his first trial he was convicted of manslaughter but he was retried in 2005 where the argument that
He was killing for sexual gratification
The Proven by the fact that he had videotaped the crime
Led to a murder can
It probably didn't help that he had also posted on that message board looking for another person
Which really made the case pretty strong that he was like
Syria leader
Yeah now you're serial cannibal killer
Exceedingly uncommon crime for someone to commit
Evidenced by the fact
Tire world knows exactly this is the same case where they cut off the penis and they
Sensational headline grabbing community
Important place
Puppies to recognize
In 2003 trans people weren't the primary target of the extreme right in terms of their desire to kick up
Fake moral panics
This isn't to say that homophobia doesn't exist anymore in our present-day but
It's not as Central to the right-wing strategy anymore because it doesn't create the same response In Their audience
People are cooler with gay people now so they got to get more extreme
They have to wait to further their referrals on there exactly
The homosexual community
It's not as vulnerable as they were to their attacks
As they were e2003
You got it be above all the stuff that the more mainstream right-wing pundits get into but
He's no different than any of them he's just ignoring
Extreme version he's willing to make more stuff up to keep his audience interested but he plays the exact same game
That
His contemporaries like a rusher and
What do
Yeah and it's
It's so it's so emblematic of who they are as people
Like deep down
That
The moments a
Minority group
Become strong enough
And received enough support
They stopped
Attacking it on whatever ideological quote-unquote grounds or moral grounds bad before
And the go to somebody weaker
Weaker always weaker group that has less
Societal support
More vulnerability
Particularly distasteful about it is
Then they'll pretend that like
I never really had a problem with that problem with gay people what they do inside their bedrooms I'm fine with whatever
Are you do at home now I should tell you they like you like to eat people
Yeah it's just such a like
How do how does everybody not look at them and they're just a bunch of cowardly bullies and we get
Trapped by them
Cuz they're so f****** loud all the
You know
It's it's brutal
Yeah
I think that one of the values of going back and looking
Episode
That the cultural milieu of the right-wing
And they're the sort of culture War narratives
Are so
Similarly
Strategized but their focus is are different
Can see soak
Clearly how that works
By comparing
Verizon
No and they just keep going down the list of letters in lgbtq has just like oh well today we're going to pick on G
Tomorrow we're going to pick auntie
It's just a monster
Stop
Alex Goes to call
A lot of calls at this episode cuz he burned himself out on guest
Dr. race Bannon I believe you're not going to get much better than that
You can't
Is a hero
Xor this caller has a great question for Alex and this
You can tell Alex was a little bit pissed off by this
I miss the bright
New York calling
Fallout
Come on
Anybody
Fallout
Hearing call yourself you can call him
Thank you so much
I love that this show could have those moments right now
F*** all those theater and is this guy the best vidock you better give me a compilation of other colors being like
Is Brian from New York okay we haven't heard from him in a while get into a fight you guys doing okay I love the moment of Alex
Responding yeah me and the scholar got into a fight
What what what what
What what's that kind of like yeah that's what happened like
That kind of rhetorical
Doesn't exist for a there's no good so sarcastic shitbag comebacks
Then to the something refreshing about that
So there's also a collar with a conversation about nuclear
Attack
Or maybe a false flag nuclear attack
It's coming
And Alex has some interesting advice about
The winners get your guard up and cry
Pearl Harbor
The may be too risky for them do it
ReliOn missile sailor
Significantly
Talk about North Korea
What I probably out
They probably already got the Warhead
Play the here in this country
Only one take
Chance on losing their own people they have to happen
Complaining
At 1 meeting
Look out whenever the globalists are out of town in let's go
Yeah
You ever do those shows that like vfw's
No
Never done an Elks Lodge or anything like that a bee but the longtime
I don't remember all of the gigs I did
More than my fair share
Karaoke at VFW Halls Florida
I've done plenty and there is that like
It's all going fine before the show
You do the show and if everybody likes you
You get asked
To join conversations that sound absurdly like this one
All the time of just like well you know obviously they the evil Boogeyman wouldn't do this they would hide the new
Inside your bedroom for whatever
And then when they go out to the grocery store that delivers
Yeah yeah
This is a false flag that didn't happen
Another bad prediction on Alex's Park
But I do like there's a there's a distinct
Difference here between the way Alex talks about what the other globalist evil plan
Compared to the present day
They are going to kill all of their over money
Everybody's you don't have to worry about the globalist going out of town anymore. World in the present
Like that's not going to help you know not whether or not there's a
So we got another bad prediction Alex's bar
Don't work
So we have two predictions here just from the beginning of this episode
That
Not good
One another National Drive
Did not happen
Nuclear attack from North Korea
Or possibly a false flag made to look like North Korea I was sleeping
Baboon pasta Club listed
Just just as a reminder of the
No he's always quitting me of things that Alex's wrong about predicting
You are the problem was you would just going out of town when the
North Koreans nuked
You are out of Chicago we got nuked
Back together pretty quick to get the win
Community solidarity, 2 gal rebuild and time
Got to get this together before.
Oh no your gossip dad that's what everybody said
So
We heard from the out-of-context drop
Mister blood
Is now syndicated
Yay
Alex gets a call from somebody who is
Maybe from the same station or another station in Rhode Island I'm not sure Alex may have to
Stations in
I'm actually think I know what is the issue is here I think I think I know what the deal is
Is he does mention that there's like two stations in Rhode Island
So this person is calling from one of them
Didn't talk to you about my name is Michelle
Freeman in my head
Then Freeman and he's on
I got to let you know
Is warl power
1820 and
Reality radio
And the Wild
Providence
Houston
It's based in Providence
There's nothing there wattage
So they have
Did they
More listeners
Look this this lady giving her first and last name is the beginning of something that ends up paying off late
There's another caller the next caller gives his first and last name
Universal last name for somebody could be calling in to make somebody else look bad
Got to cut it out
So it should come as no surprise here Jordan know that this radio station doesn't exist in the same format that it didn't 2000
That whole reality radio thing that I was just so excited about
1320 am in that area of the Northeast is actually based out of Attleboro Massachusetts
Santa's been operational
Since 1950
Going through many changes in their theme from that time
Previous rebranding as reality radio it has been following
Easy listening format
So there was another AM station in Providence around that time Wale 990 that was
A lot of conspiracy
I think that's the other station that Alex is talking about being on
They went bankrupt
In 2003 programming was shifted over 230
1820 and they sold their name to Wally
So it should be noted that he known as insignificant part of this station going bankrupt had to do with America's really f*****
Top shows
American dissident voices which was released by the National Alliance
Who are Nazi
In Rhode Island
So cropped
1320 switch formats over to adult
Conspiracy lineup took some of their programming on
And it was not a hitch because
By 2004 they switched again and we're now a Sports Talk Show
They were running Lako Nova gone for a long time
Are the matter all about these
And the women are not things
And the children are really f****** Nazis bad
I was I was
I think
Some Killers amass enough
Yeah
I watched
I didn't realize they had videos of like live performance
Oh my God
Number one
I forgot that the news from Lake Wobegon was
Such a long
Segment
I didn't realize and some of them were like 20 minutes forever was just like a little
A little thing would you remember the show in your head it is
Encapsulated by like five sentences every show and then if you actually go back and listen to it you're like this is in terminal
It's never end I thought I thought my memory dealers show was the
Variety show
Segment to the news from Lake Wobegon commercial
So I got bored
Also watching
Garrison Keillor deliver this was something that
I don't know maybe it's just cuz I grew up in this like a
Dr kind of family there was this impression of him is like one of the great orators and storytellers
In the legacy of Mark Twain Diner
Lackadaisically like Spirit like looking down at the ground and
Kicking non-existent rocks on stage
It was
Awful he has got a face for radio my friend
Did you see the way the movie
No oh man I think
I may be misremembering this entirely but I'm fairly certain Lindsay Lohan was in there
Oh yeah yeah I don't want to say what
Yeah
Don't stop excited I was shocked
Watching it how
Adjust on a compelling of a performance it was
It made me reconsider a lot of things that my parents thought were entertaining when I was younger
Yeah well it'll do it
Just make sure I never have to watch a video of a live taping of what do you know
Yeah please do that would be trouble we do not recommend
Although I have found
Old
Recordings of Celtic connections
And
Hearts of Space
Never heard of hearts
Subspace
The space
Space was a show that would play on like
I think it was Saturday or Sunday nights on NPR
And it was space music
So it was like
Soundscapes
Okay but then they were beat like the narrator of it
Haha I will be like
Hearts of Space fellow-traveller
Welcome
You're welcome fellow space straight up like a quiet storm like
Meadows SNL characters
I don't I don't know that sketch your talk about
Each episode of cyber call would have like
A theme that were just these abstract themes like to
Today today words
Dealing with Envy
Mariah Carey's first album was dropped
I could have been could have been
I don't know I still really enjoy Hearts of Space though that's
That is a lot of fun
Anyway
Alex is on the station and that it went off the air within a year
Okay Sports Talk format
That's not bad
So Alex gets another caller
This guy
Is just a nice pretty clearly Sovereign citizen fella
The government
As far as
Issues
Security number
Revoked
Driver's license
It all that
Lake County Jail
And they said in the court
Punishment
Ordinary
Ordinarily
Court
They didn't actually get to this Denver case accidentally in a little
Little bit but I think I think you can do a lot of hiding out by calling yourself a constitutional
List of Saturday's Auburn citizen
Weird Al which is what this guy's doing
My hands on whatever he went
Because I'm sure it's not what he's saying
Something to do with the constitution in his love of it a copy of
The Constitution and 16 secret police members just
Descended upon him and they had to throw him in jail
So the same color has some other ideas I think he's kind of atone for Malik
Just bouncing it back at him
You know I was looking at Birth
Minister of England
Gay guys
Let me know what's up with that
Each other
I'm sorry for
The shacknews
Thanks a lot
Family Auto
Joe
You know
It is
A sad day
Every time
I hear
A conservative
Laugh just because some guy went
Those two men standing close to each other
What if they were banging right hahaha
Oh my God that's
The funniest thing I've ever considered
It's it's an expression of some homophobia but it is also at the same time just not a
Good joke
It's just a bad joke yeah it's kind of
Clever and pack
Even if it weren't
Offensive it's just
That's just sad
So I told you they were two narratives it was sort of running through the episode the first is gay people like to eat
Human
That's not a bad
I think Alex is reporting it is about
Alright so
The second story is about David Kelley who was a not today that TV producer
Abby
He was a weapons inspector
And
Doctor
Who committed suicide
And died the day before this episode
And
Story of it has to do
With
He had been quoted in an article in the BBC
I've been had to do with
A claim that was in British
Government dossier about the Iraq War in there
Potential for weapon
The best destruction
There's a line in it about there being
RV
The weapons could be deployed within 45 min
Okay this line itself
I asked
Aladdin
By David Kelly
Was something that the Downing Street
Spokesperson insisted be put in
The report
And so there was a big
Brouhaha about this
And the characterization of it
And the BBC weather it matched
What David Kelly had told this reporter
Weather was supposed to be entirely on background
And it's it's just a huge mess right and this he ended up dying from suicide
Prior to that
The episode narrative I didn't
Spend a lot of time I didn't want to cut at an eclipse cuz it's kind of grotesque
In some ways yeah
But Alex is just insisting that the government killed him off
Because he
He was blowing the whistle
Alex exaggerate the actions and the circle
Dances around it
I'm just going to play this one clip
Because I think
Jordan to recognize
How Alex
Takes
Add absence of information and now he has
He has no idea what happened
This guy
Was announced dead hours before this show so he knows all the details he needs to
He just
Declares it essentially a cover up a murder
Friday because
More interesting for him
Moron
What is the point
Of saying it'll never come out how he died or maybe it will who knows
What is the point of that except to inject
On healthy distrust
Like just
Sleep need jerk
Based on nothing distrust
An Indian expectation of
Everything is a lie
And I think that's
Knox help
Yeah I mean
He's just saying
Look Anything Could Happen
But whatever it is they tell you is
We heard him say as it relates to the invasion of Ukraine
Never know the actual death numbers don't never tell you the truth
They're lying to you and if what they're lying to is what's truth or lying to about what's true to lie to you about it
It's a it's an attempt to insulate all information sources
Outside of
The audience's acceptance
Trust no one but me
Alex
Call from another guy
He's got himself a little militia going
Your opinion and
I need one
Muon
Information
A couple of days
Family
2002.
Are you familiar with
Rick Stanley
Future
Melissa
Did you know he's issued up
Don't we
Obligation
Black magic
Just a white dude
Denver
So this is the Denver case that Alex was referencing earlier
Which is weird because he was referencing it sort of abstractly and then this caller calls in
Not in response to Alex's, it brings up the guy that that case was about
Knots
This guy's website is Stanley 2002. Org because he's running for Senate in Colorado is a libertarian
At this point or dead
Spoiler like he didn't do too well
He did somehow get 111 vote
Which is way more than I would have expected
I bet it was all from quote
Like-minded
Could be
Part of why I am shocked you got this many votes is cuz he's clearly an insane person
Based on this collar and Alex
What's the description of input also
Because he got in the
Trouble prior to the election due to some bad behavior in an online discussion about immigration
There was apparently so offensive that is over it commented to the Rocky Mountains
Quote Michelle is a very emotional woman
Surprise surprise and politics there might be emotional women
Seems like an a******
Just wow you know just those guys so in this discussion about immigration
For some reason Stanley decided to post a really offensive racist poem titled illegal
I can't find the full text to it but here's the part that's quoted in the Rocky Mountain news
Quote welfare check
Wealthy
Medicaid that keeps you healthy
By-and-by I got plenty
Thanks to you American dummy
Doesn't really rhyme necessarily but that's beginning of it
And apparently here's the last line
From the poem
Quote
We think America darn good place to darn good for the white man race
If they know like us they can go
Got lots of room in Mexico
You know
Racist poetry has really Fallen since a White Man's Burden
You know like at least a White Man's Burden had a structure to it
This action did not sit well with folks
The idea of
Contributing This Racist poem to an online discussion about it
He's a few hundred years late that being a great poem
Little bit of Akita
He proved that in the local press
Maybe he went from
115 V 211
Correct
The event that Alex in this dollar talking about isn't quite what they're making it out to be
Got arrested for open carrying a 357 at a campaign event
Which is illegal in the town that he was in
That would be one thing and a situation that happened
Do you wait and see if you get the law changed
He's a real weirdos
Took a different route
He was set to start his 90-day sentence in jail did he got for this open carry violation
You didn't show up
That if they didn't overturn the verdict in this case is mutual militia would arrest them
Treason
Each of them notices
Guess what this is way more illegal than
From Carrie
Active orders
Against him to ensure the safety of the judge
Orders which Stanley was explicit
If he did not accept as real
This led to getting SWAT team
I have to protect the judges from the Potential Threat of this guy
Malicious
It's that he clearly believes are above the law
He was sentenced to six years in jail after the sentencing he was quoted as saying the only victim here is
Stanley America
Final words are going to be like what did I do
So that this guy that's who they're talking about
I'm going crazy it's one of these kinds of people there
Clearly
F*****-up Behavior right
Gets reinterpreted and repackaged on Alex's show as like yeah you know what he was just going
To be a symbolic protest where he brought a gun to the courthouse
He just wanted to know what was going on and then the FBI was like you can't use the Constitution
He was like I'm going to kill these judges and I don't even know why people got mad
You know what was the problem in the first place he was just
Open carrying a 357 Magnum Magnum at a f****** political rally
Black people who are doing good things do I honestly think that you know based on
Whatever I don't think him having the gun at his rally is necessarily the big
That's why he only would have gotten 90 days in jail
4 +
Be the kind of wedge issue that Alex
Wants to protest today
Him having the gun the rally
Could be the case that you use as a something
Initiate a larger discussion about it
The 90-day sentence
Way out of proportion you go 90 days they might as well be killing my child you know and then
The Second Amendment got about you do all that
Forget the part where is the retina
Judges
Yeah but the threatening judges part where you go to jail for six years and that one's going to really hurt the other
One of the parts that made the threats to the judges
More
Problematic
Is that it was
Clearly
You have to overturn my sentence or there's Wisconsin
Clearview intentions clear
Like that he was
Saying that he had the backing of this militia
Goodbye made the threat
Little bit more
Difficult for him
Not get in trouble for ideologically Libertarians are okay with extortion
Twitter guns
At your head
So Alex gets another caller
Man there's a lot of weirdos we're getting play
Shoutouts on this episode
From Idaho Dan
Me and Maya
Brett really important
Gradual
Transition a peaceful order
Transition back
You never hear about him hear about it
Turn all those guys
Distract
I tried agree it probably was
Ratify
However
What you don't need to go that route
Gary 8 tomorrow
And they've got him in prison
In Mississippi even though the 1st
Addiction was not
Executed
Because you got a jury trial
Call bakery
Oh my God
So this really exciting
Another person has a
Violence free plan on how to revert the government back to a law of the land situation
I guess probably has to be in Sovereign citizen
No taxes being illegal in Egypt
Garry's Mod got arrested for filing fraudulent tax returns and helping other people file fraudulent extra
The larger picture of his career is that he's another really scary militia demagogue that tried to take over a county and Ida
In 1996 he was the head of a group called The Idaho sovereignty Association which is
Naturally
Sovereign
Apparently part of his belief system is that your constitutional rights are actually your property in a literal sense
And each of them is worth $100,000
If you deprive someone of a right
You owe them $100
Alright
Well
I like this
Sure I do I do
I'm starting to like this idea so you could sell your write them to like
You know you can sell your third on Spotify all things
Then soldiers fetish for cutting off my own leg
I'm going to sell you my rights to keep
Soldiers
Khuda bhi of who could force you to put them up for $100,000
I think that's mine
I'll take that into effect
Because there was a woman in the area whose husband had died and she had all
Ada County had assigned a guardian to take care of her which demott claimed as a violation of This Woman's
Due process rights
I have no idea
He was connected to this woman and it's entirely possible he had no connection to her at all
Just founder
I have no idea what was really mad about this so he gave notice that he and his group plan to arrest the judge
Patricia Fleming
But this wasn't all
He is also demanding that every other official needed to retake their Oaths of office with the words so help me
Me God added
They would risk being arrested by his militia
Who's important these words be added because demott thinks
That not having so help me God in there is a loophole
That allows these officials to commit perjury Saturday Saleeby in perjury
So from an article in the Associated Press from 1996
Those who receive notices will have 10 days to take a new oath of office
On September 28th town criers will read the names of those who have not
Complied with the staffs
From every County Courthouse in Idaho
I honestly it like
There's no way to solve
This problem for good
Except I have a thought
How about we gather all of these people
Alright
And if you're a militia person who does stuff like this
You just get put under a giant Dome you go to sleep all the sudden you wake up here in a giant Dome real lost
Scenario
Nobody knows what's going on
But you're not in jail
That's better
Write go live in your little Utopia where you can be all like all were in the old west
Put them under a dome I do think
I think a Truman Show of
Like it's the only way
What is thinks it'll be interesting if you did that almost feels like a social experiment is that these people would not get along
It'll be dead in short
It would be a great like why not
Sovereign citizen Island like why can't we have nice things like we had the idea for grifter Island
Exactly one point
Island isolated from the rest of humanity
That's really the issue that we're dealing with
They shouldn't be harmed
Because we're just people trying to go about the
Their date but they also can interact with the rest of society cuz they're going to kill people
Black kill people just
Waste
Everyone's time
Put out this order that I had to retake their Oaths of office or they are going to get in trouble
And then from there to my plan to arrest all the officials who did
Retake the routes
Ann's Justice Lana
She was going down
He was going to do this with the help of sheriff's deputy
These Bots
If they didn't go along with the plan and hot said he was going to arrest the sheriff
He's already getting the b b b
My marching orders only come by
Not by any established Authority
Call the Lansing
Anyway this guy's attacks protester Sovereign citizen proponent to Triad do
Take over County in Idaho in the mid-90s
What a old school
The time you know School weirdos episode
For cannibalism Sovereign citizens have a fetish for overthrowing elected local government
Balloon afraid of threats
Exactly
Yeah everybody knows this is just another one of those things
So if Alex is complaining about Patriots shows other Patriot shows another like
Knitting circles for Patriot
I just like the drama
But
I would say that at the end of this clip Alex
Gives a piece of advice that he himself should have taken
AR
Bicycle song
Poor people
In one particular
Leverage
What's going on
Violent
White marker
Oh
They use things to backfire on us not we are a bunch of idiots who have bad
That idea is that when they are put into practice even we are forced to acknowledge their so f***
Stupid
Lucky you know they they try and get us
To take over counties in Idaho backfire good idea and then when it turns out they're bad idea
Is it probably their fault
Probably pretty strong like
Don't go to March on Washington
Amazing
That's amazing
It's just
You just never that it's never not
Arkadelphia
On this episode took a lot of calls
And I
I did get
The sense that he was getting annoyed at them
But it was
It wasn't like Edward ever any real blow up
Then the are you at are you having a feud with another caller
F*** you talking about that moment
Then these people are bringing up these other
Boca Gary demott and brick Stanley Alex is kind of being
Hey
Don't don't bring up other people on my show
I'm a patriot Arrow
There is a little bit of him being like
God I wish my callers weren't all so stupid
ISO or I wish they weren't promoting other people they were more my
I wish they weren't
Play Kirby on my team for my show instead of
Throwing wrenches in it every time it is it's a slight disappointment
Addresses
I'm just mad
New World Order
Newworldorder alligator
I'm not going to do I'm not going to be like I'm having a bad day or hungover I'm never going to do that again
I'm just going to be like listen I'm sorry I snapped at you I'm an alligator mad at the New World Order
Can't stop snapping
Because of the New World Order
I think so like if you
You hear that
It sounds more genuine
It sounds more sincere than
His like apologies for outburst in the present day
There is he has a headache
But he's just mad at the New World Order and that's like maybe with these colors
I think
I think you probably
We're about to have a weekend
Mentally checked out of here I got a headache
Who writes all these people are dicks but I'm going to take the high road and be like I'm just mad at the New World Order sorry guys I don't mean to be an ass
Albright
A human thing
Hey
We're all good
Yeah
Scorpio
He wants to touch back on this this cannibals
I'm sure kind of get a sense of what's going on here
The wrong
So this is what I was talking about earlier this strategic aspects there's a stupid game that Alex is playing
Really what he's doing and what
What kind of response he's likely to elicit
He's not talking about the
His case of the German cannibal as it really exists
He's using it as a data point to attack the entire population
Gay people by applying the facts of this one cannibal to the entire community
He knows what he's doing
Is goal is to malign and dehumanize gay people
He knows the people will see through that he's going to get some criticism for a which he'll just say is people trying to in
Cuz he doesn't want people to
Eating each other
It's a simple sleight-of-hand trick where you trying to mask the homophobia that
Behind his rhetoric
With this
There's like all they say I'm such a big
Because I don't like animals here I am using one story
Denigrated entire group people without any connection between the two whatsoever
How people are calling me a bigot
I want for the left
He wasn't paying
Super close attention to
Things in 2003 around cannibal news
But I wouldn't bet that they're worse at least some people
Who were saying that like
You do have a right
To agree to
Have yourself eating sure I would guess that a lot of a libertarian
You only you can sell your leg for $100,000 for food
I guess that's fine if you're a Libertarian right I would assume so
Entering into it is 8 like being coerced into the contract that we could see why Liberty
Libertarian can sell with kidney on the black market then I should be able to sell my leg on the black market right
If it's for a transplant
Like maybe eight maybe it offends your sensibilities
I mean how do you say scientist would feel about you taking an organ and putting it in somebody else
Somebody that would be very unhappy with it probably
The matter of
Respect
J.d.
I think that there probably were some voices that were like that but Alex's mischaracterizing it is like the entire left is just like
Yeah hooray for eating people
Because he knows that
If people catch on to the game
Yeah the homophobic game but he's playing
He has that in his back pocket as like a preemptive
Right
It's it's
Hesitate to call it
Smart crafts
There's a little bit of a strategy
Not not smart
It's it's like a it's like what you would describe a rat
As having not intelligence but the low level of God
It's just
Recognizing
The likely consequences of
The rhetoric leader of disseminating
And planning in advance
To not have to own the consequences
It is it is fun though
To make up stereotypes that are that batshit
I mean
Is as it is expensive
It is bigger
But at the same time if there was like a Def Jam comic
In the 90s who is like
Never noticed how gay people be eating legs like this
I think you'd be like yeah that's
That's insane man that's the craziest f****** stereotype I've ever heard that's insane
Yeah if I saw it I wouldn't think joke was funny probably
Intrigued
But for Alex's
It's a little bit lesson
Intriguing cuz you know what a true today
Yeah it's just pure bigotry but but
Heard of syrtis
So we come to the end of this 2003 episode and you know I think that
Cannibals got a lot of attention
Not enough anymore
Deep homophobia
Throughout this
The collars
Are much more interesting
I think in the past and in the present
And that's because I think
Make that a lot of them are
Really interested in weird Fringe
Militia e-community you bring some of that sensibility to Alex's show
Where is Maui
He doesn't take a whole lot of colors
Most of them just
Parrot back to him what he said
Just a plug for a product right
And then there's like Carlos
Canada
Calls in every f****** time Alex takes calls
And
It's just it's it's
Not
It's not like this
I mean idiots
Almost
Cute but I think the word I'm thinking of it
Quaint
Glycol of these callers
Are almost Queen
It's like look at you with your
Guy from Denver is
This is a bleeding Appalachia
It's it's
You know what it is
Quaintness it feels like a sustainable ecosystem
It hasn't self-selected out for Bluetooth
Even though it's a bigoted show and
You know obviously everything is
Saying a stupid or awful
It doesn't feel destined for collapse
No it really doesn't
If there's not there's not like a feeling of
It doesn't feel destined for Success either though kind of feels like if this
This exact show happened
Everyday with an audience of like
200,000 people it could have gone on forever
You know like this could have just been played out every day for the rest of our lives
No one would have really known about it but him and the 200,000 people and it would have been fine
But
But here we are
Is ambitions
What you going to do it like icarus's wings flew him too close to the Sun that's only it weren't a pattern that played out every
Single f****** day
You got in bed with mr. blood
That was that that was where it all falls apart
Mr. Mudd and mr. gold
Probably back to the present day we'll see if Alex has vacation at last the rest of the week
Maybe he's in the forest for good could be
I am become all the time
I will see.
Jordan
But until then I'm needle I'm Leo and bcx Clark I'm
Doctor marble
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work