Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge by now I'm sick of them posing
Knowledge fight
The elders Lane and talk a little bit about Alex
June
Question for you
We got a little Asia package in the mail
I was a big old box
Candy
Probably and I don't see it so it was a really enjoyable box still a fair amount of it left
Stop it
Eat so much candy
Oh my God it's it's a great there's some
And no
Will the wheels are fanciful
And I do love a hobnob though the oats
Man
British candies are better than ours man I should say that the candies are for me
Then there's some like weird pickles
Marmite looks for you
No more batteries specifically there's no notes
That makes perfect sense that's supposed to get the the raisin
The raisins I don't like those
Somebody wouldn't send us Ravens
Knowing that you don't like
Unless they specifically wanted me to have
Exactly you got it you got to consider intent
Yeah I know I haven't
My bright spot Dan is went out
Last night with my partner and her teacher friends to toolbar
Worst place I've ever been to In My Life who is awful
It's like a giant frat
Tailgate party on the roof
I'm not going to name the place but it's awful okay and it was
Just
It was so great
For one reason I would have a Gilbert and beer
There is a the teachers
Are all struggling with their principal at school
The school's name
I don't want to give it
However there was a giant
Cutout of a football player
From the Bears
Number for Lac
I just
So appropriately
The wind knocked it over onto one of
The teacher's head
I was just a metaphor for how
They're doing it's cool it was this football player one who is known to tackle people
Tackle people out of character for the state
Exact
Well it's fun
It was a emblematic
Awesome I'm glad you had a good time out last night because I didn't know I'm sorry I was in
So here's the deal Alex's Saturday emergency
Podcast from March 5th
And tell you that's why I'm
Complaining having a good time and released this in the evening
Flipping it around in order for us to get it out
Has been asthma
Challenge
Without a studio until Friday
And
So I so here we are
I'm mad about it
Spiritually his heart may still be in the woods
Florida
Kevin I level meetings with
You would assume so there's a lot of b******* going on here and
I'm not saying that it is a big pig
Picture of my patience has worn out
Who wears out a little bit
On the way through this episode I will I will say I'm sick of his b*******
Two and a half hours long because report power 20
I was ready to
Do I send it to the Moon
Business on this truck but first let's not take a little moment say hello
Do first
Waking up my partner with Alex Jones saying I love you is going to ruin my relationship that you so much right now about
Thank you very much thank you so much you are now but was he walk
What's next week is vaccinated goblins boosted goblins thank you so much
I came for the shrieks and stay for the freaks
Very much
Picture
So I think so much to our dear Lord
I have
Risen above
Miami star
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
Apologized
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not the reason
I'll lose my
Frustrated
I don't tend to have a history of watching Alex's Saturday special reports
Periodically
They're long and typically is interviewing people I'm not really all that interested in
And so I usually give them a pass
Listening to this made me realize a couple things
Alex needs commercial breaks
Cuz without them
This gets unbearable
Just him talking without music coming in and
Singing over where you belong to the city or whatever like
Without that
This is a struggle like a two-hour lecture
Play uninterrupted except by a periodic like a you know what I got iodine
Like it
Rough that's brutal it is
And it's really hard to because he's doing is trying to
You know we've from topic
Make the topic
It's just
It's disorienting and stupid
I mean he needs brakes to head towards
Without the without the like
Momentum downslope
Towards the break
The whole thing is just s*** my guy needs offering he needs offering his half of the show is leading towards
The off ramp
It's building towards the point where he can do a
Plug and then go to commercial like the ability to drive
More but on hill so as long as you can use the brakes right
You can keep moving
Right answers
Involve like sort of dramatic tension and that is based on the
The timing
Of the breaks we got to go to break
It conceivably will have a new thought that begins on the other side of the break or will continue this but we will got into a
Stopping point it without the brakes
S***
It's just
You get lost
If the officers didn't have the music to play people off
Ubisoft watch
It'll be long
So we start off
Beginning of this year report
I got leanza Alex's
Naturally talking about some Russia Ukraine news
He's got some really really accurate up to date news
Putin has warned that any no-fly zone any country entering militarily
War
And that the exact
Second the very second
That
Any Nation joins in with Ukraine an attack
Russian forces that the Russia will be at
War with
That country
Germany has responded
And said that Ukraine's NATO membership will not
Place
German
Chancellor
Schultz
Or something that
Did was ask
Before before he launched
Abrasion
So this is kind of a meaningless piece of news that Alex is covering but if you consider the point of what he saying
Acetone
That will be
Verified
As we go along
When I say this is meaningless it's because these aren't news items that are not unexpected
Of course Putin would say that putting in a no-fly zone over Ukraine to be considered by him to be inactive
To be war with any country
Good sides for what
Not an awful position it's not news really I mean
The idea about setting up a no-fly zone would be if a Russian plane where to fly into the no-fly zone
It would be attacked by a Brighton
So that would be inactive
DeVore
It's very simple and it's not something that
Hasn't already been understood the invasion
When The Invasion album everybody was like if we wanted to we would have already done it
Simultaneously it's also not news to say that Germany is, take the Ukraine will be put into NATO
Contacts
Prior to the invasion German Chancellor Olaf scholz there was no plan to bring Ukraine into the group
I have very strong hands off perspectives about sending Aid
Emily duffley invasion they banned any other country from sending german-made weapon
Things to help the ukrainians
The extent of their support was just sending some helmets
$5000000 for a field hockey
However the invasion was a very serious turning point in terms of how Germany Angels government
In particular
Feels about their place in
The greater scheme of European affairs
After Putin invaded Germany went back on their long-standing provision of providing lethal Aid
Which honestly is a huge deal
Shoals gave a speech in front of the bundestag on February 27th which signal
Complete change of policy
In German international affairs
Quote fellow-citizens 24th of February 2022 marks a watershed in the history of our continent
What's the attack on Ukraine the Russian President Putin has started a war of aggression
In Cold Blood
Clearly laid out the aggression on Ukraine is being a clear and immediate threat to the security of the whole of Europe a
Poze multi-prong
Plan
The first element was
Supporting Ukraine
The second was an attempt to quotes
Divert Putin from the path of War
Largely by way of economic sanctions and embargo
The third was stopping any possible sprawl in the war by unconditionally defending any NATO member country
A particularly by a particular by beefing up presents
In countries like Romania and Lithuania
The fourth was coming to terms with the fact that Putin is in fact intent on building a larger Empire
1/5 was rethinking energy Supply
This was a strong statement of participation in the isolation of Putin and the recognition of the need to support
People in Putin's pass
This is a Far Cry 4
Position coming from trolls
A week prior
That's notable because
Germany was the main country along with macron
Kaput and prior to the invasion
There's a real feeling here that this is someone who is deeply involved in the attempt to avert The Invasion
Responding to the invasion with a change in tone
Go to previous data
Is quo
To leave you to think maybe he knows something that isn't Pub
It's almost as though in those negotiations
He was under the impression that absolutely we would be able at the very least to have a good
Conversation about peace
And he's probably figured out that that was never are part of the f******
Suggested
I think that's a very possible interpretation of of these event
So here's where the angle announces commentary come
He's trying to paint a picture where the reality is the Putin is getting what you wanted
He wanted Ukraine not to join NATO and here's Germany saying they weren't going to join
But the issue was the Germany said they prior to the invasion very clearly
Joel said in the press conference which he gave a long with zelensky that quotes
What's the question of Ukraine membership in the alliance's
Is practically not on the agenda
This isn't something that's been a change in town it's with Germany's position as well as the position of some other European countries
Long before the invasion
What else is doing
Is attempted to create the image of a victory for food
But it's nothing of the sort
Ukraine wasn't going to be joining NATO anytime soon
Even if their password membership was still on the table and a future possibility
The notion that they were going to be joining and that it was a done deal
Was paruppu justification for his invasion and Alex's essentially playing along with that entire framing
Situation
Was going to go into NATO did once we invaded now they're not going
This is exactly the sort of thing you'd expect
Wait to hear from a committed Putin Fanboy Apollo
Apologist of propaganda
And here's the thing 2
Given Germany's very foundational shift in in terms of
Sending weapons
It may be the case of a rethink some other thing
Thanks to like the prospect
I'm supporting Ukraine to join NATO
I'm not saying it's necessarily going to be the case but if anything it seems like his invasion could make that more likely
As well as the
Possibility people understand the need to protect other country
There's there's no doubt Vision happened
More and more countries immediately were like
Let's join 80
I think that's a way better place to be then they guys gave being invaded right now what's happening
This wouldn't be happening if we had the backing of
The obligation of the rest of the world specially a lot of the rest of the world
Yeah it's so this is a strange way that Alex is starting
Bring out the the show
It gives you a real sensitive
The Putin Fanta
Yeah yeah yeah the best way to keep Ukraine from joining NATO is to install a probe
New regime
That's usually the best way
It seems to work to starkly
That they're going for
Yeah
Is here a vision
Now better dumb
We just are that incredible report that so important
Pentagon funded bioweapons lab in Ukraine it is
Confirmed
But US Government documents
They tried to take down
That's not fake news
Caesars
Qanon narratives that Alex must have seen someone posted a meme about on social media and he's decided to report
What's fascinating about this is actually predates
It's covid-19
State media for
4 years
Predictably this brand
Conspiracy was deployed to shift blame around after Russia poison Sergei skripal
His daughter with enervate
The US doesn't help fun some labs in countries like Ukraine and Georgia but the reasoning behind that is pretty simple
After the Soviet Union broke up there were remnants of old chemical and biological aging
Research
They can be done on these things are being done in unsafe location
USM Ukraine entered into a weapons proliferation
2005 those
Funding to modernize these facilities that Ukraine is already operating
So that they would have a far lower risk of something going
Terribly wrong
Nerve agents in
Chemical weapons getting out
Yeah that's why
This involves a certain amount of information-sharing but ultimately the Ukrainian Ministry of Health is still in charge.
These facilities
Flash forward to the covid-19 China both putting four theories of the viruses made in the lab
Ukraine
The reasons for this serve the number of purposes for each count
We're trying to help push back against the insane conspiracy theories being peddled by people like Alex about China creating the fire
A Russia it allowed Putin
Western involvement in and the Ukrainian government as a whole
As a threat
Russia which with them justify hostile action against them
Or at least rationalize continued hostilities in the Don Bosco
Right just cuz it's not true doesn't mean it's not useful
Right
Conspiracy theories of the early days of the pandemic
There are just too many shiny objects
Distraction conspiracy theorist on Old battle over Ivermectin and Hydrox
Chloroquine in the Alexa
January 6th
Holy subject attention away for of people like Alex and they lost
But now the Russians invaded Ukraine
Conspiracy theorist on the hunt
Anything that can Intrigue people
It also make Putin's Invasion justifiable to their audiences
Gold nugget is getting another chance
Spotlight
After this point I've really only heard this Theory getting play on qanon Outlets
So I guess Alex is
Just decide like my esophagus
Maybe I'll give it a shot
It's really bad and the only reason you report on something like this let alone lead your program with it is if you're trying to fight
Look good
Lecture he's bombing civilian targets and waging an unnecessary war of aggression but secretly he's trying to shut down these us run by
Biological weapons Labs man
He's creating heroic story for his listeners to accept so they don't get that idea in their head did Putin is bad
I'm not sure if he's being subtle about this but it actually seems hard to imagine awake be more insidiously trying to get
His audience to support Putin
Well trying to couches commentary in like
I don't know plausible deniability an unjust War unless
He saved all of us from a biological warfare and show you something next covid
And all of us are just
Getting in his way we do it
Ma'am
Thrust of the
Narrative being deployed
F***** up 100% okay too
Publicly murder people but is long as you're secretly
Saving the world from bioweapon
Since it don't exist as long as we can come up with a fake
Secret reason that you're doing things to do
Hey it's game on August for us
So
Alakazam
Concerns
About the way things are going mostly that
Lucaya don't like to have to
Bring this up
Buttom
All ukrainians are liars family
Calculation ceasefire breaks down remain cold
We don't know that's true because
Someone's getting Ukraine in the mainstream media lie about everything
Flyers either
You can't believe a damn thing they say like the attack on the reactor
And it would melt
Screw
The ghost
The Snake Island
The list goes on and on
Alex doesn't
Struggle with statements like this when Putin
He doesn't say that Putin said something who knows if it's true cuz he's a liar
That kind of skepticism is reserved for claims from and about Ukraine
And there's a utility to this as well
He's an attempt to give his audience permission to not believe claims that Russian troops are not honoring things like civilian
Quarters we're not combatants going to leave but
Beach cities which is something that has been reported
There was an agreement to allow citizens to leave Mario Paul
That ad that was peace after reports
Eyewear that Russian forces
Discontinued shelling the city
Not honoring
Ceasefire
Attack on
Will you could call that a lie
Haha
Alex doesn't want that image.
Even be considered
Possible for his audience
It's because
That looks bad
Yeah I want to look at these examples that Alex list in order to justify his claims it selenski and Ukraine
Lie about everything
See if there's any ground to stand on here
Any sorts of conflict there obviously some things to get played up for PR and to appeal to the International Community
That's part of information Warfare but the question becomes
What is the nature of the thing that
It's being used for information Warfare
Obviously lying about an atrocity weather saying one did happen when it didn't
Or saying one didn't when it did is an evil form
Of information Warfare
I want engages in this kind of
Action constantly
Most notably with his lies and denial regarding Syria and Assad's use of chemical weapons
As far as I can tell there's no instances of anything rising to that level coming from Salina
Notice Alex even
Have it listed ranks
Anywhere close
The first thing I'll explain that the attack on the reactor was a lie or that it was the other was melting down and leaking is a
People on Twitter definitely went a bit overboard with that but definitely
To happen
I'll be firing on the plant went on
Demetrio kuleba Ukraine
Foreign affairs minister tweeted
Russian army is firing on all sides from Zappos
Power plant
Fire is already broken out if it blows up it'll be ten times larger than Chernobyl Russians must immediately cease fire
Firefighters
Established
Security Zone
This you could say it's Sensational possibly if you want to or you can say that it was a person who
Who is concerned
But a nuclear power plant was on fire and then something needed to be done about it
You could say that the comments you made were possibly inaccurate or over-the-top but that's
Model y
Really
I mean
Because there were tons of people who were coming back with
Sober like listen here all the safety measures here all the things it's
Probably not going to explode
It's bad but it's not going
To be like a movie
F****** freak out there's not going to giant mushroom cloud that covers
You know all of Europe
At the same time
We're shooting rockets in the nuclear power plant man that's not a joke
Right right
Regardless of any possible over statements by the foreign affairs minister to whitewash
Shocking Act of the Russian military targeting nuclear power
A dangerous wax
I don't know if this counts as like
Haha such a liar that you shouldn't believe anything these people say
Yeah
The second suppose lie Alex brings up his a ghost of kids the story that went around on the first day of the invasion about it
Ace pilot everybody f****** love
Yeah
It sort of Snoopy
Yeah I mean it's just a mirror
Initially a video when around there was supposedly have a pilot who's being called The Ghost of Kiev shooting down a Russian plane put it
Video game digital combat simulator world
Halo Pictures supposedly of him have all been shown to be fake and ultimately this is a situation where this person maybe
Not a real
Single person
They're couple aspects of this that make it not the same as the malicious sort of information Warfare that we discussed Alex participating
There's no indication that the government started this story as it appears to just popped up on social media which does make a difference
Also the intention here is very clear
A huge fear in terms of the matchup between Ukraine and Russia was that Russia had almost comical air superiority and that
I would be Ukraine's downfall
People on social media amplifying a folktale about a mysterious fighter pilot with an ominous alias
It helped people believe that there was a
It was a piece of information Warfare that served only the purpose of raising morale and I don't think
The kind of thing you should really consider so heinous
Has the brand of entire country and their leader is a liar especially considering
It's a story that came out of social media
I don't think this works it's not like zielinski made up the ghost
Cube Storage
He's like let's get this out there
Yeah
The third example Alex uses a snake island actually one of the worst
Cases he could point
Initially the story was at these people who were stationed at Snake Island told the Russian boat to f***
Themselves when they died
Or at least it was assumed they died because all radio contact with him was lost
There was yelling and no one knew what happened so it was assumed
As it turns out they were taken hostage by the Russian troops are still alive
This wasn't known until Russia released footage of them being held in premiere
It doesn't actually change the real powerful part of the story though which is still true
I think the people responded to so strongly and that story was the audio of the Russian boat telling them to surrender and them telling
The f*** off
Defiant in the face of not just overwhelming odds but
Comically overwhelming
That is true and they tried to repeal the Russian
Attack but ultimately ran out of
Emma and they were captured but that the Russian troops to f*** themselves was real and real and that's why
People were responding to
Ibotta
Ultimately none of the things Alex brings up as examples of things that make him sure that selenski and Ukraine or Liars
This makes sense
Because all he
He's doing here is grasping at straws to create a justification for his audience to believe that everything they hear about rushing attacks on sofa
Is not true
Because how can you possibly believe these people with what
That this damning list of lies that Alex has presented
It's all just more attempts by Alex does a pork bun without having to say that that's what he's doing he's a coward
That it's totally okay for food to go into another sovereign country and bombs
The s*** out of innocent people
But I will say that it's okay
So long as
Whatever is okay they even have his m************ Liars
Talking about a ghost pilot
Exaggerator
These these people who are
Relying on hyperbole to expire inspire people who would ever consider that
I think that there is a difference
Between like
Let's say
Propaganda the country would put out that denies their own like
Atrocity
Atrocities
And
Propaganda that a country could put out whether it's someone else puts it out of a tacitly approve of it or they even put it up
Absolve
Hey
Soldiers get laid
42 like propaganda films words like
Yeah that is kind of like
It's a little bit
Dishonest jingoist
But it's not the same thing as like
I can't believe anything these f****** today
I think you'd be hard-pressed to find a country that would
Engage in that kind of morale-boosting
PR campaign
Because why would you be like
Chick-fil-A
We are dedicated only to the truth in advertising here we have lost this battle brutally
We're going to win this war or the opposite side like nothing is going to help holyshit
We're f****** dead said even the truth it's like
Lay down
Just latest
So anyway really strong sense from the beginning of this special report that Alex is pretty invested in
Well the same time pretending he's not
Yeah
Something really weird
Show the prognosis
Run
From bad to worse
I just really can't lie to you and I'm not
That
This is the date
What not everybody is going to
Hold on
Find God
Lot of folks are going to find
Chaos in Oblivion in Mindless
And this is all just a big test
Equipped understanding and gods
Input it was them
Complete
Wisdom
That this is simply a
Test
And so we have to be very sad for those that fail it
What realize that this plan and everything on it what we're doing is
Completely and totally
Prince
The actor just turned loose on
I think listeners and viewers know things aren't
Going to get very nice
Llamas playing at 90% of everybody dead
By 2030
Explaining like they really mean to do this and they're really putting things in
Function
They're going to end civilization as we know it
Civilization breaks down
Go watch a movie like The Road Warrior
For the early 1980s
And and that's going to be like Jose
Vacation spot
That hellish dystopic
Nightmare future
Is that guy's I had this framed over the weekend
Friday and I forgot to bring it
It's sitting here on my couch and my officer on my desk I had it
Meant to bring it in here with some of my doors open mob
Well what are you grateful
Carolina office and get me
Diagram
Got a bunch of overlap
Points
It's a meme I saw a god
Good work of God meme
Framed it
Frame to meme
That's your real NFP right there oh my f****** god
Yo
Doing this
Disgusting
Justification session then
Patience bad at everyone's going to be dead
8 years here's a business all the simulation also I should tell you I framed of meme Jesus Christ
I've got to have somebody go get for my office going on in that short clip
2 minutes
What arrived
Amazing
Also I can
Cialix being a post-apocalyptic guy wearing a wearing a hockey mask for screaming on vacation
Soro Soro
Yeah I would say that if I was going to come up with a title for this episode
It would be Alex frame to meme
It's shocking
And it is
There's more time spent on it then you might like
All of the Nene is more times than I might like you're out you're not wrong
But I was promises he's going to talk about this Meme and then he's going to get to the real shift
It's a meme I saw
Thursday and I ask my assistant
On my
That's Daddy
Someone
Tell folks that has mild
Walk down the hall
And to bring that to not be great
Thank you very much
And I think this says that also
What I'm doing here is this diagram
And then I'm going to be a good
Boy
And stop
Holding back
And
Go ahead just
What are you holding back
Hot you know what I'm telling you everybody who is ever written like a history book or anything like
What kind of idiots are spending thousands of words
Whenever you could put a meme out there
Explains It All
You can you imagine like a text
Book I was just full of memes
That's how you would get a
Good education as opposed to these words
It's so it's a better way to learn
So he has to get somebody to bring it from his office
And this takes a little while so this is a bit
And I
He's talking about some muscle covid stuff
That's great news
It's coming out that they did this
But then when you read the sparse 20-25 2028 Dodge Demon
Put out by
Rockefeller John Hopkins in Belmont
Grove
They talked about
How would they hit us with the bio-weapon
How they're going to get caught in the process
And how that's meant to
Trigger
The loss of confidence in the government the system and collapse
Civilization
I was just making that up
When we covered Spar as in-depth episode
The park is just
Completely
Is just out of his imagination
The idea that officials want to get caught with this whole Web of Lies in order to Road faith in the government notary classes it comes in
Byerly
Discussing the late stages of the pandemic response
Square a fraction
Send reports a Big Mac
Emergency funding appropriated by Congress to fight the disease became available partway through the course of
The pandemic
Federal state and local public health agencies
Struggle to manage the procedural requirements
Despondent
I would result in significant amounts of emergency funds remained unused as the panic
Pandadoc wound down
Have you been suggestions grew in intensity several high-ranking officials at the CDC and FDA were forced to step down
And withdrawal from government in order to
To quote spend
More time with their family
Exhausted employees of these agencies many of whom worked long hours six or seven days a week throughout the pandemic
Simply wanted to put the whole response
Behind them
Little desire remained on the part of decision-makers are those who served in the trenches during the response to rehash the events
How the past several years
In this fictitious scenario that's being used in the sex
Exercise some people had misappropriated funds and possibly stolen some of the money but
Instead of dragging through the mud they resigned
To quote spend more time with their families
That's the passage in this document it out
What is transformed into the carburetor that you're seeing him present here
Cuz he's a malicious liar and also it's ridiculous we saw in real life it's people from the FED who wanted up resigning for
All of their insider trading
Duh
They got it wrong
Anyway
He's he started to read talk about
The sparse thing
That's that seems to be more present in his mind
And soon
I want to just give a little bit of
A refresher on it here and there
But the meme
Shows up got to find out what it is
That this meme
Explain this meme
Is tragic
How tragic
So-so
So so so tragic
No Titus isn't included a lot of other works of fiction.
Show
Here's a meme I saw
Meteors
But it's a bunch of
Overlapping circles
Diagram in the middle it says you are here
There's a bunch of
Disculpe
Films and books
TV shows
You got the Hunger Games the bottom in 1984 at the topping
Brave New World over on the left
Idiocracy on the ride
And they lives up in the
Corner and you got Fahrenheit 451
You got animal farm he got Mad Max
You got soil it green
You got the mail
Really you are here
Black artists
And futuristic
Can people
Projecting forward
Of what they thought the world would look like if things weren't turned around
This is really stupid moron brand for Alex
Moussaka
Cat meme
Huge huge loser
Problems of his meme
What are the largest being good to Worlds that are depicted in these various pieces of fiction are at
Contradictory with each other mutually exclusive
Explicitly at odds with each other
And Aldous Huxley speech Brave New World Revisited that Alex likes to cite and lie about all the
What time
At its core this meme is a complex Venn diagram
That's really where the trouble began
The point of it is it's obviously supposed to be that you're at this intersection of all these pieces of dystopian fiction
The middle
You're here
It's cute
But it's also really lazy and doesn't pay any respect to the pieces of fix
It's using as a prop
Are there are
For actual Circle
Send that everything else
Is just the intersection of those Circle
To the four circles are 1984
Theocracy Hunger Games
In Brave New World
From where you get the areas that overlap with your label does being depicted as other movies
Okay now
Play a game
Alright I'm going to give you the movie that appears in this Meme and you have to tell me the combination of what makes that movie using those
For initial
Movies wow this is fun I think you should bring this me
Service audio jidenna
Lord of the Flies
There's three component okay those for initial movies create the Lord of
Okay Lord of the Flies
I'm going to go with
What were the four movies again
Idiocracy 1984 Hunger Games in Brave New World
Hunger Games
Nineteen Eighty-Four and Idiocracy
Lord of the Flies they didn't create a good Brave New World
World where they kill Piggy
I did not see that part.
There's two movies that makeup they live they live has to be 9
I'm going to tell you your correct
And
Stampy Hunger Games
You know what I'm going to go ahead and go with Idiocracy
Brave New World
The Brave New World
So that means what
The Matrix there's three components of Matrix
These are a combination of 1984 in A Brave New World
That's what I thought
I guess baby by you should be able to get this by world and hunger
Matt was Hunger Games simulator
Who knows
Mad Max
Okay well that's got to be
Brave New World
Hunger Games Hunger Games Idiocracy
Nothing idiotic about the government
What are very smart for 51
Idiocracy because they're burning books
Maybe anyway the point is if his name is stupid but he pretends to be literate make
The points are Alex's printed it out framed and he's possibly mere days away from selling it as a shirt
There's a ton of variations of this meme using different works of fiction like one
Once other than Alex's version use things like V for Vendetta Logan's Run handmaid's tale Gattaca Clockwork Orange
The point is that the specific pieces of fiction or interchangeable for whatever other books
The movie 1408 because
This isn't about to make
An actual point it's selling a feel it's just flavor of dystopia today
Yeah but interesting lie if you look back over the history of this me and you'll find it actually grew out of a mean friend
Or people are making
Fun of people comparing everything to 1984
Early versions of a really simple just a Venn diagram of 1984 Brave New World in Fahrenheit 451
With a you are here in the middle
More less mocking the idea of how unaware these books people are real about everything being orwellian
Using this meme structure to make fun of people like Alex going back to at least last year so
It's pretty fun that Alex has decided to frame a picture of people mocking him and his illiteracy he's taking it back though
He's taking it back
Houses
Been on vacation for a week and he comes back and he decides he should take time to brag about framing a meeting listen to possibly insulting
Sing to him meme
Guys just f****** impressively stupid
What does mean for like half an hour or so
But here's that he's a real Mike
Mo McRae
Humans are really good at envisioning where things
Are going a lot of people
Another bad if it's books
Instead
This is kind of where they think the world's going
These are social commentary about
What the world would be like in
The year 20
You know what movies
In 20
No
Guess which one
Soylent Green
Haha we're made of people
Crew make in 1999
Also the book didn't involve cannibalism in the form of Soylent Green thousand invention of the studio so I guess Alex Reid
Really likes the prophetic work of Richard Fleischer
Who was the director who also Direct
The Jazz Singer which featured Neil Diamond blackface
Bright Perry Harrison the author of make roommate group has even said that the cannibalism ideas dumb because you couldn't process enough
Enough meat to feed the hungry people that way
What is that
Every time I've Been Told
Because I've been told many times
Neil Diamond
Did blackface
Every time I'm like
Behringer Jazz Center
And then it happens again
Exact same way and I think that must be why everybody just gives him the pass on that is because nobody believes it
Really happened it's it's shocking first of all to hear that Neil Diamond starred in a movie
Yeah yeah
SMS redirected that
Alex's seen movie
He said he wants to pretend or real but he also knows that he would sound really dumb if you didn't protect these ideas
Literate background
These people who wrote
These works are envisioning
In the future they worried about coming to pack
That's right
Really not true in most of these cases and all that Alex is either intentionally missing or incapable of grasping with the actual point
Have any of these stories actually even about
Also who gives a s*** when they stories are set
Idiocracies in 2505
None of it means anything
In my book
Spoiler alert
The world end
And it's not cuz I thought that's how it was going to happen
Little John
Some of it is a rhetorical device
Alex is really dumb
He's been a long time so I can let this meme but finally decides to jump off
Into other
Territories
When we hit this imma try to move the quickest
All this
And I'm just
Pearson Realize
What a big
Deal
All of this is
And the fact that
This information comes out
And then
It's like
Blowing on a dandelion in a little
Little parachutes
Spores
BuzzFeed go out of it
Disappear is a WinCo
They don't know where they land or
Ali eversprout
Where that information goes but
Nevertheless
This information needs
To find fertile ground
Cloud Music spikes pressing like his is
Show is being like a Dandy lion with all the parachutes going out
And they need to take Route somewhere in order for the plant to
Continue but I would say that it's also
Kind of like that because
It's just random
He just throws a bunch of s*** out there and hopes that landed some soil somewhere
Breakdown let's call it Society sidewalk
So to speak
Yeah if there's other there's other ways it is an apt metaphor it's a surprisingly good metaphor for him
It was delivered in an incredibly clunky way
Yeah that's terrible
So did the big news there's there's some big covid news
Is that Alex needs to get to
And the first has to do with
I recently B commentary made by the head of the CDC Rachel y Lennox
The CDC come out Friday
I got the clip coming up
And she said
Oh
We were wishful thinking
The vaccine doesn't work where
Sorry
You follow it's a war game
Attacking us
Is a simulation of what you really do
A great deal this talk is just Alex rambling and grandiose terms but it is a bayou
And all this other s***
There really wasn't any concrete claims being made for long stretches
Isn't that so
Is actually just
To talk about
CDC Rachel come out and apologize and say the back
Don't work
That's about to pull
Yeah that doesn't sound true University of Washington and that's a very reflective things
Things to say about the pandemic response of the messaging around vaccines
Speaking about how vaccines are being tested and they were seeing 95% rates
Let some people may have been too full of optimism but little Caution particularly surrounding ideas
Waning immunity and possibility of new variants copy and covered
As effectively by the vaccine
This was specifically in response to a question of where
Could have been
True speaking about messaging failures less than she was saying at the vaccine didn't work mostly because she wasn't saying that at all
How it seems pretty hot on the sparse document on this episode
Bring it up and making s*** up about it
I suspect he feels like it's been long enough since he's really talked about it his audience with his
Forgotten the main talking
Points around the document we could just use it to fill in whatever holes
But he hasn't his conspiracy like I originally part of the
No
Let's just almost
Like he's just using it where like where it's convenient cuz that's all he ever does
This thing about vaccines not working doesn't happen in that scenario exercise
It's important to remember that this is an exercise based on public health message
So every chapter is meant to pick up
Particular challenge
I could come up in the course of a pandemic
Make a turtle house
To effectively communicate information
Open to the public
Henderson area there are two drugs that are Central in Port
Thursday
And there's an already existing antiviral drug that shows some promise of work
Condensed bars
Called Kawasaki
Chapter 9 is about messaging The Dilemma of finding out that 4 in further Trials of color severe the
Actually effective
Treating sparse
And they pursuing it
Is possible cure has to be abandoned even though a lot of money is
Open put into test
People ever predictable social media backlash to the withdrawing of Kelo severe is a pretend
Which is
Expressed as distrust
The government has any idea that they know they're doing
Around the pandemic
This is a no way and I'll get to the story that Alex is telling anti be generous when I say that this is the part of the document he's lying about
It's entirely possible that he's just
Making up what he saying
Yeah I was going to say
You can you can
Can say that it's part of this part
That he's
Yeah yeah he could be he could be thinking about a completely different parts
It has nothing to do with what he's talking about
100%
A physical thing is just
Out of the
The realm of normal this is the problem of trying to like ground some of the stuff in reality and sources
Is it sometimes it's
It's not going to happen
Another big narrative is the big
New listen to Big Nate big covid-19
The Blaze
Okay
Glenn Beck's outfit new bit of
Information
It's all come out it isn't a vaccine
It's all come out doesn't help you
It's all come out attacks your body
Attach your double helix
And now what
This is the big new news
The new news
The great researchers thank God there now fully awaken our naive anymore
At The Blaze
Did something smart
They put in a foia request
Concerning federal government spending on propaganda
Pushing the cupboard narrative
And the ended
Anti Ivermectin
Demerit Amanda pro-vaccine there
It isn't a vaccine
Documents for yourself I spent an hour today reading
And the government admits they're real
$1000000 with spin
In the first year
Abide Megan office secretly
To buy off
Thousands of mainstream media Outlets TV station
Networks
Newspapers local TV
Just one program we know of
1 billion dollars and they had to sign agreement
But they would have no
Anti-vaccine cover
Total fraud
So when real investigative journalist Folia documents one of the really important things that they do is they post the underlying.
Document so people are reading about their their release can review the actual documents and assess whether or not they match up
But the claims that are being made in the reporting
It should come as no surprise
The Blaze article that I was just covering
Contains no links
Any of these actual documents to claim that they got from the Department of Health
Human Services
The article is posted on the blaze has nothing to do with any information they would have been found at any of these supposed
It's just complaining about media coverage of covid
And then pointing to already public in
Information
Like the fact that the American
Rescue plan act or HR 1319
Contained 1 billion dollars in funding for hhsd engaging activities to code
Strengthen vac
Being
None of the information in this article would require any for your documents to write
If this guy even got documents
They aren't as revelatory or shocking as he'd hope so the strategy is just to use their supposed existence as a prop
While repeating
Other salacious information that's already public in the body of the article
Also to be clear the 1 billion-dollar claim isn't from Florida.
It's from HR 1319 and not all of that
Was spot-on advertise
Without the actual document there's nothing being reported here it's just insinuation invade client
Also
Another report they can point out is that these guys really f***** up their story
The whole thing is
Administration did this but if you go and consult The Blaze article they say that this happened
Did fiscal year 2021 which is the same as 2021
No year 2020 what goes from May 1st 20
22 April 30th 2020 W it's actually something happen under Trump
Ouch
This is partially because the blaze article is cherry picking
Information and not putting it in
Contacts for the readers
Recite the American Rescue plan act as a source of this funding but the language in that bill is real
Continuation
The Consolidated Appropriations Act of 2020
Future signed by Trump
Overall this whole article seems deeply misleading
This paragraph shows up in the post
Quote though virtually all of these newsrooms produced stories covering the covid-19 facts
The taxpayer dollars flowing to their companies were not disclosed to audiences a news report
That's common practice dictates that editorial teams operate independently of media advertising Department
I am news teams felt no need to make a disclosure
It's a Publications reached for comment explained
They have literally no evidence or even the suggestion of Ebony
Any of the money went
News reports about covid
The best of Blaze can do is include a comedic video that was run on NBC featuring Elton John and Michael Caine
That ends with the big placard disco a disclosing funding from the NHS
That's not even the United States and it includes clear disclosure and it's a funny video
I would say whatever documents they got show that they chest
Slots for psa's if they made
And which contain disclosure funding
Sources and now the story is being spawned in saying they paid NBC-2 have fauci on or some b*******
Also important to point out that Alex is also making up details here
The Blaze story itself is
Dumb just making stuff up about it that doesn't even appear in the article
Other weird Point those it
Infowars didn't even
Post The Blaze story on their website
They posted a write-up about the blaze article
From someone named Emerald Robinson substitute
She seems like a dumb dumb
Buzz Marketing
Infowars is worried that Glenn Beck wouldn't just let them steal his contentedly Post-it like everybody else
Either way this is really dumb it's not a bombshell at all
I would say
This guy's got to post these for your document
If he wants me to take this seriously
Yeah one way to say I'm not going to go I'm not going to go to wild goose chase cuz I went to the foia site and I searched
Didn't find anything and I'm not going to
Through every single HHS
Related
No you are not I don't have time
Nope sowbug
Show your work ding dong
Another way of describing someone is having bought off
The media company
Is to say they
Purchased advertise
Right
You know they spent money on creating psa's
Which were very clearly psa's someone could assume that they're from the government included was funny too
But it was Elton John audition
To be in a commercial for covid
Weather like
It's giving me directions on how to deliver the line
Conduit Michael Caine impression
At the end of the I don't know what call you back we'll see
Glycol Yahoo NFL
Who you going to get in the short time then flashes to Michael Kay
Alright that's fine what are you going to do what you going to b**** about that
So yeah they paid for those to be made and probably take for PSAs lots and I don't think that this is ask
Scandal
Bike Raven desperate weirdos who work for Glenn Beck's
No it's not strong
Man
They could do so much better
Really couldn't
Do all their processes based on building these convenient and useful lies
Is they can't do better and
Because
Reporting accurate things
Wouldn't be exciting for the audio
Now and then the feedback loop gets broken up
People stopped paying attention
Your side cuz you're too into information
Contacts how do I remove you're not giving me that adrenaline boost that I'm looking
Did something I don't like
And so inevitably you just
Do you do you
You had a chase the dragon that is the audience's fickle attention
Anyway Alex gets mad about how
No one told
Us that we were beat these things were
Being done this piece fundings Scandal is it Fox News
And
Newsmax
Are apparently people who took some of this advertisement money
They're supposed to be cool
Supposed to be on the side of the Patriot Railroad
While the FED say it's secret how much they paid news
But they did
And of course Fox
That's what I always say I'm not saying you shouldn't take the vaccine
Everybody should get directions
All we're saying is you shouldn't be made to do it
They were told on ABC NBC you name it Fox
Do criticize it in anyway
If you have to say
Everybody should take it but
We have a quest
The Segway
Did anybody at Fox News or Newsmax
Rcnn
Tell you
Did they tell you
That they were being
Paid by the federal government with your taxpayer money
Ensign agreement
Do any criticism
Or talk to anybody that was critical
No
You didn't get that memo did
Because it's not true I mean I I would imagine that most of the on-air Talent have no idea what the ad
Department is up to
The complete disconnect from that stuff
Also
Dialysis make up the part about them siding
The agreements
Do they can't do any critical vaccine coverage
That's not even the boys article
Although a good piece of evidence that Alex seems to have forgotten
Counterexample to what he's talking about
Is the most
Person in the world Tucker Carlson
If
That would blow this whole advertising campaign probably if Fox News is getting all this money and Tucker Carlson won't shut
What is deadmau5
Yeah he cuz he was definitely I mean
If the money was given to Fox News 4
The previous
You know
Then Tucker
Wouldn't be the most important person in the world because he would
Have to
Say like
I'm not saying don't take your vaccines
I'm not saying no.
And then there's no way
So
Alex gets off this topic and if he starts
What's to get kotopoulo
Little introspective
About his
His court hearing
Sprout is the Saturday evening
I think
If you listen to this clip
Just trying to express
That
Globalist
Are trying to talk to him
Through his court hearing
Interest which is
That is interest
Full disclosure I'm talking to lawyers right now
Because right now
People can't do things
And mediation
That in my view was unethical or illegal
And then expect
We're not ever going to talk
But I'm going to leave it at that
But you can imagine what
Democrats
Subnautica approaching us
The frets
If we don't
Get on board with them
And they even do it in the vehicle of Lost
Which make me like okay
I never said one
And I'm going to go all the way with
Because
Here's the deal
There's no bottom
To these people
And they're so confident their takeover
They'll sit there face-to-face
And say
Get on board with us
And not only will this be taken care of
But you'll be taken care of
And you know
This isn't the only time it's just happen
Cuz I like to be able to have these meetings
And
As long as something somebody in doing it's Criminal
I'm not going to talk about it on air
Cuz I need to be able to meet with me
People invent over the years of all the
Had.
It's just insane
Show
They called the people on I said you want money or you want to be fired
Do you want money or you want to be sure
But what good is all the money when you're giving
Hundreds of millions and billions of people are shot
Double Cuts their DNA
And give them cancer and give them blood clots
I guess Alex is not decided to imagine that he's being tempted to The Darkside by globalist in his court hearings and this is getting exhausting
And really dumb
Globalist is so f****** stupid
Beaufort High School as long as people are doing anything illegal but these people are working for the devil too
To kill every human
Supposedly proven all their plans and not only that they've admitted he's right that they want
Join them to
They're doing very legal thing
Most illegal things
Anything Alex is saying
It's true if you are telling me
20 minutes
Set the globalists plan
Is to kill 90% of the world within 10 years
8 now
You're going to tell me that you're taking meetings with these folks and they're trying to convince me
To join their side
Kill 90% of the world man what's up
No no I got to keep my journalistic Integrity intact but not saying it often items I was off the Record
It was off the Record so dumb
Put aside the whole Intrigue of killing everyone off and all that stuff like chicken
Because they're attempting to extort him
None of this is real at all it's just Alex's
Do you the way that he's decided to dramatize his court hearings
Use those dramatization sad to Zone victimhood in martyrdom complex
It's kind of boring and I don't believe
I don't believe that even he believe
But yeah it'd be more fun if one of Tom Clancy's Ghost Riders rode his trial
That's what he would be gone for there
Yeah
So Alex gets to talking about how Greg Glenn back
Because I guess
He's cool now konsisten
Can't even talk about how good Glenn Beck is
I got to making it about himself
So again I will recap
The big nose
Infowars.com it's on blaze.com
I want to salute Glenn Beck
I want to encourage people to turn into his show
He's a good man
He didn't believe me
20 years ago or 10 years ago and
Thought I was a liar
Because
I was a man way out of my time
But he now knows the truth
Funny how this blood for Glenn Beck is Alex's uprofit the time nothing
To do with this article
It was written by Chris pandolfo but Alex has no interest in the little people
Everything that happens at Infowars is essentially dumb underling
Carrying out Alex as well so I
I guess he assumed the same as true everywhere else in that
Everything at the blaze is a function of
Of Glen back like every Dave Rubin episode is basically under written by
But he believes all news organization
Jebaited
Is a megalomaniacal lunatic
At the top was just telling everybody like Doling out tasks
Because a lot of the appearance
Personality trait
Sure but I think he also
Is not
That much
Of an idiot to like micromanage
So much and doesn't want to work that
Alex is working hard
So Alec
Textbook man
He left unicorn.
Everyone. It's all about God maybe
Siri is no future if you don't stop this
There's not who's the biggest talk
Show host who's got the most money in the bank
None of that means anything that might have meant something to him before
All that matters is
Good
Having relationship with God
Being able to protect
Yourself and your family into the future here
Because we may not be able to save even
Abase
6 symbolization
We are approaching
The point
Of no
Return
Right now
And that's okay
Because what
What this is really all about
Is our personal
Ship with God
And infinity
Eternity
And that's what
I thought it was about the banks
Super duper World Order
When you're when you're running Putin apologies
I'm trying to get people onto the side of it
School for Putin to go to another country murder everybody
How's your personal relationship with God strong
Strong is Godlike man you are
Crocheted apron kind of feels like this might be cowards Refuge
I think might be relying on religion to fill in the blanks for how
Terrible in cowardly
Haha
Now
I will admit
Myerly careers
Was Paul was great cuz he's going to reduce regulation
He's going to audit
That's what it's all been about the hotel really that was about to die
Auditing the Fed was about the devil
Horse
Play this next week where he's he's sort of going deeper into these thoughts just like
Imagine if after 9/11
He spoke like this
Imagine how
Non-career he would have he would not have a f****** career
If you didn't wait
Until he'd already sucked a bunch. Start with this s***
The Bible tells us
Before the simulation ends
Three-dimensional real simulation
Play everywhere the Bible says simulation
Universal
Leidsa
Where do the simulation ends next month or in
Thousand years are a trillion years
But
God gives a pretty good idea about
What
Simulations done God rolls up the universe
Scroll
We jumping
That's not in the book
Who knows of our memories will be wiped
What
Point is is
That's what this is
No career
That's gotta suck people in with this fun International conspiracy Levy the bush did 9/11
This phone false-flag stuff in Mysteries that are terrestrial that you feel like you can solve
Various influence of the Rothschilds and what have you
And you have to make
Fun of people like David Icke you say the people of shape-shifting lizards
I'm just about to
Solid provable facts
And then
Once you've duped enough people into thinking you know anything about what you're talking about in your careers
Kind of falling
Copart
Might as well just let it go and
Start with your you know
Your constant insane
Rod religious trance
Well I mean they don't start you out with Xenu on day one at scientologists true he's into that
Hey by the way
I'm going to ask you to cut your arm off in a few years check that out the cost of entry for Infowars is cheaper
Iodine is not cheap but not
Not as expensive is
Some Scientology courses
Also I don't think Alex is interested in having blackmail on dieses listener
Let's see how desperate he gets this is lunatic
Straight up
You don't got to go to wipe your memory if you believe the whole thing
What is the test
What's the point of God wipes your memory
Your memory not your ancestral memory
Your race memory
Cuz he's got to make my stuff up and then giving it religious significance
Which is what real cool Nan
Malicious narcissist when's the last time a Sci-Fi nerd got way too into religion it
It went great
I don't think Alex has the organ
Relational
Capacity
To pull us through
If the people out and not big enough
So I look
People come to him much like
Take the HHS turnout and offer him money
I have some follow-up questions
About some of this stuff
Just pathetic I mean good job Blaze
They are not to come to Blazing offering money to push the vaccine
They do not come here to offer money
Yeah that wasn't hard to give me money and then get anything you want
You don't put quarters in in Alex Jones and then
You know get back out of it
What you put in
Smash got to him doing a my pillow ad
Last time I got offered a bunch of money
3 years ago reset Wars what
That wasn't about
It offered money by government
Bi-Lo
That's how the real world Works folks
And you're looking
At the guy
I'm not bragging
I'm just telling you you're looking at the guy that can't be bought right here
Looking for
This is the real thing
This is a real McCoy warts and all
You got it right
And I know you're just like me
Okay
3 years ago Alex was had a governments try and give him a bunch of money anywhere to the FBI about
What was that Alex
Oh boy
You know there's one government I know specifically who's really into that guy
Trying to pretend it was
Trying to pretend that Russia
Tried to give him a bunch of money
I think that's
Probably the application
If this is true
That he went to the FBI
That's the part that I would like
U.s. government cuz he went to the FBI know I would imagine that what really happened is somebody
Faked being from a Russian troll
Play sounded like I hate will give you 10 trillion dollars if you say bubba bubba and he was like
I also don't believe you went to the FBI's at Dr 11999 4678
I mean like
I don't know I don't know how much I believe
I kind of think there's a possibility that there might have been
Some like
Like with the DHHS.
Maybe there was a
Buying
High-interest like Artie or the one of these thing to buy advertising on little Wars totally I could see that be
McKay's all of that describe it like that
I don't know anyway I just think that when you say something like this
I think you're required to follow up with the
Details
Because otherwise do not do that leads me to believe first of all you're lying
If you're not lying
You're covering up what government it is
Because you know that it'll make your coverage look bad
It's all a bunch of money surprise
Weird weird
To save his money I think
I think that it raises more suspicions
To say nothing
Explain what you're talkin about to be like Luxembourg offered him ten
No
Alex gets back to his wacky religious stuff
Your
And I will tell you that this
Start
One of the best Alex Jones
Starting
He wants to explain what the theologians are wrong about
Okay wow which one
All all of them
Anyting
Has been gotten Wrong by the theologians of the
The culture the rest of it
Is that the
Which level you just
Everything so
Happy and total perfect
If you choose to be in that presents
And be complete
You can choose to stay there and be complete in God's presence
You can choose to stay at that level
Absolute connection doing Saturday
Add
Attainment
You can
Go to
Places
What
What places
Side of the concert
God
That doesn't make any
Satan's attempt
At this level
What's places
Those places
Okay
Tell you my friends I've been beyond
No career if you absolutely f******
Nuts thrown to the f****** trash bin if he was talking like that
Get him to stop stop doing this cuz it the Saturday show you work for this man as he says
Don't worry Satan tried to make his own evil Universe outside of God
Subconscious and I've been there my love
I'm not sure what the Illusions Alex is referring to but I suspect
It's just the Illustrated children's Bible he reads out of with pictures of people playing harp
Yeah that would be what's going on
Stupid there are two possibilities here and I think they're both trash
The first is that Alex actually means the things he saying and clips like that and in that case you should be hospitalized immediately
He's completely insane and detached from reality rambling Beyond gods
Consciousness
The other possibility is that he doesn't mean any of this and he's just a dorky f******
Can child drink these meaningless esoteric ramblings
But how holy he isn't it that case I think he probably should be hospitalized too because it's
Speaks to level of narcissism that is
Dangerous
I know I've been banging this drum quite a bit but
Just try and imagine
Him
I think he could be taken seriously like 2003 talking like this
His career would have
Vetoed amazing
It's it's
Embarrassing
You listen
Sometimes
You don't necessarily need a boss
But you need somebody
Need to check on I like what I was saying about how unbearable this show is commercial breaks
You need
Something
You need something to check your b******* yeah you can't you can't live in a situation where your narcissism
Can't be
Let run wild
Does inevitably I think you
Do you have the Tendencies of someone like Alex you just going to end up
Turning yourself into like
Transdimensional
The pseudogod
It is fun
But you shouldn't do it on the radio
No it specially when you're whole
Stick is that like
You've proven everything you say and I'm right about everything
Everything we say is documented tomorrow's news today
Absolutely
Frames a meme on his wall buddy where do you think you bring that back from a universe outside of Gotham
How much does a passport cost
F****** idiot man
Anyway back to news
Stories against seraphim at the f******
Gates just alright you bringing anything in from outside of God's consciousness
Like a
Yummy fruits
Vegetable are they
Is it just cuz we're in multiple Dimensions doesn't mean we don't have rules
Backup back to news news
Another video on a plane a moment
Are executive brags mRNA shots
Are gene therapy
Marketas vaccines I'm going to hit
This news the wrestler
Story
Here's the clip
World
Health Summit
And the UN here it is
Ultimately
Are an example for that salad gene therapy always like to say
We have surveyed
2 years ago
And the public would you be willing to take
Jeans
Dino cell therapy and injected into your body
We would have probably had a 95% refusal rate I think this
Pandemic has also opened
20 people's eyes 2
To Innovation the way
That was maybe not
Possible before
This was a guy named Stefano Ricci
Giving a speech at the 2021 World Health Summit
The clip really illustrates Alex's failure in terms of reading and listening
Incomprehension
The clipboard Alex plays doesn't include all Rick sang with covid-19
Sian is a gene therapy
He's saying that the success of this mRNA vaccine should give people hope about the possibility for future Gene
Or cell therapy
I was just lying about this guy's paying B
Because what he saying seems close enough for Alex add false context to his comment
Puerto Rican Solitude is audio
Even though it's a lot
It's brazen
Like if you go to the Infowars article about this
It includes this quote which is
Is one of the things that Albrecht said there
Ultimately the MRNA vaccines are an example for that cell and gene therapy
Which is meant to give me in person that already saying that the covid vaccines are example
Settling gene therapy
But he's not
If you watch the full speech you saying that the
Leap Forward embodied by the MRNA vaccines are an example of how he hopes progress could be made on selling Jean-Pierre
Are bees the bear is working on
I see no way
Describe this other than
A complete intentional li-ion Allison Park
It's disgust
Yep
Such a shortcut take
Can prick
Call me baby
It's a very good point
It's it's hard hard to argue with the point that he's making which is like
Tons of people
Would have been like
He's old and he's also not
Citing any kind of information that people are actually more willing
To take salary
No so like
That is only a thought
T.i.
End
Maybe there's green stuff thought maybe there's not but whatever the case Alex is taking this and
I'm just
Bucket line
This makes go back to the kind of made me chuckle
The documents
It's out of a Statin
Statistical site
Stat news
Ms articles out
A long time ago but it's been Republic
And it goes into hell
Lavishly funded moderna by Bill Gates in the defense department
Hits safety problems in
Bold bid
To revolutionize medicine
That news is not a site about statistic
Hate to say that focuses on healthcare related stories and the name is a reference to a doctor say they need something stat
Kirara tolerable to not be able to take every opportunity to present himself as the guy
Who knows everything
We can't really resisted making stuff up to make himself seem smarter even though if you know anything about what he's talking about it just makes
Look like more of a desperate idiot
This article that Alex's reference
Dancing is from January 2017
Illustrate that mRNA vaccines were never able to get approved because they killed everyone in the trials
Here's a little clip of him talking about that article
And it goes into
How they set all this up
And how they develop these systems
But how they had so many problems and trials
With them having bad results for killing people
That Madonna was in trouble
You got to go read this whole article
Lavishly funded moderna
Hits safety
Problems
In bold bid
Revolutionize medicine
Add from Yahoo news
And it goes on to say
MRNA is a tricky technology
Several major pharmaceutical companies
Idea
MRNA into cells without triggering
Nasty
Side effects
The essential problem here is that Alex has once again
Making things
This is about how an mRNA product was working on
Jennifer kriegler Najjar syndrome
Direct edition if I can deliver it wasn't working
I did run into troubles in animal testing
Alex has had multiple times on this episode that it made people's livers liquify but this article is really specific that the drug
Never made it to human trial
I think he's just making that part up about because he saw the word liver and the description of crigler-najjar and even wrote his own
Story about it
Yeah it's going to look water water livers
Because of the difficulty with this particular treatment this article explains that moderna was shifting its focus
Vaccines for quote
To Target strains of influenza
A service for zika virus and
The fourth remains a secret
There may have been some trials for perspective medications that used Mirna technology that resulted in some
Side effect you might say our nasty
But the same is true of many different medication types
Veteran trials
That's why they do trial
Exactly
You can find plenty of examples of free covid mRNA studies that don't show horrific side effects
Reply was always the case right it's just his argument s***
It is very interesting but it's
Not really about
The negative side effects of being a problem woman and more of it
Just being like
Their countries are there that company seems like an a*******
Thrust of this article is
That's probably true
Perform Alex does get back to talking about liquid livers
Help
Maybe I just read the prologue
Do it
I dare you
Incredible
Stat news
The whistleblowers
Other times that whistleblowers come out of these companies
Stop it
And the biggest thing it does and you read the articles that are linked
From that's what I did
Is it
Eats deliver
The biggest problems they try to cure cancer and stuff
Eating live in mRNA technology that like
Literally
Killcams
Open 6 months later your liver
Jerk
Yeah bring it up the liquid livers
There are five articles that are linked
Any sad news article
One is about the other zika vaccine candidates
Better come and get the trials that are in competition with moderna
Right one of them seems like a dick and he's lost some top talent because he's a dick
Another is an interview with that Co in Forbes
The 4th is a CB insights article about modernist valuation
And the last one is the closest without stalking
About which is an editorial in nature that
Pretty negative about moderna
As business plan
From liquid livers.com
If not
The problem is that article is about how moderna wasn't publishing information about their research so not really could evaluate what they were doing
Couldn't tell if they were just another theranos
Right right right. The publishing schedule
So here's what the article says in relation
Delivers
Quote patience with crigler-najjar are missing a key liver enzyme
Needed to break down bilirubin a yellowish Subs
Since that crops up in the body
Has old red blood cells break down
Without that enzyme bilirubin proliferates in the blood leading
Jaundice muscle degeneration and even brain damage
Yet but I could not make it therapy work
Former employees in collaborators say
The safe
This was too weak and repeat injection
David O strong enough to be effective effects on the liver in animal studies
The rest of Alex's entire presentation is just completely made up which is why he's never going to read the entire article when he says he should
Cuz he knows he's a liar and the information that he'd end up reading
Wouldn't satisfy
And why do that
If you read the article he would just have to editorialize and
Say about the ship pretending it's in the article why not
Skip that step it up anyway seen him read things they actively counter what it is he was
Just saying
Say something that disagrees with his like
And that's why they're that's how they you know they're lying
F****** piece of s***
Total
Total piece of s***
My father
Do I love a lot
Almost died
From Delta
My mother was the second she's ever been
Robbed
Almost died
Still seriously sick
I have other family that
Died
I felt like I had 1000 lb gorilla
Sitting on my chest
For two weeks
Did make a big issue out of the time I was on there with it
You came on are you came to Studio
For two weeks without
A mask everybody around you you're saying got really sick and still dealing with the side effect
You are I would say a central
Hub in the middle of all of these other data points
I too if I were Alex will probably invest a lot of emotional attention
And you trying to talk about how this is a
Bio weapon plan
Voice did Upon Us by the globalist
Because the alternative is recognizing
That he's
Stubbornness
Inability to be
Be careful
And take things seriously could
Have it affect gotten everyone around him sick
And everybody that he cares about
Almost dying
Probably pretty difficult emotionally handle
Probably Retreat into bulshit
Conspiracies too if I heard that
And I work today
Infowars.com
I would be like oh goodbye I have a massive lawsuit guess what I'm another person who's going to the globalist
Message which is you piece of s*** cuz this is Alex saying that he
Knowingly
Yes that is that is
The very least they literally I can't give you a disease
Unsafe working environment but I am fairly certain
You could at least
I mean did you do did he travel
He walked in the office without his f******
Mascon I don't think so because I would
Assume that at least some of them would f****** leave
I know that at least some of the people who work it in fours or probably
They're on board with everything and
Zealots like him
I don't think everybody is just have to be like this
It's a game
I don't know
I think crazy
I would encourage anybody who works at enforce or work out of him
Abuse lawsuit that you almost killed me you dick
But he loves them a lot well I wonder how much
Alex
He also now loves Glenn Beck
Why not
This is sad
One back is the biggest show we've got
It's getting deep cleaning right
Rogan's
Bigger but he's only getting into
Some of some of these starting to really
Michelle wants to know some
Carlson's Heating
Song that's good
Patty processing on Glenn Beck
Because
Cuz
It's really good and fully awake
I'm going to Amazon.
Not even that
It's not even that I don't want to be here anymore
Wichita
I just feel like it
It's time for other
Just stand up
Ficus
Yeah please
Please
Let let let Glenn Beck be your spiritual successor you dumb prick go for it oh my God
Wait wait for him to take over the mantle for Alex and then like within a year apologize for
For everything and then leave
Try to get on Trevor Noah's show on some apologizing
Mark Levin pulls out all the funding goes away for
Blazing
Oh I don't know he has to fire Dave Rubin and Steven Crowder and then write the fun
1 right turns against timid
Oh no he's crying
I just pulled out of chalkboard cuz it's his only friend that's life
Also let's imagine how f****** quickly this whole thing falls apart if he
Baton to Owen
Doesn't answer your question that we've had for a long time and that is food is he
You feel is his Heir Apparent
And obviously now we know that it's
Glenn Beck
He's got divorced goes out of business
6 weeks
That was just a six-month busy very generous if the reserves
Rrd
Oh yeah I mean just imagine the day one or no the week one Revenue drop
Would be
Staggering
Week 2 cuz I think there would be like some
Shiny new car kinda feel like first week
Odo
Well we already know Zike
Whenever it's not Alex
And it doesn't we don't need any special information for this
What is not Alex
They're not telling s***
No and the numbers you can even see unlike banned. Video Drop
Dramatically from Alex's shows
To the other shows
And there are no real if there's no interest
I'm on radio stations to send to Kate
Norwinds
War room nor is there any interest in the American Journal
Yep the Dorito
Drops
So f****** hard
Owen doesn't have any real handle on
Some of the stuff that gives Alex plausible deniability which is
The historical tradition of anti-communism
I am
Ibiza far-right
People write baked in that world
He came out of that from the John Birch
Society
And because of that you can rattle off all kinds of nonsense about Cecil Rhodes and what have you that make you think
But he knows this s*** backwards and forwards doesn't he can yell at people he thinks are cut
That's what I can do if it's so weird
To say this
But Owen
Is just too shallow
Exactly
There's a presentation of of something
Can you
F****** imagine Owen
To get on the show at doing that I've been beyond God's Consciousness nonsense
The f*** out of here
Wouldn't be able to Intrigue the audience at all in the
Dumb s*** that Alex does
It's a recipe for disaster but I think it's
F****** hilarious
Is that the thing
It'll be like okay now I can retire is
If Glenn Beck is doing a good enough job
Tell that to yourself a 2009 you dumbass hole tell that to yourself honestly
Now in the mirror
And say it's like I just want Alex to really look in the mirror one time and just be like
Glenn Beck is who I want to be
Glenn Beck will climb back will finish my work. My standard
To the Future
Crying Glenn Beck live
Dumb chalkboard one guy who's a steady hand
No the only way they work is like completely
Like what if Alex leaves
Infowars has to be like okay
We have to distance ourselves or Alex
They are probably the only way
But I don't think there's any real space in the market
It for that note I think our funding goes away and so the one thing that makes them special also goes away which is the
High production value
And the appearance that similar enough to an actual news station
I don't think anyone cares about a web show that Harrison Smith does
Or Owen
Do you like Harrison Smith alone in his room with a painting that isn't hung up
What kind of audience
Decrease the David Knight
Experience when he left and started doing his own videos on Tik-Tok over the f****** light on
Adorable
It's that that will be sir it will be all of their futures
Linda Glenn Beck
Is
I mean
He's just a dick who goes wherever the money is
And the money is in this
Extremist
It's similar to Alex right now
On the exact same page and like all Alex you woke me up or whatever the f*** play a different area 5 years
I tried to go there as soon as this this
Tide changes if it changes will be back Tuesday and like you know who's great
Yep Mitt Romney you got it I was never on board with all those extreme actually I was and I'd like to apologize
I'm so sorry you don't press campaign apologize.
You will never admit they're wrong I'll admit I'm wrong twice
And then I'll do it again baby Alex's real actual desperation to not do
Do this anymore
I can't believe so many people still work
What are the ratings on the
Man trying to kill all of you by giving you covid and I want to leave
I want to quit
I hate
Wow
So over the weekend there was a interview at the end of last week
Interview that Melinda Gates
Stead
What show was on but you talked about how evil Epstein
Sure isn't Alex is really excited about the
My ex-husband's buddy real piece of s***
Really excited right on time lady
You know you got to give her the benefit of the doubt and I like
And I said she's distancing herself
And they are
Splitting off the foundation
And they're putting
McCullough said that
Mercola. McCullough
His Halo bendy Angel and buying off the
Comedian spend billions a year to control the Press
Medical news in underwriting
Nbcnews
CNN MSNBC
You name it
But they're moving the hell out of her
But I said if she comes out and actually
Ataxia
It says Jeffrey Epstein is evil
When says Jeffrey Epstein was a mollusk
And says this is part of a satanic system
Then she's not part of it
And we should
Say she's evil
If she comes out
Pulling in attack
Text Gage
For being part of Epstein admit stats
Are the reason
She did it last week on
CBS News
Show people need to give her the benefit of the doubt
We've never gotten information if she's even Genesis
We've never gotten information
Child molester
What
I think it's really nice that Alex has given Melinda Gates benefit of the doubt like
I have this vague memory of something that Alex had in the past
I have been
His wife knew years ago in Germany
Shadows of you
We're running a worldwide
We're stopping her from saving people know it was a public
Alright
So we have no evidence of public death threat really
Hold on another memory
People
What you just think like we don't know how dangerous it is to go up against ya'll home I got you threatened does oh my God
Scared now
I think we're stupid they keep going
I should back off
Shell out
Killing everybody
Show up
With a bunch of demons
Hell no
Are you pretending happened pretty seriously but this is also a little unnerving
Melinda Gates is a demon
According to Alex in the past
That's still kind of vague you know he's really talk about a group of
Sweet baby meant that she was like a really cool person who's making death threats on behalf of a group of demon
Another memory
Something very interesting happened crystallized
Melinda Gates
Went on today
Good morning shows
Wearing
Upside-down cross
Oh
Give her the benefit of the doubt
That doesn't mean affiliation with the Church of Satan
Because they supposedly the authorities
With them
And they said is she a Satanist
I'm not kidding
Oh well
Upside-down cross
Isn't necessarily affiliated with
And
We blown it up
When I say some shots of that
Coming up
In the
Last segment of the shower and it is an upside-down cross
Sure there is.
With a
Ring of rubies around it
I went and did some research and I sent it over to the producer this morning
Today
I didn't get my full stack them to resend it to the new producer
Do you actually wear that someone comes from I said where am I seeing
Upside-down cross with a
Red
Coronavirus
And that where I thought I'd seen
Very
Horrible sign
Symbolizes the death of the son
As you can get
How to such a fuking idiot nothing means anything on this show because you just making things up to suit whatever is convenient
Troyman the moment
Melinda Gates is presumably happy to Bill I'm a happily married to bill then she's a part of the Demonic cabal and it may be the worst of them all
Jewelry
Great fun game that only gets disrupted when she's getting divorced
From Bell and his critical of his association with Epstein
And that two of your narratives are running into each other in a way that shouldn't be happening
If you're well do mean anything
What do you do then
That's simple
He is pretending you never said all the stuff you said in the past
No evidence that she's all evil and what-have-you in May 2020
Necklace is a deep satanic messages was putting out on The Today Show
And ensure she was married to bill for a long time
I'm sure she's been heavily involved in the Gates Foundation for a long time
I'm sure those things are
Fundamentally work
Looking for the devil
Right
We don't know that you
Wanted to work for the devil
Maybe she was being held captive
Divide the billions of dollars that she had you know maybe someone forced her to wear that on upside-down cross
Tower of gold
All right I just thought there was stupid
He's trying to rehab Her Image because the narrative now is
Like hey if people are trying to defect over to the Patriot side let's give him a chance
Mine is going to be the cheese
Trying to become
My Galaxy
Never seen anything so dumb
So Alex does a does
I will say surprisingly few ads
On this side episode but he has one
And this is this is 2 minutes long
This is a sales pitch
Where he is legitimately just describing a bad business model
I'm in a catch-22 and I'll try this
We can sell
Enough wintersun
Enough
Rainforest Ultra
Enough X2 + x 3
Defender operation and stay the same size
And fight off a Democrat lawsuits by Rasmussen
If we could get the
These products
In stock
But they're routinely sold out
On average more than six months
And here's the Catch 22
You want to sell them at full price
Weed on the map
25% off
People are habituated where I always sell stuff
The 30-40
40% off
Some people wait
Until that happens
Then I so out of it
Quicker but don't make enough money back
Vallarta Market
Should you be explaining this to me such high-quality stop at Cinema won't adulterate I won't cut the quality
It's a lot of our best friends are now
Not available anymore we have to discontinue
Cuz you just can't get the product
The price is going up
Supply chains broken down
I don't want to go up in price
Anna buy discounted
People buy it if I don't
People don't buy it
Like 2 weeks ago I go well
I'm going to stop offering Tabitha
50% off
But then I talked to the account when they go will he really need to move all this
Percent off
Just don't forget money into be able to buy more that's coming in in 15 20 weeks
And so we're doing this math
Stop trying to figure out
What we do
Decision right now
We're going to sell
Down to just a few thousand bottles of each
A few hundred bottles of
Of all these products
Watch and then hits
Force
The biggest sale we're going to do on these 25
Because again Supply Chain break down all of it
Cost of goods going up we we cannot discount
At 40 or 50
Percent off anymore
He said that like over and over again I can't
I hear this stuff I'm sick I'm going to look for my stuff elsewhere
This is not this is this doesn't Inspire confidence
It's not a catch-22 your options are both failing
That's that
Catch 22 that's just you you're going to fail
Right if you do this you fail and if you do that you fail
If this description of what's going on with his businesses in any way accurate
It's like they're going out of business
It's just an avitable eventually
Start long enough time frame
You're going to bleed yourself dry
And if I were an investor listening to that I would be like
This is a failure
I would not want to get involved with this
Owen
Do you want to take over a failing business
Just so you know and I want to say this to any future investors or anybody wants to buy a product
All right we we we are going out of business what we shot ourselves in the foot because we do these ridiculous sales
In order to have a
Money bhavesh well affresh
Of money coming in
I think people recognize that our products are fine but they're certainly not worth paying more than
40% off for and so they eventually I'll give in and
And do those sales and so we can't make enough money to do it
We're doing good
Listen I just want to tell you that this business
Operating the red
And it will never know
So if you want to visit
That you continually have to put money into that you will never get back it could operate out of the rug out of business
Operate out of the red if Alex could sell these things for 10% off but the audience won't buy them for that
See that's not a catch-22 that they failure
I don't know if it's necessarily a function of the audience getting used to him having these sales
As much as it is
10% off prices for it's not that doesn't
They can get it cheaper elsewhere
Elachi maybe they'll pay a little bit more right by from Infowars
But not a lot more nope
Yeah you're f***** your f*****
Good actor
So Alex starts.
More about the Russia Ukraine
Great situation
Things are always smarter so good
Back in the Trap days
People would talk about Alex being a Russian agent question
And so on
Decided back then
He was going to go to Russia
The troll
And Alex is something that's a little bit of a revelation
In terms of the
I was going to go to Russia
4 years ago
Do interviews and live feeds and get mass of yours
Start
When I put out my passport on Twitter they said look he's a Russian agent
Democrats up on the hill say
We should investigate Alex Jones he's got a Russian visa
Real quick
That was a fake Visa
Passport
That's it it wasn't
Anybody
Could get if you're in the media want to go over there
They called Tucker Carlson a Russian agent
For wanting an interview with Vladimir Putin
But everybody else
Interview Vladimir Putin from The New York Times
We're seeing in but he can't
Fox News
It's how they
Handicap everybody
Were you can't
Even
By the way I had them to the Russian media
Duarte we sent an email saying
Yes
If you want to fly to the
These mountains may be on this date
You'll have a press
Junket and you might
Get one question and while he's hunting
We were going to go interview
I'm going to go do that
Estimating it one question in a potent
I'm sure be sure
Cool
Mountain in the urals Wiley
Hunting god-knows-what but no I did
Go to that
But I don't want to
Go to Russia to be a Russian agent I wanted to go to Russia cuz I want to go to Egypt I want to go to Israel
I want to go to Easter Island
I want to go to Alaska
Supporting Putin the way he is he might be able to visit Alaska and Russia at the same time
Yeah I also stay the f*** out of Easter Island you a******
Play you can't run dance holy Island
No
That the thing Motu is that I think Alex might be making
Too little of this
Notion of being offered
To ask
The question itself
Mountain Resort's yeah that's kind of
If true
Real kind of Overture that's being made by
The Russian media
If true I really do feel like Alex would have
Yeah yeah
Yeah
I mean he wants to
You would at least get to stand
Eli cologne
Yeah or associate yourself in some way to have a clip of him asking Putin a
A direct question and Putin responders about the globalist Alex you're a good boy
We needed to hear.
Russian TV show you started crying
When they talked about how he was a great example of American man
I have a good boy thank you I almost killed my dad last
Cheer
Because I don't know
I'm conflicted about what to believe about this
Maybe
Fell through or something this is Alex's way of saying like I didn't want to go at all
Making it up entirely in this is how we make the
Believable also possible
Not sure it is weird though I mean if you put
Contacts
With other stories he's told about like
Weird background stuff with Artie
Possibly a government offering him a bunch of money through years ago
That's there's such there's so many details
Something sketchy here absolutely sketchy is going on
Either Alex is making up a whole lot of stuff
There's there's some other details he needs to provide
And the fact that they continue to
Drop-in like
Weird ways
Unrelated to nest
The Sara Lee what it is he's trying to say as almost like a little Bragg outside
We're like
That's you only do that whenever you
Our kind of proud of something
Something's going
I don't know what to make of it but it's weird
Alex doesn't like
What's going on in Ukraine
Murder
But
Right now there's nobody
Add
What I see out of Ukraine
Now that Russia has invaded
He's not good
Ukraine has lied about
Nuclear reactor
There was no leak no extra radiation
The Snake Island Massacre didn't happen
It was all made up
And almost everything coming out of zalenski's mouth
Is a lie
Spell I don't say that because I'm Pro poop
I say that because I'm
Protrude
Okay
And I Pro puto caveman
I would say that this
It's not being weighed with
Eli's that Putin is telling from what I'm seeing out of Ukraine it's bad
I'm the reason it's bad is because zielinski did not
Tell the truth
About how a nuclear reactor
Did not melt down
It was just
Hit by large-scale
Yeah
I'm going to tell you
That makes me think it's okay for Putin to go in there and murder millions of people I think that's total of
Obviously this is the way that this is
This is being used
But I think it's
Just an absolute coward
Move to
Say that
Zelensky and Ukraine
Just total Liars
And then
Do not discuss what lies are coming out of
Like if you're going to pretend that you just care about the truth
Then you need to give equal measure to
Do both
Sides of this supposed allies that are coming out of it and if you were
To do that this
Would be a four-hour Special Report
Putin flies
This lies in fact and the interest is in just branding the other side as Liars which is in service
Service of supporting Putin without having
To stand up
And actually make that your position
Because Alex is a
F****** Tower it would be so terrible if you stood up and said I see
Support Putin
War of aggression against
Ansa Sovereign Nation
Because I am thoroughly ProPay
Putin and I think
He's going to murder my political and
But I will say that Alex does kind of have
A little bit of a
The criticism
Call
I said this week ago I said looks like poop
Putting in his
Junior varsity
Is conscript
They have a draft over there
Using a human
Pull out
The identities
Replacements for Special Forces
Of where the
Ukrainian troops are so they can kill him
And indeed that's what happened
That's a nasty tax
Sending in his
Greenish cribs
But it's and it's a desperate
Alex didn't say that a week ago.
Paid off the Ukrainian government was going to get zero resistance trying to take the country
He also said that the Lansky was a double agent secretly working for Putin
Is complete horseshit an example of his past position
Make himself sound like he knows what he's talking about
In hindsight
Also if that's what I was really think spoons doing I think it deserves
A little bit more of a rebuking what I'm hearing from Alex
Softball treat all right okay I think it's bad that Putin is sending complete children
To die in order for him to kill more people
Seems like a kid gloves
IPad 2
It's not I don't have any problem with a mask
Again this is all in function of
Supporting food in Whitehaven
Cowardly
Over yourself of pretending that that's not what you're doing it's just crazy to me that cowardly Shield
Even still come off like a psychopath
You know what would I think that if you're not engaging with it out with Alex is saying critically it doesn't come off like a psychopath
Has the appearance
And the delivery of someone who wants
Be
Passive listener and somebody's not engaging all that much
I think he's looking all the angles
He gets away with that with his audience
But if you take the time to actually
Listen to what you saying
And ask yourself like why is he
Is he saying this
What is the point of this
You get such a clear picture of like this is
All just prudence
Here's a great example.
Like why would he throw this narrative in
Did conversation about the situation
Of Putin invading Ukraine
And so I do want to be like the corporate media that's
Says somebody said something and then not show it
What's playing new clip that I had
Seen until now
I'd rather
Is foundation
Saying it
And Fiona Hill
Never shooting sad
Where he brags and calls
Eastern Europe in the caucuses
And OMG Slavic Nations
The border Russia
Former Nazi
Happy happy Hunting Ground
Literally
He calls it
Thesaurus Empire
Here it is
When the Soviet Union
The Soviet Empire
Collapse
Empire
I've moved in
And
Picked up the pieces
Ask question hungry
And 1984
And then pull into foot in the 87
China Mac
Just having this route
So this is how
What's up with the tsarist empire
Replacing the Soviet
How do you think you're doing in your Imperial ambitions
There you go ladies and gentlemen
Let's let's play that clip 1
More
Time
Just everybody gets it
Very clear and has no record so you can
Puritas
Play twice and it's not the laughter so it doesn't sound like he's very obviously making a joke
Yeah it's so clear soda
I mean that could not be more obviously a joke
Well I guess he thinks he's the arch
Sudoku
Vampire
I mean come on
Ask yourself though Jordan what is the point
Of playing that clip in the middle of a conversation about Putin invading
Ukraine
The only possible point you could be making
Is the Putin is Justified and correct
There's no other interpretation you can find
In the context of Infowars I mean he's not trying to overthrow Ukraine he's trying to overthrow the wrong
Empire
Jose Rosas meddling
These bio-weapon Labs at the United States
2023 you're whatever I mean the funniest part about this
This is right now he's so cowardly and trying to couch
This differently
I think he's going to wind up talking himself into being like I think
I think once he has cover to do it yeah I would not be surprised
Opus weirdo they clipped at the end
So you can tell by where was cut off social media
It's a 42-second clip that's going around being posted by weird Twitter account
Mississippi making the argument
The Putin
Isn't wrong
Invaded Ukraine
Soros
This is from a 2015 Cherokee gave at the Asia Society
The full videos up on their website and if you want to you can go watch it it's clear if you do the Taurus is talk about finding organized
Stations that work
To promote democracy informally undemocratic
Countries that's the whole point
The chat
The clip out of context if you didn't just get this little snippet Twitter
I'm sorry to report on it like he knows what he's talking about
And again
There's no reason to introduce out of context
Clip into the conversation unless
You're trying to score
100 no other funk
No. Whatsoever no
Sounds good
Soros it becomes like a really long
Soros
Complaint session
Sounds about right
Unfortunately because of that
I actually realized I don't agree with Alex
About something that I thought we were in agreement about there were very few things that I thought we had like common cause
Civil asset forfeiture b b in play
Drugs
And he has a list of things transgenderism
Fluoride the water
Weaponized marijuana all the screen
Drug legalization
People
Cuz I don't think we should decriminalize drugs
We should not legalize
What
Don't put people in prison for me on heroin or cocaine
Then but Don't Legalize It
Why do we get a dick
You just
Penalize
The big the dealers
You don't
Pennywise
The users
Aeropostale legalized
You're so blown and blasted out of your brain
You know who you are so
Wasn't incoherent position and I would say that it's really counter to his
Fake libertarian ideology that he likes to pretend he has legalized drugs
Analyze
Well I mean yeah it's it's it's like Don't Legalize It decriminalize it except if you have enough that
The government can make an argument that you're dealing it and that it's still criminal yeah I just think it's by degrees
Still
The same thing exactly
This is a meaningless difference
Fats are you suggesting
I think it's dumb
Play my heartbreak
But like
It does bum me out
When there are things are like well at least he's on the right side of this
At least he's we can find some agreement
Criminalization illegalization
Of drugs
The drug war itself
Is
A stupid waste of resources that has been used to
Destroy communities
That's that's not his his position
And that sucks
To criminalize
Black people
Being sick about what intent to distribute laws have been traditionally only
For good what's the line between personal use and intent to distribute
10 grand
MoneyGram friend of mine friend of mine back
And we were like
Now 18 19 or something he bought a trash bag full of weed
One time
And he did not intend to distribute 0.04 personally good weekend
I think that
It's so
Transparent to anybody
Experience with
Drugs for anybody who thought about the
Is for a while
That the position that Alex is advocating for
Lip service towards caring about
Drug use
Insulting that problem
In reality it doesn't
A table
No one even reduce things it just be used if
Shore points
Also
Transphobia that was inherited by Clippers well
Like that noise
He's got all these things he's trying to destroy the world with
30 ft
Thousands of DEA
More than 20
Attorney General
Empower
And if you're a conservative
Anu
You had two beers you're getting
The book thrown at you
For DWI
I thought you are black lives matter person that shoots 5 people and kills them
You're out the week
Galaxy come up with any black lives matter person who got away with murder because of a saurus district attorney
On the flip side Alex is actually an interesting Counterpoint to his own argument
Seeing as though he got a DUI last year and he didn't go to jail
Anything digging into Soros when he was setting out to have a conversation about Ukraine and Russia is super telling
Who's the most cowardly weaselly way for him to support food without having
By pretending talking about Soros his longtime anime
Artery weeks from this a******
I forever I told you maybe was before we started recording or maybe it was at the beginning of the episode of can't remember but I lost
What's with this
This episode end
Don't worry we're coming to the point where I
I ate just lost all
Interesting that
But you eat it's such a
Trashout needs commercial breaks
There's just not a Centrist position
Award
If you are pulling this
Bulshit
About
They're being like I both sides argument for Putin invading Ukraine
Then your f****** dumb
You're just running interference
I saw your profile
I think this
I think that you can have
Critiques
And concerns
About ways that Ukraine may be carrying out the defense of their own country
I think there's room for that conversation
Alex were having that
I think that there would be a lot more
Credence
The things he's saying
But he doesn't want to have that conversation cuz that doesn't justify The Invasion
He's doing these things he's using be specific talk
Pinpoints because
There are ways that he can support Putin and Putin Zacks
Without having the stink on him above
Being the guy who's like hey you know what I love Putin
Do you know who does do that though
Nick Fuentes
There you go who's on Alex's Network
The channel on video straight up
And at his
Speech
Straight up was like
Getting poop
Dance going
So that he's not willing to be out in public
Even though his business is failing
He still has something to maintain and protect
Headlined by Putin
And you'll notice he has to editorialize a little bit here
Houghton sanctions are declaration of war
No-fly zone warning Waze
Cyber attacks
Azelastine
Engages in cyber-attacks again
Russia
The war Russia launches any cyber
Very very dangerous
Situation
What else did is so true
Transparent
You read a headline that said the Putin's weighing a cyberattack and instinctively almost at second nature
He pretended
Extend a headline to say that Putin is being attacked
Preparing a cyber-attack obviously the only reason he would do that is cuz he's under attack
Supports Putin
Clear but the other part is the poon's almost painfully intertwined with Alex's narratives at this point
Really do much negative stuff about Putin Without Really tanking some of the plates
He's trying to spend
He's got this whole thing going about how class Rob is going to do a false flag cyber-attack so
Alex accidentally read the headline about Boudicca
Considering
He's going to have to immediately invalidated or run the risk of weakening his Schwab narrative
In order to keep his own bulshit afloat Alex's essentially required to give Putin
Compassus
A whole lot of stuff
He has to pretend to not know a lot of stuff
That's a lie about time to stuff
Kind of
Where is constrained by his own
Machinations
Teen holds him
It constrains him to not being able to talk about certain things
I mean you've set this guy up
Who is very obviously evil to be the leader in the fight against the globalist right next to
Trump so you have to say that committing war crimes in murdering people is fine
Killing killing civilians
And shelling
Humanitarian corridors
If you have to deny it by saying well what about the ghost of Ciara Ukraine is just liars absolutely
Food weighing cyber-attack you like no no no no
It's annoying
It's
OneNote
It's very see-through
And this is exactly where I decided
Say how about you go fuc yourself
It's not because of any negative contact it's just because
Show is
Trivial
To a level that is
Disrespectful
To the issues that he's pretending a cover
We are disputing
More than four years ago
Back on Trump
1st and office they were calling us all Russian agents
There's a restaurant
Downtown office
Why should I
European Flair
What's the name of that restaurant
Russia House
A cloakroom with
Russian outfits and things
Is a joke
Theme party
Pretty good food
Adventure near
Fine
So we had a
What was party there
Are you can see some of the ladies
Work here
And smelly
My camera on the table
IPhone
It was pretty
Pretty funny there
The media pick this up and said look he's a Russian
Picking their viewers are so dumb
And the Russians were insulted B and look at Jones
Making fun of us to Saratoga National
Russian TV but I think the rush
Russian Sable
Sense of humor so
Corefirst kanarra really funny clip of Russian
Russians trained with a bear
And it's really funny the Bears like shaking the tree or the guy bounces up and down on it
The Russians are known for taking
Both are grizzly bears and other Bears couple species is a grizzly bear
At pets
And then so they've got one as a pet
The playing with the soldiers
And folks were joking that the other sister
The Alex Jones in Rocky
Before that was
Between sad
So here is the Russia
I'm praying for the bear behind him
Comic relief
Animal play the next clip Alex Jones
So first things first no one of the media covered Alex's dumped rolling video of him at that Russian restaurant talked about that
Seriously I strongly doubt that anyone in Russia took offense to it either absolutely
Is anyone in Russia ever saw that under closer surveillance than I would have thought
Real awesome use of time on this emergency broadcast though like I can't believe you spent a half an hour talk about a stupid meme with the beginning
Troll videos from like 4 years ago
A f****** a******
Video going around on like Tik-Tok and Twitter's and guys training with a bear
Because Alex it's just another medium that he thinks is worth covering not a super important new show
She gets done with playing these videos and then he says this Miz where I turned it off
Only show you some memes that I thought was pretty informative that I saw
No
A cartoonist
Photoshop
What the f***
Doing a meme Roundup
Ideal imagine anything less
Respectable in terms of a broadcast
If this is
Pasta to our point
You set up to do two hours
Just stop
You don't need to do meme cover
Every apparel
America's racist home meme
That's that's why I mean he's doing like
Tosh 2.0 from me
Beirut
Barely
Exactly
Pun unintended celebrate
Absolutely
This sucks
This
I was
Special Report
Cuz it's trash
I mean like the information that he's covering
Thanks
These commercial breaks that's really add as somebody to listen to his shows so much
Like that's one of things I Come Away with most
Essentially it's like
It's
Awful
To watch or listen to without
It's just unsustainable
Is commentary jumps around
All over the place
It's
Meandering
Yeah but how would you know
If you hadn't listened to this way
That the devil was currently trying to create a separate pocket Universe outside of God's wearing
And there are other universes that Alex has been Chinese window bunch of them
And
Instead of
A harp and having like The Illusionist think you do
Oh well that is a choice you could probably think it's the only choice
You can go to these pocket universes I don't want to problem
I think
Look
Obviously unhinged and stupid but also so transparently
Trying to support Putin it away that he thinks is hedging
His position to make it not
Something they could be damaging to him
Should the people call him on
Yep I think that sucks I think I think it's
I think it's
I think that
You should just
That come out with it already
Nope and let the chips fall where they may
Stand up for the things that you obviously support
If you're running interference for Putin
Your pro-putin
That's how it work
Right you can't just say like I don't take sides in this war
Of
Like
Why Ukraine is right
Why is what are the things
Does that make
Ukraine correcting the situation
It is only
Zama's liars and zelensky the liar
And these is right
Yep that's the only coverage
That really is
At all put forth on this
Also applying his
Standard villains like Soros
Ways to communicate
Why Putin is right
It's not it's not that he supports Putin's invasion
However George Soros invaded already so it's like why it's not really invading he's on invading honestly
That's what it is right in the wrong I mean I don't even know why Ukraine's fighting back it's it it's not like they're that it's not
Putin trying to take over there
He's trying to give it back
To them
You know what Dan
Like America before him Putin's just deliberate
Is liberating listings
Yep covid narrative sucks sucks butts
Sad part about all of it is
Memes
No
Glenn Beck
That's pretty sad than framing a meme
Yeah they specially a meme is
Part of
I mean Trend that's making fun of people like you
That's that's pretty sad listening to this
Which I assume he is Glenn all world leaders wind-up listening to the show bedroom
I would just say that if you are sadder than a framed meme
You should really think about
Yeah
She see if you can call Samantha be another appearance
Will be back in the next episode
We have websites truitt's knowledge.com
But until then
Emilio Emilio I'm dzx Clark I'm Doctor marbles
What the sex role
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work