Knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Alex
College.com
Books that are endorsed by the author of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
I have enjoyed it quite a bit myself of that is a meme format
Alex holding up a frame me and Replacements album covers and and what have you
We were smart at all we would try to find some way to like make this
Friend or something
By the beginning of our show we would like
People do do that to create those memes and then it goes viral and then they get all the attention
It has never occurred to me that we could try to do that just did right now for that
Not what we did make me feel gross to artificially trying to do my brakes bought is ruined
Lot of fun
Bassmaster is releasing in Boston's former character the task
Kind of game show thing and what happens is they get 5 comedians or
Personalities from TV or whatever and then over the course of a few months
I may have to do these tax so
They'll have this task like
Put these three balls at the top of the hill
Bright MLS
Try and have to don't have to do it yeah you you've mentioned this
And I think I'd want to realize
Cuz whenever they
But this news out
And then we then I re-watched a little bit
I was like Dan you and I need to be
Doing the task Mass
If you and me
You're Greg Davies I'm Alex Horne
Yeah okay I don't want to ruin it
Riverside cuz you
Do all the work like Alex
And Greg Davies like me
Does f*** all but talk loudly
Correction I do apologize
Stone Cold Steve Austin was the ringmaster Kevin Sullivan's character
WITN you corrected yourself a lot of memory
This terrible formula
What
Very fun idea that something from
I guess my childhood or my youth might be able to Stone Cold stun somebody a couple times
Just like
Beat up people WrestleMania from sort of recent times
Hangout
Giving someone a Kik somebody in the gut you'd give him a stunner and then you get out of there the upgrade
In the world
You guys probably make
So anyway we'll
Enjoyed stone-cold coming back when that happened
Do the folks
We were thrilled to sit down and have a interview with Elizabeth Williams
Author of the new book Sandy Hook
An American Tragedy and has a lot of fun
Amazon
Isaiah
So first Paul Joseph Watson distressingly redlips thank you so much you are now apology
Thank you very much
Jim
It's about time you finally married my aunt love Michael not me
The difference be clear
Next celebrating 18 years of marriage with only for anniversaries it's a riddle
I'm a policy wonk if I believe so
I'm a policy wonk I do recollect so far
My nickname and University was the number 23 thank you so much and I apologize
I'm a policy wonk
Very much
Answer thank you to look for taking some time out to book
Available
In-store STI
On the page where we released
Please enjoy this interview
Hello welcome joining us today very this is very exciting a rare guest
Indeed adding to the pantheon of
A couple of gas
Most shows after 670r episodes have more than three
True three bucks a convention and
Have
Nobody I think largely because
You and I don't want to
Inflict other people with
We talked about it and I think the most people don't
Want to talk about those things
People who are in Merced in this world are kind of rare
To the interact with him and luckily today we have somebody who has immersed herself
I in this world for the New York Times and actually has a new book
That is coming out called Sandy Hook
An American Tragedy and the Battle For Truth
Elizabeth Williamson thank you for joining us here today
Hey Dan hey Jordan it's so nice to be with you guys
Welcome to this
Awful content podcast
It's a tragic
Sort of subject matter that we all cover in that
Kind of fitting
Related to
Tragic topic
Yeah
Absolutely
Yeah you guys some
Remember store Southcenter
Alex Jones's
Coverage of
If you could call it that Sandy Hook from the very beginning
Yeah we we
Babe that mistake
LaFerrari Ferrari mental state
Yeah
And lives and you know
Just general
Cynicism is taking hold
Yeah I know I had hoped before yeah it it was an interesting ride certainly
Watching all the stuff from late 2012
Onward and I imagine that you
Probably had
Exact same but fairly similar
Experience
Diving into a lot of
Material
Yeah in fact
I first got to know both of you your work that is and your show
Because Lenny Posner who is the father of Noah Pozner the youngest Sandy Hook victims
Recommended that I listen to your podcast
Sort of going back and taking a look at what Alex Jones
Said on the day of the shooting
So that was
How I first
Became acquainted
Out with you both
And had that whole show trance
Ascribed
And you do kind of really studied what you had to say about it
What is like what see let me see if I remember some of the things I said about it
I believe he's a trash
Human made of
Garbage and feces did that one go into the book
15 not go into the book Jordan alright quote you on that alright
Okay it is a little surreal to know that random things Jordan was yelling as maintenance
What was research material
That will be our our
Close toll
As we sit here and
So this
Do you think that's how you sort of Came Upon Our show but it was that in the context of you.
Already had it in your mind to write
A book about this
This subject matter
Yeah it was
You know I got to know
Lenny obviously at
The very beginning of the
The project
Because he was one of
Two families
Is that sued Alex Jones in
In Texas in the middle of 2018
And when I saw that kind of come over the transom either one of our reporters who covers
Breaking news
Put that in the paper
And I thought
Wow that is a pretty
Cast of the First Amendment and at the time we were really in the middle of year the very beginning of the Trump era
Untappd
Truth and
Alternative facts and
This just seemed like
A real test on you
Alex Jones
As you guys have documented
4 years
Often claims it not always
Claims the First Amendment as a defense
For what he says
Sure seems like
A great test of
You know
What is free speech and
It's a deer
Your first amendment rights
Hover
I'm spreading material that results
Open significant harm to already
That is one thing that I enjoyed about the book
Is
No I mean it doesn't matter how many years we are going to do this
You still have to write out the entirety of the First Amendment
Put it in the book and then remind people once again it only protects you from the government
It's hard to protect you from face
It's like there's a lot of these
These people kind of say they call it my free speech
And my first
Amendment 10
It's kind of hours
You know so
There's like they don't exist really in the context of a community interaction
For a team member
Promulgated thing yeah
Knox
With the proper
Yeah yeah yeah I think it's really fun to is that now that is
Come such a meme kind of that
Is used by people in other countries as a sort of a buzzword you saw there with the Canadian
Truck organizer
Oh yeah
Yeah it's
It's very strange how that's a better understanding
Then we just talked to what's his dumb face the guy who's lizards Which Wich
David Icke we just talked about David I can he was talking
Think about his first amendment rights
Senor like
You're from the Buford Britain man
It's true
I think he still lives in
You came to
He's relocated
Yeah yeah
It's very it's very strange
But you you were
You're somebody who I know you were you were writing about Alex
Or you had written about Alex prior to this
If I understand correctly cuz
I know that
My first interaction with you
Was Alex yelling about you
I ate heard him
Complain about something you had written
Before we had ever spoken
It sounds kind of wondering
Like where did your exposure with
Jim begin
Like what do you do recall when you first
Gaming contact
With his
He's content in
What what the
Kicked off that path
Yeah I do
I may have heard about him a little bit
During
But my first
Exposure to him him sort of
In the Flash
Was during the Republican National Convention in twenty
16 and cleave
So he and Rodger Stone and Ida
Describe this in the book
They were on the stage
At the the America
The first Unity rally
On the Cuyahoga River
On the convention yeah sort of in the convention City if not
Play convention grounds
And I sat down next to a woman who
With a very
Nice
She seems like just one of those nice women and you know she was sitting there
Yeah we had
Really big smile and kind of it
Gentle way about her she was
Early sixties and
I was asking her the way I was asking a lot of people who were there for that rally
Alex Jones and Rodger Stone drama stage
And I was saying where do you get your nose and she was saying
Louder with Crowder
Infowars
Bench
Shapiro
And she said you know
If you're a journalist
Cuz I have course dinner
Myself as one
She said if you're a journalist
And you're not listening to those shows
You're only getting half the
I can that makes me really sad cuz like I can understand
Someone
Of that age cohort watching Ali
Likes possibly
I could see them watching Ben Shapiro
If you have these presents himself is like
I'm pretending to be an intellectual / 25
Would watch louder with Crowder is so sad
That show is the dumbest
Sophomoric attempt at comedy I can't
I can't imagine an adult watch
Watching conservative,
Sophomore
Does like poo poo jokes
It's that
Done with her and I would say her son
Was
Maybe 30
Or so maybe a little bit younger little bit older
And he
They hear she spent her son was disabled so he was in a wheelchair and they spend a lot of time
Together because he had a lot of difficulties in
He or she mentioned that they'd listen to these shows
Underway
Two doctors
And some things like that
So I think they were
Things that he started listening to her that he was listening
Thank you for a long time
And she kind of you know
Picked up on it
From him that's a bit that pointed to parents
Responsibility
You got to be a bridge would you jump off of it too
Well I mean pretty hot these days
That sucks that there's also a nice irony to that image that you're painting of
You know this
Rally involving people like Alex and Rodger Stone you were so staunchly opposed to like government regulation
Happening on the Cuyahoga River right
Essentially a testament to the effectiveness of the EPA
The tragic image
Running into this
This is this
This protest is this where you at
Did you end up talking
Rodger
It was a very crowded then
There were a lot of people there are a lot of Hillary for prison t-shirts remember those
Oh yeah
And and so know he was up on the stage and kind of in his
You know Entourage and sort of you know security around him and
And things like that so you describe him in the book as just
Him and Rodger stone is just swaggering about when their retinue
Yeah acting like celebrities like either that's one of the big things that you you bring up for just specifically that
Is Alex
It's such a
Strfkr
That like he goes to those places to soak up their celebrity which is such a great point of
Yeah he it was interesting his staffers
We're telling me that that
You know
One of them described him as he would always say you know as you guys know better than me
Hollywood the root of all you know globalist evoland
At the same time he said he was like a girl screaming after the Beatles
When it came to itto people he was meeting at the convention
You're the best
He was really and also the other thing with
He was doing which is
His cameraman who is with him
At the time told me
For the book
That
It what they were doing is
You're making their way through media row you know they were inside rather than outside the convention barrier where it you know
Alex Jones would typically be with
His bullhorn you know always on the outside of the perimeter
Instead they were very much
Departed things
She was definitely on the ascendant
They were you know kind of sweating through the crowd
Creating provocations you know I'm needy arohi
Get crashed sank uyghurs show the younger
Jimmy Dore spit on them
You did yeah Alex Jones did wind up with
Spit on him that day
But that was all great for him because
This cameramen filmed all of that and they were really looking for
Viral video from there and they got it
Damn now that's
That's the unfortunate thing is that strategy does to
Ends up paying off
Yeah there were a lot of events that I'm I think I just grabbed him in the book as
You know he was
He's like
A shark
He needs attend
If he does
Get it it's like a sharks
If he doesn't spill never sleeps
But with a shark it's just sort of
Evolve that way with Alex
Because he's on standby
Yeah well I mean that's a certain type of that
Addiction evolves over time
That is true
Is this weird like your first
Article
Involved
Come from is this
This where that's at the
Let's burn out
Yeah I was on the editorial board
For the times
Then and I wrote you a short
Peace just on
What is this
Alternative
News ecosystem that
You know these folks are really wired into a louder with Crowder that I hear
Apple talking about
And I really did feel like very much an outsider cuz of course as soon as that
That story went in the paper I got a lot of you know
People who listen to Ben Shapiro do not listen to louder with Crowder and
How could you put them in the same sentence end
You do all of the
So
But my
My
Broader point
You known earlier point
Was just
That
This is a whole group of
Personalities
And shows and sources of information that
Most of us have never really heard of
New York Times
NSAID
Yeah
In the in the intervening time
Cuz I mean one thing that we talked about with
Mark Bankston
Who is
Solid protagon
Going to send your book
He he specifically said you know over the years that I've absorbed myself in the
In this case
You know it is definitely changed some of the way that I think
About things
Do you feel like this is this is had that kind of effect on you as well
So I remember a moment
With Mark thank
Winston and Bill Ogden
Another
Another partner
On the show have you been on the show strong and no bill Ogden policy
Go on TV and markets to hang out with us
Okay I get it I like Bill I met him when I was down in Austin.
He's great but I like I also kind of like to Pretend There's a
Oh I see okay alright well I'm not
Step on that but
Iam
He told me once we
We after one of the Year while I was working on the book we went out
To dinner and now
I remember Mark went off to take a phone call and Bill was talking about how his role in
McKay's
Was listening to hundreds and hundreds of hours of
Infowars broadcast
To find the points where he references the family so that they could make sure they had every rough
And
She said
I was seriously starting
To lose it he said
One late here late one night he just was listening to it you know what his 40th or 50
Successive Infowars
For our programming stent and he was saying
Oh my God
Yeah that's that's a fairly chilling line in the book
And and and I thought
You know but it is true that if you
And that's the sort of frog boil of all of this isn't it
That you know I mean
This is this
Form of propaganda is like
90 * you know you start bike with it with a relatively minor suggestion
Then you start with something a little stronger you you have small live and you have a little bigger lie I mean the very
First lie was about crowd sizes at the inauguration right I'm very first day
And then you don't look at the size of allies
By the time we got to January 6th
And it really was a kind of
Can you I'm like that
It was sorta like
Before we really knew it
Earwig
We were looking at this and saying
This this
Lie about the 2020
Action was
Unthinkable even a year ago and here
Is a significant swath of Americans who really believe it
I mean I supposed supposed to my next question then is like do you feel like this type of propaganda is differ
Because
You know before before
2017 before the inauguration it wasn't like that's the first time people
We're believing in things that were
Clearly in
Incontrovertibly
Bulshit
So you feel like this is something that you
Have
Interacted with in a different way from
Let's say other forms of propaganda
So I think taking the Long View
Jordan
The big thing
Obviously that
Is a big difference
Certainly from the Nazi era until
Till now
Is
Social media
And
You know the gigantic up
Take
In social media even from
You don't say
So I went back and I
I talked to
Parents
The mother of a young woman who was involved in the
Virginia Tech
Masa
And she was saying you don't hear was a huge
Shooting on a college campus
Interstate
Where you know people would get
Concerned about
Gun policy in the aftermath of that
And they're just really wasn't a lot of
Conspiracy theories
That shooting
If you look at you know how many people
Side
Facebook
For example in 2000
7 when that occurred
It was 20 million people
By December of 2012 when the Sandy Hook shooting happen
That number was
1 billion
And I really think that that has
Accelerated I mean we've we've spoken
Together
About
Someday old
Cultish things and things like that
The loan guy on the
Subway with
Casino
A photocopy
You know about the JFK assassination or
Those people were really icy
Before and now they found
Each other and they
Feed whatever they
Come up with around the
The world ends
Yeah
And I think that they
Look through social media and like YouTube
They found
Really efficient ways to monetize
This is out of
The speediness of that that messaging that's got to be
Like a pretty negative
Reinforcement
Yeah that doesn't even
You know
You think about you think about that change
And now there's a Tik-Tok as so impenetrable to
So many people above the age of 19 that's that's like my louder with Crowder
But you do see millions of views on these short videos that are all bulshit
Instantly
But you know
They're there and then they're gone and it's
It sticks in your brain
I think it's impossible for humans to interact with social media in a responsible way
I could be wrong
I'm kind of with you on that one I think you I do think I do see a I sound like a
Super Midwest
Pollyanna here
Cunningham
But
It's I really do think
The newer generation younger generation coming up are much more skeptical
About what they redone
And about having your
Of course there are thousand except
That but I really do feel like
You know I mean I have kids who are that age
And I really feel like they are much worse kept
Article not only of what they read on there
But about having an accountant
And what that means
Sure the privacy
The stuff is so much more clear
You know I got I think
It in just my time
Since I was
In college
You know
Facebook went from the Facebook
Where was the thing where only college students were on it
Two big white Lake open
Interesting wave you could like
Promotive
There's all kinds of possibilities to attend now
It's like your grandma's on there and she sending you change emails
It's it's taken on in addition to the privacy
Concerned because
Becoming more clear
The evolution of what
This is
Has train
Your Point Journal you were bringing up the
It seems like Tik-Tok is kind of
Like a place where there is a a newer
Sense of life
Migrated it's a little bit to that
I wonder if what you're saying Elizabeth
Babe you feel like some of these
Like younger folk are just avoiding even
We can gauging at all
Beekeeping with stick
Yeah I mean you know I have a I have an 18 year old
And she
Got on Twitter maybe in the last two or three months
Because he's communicating with
You know his football.
But
Even before
Before that though no snow
Social media accounts whatsoever
You know Joe
Kind of
Took it on board that
Boy if you want to go to college
One great way not to get into the school your choices have somebody surface one of your old
You know awful
Twitter Facebook post
Nino orb Instagram
College admissions looking for
Some some racist thing you posted as a thirteen-year-old or something
That'd be crazy
Yeah and I so I think that you know to some degree
That message
And also you know
They're just that much more time
Technologically savvy
You know they kind of understand how the sausage
It just made online
Which is really in
Interesting I mean
And that actually that knowledge
Being used as a say in the book you know there's
There is it that there's a series of games now where
People can make up a conspiracy theory as a kind of game
As a way to inoculate them against
Bamiyan to conspiracy theories and
Spreading them online without really knowing it before they hit the button you're so they kind of understand
Yeah
How do you make one you know how do you make a
It's spread
Like what elements do you put in there to make it really viral you know just responding to that you know outrage algorithm
All of that
So if you see something online
And they're studying this
People who
Looking at this and if they
Kind of inoculate people in that way by showing them how this is made and how to spread them
Then when they run into him online they're less likely to spread them
And to be more skeptical
What is
The belief in a conspiracy theory right it's sort of saying I possess
Superior knowledge
You know I know something the rest of you Rubes don't know
And so you can use that in this sort of
Free banking
Anything that they as they call it
All to the good cuz talking people out of this stuff
As you guys know is
Really
Yeah that's that's definitely something we hear a lot has also sounds like you're a tyrant pushing vaccines on us
Inoculation
New York Times of the Caballo weather to me
Yeah I think one of the things that I find very interesting about my experience
With
Doing the show is that there is not really been a ton of
Interaction with info Warriors let's say
I think part of that is just due to the fact that we don't really engage on social media all that much here it's kind of like
The wave that folks end up having most
Their argument
We have not had a ton of
Instances where we try to talk somebody out of these beliefs
What second-hand I do hear that
It'll be program
As it were
Can be very difficult from what do internalizing idea like
Sandy Hook was fake
2 or
January 6th was
Provocative Santa by the FBI
Antifa
Yeah yeah
Do you do you get a lot of that it from your from your work you get a lot of
Folks who want to convince you that you're wrong
Oh absolutely and in reporting this book
Just every
Conspiracy theorist I spoke with
In fact there's one in particular Kelly W
Who is in a life I really started delving
I was just very
Curious about
How you know how does someone with the email handle
Great mom
You know GR
Numeral 8
Mom
Actually
Get to place where she's posting on
Lenny posner's Memorial site
To his murdered son
I want Geraldo to open the cast
Yeah
That story was f***** up
Yeah I could not
Understand
How someone could get
Play send
So I Geraldo famously opened Al Capone safe and there was nothing in it she was kind of making
I'm being too
No she was
Yeah
You know and then the idea of so she had a cleaning the house cleaning the house and office cleaning business in Tulsa Oklahoma
And you don't hurt her sort of unique contribution to this
Crazy quilt of Sandy Hook series was
Let's find out
What company
Cleaned up this
School after
And that became one of
Toxic
Request
That these
Hoaxers pudding
To the board of ed in
Did the city of newt
Either we want a copy of the contract
And we want receipts and we want photos and
They were extremely graphic
Taken what they were describing might have been
Been cleaned up from
From the school
And
The thing that was really interesting is
One of Lenny Posner song
Tears
I'm into bunking all of this stuff
Actually found the records
A police report that
Etc
This is the name of the
Company I actually called the
Company I had a conversation with them
Confirm that yes they didn't back clean
Extremely detailed record of what was removed from the school and what have
Happened to it
And so I presented this
To her and
Comes the answer
After some silence
Where's the receipts
It's just
Never
Ending and you know there is no and I actually think that maybe someone like her
They are so far down the rabbit hole
That there's a there would be a level of Shame involved
I mean
Course your entire life is a lie
And not yet that definitely Jordan and
But I think beyond that
You have tormented the families of murdered children
I mean at some point
Maybe you can't
It's easier to believe
I think I would personally
I have a really tough time but
I also think that maybe
If you're in that state
You can't even
Conscious you're not even consciously making that decision
Like you know didn't you know what I mean
You can't you obviously
Except
The possibilities that you did something
Yeah.
Yeah you're just
You just won't allow it happening manifest
Fasb's like
Instinctual denials of any proof that you're wrong
What do you think is different Elizabeth because
There is the story from where Lenny Posner joins the
Oaks Facebook group
I do believe it's Jen
Who eventually exits the group and help yet
Lenny starts
That his is a program
Wondering what do you think is different between Jen and
What
Great mother
Great mom
So that that that woman Jen Force
So
Here's what I think happened at the beginning
End
I think a lot of the parents
You know enlighten me
To this
Share this View
That in the beginning this was such a horrific crime that no one
Wanted to believe that
You know it was
The parents themselves that they when they
Right and
And speak about it
They talk about waking up in those first
Stays you know and say
Oh my God what a horrible nightmare I just had and then realizing that their living
That is their life
And that did how
And there was there were a significant number of these early
Entertainers I'll say of the
Conspiracy theory around Sandy Hook
Cooper young parents themselves
Two had children around that same age
And one of them you know I profile for the book
A woman named Tiffany mausser who
Became one of Lenny's most convicted
Convinced and uncommitted
Volunteers
Who you know
Had had a tragic situation in her past
She hit a child with her car and that child died
We had
Two children who were around the same ages
The children who were killed
And she went on to the Sandy Hook hoax
Facebook page
Just say I am here
For whoever
Can tell me this didn't happen
I just need to believe that this
And that was and that was Jen to you know s*** also took a little bit of a true crime
Kind of approach to the
To the whole
Prime right but
But these were the people who kind of
Peels off
Because they were open to being
Convinced it was more of a
You know a gut
Kind of emotional reaction
To the crime
Itself
This level of evil is possible
Kind of thing
Exactly exactly
Yeah they just put
Do it
It's interesting that you brought up that has people with young children
Around that like
That it would somebody find really bizarre is that
I just realized that Alex's kids would have been
Younger
At that point
And it's that that wasn't the reason I wasn't in
Experience
But he had
I believe it was actually on the very first day when the news broke
Because
This is something that I remember specifically
When we covered
Is when the news first broke
Alex did not immediately have a negative reaction
His first reaction
His instinctive reaction was
I'm sorry
I'm sorry for the fam
Yeah that was his instant reaction and then the next day
It was awful
Everything was a lie
He was crouching ways to make a patient first day that's true
There was that there was a gut-check a little bit but it didn't last the whole show
A little bit coffee
My memory is literally always fuzzy that's the only reason the show works
But there was a moment remember when he talked about
Okay this is happening at the holidays
Oh my God
You know however many kids he had the number wrong but he knew that it was it was a a large number
And
And he did
Seem to be
At least momentarily taking a bath
Right
What an a******
You know what I'm thinking this guy is no good I'm having a negative opinion on it
Yeah
Really that's
Really bizarre.
There's thinking about the difference
Between what make
Somebody
I
With somebody who would
The give up on the
Conspiracy
When confronted by some reality and somebody who's
There's just never stopped yeah I wonder if there is even
Some kind of
Consistency
Doing what
And what
And what were you could learn
I think it is I think it really has to do with I mean that this not University of Miami Joey Shins
Ski who studied conspiracy theories especially political ones
And I would
Call this one of those because
Gun control
Always a factor and you know or or almost
Consistently and definitely the government planned it makes it
Protocol
Conspiracy theory but
His
Peebles
He will say you know even qanon
Does not select
Politics
That
You know it is really your kind of mindset
And your
Personality
Much more than your politics that determines whether or not you
Conspiracy theories
And you know I was
Skeptical because
Qanon
So much about
Hillary Clinton and the Democrats
You know
Democratic stronghold and Balboa
But
If you really look at you know the different variants of that you know
Child traffic
You can kind of understand where he's coming from
And I think you know a lot of
These people there's a level of narcissism is
Documented so well with
That you know I need to possess the
Superior knowledge
And then there's a certain you know in this
This woman Kelly W daughter Madison explain to me
You don't my mom never felt like anybody really
Respected her for having an a
Original
Idea or
You know making a
Kind of intellectual conch
Contribution
Or something like that it was it's really important
Her
To be the sort of bear
Unique
You know it's hard to even
Yeah
You know
Other people would ghettobaby like get an advanced degree or
But
It's an emotional thing you can
Kind of relate to understand us
It's a
How to struggle but with the way you
Proceed from there
Right
Is not good now the interesting thing about
What's your book
That I appreciate is that despite it being
Very focused on Sandy Hook it is also
A really good example of that kind of grapes
Conspiracy theories
Singularity
So many of these people wound up
Sandy Hook
Conspiracy theories
Coming from different motives different backgrounds different things that they wanted to be true
And
As we as you point out you know yoga moms
Turn into anti-vaxxers 5 years later
And it's all the same conspiracy theory but
People are just coming out at 4
From so many different
Ya know it's true and you know I
One thing I didn't explore a lot although I did in talking about Kelly Watts life and kind of what her life
Had been because it
You know there's a lot of trauma
In her life
I do think trauma in some of these folks lives
You know like Tiffany mausser that the woman you know who had the access
Set with her car and a child died or
Either we just had a story in the times yesterday about
Robert F Kennedy Junior and his belief in it you know just
One of them
Biggest anti-vaxxers you know with an enormous following
And just like an absolutely divisive force in the
The Kennedy family
But you do a lot of trauma neck
Alex was stuck under a house one time
When they were fumigate again,
No I mean it is it is very much a I find it so analogous to
Evangelical born-again Christians
The ones that come to it later in life
Because
Something
Something is like prison
Yeah I mean or
Cyberweld rogerstone of course
But but there is that like there's an inciting event that where you're at your lowest
There's a group
That love bombs you essentially
And then you're just
You know so if you're at your lowest point
Your business isn't going so well
Nobody's helping you out you find a qanon website
You're immediately love bombed with guess what you're so smart
Validation
Yeah no it's that makes me think of
I think that's a really good point it makes me think of somebody like Mike
You know
Mike Flynn when he was in the military was
You know people called it
Information
Ghetto his plight of misconceptions about
Islam or
Or
Radicalism
Or you
He didn't have I mean
It's a general side you're telling me that they do everybody's like oh yeah we know that guy's full of s*** but we're going to continue
Foreboding
Offices with Fluor like
National Security advisor exactly yes
Scrapes
Yeah but it was that you know that kind of
The thing that really struck me about a lot of these groups like the Sandy Hook hoax group or any of these gatherings
Casino on
On social media
With how mutually reinforcing
You know that
Almeda
Each other feel really
Smart and that's what Kelly Watts daughter said
To have a guy like
Jim Fetzer
Who is a PhD
Who are the former professor of
Wait for it
Logic
University of Minnesota
One of the biggest Sandy Hook hoaxers out there
Praising her for her insides for her Scrappy reporting for
Calling hundred
The people in Newtown and never giving up as she sought you know
The contract the holy grail for
Who cleaned up
School
That makes
People feel good and if they don't have a lot of other sources for that
It's really hard to
Give that address
Yeah I'm bummed out the gym pets
Was a professor of logic
IAA
They studied a bit of logic
Acknowledgement
Did I do
Think they
When people who
Study that
Break
It's not a twig at the 309
Really hot rail for you you know once logic breaks you're out of your out of games you know
You can use also for deferiet
Ways to make really bad argument
Arguments are not logical
They're not they don't follow
Formal
Structure
I don't know I'm sorry I just got lost there for a second
I am amazed
One thing that is I will give to Jim Fetzer is that
Even in print form
When you write out his quotes he does sound like he's shrieking mad
You know like you can hear him going in your in your head while you're reading is quotes
Yeah
That
How to interview him
A few
In person that interview in the in my rental car
Right
I enjoyed I enjoyed that story
He's laid low after the case
And he does not want to talk to Olivia and
Eventually like fire
Your car
Absolutely like a drug deal my family doesn't need to know about
I'll get in your car
His family was so angry that
Is it but
It was like crap to him that idea that
You would get
Yet one more interview and
Some attention
And be able to trumpet his
Because he had been
Successfully by Lenny's lawyers
You know Lenny
Failure failure listeners in
He had sued him for defamation and won
They wanted $450,000 judgment in October of
And
So I went and spoke with him after that and after he lost
You know this was enough to bankrupt
Probably two generations of
What is familysoda
Yeah so he was saying you know my family doesn't
Really and it was killing him to say that because it was his wife and daughter so it just seemed like he had been completely
You know
Emasculated by this
But yeah it was sort of like
I'll talk to you in the car so then my wife
And then he immediately decided to find a way to double that judgment against two
Four generations of his family
I sealed videotape
Deposition and gave it to the hoaxers and then they put it online
And they compared
Lenny's
Ear
To his ear in previous photos and
Decided that the Lenny who testified in that defamation case in the courtroom was in
This checks out
I remember that actually being like a really popular thing
Conspiracy message boards
Leslie like
Let's compare ears
Well so weird once you get an ear you know the rest of a person
Soul
That's picture of
Joe Biden Iroquois
Conspiracy to
One of the hoaxers told
Lyrica I'm sure
There's a Joe Biden body part conspiracy forever is top-to-bottom
Everybody's a queen
Honestly Joe Biden is three people he's a clone he's a walk-in also Jim Carrey and he's Jim Carrey we learned
Carrie is wearing a bow tie
You play as Joe Biden that's why he does these gaps
Yep sometimes he does pratfalls
Very insightful stuff
From actually Project Camelot who interviewed Jim Fetzer Olga
Full circle
I can't imagine
What that but like would be like
Be in a closed space
Face with him
Would you would you say that that was
Maybe the most bizarre
Experience of the book preparation
Cuz I would like I would
Love to hear about
If there was something later
Weirdest
Jim Fetters brat
Yeah I do mention that in the book that's the only reason I brought it
It was quite funny
On a technicality I still think that's part of being in a confined space
Yeah I can't see can't barely separate that out
I would have to say that Alex Jones interview
When I when I interviewed him
That was some
That was really interesting and it and it was funny because
Andrei interviewed him I had a couple years to think about it
So I know I kind of listened to it again and again and thought about it and thought about it in the context of a
Paymaster
And
I think
You know
It was a really
Interesting window into
The man
More so that it seemed on the day of
Because at
The time it seemed like he was just
Doing the show
You know
She called me the next
Stay and then he spoke
For two more hours on the phone and that was actually a little more real because I think he got
He might have called his lawyers
His mistake
What is an item actually put snipers on the roof of my build
Yeah it could have just been drunk
Perhaps
I don't know but
No idea but I got the sense
Like when we were
Speaking Rob do his
Naruto
Lieutenant was in the room
And I got the sense that he was trying to end
You know watch me intimidate this woman
You know watch me like make fun of her watch me make fun of her paper to her face
Etcetera etcetera
How come stuff really doesn't
Bother me
And so
It didn't really
Rattled
Play much brother such a there's such a good little part in whenever you're describing the interview in your book where
You say if he was really trying to intimidate me he would have come up and put a
Space right into mine
And instead
Just kept backing further and further away from
Which spider moving around the room and
Yeah I was great Connecticut
Description of his
Complete and utter cowardice
Bedford I do he didn't get a ship that's that's really where my heart goes out to
Poor guy
He gets to be the corporate representative a few years after
Somebody gave us a show
Yeah
I'll say
That was yeah that his
His behavior was also really enjoy
Interesting because
It was such a like
He'd laugh at Alex's jokes and that's her to check Alex's face to make sure it was okay that he was laughing like
Was that a joke
If you didn't mean it as
The Joker
I don't want to be laughing
That was that was
And that I remember calling back
Writing it if
Different story
And he
And here is
Like
Is this Elizabeth Williamson from the CIA who says
Lame
You could do better Rob come on
Oh yeah
Is Alex
Surround
Rob can I talk to your dad please
I pretended to be a big boy
Yeah that's actually kind of sad
You can do better Rob but I bet you
Fighting history teachers
Yeah I have gone back
And I realize that one of the things that I have
Generally missed
Over
But I'm doing the shows
Since of the Infowars Nightly News
The show that Rob was the head of
I've gone back and watch some of that new
I was right to ignore it
It's so bad
You eat it a terrible job for years
Naturally by David Knight
He was for the
Beset
The the older crowd who might be offended by Alex's gallon instead of louder with Crowder Ben Shapiro
Quieter
What's Covent down with David
Have some chamomile tea in the morning
You like to go to bed at 11 a.m.
David items for you
Forget you celebrate New Years at 4 in the afternoon
Do you you interviewed Alex and what worked was the
What was the surrealness of it other than him backing into a corner
And and
Failing to in
What would you
What do you win with about it was so surreal
I really was trying to get
So the idea of
How
How do you sort of
How do Tuesday how do these two things exist
In Alex Jones
He is
Good father
Three children
Sorry now for
And
He is someone who
Knew that he was inflicting a lot of pain
On
Parents who
She had to have known
Obviously that he was inflicting a lot of pain on the
Her parents
Of children who were his
Children's ages
Who were brutally murdered
And I just
You know all the joking aside and all the
You know the the
The sort of bravado and the end the China Vino
Performance
I just I couldn't really get there and it made me think about some of these other
Conspiracists wear
Is it that if you actually looked
Set that
And you didn't just deflect
The question
Could you ask
Actually live with yourself
You know I mean
Jon Ronson
And you know the Welsh
Filmmaker who spent a lot of time
Without Jones from
Wayback
And you know he
Thanks
She was different
Person
You know that earlier on he was not
The kind of person who could do so
And the islamophobia and the racism and all of that and he thinks that with
Money and power
Came a lot of that what do you guys say
I don't necessarily believe that
I think the John knew him
And obviously has more exposure to him
I think
That a lot of the stuff
But say the big
3MP
Denial of
Stuff
Those Turtles were there in his earlier career
It's just
Are you with money and power you'd more to protect
And more need
To accelerate
Eminem
More dramatic
An interesting person
You start to make money off
Being
I don't know
What's your head
It doesn't
I excite the audience as much
To maintain that same level you going to have to ask a late in order to keep people's attention I think
Yeah I think that business model maybe he you became
A slave too but I think
I think a fair amount of
Those Tendencies were already there
A big John Birch guy like
From the beginning of his career in
Right there nothing is not a ideology that's based around
Racist
Be a nice caring person and also believe that black people are part of a communist plot to kill
Kill white people
The idea of civil rights
Is a communist conspiracy
Feel like
I don't feel like that at
Exist generally in a non bigger
Yeah I think I think less
That's what I mean that is an interesting question
What Alex was like indifferent
Time. But
One thing that John said to us when we when we talk to mister
Was
He doesn't know if you can really Judge Alex
Based on the way that we would judge
Other people
Because
Maybe Alex is really just a narcissistic
Psychopath
And if that's the case
What really do we have to say to a person who is just
Utterly incapable
Of giving a f*** about
Whether or not murdered kids
Families are are
In pain
You know
Yeah I mean
I always am shy wave
From those things cuz I'm not a
Psychiatrist obviously
Just a journalist exactly Goldwater
But
It is awfully hard
To come up with
The
And not only him
You know how
These people could
It's either maybe it's that
They truly truly believe it and now it's just case
He is already set
She thinks she'll be
Open. So this is this
Does not apply to
But
I think there are some of these individuals who really do believe that
This didn't happen or didn't happen the way it was reported
And then I think there are others of them that
There's something they're getting out of this witch
That is much more precious to them
Then
Even their reputation
You know or there
You know or the sort of ostracisation that comes from
Espousing a theory like
Like this so they're kind of driven back into their own
Proud
Because those are the only people who
Will give them the benefit of the
The doubt anymore not only as a
Conspiracy theorist but
Yeah I mean it it makes sense if you go out into reality
Painful and if you Retreat back into fantasy everybody likes
I mean it's it's
You know if you go outside and you're a vampire and
Get burnt
You're going to stay inside
Yeah yeah 53rd group it's become a kind of knew family to them
You know one number then
I am in Wolfgang halbig again Springs
His wife left
Him he is completely estranged
From an insofar as I can
Intel
You know from his
And from his grandkid
And you know this
James Tracey you know University of
That you
FAU thank you for the Atlantic University
Thank you so much and I just
So yeah so he
For him I mean he lost his job he told me he's an absolute Pariah and Academia
There he is
Unemployable
She has a lot of kids
And including a child
With a lot of difficulties you need to
You know Medical Care
And yet
He doesn't find a road back for himself and as I'm getting off the phone kind of feeling awful it
You do what is just
Described as
You know his life
He's like
We can talk about coronavirus yet
Yeah
So
There is no Elemento
Psychology there that
I think requires some
Special training.
Yeah probably that's a good way of putting it and it's really interesting
To the look at that person
These people like Fetzer and how big
Tracy who you're describing as like
Effaced
Drastically severe
Secuencias
And
Maybe that's what's coming for Alex
But it's so weird that he's
Been able
To some degree to avoid the Fate that these other
Folks have
Just Duke boys in the General Lee over
Laws
Yeah pretty remarkable
Yeah it is well
He's made a lot of money doing this as
You know you guys know from
The documents that have come
Come out
Court cases
You do he's
Cannon fire
Legal count
Council and
So far
He's
You know
But I do think
The Reckoning
I think
I think what I'm hearing from you is that
Setzer's mistake was he didn't start a pill come
This is the classic mistake
That we need a pill
Pretty bad
I was thinking about this
The process of writing this book
I took
Quite a while
And it's
It's as much as it is a creative process
It's got to be also
Like a learning
Experience
Says well going along
What do you think is
But one of the most essential things that you learned
Over the course of the
Experiences
Of writing the book
I think I'm not original in saying this and that set
Every book
Is a lot harder
To right then
You think it is
Starting out
That's what a lot of
Call ezoo written books told me complained about that a bit
Don't you think
It's it's great
The process is awesome it happened so quick and you never ever struggle
That's the thing I learned from writing a book
Oh no
You never stare at your computer screen and wonder if life is worth living
The process
This is obviously very difficult and then you add the subject matter being something
So uncomfortable to wrestle with something
Yeah
I mean one thing that I struggle with Az a writer just
In general just in my day job at the time
Is
You don't that sort of
A blank paper
Kind of feeling I will just put
Something down just not to have to look at that and
Because one
As long as the page is blank
I can come up with the most amazing things to do to keep me from actually writing I'm sorry
I organized an entire
Linen closet during this book project
Before a chapter and it wasn't even Milan
Closet
To learn procrastination taken
Really new one
Impress
Steven Myself and I
I'm used to myself on that so
I found that bad happened
Before every chapter
26 chapters
So I added up all the days that I spent you know kind of
Stalling between chapters because of the
Total Terror of
Starting a new chapter
And I thought you know I could brazenness this book 6 months
Every every now and again but like when I'm trying to not prepare an episode
I will consider learning a new language
Or something
I find this at
That's been such an impulsive like
This material is
Ugly I remember
I don't actually do it I just think about it
Alright sometimes I scroll through Duolingo and maybe
Maybe today is the day that I
Brush up on my French
Or whatever
It's great day exactly remember what
But I was riding by and I had a blank page and I was
I was doing everything possible to avoid looking at it
And then the next time I turned and looked down I had written
You're doing alright
Just without I didn't think about it it was there waiting for me when I went back and I was like
I think I need help
I think you might need that medicine
How did you get over that feeling that blanket
What I mean
That was kind of
Part of it will be we talked about it before we recorded but that was parted by
Chopping up so I printed everything out and then chopped it up
And so having the physical
Watch I'm not pieces of paper with stuff that I'd already written on it
I could look over at that and then start writing a
So that was really you know I'm holding
Are you know to win
It's it's trying to mix
The transcription and
Turn it into something new
You know
So one thing that I did was
And this was on the advice of
Time is a mentor
To me who's written
Name is David Harbour
And
Wonderful wonderful friend and he said
One thing you want to do
They are bunch of chapters or if you
You can swing it your whole first draft
Send it to a group of readers people
Russ not just journalists not to
Just people and wash
Container in New York or wherever
Like some friends who are
Read a lot of books and
You know who you trust to give you some honest
Feedback
So I print all that out
You know it's 16 chapters
I realize that at 16 chapters and again there are 26
I was a hundred thousand words over
That's actually an entire book
So I had to talk my entire book
A hundred thousand words
From the first 16 chapters
And then write 10 more
So
But those 10 those following 10 were definitely a little more refined than the
The lesson of 100,000
Was Larry
I mean one thing that I will say absolutely is
Is great
Is how readable
It is so
Straightforward well-paced
Written organized
I mean I read it in
I think 3 or 4 hours
Like sat down and just
Bang it out is great
Thank you so much
And thank you for reading
You welcome
Exchange another quick question
Before you
As far as what we found is when you
Study the misinformation world if you
Get good enough at it you become part of your story
You know like
From the beginning the idea with our show a Dans Dans intent was we're not going to interact with Infowars
I don't want to become part of
The story
And in your case
You
He talked about you on the show
Do you feel like you got added into the story more than you wanted to
Oh that's a great
Question
It is
What a great exchange exchange
You know I suppose
Suppose it was going to be inevitable
Because when you're asking
People why they do what they do
And
You know it's
Clear that
You're not on there
That they're going to c&n against the nature of this was
These people are are getting so much
Psychic income from what they're doing
That
Anyone on the out
Side of that asking
Questions and saying
What you just said is
Shrew
Is a threat and antenna
Righto
I think.
There was part of that
And then also you may have noticed over
The past several years that
The New York Times in general is a pretty handy file
For a lot of
Folks who
Sure
And it's something that has
Permit
Implode attached
Stewart
To like
The New York times is attacking me
Is is almost
A sign of validation
Someone like Alex would be very difficult to resist
Yeah
Yeah and
You know and I I tried it like
While some of what I was
You know I knew had gone on and and what I was learning and and what p
People were saying
Was absolutely
Urinating
Juno
Really
Beyond
Creating
I was trying to
Stand you know I just kept trying to thing
If I'm passing judgment or I'm just pushing back all the
I'm not going to
Gain any fresh
Insights I mean we know this
Stop is wrongheaded you know we already know that so they don't
Need me to tell them that
You know I'm trying to figure out like
How did you
Become this way
And
And why do you say
This is it
You do it
Is it like a prophet reason
Is it an ideological reason
Is it something that you know is there like some need in you that
This fulfills
I was trying to understand that
Just be
Because
I wanted the book to Ashley
Help our
Collective
Societal thinking about this and maybe help us arrive at some answers
You know how can we bring
People back from the edge or
Keep them from
Tipping over in the first place
That's what I was trying to do and I guess by fighting
With people your
Yeah
No you might be able to write a book
Action sequences
But yeah that might not be
Societally is
Yeah
And then I also you know the thing I was always
Obviously
Holding
Close with this idea that
You know these families
Telling me their story
You know they were trusting me
With the worst
Possible
Day of
Fairlife
Slice and
And they were doing it not because
Anything
Having to do with me
They were doing it
Because they wanted
You and all of us
To understand that this was something that
If these folks
Income
For the
Parent of a murdered child
There come
For all of us
And that this is
Societal warning that they're trying to raise
And and you know
I just
That's why I and I know that this is a really hard topic this shooting is is something that'll
A lot of you know
A lot of humans in it
It's a very human reaction to want to look away from it and not
Wanted
Relive those days
Details and where
You were when it happened and how old your own children were
And all of that
But I kind of feel like
We owe it to the families
You know
Walk through that with them and understand what happened afterward because they are trying to
Italian
Story
Well yeah
That's
Agrate
Great thought I thought
I feel like
Doesn't get better than that great plot 222 clothes on
I think there's a lot to say
Think about their yeah we're not going to we're not going to be able to top that one so soon he'll get the best line I think I'll just end it
Call Darrell
I'm so grateful that you guys for having
Beyond and
And for reading a book
And really for
I mean you guys helped me so
Much
Facebook I mean Dan
Just you know
You know so much
About the way Infowars and
Alex Jones operate
And I know you're going to feel embarrassed that I'm
You know giving you but you really deserve so much credit for helping me understand
This guy and and where he's coming from
It's probably good that we we give full disclosure that I did we did speak in the process of you write in the book
I don't want to try it
Hide that that the appoint no not at all
No not at all I mean
You guys helped me alot
To understand do you know
Corner of
Of what
It's and it's a big
Corner believe me
I'm really grateful for you
Using the plural
That's really nice of you
To really include me
Even though you don't have a royal you guys
Well I was I was that I was thrilled to be able to put this information to use cuz I mean
There's a lot of Lionel just like you were talking about with the with Bill Ogden
IMDb.
Watching a ton of
Alex said it's a
Incredibly painful
If you're actually engaging with it and
Looking at a critically
I think going through the process of learning so much about this
If it wasn't
For something that wasn't used for something
Thank you for providing
Something of an outlaw
Oh my gosh yeah I know I just remember all the times thing
Where do you think he was staying when he said this
Or I'm just
Circular date
Or do you have this
Particular video or
You know it was just
You know
If you offered is
To try and understand why this happen
Thank you so much
You're you're quite welcome and think
And thank you people can't find the book everywhere
Right
Where do people get box
Barnes & Noble put it on a website
Download books
That's all I didn't you can get it at the library you can get it at your favorite local bookstore
Wait Talk Dirty Library
Trump kill all libraries
I don't think so only the only his own Presidential Library
Presidential Library
Library
Yeah it did against called Sandy Hook an American Tragedy and the Battle For Truth
Thank you again Elizabeth we appreciate you joining us
Yeah thank you so much
And boats
Really appreciate it
Well folks hope you hope you enjoyed that likes to take a little break
Little break
It's about to get crazy I mean we just doing better today
Well we had Enrique tarrio just got arrested today as we recording these intros
Spirits in charge said also includes Rambo
Believe it was actually just conspiracy to obstruct an official proceeding nice
But in the indictment it does involve
At one point
In an underground parking garage
It's okay alright
Sneaky stuff might be afoot deepthroat there to everybody the whole gang
Calder
That's some crazy stuff may be about to pop off
I am so tonight's nice to just get ready for that incoming barrages
We are we will be back Jordan dealing with that probably
Besides to deal with it. I guess we might talk about the
F****** Convoy in DC this again
For no reason whatsoever I am buddy I'm recording this from the underground parking garage
Clandestine meeting
Sounds great amazingly
Acoustics
Amazing wonderful
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm dzx Clark
Doctor marble
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color