Damn important
I have a great respect for Tenaya Lodge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
The altar of Celine and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
I have a quick question
What's up
Jordan is
I was
Going around
On the Infowars webs
Believe it was
The Bandit
And periodically you'll see some fun advertising
That's on there
And there's a new one
Which I will post a picture of this ad
On Twitter but it's
A picture of Alex doing the Uncle Sam
Going to pick up the camera tax relief get the number one tax
Planning attacks relieved recommended by Alex
You saw that I just like
So great
Half of his career has been talkin about how the 16th Amendment
It doesn't exist it wasn't ratified
Can't be happy
With Infowars branded comply
Really hear about Irwin Schiff if he's running this time
A relief hotline
Joe Bannister
Beckman Murfreesboro f****** old-school weirdos
Leaving Centerpoint. Where it's like
Have you had a personal injury Infowars says go to you know it's a were there
Yeah
That is actually like
I thought I would find that more acceptable people
Vetro haven't spent most of his career railing against like
Have you been busy of personal injury suits or something
You shouldn't believe that I don't want to pay taxes why you having a tax settlement first
My bright spot Dan
Is baseball
Going to happen
Going to do it okay they're going to they're going to have today
They're going to do it nothing great
Maghrib today
2/2
The Baseballs the new play 460 I didn't even know there was a problem with Facebook
Has not been happening for almost 100 days
Isn't that the offseason though yeah but even during the offseason you still do so
You throw the ball Camp none of it
Nobody got paid
Nothing
Is brutal all because the owners were like what if
And I'm
Throw this out there
We could negotiate with the Union
What if we broke
The union beneath our heels in Smash
Their teeth
Grind up
How old are so weak
Power armor
F****** penis
That seems like coming to be more
Yeah and they almost did it
CLA convey in the mix man I hate themselves
Nobody ever in history of the world is the rickets are here ever never there
They're like a tubal
Yeah it's
It's like the reverse of that weatherman
Tom what does negative
Everybody says everything negative about the eclipse
Congratulations on getting your baseball
We have an episode to go over give me jumping around a little bit throughout time and the reason
Is because
By Kurt Vonnegut
Exactly it's these
Spiritual sequel to momento
So
Taylor Green's been making more appearances on Infowars
And I believe this to be
B A troubling
Where else would you find a shrieking harpy
Probably some other places but
Well
Not so much a media Outlet
So yeah we're going to talk a little bit about that but before we do
Let's say hello to
The great idea superstreets Roper's blue comb
Screamin Demon companion thank you so much
Pics of weird I listen to you and I kind of do to thank you so much
Termites
I'm a policy wonk don't you f*** with DJ Danica I'm telling you
Thank you very much
I hear from some people that they
Speed up and listen to the podcast and like
Look there's something about a timing you know like
Really kind of
Comedian it is
Kind of an important thing that we care about is almost unfathomable to me
I guess if you like doing that do you think
Next number one
Thank you so much,
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Bucking horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Come back here again
I apologize to the crew in The Listener jester
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
Tomorrow they're bad
It's definitely
For concern
Repair
The relationship
It's growing between Infowars and Marjorie Taylor Greene
They're becoming a bit more in
French then you might have expect
Did the taste of beer or
I could have predicted
Green appeared on Alex's February 2nd show and we discussed that appearance but
Connor further interaction
Invading Ukraine thing definitely seems like a more relevant topic
Take the cover but now that Alex is kind of settled into his
Very transparent status quo cuz I big booty while pretending he's just looking at all sides
We have an opportunity to go back in
Can fill in some gaps
From things that we missed along the way
Order initial appearance Alex mention that he's excited to meet Marjorie in person and as it turned out
He didn't have to wait all that long
And she ended up making her first in-studio appearance on February 20th
Which is where we're going to begin our episode today
Screen doesn't show up until the 2nd hour
Of this Sunday episode but
If you take the time to listen to the
Beginning of it
You'll notice that Alex's pop story is not one
It looks great in hindsight
Marijuana
Europe
Northeastern Europe
Crane with her soulmate
Foxy War
Between the globalist
Russian
Here's are some of the headlines Russia plants big
Biggest war
19:45 says the British
Globalist
Who knows it might be true
Russian troops receive orders to proceed with Invasion USA
Intelligent shows
The same us intelligence
Kind of brazen wire that Alex is
He specifically casting doubt on assessments
That Russia was going to invade Ukraine is February 20th show
Bad and I think a lot of people would have said similar things
Problem is
Just a few days after this
He decides to put together a compilation of dumb clips
He's pretending he predicted the invasion
Back in August
This is Central to one of Alex's deception
Games
Key to getting what's going on
On February 20th is probably aware that he'd made a prediction that there would be War by February
You swear that he yelling about war being imminent for a while but he also knew that he been saying it was going to be a war with
China
So there's news coming out about the possibility of Russia being involved in a war
At what house is looking for
No
Alex Lopez booty
And hates the United States government took an agency within the US government to save the food
Was going to invade Ukraine
Of course that's not true and now it's a supposed predict prediction isn't even a factor
Doesn't
It doesn't come into his mind
13 actual Invasion calculation
The prediction of war with China dematerialized
Is close enough for him to use
This is what he was talking about the whole time
We hurt we heard how in the
Is compilation he used
The clip from last November where he
Headed out the part where he said that he didn't think Russia was going to invade Ukraine
Here you see that same mentality stealing place on
February
20th
At the core of things Alex's just a mod
He legit Amelia's willing to say whatever feels good to him in the moment he's more than willing to lie about the world and his path
Bass positions
Lanterns a very serious topic
Sex even including the invasion of a country
If there's a chance that doing so will increase his status
And make him a few bucks
Ratatouille sucks
Right right
It is
Important
To remember
Do you know like the noble truths
Like life is supper
That's a really important
What people
Forgot and what God, wasn't even
Really thinking of
Was that if
Life is suffering
You should
Therefore be able to make money off because there's nothing you can do baby
Come on
Also if there's one
Problem with katanas conception
It's the idea that when you die you just
Play a harp
I was so mad whenever I read that
Like I mentioned
Marjorie Taylor Greene the parents here on the show
I want to give a bit of a
Content warning
The generally goes over I would say a lot of
Of this episode
It's going to pop in and out there or not it's not the sole topic
It's going to be covered but
There's a great deal of transfobia that's going to be emanating from Alex and Marjorie Taylor Greene
And I hope that we can
Discuss this into the sensitivity that is appropriate
Nam and is it something that
You do you find
Objectionable
You might want to
TuneIn on Monday
Yeah cuz there might be some stuff
Knock knock
Not so great
I tried to not put anything
And you know that's just
Gross for
Pacheco
It being gross
But
Some things are unavoidable
Yep
So Alex
Starts to introduce Marjorie
And
He gives his normal speed about how like
Celebrities male
Well I could care less about Hollywood stars I could care less about Paula
About anybody but my family and
Other hard-charging
Excited
Down
Before she got
Extremely
Excited to have
MTG
Marjorie Taylor
From Georgia
District
Weather Friday
Greatpeople
Have you good people in Congress
She's probably my favorite
But I tell you
She is just the most
System coming after her
This is so funny Paul is the son of anti-communism royalty and Alex's favorite politician of all time
Who actually come on Alex's dumb show
As someone like Marjorie Taylor Greene gives him a second of attention saw like Rand
Who
Yeah that's
That's very sad
Alex's show over the years
There was at least once at one point the pretense of being about principal on the issues where is the Temps
The hijack people's attention
Do some trolling and then talk about meme s***
How do you Sue at least pretended
Discuss documents
Wheats or sub stack
The people write F don't mean anything
How to set up guest wedding air of seriousness around then whether or not they actually were but people like Webster
Guitar player G Edward Griffin
But it wasn't so long ago that they were replaced by people that Carpe donktum Linda Mike cernovich
Alex Beverly Headley
True depth of the stuff he was saying and covering but
He was earlier career there was at least an expectation that he
At this point the cultural landscape has changed enough
There's no real point in pretending
And now it's good enough just to do the troll s*** and pretend that that is itself Subs
Well I mean
Are you kidding
Say that it's gone downhill
Or you could say that it's
The modern Algonquin Round Table sure so I mean they're The Luminaries
In their individual field
Dorothy Parker she is not Marjorie Taylor Greene
Anyway that brings us to Marjorie Taylor Greene popping onto the show
She's fairly popular witch
Clearly extreme right-wing politics
The only reason with Alex's any interest
She's actually desperate enough for it
She's willing to be on Infowars
There's a pretty good
Good chance that she's going to retake her seat in the 2022 midterm election
Just have to do with the inherent
Advantage of
Incumbency
She's a really f***** up person who's willing to give speeches at Nick Fuentes political
Conference to make regular appearances on Infowars
In the position of being someone with a bit of a
Constituent constituency seal
Well it is true that the GOP is drifted closer to their brand of insanity in the past
In terms of a potential GOP Primary
She's ever up against a really strong candidate who doesn't tolerate with Nazis
Or if she's up against like
The grand
Dragon of the KKK
You know like that she can go I can go
Way to Dolores and everybody's like well why we even bother with her
Is the grand dragon by actually I think you're wrong
If the Grand Dragon of the KKK was in the GOP Primary against her
A third person would win because they would split the vote
Yeah that would be the misogynist racist
And the non misogynism that is under her constituency ceiling
And that would be problems in the GOP candidate would probably
Just get everyone else
And that would be the grand wizard
The two of the Grand Dragon on Grand River
Marjorie a the proceeding
Global Awakening
Against the people and I said
What do you want
On my list
A my list was in this
Synced up
Right now so
Vanoss
Send text message
Studio
I'm so happy to be here with you Alex
Some of the most
Yes I can do so I'm so high
Happy that I'm here
Maybe some exciting interview for her cuz she can just talk s*** in
And speak freely
Other interviewers are probably pushed back on completely insane things you might say but Alex's
Just let that s*** slide and then try and outdo her
Bigotry is on the table stupid conspiracy theories are treated like serious concern
It's much more fun
Been being on CNN for some reason bigoted and really loved stupid conspiracy
You don't have to hold back I know nobody's going to be like
Children to Cthulhu and you'll be like look like I never said that I'll tell Tera Coca
Cthulhu positive conference
Because I didn't know anything really that you say that's a negative
Paddock
It's like you're already on Infowars
What what
Anyway
Marjorie Taylor Greene congress not too long ago
And you might be surprised to learn that she was surprised about something
Call yeah
B l u
For me what I see
And I'm just a regular person I've never been in politics
And going to Washington the most disturbing thing that I
The people in Washington
And it's his tiny little world
If you really look at it
It's a small percentage of people
But they truly look down on the rest of America
And they sing
But everything they
Think in their little bubble
And what they want for our country is
The most important thing
Look down on the common
American man and woman
And they
Don't care if their sodas
Disconnected
Wow that's really profound how the thing that Marjorie learned what you went to Washington is literally the most obvious
Complaint that everyone has about Washington any complaint more obvious
They're not in touch with the Working Man
She's so unlike these cloistered Washington bubble beings and you would think that our legislative history of all kinds of important
Bill's really help the people who she represents
It certainly wouldn't be a bunch of s*** that's essentially just playing Washington politics games and appealing to right-wing media entities
I was going to put this up.
It looks like she's introduced 18 bills in Italian she's been in office
Expelling Maxine Waters from the house and her committee
Didn't go well.
Open Arms about water saying people that stay in the street and protest
Through the Chauvin trial
Play something it's super relevant to the constituents in Georgia's 14th
Whether or not a congressperson from California keeps her committee assignment
That's definitely not just a desperate ploy to ride the wave of right-wing media attention and get a little bit of yourself
I know
Both of them died in
She also introduced for bills
Joe Biden
Do you know they didn't go well
I guess it's a little more relevant to Georgia voters
Georgia is in the United States
Like it's a little much
Maybe looks like she also introduced a number bills are obviously going to die in committee but had names over his perfect for folks in the
Stuff like that
The Wii will not comply Act
Probably got a law that
It's called we will not comply otherwise I can't
In November she introduced the bill HR 6070 which was known as the Kyle
Rittenhouse
Congressional gold medal a
She wanted to give Rittenhouse a congressional gold medal
You know that thing that's been awarded to people like Rosa Parks
Nelson Mandela and Jonas Salk
This seems like something that if I were just regular person living in Rome or Calhoun or Dalton Georgia
Be pretty interested in my representative taking the time to do that
That stuff right
Fight my battles for me
80s like
The people in Washington
I just disconnect
And all they want to do
Is give gold medals to murderer
You know and it's like
I know people think that they're that washing
Is working for them but I swear to you all they want to do is give gold medals
All they want to do is do stuff it's red meat for the right-wing media
They just love it
Define criticism of Congress to say that Congress members are often two in their own world in a bubble but the reality is the Marjorie Taylor
Evergreen is in a bubble to
It's a way worse bubble
It's a bubble where the mechanisms of government really only exist in order to create opportunities to bring yourself more media 10
Nms strengthen your own brand
It's essentially all marjorie's
Been doing since he's got into office
Introducing these meeting with bills that are read me for extreme right-wing media
Going on tour with Mac
Gates speaking at Nick Fuentes event now showing up on Alex's show more than once
The normal Congressional person
Bubble maybe an issue because it does keep them
I'm a bit detached from the larger world
But Marjorie Taylor Greene bubble essentially only has room in it for herself
Which is a big
She's in a bubble
Created by
Delirium from the Sandman
It's like we're at we have to go
Downright mythical
To get to the level of weird-ass bubble sheets
I got really lost their cuz I thought you were saying that like reading the same and Comics gives 1/2 l
The endless
Washington
Care about important things like
Canadian truck
So disconnected
That's why all they want is like war in Ukraine
Instead of even
I'm thinking about
Truckers Who deliver food and supplies
They don't even care about kids wearing masks they don't care about our border with
Fentanyl pouring across
Killing young people and being the number one cause of death
Not covid-19
And it just bothers me so much babe
Play treat me
Some kind of
Happy person
I feel like
People who the guy you're talking to someone who talks about the people having horns
Being a demon
String of words
Meant to appeal to a far-right base but
What's the relationship between any of these thoughts
You can see that there isn't any because right-wing media training is essentially
That cram it into the sentence
It doesn't matter what your sentence is about cram a little aside in there that's like
And Democrats kill everybody so that then then get to gas prices
I guess is up by 5
Kind of like a
Poorly executed debate
Strategy to make a bunch of points
As quick as you can it's just this.
Also fentanyl is absolutely not the number one cause of death
Summer Country
Even with covid that owner still ghost
Heart disease
The cancer coming
And second
In 2020 700,000 people died
Yeah it's
Names of the number one cause of death of Americans aged 18 to 45
Which is a problem but ultimately she doesn't have a solution
Or the Border or something
If you wanted to make a concrete difference in this area she would support safe access to drug sampling and test strips
So people can know if the drugs that they're using contain Fenton
This would be ultimately unacceptable to someone like Marjorie though because it would be tacitly accepting the reality that some
People do drugs
You can't have that
Same thing with like safe needle programs in the right-wing opposition to that s***
Okay so you think this is
You think this is a bad idea
We never tried to limit the supply of drugs
Is coming in
Because
If you limit the supply then people won't get it
So all you have to do is close up those borders
And there's no way
That drugs will find their way into this country
It's just like
Whenever we prohibited alcohol
Nobody got alcohol into this country not one-time totally worth it was a 100% effective
I don't know why anybody stopping terrible idea
Alex Alex
Do you recall from Alex's shirt
Of the presidents
Yeah one of the things that was glaring at it was it for some reason Teddy Roosevelt
At 8
But nondescript
Non-random
Call Bland face
He had his own caricature all those in the wrong place in the order
Is definitely supposed to be Teddy
That's because of Alex's favorite speech
The man in the arena speech
Alex
The highest honor bombardment Evergreen Arena
Congress
Winning by record number
Attacked being
The woman in the arena.
Roosevelt
What is that process
In the last three years is
Stronger.
The Roosevelt speech was about the man in the arena and it's very specifically not about the woman
The arena
Literally or metaphorically
Teddy Roosevelt president from 1901 to 1909
Adele 1920
The ratification of the 19th amend
The first woman was elected to congress in 1960
Hey Rebecca Felton was the first woman in the senate in 1922
But she was appointed to fill a vacancy and only serve for one day because she was installed as a PR move on the part of the governor
Who is running in the upcoming senate election
I didn't want to appoint somebody to fill the vacant
But he might lose against
Supremacist
She's remembered as the last slave owner to be in the Senate so that sucks
Yep
I set up to talk about one depressing thing and it turns out we found another
Teddy Roosevelt would come out in favor of women's suffrage in 1912 but the speech that Alex is referring to is 419
Team 10
So the little incongruous
Betty White
You know
There's some deep
Deep lessons
That you learn
Way to go into
Dan Marjorie has the opposite
When I got there
This is what they told me
Marjorie
That's not how we do things
You see they wanted me to come there they want all the new members of Congress to come
And talk about that
Talk about
Decide taking lunch
Well it just comes gradually
Play from different people
So they have their committees everything
Setup on committees
And what you have to do is you have to
The chairman or the leaders of the Committees
Want you to vote
And that's how you're being a team player and
That's how you're doing the right
And if you're not doing that then they want to minimize you they want
They do not want your bills or your your voice to be
You know
You're saying it's not just the Democrats doing this it's a republic
Percent
Alex and Marjorie legitimately sound like children having this conversation really surprised that political parties have
A vested interest in
Corralling the votes of elected representatives within their parties
I started a new job
And this guy
This guy he was like
You have to do what I say
Less Direct than
The boss but
The coalition
Is it is it really something that they're going to present to the conspiracy here that political parties derive their power for being able to vote Isabel
That's essentially how
Democracy works
Honestly this is painful to listen to not only because it's stupid but because it revealed a shocking level of despain.
Marjorie have
For the people who are listen
What Marjory is describing is
Strongarm tactics
Some kind of a weird conspiracy within Washington
Caucus
Martyrs actual
Complaint is it she didn't have the political Capital to
The dictate the direction of the
The party in her first term in office
It's really an expression of narcissism and entitlement being disguised as some kind of complaint
About Party politics
If you have a problem with the gop's use more than welcome to leave the party and become an independent and then she won't have to get all the s*** that
But she might get if she doesn't want to vote with the party on some important vote
You can't do that though because the GOP is a very powerful
Fundraising machine
And without that are next door name
Should be essentially f***** in any election in odisha
Especially if I fundraising
Machine where to go behind one of her opponents
What do you hear March
Greek gyros essentially impetus
Because she doesn't understand how to make things work in government
She's not willing to
To figure it out
Why would you what doing
This kind of b******* then do doing media spectacles
Is clearly more profitable for you than cover
Governing is hard
Using your power and your elected influence
To make money for yourself
Is astonishingly easy
You can guide me she's already made a s*** ton of money at the stock market just because she knows it that she's not
I don't know that to be true but I'll take your word erupt
Well I was looking at her primary race in in Georgia
Adidas discrepancy
Between her fundraising and her neck
Closest
Big guy
Weird weird
Weird weird weird
Looks like there's a correlation between how much money you have and then How likely you are to win
And also being part of the political party
Get lens you a little bit more
Credibility
And such With Envy the fundraising
Apparatus
No and you have a lot more resource
You can hear her literally being like
Ignoring the fact that yes that's why you're part of the Republican Party
Just being like me
I shouldn't have to
To make trade-offs
Nice to get everything I want I want your money I want your power I want your influence and
I want to do whatever the f*** I want to do and you not to Quest
I want to be able to reject
Whatever you bring to the table that I don't want and I walked
To be able to insist
You backup everything I want
To do
All right fine that is an adult
Great if that's really what
How you model or that's what you want
Meant to be great
It's on it's counterproductive
Obviously you wouldn't
She is
Otherwise you sound like a child
Yes
Take a civics class
Anything tonight
Be
Forced to accept publicly the
Rampant narcissism
What's behind your belly
Interesting question that comes up
From Alex
Hey Marjorie
Who's Maury
Alexandria ocasio-cortez
Call Mitch McConnell
At such a difficult question for Marjorie Taylor Greene
Who's more evil
Simone biles
Flies first class
Thousand-dollar outfit
What's his hard-working mom
Verdad
Is she mad because she admits
Or is somebody like me
Mitch McConnell
Cuz he claims he's with us
Well there's a big
Comparison there I would say ayo
I see is death
Definitely
She's a she's again
Start
Can Waze
He's honest about it that she'll tell you
Where is Mitcham
McConnell he lies to you
He says he's a republic
Like an he's the leader in the Senate
Of the Republican Party
Everybody's married to Elaine Chao
Call record on record
Wow
Second this is really interesting thing for Marjorie to be doing because
In some ways
Kind of behavior is only really going to drive a further wedge between her and the party
You seem so frustrated that she isn't in control of
The kind of seems counterproductive because it's Grandma's things may seem
The odds are enough completely insane people like her getting voted into the house to make a coalition
The chica
You know used to
Getsway it's
Kind of low
Being able to actually work together also
Incredibly low
TCU the crazy kook correlation and then you'd be like wait a second that could be cake
KK and then you like all I get it
And then they're just trolling you they make $1000000
I want to die 2021 green tried to start the America First caucus
Yes but was only able to bring him Paul gosar Matt gaetz and Louis going
Immediately after announcing the faction the GOP leadership Express their strong disapproval of it and the group disbanded
Most likely because people like Louie gohmert knows where his bread is buttered
Surgery is a little too obvious what they're actually for want to sign up for that
Speaking of making things to offer
CVS on their policy platform statement the America First caucus had a section about immigration
Little bit too
Domino's
They kept referring to people as quote
19 6
55 Emigrant
Which is a dog whistles white nationalist to believe that the Hart Celler Act passed in 1965
Was Anna Faris blocked
Diminish the white population
In the country
By stealthily bringing in non-white immigrants I mean
Just really putting those
Specifics down on
Paper for pee
People like Marjorie of big ideas but unfortunately
Timcast awesome
I can't really help but wait
So they're big at audience in their statements
The beliefs
The whole thing doesn't work
Naturally Marjorie Potenza
How to position paper
She took her shot and fail
Because the accumulation of political power when you want to work within and without the established party hierarchy
Complicated
It takes Precision Tools
She's just a jackass
Destroying anything she tries to create
Outside of publicity
Those
You don't need a soft touch for
You need to yell
She could do that fine
It's not hard
No
Mitch McConnell's wife
I'm not sure if she and Mitch are on the Chinese payroll
Metal how much of that is being said by Marjorie just because
Travis Chinese
X100pre
I suspect that
In reality child's family owns a shipping company
Does business in China called
Though she's not formally connected to the company they stood to gain from foreign policy decisions
The Trump could make
Let's not forget the truck named Charlie Secretary of Transportation
That seems almost
If you don't want to touch that part of it because then it looks bad for Trump
So this seems like a case of racism intersecting with some good old-fashioned
Corruption
Depicted as proof that someone is a spy for
A China
Actually is a Chinese spy
A real idiot for making a part of his cabinet
Sherwood
That's not impact that though cuz this isn't a realization
It's mostly just
Racism
Easy to be racist in it
Mitch McConnell doesn't care
Probably not
What are you talkin about
McConnell
Is s*** in the world
But the reality is
Marjorie
Believes in the p
Much like a Dusty Rhodes
People drive me
I don't like that
I don't like that I sent back
You know sometimes I wonder is that too late
But I don't think
So hold on to hope
Constantly
Because I do believe in the mirror the American people
I believe in you
I know you're for real I know your voting records
So we'll get to the greens boating I could but I wanted to bring up something I didn't realize until I was poking around about Marjorie for this episode
Did you know that between May 2021 and January 2020
Marjorie was find at least 34 times for not wearing a mask in the house chamber
I knew she was find a s*** ton
Did not know is that many times you believe you can find it
At least $78,000 for not wearing a mask over
With the course of about 27 months
That's approximately three times the per capita annual
Income for people in her home District Georgia's 14
What an amazingly childish a****** luckily the good news is
Either one no one will ever come to collect it or two it will come out of the
Taxpayers
Second one 100%
Gun to his head Alex
Couldn't come up with a single vote Marjorie is cast
He has no idea what a record is like outside of a record of making
Inflammatory public state
My son he likes those
Do you remember that time she voted yes
I remember that one
I was going over to record American Adventures
Everything points to come up
The first of the
Didn't vote against
The gop's
Position then dinner time in Congress so far
24.2% of the time
Ben-Hur the third most frequent person in the house
Going against their party
That makes some sense
But was really wild
Is that if you look at the list
The top 41 of them are all Republicans
Of course
It says
There's chaos in the house for the Republic
I mean they all agree on the big things
It's like telling people who disagree with them
And then that causes
The problems cuz on the inside they disagree with each
So it's like
The God I have a constant stream of people that hate outside of their otherwise like
We just shut off.
TV around the Senate
April like 2 weeks
There would be 22 Republican Senate
They would have just eating each other
N6 new political party
Medicaid
Amputees
I was I was pretty shocked at that that
That lack of
Sort of Coalition management
People in the house
But the highest percentage of voting against their party line
All Republic
Nuts I realized that I'd get into her voting record by realize WhatsApp
I wasn't gonna break up
Pacific
Who cares
Not at all one of her votes has mattered about any
A large part of this interview is
Iraq transphobe
It's pretty bad
Pretty pretty
All around
Introduces this next segment here just
Reading off a laundry list
Deceptive and misrepresented
Headlines that he's using for the sake
Of spreading
Transphobic narratives
Santa it gets to this clip which is
Is bruised pretty bad
Fiji is here
Weather
Oh I think
Make it straight
First off
If I was a parent and my
Had to had to sleep
Shower in some kind of
At some summer
Camp that I paid money to send my child to
And there was a man calling himself a
A woman sleeping in her cabin
Showering with her at that guy with
He be in jail
He would be in jail will first off my husband what Abby
Beat him into the ground
And then he be in jail
But this is exactly how we need
To stand up against this stuff
So one thing that's pretty important to point out here is the story that Marjorie is talking about involved absolutely no wrongdoing
No child was hurt or anything
The entire issue is that one of the counselors at a science camp
That's a fifth graders went to
Was non-binary
And use they them pronouns
Business to do with a 5th grade students from Los Alamitos
Is any of the people who participated in Outrage ramps like Marjorie
Took the time to look into this at all
They can learn a little bit more about this camp and realize that it's
More or less a luxury camping
Set up
When they say that the kids stayed in the cabin with the counselors
It's meant to evoke the idea that they're staying in like
His tiny Shack
Big buildings
That has 10 students in bunk beds
And have separate rooms at the counselor stay in
Also eats cabin his 223 private bathrooms and showers
There's no communal shower and going on here at all
Of course
Everything I can tell this started as a local news report from KTLA about two parents who are bad
Debbie School District didn't tell them that someone who worked at the
The camp that their children were sent to
Was non-binary
And if they'd known they wouldn't have sent their chill
From everything I can tell no other parents were upset and I can't find a bunch of other complaints from other parents
Golden to this camp
Kick-off a right-wing media campaign
Skip
The fact that everything was fine at the camp and no child is mistreated leads
Folks having to show their cards
It's a little bit too clearly on this one
Nothing happened
But tomorrow jury the mere existence of a nonbinary person in proximity to Children is a threat
Do that child
Because she believes the trans and non-binary people are in
Inherently dangerous to children
In the same way that the right-wing Media made that argument over gay people in the 80s
Are black people decades
Doing the same game
Over again
Disgusting every time
Also Marjorie needs to be way more
Careful with her language
I have no idea how intentional what she said was but at the end of that clip if you
You just take her words in the context of how she set them
She's advocating for committing acts of violence
Against trans and non-binary people
He's pretending that it's about people sleeping or showering with these two
But in the case she's talking about
That didn't
Happened
The story she's basing her outrage on is just that a nonbinary person was employed
That's the long and short of it
Is if these people acting the way that they never have
Never will
And frankly wouldn't make any sense at all for anyone
Then I think we should commit violence against
Won't
Can't and never will should not stop us from continuing to commit violence against
It's just
It's just a boring
Becomes kind of
Amane sticking
Throughout
Some of the stuff that we're going to be talking about today this this case of that
And it's just all around.
But of course this leads to a conversation about trans people in sports
Cosgray
Here we go with that rate
And then the men
This guy
Lea Lea Thompson I'm sorry that
That's William
And he's not ashy he's a he
He should not be
Women's swim
He did not win whoever came in
Second place
The real girl in the race
He should be
Thrown out
Swimming completely
And I do not care about it shouldn't matter about what they do in their bedroom if they want to wear a dress
But what they're doing is they are defeating women
It's about beating women.
That stands up for it and
America needs
Most Americans agree that this is
Ridiculous and I don't know why
Goes along with the whole pronoun
He's in the season that she's in whatever
These are men
We need to call him what they are there men
Makes them and he
And not play the pronoun game anymore
And 16
Easy place for people like Alex and Marjorie to hide their hair
Bigotry coming from a place other than what it is
Which is just
I've never once on his show or any like it the conversation about transmitted
Abita men's sports
Cuz it doesn't work for the narrative that they're trying to use it this mask to cover on the same page
Discussion about unsuccessful trans women athletes because
Again that cuts the opposite direction
Albania be image
To look for their propaganda to work
If you knew that there are plenty of successful transman athletes competing in men's sports and that many trans women athletes or either just
That's okay or
Not very dominant in their sport
Complicate the issue to the point where people like Alex and Marjorie couldn't
Use it anymore
Just ignore the other side of the story
I want to put a fine point on this
In the way that I mean to be very emphatic
What Marjorie Taylor Greene is doing here isn't making a political statement about trans athletes or anything like it
He's categorically dismissing the validity of Dreams people's exist
Very least she's producing being trans to being a pure purely sexual thing by saying things like whatever you do in your bedroom
This is an unacceptable level of ignorance for a person who's an elected official to have it
It's particularly relevant for someone like Marjorie because she represents a district in Georgia
Which happens to be the state
With the fourth highest percentage of the population identified as Transit
Very relevant
Constituency
Probably
Leo lot more so then whether or not
Kyle Rittenhouse gets a gold star from Conger
Yeah this is this is actually a very destructive thing
For her being able to represent
The people of Hurst
Guide mean
You know
It is
It is such that
She
It's a club
And it is
F****** discuss
That it's it's just like what
How
How why what
And it's just
Like she just gets
Personal satisfaction
That's it
You know
Like really at the end of the day
She gets nothing more than
The personal satisfaction
Of having herpes
Because she can get money out of it but she could get money in and any other difference
You know you don't have to go to Congress
To get money
And frankly you don't have to go to Congress today
Get money for doing that
It's just that she
F****** hate
People and then everybody gets so happy for like wow you're so great
Hating people
People I think I think a part of it too is signaling to the the folks
Set of accumulating power which is
Engaging in the
The communal demonization of
The Chosen victim
Or the Devon herbal group that
Bedside the rest of your
Group is ostracized
And I think that she
She gets something out of that it being part of
Signaling
And make very concrete that she is part of this
In group
That is doing the
The Hating of this vulnerable
Also Alex
Had some old talking points he wants to leave back in
And now that's
It's just grass
Women's
And children
Free time
The Big Show
Batman
Clown outfit is a woman
Sorry
Not a woman
This is all
Very very
Sexualization
Little kids
Who had no
G-strings
Glitter on their genitals
And hugging little kids
Naked men
This is four years ago in Austin
Make naked men
Literally
Grabbing show
No that's
Get here
I can't even understand that
But most drag queens aren't trans
Performance art doesn't really correlate with someone's gender identity
How to do some talking points that are way past their expiration
Stop
I also that video that Alex's describing doesn't
I've seen the video that he claims the pics that
Absolutely not what
Describing
Alex is lying to a member of Congress in an attempt to make them even more radically anti-trans than they already are
Which is
Man you know
It's like how did we get
The other day
I saw my neighbor
She put
A frog
Holdrege
Cauldron
3 Doors Down
Immediately felt at Walmart
Her fault entirely how did we get here
It's unfathomable
You know what we got to
All of the f****** rules
Yeah
I think that's why I hate
I hate this
The contact
But
There's something about it
That I think is
It would be negligent
If we didn't bring it up
Inasmuch as
This is a sitting member
Congress
That is actively engaging in this
With Alex
And
It's bad man
Got no a member of Congress is engaging in stochastic terrorism in order to
To get trans youth killed
So
Yeah I would say that's the
I can't
Express
How infantile even these these thoughts
The cheese bring to the table are
This is such perversion
But it's also grooming children it's grooming them to believe things that are lies
And there
Completely wrong
No children are not born a certain way
Thinking there another gender it's there
Parents that are training them that way
It seems mother said
I think it's like a handbag
They need to have a boy
A girl and a trans child
Because if there's some kind of
Hollywood
Stars
Exactly
What do you what
Why did Alex stop himself when he was he was clearly saying the status symbol
Clearly what he was
Yeah about to say
And then changed it to like
What Hollywood stars do which I assume he means like
Paris Hilton having a dog in her purse or something
Kids are possibility
I suppose
Either either are possible but this is a grotesque
Perspective
So she also has some complaints
About
People not
Stop it
This
Or something
I don't really
This is just
Just awful
Yeah now it's really disturbing but here's what bothers me the most
Is
So many good men
They won't
Say anything
Stand up and protect
We want men to real man to stand up and say
We're not going to allow you in our daughter's bathroom
We are going to allow you in our girls cabins at
We are going to allow you to be
Down our women and our daughters
But we need the UFC or other.
Literally
2 open trans women who competed in MMA professional
There was Fallon Fox who retired in 2014 and Alana McLaughlin professional fights
So far not for the UFC before combat global
Not a silence B for UFC fights
Most of them were with the championship Fighting Alliance
That is to say that there is not been
A trans woman fighter
Competing in the UFC
Right but that doesn't mean that they haven't been killed
Well I think that I was just lying about how in her last fight before retiring Fallon talks did break her opponent's
Skull in the ring
And then he's complaining that with it a 2019 story about the CEDA elata
Who was a woman fighter in the UK
Who competed in the fast
Furious fight series
How late is a brain injury
Text day
Her opponent Jamie Morgan is a cyst woman
How to combining these things in making up details in order to suit his purposes because this is a trans
Episode he's got going on here with Marjorie Taylor Greene
And
Why not
Pretend
That
Hey listen
If the enemy
That you want isn't doing the thing that you need them
To do in order to make them your enemy
Just say they are
So
Jump off this this subject
There's more than it said that is
Dear God Dax
Unacceptable
Open the
Exact same thing
Play more would really kind of tend to be
I think it might feel like wallowing around in like them being awful
For the sake of
Demonstrating the awfulness
That's right
Will jump 22 this where we get back
2 Civic
And at our lack of understanding
Someone's like 100
But here's something that a lot of people don't understand about
So most of the bills that get passed
Our path
By Voice vote
That is until this year
And you know everyone remembers the story of me being kicked off
Committees
Not that big of a deal because
Democrats are in control and Republicans can't really do much on committees anyways when the Democrats
Control
Because that means you know what that means swamp
Exactly who I
They knew that I wasn't going to hand over my
Well nobody wants you looking at the legislation incompatible with getting anything done
The the consequences is virtue it's just
Stop
Do you know that you know that you're on the right track when everyone
Does not like you
Imagine looking apply that thinking to Osama bin Laden
Yeah
I mean nobody gets more right
All sorts of
Negative figures everybody hated Hitler
Everybody
Some of the people who are on Alex's Network might actually
I think that might be it might actually believe
Marjorie after she lost these committee assignments it don't really matter and it's a badge of honor that you lost them
Begin with I mean in her defense
EXO
I will say that
When everybody in the GOP kicked her out those committees
Is there has been like
We are not here for this
So we can use her
This is not what
Start time for someone like this
But unfortunately
What do you got understand is when you try to use
Somebody like this to play a role
They will end up attacking you
The chair
Recognizes the congresswoman from Georgia
The weapon the weapon will be turned on you
The very quick
She lost this committee assignment you know what
Cited meaning should learn how this year government
Works
Is Abdul still builds
And so when I lost my committee's ice
Sitting on the house
The story
I started sitting on the house floor and what I wanted to do
Is Lauren Dupree
And so I started watching them.
The Bells
Back and forth
And they would
The person in the chair
Speaker Pelosi
She would or he whoever it was with a man
I had no idea but it usually wasn't Nancy
They would ask
The Voice vote
And so on
They debated the bill the Democrats
Say yay and then the Republicans on our side
Woodside
And then the person
Sitting there in the sky
The speaker share with the gavel
Say the bill passed
And like 10 members of Congress
Would have voted
Insane yes or no
I'm not kidding you
And so what I started doing as I started using floor procedure
And I started
Call boats
So they would debate
The bill back and forth
And then this
Person in the chair
A speaker mask
For whoever it is
With
The Voice vote
And before the bellapass
Speaker II
The recorded vote
Well that means that all members of Congress had to come in and ask
Do you see we have a voting card
And worse
Supposed to use that it's
Supposed to be an electronic vote
And it should record all of our boats whether it's yes or no
And so I would
Would put my
We are
Are supposed to put our card
In there
Push yes no
Vanna White is present
Either yes or no
And you should know
Weather Fresno fence February the house Freedom caucus
It's joined in with me
We have over five
500 bill
They're on record
But you can actually look up
Any member of Congress you can look up their vote
And even CD
Did they even show up for work that day today
Actually boat
Did they vote Yes did they vote no
Is there doing it not just a minute
That is exactly what I'm telling you
I mean Ori one could argue that it's a
F****** Mass
Massive government
Stroke and all of these things are negotiated for months in advance
Time to learn about what it means to be a member of the House of Representatives
Is when you're they or anybody
Take off your committees
Yeah the time to get down to brass tacks and figure out what you're supposed to be doing
Marjorie's are real idiot but I guess in the long run on this one who cares
Vote on every measure with call votes because there's so many members that body that if they were going to do it
Forever and essentially nothing would ever get done
Conversely with
Just 100 members the Senate traditionally does do roll call vote
Formosa orders Abyss
The way things work is that bills are measures a resolution that are most likely to pass or fail or put up to a Voice vote
And then it's
It's decided by the
People's men call for a rule called
So someone can test
The vote that can be looked at more closely in the house
Laborious process
What Marjorie is discussing doing
Could have been a problem in earlier days but at this point it's
More lights just an annoyance
About yay or nay
Also
You can go to congress's website and look at the list of roll-call vote in previous session
Samba Congress
And honestly it doesn't appear that there any more or less of them since Marjorie started doing this
Princeton silver 449 roll-call do to the first session of the press
Congress compared to
705 in the first session of the 114th Congress
Which was in 2015
You can find the voting records for folks in the house
Spectre
She's making an impact
I really don't think Marjorie is having an impact at all these especially not the way she thinks
She is part of that has to be Deuter clear ignorance of how government works as evidence
Bewilderment at the idea of a Voice vote by the idea of
People voting present
This indicates that she doesn't understand the bodies of
The Congress and now they need a quorum to carryout business legally
So if you don't want to take a side but you also want to make sure the vote can happen legally
Foolishness to vote present
Yeah there's other
He'll be done in a caseworker
Congress member has a conflict of interest
So they can't vote one way or the other
If they were to I cannot vote and it leads to a core I'm not being there that
Effects could be
Them working in which F-150
There's a number of reasons why on my phone
Basic things before they decide to run for Congress but when it's all about attention and just yelling
Why would you
Why would you care about how to effectively do the job
You're asking people
A public elect you to do
It's disgust
It really is kind
Astonishing
About that
I think back about my
Civics education in school and it's like
Yeah I can
Can see somebody
Who at just has my Civics education from school not like learning anything outside
Going to Congress and being like this isn't how it's supposed to work
Yes I can
Well maybe we should spend more time teaching people how our own f****** government works or or people who want to run
Should have to take a
The clubface
There should be
I don't want it to be like a ridiculous
Bar of Entry I mean obviously
That would work against people who are working people don't need that
In terms of the time commitment that it would take in order to
Like
Can you create an aerostat aerostatic ruling class
Already have
I just I I find I find it to be really difficult
Think how
Can function
If people like Marjorie you have no idea how any of this stuff work
Yeah
The people who get elected
It's it's a it's a
Electing a stick
Do a wheel conference
That works
No
But it is it is so counterproductive
Cuz she thinks and these Dum Dums think
But if they go in there and they like disrupted
The process
Right we'll give them more power and bring more attention to the sub
When in reality when you go in there and you obstruct
The process
That only makes people who have any actual power
Go as far away from this b******* as they can in order to do things in those secret back rooms that you hate so much
Obviously we're living in a point where the Democrats are in control of the house
I am fighting
Is president
And so the people who may be wield more of the centralized power within the Republican Party
Obviously don't mind someone who's just
Meaninglessly obstruction
Oh yeah yeah
Trying to not get anything done
Hooray
Your hero
Anybody else comes into office the house
Flip Republican
All of a sudden they try to push an agenda through
She becomes
The problem or Republican
Suddenly the
Chip is a little bit different and your antics
Anyway you got to give her some money
Coming after you like
Need you to win with a record level or they could
Remove you from Congress
When you're such an important
Person
Donate
2mt
Fiji Water really appreciate you asking that
The coast.com
Supported by Regular People
I don't take money from lobbyists or pack
Ntg4 america.com
Cloud
Here's some of the donors that Marjorie has gotten money from this cycle
Breaker on regular regular people
First event so that probably.
Broadway
On Google
Money from the house Freedom fund
And the Freedom First political action
Both are regular
We consider marjorie's larger record
In 2021
She probably broke house rules when she appeared in an ad soliciting donations for a group called The stop socialism
The issue was the candidates and elected officials can solicit donations larger than $5,000 but people can give an unlimited amount
Faxed
So this was a super unethical thing for her to do
The systems already on ethical like the fundamental system is already on ethical at a certain point
Even the Republicans are like Jesus Christ
It's already yours scam
Not only that though at the end of last year when Marjorie is going on tour with Matt gaetz
It's part of that was Italy
Organization deep put America First pack
I completely fell apart because they spent all their money they raised on a tour with
Go to the Boston then the pack ended up centrally broke
No problem with
Incredibly Shady campaign-finance stuff is all bulshit
It's that virtue signaling if I ever side
It's also like if you understand the funding different
Between her and her next
Closest
I think it's Jennifer Strahan is the
Did the other person running who's closer
Sister her it's comical
The gap between them
There's no reason anybody analysis audience should be sending her body
Even if they believe in
While it's redic
This is a
Totalscan
Anyway she has an idea though
To me you know that
About the Civil War in the GOP will I fully embrace it
Because I believe that
Iron sharpens iron
And we need to be the GOP conference actual
Something for a change
Instead of talking
Easy I think Republicans have a job to do and that is to job
We need to be the American party
Not left or right
The American party
So fun how these do Wanna Party that's the American party
I will say that it happens have literally all of the positions that are miles
To the right of the current GOP
It's not about left or right
It's about America where the people who when we go to government we don't know anything about how it works
We don't
No
We'd know
Nothing let's make a party
Is the last Refuge of the scoundrel but there's an addendum to that
Early refuge for really lazy con artist
That's what's going on
How do I say that's about as much as their reasoning February 20th episode
I will say that I say
Think of the most relevant element of this is like
I know that Marjorie was awful
No that she wasn't of this ill-equipped
When I heard her talk about being surprised by the idea of Voice vote
They're not knowing why people vote present
Was trouble
That's that's a problem
I'm at a larger problem obviously is
The willingness to be so explicitly and disgustingly transphobic
Score
A benign story
But nothing happened at teachers
0 event
That features only the existence it might as well have been like a
Dad
I went to a God camp
When I was younger
Right
I kind of story I wear were people there from mission trip with Kaylee
And like
Make people shower together
Because I was uncomfortable with it and I was made fun of for it right
And while we were in the
Bunks like one of the dudes who is
ICarly derf
College dudes running around naked
Coolers with a towel
Classic
Cisgender good behavior that no Parenthood objective I told that story
Other people who went to like Kristen campson
Dates never like
I can't believe that happened
I went naked around noon ziplining with a f****** Christian band All In
In their 20s
Who were Camp counselors and they
They grabbed me out of bed at like 2 in the morning
To go take me to zipline
No one had a problem with it
And those are not okay things that happened
Definitely more problematic than the story that Marjorie and Alex
We're responding to Ryan made
A Transformer
Oh yeah I know know if any one of those band members was a vape
Then it would have been a problem maybe not them though
Well it wasn't the hot issue for the GOP at that point
Cab if they were they
It would have been tried
Find
So
While she was in Austin
Alex and Marjorie Buckley went to dinner
And they released a little 6-minute video
Of him interviewing her I guess about how Nancy Pelosi doesn't wear masks enough
It's a little dumb and honestly there's a feeling of a couple people drinking and then one of them grabbing the camera
Say that thing you said so I can record it
It's very clunky
It's a 6-minute video but actually only 2 minutes or Alex talking to Marjorie
The other two
Two-thirds of the video is a compilation of people like
Joe Rogan and Tim pool talking about how right Alex is about everything wow
As if Alex has every reason to assume that having Marjorie Taylor Greene in this video is going to draw eyes to it
So while he has people's attention to me
Goal is really to make sure that people know that idiots like Joe and Tim like him
Pretty bizarre
Also Marjorie says that she's going to be starting a podcast
And that it's hard
Possible impressions videos
Convey
One is that a podcast has to be done through Infowars
The other
Is that Alex desperately wants
To give that impression too though it's not true
I have no idea but I would caution Marjorie against
This plan
Actually doesn't seem to have much to say and I think
She did a podcast with over it
Expose her I don't know how much of an actual committed audio
She has
You have to factor in the reality that most of her audience is probably been outside the normal podcast audience demographics
And younger people who support her
I don't like Nick Fuentes followers
They look at her is just a useful tool to bring their white identity ideology closer to the mainstream they're not somebody who they would take
Take the time to listen
To that very sad moment when she is like
What do you mean I'm not a puppet I'm a real boy and they're like oh
That's nice
You enjoyed our piyo think we like you
Ruffling their hair
Also dumb was Marjorie showing up on the War Room to chat with Owen
Some other dumb things happened over the next days
Last bit
Ananda present-day The Washington Post story came out there
Someone apart thousand dollars
Was the worst mistake in American history
Really wanting to get out of town fast after things
Stopped off at the Capitol on January 6th
Really wild that he would want to do that
Probably just him throwing a temper tantrum because Trump pardon
Steve Bannon
I'm selling a parking tickets just good old-fashioned Rodger Stone corruption
Play Rodger is decided
The claim that those videos are deepfakes
Play by the North Korean
Annabelle
Disrupt
Yeah King of the Heavenly features of Rodger
Is really dumb but I guess it's good enough for the importers audience
I don't particularly care about what Rodger has
How to say anymore if I'm being totally honest
Tim's really clear to me that the walls
They're closing in around him and that he's going to be increasingly increasingly combative until eventually goes back to
The jail
Really disconcerting how many different groups are there were involved in planning to Riot on January 6th and he was
Directly involved
I think I saw the Riddler in even more about in the future
Yeah Joshua James remember who pled guilty to seditious
A ain't guess what he was providing security for Rodger Stone on January 5th
Along with dirt roads.
Team leader for January 6th Michael Symon
I bet he heard them talking that Rodger was working really closely and even directly with Allie Alexander
Durant stop the steal stuff
I got a permit to hold
What's on the capitol grounds under false pretenses
Doesn't sound like a problem at all
The proud boys
Leadership which just got a wreck
Texas bid on conspiracy charges
Related to January 6th and if you read their indictment
It's super clear they plan to storm the capital well in advance
What does deep connection
Well-documented plants do what they did on the six
But yeah
My really weird yeah Rodger isn't super guilty
I hear he has some real serious explaining and soul-searching to do but how he's mixed up with all these people are planning to try
Overthrow the government
No idea
We're up to
I'm looking forward to the moment in court where the defense lawyer is like
I would like to remind everybody we have a presumption of innocence in this country and then everybody in court laugh
Come on man
Rodger came around to whine about this article on the post and then try to get the audience to give him more money
Scrap mechanic
Help somebody pee pee
Marjorie was in person with Alex on February
That's because she
She come to town to support Christian Collins
The GOP Primary for Texas 8th District
I also present
They were coming in to support this Collins guy in the primary
And on March 1st Collins loss
Morgan Luttrell
We got 52.2% of the vote to Collins's 22
Doesn't seem like right there
Don't seem like the
Combined powers of Mike Lindell, Florida and Marjorie Taylor Greene
Can over overcome a
30 point loss I mean it's tough when you're behind that far
Okay
That far behind because of a k Munoz
Why would they come
The 22 rally for someone who isn't that far behind
You wouldn't do that
No
I think it was close to be the most Greenwood has no stomach in the world
Thursday
Isabella bunny
You don't want you don't want to go in like like I'm headlining a rally
Tragic losses
Then on February 25th
Green was off to Orlando where she spoke at Nick Fuentes is pseudo Klan rally and then it's c-pack the next day
People were a bit shocked in disillusion by the depths of
Ethiopia
Totally fine with somebody associating with somebody who started a propos
Ain't saying the n word one day
Remember being welcomed at the biggest GOP event of the year the neck
This helped to give a little bit more attention to the profoundly hateful things
Is the Greenwood said on Infowars a week prior to this
There were a few articles about written about her appearance and
It's probably apply
Add support for violence against trans people
What group is doing this kind of situation is double.
They recognize that there's a tension in them thar Hills and they get to mining for it immediately
Runs largely on
Something the best way to keep that outrage and attention pipeline open is
Do more of the things that made people angry
Conversely an elected official really as a responsibility
To carry themselves
So naturally Marjorie decided to double back on out to show on Tuesday March 8th
Which is now what we will
I'll be getting in
Be mad at her what is she going to lose her election what do you got
So just to check in here Alex on March 8th is continuing his
Boy I love poop butt
I got to say that I see both sides
Finding Russian position but I understand
Well-known
But doing this would make Russian
Just say
But you're not going to bring
Ukraine
Hi Joanne.
I will not invade
GameStop
Sabotage
In the South area
The Russia and
That they overthrew Ukraine
Stop meddling around in this area that we've seized from you illegally and also
Say that you're not going to let Ukraine into NATO which
ACTA mean
Germany's chancellor
Say that prior Terry specifically eyes
To keep them from abated
Yes I mean like this is all the
Just b******* you just telling the Food Lion
I do like
How it's a warrant
You know it's not
If you do these things I will invade and murder a lot of people
For fun
And in trash
That's a warning
Definitely not a threat
So it becomes a good guy he was just warning people
He was just like take watch out there's a car coming and I'm driving it and I'm going to drive through your body
Crossword
So we have two big news that Alex is going to go on a little break again
Schedule right now
To California next week
Really big podcast
Meaning something
Guardian of the Galaxy
Things are so dangerous
Not go
The situation is
Titusville
User user user
My guess is Russell Brand
That would make sense
He seems like the only person that really fits
This description of being a large platform and someone who'd be stupid enough to let Alex
Pokemon interview with s*** on challenge
Tucker's based in New York so it's not him
I feel like most people in California wouldn't have Alex on
Jimmy Dore is definitely dumb enough to have Alex on
Possibility that Bill Maher might be craving enough to have him
I wouldn't be surprised
It is just so sad
Break the internet so maybe it's like Kim Kardashian
Or cognac that would break
Talk I would watch that
And I don't think tension
I would find that surprising
Donda to is the first album
Did I have
Absolutely categorically refused to listen part of the press tour for that album
Infowars exactly. That was so bad
That I refuse to listen to down to two.
I have written
Several hundreds of thousands of words about how much I like
Kanye's music
Yeah I think Russell Brand
Jimmy Dore in Belmar in that order of descending
Likelihood
Are the people that I would put in the in the possible
Honestly if history of Prelude this thing's going to end up having some weird podcast I've never heard of
Write some somebody with guitar
Audience that
Is so
Niche that I've never I would be surprised if he did Tim Dillon podcast
Is he in LA or
I think you move to Texas City move to Texas
I don't know but yeah I think that would be a
Right right I mean even on Rogan with Dale and Dylan's got to have you on his show
Yeah and he doesn't care
Now I don't know
I don't know.
I can't really think of many other possibilities my big money
Nutella green is on on this March 8th episode
For some reason
Some of them more interesting than others
This one is
Only if more interesting
By default cuz the rest of it's not very
When you were in studio
Done it today
Breaking news right now
About this
Well my bill is the Congressional voting accountability
Since I've been a member of Congress
It's been a lot of time in the house for calling for recorded boats
Do The Voice vote conundrum
Oh my God
Y'all
This is absolutely going nowhere and that Marjorie will be able to make a huge deal out of how the evil government doesn't want accountability
Because they wouldn't accept her bill
Essentially this bill is a propaganda trap and she knows exactly what she
He's doing
This bill is
Categorically designed to fail because of what it entails
The bill would require the prohibition of not only taking voice votes in the house but also would make it so Representatives
This could only vote yay or nay
Prohibiting them from voting present
It's honestly hard to tell if Marjorie really doesn't understand the basics of how Congress work sorry
If this is really just a childish Outburst of someone who does
Get to do whatever she wants
Under the current rules anyone can call for a roll call vote if they disagree with The Voice vote
Take him to a roll call vote
1/5
How the Quorum needs to agree to it
Marjorie likely can't drum up 1/5 of the houses support her desire to slow down every piece of legislation to a
But she still wants to get her way and this bill is an attempt to do that
Yayoi
You're just not going to get
90 other people
I mean you can probably get 70ish people
In the house already
What ended the house
But also the rules
Vaquera mistaken need
100 members
Is to be there type of coral
If the Full House is representative
But still like whatever it is she doesn't have numbers
Like I said there's no downside to this move that she's making
This bill is going to fail and when it does it'll be a prime opportunity to hijack everyone's attention with claims at the houses
Covering up their vote
Which will feed into marjorie's attention economy and revenues
Is just using the government as a tool to graft
Bandits
Kind of boring
I mean
It's literally she must have introduced that and everybody in the house went
This
Why don't you try to get Rittenhouse another medal
Please
Grow up
So glad we talked a little bit more about what her bill would do is very dumb
And the reason why this bill is so important
Is it wood
Asking bills by Voice vote
Problem
Sitting on the house floor and they simply say yes and no
Members of Congress
This bill would force
Every single member of Congress actually
And not vote by proxy
Show up to work and vote in person and on record
The American people can see our jobs
Performance
Absolutely wouldn't do any of those things
There's no way she could
Wouldn't help did this even though the way the bills written
Waste ever because of the way the coram's are formed it would not require everyone to cut
It's just
Complete
Complete waste
Another thing I was thinking about those listen to this is how much of a boner Alex's with the idea that American government grew out of the u.s.
Western British tradition all the time
Our tradition
Voice votes in the House of Commons
And this carries over to governments in places like Canada and Australia is well
A big part of our system
I'll let you be staunchly opposed what Marjorie suggesting because it's a radical departure from the traditional upon which the founding
Fathers built this
Here's some fun for you in 1801 Thomas Jefferson rotateq
Call D Manual of parliamentary practice which Marjorie is explicitly calling to upend
From Jefferson's manual
When the debate is on did the speaker holding the bill in his hand put to the question for its passage by saying gentlemen to all of you who are
Of the opinion that this bill Shall Pass AI
The answer of Isaac
All of those
The contrary opinion say no
The affirmative and negative of the question having been both put in answered the speaker declares whether they yeas arnaiz have it by
By the sound
If he
Himself satisfied and it stands as the Judgment of the
House
But if he be not himself satisfied which voice is the greater
Or is before
Any other member comes in the house or before any new motion made
Any member shall arise and declare himself dissatisfied with the
The speaker's this is
Understanding of the founding fathers he pretends he studied and idolizes
He would probably
We kick Marjorie Taylor Greene out of the studio for daring to propose a bill
It spits in the face of Thomas Jefferson's rules for how the house
Conduct business
It doesn't mean anything
I mean it is one of those fun things where it's like
Lesson
Those assholes
Wrote that s***
300 years ago everybody knows the
This is
Not tenable for the modern world even these dubbed
Cuz they don't
Right but as long as you're citing Jefferson all the goddamn time I guess what
He wrote that to
Douchebag yeah you're you're actively promoting
Endorsing somebody
Who wants to undo the Jeffersonian model
Of how the voice votes are taken
In the in the house
It's a disgrace
To the tradition of America I will say
I will be off
That one that one is hard to put on a meme
So
I mean as far as Thomas Jefferson quotes
That one doesn't go down in history quiet
As well I will tell you that reading that kind of language is not my strong suit
A words
In places they don't belong
Knowing
Yes
Not only does Voice voting go back to the literal beginning of the House of Representatives
It also predates
The American government
This is pretty funny
Most
Love the fact
I mean that is
Just amazing we know how long they've been pulling this trick
They've been doing it for decades and decades and
Decades of decades
Paula District
What are
What are you guys doing
What are we doing here
What are we just put a camera showing their ignorance entirely and a lack of Interest
A government operating this is borderline
This reminds me more of
Like those reaction videos where they give six-year-olds
Like I Super Nintendo
I know like
What is this is this a phone
Did they use this in the olden days and you're like yes I get it I'm fine with this is great
This is that being like I don't understand what is this government you speak of
Right or like you're in the horizon
That they have a watch
It's called a never the f*** gold high or whatever I tried
We get back to now
Phobic content
I am so just another warning
About to dive back
Can't not because
There have been these articles written
About marjorie's,
Right on Alex's show
A part of her coming on is to announce this stupid bill that's going nowhere
And is an affront to Thomas
Persons Legacy naturally
The other part of it is to deal with
Criticism that is being Levi
Against her
Boys build a man of straw ladies and gentlemen
Creating a fake version of her comments
5 minutes the next hour cuz I want you to be able to respond
Annalise and
You actually said
Interior two weeks ago
Put on the front so we can have a
Get out there
The counter the fraud
We were talking about men in girls showers
Logical man in front of little girls
And some of these man it was in the news a salted women
Kevin White
Imprison and raping them and you said
Who doesn't agree
Woman rapes a woman or man rapes a woman or a little girl
Beat up
RuPaul on you know their TV show
You know show me some transgender person
Listen true
Although Alex was in a deep hole of mostly fake stories that he uses to push intense hatred of trans people to his
Inflatable for marjorie's comment
Marjorie wasn't responding to any of that stuff with her comment
That led to Violent talk
Little bit complicated
She was responding to a
Fake version of that story about camp
Holly when she said her husband would beat somebody up but ultimately
The only thing that triggered that response in her was that a nonbinary person worked somewhere where kids were press
The fact of this non-binary persons exist
In that space is enough for her to experience as an attack or violation on a child so that's
How they talk about
And that leads to them fantasizing about committing violence
But here's the towel that they know what they're doing
In order to make their violent rhetoric seem defensible to Their audience stories like the one from
Harbor grown men
I'm sleeping or showering with 5th grade girls because
Do they actually Express their real grievance
It'll be way too obvious that they were full of hate
They don't come to their audience
Some say that they're mad that trans are non-binary people are allowed to have jobs and places work it might be
Because in reality what they're saying is that they don't think the children should have any exposure to Transit on binary people
Which ultimately leads to the real point of the rushing
Which is the trans and non-binary people shouldn't be allowed to
Existing Pub
It's really clear of this goes because think about it
Ultimately what the
The story that responding to his about is
A couple of parents are uncomfortable their kids came back from camp
Inside the Bay Medical Florida
There was no crime committed there was no problem it was just fifth graders meeting a non-binary
If this is enough to Merit the reaction that Alex and Marjorie are having
Then where would they draw the line
Leica Transit on diners people working retail
Could they work at a library
Could they be teachers
You can easily see how much a society Alex and Marjorie wish to exclude
People from under the pretend justification of
Protecting children or whatever
But here to things that they would never do
It would never discuss the underlying stories as they really happen
Because if they did it would become way to clear that they're overreacting
And they would never be honest about what they want
Because if they did their bigotry would be way too clear
They only respond with grotesque bulshit in anger because that's the feeling they want their audience to experience and adopt towards
Trans and non-binary people
Anger and the Prejudice of
Beer that they pose a threat to children by their existing
Oceans notoriously for keeping you from Reading another story immediately after being so angry
I'm so Furious I better look at it and make sure that they're accurate
Curiosity
This just happened
Repeatedly
Just creating fake versions of her comments in order to Justice
You were very clear that when men pose as women and sexually assault women little girls need to be punished
Yes I was
If there is a grown man in adult biological man
Dressing as a woman to be able to go into bathrooms dorm rooms going into
Women's private places
Showers and so forth and we were talking about
Adult biological men
Camp counselors
Who identify as women
We're staying in
Camp Smith
That's not what you said
You can see even from this rewriting of her position how indefensible her comment
That's where he's trying to rationalize her approval of viola
Once by lying about the circumstances of the story from that count
If there was a camp counselor regardless of gender showering with the kids and it makes a bit more sense to be
But that's a fabrication
That's just from her bigotry and the bigotry of the right-wing media that you can sue
Keep pushing a fake version of a real situation in order
Go to justify her reaction of endorsing violence
If that's an essential element of this that she steadfastly refuses to accept
Because she knows
That she doesn't want an accurate image
That she's a dorson violence against trans and non-binary people
Who work anywhere might involve children
That's the position that she's actually Express
How do I sound like a broken record but this is just disgusting Behavior to see from someone who's in elected office
No she is she is
Look
I mean
It is it is
Easy to be like oh it's it's an exaggeration or it's an overblown or or whatever but
The ultimate desire here
Is
If not
Complete eradication
Then
It is
Going right back and it's the same thing with everything I ate today going right back to
Okay
Trans kids
Cannot be in school with this
Cisgender kit trans kids
Drink at the same f****** waterfall
It's like that is not
An exaggeration that is the desire
That is what they want
Whether or not they're willing to do all this slightly differently
You can tell from contacts
Clues that
What is it like
They're expressing is essentially a desire to
Criminalize parents
Of ptq
Non-binary children
And so it would be it would involve
Arresting their parents
Re-education
Probably getting them to
The Camp's the things that would be just terrible
Call
For Alex to
Support
Steam it seems like that's more in the d-line
And then like Direct
Repression
Like yeah
Trying to create societal situations where it would be
Just
Harsh
Penalties for
Not
Livingway that someone like Marjorie
Would approve of
People live
So again
Pretender setting the record straight but they're not
She wants trans people to be physically attacked
What she never said that
Hundreds of publication
She's here
Congresswoman
Thank you Alex I'd love to set the record straight as usual
Corporate media lies they always put the lies in the headline
And then maybe the truth in the last paragraph of their article
The truth is that biological men are assaulting or attacking
Anyone under the age of eight
Children
Yes later
And there's nothing wrong with saying that
Corporate media and the end the radical leftist Arc
Sbl
How the rest of America fields
Not only do they deserve to be that they deserve being arrested they deserve to be charged
Deserved
Prison
This isn't setting the record straight
It's lying
Is marjorie's position was just the people who sell children should be arrested or even if
She understands that a person like apparently
Instinct would be to respond violently their child is assaulted uncontroversial and don't really
Think writing a better comment not a word
The problem in the issue that Marjorie and Alex will not disagree gate from their b*******
He's lit she and Alex believed the trans and non-binary people existing in public is in and of itself and assault on chilled
They won't make this position that they hold clear because they know that to do so would mean some real problems particularly from
Marjorie said she still with the fundraising and stuff
Being in the house gets racks
She's not
Outside of
Being a lunatic who's in the house
Have that then
She got nothing
She can maybe get a show on Infowars Mabel sinking ship
When Marjorie said when she said she was responding to a story that had nothing to do with violence
Or children being assaulted
G imagine that that was the case
Because of her underlying bigotries that equates
Trans and non-binary existence 28
Threat
This is an essential question when it comes to assessing our comments which is why it will never come up on Infowars
The lying and spinning masquerading as correcting the record will continue
The charade can continue
And it says it's pretty repulsive
Yeah
Yeah a lot of this is really just want to boil it down to be like
Listen
Do you want to improve things
Or do you do or do you want to do things that
Satisfy you almost
You know like it's very satisfying emotionally angry but if you're not going to get a straight answer
I hate that the truth
Satisfying myself emotionally is
What I call making
It's not what if you did make things better and it didn't satisfy you emotionally with that
Abbey press
Rebel
And the answer is no
Again it's just
Marjorie there's a justification
For what you said
Now biological men that are trying to act like their women is Camp counselors
Going into showers with this graders or sleeping in their cabins
With other little girls or boys
That is completely wrong and it's okay for me to say
They might
They might need a
You know there's nothing wrong with that and I'll double down
Say it again
About hating trans people are anyone
It's not
That story isn't
Like that's not an element of the story
If it were thicker, so
Still be wildly inappropriate and Unbecoming of somebody who's an elected office but
She's just lying in order to soften what she saying or make it more defensible and it is not it is not
Commentary is not defensible
It's
It's a disgrace
I don't know I don't know what to say really
Outside of
It's nuts
That
She's coming on in Fort Worth
I mean even Trump only showed up once
Priority was mostly the shallows book
He's coming on and there is a part of me that's keenly aware that the midterm is coming up
And it might just be something where's I got maybe I'll be able to get some voters out of this
It's
A bit more of a connection
It appeared previously
Fasting
Is predictable
And also troubling
It's predictable in the sense that
She's trying to sell these stupid
Publicity stunt bills chair
Let's get everyone excited and I'll create these narratives around
The house is hiding everything they do behind voice votes or whatever the f***
There's that
Say level of
The transfer is being
Deployed by her
And Alex and
In conjunction with her
Is further than some of the
Some of the stuff it may be happy
Canzano more regular basis
And that's
That's not good
Yeah
I mean even if the story was
Exactly what she
She characterized it as
Even if she was
100% getting this story itself right
It is still not
About biological men causing
Harm
If it support children person
It is
Committed a crime
Importantly
It's not about Ben
It's not about men. It is about
Trans people
Non-binary person
Anybody outside of the f****** door or whatever
But what she considers plenty of violence that men
To get swimming that she is 100%
It's not about violence against women or children
I'll see what I'm doing with Matt King
Yeah it is
Yeah
So I mean I expect Ally
Yeah.
I don't know I have a tough time
Putting any kind of
Summation on this other than to say like
I find this deeply
Troubling and I think it's a good
Deserves
You know and I cast upon it
And I don't
I think it's something that should be overlooked
Obviously
Enough thing when I was sitting person
In Congress
Who's not named Ron Paul
Shows up on Alex
I think that's
Problem
And then when it's
The content is like
This
It's just
And then it's also a person who spoke at Flint this is bulshit
I guess it's
Yeah
Yeah I mean the summation is like
Care for and protect
Text trans people
Do as much of that as you can
And just making them
On a functional level making them happy
Happy trans people is a f******
Terrorizing thing to the
To the right
Don't don't
Use violence
Help people
I think obviously is
The most important
Something the people
Can do
Like beat like
I don't know
Vote for Jennifer Strahan primary
Find some way to stop these people
Retailer green is somebody who
Getting outraged at her speeds Nicole
This
And her comment
Leads to her being able to do it a Victory lap on Alex's show double down on stuff
And create a larger false presentation of what she was saying
And
She's vulnerable in the GOP Primary
Caribbean Pools that have shown
But there is a possibility that someone could be
Beat her in that primary
And
I feel like
It's entirely possible she has no place to be in government absolutely not
Credibly
Horrible positions
Then also for her clear lack of understanding of
Literally anything about Civic
And corrupt
Corrupt
Wow that's kind of
That's par for the course right
With another episode
Maybe you talk
More about
Maybe we'll cover Alex's appearance on Real Time with Bill
We also are on
We are now just fighting that go to bed Jordan
Dzx Gorgan dr. marbles
And now here comes
The sex robot
Alex