Goddamn
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Everybody look like now try the best
And for you sir
Wow oh my God
Think is that I think I've done with Wordle
I was a late adopter yeah I saw people posting these a green dots of s***
And I was like I don't want to get
Get involved I see these things come and go and I just like
I'm too old for this at this nonsense but I do like word games
I like
You know
Arab Scrabble guy
I have been in the back
I like to kick my ass
Every time we played Scrabble
Boggle lovebug
Equally
Ill-fitting names that I enjoy
25 day streak
And it's
Not even
Fun
You got it right board
I don't want to
Do you like bragging or anything I'm like Alex here
No big deal but you got the right 2500 very easy thing
Yeah very easy game not be all that much to it
I mean I'm
Pretty sure that is the specific charm to the game might be
Not for you it might be the a b b y n is universal appeal it's the bar of Entry is
Challenging enough
So pick it up
They are tied together
How many times do we have to say this to you do your time
Wasn't
Getting them right I'd be mad
So the flip side
I think you need to be getting it right
At around like 85% of the time
You both have the satisfaction of achievement
While at the same time something to like shoot for
25 days out of 25 days in a row you're just like I can
I'm the master of
I'm not I'm not going that far but I didn't
It's the opposite of Elden ring
Whatever you think about this way
If you got one wrong tomorrow
Then the next day you'd be so ready and raring to go baby
I might not
That's true I might be in the exact same place I am that which is I'm not
Brightspot
Is
I have as you know we talked about it I got contacts
Right
But
I hadn't even noticed cuz you also shaved your beard around the same time
Multiple switches at the same time
Of my face
But
The eye doctor
Whenever I got the contacts
We put in the regular ones
Is everything is going great
And then right as I'm about to leave
He just puts Toulouse
Contacts in my hand not loose like they were out
Little yeah to Lucy's
And he kind of gets in real clothes like he's
He's doing a drug deal and it was like you know these are transition contact lens
And I was like I do not understand what you're talking to
In the light they change to a darker color
Very sensitive ice I do like the idea of the doctor tried to be like a
Coronavirus
Check these out you don't even know me
I don't know things like strep throat in college one time
Swallow pills and Health Center to get to
Steroids
Right to alleviate things
Because I couldn't take pills I needed to get the liquid
Steroids
And the doctor when he was given
Sarasota like
Conspiratorial
The stuff the Retro 7 about
But for me it was about getting messed up on purple drank
Though I was actually sick
Anyway
We do excellent number of episodes
Alex and a little bit of time
So just some awful Basin and such
But
I'm not going to chase him around
Back to the past again
3 because there was a story that we had left hanging sort of
In 2003 which was the situation with
The
The weapons expert in Iraq who had died
Suicide
And I felt like if we left that hanging
We might
Forget that that was something that we had to like the back of it
So we're going to take care of some of that talks about it
Painfully boring stretch of Alex's show
That leads to something quite fun
Let's
Tabby
I'm a policy wonk hold me closer Tabby Prancer
Thank you so much
Thank you very much Charles Schwab thank you so much
It's hard to tell
Ricky's mom has got it goin on
Thank you very much next Unity paint stuff punk-rock King of the cats thank you so much
Thank you very much. You know what I am mad at the cruise
Thank you very much
July 21st through 23rd 2003
I kind of had just intended to you notice
Just do one episode
Fast
But then
No man's land
Oh this is a
Long a desert of content
Alex is going to eat
Weird weird
Stretches
Saying nothing for long periods of time
On the show
Which is why we need to
Go three days back about literally catching up with
Yeah and so
We do get to on this July 21st episode
Alex brings back up the weapons
Inspector from the UK David Kelly
Clean the Slate on this one
I'm going to
I'm going to get my
And I was
Walked
A big Walker
We cannot read his email
For there
So I decided not to cover this on our last 2003 episode because I knew was a story that was going to come back up and then Alex
Who's going to develop
Conspiracy around so I wanted to wait until you have a chance to do that before getting into
Any rebuttal
Also the piece that we discussed on the last episode is just details
Aftermath of Kelly's death
In order to prevent the idea that he was murdered
Now more information has become Publix Alex
Claiming victory in his prediction that this was a murder that's being covered
So now let's try and understand this case a little better in its proper
This Story begins with David Kelly
A well-respected expert in biological weapons speaking to a couple of journalists under the assumption of anonymity
These were Andrew Gilligan of the BBC and Susan White
Reported for Newsnight
What are the strike
Details that was
Included in both of their reports was that
Had intentionally misled the public by injecting the claim into a dossier about a Reiki weapons of mass destruction
Capability
Namely that the Iraq
The government could activate their weapons within 45 minutes
This was a salacious detail a very detailed
It was in both watts and Gilligan's reporting
From an unnamed source
It was something
That previously today is even Tony Blair
Yeah in the rationale for going to war
Dying
Fake source that they use to just lie there at headed their teeth off of this isn't he
I know that's not David Kelly but they had the special about
The guy from Top Gun
I was thinking of mister
David kellywood
So Gilligan's reporting specifically alleged that this claim was put in as an attempt by the government to me
Mislead
His initial appearance reporting on this on the May 29th 2003 episode of
Today Gilligan side quote
What does person says
Is that a week before the publication date of dossier it was actually rather a bland production
It didn't leave the draft presented prepared for mr. Blair by the intelligence agencies
Didn't actually say very much more than was public knowledge already
Our source says ordered a week before publication
To be made more exciting and ordered more facts to be to be discovered
Gilligan stressed that this detail the 45-minute point was very Central to Tony Blair's appeal to go to war
Scented stress the immediacy of the Potential Threat and it is reporting he was strongly suggesting
That based on this unknown source
This was something that the new shouldn't have been included in the dossier
This was primarily because it was something that only came from One Source initially who this apparent
Atlee this intelligence Source claimed
Was thought
To have been mistaken
The person who was
Did the person do one sources behind the 45-minute client was known to be probably wrong
Yes why what are a liar
Or just like a fabulous or something
After this May 30th Susan W contacted Kelly and interviewed him over the phone
Witchy record
The transcript of this call makes it very clear that Kelly was aware that he was the source of these clients
Emmett from particular details and Gilligan's reporting as well as that of another BBC reporter Kelly it's Boca
Continue
It was clear that W could tell that he was
Their Source based on previous conversations that they had had
Right so pretty immediately the ministry of Science of Downing Street came out and strongly denied the claims are being made in the media
And the House of Commons set up a committee to investigate whether or not the
The decision to go to war even done with complete
And accurate information
Hahaha
One of the MPS who launched the effort Donald Anderson
I'm specifically cited Gilligan's reporting as one of the factors that led to the decision to open that inquiry
At the same time the ministry of Defence was curious about who leaked this information but they
Assault was
Accurate
On July 30th Kelly wrote a letter to his higher-ups
The ministry of Defence which
Definitely intended
How to create the impression that he barely spoke
2 Gilligan
He didn't say the stuff that was being reported
How many didn't even consider that he could have been his Source until June
18th when someone informed them
But some of the evidence
Since provided in the House of Commons in Korea match details
He would have given
This is demonstrable be untrue the stuff that was he was saying in this ministry of Defense
Gordon Kelly's conversation with
From May 30th
Hey discussing the reporting it was happening she asked are you getting much flak over that to which Kelly replied
Club me
No not yet anyway I was in New York
What says quote yes good-timing I suppose and Kelly offers up quote I mean they wouldn't think it was me I don't think
I think maybe they would maybe they wouldn't
I don't know
Wow
Retrospect probably should have said that one
This letter prompted some internal conversations and interviews within the ministry of Defense
Really we're not good
For Kelly
He was interviewed by his superiors on July 4th and on the 7th and note was prepared in respect to the interview
Music starts quote
I began by explaining to dr. Kelly that is letterhead serious implications
First on the basis of his own account it appeared that he breached the normal standards of civil service Behavior
And departmental regulations by having a number of unauthorized and unreported contacts
Journalist
Regardless of the detail of what passed
This opened up the possibility of disciplinary Acts
This is really bad
For Kelly because even if his story about not being the source for these claims was accurate
You still might be in trouble and the fact that he's admitting to undisclosed contact with journalist
Necessarily meant that more questions were going to be asked
How about these
Initial interview
Go all that well with it coming out the kelly didn't even seem to be aware of the ministry of Defense protocol as it related to
Interacting with journals
From the note about his interview
He said that he had not really regarded his discussions with journalists academics etcetera
Has being about defense business but as a continuation
Ibiz roll
As a u n x
I said that this was at best extraordinary Li naive
Journalist or not seeking information out of academic interest
But to construct story
In that interview the stakes of the situation became pretty clear
Which may not have
Bet the case prior
Richard Hatfield the Personnel director of the ministry
Be the case or not
His conversation with Gilligan maybe Central to resolving
Any public dispute between the government and the BBC
Quote it might become necessary to consider a public statement based on his account
Gilligan's reputation was at stake and he would be bound to challenge any of accuracies
And I reminded dr. Kelly of the possibility that
He might have been tape-recorded
Ultimately Hatfield took Kelly's word and decided that his actions in terms of talking to journalists was very naive
But not rising to the level of requiring disciplinary action
Essentially got off with a warning
Stewby's
These meetings that were about his letter that he sent to the ministry of Defense
About the pizza special
But questions lingered and is more details came out from the Foreign Affairs select committee inquiry that was going on there was
Initiated by the House of Commons
It became more and more clear to people within the ministry of Defence that in all likelihood
Kelly was going
Open source
Gilligan was making things up in a way that attributed his coverage to a source who was meant to look
When is a.c. report was released they determined that there was no evidence that the claim that the 45-minute.
Detail was
Against the wishes of the intelligence community
As was the contention of Gilligan's reporting
Which relied on Kelly as a source
Because of that it became clear the people at the ministry of Defence that a bunch of questions are about to start flying around
About who the source for Gilligan story was
And that if it were asked
They would have to say that someone had come forward internally
Or else they would be
Engaging in a cover-up
They wouldn't have to come out name Kelly
There was a very high likelihood that his name would come out
Based on his contact with multiple journalists were probably going to be able to put the piece
But your host
That's where there's at
There is a possibility of something
Going bad
On July 8th the ministry of Defence released a statement that someone inside the ministry had come forward to say that he had met with Gilligan
Though Kelly was not named in this statement
The statement reflected terms that Kelly had agreed to and that what he had said when he met Gilligan didn't match the
The accountant the reports
That was the base
Like I said Kelly agreed to this meeting
Early scores
Naturally dislike the BBC releasing the statement defending their reporting which led to an impasse
Since both sides
Really reveal who they were talking to
Let's Travel
Yeah
On July 9th
Kelly's name was confirmed to the press as being the person who came forward as the result of a
The q-and-a session
With a representative from the ministry of time
A policy of not naming Kelly but if
The question was asked directly to them
They would be able to confirm that he was the official in question
And Kelly decided to not poop for a while taking his family to a coastal town
Kelly understandably felt hung out to dry by the ministry of Defence in a secure location
Alex
Talks about like him feeling mistreated by
The government
This is a large part of
He wasn't given any heads up about like you're going to confirm that I'm the person
The ministry of Defence policy was essentially Will Ferrell in Austin Powers worth
Now I have to tell you it's mr. Kelly like what are you talkin about
If they ask a good question but you have to tell him the problems that to conceivably is there like you just listed
Turn off names eventually
It's not not at Ironclad way to keep information
Here are my guesses
Snow isn't him
No is it him yes
So on July 15th Kelly appear before the Foreign Affairs committee and questions came up not only
About his conversation
Gilligan but also Susan what
In his testimony Kelly claims that you'd only met with W one time and it was in November 2002
On this basis he denied making the claims that were alleged
And Susan watts is reporting
This will become a huge problem later because as I mentioned
W recorded their interview
Ferrara
He's an interview viewed in the context of other known information seems very evasive
Attract
Probably met somebody acting malicious
It is the feeling of somebody who made a huge mistake and things have gotten way out of hand to the point where reputations
And wipes
To work we're in danger of being too
Destroy yeah cuz he was a very credible well-respected
Weapons expert who had a headache deep resume
I know it seems like there's a possibility he was just talkin s*** and it got out of hand
He just started talking and then kept trying to like
Do inconsistent do damage control only made things spiral further out of control
If it has some of that vibe
So Kelly left the fac hearing feeling good
The press that included this line
Quote colleagues have also asked me to pass on their view the doctor Kelly has been poorly treated by the government
Another place where Alex is taking this claim of mistreatment
The government towards Kelly
The next day July 16th Kelly was set to testify before the intelligence
And security committee which followed along a lot of the same lines
As the previous day's hearing
On the 17th Kelly provided a list
Journalists have been in touch with to the committee's
Is Android a bunch of emails to associate
Many had reached out with well wishes
Blow over soon
Alex's mischaracterizing his emails
Has it been saying he's going to fight
Doing that because that's what fits the archetype narrative that Alex sells
About whistleblowers
That's Alex budget details make a particular case fit his mold as opposed to him recognizing details that are
Yo I seen them out in the wild nugget it's consistently reimold
Jamming it into the
According to Kelly's wife's testimony morning
They've got nothing
And he seemed normal but pretty tired
A little later in the day she found him sitting silently in the sitting room which is uncharacteristic of him
I thought he had a broken heart
He was very very
It shrunk it to himself
He just looked as he is he a trunk
He couldn't put
Two sentences together they couldn't talk
20 that afternoon Kelly left the house for a walk Evan previously received a call from an associate of his wing
Commander Clark
Who had discussed issues related to Susan Watts
It'd be rise in a full investigation of his dad that it's some point after the hearings he became aware that there was a recording of his interview
With w and that he had testified that he absolutely not said the things that were on that
Bright
Clark's mansion
But they had discussed W in their last phone call give some Credence to this those Clark's testimony regarding Kelly's
Spots to the hearing on the 5th
Quote you was totally thrown by the question or the quotation that was given to him from Susan Watts
He spoke about that when he came back to the office
He said that through him
Yeah he did not expected or anticipated that that would have come to the fore in this forum
I'm not going to get into the details about it but there's a very compelling
Evidence that he died from suicide
The story are just figments of his second match today
This story is a tragedy and it all likelihood it's a story of someone who made a really big mistake and then in the process of dealing with
Take me to series of further mistakes
Until he was facing the prospect of his reputation being destroyed
Is freedom possibly being taken away and even the possibility
Have him being seen as working against his country's government
David Kelly at the rudest things
Wasn't even a whistleblower the way Alex uses
Is the term stories just disgraceful
With no evidence other than his imagination Alex's suggesting that Kelly was ambushed and murdered because if that were true
It would really help Alex
Spell the kind of
Scary stories that he likes
To tell to keep his audience interested
He's exploiting tragedy and using Kelly's death is a prop
Vines
Inexcusable
And disgusting
Zeinab
The story of
Kelly's
Fall is a tragic but very interesting
Right
Tail
It is it is very much like
Cinematic and it's
So you know just that like
Oh f***
Ofac
Keeps trying to get ahead of it
Keeps trying to be one step away from like
I got away and it just
Caught up
Just caught up
Man possibly or I think there's an entire possibility that he didn't think that he had said the things that were B
Being used in the reporting
Until he realized there was a recording of stopping that it became
Became harshly real
I I don't really know and since he's
Gone
You know I don't know if you'll ever really know
But I
Yeah I don't know
That did not have to go this way
And I think Alex only makes it worse by trying to
Co-opted it for his own purposes you betcha there is one detail
That actually does lend itself to Alex's
Theory
Bring it up in this next clip
I am done
I'm being harassed
Dark
Are all around me
Exaggerating that but there is an email the David Kelly sat that morning that mentioned
Quote dark
There's an irony that Alex is missing here though because that email was sent to New York Times columnist and Iraq war All Star
Judith Miller
On the 16th Miller Road Kelly saying I heard from another member of your fan club that things went well for you today
Hope it's true
Kelly replied on the morning of the 17th quote
I will wait until the end of the week before judge
Many dark actors playing game
It's certainly a weird thing to say but there's no context for this combat and none of his other correspondences
Nor his family members testimony match the conclusion
Alex is jumping to
You could easily see it being some
Reference did between him and Judith like I don't know I don't know how people communicate right
The other emails that are
Is like the investigation
Documents you can find
None of them
Have that tone at all but maybe image
Weird terms
Entirely possible
I mean I would imagine he that
Time with his point of view in the circle
Stances
I imagine that he's
Definitely got some like
People are out to get me
You know what actually one of his big fears
That you can find if you really look into the details was that the Iraqi
People would
To get them
That's because
He had been involved
Boudin
Looking at weapons capabilities and also with
Some not necessarily the highest levels but some elements of negotiation
And salt discussions with
The Iraqi side right about like
Just give these things off mcgiver sure and says and then there won't be a war do nothing for happen
And he had some fear that he would
End up
Becoming a CNA somebody who's lying to them
Attack them right yeah right
Could not be higher
Yeah
And
Brutal
Just just horrific
Alex gets a call
He is not going on
This caller wants to know like
What is
The military-industrial
What is this
Shadowy organization alright who's on top
It is
And Alex gives me the pecking order
Industrial
WhatsApp
What
I understand that
Sound system really giving the pecking order of the military-industrial complex he's putting it into another flowchart which is the New World
Order which has the Rothchilds and the bankers and the crops
Sprite above them
A man above that is
Queen Beatrix
Barnard
If if somebody asked me hate Jordan what's the military-industrial complex my cream my first thought isn't like
Well the Royal Family's own tabloid
That's not how you begin a response to that question
It's it's
So Beatrix royal family owns tabloid man
Set back they own tablet
And then they owned Banks and then the Rothschilds
And out of them comes to military industrial complex
But
Again
That's just Lockheed Martin
Ncbc and then BC
NBC
Prisoners own everything
Well no the Lockheed Martin of the military-industrial complex on the TV stations
They're owned by the bankers and
Who is that owned by the family
We know because of the present-day that the devil is about that
Topmark Alex's
Either intentionally obscuring this fact the past true or it wasn't a piece of today's cosmology
I think you got the vision
From God yet who knows
You have been hit on the head enough times
Tony Blair bush
This life is meaningless and there'll be no reason to included in the show on its own but I wanted to play at Notre to bring up an important point
Because I think it's actually really detrimental to Alex's entire world
As he sees it the evil globalist are essentially in control of every
Which is how he's able to determine what their next moves are going to be
Bush and Blair are losing public support so they need to do something to regain control over the population it because Alex knows that they can
Literally
Anyting
The obvious solution is that they're going to do a false like
To get the population back into a state of fear where they could be controlled
The only thing that makes sense.
But that didn't
There wasn't a terrorist attack in George W Bush's approval ratings
Continued to slump all the way until the end of his presidency
If Alex is worldview was correct this should not have happened
It should not have been possible for this app
Bush should have had all the control over the mechanisms that manipulate public opinion and Alex knows that a false like carrots
Back is our favorite tool to win the people that world savior
It didn't happen
The reason is Cliffwood usually never make it into an episode is because Alex has s*** like this all the time to the point where
Even notice these predict
10:30 got wrong
What I'm listening to his show
These misfires that actually point to the conclusion without the worldview is meaningless
Just blend into the background of the show
It's just
I mean it seems like at this point he would say if he knows what's going on
That's better going to allow George Bush's approval ratings to drop further and farther
So they can bring in a Democrat president
Maybe even
All black one
Well if he pulled that off man I'm on his team but he
Alex isn't even
2004 election
I work quite a ways for 2008
Then we're talking about some serious prediction ability
But him being like
They'll figure it out he'll be given that much like sort of predictive credit for that cuz
It still could be rooted in some kind of bigotry
So could this be like it could just be like a race is Grandpa on a chair
That would win people over
Those bastards I could see that still not being like
Strong severe the future
Forklift from July 21st cuz honestly this show
Stinks
A large percentage of it is Alex reading the entirety of a Ron Paul speech called
Neocon
Where are you sad I talk about how bad the neocon talk
They do disagree
To Alex reading in 2003 cuz
It's a little bit
Well Lot B better than the Press
He's better at sight-reading a little
It said of the constant struggle
It's still awful
To listen to
It's not nearly as torturous
But use another dumb
Bad prediction
Terrorist attacks that the government and the globalists are going to do and I didn't going to be
Be a draft in response to that which also didn't happen
I don't know I mean like
If I wanted to I could make this show just
A wallowing
In bad prediction Alex likes
But it just
If it serves our entertainment purposes
From just
Hitting that drum over and over and over and over again
So-so
Now we start the 22nd
And actually
Holyshit
Me and Alex agree on something
The royal family does whenever
No
Now
Will
Vietnamese
Alright here we go I know that some people probably don't believe me but I really do try to keep my ears open for insta
Anticipating that I think Alex gets right
And they really don't come up that often
It's easy to think that because our shows about how much he's a huge liar and a big hit that we wouldn't want to allow any perception
10 degree pin that he could be right about stuff
But the truth is they when it comes to concrete stories in position
He's almost always wrong
But here's something I can get down with
I do believe the torture is always wrong but testimony that's derived from torture can't be trusted and I'm glad that Alex is on the same
Yep
Unfortunately I know if I'm listening to Alex into the future that he doesn't necessarily have this is consistent position to be always
62 totally fine to ruin the fun for the moment
2003 though we're on board
Thank you this was a story about it MI5 expert testifying that they wouldn't
Think that information derived from torture is
Always not correct
And it's sometimes it could be useful which socks
Even if that statement is true it doesn't make the case for using that practice anymore compel
People's 9/11 time was a horrific.
Where people were openly discussing whether or not the benefits of torturing people made up for the inhumanity of it
And it's
Not pleasure
That's early to go back in
Just how awful things were those conversations that were happening in Buena presumably mainstream space
The Alex has such an easy stance to take to appear to be the same
It is hard to imagine
Not
Reaching the bar of
Don't torture human beings
And it's like
It is amazing that the
Bush Administration
Was like okay we got to get the shadiest most evil lawyers we can find to write a torture memo that says it's
Okay for us
To torture and then we haven't even hunted them down and put them in jail for the rest of their life you know like they're just allowed
Continue
Walking the Earth like they're fine you know obviously were opposed
No
Some of the more mainstream figures that you might see like politician yet maybe wear
More
Tied to the political system and more encumbered
Then someone like Alex who can give full-throated condemnation right and then ramble about stuff that's really exciting
Bright whether it's true or not in many cases
And I can really see
Do that
Would make him pretty attractive to people who
Can't understand why people are having a conversation about whether you can torture people
There were some people especially we're representing the military almost always
Who were just so
The heminsley pro-torture
You know they would have those
Fox News two heads
Two sides like man, was fine with waterboarding until they want water
Boarded-up yeah yeah
Amazing
It's just it's just
Incredible disgusting
So Alex realizes the hey man maybe there is some first-time caller
Probably lay out who I am
What am I about
What are you doing
And wonder what we're all about
America
We believe in controlling our borders we believe in
We believe in
The big brother
Lowering taxes
Nation
We're mortal enemy
Add also demons Walk Among Us really needs a devil that feature more heavily in what's going on
Right now cuz the sales pitch of
I am opposed to torture
You're going to get people to wiggle off the hook
If he look like
Also
I fight literal Satan
I do understand that liberals you're all just working for the devil
Yeah that would have been a tough for sale
Yes to be like
No no no
I know you think that the royal families are the problem
The Rothschild
At the end of the day the only person who would really torture
Like Alex is talking a lot about like
You know vaccines and what have you but
Fauci doesn't come up
Does not come up strangely
He knew that he knew all along that she was bad
I mean except for that stretch where he did a shoes and things
Like monetary stuff and
It seems odd
Seems very strange
Bill Gates is not coming up
Anyway not a whole lot of content on this episode
But there is an interesting breakdown that Alex has
Where he decides to start talking about how like he doesn't watch TV anymore
Definitely
A very long
Ramble
More than
Literally I get nauseated
Hillary Clinton
Not watching TV
Market
I understand it's better to not
Spend a lot of time watch
Watching TV
This is your job
Yeah
You're just making other people do your job now
I mean you could you could hire somebody to do it for you
A lot of shows
In fact
Everyone Late Show
Has a writers room dedicated almost entirely do watching s*** all day
That's true
I'm even on the on the flip side of head like let's let's look at this let me like
Listening to Alex's show sucks I don't f****** enjoy it much
I'm not going to crowdsource that's 37 like listen I'm not doing good job
If you guys want us to talk about something Alex just said
Send us the clips on you
I can't handle it anymore cuz it sucks
I must subject you to the thing that you put Alex call-in show
I thought this was going to be short but it is it is not because Alex
Fix
Something of a physical response sure
Kaylee
That's so intense the feelings that I'm getting from him right back.
He's supposed to be going to call
Shivering
It goes on it just goes on and on
Walk around home
And
Alright
But I literally
Headache
And
So painful
Started getting nauseated
Because I
Control
You think that
Headache
7 cake
I get it to keep it through explaining that
I can't stand to look at these people I
One more time
Why you got to
And not only is he going to say if he's going to say he's going to consult the police a little bit
He has a misconception that like okay you know
Police
It's got to be tough
To see somebody that you know is guilty
Get away with a crime
Sure
But it's not nearly as hard as what Alex have to put up with
Bigger cross to bear
Murderer
And I watch him
Really.
Bringing back those images
Alright alright
So this goes on quite a while
Wow
Does he think that
More explaining memes
He gets more sympathy from me
Cuz it's the universe
The more you explain why I should be sympathetic to you
The less empathetic
Maybe he doesn't
His point is been made
You know
I think that sometimes he feels like
I have to come up with another way to say
Eating the same right he's he's like oh my God
Better keep eating it
So
This doesn't eventually
I'm going to guarantee that Alex has been watching plenty of
But you get the call
From somebody who wants to know about a
A draft piece
Legislation that Alex is pushing
Oh boy
Here we go
Forward my resolution
Define
Are you sure
Confirm
Vulcanized
County
Members of the council before
In the morning
Refuse
Hell yeah
Really interesting cuz I think it really boils down Alex's approach to politics
Where we seen them play this out on a number of occasions like when he was obsessed with state legislators passing bills to affirm the 10th
Amendment for a few months of 2009
He does this s***
What's what happens is that identify a perceived threat
And come up with a completely symbolic and meaningless solution to it
He's mad about the Patriot actually want States
Institution is real
Weather in Northeast 8th pasties bill
That is no effect on whether or not the Constitution is real
Is the pr ploy
This may work in some places but not many
Most governing bodies would be able to see that this is a purely symbolic entirely meaningless act and to pass a bill like
This would only serve to give the appearance of folks like Alex
Have real institutional power within the party
This would be giving me Fringe right-wing the appearance of a victory with nothing actually achieved and nothing gained for the
Politicians themselves
It would in effect be the government's ceding power to the fridge
Which is unlikely to ever happen
In normal time
Without a fight
And that's why the second aspect of Alex's strategy comes in
Where he tells people to decry politicians who won't play ball
Is people who spit on the graves of veterans
He's basically hoping that this kind of threat will be enough to get these politicians to go along with his meeting was Bill and that will to some degree
Allow Alex to demonstrate his own relevance
And influence within mainstream
Text without anything getting done
And no risk actually being taken
This is the model that you see often in the right-wing media but
Why don't things have kind of troubling is that in our last episode we saw Marjorie Taylor Greene basically playing the same game with her
Congressional accountability Act
When people lament that the right-wing has become
Conspiracy-minded and like Alex
I don't think really keep an eye on his how much is it
The folks like Marjorie our governing
Like Alex knife
As opposed to just
Saying the kind of
Think Brett Congressman should be here
Okay
All right so they can
They can vote
Anyways
Now they'll Superbowl
And if they don't do it we will
Harass let me throw this out
Cover-up artists
Let me throw this out at you
Here's how useless
That bill is
You Alex's bill
You couldn't write a bill
Saying that there
Not in
Effects aha
Right so it doesn't matter
If you if you can't write a law saying you can't do this there's no point in writing a law saying you can't
Right it's not like some town in Florida could
Write a bill that says you have to quarter soldiers
That's not how it works
Nope nope nope and you can't have somebody who's like you have
Have to quarter soldiers
Because here
We don't even worry about the Constitution
What are you talkin to
I didn't go anywhere
And neither does this f****** episode cuz we got one last clip and it's Alex making another dumb
Prediction
Malia
Before the War Began
How does monkey
Ford
So it's fair that these are real documents and that Judicial Watch to get them released but the cover
To them is a little bit skewed
16 pages of documents do include a map of Iraq soil fields
But it also includes a map of the oil fields in Saudi Arabia and the United Arab
It seems safe to save these documents show that Cheney and his energy task force were aware of Iraqi oil fields prior to
But the larger picture of a set of documents make it difficult to use as definitive proof that the Bush Administration did
11 or started the war specifically for oil
Whether or not you believe that to be the case for other reasons these documents are not good proof for that conclusion because they also
Oilfield
In other countries that weren't invaded to be counter-examples
To the presentation that Alex
Who's making about Kentucky
Larger picture though this is a good example of how Alex covers stuff
There's some documents that got released but he can exaggerating sensationalize and in order to amplify their importance
Please address the bush might set off a really small box
In order to distract from these documents
Yeah this very common for him and probably the only reason we don't have a clip like this
Every episodes cuz I ignore this s*** most of
The time
This'll get tedious
Like I mean just simply
You don't need to set up a nuke to get people to not pay attention
Did you dishel
True
You know I would be
Interested to do some national polling
To see how many people even know Judicial Watch
But I would say a lot of people probably.
To be fair in 2003 Larry klayman was not
In charge yeah that is true
This is not a claim enjoy
I mean to distract from Judicial Watch you could probably like
Turn the lights out
In a little part of Nashville and the whole country be like
Well we don't need to pay attention to Judicial Watch now there's this
Lights out Nashville
It's not that big of a deal
Yeah I think to distract from this
You could
I don't know televised
Concert
Celebrity covid messages on basketball
Call Ann
British accent release documents
So we don't
He starts off.
Weird weird story
Juan Carlos
The weirdly I thought this had to have been about the fact that
The night before this
There were two bombings a popular Spanish Resorts and allacante
And Benidorm
For sure that's what the story because
Of those bombing
They instituted a curfew I thought for sure that was the case
It's for that to be the case to Resorts that were approximately 29 miles apart so obviously a terrorist attack
Required coordination
And a basque separatist group called the ETA had to take
Responsibility
I was certain
But this was a situation where there's a curfew
McKay's never even brings up those Bahamas
This actually is kind of what Alex is klimek
The mayor of a town in Spain
Vienna by 9 on Thursday so they could do chores
It's real B it is been up
F******
Love it I think it's great Thursday isn't that to be ladies night from that on
This was a guy named Javier because of decisions like this he lost a re-election for mayor the next year
This was ultimately an inconsequential human interest story that will happen
You act like a silly clown
Taqueria
This story might be relevant to the people who lived in that town but the idea that Alex's were boarding
What is a national radio show is some kind of proof that men are under attack life out-of-control feminism is
Comical
Motor out of a
Zyrtec by the Mad Hatter
Everyday and imagining that this had anything to do with one car
Oculus
I feel like a better use of Alice's time if someone is interested in important
Bombings resorts
Table for
What happened
That would make
These talk about dudes out of Spain
Bulshit like this
As opposed to
Who rides
Where foreign Nationals right right but I mean come on
Ladies night on Thursdays
That's a fun story that's more fun to talk about the bombing but it shows it shows the level of content that Alex
Got2b quipped
22 Rockaway
He never talked about anything but like
Ladies nights in weirdo towns that's great
I bought an RV I'm going to check it out ladies night
Ladies nights
Diners lies and Drive-ins that's what he's going to do it
And it's all Luby's
Bad news about the Luby's close
So
We have Alex
Bouncing around talking about talked about topics gets into a little bit of fluoride stuff
Causes bone
Written the night
Literally
AR
Retarded
What
Secretaries
Organization
Berkeley
University
Cornea
New world
From here
That's a complete lie.
News item
We revealed that
Brave New World is actually my brother's plan from the beginning
Yeah you can go to listen to Brave New World Revisited if you want it's as readily available online at it and no point in it.
Aldous Huxley say the Brave New World is based on a secret government plane is brother told him about
What you doing
Nor does he cackled maniacally like of the supervillain he would be if that were true he does not
This is an absolute lie
I can get this Alex knows that it's a lie I know that he knows.
I can say with confidence because he uses selectively edited clips
Of Brave New World Revisited in his documentaries
In order to get those clips that he uses he would have to be familiar with the larger context
I need help to you'd have to know that he's creating a distorted manipulative image
Also we talked about this a hundred times in the past with fluoride doesn't dumb children down
It's a positive and has dramatically reduced dental problems in this country though there is definitely a concern about it having a dangerous
Effect in high enough doses
That's what the studies used referencing are which he's like about to apply to the incredibly low moppets in tap water
Alex says a lie about fluoride witchy
Can't backup if he's forced to actually get into the details about it so it's
He just distract with a side story about how the addition
The fluoride in the water
It creates a fun conspiracy for The Listener to make themselves afraid of
But it's bull
Fluoride terrifying now look over at these jangling keys wahahaha
Alex runs out of gas a bit
About 40 minutes into the show he's been
Talking about nothing
More or less nothing
And
Par for the course
Oh boy this was a
That's not
Because this first color that he gets
Is itching for a fight
Is
This is very exciting you know we have this stretch of time where there's really not much going on
This is where I felt like business is really going to pick up this guy
This Canadian weirdo
Idiot
Horrifying
I'm one of your dishes done so I hope you don't
Cut me off
I'm a Canadian
The u.s. troops
End the war in Iraq
Hello
Canadian
And we're not a bunch of
We did it in Vietnam also
Dodgers
Canadian
They didn't have
Did you know that
Jordans
Vietnam
Do you twist
Manipulating the news every morning
The biggest news
Story this morning
What's the killing of Saddam
You apparently haven't heard about that.
One of these guys
Weasel weasel
How excited I was
The last few days in the show has been a slog of Alex rambling but nothing
Canadian weirdo seems like a shot in the arm but Alex is going to need
To get his game face on
It's a perilous situation sometimes listen to these callers
They almost always just agree with whatever Alex is saying but in the cases where they disagree with him their offense still assholes
A wrong
That's the kind of situation we have here this dude in Canada's pumped about the Iraq War who wants to emasculate Alex for not being mad
Manly enough to support it
Pretty font
Kind of sucks though and it was looking like I was going to have to side with Alex
Obviously opposition to the war is the right position
F****** bomb on Alex's play
This is like 40 minutes into the show and it hasn't really covered
Any actual news
Arizona slow day but saddam's kids were killed that day
And I'm honestly not sure if Alex would have even gotten to that story if the caller had brought it up
Alex's whole thing about a rack is that Saddam has been secret it out of the country and is living on some Island in luxury or paw
Possibly in Russia so it seems like it could be a little hard from decide
Where to land on this story
If he accepts that it really is Uday and kusay who died then he probably assumed recalibration to do on his
Narrative
How are the listeners supposed to believe that Saddam was taken to a beach resort but somebody's children were left in Mosel and killed
In a firefight with US troops
That seems like a hard story to make stick
Conversely on what grounds is Alex going to be able to claim some kind of conspiracy
To hear does it go with like a body double Theory or does he just deny that it happened
This is a piece of news that I can definitely see Alex being a bit reluctant
Takis position on immediately because
The implications it could have four other larger narratives about the war are are real and they're more important for him
You got to think about this
I do love the collar is forcing his hand on this issue
But I have to say it's very clear that this is
This guy is probably a huge ass
Not only did self-censor he almost said you're sure taking your sweet ass time about it and then he was like
You are you sure took your time
You get there. Canadian polite
So
But I'm going to say thank you and please
Salix I was causing a weasel
Things like hey hey weasel
Your point though here we go and so here's the first attempt
Let's do it
So this really doesn't do much the counter with the caller said
The caller said that he was tired of all the Braves go to something like that
That is a Ron Paul was a doctor in Vietnam and he says the war is bad
It's basically an appeal to Authority that
It's pretty much
Meaningless in this conversation
I was waiting for him to reply with
See the royal family owns all the tabloids I don't know about Barnard Pediatrics
But I guess equally unimportant
The boy that's going on
So far this seems like a bit of flailing on Alex's part possibly attempt a pop-up Ron Paul's military service
Credentials
That's the first point
I never get to the second point which I guess is about the fact that Alex hasn't covered Stomps kids
Number two
I'm sorry what
NyQuil night
They claim that they killed
It smells of b******* Alex's position was the globalist
Constantly report two people are dead but actually aren't
He would have led the show talking about others is a big
Cover up in there today and kusay weren't really dead
He didn't do that
Until no indication of even being aware of the story until the collar
This sounds more like defensiveness
Alex does bring up some cases of misreporting that have happened in the haze of War
In April 2003 Aldi Hassan Al majeed or chemical Ali was thought to be dead after his Villa
In Bozrah was the target of an airstrike
The New York Post reported on the situation and quoted Rumsfeld the same
We believe the reign of chemical Ali is come to an end
Additionally they spoke to a major in the British 3rd Battalion parachute regiment and said they'd recovered quote
A body that was thought to be meje
This book like a fairly safe assumption to make give him the information coming in put it all to mately turned out to be wrong and that can
Can happen when you're talking about
Casualties in the aftermath
Immediately have an airstrike
What's Saddam himself there were instances of rumors of his death being reported by Western
It was ever officially said that he was dead like strong confirmation
I think somebody did
Start singing you something like chemical Ali
Evil is he
Now he's dead
Ali Ababwa
Saddam had a lot of enemies and it was in poor health particularly in the early 2000s
The rounds
There was a part of this reporting is probably something of a psych Warfare tactic meant to make Saddam look week
Inspire one of his Rivals to be like on Now's the Time to seize power
Not necessarily a good thing but if that was the strategy it kind of makes sense right
In the case of Uday and kusay
This wasn't a rumor or a possible killing from an airstrike this was the on-the-ground fighting that happened in the troops released
Photographic evidence confirming
That's a Dobbs children at one of his grandchildren were killed
U.s. troops were also tipped off to you today and kusay his whereabouts by the guy was letting them
Stay with him fairly strong until
Even prior to going into the fight
I can understand Alex's into instinct or skepticism but it's leading him off track here in the territory where you just assume that everything is fake
Lake without any justification
Instances of misreported that's in the past but that doesn't
I mean that every death it's reported as a fraud and the only way you
You can really tell is if you engage with the actual reporting
You can't even gave the current Story by just Gallagher about things that have happened in the past because ultimately those things in the past
Don't have a direct impact
At the present story
Also I'd be remiss if I didn't stress that the cases that Alex is talking about being fake in the past
And the case of storms kid
Two dissimilar to equate to one another
Suspect
Someone is killed in airstrike like in the case of chemical Ali Israel until that someone wasn't a certain place
Finding them there and then getting into a gun battle with that right
It's very very different
Ultimately the feeling I get from this is that Alex didn't plan on talking about this story weather because he didn't know about it or because you didn't want to stay
Stake claim
I feel quite strongly that this clip is essentially him talking around the issue in a way that allows him to
Call the take a later if you want
He's like I know I have to respond to this and I'm going to try and do as much as I can
To like
So maybe he'll quit and I can just stop talking about it I'll be able to have time
Time to think of something better I have to defend myself
From the assertion that I didn't talk about this
And I don't want to make a definitive claim perhaps
And so the way to defend myself is to be like aha I didn't talk about it cuz I'm too smart about it
I do it rings.
Yeah it rings A Little Falls
Because
What he does is just trying to shift the conversation
Record
Alec can I say something now
Okay
As one that Alex read
It's exhausting
This conversation and he's insisting of collars called him a liberal social
This is the effect of taking the argument off of the territory where Alex really is nothing to say
Into a framing where the caller is going to have to respond to strawman
You were saying we're liberal social that's for being against the war but most conservative person in Congress Ron Paul's against the war
Are you against Ron Paul and thoughts about really conservative
It's a cheap game but I found a prospective it's a super effect
Debate tactic that Alex
Constantly personal insult will help keep people from
Weasel
Alex has presented it to this caller there's a yes or no answer he can give the takes
Conversation nowhere productive
It's essentially meaningless if it's
Conservative or liberal to be for or against the war but this is the water Alex wants to swim in because that water is f***
In shallow
To be honest Alex is going to win this argument no matter what if it goes
Keeps going this way because
This guy is going to have to defend the war and now it's going to yell over but that point
Those are 22 kills this caller has
The climb and no one who thinks it's a good idea to call Infowars is up for that kind of work
You bet it's just not good although
This caller gave me some glimmer of hope okay because
Alex is really trying to Rattle him
And
D2e credit
Whether intentionally or not this caller does the one thing you can do in that situation
I'm talking about you did you ever did you serve the military
Mercenary Army
Good work
You don't have any
So you can see something really remarkable I have in there and I'll bring sharp Focus
What else is doing is trying to Rattle off as many as he could and attempt
The Foster the color
The goal was too overwhelming with things that he's a
Expected to respond to and avocado tries to respond to any of them
Well there's that response pre-loaded
And and and even if somebody he doesn't and the caller response to something Alexandra say like you didn't respond
Find all these other points that I made
Yeah discolored
Exactly the thing that Alex couldn't handle and that's what he ignored all of Alex's destruction
The point he was kind of trying to make
The color never brought up Ron Paul or whether the war was conservatives that was all Alex trying to put a position on him
From everything I can tell the color seems like you just want to argue with Alex about him being the coward
Weirdly didn't cover the story about Saddam son
Though I'm certain he's a complete a****** I applaud this color for not taking Alex's bait and you can
Kind of see what happens at that point
How it's essentially deflate
Like okay
Points which really just mean
Disappointed that he didn't get to bicker about Alex's chosen points
Alex Goes many dokkan which is the most insulting the shows
Weston Democrat
Really brought up political labels at all almost everything you see going on is a piece of window dressing
Alexa setup
In order for this argument to play out how you want to do is color isn't playing ball with that
Fascinating
Iic sucks though I think it's fascinating that it seems as though
He did settle
On one position which is
Ron Paul is my shield
Alex
Yeah so it's like I don't even have you I don't have to get through this rhetorical barrier
Ron Paul is the most conservative cell I don't even need to think about my position right now I've got rampal
Pause the shield
And then tomorrow I can come up with a good kid
Conspiracy theory right now rampal is
Blocking my shield and then my distraction is this laundry list of all these other talking
I don't know if maybe was assuming like I assume you talked about Blackwater or
I want to go to 54 Nadeau or you at
Yeah
Collar stays on point
And besides
What dude
The sob story
Wait what about that
Come on man you got to talk about sucking let's do this
Gettington
Utah
Grown out with Millions
I know here they are in back.
Well this time they have the party
Now
Okay
This is humiliating for Alex
You can tell the positions on
The caller
Alex really isn't making much sense with his insisting that the deaths of Stomps kids must be fake because there's been misreporting Antipas
So he decides to ascribe to the collar of position he didn't take
That the government never lies to us
This is another instance of Alex he's in the same trick he tried unsuccessfully by appealing to Ron Paul
He wants the conversation Beyond his term so now he's trying to force the caller to make one of two stamps
He confirm the position Alex's forced on him and say that's government never lies to us
Alex guilty off about time the government lied and then claimed victory in the conversation
Or you can reject the position and Alex will have an inroad to say so you admit the government lies to us and I'll prove that this one isn't Delight
Exchanges like this are really interesting to me because
It's actually really rare to see Alex's brain working
Micah in this in the sort of Arena
I passed a lot of the colors you would get would be as fans or
Sometimes it just be annoying like the Republic of Texas people have all declared themselves president of Texas
Really mad about it
In the present-day this stuff never really happens at all and if there's disagreement about something from a collar Alex
7 hang up
It's rare that is actual debate techniques are on display if you pay attention to them you can see that almost all of them
Easton misdirection
He's trying to avoid any underlying argument and I suspect it's because
What the points is color brings up or a bit threatened
To him
41 it is true that Alex never brought up Saddam son's being killed which seems like a mark against him as a journal
Even if he thinks it's all fake
Seems like someone who talks about geopolitics on his show so much and
A lot of thoughts about the Iraq War
Bring up people saying that saddam's kids are dead but he thinks
Bulshit if that's his position I mean on the day that's probably the
Most
Important geopolitical news
You better do that which is weird
Weird
Secondly it is true that Alex never serve the cont
Which could be a sore spot for a lot of the military obsessed people in the audio
I was born in 1974 so he would have been a
18 + 1992 + 8
What about knowledgeable to go fight in Somalia or in Bosnia
I understand that he wouldn't have wanted to or might have even been philosophically opposed to it
But he wasn't even in something like a ROTC in high school or when he was in Community College
Is audience is particularly focused on the military but only a part of that has to do with service to the country
The other part is kind of a cultural thing where there's a distinction between the people who would sacrifice and subject themselves
Do a thing to require such a heavy amount of discipline
It kind of sets you apart from people who didn't go through an experience like that
If I were Alex I probably would prefer that this was brought up Israeli as possible and this color does seem
To be hitting some softbox
And not taking Alex's distraction bait
What are my point here is that Alex really actually isn't good at
He's a bad debater if you're aware of Justin Bieber's really basic tricks he's trying to pull and really most of the things he had
Hasn't his toolkit are just yelling and hanging up on people
It's really it's really interesting to see this
This is this
Is empathy
In terms of
I like
A back-and-forth yeah I mean it's impotence in the sense
I'm a
The conversation itself was to have any meaning what
I mean it is also one of those
Demonstrations of how stupidity
Can appear to be Authority you know where it's like the fact that he
He is the one in power
Despite having nothing to say
He gets
To say the last word every time
No diffuse both of these points
Easily without talking about Ron Paul
You can say like
You can talk
Lie about his opposition to the war is conscientious
Nah-nah-nah participation in war right he could do that
And that would be fine
That would
Possibly alienate some people in his audience for his military service is so important
Right there maybe that's
Part of the reason why you wouldn't want to do that
I don't know but he could do that
Simultaneously with the story about saddam's kids
Look I think obviously that's the biggest news story of the day you would expect the next show like his would lead with that but
He could defuse that instantly by just being like
Look
Overload to lay out the editorial structure of my own show the way I want to and I understand that you think that they should
I've been brought up at the beginning of the show
But I have a method to how I'm doing things are going to get to it I appreciate you bringing this up
To the Forefront
He could have done that very easily and diffuse this point entirely
If you wanted to be full of s*** he can even meet like we have internal metrics
Most people tune in around Deccan.
Yeah if you could do something like that sometimes we like to warm up at the beginning of the show
Maybe
Even how about this
A lot of Affiliates don't pick up the first hour
That would work perfectly
Eddie
This mess of just half
Half-assed
Go to debate tax
Grim I mean if you wanted to really be like
Fine f*** you let's go into my world
Just just be like oh you fought in Vietnam
How did that work out
Was that a good idea
That's about it that's a bad move cuz this guy probably would
But he wouldn't he wouldn't back down
Think about how that turns from
You know if your service or any of that s*** and takes it all back onto him it would but then Alex
Would end up having to engage in some substance with a guy comes back at him
Crimes that the government lied about in Vietnam
Engage with those animated bunch of
Vague pieces of information that he kind of remembers
Goodnight scattershot way that he did with
I bet the instances of rest reporting stats
How to do it there a million different ways to die
He just doesn't have a sword
Honestly the better way I was to do this shock-jock s***
Like you should just be like you have the queen on your money I totally totally
Bulshit
Yeah because engaging but also not
Is transparent
He a job he's doing and that is
Piano
If you're paying attention to the show Alex does not come off well he know
Could come off really funny
And also dismissive of this person
If you were just to like
Alright want to fight boy
So the long nose like WWE Do-Right
You're m***********
Yeah I think that it's the
So
911 comes up
Sure
What happened
Well Alakazam ideas about what happened okay so I Diaz he would not
Admit he supported the present that I didn't say that
You know that whole pentagon
Story that's what you claim never have
Call remote
Control
Melon Portugal
Good Wife watch online
Murdered
Cease using that trick again total
Please adjust a long list
The tenuously connected talking point
Alex is able to pull out of his memory
In order to try and overwhelm the collar and make it appear that he can't answer any of this stuff
All this is 9/11 truther stuff which isn't really relevant to Alex didn't
Join the military
For how Alex didn't talk about Saddam son's being
I will blame the caller for bringing up a 911 stuff though
Exactly
Make sure the caller has nowhere to go and his boss
The only thing that can really counter this is ignoring it all
And staying focused on the point that you were discussing to begin with
Is the solution to this kind of attack.
Just kind of brush it aside
It's because
Did well substance wise all Alex did was go
Baba baba baba baba baba baba baba
Great. You just ignore that distraction can only really be countered by staying on target
But all too often responding to the items and Alex's laundry list is just too tempting
The color doesn't actually do
Either thing
11th stay on message and at the same time he doesn't really respond to something Alex said
It's did you choose has a new road to go down which I found a little bit confusing and I think he's lost the three
Okay
Canadian troops United States
We don't have any Canadian troops in your country
This color was doing okay at dodging Alex's shift for a while but I think he lost the plot now
You didn't get distracted by something Alex said though which is weird
He distracted himself
Basically over now
Alex is pimp
The caller into a bunch of positions he didn't take in the actual point of the call
Been long forgotten by anybody casually listening to this show
When do the couple times you probably legitimately wouldn't remember why this call was happening
1812 when Canadian soldiers burned down the White House is that what he's going though I think he's talking about Alex
Theories about florist proofs
The UN bringing in foreign troops
Side of the country
Alex's audience will just
Hear this exchange is a time what a Canadian who thought the government was always truthful couldn't handle
Any of Alex's going to thought Alex was a socialist called in
And Alex school then
And that's the goal of these debate actor
Fix that Alex use
They create the impression if you're not paying attention
But Alex's
Killing it
Most of his listeners are paying attention
So they'll probably come away from that thinking like I'll name you nailed that
I mean it's always it's always a unfortunate truth that debates are
Despite
Supposedly being about words and ideas almost entirely about emotions
Save-A-Lot of Optics
Stop
A lot of it isn't really worth engaging in
So
I thought this girl was pretty much over cuz I felt like well we've completely gotten off
The point
At hand
And both of them are kind of
Gotten
I'm confused on their own
But also if there's some insults that need to go around good
You hate America you're a trailer
You will hate your country
New World Order
Context Mars I had every one of his books
You know what I did recently I threw them all in the
Trash can
This is pretty f***** up for a number of reasons
The first is that I was saying that he goes to text Mars's Church
And attacks performed as wedding
I would have thought that text would refuse to do that weddings and Alex's first wife was Jewish and text is a huge
Alex going to Texas Church
A Texas a giant anti-semite there any sermons were often it really anti-Semitic
I want to go to ride on a technicality though and I was writing books
Going back to 1983 which would be 20 years prior to the show
But his first book that he wrote with was with his wife
I found was titled quote
A perfect name for your pet
This was not an expose I'll do World Order
Legs
Four of them a couple years later Texas output with change
And he started releasing books with titles like Rush 2 Armageddon and dark secrets of the new age
1987 only a few years off but strictly speaking Alex is right
I'm not necessarily bring that up to Pat Alex on the head I'm putting
Illustrate that I think Alex knows a whole lot about text Mars and it's a big fan of his work
What I say the text Mars was a career I mean that
He was a bigot early and
Two of the books You released in the years before his death were titled quote
DNA science and the Jewish bloodline
And quote
Holy Serpent of the Jews the rabbi secret plan for Satan
Crush their enemies and voltage Global Dominion
Yeah he was an anti-semite and he's about 16 feet also
And he was a
Like the he's heavily influential
In a lot of the lot of them
Definitely will not admit
Nowadays
Alex would not talk about how influential and important xmars is in
No I don't think many of them want to lay claim to their intellectual forbear
Cuz if you will it was a little bit less problematic for Alex to be upfront
About these bodies Association dragons like
Sort of places where his intellectual lineage go
Couldn't get kicked off Facebook
Text Mars is a disgusting bigot and I appreciate how much more forthcoming Alex is that being one of his followers at the
This point I'd get into this more deeply but I have some thoughts about doing a larger series on text so that might be
What we deal with at that point
Also I sure hope that Alex doesn't ever find out what text Maurice thinks of his buddy Ron Paul
The most conservative member of Congress
Frenchie's
Overall things
You can talk
Hell
Pandora
Okay LOL Ron Paul
Text Thomas from what was the title of that sermon
Ron Paul is a takeaway my tax-exempt status rampal is a pro-homosexual
Will pervert the title of that song
Yeah
Text Mars
Yeah yeah little hater
Both the sense of
Yeah so after the call Alex
Debrief
Because
I think he went through something
Compartmentalize
Name-calling have an emotion
That is just
Projection
They both called each other a bunch of names that definitely was not one-sided and for the most part it was Alex who refused to stay
Stay focused on anyone topic
He was the one doing the shotgun blast of a million topics I'm talking points and you know what I think that Alex was also the one who was acting
Emotionally
His emotional outburst
Might not have been his theatrical is they are the present-day but this caller
It brought out something from Alex and it wasn't analytical
There was composed person just methodically going over the fact that was a guy lashing out
But doing so using Shady rhetorical tricks
To make himself seem composed while doing it
Right now what happened was the guy said something
And he was like
I'm not ready for this so he was he was afraid
Right
And then that fear
Let him to feeling angry
And that anger
Leads to hate
Alright
And that hate
That's the dark side baby on the dark side of the Minecraft story
So
Alex is
Kind of focused on this call for a bit
Left right
Ron Paul
Alex is building up this way for his audience to remember and Havoc
Experience the call that doesn't match up with
What the call actually was
Kind of a Telltale sign that Alex recognizes that he kind of whist
Kind of kind of dropped the ball on that one
Yeah I mean generally there was this book
That really had a lot about that cuz
What would happen is
You know something would happen in the government didn't want you to remember it the way that it happened
They wanted you to remember it the way that it should have happened sorry I was distracted there or you talkin about Men in Black
Real dystopian kind of tactic if you will if you know what I'm saying
People would have written about
So we
Most of the rest of the show is Alex interviewing his friend George Humphrey
Movies talked about in the past
He's a weirdo but
Kind of boring
Not really
That
How to describe the kind of boring he is
Not really
No and it's
Kind of just another Alex
Kind of like a less interesting Alex being interviewed by Alex and Hell
I don't really care all that much but there are a few clips of things that happen
Auburn the first is
Hypothetically Alex has to start off the interview
By complaining about that last caller
Georgia
Alex
Good to hear your voice and
You and I both
Charge
Patriotic
Didn't I call her do me dirty George
Comfort me about this caller who
So can he fight. Anyway he hasn't for a long time
There is a lot of that to be said
Obsession with trying to do after care about
So this call it's just bizarre tell me how good
So at least they take some calls Alex and George
This caller brings up something that I think Alex
Say
You need to get help
Whatever you're imagining you're experiencing
You're not
I'm guessing Alex does not
And are also like
To make another point
Just real quick
Hawkins
Making out in my air
New World Order
No because I was in the
And I've been calling
Elastic
Black
Flying a flying a
Come up to me
How does the owner
Supermarket
Hey
Need to stop talking
We know where you're at with
Can I come home
Another day and they were putting
Anthrax
In my house to USB
Guns or something
Like that
Those two have thing I had
That I wasn't
My house
Let me breakdown
What
They have
Wow
Yeah
Sir please there
It sounds like
Outside of your mind people are concerned about you
And I'll maybe you are somebody who has some military service in your past
And maybe
You have some illegal weapons
Baby
You're telling people all about Alex Jones and black helicopters flying all over your house which only give you need to calm down
Hoo-boy man
But yeah the military
Put Anthrax in this house
And everybody
Is gang stalking him that is so like
I mean can you imagine if they read it it's like I've Ken Kesey Road
One Flew under the Cuckoo's Nest and Nurse Ratched was like
Yeah man
I mean to some degree
What he's doing
I feel like you have a responsibility towards
Towards folks
Especially when it's public
Like a private conversation
I think you still have that responsibility but publicly broadcast
I just
I think that what you're doing is
Modeling
That it's okay for people to experience these delusions
And not to be like
Not to recognize the people around them might be concerned about them
There might be good reason
No it's s***
It keeps real trap it's giving a blackout drunk
The gift of a gallon of whiskey
And being like hey man
You're more fun when you drink
And it's like you're if you're killing this person
Alex has some news also on this episode
About
Spain bombings nor about saddam's kids
But it is about some
Proposed amendments to the Patriot Act
How old is really really excited about this
At the end of this play
Pahrump cell
I wrote
We just take the time out to
Please
Modification
And I
Library
It's so weird
That you can ignore someone socialism when it's convenient
I mean
This is just another one of those things where you're like
Everybody likes
Do you know why
Cuz if you maintain good
Consistent ideological positions from start to finish and you act
In accordance with those
Regardless of whether or not people are lying about you
Because if you do this chances are you actually kind of are above the left-right paradigm
Everybody winds up being like wow that's right
Good call
It's so weird for Alex like constantly be going on about like
Cows socialists are the devil and left-wing people are the devil
The person in Congress that is to
Side with Alex's s***
A bit
More than anybody else is Bernie
Whether it's through this
Third Lake
Basic Allied things
Should be able to recognize like
Hey this is socialist seems to
I mean I think
The most ironic thing
Is that earlier on he's talk
Walking to Canadian
And he's assuming that the Canadian is
Calling him a socialist because he's against the war
References that one thing
4 is a socialist Center
Who is against the Patriot Act so it's kind of like
You know
I'm at the store fits
Another bit of a little bit of a pattern on this episode and that is
Is dumb predict
Bushes
Approval rating
About 8
They've been cut
Coming down
I think they're it about
So whatever the number is
The number get
Down
Below the
Magical number
Start initiate
Getting and they've already got the
I do not
That they will do
I think that there is
Some sword
What is called
Amber will be here
The fact is
People operate
Off the
Beer
The Americans
And it would be
Zoe's
I think that they will wait
Until
The end of this year
Early neck
Here
Institute
Another of
They didn't
Go f*** yourself with this is a operate off-field
You do that
Let's do it like
Constant
Obsession and preoccupation with this
Imminent
Fake
Constant everyone's about everyone's about to die.
It's not like they're going to blow up the building or biological attack of smallpox
Fox getting released
This is this is fear run roughshod is is the way
Operate Mucci constantly
It's just it's it's a it's effective
Yeah and there's so many people that you really do
It's like
Oh you actually do believe that but not because
And it's true it's because that's the only way you think
You can't imagine somebody operating in any other facet cuz that's the way you operate so if you operate that way
And you're the smartest person in the world
Obviously didn't clearly
Your enemy must operate that way
Because if they're smart
Then that's the way you do it
It can't be that I'm a big dumb dumb
Manipulating exploiting people
And in fact
Hurting the people
Are exploiting people and they think you're dumb
Yep I think there's a lot of projection
I mean it's the exact same thing that I stayed in the aftermath of that fateful call from Canada then project
Eating all of his own
Deficiencies and in bad behavior
Helen Keller was guilty of a few of them
I don't know
To be a really rewarding
Nothing to hear
Alex's
Call
2000 fun to get those in the present-day anymore
Gold like that
Even though you got to sit through hours of
Nothing
To get there
I think it's breaking in the past was
Learned
Dialysis present
0 transphobia not even on his mind no I know of course it's their under
But he doesn't have to say it
Probably not aware that same people exist
Old to be mad about it ain't that the truth right
So much of it
Inferi be
Like long-standing things that he says they are
Whether it's
Klaus Schwab or fauci or
Right like there's a there's so much of that whether it's
People who are supposed to be villains or
Cultural issues that he's decided r r
Stage in front of the culture War
Zoologist
It doesn't matter it doesn't that stuff doesn't exist Eric he's mad about neocon
I mean he is right though I do remember that in 2003 the Cubs
Went to playoffs
Yeah they didn't make it to the national championship
Hey Scott I go what you say
Made him stronger that's what Moises eluded
Batting gloves
Why isn't Alex covering Miss 2003
Hand pisser
He's out there trying to give him some super powers by pissing on his ass out of that pissing all the time
Next episode will find that talk about boys
I don't know
Talk about the present day
I'll try you up we are also on
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight not go to bed Jordan
Doctor marble
And now here comes
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color