Alexandra Thurston color
Specific to the twist
Of yesterday
Lestrange
We are going back to our roots
The root
And the reason was given to me by Dan as
We might have to brace ourselves
Steel Reserve
I think that we've been getting July Reserve
You know we got a lot of food squared away we
The cover it
Think about it
Amen and I realized
About
The people were posting T-Bone Iver video meme
I was right
I was way too mad
And I don't like that I wanted Alex Jones facsimile rhymes
Screaming really likes
Solution is let's get drunk
Kind of thoughts recently where
Are we becoming the anti Alex Jones like there's been a couple of things where I
I've noticed like
Sing back
Oh that's
Exactly
But we don't build up false narrative
A specific
Purpose narrative
First Pacific
Which is the anti Alex
Tear down the wall
Adjectives
David Hasselhoff
Like I want to also say that
Like I said
Derecho
Start back up vocals
I want to say is that about that Bon Iver video I'm totally right
Twice we have
Confirm.
What is right
The $20,000 contest for people to make parody versions of the parody song about him
Yep and that's what I am saying he's going to do what he does all the time with this trip
But
To talk about it yourself.
You should have given me a little
Like damn you're so right
The reason I brought it up
Congratulatory note is
Because I know exactly what the
Plan is
For what this contest is going to achieve
He's basically going to have all the all the lyrics
Of the parody song
On his website on infowars.com
And what are you going to have people do in the winter who ends up winning
$10,000 / 20,000
Cuz it's broken down
It's 3 price
4 best parody
That's 10,000
Person who films at in the best location
Their videos
Congress is that a way to avoid paying out that five probably
I know he's going to do
All the lyrics
He's going to
Essentially
Get people to
To try and reinforce
The Lions and that song that people are making fun of
So it'll be like
We love our somalis
I'm at you know flash up on the screen something about how somalis kill people
It's going to be a thing where you takes
His propaganda and it's reinforced
Of that parodies
All of it true they do want to eat
You guys are fighting a losing battle
Anyway
It's going to be a bummer
But the good news is way less people will see that Feherty version Bengali version
Something to be said for that
Let's get into greener pastures and happy things would like to give a shout out to a couple
That's right like to give a shout out to
Thank you for doing a T-Rex
Arthrex for my favorite pro wrestling themed punk bands
Alright well then nevermind Rex
I'm a huge fan
Directions mention I also like to give a shout out to
Welcome board Anthony Weiner I'm just going to do this every single time you actually Anthony cumia
Host of the 4th power Ballesteros program periodically
Anyway
Infowars
Actually stealth donate to us
He won't he won't let us leave
Today we're going to be going over a investigation where we go
2015 and find out what the f*** happened to make Alex Jones go crazy
Due September 17th
This is
Like what
This started in
June
Our investigation began June 15th
How is this how is this still going on with his
Is full-on like
Substantial
No
The weather
The 73 - 14
The end
Of his big-money bomb
We've discussed
Opportunity
Bizarro money to come flowing in
To the show
I don't know we'll see
He get into like
And a lot of $1 bills
Kind of around him lie.
Yeah
As many of them as you can in order to help
Do you want your bills covered
Getting a tattoo
I don't know
That's way more fun than about $10,000
No
Fly somebody
Put them in a tube and throw $1 bills at that
Ben 10 grand for the story for the experience
Can you go and see how we're all going and
Alex Jones
I don't know how that works
Never attain full consciousness
I can't judge
I'm trying to figure out why these demons from
Conscious
I don't know it's just food for thought I don't know
I love the the mind-killer reference
Two gang everybody knows
Play
I completely f***** up
I forgot that I know I forgot the video
I forgot that I had another thing I wanted to discuss
Before we got into our main episode
So guys forgive me
But I have another clip
I recently
I don't have permission to play this but I'm going to anyway I hope he doesn't
Recently
Jimmy Pardo on never not funny
Had Tom Arnold
Had a very interesting story about some of the people that are involved in our universe
Comes up in this clip Mike cernovich
And
Alleged Nazi
This Sandra Bullock
Also it Lads not to no no no no no no
Hi when I heard
Squealed with delight and I want to play
For those of you out in the world do not have never not funny
I don't get the episodes
Enjoy
Barely was
Pizza
Everything
He wrote a book called gorilla
Is about
Unfortunately
And that's what really happened
Different than the version That's Mike cernovich towels
Also I'll tell you this
We get to use that clip
Parto a part of headline to show that I was emptying and
20 minutes
All right we got the
And some sort of bizarre Feud about using a clip of Tom Arnold
The terminal does realize that Mike cernovich
Calling Tom Arnold
After they had already agreed to have a celebrity boxing match just another version of promotion
Perfectly
His wife couldn't follow through
If Tom Arnold
Doesn't have his
Beat out of them
Yeah
The whole game is over even if it's closed
Like it's like
Oh it's closed at the disaster for Saturday or Jesse James
That you got beat up
If I feel bad about it
It'll probably be like
For the experience
Anyway
Anyway as I set up on the outside of the state
Is that a stealth raises thing about juice now I realize Ed
Oh well anyway
I just like to bring up anytime in pop culture we get
Evidence that these dudes are wack is
So
Behind the scenes
They had already agreed
Is what his point is
And then they back out
Yep that is
That is the most Vedic movie
You can do
Challenging him and then getting biker Jesse James to stand in for him I use you as
Game of Thrones ship
You know exactly
Let's get to the episode Jordan
I feel like we've done decent job staying where we left off the money bomb is coming up
Alex Jones
Is clearly needing money at the end of the fiscal year these to try and raise a million dollars
Fans only
Said basically that he likes what Trump is saying but he doesn't trust him still
September 6th starts the show
Honestly
Usually Cumberbatch
Maybe a happy cuz when you look at this world
Call Jennifer Katz
Your cat doesn't love you
I don't need a scientific study to show me
You have one cat
Because no animal has ever loved
My stomach
But they could care less about fell down and died tomorrow
When I'm Gone
He wants a free
Basically died of heart attacks
If something happened to me
Spiritual connection
If that
I'm a dog person.
Great
Batman
You think you're cool
Only care about yourself
Go to the bathroom
Can you check on everyone else you put on yourself
These are just Elementary understandings here
Right
Prairie
I let you look at the cat to our practice
Ivana
Merton foremost
Cats are cute cats are funny but make no mistake
Be there for you
Stand up for you
Goodwill
You don't hear about cops going people's houses and shooting a cat studio
Because they're not cowards
Dog Society
Trying to make a point about the world while at the same time
Trying to work out some material for a weekend
A real castle would be like this
Yeah you said it
Haribol
Hacking
Nonsense
Yeah
Kind of love you know that's how cats and dogs are
Dogs are simple cancer complex there we go
Now I'm getting it done
People who explained
I got nothing for that
I think is an indication of how
How often does like
The Sunday shows are low stakes
He knows that not many people are watching
And so it just kind of feel time
So why not start off the show the five minutes
About why don't cops kill your house
Right out of the gate
Sometimes I feel like I got to get into all of this news today
So he doesn't stay on that beat
You feel the same way
What time are is
Interesting
Take on the property
Michelle
Take on the properties on the property
I think they would have to
I mean there's got to be some sort of genetic influence from the post animal
Sad
Humans aren't sad all the time
We have no idea what the psychology
Animal
Really depressing thing
Scientists reveal that fish are all depressed all the time
But nothing else
A very long
He does killing your fish
That's a good point
He does get weird
Indispensable
I don't think if pressed
He could explain what the f*** you talking
And here is the first of those clips
Books like echoes
Think they're Gods they say the public
Like you say
At a spiritual Intergalactic level
An Interstellar
There Are Rules just written by God
Something
Then you are a queen
That's
Really weird
Interstellar left
Intergalactic light
About Makati
God wrote that rule on the universe
Just keep living
That's what we do
The super Bazaar
He's expressing the belief that
Do you know if you don't fight back against something you consent to it
Yeah
I disagree with
How he wants
He's defeated
Denying the nerve
The Nuremberg
I was just
Orders
Is not an actual defense
Towards you
Putting Jews into account
Right you know
So
He is right
And it's something that I've talked about earlier I talked about
Lady witches
Everyday that I'm not protesting
The mistreatment of black p
F******
I am
I think it's a little more complicated
Bad well that's because you're a cat
I don't think there are Universal rules
Especially in the way that he's presenting
Globalist
Like Bertrand Russell ecosciences bring it up the recent
Writing in the 30s right
John P holdren
Text bookie cosine
Yep does not say the things that he says
You think they're putting this out there they're giving the information of what they're doing to you and if you don't fight back
Then you just accept it
And that's cockamamie because he's lying about what those
Eco science textbook
It doesn't say dumb down the population
It's a f******
It doesn't matter
Anyway
I'm still mad about the jogging
I couldn't even listen to
Pretty weird also I'm telling you
Interstellar the plot mechanics are not
Okay
Great when you're on Doug Loves movies
What time is it the Rosemont
Whatever
But I'm telling you this next clip is much weirder I invited oversold how weird that clip is I think it's f******
But he believes that there is Interstellar rule
That's very weird
B next clip
Is there a
I think it's undeniably weird
And I think that people lining up
New iPhone
That's technology
Analogy
Is evil of this world
The elite all know that
They're just they're dumb in the public down
Not like she's eating after the elves we are the elf
They want to play Godly run around watching NFL that's what the joke is
Vinny favorite item
My idol is myself
Tell me the truth
And
Try and reach as many as we can
This is not only that would put stuff in vaccines to lower IQ
Bunch of retarded idiot
You are you are
Creations that dominates you
True Humanity
They will go to hell before they
Jamaica
Just get that straight.
Failed they're scum selected
We win for eternity
Jesus Christ
I am tired of these people
Man
Man-o-man
That is smooth as silk
Hearth
I think most Christians believe that right
Anything outside of like the weirdest
Theosophy like the weirdest
Pseudo spiritualism
I mean I guess there is a little bit on the seventh day God rested
To the negative first day was like
It goes into a little bit of vaguely Gnostic beliefs
There is a tiny bit of
Pieces of your spirit predate Humanity everything
I liked a little bit of Internet message boards Illuminati talk
And the idea that he presented
Vivi's globalist
They all of their therefore is to be a challenge for us to get to the next level
Within Christianity
But it also goes to the ideas that have been pitched on internet message boards about the Illuminati
So with all of the and with all of the b******* that we
Deal with
Said that weird
Religious Act
Has so much more of a ring of Truth to him
What is a verb
What are you saying
Teaching the elves we are the
Yeah
It feels like
Like terrible
If you guys understand
You got
YouWager
Yeah
I wonder who talked about the DMT machine
You know when people take DMT they often
MC machinery
I don't know what that means
A tall dimethyltryptamine is a substance
And when you do a lot of people
I don't know what the
I have taken at my
But a lot of people report
I suppose the next episode
You can't move elucidating so hard
But a lot of people report that they seem elves working gears
I am machine
Some people have speculated that
Behind the veil of reality DMT allows you to
Beyond
Elves
Machinery
That create whatever we see in our our reality
Countries that have helped factories
Let's go any further down this road let's okay
Establish that we're doing an eight and a half hour logout
Never drinking wine over to Everest
August 6th
And then in addition to that
We start
To be this creeping
Pro-russia stamps
The beginnings of it starting to develop
But that was more like
Pro strongman
The mail
Yeah
We're starting
Be a little bit more of it
Assad
Show tragic plight of refugees
5 years ago watches Al-Qaeda
In Syria kills 300,000 of these innocent people
Serious fight back we call them terrorists
Media says it quote.
Nashua dead little two-year-old toddler
In the sand that won't show the tens of thousands of dead babies that I've seen online
Eonline
They were killed by western-backed rebels in Syria
So they create the crisis of the shapes
Look up
Look
Compare that compares
Bulshit
Empathy
Somebody like when terrorist attack
In all of the people who look at how right and then he pretends to give
F*** about that lips
And
Complete
That doesn't count
Fake bowls
Basically Russia
Well actually you know
Is Labor Day
So you don't have a show
Union holiday
Well I think you love the free market
Prosperity
That he has to be
A day to celebrate
Union he does actually make a little bit of a point
I got to get my
My fever
Are we come back on
8 +
Still on his b******* about Russia being the good guy
Because
This is the reality of what's Happening
All the other news
Refugees from coming here
See I mean
That's not that's not in and of itself
An evil thing
Wrong
Syria.
Good things
Pattern developing over the course of
Early September just outright
Russian guy we're the Bad Guy
Really bizarre
It's really bizarre considering Alex Jones
Just got to be played into
So much Roosa phobia is early career and the Last Time Rush
The favor was in World War
That was the very last
Yeah damn
So I don't know I don't know what to make of it is really interesting that
If we look at the timeline of the world
It seems like
Summer
Fall
Of
Is when something
Really sucks
Might be the branching points
When are our world could have gone one way or the other and we went the wrong way
That's when
Is starting
YouTube
Warm to Trump
On his show
I don't think so but it's weird
The thing that I
Think about
Pretty
What's the balance
Between
Advantage of a situation
And Putin
Right so all of these guys right
Now in 2000
We'll look at this strong man doing
How much is that
Russian proper
Ganda steeping
Out and then gone
If not
Himself directly but
His circle of oligarch
This is something we can
And how much is
Directly
Look at what I do
Like that
As it relates to Alex
He's taking in like Artie and Sputnik
Getting the Russian line as
True
Because it's more appealing
Masculine culture
I'm at they've kicked out the globalist
And therefore their media is much more reliable than ours
Ours is just full of propaganda
And CIA plant
Better in the media
And Sookie just
I have no reason to doubt things
Is it come from
There are Outlets
See through these
People's eyes
It could not be
Is a state-controlled media
What the state wants you to
Yeah like it can't be more
So how come
Can you not
You don't want to
I mean I do understand though because
If you built your entire life like if you're Alex G
Maybe
Migrated
Stalking with his a
Entire life around
You said we have this
We have those
Dark timeline versus the lights
Damn
Where in
Either or
Really confront the
What I believe
Israel
For they do
DoubleDown
They Double Down
And of course
Rollies new episode
Whatever's happening
The entire politics
2015 was the
The Firm cementing
There will never be a
Shared reality
Call Totally
Like Fox News
Toughman it started
Like it Regan
You're absolutely right
Lobbying really took off
But that I feel like is whenever it
This is
How it's going to be
Yeah things wrapped up to
I think it's because
People realize that election was coming up
And they realize that
It was win or lose at that point
Yeah and
The trends in society that we could see were like well if something doesn't happen Democrats are never going to lose another election
Because that's the way Society is going
I am that is
Right
There doesn't seem like there's any shot there
Because they were the ones
To realize
That
The only way
Too lenient
To being the wife
Supremacist
Because if you look at that
The
GOP autopsy
They did on the two
12 election
Is all about
We need to return back to the Big Ten
I need to expand we need to
Find more Latino voters
Need to do all of this
And they took
None of that
I didn't mean to
Stanford Federal
Today went
Straight
And God bless them
I don't know
Because they give us something to fight back again
Diamond Audio Harley
Alex Jones
Has a long interview
Really long interview about how great
Their products
And about how
Both the same to scare people that are going to come while simultaneously being like
Products are fuckingawesome
They're spending way more time on the show.
Trying to sell stuff
Periodic visits from Doctor Who comes in for like
The hour-long
Session
Gucci Artis on almost every day doing something
To try and sell products
That is not on
Remarkable
Part of the leader for the money
Yeah so in the Muddy Bottom world
After that
Alex Jones interview with John McAfee
Who created
McAfee Security
Every Windows computer with junk
He's also the guy who may or may not have murdered his neighbor in South America
I don't know if this is the case
His neighbor wound up dead and he fled
He was living down South of the Border
And his neighbor ended up dead and he was being
Pursued by the police
For questioning
I don't I don't know if you did it I don't have no idea but I do know that he flies
Eminem's house burned down
As I understand the timeline
I admit I haven't done a ton of research into it
Hafizul Wild
I'm not ready to say that no time you man
Computer software
And weird goatee
Superhero McAfee is on
Alex's
Four presidents
If Alex is super excited about it
Cuz it McAfee has a deep libertarian pass
And what have you
And anybody who would you like
The full-on like we're going to build our own
Why not if you can create a World online like when you create a world in real world
Alex Wood
Obviously
John McAfee is being like his whole
Storyline is
My age
They went out and they filed paperwork
For me to run for
Yeah
Are you giving us the exclusive
Are you going to run for president
I give you the exclusive
They filed some papers
F*** you and that's really not a great exclusive like if I run
I'm going to win
He didn't run any didn't win
But in the middle of their interview Alex Jones says really trouble
Is he real
They're really good
We've got a radicalized
I really am tired of that mentality because all of his that's exactly what he did because all of his stuff is based
It's on live
So he perceives an extreme enemy that he's up again
It's okay for him to radicalize his
Gorgeous
Essentially what Terrace
Yeah that's exactly what
Isis has a better argument than he
He does for radical
Yeah I like
Short of advocating
Just on a logic basis
Their argument does make more sense
A real animal
I like I
Yeah and those don't make sense
Certainly.
Imagine imagine
A terrorist group
That was fighting again
Imaginary
Without
Explosives we do
Yeah
Was radicalized
Partly by Ali
Partly I mean he's the most mainstream voice of the website
Network of monsters
Out there
Yeezys
He's responsible for a lot of terrible
In the end of this episode we get a phone call from old man house phone
He called Becca
I love me some old man house phone
Because it's boring
But he wants to talk to John McAfee about guns
Oh that's fun
It's just important to point out whenever house phone call then
So we move on to the 10th
Hold on let me backup
I think I've forgotten
Is hazrat Portia
Jon rappoport
And I'll tell you to the end of the money bomb build out there
Bonjour
Due September 9th
On the show Alex Jones is very obsessed with
The story out of
Where at
A Ron's Barber Shop
$50 for refusing to cut the hair of a lady
Okay man
Mouse.
Like like the movie Barbershop like a white dude
Second one
I'm showing up on
A lady went in the shop and you're not going to get
Alright complain about this
And they got fined $750
Hey these guys just don't have the technology to cut ladies hair
They they don't know how to do it
But if you actually look into the story
Confine that this dude is basically running The Man Show
Out of a barbershop
And his reason for not wanting to
Like through a woman
Who came in
Was less about I don't know how to cut your hair predicated on
This is where dude go to Hangouts
He ends up calling in and they have an interview on a later show where he's like
Montgomery
Make jokes
Some fart
They can't do that if ladies like you should have gotten
Clubhouse
The Little Rascals absolutely
Azilect
The stand-on in terms of
Play
Is that he doesn't really necessarily believe
Everybody
Yeah I believe that his libertarian beliefs
If pressed he would say that a business
Could deny service to African Americans
If they wanted to
All of the free market
Example of a workout
Is what is
What kind of support of
Barber shop
But who cares
Listing to me if
The guy really just does
Use for it like
Flag of his defense in
Court was like
Went to
I don't know
I don't know how to cut
I'm just go
Copper hair
Yeah
That's borderline reasonable
Is not
Something
Way more
Important happens on the September 9th
That day
Before
Donald Trump
Came out and said some stuff about immigrants
Has a very strong response to it
And it might not be what you expect
Donald Trump
Cuz we have the moral High Ground
This is suicide let's go to the clip
Well it's a serious problem we haven't seen anything like it since the second world war and it's getting worse
Edward said I was actually impressed in one way but surprised that Merkel in Germany allowed
This to happen because they're really flowing through all over Europe and if you notice Russia's not taking and
China's not taking and the Gulf States
But some of them are
Really.
84%
Cross the place somalis at the Minnesota
Welfare
Dollars
Holyshit
This is
Why
Yeah
Alex Jones on September 9th 2015
That's more like
Vitriol that's more passion than
Yeah what's your shut your fat mouth
Yeah for interested like
That's exactly what he said fill your hands ya goddamn
That is
More passionate than all of the stuff you said about his mob ties in the past episode 3.
That's super Bazaar
Yeah that I don't know what to make of that
Wow yeah
What
It should be over by now
What's this song
Austin turns
So on this show after this he has an interview with the sheriff
I got
Running for sheriff in Houston
Okay this guy is
Nuts
He says that he thinks that Obama is creating racial Strife in order to cancel the 2016 election
He does not win the election for Sheriff
Just cancel them
Good thing we have to deal with the militia Uprising easier the revolution out of the way pretty quick
I just moved on
Ted Nugent
He put up the nude signal on the past day
There
Call in about how I his show on the Sportsman Channel has been cancelled
That's because everybody's afraid of guns
He's got the best ratings ever
And I don't think any of that
I think it's just a convenient way for them to play victim about the 2nd Amendment
Yeah and
It's very boring
So
It's hard for them
Also I would like to wonder what is
Why was Alex saying that
10 years ago the NRA was very bad
And now it's very
Stream about the 2nd
An amendment
Gone into. Where they were
Semi automatic
Rick
Maybe that's reasonable and because of these other people.
These moric
Stream gun group
The NRA.
Stream organization
Dalek believes that gun
People should be on the offense
And actually he has an interview later on
Hearing that sentence does not make me feel good
Later on
Problem with America
Bellator is an interview with a guy who runs a like citizens
For gun rights
Organization
That Ted Nugent was involved with
Very false claims
Fold down the road
On the 9th
Alex said that they called Trump a punk
Yeah
Then on the 10th
Alex
What about the factory flip-flops on dump position
There was a reason not to trust you
The streets and people sign a petition
Tabantha on Amazon
Adit Barnes & Noble
Mark Dice is the worst
Decided leave me alone
But then beyond
Based on
Free market
Based on Alex Jones is libertarian beliefs
You should be able to not tell the Bible
Yeah if you can refuse service to a lady getting a haircut you'll be able to refuse
I don't understand where the line between your belief and religious supremacism in Liberty
Where is what is more important
Religious
Your principles your phony ass Principe
It's insane
Almost gets into a fight up with a guy
Because he's trying to ban the Bible
Don't sell it on Amazon or at Barnes & Noble
Got really mad why did they leave it in the f****** clip because
The guy gets really mad at him and he's like
I'm doing a hidden camera show
We're trying to point out the people are stupid for signing day
I don't believe you f*** off
Heaven Mark Dice chases them down
Isaac no man don't you get it
A right over there
Yeah that's really sad
Alex Jones tell the story about harassing a lady at the hike-and-bike trail
Which is the
Not at better than elves are we are l
I'm just giving you a run down the steps because like we can't possibly cover everything
We've already spent an hour-and-a-half onto clip
About
I think I've made up even in his made-up story
You still a dick
What you doing at the hike in there all the time
You taking his kids there all the time
Stories about the hike-and-bike trail at least every third outfit
Handsome handsome
Will you tell me a story about the immigrants who were fishing and cooking the fish
Outside
Infection from
From the hiking bikes
But using it as an opportunity to sell
Silver Bullet
Is colloidal silver product
This is an opportunity to sell silver bullet
I'm halfway like
Do you think werewolves are real
Alex Jones has a lot of really bad stuff in the next couple days
And here is one of those things
I tell you
You talking about
It's not just a fetish
To smear
Your daughter
The most degenerate their most
A bunch of eighteen-year-old twenty-year-old troublemaker
Bunch of Christians heads off
Quarterback in Vermont
Not local
That's so close to a Dennis Miller
Heretic Brewing is run by the way
White House
Okay
Does the CIA not really over their overseas
I don't know
I guess couple stories that have come out of
People Young
White girls
Who's going to join
Isis
Yeah in the same way that there are a couple stories that have come out of
Young white dude
Sue gone over to
To join
The opposite
The actual Syrian resistance
Or they're even trying to come here
He takes like
Colonel
It feels like one or two
You stories that have come out
Embellishes it to be like 1,000
Of young white girls who just want to go get beat by a by a Muslim cuz that cool
Yeah maybe women just want it sewed
I can tell you this there's not
Definitely not
So
He's snoring that's bad
Your impulse
Both bad
What is nothing on this next one
This is the first of two very severe historical misrepresentation that Alex make
It will discuss on Today Show
And I think it's probably the worst
So the two I'll let you decide
Because Hitler was a project of the Allegiant Air
I'm already out
But it's beyond what they tell you
Hillary's bad got it
Because
New York City
Get out
But after he was born
Because New York City wouldn't take him cuz the Jews shed
You didn't pay up
Shrew
If I was a real Nazi collaborator then it would be okay if I was George Soros
Schwarzenegger
Evil
I'll be right
Robinson and sucks off the Jews
Israel
$1000000 today
Middle class
Heaven Help Me
Holocaust narrative
The average amount
Truck stop
I feel your hand Nazi lovense come and go straight to hell where you came from
My friends it is official we can now say that Alex Jones is a holocaust denier
Wow
Wow that's pretty wild look into it there are a bunch
Get themselves out
Occupied York City out of camps
If you bribe a lot of money because
I want the money
Alex is extrapolating that to be like
So it was
It was Jewish groups who were keeping the poor Jews
In these camps to be killed
They plays on a
By their way out
And
America absolute
Do you know why
Because of the same
Walking type of people denying Muslim refugees
No that's why they're rewriting this goddamn history so they can't do it like
It wasn't us we're the ones who aren't f****** bringing it
If Alex has been around
Can be allowed
Their secret knock
What walking b*******
Sneak Nazis in America they play on your sympathies and then before you know it
They're making a little right
Play Pandora country
Even though
Very
F****** anti-semitic beliefs
Hitler
Intellectual here in the 19
Totally
Who f****** b******* in history to make
Like if you're if you're somebody now who says all lives matter
Doona
Do not
10 for a second
During the Civil Rights era
You would have been like well I
I get why
Martin Luther King Junior is angry
But I really don't like what he say
I'm I'm pulling on my
The neck of my shirt because the next
We're going to play it starts with him in the middle of a rant
It's about all lives matter
I want to just tell everybody in case you're unaware
The Holocaust denial is much more complicated than
Just someone saying it didn't happen
There's a lot of schools
The thought Within
The Holocaust denial community
They're people who believe like it didn't happen
But there were
But they were work camps they worked at camp
It didn't happen
But the reason the people died was because of malnutrition not because of a concerted effort on the
Unathi parts
To kill the Jews
The other another Branch that's just like
Hey yeah 6 million Jews.
A bunch of other people died so why do we care
There's all these branches end
The thing that Alex
Expressing
One of the branches of helicopter
This is
Incredibly
Disgusting
Certifit
This is the
Still pissed about that
After our last step
Is exactly the same s***
People try
With the alt-right versus
Light if you are
Minimizing the Holocaust
You are denying
You are not
Pretending to be
More intelligent
More research than anybody
Holocaust
Equivalent
Equivalent to somebody saying that it should
You're a f****** monster
On the head earlier and the reason
Engages in this sort of thing is that there's a part of him that realizes
That his mentality is
Was the problem in our country
Yeah
I was drunk does have a little thought about all lies matter but that's not the most important
You justice where he begins
Starting he's ranting about all lives matter
And how Democrats
Have to apologize
For saying all lives matter
But it leads to another really weird sort of religious
That I actually think is much more interest
Is a fraud
Sr raised
Machine
The devil isn't real for the sake of argument
Where is that Revelation that there's a telephone
I want to be clear
About before the truck started
I just came out that there's a telephone don't know what that
Talk about what
Oh you think the Rapture is
It's a f****** teleporter
Anyway.
Special
Fair
Deanne twittly. Preachers
Veyron
501 c 3 script
Forever pots lines of that's great what I think is really fascinating is to look at like the preachers that he
He does have on
Complains about
Cuz he's had this guy named Pastor David James Manning's on
A bunch
David Manning is one of the craziest
Black nationalist
Homophobic pastors
Called Ministry in New York
The most notable thing he's done recently
Is a couple years back maybe a year-and-a-half ago or so
He came out and said that the gay agenda
Is way more
Then we think
Is that they're putting semen in the
At the Starbucks
The frothy milk
It's super fun because
You go into Starbucks when you get a latte it has semen
How many get a taste for semen
The gays like to eat a lot of fun so you'll associate these are these good times that you have
It's wild
Pretty Ricky
Regularly
I found at least 10 times he's been on
X7
It's wild alright
Bucking
True true
I like to say just like
Full disclosure I used to Starbucks
Bigotry
Full disclosure
I drink a lot of semen but just recreational no sex involved like I got a
Did you get
You get to Market
Produce milk
And it's
Juan
Complains about churches all the time and yet
Him on
Yeah f****** Bazaar
Everything
Everything nothing
So like I told you a lot of sales
It's like every single day
His big Anthony gucciardi appearance
Dr. group coming on
On the 10th
They are even bigger
Sponsor for 4 years
44 years talks for 2 years to do this
Finally
We got it all done I'll be honest with you I went out and talked to somebody
Just couldn't provide something as good as is
That was
Because I believe
Group called my Patriots
Reply
Other private labeling
Legend entire lineup
You get Buckets
What he has
Approval to buy
So we need to make money
Can fast
So you get a little bit of a markup on this news
Right it's a good new Revenue stream specially when you're f******
Spending all your time
So there's that
Also on the show
Respond to note
Alex Jones legit
Forget what your 9
2015 anniversary
You coming up with 911
Hold on
Is that right
50th anniversary
Even thinks about
It's fun
Like remember when people forget
September 11th 2015 is the next day Alex Jones
Forgot about that
911 episode in 2015
How to blase
We all a little
I've moved on
So here is something
You know
Seeing 2000 people die
The half a million civilians that week
Iraq
You know what
Kevin Kevin Graham
Turn up
9911 that was the day that he has the interview with the guy with the barbershop
So we talked about earlier
Levy Seaman dude
Very bad time
This dude can't fart
Wait what
That sort of hit one of his arguments
Fart women around
That is legitimately
Like what is argena
Comes down to it but
More importantly
Alex has somebody
He needs you to be really afraid about
Here is that
Islam mesom
That's not
The New World Order
In Saudi Arabia
You understand that
Right now
Following the governor around
Insider trading
Target adore
That's the one
One of our governors
Even our even our best Governors have committed at least
Most crime
Light crimes
But that
False flag
They're going to overthrow the Middle East
Anyway
Has
Information you should be more afraid of
What time right now
By the way the FBI
My source is false but I mean
Not yet
I know so much more that I have because I can't reveal sources
You have so many times
If they're looking at a whole bunch of arrest
Legislators
Surrounded
No second suicide your wife and kid
You're going to preside over the destruction of America
And the world
Getting locked in prison or killed
Because of your
Really really great
GOP under
You guys
Because of your inaction
Canyon Lake
Because the end and let's be honest
If it now
It's entirely possible that we don't make
Get through
This whole section of
Of democracy
We've done it we've done a lot
They want to believe that
The grp agenda and the
Restrict voting rights and all that s***
It's not like our voting rights haven't been restricted before
Do I like a large
Women got the vote
If they don't pull it off perfect
Sooner or later
Come after that
Right
Wind
A hundred percent
Sooner or later
They're going to get
And they don't understand
No but we're not saying
Fucken are we
Now you're down
Video of the place we're doing stop Jones
Governors are legislators
What kind of lunacy Whitaker
If you
Little bit off
It's not the wine Jordan is watching the baseball game on this phone
I'm just keeping
I understand your fam
Iuic
Angry about that
Ascend
If you just said it was are you sure are you sure it's not because
Nevermind
So on September 11th
That was one of the
The idea that has high-level sources
All of our Patriots take him out secretly
He also has an interview with a guy named Joseph
Farrah
Be aware of
Sferra
I'm not never heard of that
WorldNetDaily
He is a dick
Yeah
I was going to say you you said WorldNetDaily and
Betty's
Horrifying
He is big into the Clinton
Conspiracies along with our friend Larry Nichols
And then also he
I've made a lot of
Public claim
Butta bomma
His birth certificate is fake
He offered to pay up $15,000 if they could prove it was real
I meant reneged once the birth certificate was revealed
Easy easy
But he
He released
Some information about the clintons
Empath
About how they wanted to
Silent
Conservative voices
Interview about
You know the growing Clinton Menace
In the 20s
16 election
And he asked
Joseph Farah
Hey you got a bunch of information
Why don't you release it
Will you have a bunch
The stuff from the Clinton stash
Do you have
Now
Let's see how legitimate his answer is
About what
Bombshell
Yeah well it is near but you know when I look at it just means something to me because I
How much do I put out there without
This Is How They
Such an early stage
Breitbart androgynous
And a bunch of
Want to release because people think I'm being sentimental ornithology
What is Delphine
Okay I don't want to look like I'm just all
What that means
I think if I was going to
To try and
Give him a tie
I would say that means is people think I'm trying to sell
I'll try to make myself the story about the
And I want to avoid that
Hey Tim try to be magnanimous in Humble
But the reality is he
Give no information
Obviously you're the f****** guy who runs
Started World News
WorldNetDaily
You're on Alex Jones Show talk
Shut about the Clinton
If you have any concrete information
You told me that mother f****** s*** up
Concrete information
Makes
You just want
You want to have this
Possible thing right
Because it's the same thing with W on the server
Creates in your mind is
Way more potent than what the reality is
It's the same reason like
I've been putting out these
I made an archive of the episodes of that they wanted
Me and Marty
Conspiracy theories
And we did what
Thanks we didn't want episode about a group called The hellfire club
Secret society that existed
Guy names for France
Dashwood
As love their names
Secret society
Self-esteem
Sodomy was involved
But they had
They created
Secrecy
Intentionally
This methodology
Wherein they would publicly talked about how secret their society
And because they would do that
There was a mistake to what they did
Way more important
They were actually doing
Perhaps but it wasn't
To any larger goal
But because
They would be like like Acme
About the hellfire club
Have you been to the house and I haven't
They're really upset
I have no idea
I've heard stuff
Table
Did he stop Red Rock workout
No tomorrow
I don't want to because you're mine
He's not putting it up maybe it's dangerous
Representation of
In one of his I think it was The Long Dark
Tea-time of the Soul
He had a famous author
Who famously
Taken
Into his hotel room
Nobody knows
And then later on is
We are you just hadn't brought it and had him smuggle that with nobody knowing because it created that sense of what the f***
Like so many weird celebrities
It's unfortunately way more.
Create
Is part of that
Vast right-wing
Conspiracy that Hillary Clinton so accurately complained about
And let's be clear we're not
Sitting here saying that
That's not our game that's like
I'd like
The thing I think about
Whenever we talk about the
A lot of what's going on with
Emmanuel
Omicron
Right now in
He's way better
Then what
Then leave
The king like he's not good he he sucks in a lot of ways but
It seems like our world now exist
In
The extreme far-right
And then people who are you
Woodstock
How about Progressive
This is a thing that I thought about
Which is
The way that a lot of
Conservative
Before the Tea Party really got going
Is that like a
The center was liberal
MMA
You know what I'm saying
What's the Republicans will come
Hey man that Democrats were straight up socialist
Yeah
Launch this hard right thing
And they have moved it
Super Fart the right
And maybe
I don't know
I don't know how I feel entirely about the blossoming internet socialism
That's been going on look into it a little more before I before I speak on it
Yeah but it's possible that sort of
New version
On the list of the Tea Party
And swing thing back
But unfortunately
It will swing the other way
For every action there is any
Yeah
Siri
Dead Silence
Brookfield recycling
This next clip from Alex
Is one of the most misogynist
Never had to say and that's saying a lot
Illustrate how serious this year
Just real quick
The story about what happened
What service
Search lady who on LinkedIn
Send her a message
That was
This might not be but you've got the best
Picture on LinkedIn
Professional networking site why do not want to be judged by my appearance
Everyone started calling her
She started
Threats
Over social media
She was inundated with
So much abuse
From standing up for yourself I read the messages
That were sent
Are there post that you can read this Guardian article about it
I don't think she said anything that was like Hey fuk you man right
F****** I'm a
I'm a person
This is not a place picked me up
I've had that so many times it shows where
Afterwards
If it's me and
Why steel comic Kristen Lundberg
Comic in Chicago
And one of the guys on the show
Afterwards came up to
Man whatever you pulled out that violin you were so sexy
There are compliments about
Comedy
You don't need
What's that
F*** is that it's very weird and the reason that like
You were very funny
Instead of
That's exactly what that is like are you going about him
Yeah I brought it up
You know the conversation has been having a lot of dudes aren't listening to
Is that the sexualizing and eroticize and compliments
Especially in non-romantic text
What it does is a of exerting power over with
See you there
I'm at the point that she was making it
Now what's your Alex discover
For complimenting her
I don't want to know
Mike down
Now in the London Telegraph today lawyer
Will be attracted to the opposite sex
Stunning
Andre was surprised man for their physical appearance online telling them they are
That she just chose to do this Infamous groupset good name even shaming
To get her
Charlotte proudman
27 divided
That's why you had your hair all done up there
Online message from Alexander Carter
Connect on professional networking
Stunning
Caldarium
There's an old lady
Check me out at Dillard's or something
This is sick
But it's all selectively enforced if you want to have liberal Hollywood
Nope
Appreciate this
Picture
Even prostrated himself
Before then I'm so sorry it's slightly correct
Incorrect
Bug-eyed piranha
To come in and go after him
Members of The Cult
Holyshit
Holy
S***
That and is
Crazy
If you get jumped
F****** outright sexually harassed her as opposed to count
On LinkedIn
That's so f****** awful
That interpretation is wild
I don't
How can you not understand that
The context of a
Look
I want to fuc
Yeah but that's not why I would hire someone on LinkedIn
What's wrong with you
Rate
So long as you're not being a creep
Yeah you're not pulling them off the streets or within a context that makes
Sent threatening
Do that in a professional Circle
Wild
Bizarre
Also the reason he thinks he's an actor
Critique her and call her like a wild out-of-control feminazi blah blah blah
Is that you said that she called men sexy and hot stuff online
That's exactly
If you look into that
Yeah
She commented
Sexy
On her friend
Photos
F****** which is completely different
Very
Very different
Congratulatory
He knows that
People aren't
Knows that his audience
Duties anti-feminist
Mentality
That's like this
Just like whenever they show the the little headline
Stuff like that
Where it's like
Convict
Murdered by the cops
Yeah
Father-of-two
Father-of-three either words
Yeah pulled someone out of a burning car
Spelling
Saved
Former actress
So
F******
Unbelievable
Or just
Just the way that the white lady shot
The Australian white ladies
So differently
Yeah I'm over it
F****** believe it's so tragic
Now what are
Like the actual elements of it are farts
But that's kind of where we leave off September 11th
Really is an interview with our favorite homophobic Pastor Chuck Baldwin
Here's the guy who said that no civilization that has
Officially endorsed homosexuality has ever survived
Christianity is responsible for saving
People from slavery all sorts of
Everything is good
Even when Christians did bad stuff well that's cuz they weren't Christians
The 11th
And then almost as if
Regardless of your religion people are
Capable of doing good
So the 11th is a Friday
Over the weekend
Bike trail
And jumps into Lake
He's gone on Sunday David night host
On 13th
I host again on the 14th
Yeah
And we get back to the 15
And it's weird cuz the end of the 11th
And he comes back
On the 15th
And he wants to talk a whole bunch
About West
But instead of religion
It's based
In
I would posit
He does not have a good handle on his
But we can discuss that on the app
Did we just discover that now we can discuss that on the other end of the
It's just not true
And why the West is great
White or batteries other things for whatever manifestation
Different breeds of dogs
Why dogs are better
Has been the great innovator
Builders the Great
Much of the ideas the last fireworks
17 lb
Come from even older cultures
But whatever reason many of those cultures fell before
And never Rose
Emma
Volcano
Four great innovators
In other cultures and using it when other cultures
I don't know what that mean
And that was the last
What is The Melting Pot
Racist
And your father
Sure
The first is
Where do where do we start with his b******* and work backwards
Sundial
VIP.
Old-time Western Civilization
Patently absurd
I haven't gone to Rome all that much but I've studied
Excessively
Big part of my college education
An example of analyze
And understand
Is that Barbarian
You know where it comes from
Because it comes from
Barbaro
Invading
Because they thought that everybody who didn't even immigrants
Yeah they did a really interesting idea about having to take people into your home strangers they had like
Actual people
They would
Barbarian comes from barbar
They didn't respect anyone else's language or any culture
Onomatopoeia
Okay come from
That's really fast
There's tons of stuff throughout the history of Greece and terrible
Father a culture and civilization
The idea
Well it's like this great innovator that took things from other cultures have been made it better
Take the big Kill Everybody
The idea that the West is the great innovators have pulled
A list of Chinese Chinese inventions paper
Printing movable type gunpowder compass
Alcoholic beverages
Wooden coffins
Daggers
Lacquer
Millet cultivation noodle
Rowing oars
Ploughshares
Pottery
Soybean cultivation
Acupuncture
You know what we can stop it
I think you should have just stopped right before acupuncture
Blast furnaces
Bristle toothbrushes
Steiner's
Is that it is directly the Chinese
These faults Coronavirus
Chinese cars
Crossbows
I have
Domino's
Firework
Flamethrower
Fragmentation bombs
Fragmentation
Hey let's talk about India
Stop in the third millennium
Indian flushing toilet
Flushing toilet
All sorts of
F*** with metal
Plough and what it was he was talking about when he said he didn't
Want to reveal Hillary Clinton's information because it
It was self
Indian words
Tons of games and ladders Snakes and Ladders
And I will never forget that
So here's a here's the thing that
Here's the thing that I hear
Though all right
Pretty amazing
Although that is
No it's right
References other podcast
Here's the big
That
He just misses
Entirely
You point it out
Look at all of
These inventions
China Inn
And then he talks about
Being Rome and all of those
Who the f*** was right
Who the f*** put together all of these
He says the West Was the Melting Pot
Unbelievable
Be still
Road
Begin and end in the middle
On the west or the east
It was right there
In the f****** middle in the Middle East
Yeah was those it was those civilizations from
Iraq
Those places where the ones that made us all what we are and affected
Misrepresentation
Visitation of all time to go through all of the Middle Eastern countries and their innovation
0 or 40 or or Africa the things that have come out of Africa or South America
All World cultures
Haven't had innovation
Within them
All World cultures have brought amazing
Thornton Park
Is that
Areas where they all met
Everybody mix
That's where things got a lot better
And a lot more interest
Yeah everywhere
Everywhere
Like when you're when you're talking about
Especially in the historical
Text General
People wind-up toy
Yeah
Parts of Africa
Most people today
They are so isolated
Did that they never
Wind-up interacting
In the north and they weren't close to other
People came in boat
From far-off lands
In order to
The idea of isolation
The idea of
Removing
Any Innovation or invention
Exactly
If you want great work if you want the world to die
Nationalism
The way you do
He's wrong about most of them as
Discussed but
This next clip is super bizarre
We
No Alex Jones as a man
It was primarily against
Tyranny
He's afraid
Theoretically primarily
His words
Hugh
Sort of world conception
Liberals are not really liberals
They want to push socialism
Which will lead to Communism
To a totalitarian regime
Tyranny
His big
Kefir and how much
Fewer steps
It takes to get to
That is
His
His career now
Talked about
For the beginning of this episode
There's also that weird pseudo-spiritual
That's going on in the background
In terms of what he's really willing to
Present as his overarching theme
It's a fight against
Epsom salt
All the time
Is super f***** up when you keep that in mind
Do not want you to be perceptive
Powerful
And all I know is
Total control system Wars and functions killing each other
That's not good.
I would say it was a lesser of evils very dangerous might be coming down the road but I wouldn't fight
Does that mean
What you just said is
Is cool as long as it's on my side
As long as it's the right kind of tyranny as long as
That's incredibly f***** up
Like most of his beliefs
Let me see the principles he's just on a team
Your sister his team is weird yeah like his team is not the Republicans
Rotarians
That's its anti-government
Weird
I Constitution
That really is
Swear
You do point back like
All over the founding
Congress's
I refuse
To call him the phone
Sure that's f******
Annoying
King annoying not patriarchal just very
It's what it's like saying the Pledge of Allegiance
Just in a gross way
But the the
Framers of the Constitution
I don't know why
Paper and made it words
Cookie cookie with a paper
I'm trying so hard
Richard
Awful
The one thing that you will
You give them
Is that
All of those guys
Really did come from it
From different angles
Like there were in general
The same concept of Republican
In the Democrats
That we have now conservative
We're against
F******
Throat
I'm cool
Maybe it turns into tyranny down the road but most dangerous
What is that now
That is the one thing that you can do with our our overarching
Idea of the overarching
The Declaration
No
Yeah and right now we have a political party
That is
You look at it LOL.
Probably 40% of the other party
Like the exact
The powers-that-be
Who is maybe in response
To the fact that we had
Most
Obstructive Congress in
History
And so the only way to actual
F*** it I'm doing
Fayetteville largest financial crisis
Bunch of wars and fact that's our Healthcare System
List of reasons why it happens
How you get to
Bright like a whole bunch of crises come together
And people f****** along
And wants Trump gets away with everything
He's been doing
He has
He will
And your eyes gotten away with
Yep and Alex will cheer lead all the way
Also a couple couple more points
About the September 15th episode before we get
More clips
Yeah I open with John bowne report
What about Howard
I do a great job.
How many episodes start with a John bowne report
I'm at it because
The radio station
Start at 6 of the hour
Shows start at 6
Laughter
Commercials and station identification or what have you
John bowne report
F****** babies reports are terrible
Because I got to fill time until 2
Stations actually pick up
More pro-assad stuff more pro-russia business
Then
Proceed
Such a perfect
Bellwether
Whether or not
Like if your profile just f****** died now
I'm okay
Super mad about a story that he read about l.a. trying to call themselves the capital of Latin America
Well you know why they did
The Olympic
I was going to the World Cup World Cup to come to LA
PR campaign
Talking about how
North America is one of Latin America
I'm coming out into the open
No they wanted to make a ton of money
Los Angeles
A very large about it
Will probably get the Olympics
And that's why that's why
Calling
We need to check in
Alex
Like I said
In that
Call
A punk
Called him to tell him to shut his mouth
Now it's often
So now we got to check in on this
15th of September
Has some thoughts about Trump is where we're at
Trump
Because I love Rand Paul real
I support him I want him to win
I know he's listing more milquetoast political advisors
General election
Because he's too extreme he's not a string
I don't know I trust or not I don't know
But
I dunno what he's saying is true
And that's why you so popular
We're back to where we started
Of course we have made no progress
Nundi win it just went
Yeah
He's very going on and the Baseline is I like what he saying but I don't trust him
I think it's
Real problem so far
To be the
Rand Paul actually believe
And Alex Jones doesn't actually believe in what he says
That might be part of the tension
Like that's what it seems to me like
And I think Grandpa is a little smarter than Alex
So much smarter than Alex
What is possible what is impossible
Is also sucking dick
But faster
Inconsistent
Which is something that we cannot say about
Partial tear
Alex
Is the wind
Blows wherever it may
On this episode he has that interview with the guy from the citizens for guns
Or whatever
Remember the name of the organization and I'll tell you this it's not important
And the other
He's just sitting in the room
Yeah doing this interview with Alex
They end up having this conversation
This is the second instance of
Historical revision
I think it's slightly less offensive than the Holocaust
Denial that Alex engaged in previously
But it is just as well
Federal government you can go here and no farther
Then the second amendment comes into play
And to put it a little bit more crudely
If you try to act
Tyrannical
Wasn't about
About
Being free
The Revolutionary War
Was about Gunn
That's okay
Alex
The Declaration of
Sarah likes
That's why was the Second Amendment
Yeah I think that there was were more issues about taxation
Certainly Alex loves
To bring up Harris we talked about the Civil War this one might be more appropriate
There was a
Redress
Of grievances there was no representation
I know that
Parties Boston Tea Party
Was not about gun
I know that
Maybe what else what else
I don't need to
Not
It's just an assertion
It's just an assertion that the Revolutionary War was about guns
What
I mean
What do you say to somebody who believes
Is that the Civil War was about
States rights
Like what words
Are possible
I think there's a way though to like
I don't Tara snow
That's not true I think there is a way
To look back on what happened
The Civil War
Rewrite it
Reasonably
With the states
What's going on
Then
This is going to be a dangerous argument for me to make this is already Danger
I think
In hindsight
You can make the argument that what they were trying to argue
That we should be able to decide whatever is legal in our state federal government
Like
Think you can do that you can't
Use what they were saying back then
To make your argument
Clearly
But you could do that
I don't think you can do that with the Revolutionary War being about guns
Absolutely
Cuz I don't think
Do you know what I don't know
Between
The British and US was
Gun owners
Do you know what the primary disagreement
That
Is
Through-line
The Revolutionary
Pre-war and the
Civil War
Rich people are fuc
I think it's over
Yeah that's true
That's what that's what the argument has been
That's what the argument
As always
End of the Revolutionary War
And the Civil War
It was the rich
The rich people
Okay and I don't I don't want to pull out
Because they were employment
Even though it wasn't even the southern
And then it was racist
It was the whole time about how black people are
Right it is it is always and I'm not going to pull up
Hardcore socialist
Argument
I am just going to
To point out the same thing that
Always been
True that it's a rich man's war and a poor man
Rich people always
Wind-up
Yeah
Winning
Others regardless of who wins
F****** insane I mean Smart in terms of like cunning
In terms of evil ability to no matter what the outcome I mean
Information
They're not smart
Brilliant
The guys who voted on the health-care bill
We're like okay well we're going to invest
In the same day
On companies that
From this exact vote
Yeah not that they're smarter than
A butt
Manipulating the system that we allowed
The day before September 15th
Something really f***** up happen
What number 14
Donald Trump
Had a rally
Intex
Okay and Joe Biggs went to the rally
I bet he asked
Insider information
Never found
A couple clips
From Joe Biggs reporting about going to
To the Trump rally
The MoMA
When
Alex Jones realize
Trump's the way to go
Yeah
No s***
Now
I'm not
Really sure about this
Doesn't give a lot of indication
But I'm correct
But I will make my argument over the course
The next three or four
Hero 3 hours
We got way more than that
The first clip of Joe Biggs reporting about going to the Trump
And
Again it is not what you'd expect
Lorie Line
He says a lot of good things out there
He's not motivated or convicted in a sense when it comes to the issues at hand
Issues in a presidential candidate
Have knowledge in
Certain questions about these issues
He doesn't have a really good answer he doesn't know what he's doing he kind of reminded me of Rodney Dangerfield Woody's one-liners
Like hey we got a border problem huh what are we going to do about it
Art stores
All he does he bring to the table without a solution
Go to the table without him giving any kind of clear
The how he was going to get the pollution to these
Issues we know I won't work
What really works is Prosecuting people that are little
So at this point
That
Slightly reasonable report
I'm going to get into this next clip of the two of them kind of advocating for
Reasonable moderate immigration reform
Trump Jones
Saying that a wall won't work when months later
He's screaming about a walk is the most important
Which there isn't
Later
He has an interview with Jesse Ventura
And Jesse Ventura lives in Mexico what about the wall between Mexico
He's like I don't know if
I don't know
Proposes was the Berlin Wall
Does inventory also brings up a bunch for it
But this point like
He's absolutely making sense
Trump has a bar like you're about to bring the hammer
Not yet
Problem
No Solutions he's up there he doesn't have a grasp of the air doesn't know what he's talking
Is just coming in with Rodney Dangerfield style one-liners
All this is
Not everybody the Showman
Right
Vitamix
In this next clip they talked a little bit more about immigrants
Surprisingly modern
It's very weird
The month screaming about how
The globalists are trying to flutter
With
People need to get rid of them
Or not let them in
This could be no now versus
Is the man that were in 2015
The present day of the previous Alex
In terms of the wall
Cuz my
Yeah
Complete evidence that he sold himself out
Nothing
So here here is it bad
I've labeled this clip Jo and Alex
Seem very moderate
On immigration reform
Going to have every legal out of the country
And find her
Are you American I need to see proof
All the illegals out
Welfare
Reasonable position reflective
What do you actually believe
It's the way he presents
Joe Biggs
Republican
McCain ran
Like
The kind of idea
Hey we know a lot of people are good
Just don't want you taking advantage of
That's what we're going to do steps to stop and as we already of covered when Jesse Ventura was last on he was talking about
If these people are
Program say they are
Why would you not blame the system as opposed the first
It just trying to survive
But far more reason
Joe Biggs is coming in here
Impossible. Turning into a f****** police
Absolutely not
Pushing back against that Alex is fine with the bush
Yeah
This next clip
Just Divergent higher leaf
No not yet
Daingerfield
Teva crowd-pleaser he doesn't know how to work a crowd and that's what he was doing
He didn't have the first
We don't have any 15 million dollars
It took 30 minutes before he even
He talked about this vague tax plan that he had
You going to release it
So
Wow basically there's no substance to what he's saying
Carnival Barker
But at the end
Talkin about how
Even with that lack of Subs
Crazy
They were in
In Arena
Trump is able to draw
These crowds
These massive crowd
That are mind-blowing
Oh he would be
Booked at The Improv
Woodlake
I pay for that
So I think this is
I think
We've heard a lot of
A very reasonable
Respect
The Joe Biggs has
From going
New to this Trump rally
But I think
We're going to
Start to see here
It's going to start today
Deteriorate well maybe beginning of the end
Maybe I'll make my point after this clip Anthony
Also do you know how great Todd glasses
Hilarious
Can't stop anytime you bring up Rodney
Dangerfield now I don't think of Rodney Dangerfield
Mitch Hedberg
In Rodney Danger
Rodney Dangerfield
He's the best it's just amazing anyways
Not the best
My Hillary for prison 2016 t-shirt
Under my suit
The best seller we have photos you sent me those photos
Of my cell phone in the front row
A shirt like Superman
And you can see the Hillary for prison
It did that for real
A ditch
Well
So he's like
Punk 1007
Trump is in the middle of saying something with the crowd like
He yells Hillary for prison
Trump is like
The polls Hillary
Highest points over
But hear me out on this
Has been jerking off for
3 years
They're as a marketing possible
The idea of going there and finding out what's going on with Trump
Was secondary to the idea of field test
Nothing is Hillary
So he goes there as a marketing opportunity because Trump has pulled
An arena full of people today
Which is there might be audience Crossover with
SoJO big goes down there he does the Superman sing
People seem to really like it
Now listen to this next clip
In the entire crowd erupted
Thinking of what we're doing
So sorry about the sound on the clips from this episode
That this is the mama
This is at the Hillary for prison
It's because of the potential sales of Hillary for prison
Bear
Yeah tall
I f******
Love and Hate
How my perspective
Keep changing based on the information that we keep getting
But I legitimately think
That
That moment for them is trans
Informative cuz they realized
Alex Jones loves Trump
Now
Because of
Hakeem go beyond t-shirt sales it's at Market if fertile Market
Alex Jones couldn't get people to show up somewhere
Dustin like gristy Georgia
I imagine behind-the-scenes they did
But I saw a spike in traffic to the site
Probably got a bunch of sales from it and they're like
Might be something we need to do
Too much right
Yeah that's taking it to the streets
Alright we're done with that
Relieved
On the 50
Dumb bulshit that happens on that show
Alex Jones does reveal he doesn't want to
But he does say
They cost him over 50
18 million dollars
So if you
You take that number
And you can
Twitter
Right is about
Chameleon
It's in the realm of believable
Exaggerating is always
Jasmine
Let's meet in the middle at 12 but be that as it may
It don't matter
It doesn't really matter
What are the number is 10 or 15
Because
The money bomb that we're about to get into
Cuz we're about to jump into the six
Just the beginning of the month
28 hour live
He doesn't
He's trying to make $1000000
So
He's trying to make a
Play but he's trying to make a certain amount of money
Hopefully tamilia
Right
All things
He says he wants to do with million dollars
Is weird. About shooting the show into Europe
What you said what you said already
We're not going to do that immediately
Stuffy's already doing
Paying for reporters
Paying for cameras
Paying for syndication
Paying for closed captioning
Already
So all of that million dollars is just operating expenses
This million dollars for
Cuz these are I watch this s*** on YouTube
This looks exactly the same
Jezebel
There is no
Inspiron 15
There is no discernible change that has been made in
In terms of
The studio
There are no people
Who are there
That
Rapable
No talk off Rapport work for free
They're probably does rapport the soldier
But there's no
Greater number of people that work there
Did aren't balanced out by the last numbers
No
So there isn't
Really like
Wide expansion
You pretended that
Expansion in his audiences
If you look at these statistics that are available on quadcast
And other tracking
Sources
Yeah if you look at the numbers that are on his YouTube videos even they aren't
He says they are you add all of them up
But be that as it may raise money for a fictitious thing that didn't happen
Yeah I understand I understand your point
To me though
It seems like it's exactly the same thing as an MP
Yardley
Hey we
Live
Entirely upon
Public mod
But he's because he can't
Supplicate
Because he
He can't be somebody who asked
Operating
It's possible hyper-masculine NPR
It's a hyper-masculine fun
That's what it seems like
To me so far
Typically
MPR is not going to go hypothetically out of business
By the end of the year
And I feel the panic
I don't think
Going to go out of business
You would have to
Did the reason that strikes me as false
Biggest
I know that it's easy for us to get
MPR
Liberalism
Money what a dumbass
That's what he would think we're doing
Can donate to knowledge fight if you go to the
Thank you for all the policy wants
Thank you to all the
I'm getting a
Circumstances
Much more
Yeah cuz you presenting
Fictitious expansion
Of the show
He's doing it at the end of the fiscal year
Which is 2
And then the third is keys in this will-they-won't-they
Situation with
Trump
3 super
Bucked up
That's
It's not about
It's
If that because he needs money
There is motive
In order to make the
That's what we're talk
A baby are going to do a fundraiser and then
Stealth
V
Because of it
Legitimate news sources don't have
Like
They are
Doing subversive
Marketing
The guardian is
Now
Blacklist
Journalism
Needs to be paid
Rather than put us behind
We need you to donate
Yeah the guardian all the sudden
Become the f***
A Daily Mail
No because
Trump gave them
I would hope not because Trump gave them 10 million dollars
Is that the areas
Probably
A future
Better civilization
Involved
All public
Financing
4 presidential campaign
Political campaign
And journal
Does Michael
Need to be incredibly unbiased
I hate Alex Jones
Are we hate Trump
But at the same time
I think you can go back and look at my previous statements and do that I have no bias
Clear but at the same time
When I was dead stuff that's like
Yeah rock and roll
We've been totally cool with that
Weave
Props
Also
Alex
You really need to look into what Jeff sessions is doing with syphilis
Forfeiture
So far no comment
Dissident by Pearl Jam
Committed
Because he's
He's under investigation
To take his stuff
By his own rules
The great point
Galaxy us those assets
So citizens civil forfeiture
Have a great
Like maybe 60 bucks
Speaking of things that have to do with money
Jordan
Here's the bad news
Look up the money is
Incredibly boring
Of course it is
27 hours or whatever the f*** it was I didn't watch any of it they didn't have Alex Jones on it
Smart but there is one piece that I wish I could watch
Because why would five
Yeah you've already hurt yourself
Arnaud arbery
Here's something that we didn't realize about
The money bomb
It is at the end of the fiscal year
But do you know what else happened on September
No
The second Republican
Presidential
Debate
To be on the night of the debate
Oh s*** that's really
Smart
Really smart
You got to give him credit
Is Lee Ann McAdoo David Knight
I think Rob do the third person
Mystery Science Theater
The debate
F****** wow
I saw a couple clips of it and it's
Nothing
No no professionals are no fake robot either like
Alex
Create a robot
You can get even with the real gypsy
I should be good about that
I don't like you
Music
On September 10th you did talk about how the gypsies have
Free rein
Steel RVs in Europe
Vincent f****** reaches thing from the 1700 what are you doing talking about
Gypsy Wild
So
Jewel of the 27-hour 28-hour broadcast
It was really disappointing
Are they had that
You know Mystery Science Theater blah blah
Thanks for his show on on
The beginning of it on this
16th The Alex Jones Show on the 17th
Their reporters tag team like it Daniels did a show
Never never heard is a writer
Somebody always goes well when you put a writer guy on air
Some of these other guys like
Just people drop do the interview Leo zagami Illuminati
Midnight
A.m.
It was just not
Paul Joseph Watson
Doing a bunch of stuff on the office hours
Because he's so
It's again
You're doing an overnight thing where no one else
To stay up overnight
Look
Tortured slave
Infowars
More and more as time goes on.
He's kind of
Charlie Brown
Like
There's a
There's the football right there and robbed is about to kick it
Always pulled out
He's probably way worse
He appears
Cuz you just seem so boring
Is dick
Cuz how would you stay in this business
For like
Years that there really
Your point
Have you considered that he is actually
Control help
I think there's a decent chance there's a good person
Behind Rob do
Cutting soap
Specifically and only the Alex Jones
Portion
Of the Moneyball
What's a 16
Talk to you about his audience
To my house last night Buckley Hammond
Horsing
You're getting people to your old numbers
Here they are they pulled them up in front of me
Internal
Server systems
Infowars now reaches 41 million individual different people a month
Nope
If you count all of our social media it is several billion more
We did a
Videos
It's over 100
But it appears we're reaching upwards of a half billion
Vermont
Have some access to the internet
Heavy access
That's insane
What in full disclosure
Text out of the 7 billion people on this f****** planet
Have internet access
Three-point
Between 3.2 and 3.6
Have
Oh okay well then solve access
Now here Alexander
700700000000
None of them
That's almost billion
Alex Jones
And s***
Of course not 700 million
Literally impossible that covers
He said there's six billion listening
Bob
So that 700 billion covers BX
No cuz you talk about the people who have access to the
3 billion
They
What is that
Social media
It's the same reason he says Paul Joseph Watson videos
Postum on
Facebook
People scroll autoplay
This is the same that you look at all these nonsense videos
Watching videos
2 minutes
For a good while I remember this from back when I was
Coronavirus
Trolling around on that dumb
Look it up
Girlfriend
But most
But he's also we have to
Really
Really have to point out
He's double triple and quadruple
There's absolutely no way cuz he's talking about the top hundred sites
Post-Star videos
Which we've already established
He's at like
What
He's not even in
The top 20
100 posted but you understand
Yes
If you know but as you've explained them
Come to me in regards to a
If you embed a video on your blog
Let's say
From
YouTube and someone
Who plays it from the block
It counts as a head
On YouTube
But if
There is
You got this
This blog post
That is about your video
You can count that as another hit
For the
For every single person who
You read because you're in
Avid info Warrior
Newly-elected WorldNetDaily repost
Thirsty
Breitbart has in the past
Done
Reposted their links to the videos
How many
Just with
The emails Trump
Now to all of his donor
There was a video in bed
Yeah
There's massive manipulation going on there in terms of the audience.
Exactly how you want to start the money
Course at
How you want to start so we're reaching 3.5 billion people a month
That everyone in the world
Considerate
Think about how many children
Do you know what your
We talked about there being 7 billion people seven and a half billion people in the world
How many lizards are under 12 most of them most of them are just born
That's more than ever
Basically you consider the amount of
Considered
And they're not the only country that restricts the internet of course other countries that have blocked internet
Does numbers make no f****** sense
He's back
Way of
He's reaching 10
And one of them is me
Down 10%
He tries to sort of like couch and he's like now maybe people are
Coming to our site from different devices
So maybe we're reaching a billion
Even though
Facebook
Damn
Yeah
Check your Facebook on your phone
I think
You track IP addresses
I think that
Especially if you're using mobile like if you're on the bus and you check your Facebook
Incredibly difficult
The towel like exactly what your meth
Patrick Star
He's not doing legit work in terms of statistics
Open
I love it
After that we'll there's no there's no arguing with Matt but all of this other stuff
We can deal with reality versus non reality
And there is a question there and there are
The truth it is
Pure Analytics
You're lying
Yeah I got the clip and where you goes from there is talk about how like
I'm humbled that I'm talking to
Do you know you're lying what's going on here
Humility that's really fast
But
There's no possible way
Alex
Beyond his b******* about his audience eyes yes Mother
Things you want to talk about on the money about
Jordan
I've said a lot of things
Are not true that I
Astronomical it's maybe three and a half billion things
You get you upset or not true
Not true
I don't like that one scared
Never never
Rareform
Cuz you got that 40 in my heart that
Starbucks
I'll be just fine until all this comes true
I want to I want to I want to go back there tonight
It's screwed everything up I apologize
I'll be just fine until all this comes true
Criticism is
Go to level and put everything on the table
The end of the West
Now it's not
But
What
George Soros
Is he hanging out with
What
Okay you believe
Global
AR
Demonic
Beings from a different dimension
Rich if you see one
Skillet
Why would you
What would you have like a
Hey listen I know you're a demonic monster
Hell-bent on destroying Humanity
But come on you got to leave juicy inside tips for me like a MySpace
That's right cuz that's what he's talking about
Keep on
Keep on your ears
Well know this goes back to what we were
You better get out this goes back to what we were talking about at the beginning of this episode of the internet
Version
The elite
And the Illuminati
They need to have everyone know what they're doing
At work idea
Do anything you can say
Big either using Alex
Conduit to tell people
What they're doing to them and if they don't fight back
Then whatever
F****** believe what's magical about that entire line of argument
I guess if I don't really support him
Then being destroyed
Really
Brilliant
I don't think you could
To be able to articulate
Exactly what
Lineup
That trains
Sixth Sense
It's not that these people are all insane
And it's at their tariff
I don't know
I spend a lot of periods of my life in various stages of paranoia
Xiety
I have mental illness I've done a lot of drugs
In the past until I know weird
Yeah and I can sort of
I can suss out where things are coming from right
I don't I don't mean to put two
These conspiracy
The Forum
These weird
Illuminati forums these message board
Like I've read all this stuff that people talk about
And none of it's based on
It's so much of it is mirrored in what
The Lesser Magic
We've got it
Then you're in
Its soda
It's So based on nothing
And that's what he's doing it's great
I love it
Play music
What
How would he ever getting a meeting with top global us-iran
Bride runs
The join up I got you there
Alex
Mythology
Easiest b******* like
We need to be more like Prometheus who God loves
Like wait hold on one second
Oh I did
Cuz
You saying is the god
To the elite
Version that I would be into
Is that one who brings up for me the entire
Just bring us the fire then got his liver pecked out
He makes for Humanity
Is it that the God that I would worship
Is the one that builds us up
Cuz Prometheus give us fire
Gave us.
No
Multiplayer
We have a lot of Christian knowledge
It's like we do
If you do God bless
I don't care I don't
No comment
So this next clip his bulshit for
Ever
These liberals want to kill cops
Yes
Okay
You have an interview with this guy named
James Wesley Rawles
Runza
Rate name
Yeah I would totally be serial killer
Serial killer
Like his own serial killer I think it's a lot of prepping enough
Here's a step-by-step don't piss me off
He is a guy who used to come on on
On Skype and basements on Rhode Island
Just told us
Used to come on on Skype now you don't even want your picture out there cuz you're so freaked
Too much
Gobs
Most of the show with an interview with this
Let me get into talking about cop killing rhetoric
What have you here use that
It is a paradox
We still put up with it
U-Haul Westchester out chilling
So they're so fired up once
I wish there was some sophistication out there
Everyone not be played like fiddles
Where
Radical
Rrb
Towards
Dispensary
Steve
Nation
NWA in 1988
Body count cop killer in 1992
How many times
This happen
Boba tea
911 is a joke came out in 1990 that wasn't cop killing
Always come with us
I've never heard this s***
When did they start
Why not community
That's really
Like when we talked about like feminism and racism in these sorts of things
And how blind Alex's do so many
A lot of it really does boil down in some ways to like
You're not listening
Well you're not listen
The larger Avenue is just that
Nobody was
Nobody
In your world
That wasn't like if you go back to the 80
See all those local news
Is out of control like all of those different
Never
Now let's take like reality out of it and sensible
Discourse out
Let's just remove that first
Which is how many people
We're f****** talking about taking out the police
After the Rodney King
So
And that was not in the six
Is just
Very clear example
Talking James Wesley Rawles
He's an idiot
Music f****** historical
And I want
You got a Blog
That's pretty cool
Goddamn
So naughty
Arguments that he's making within this
Interview
Is that the global
Created radical Islam in order
Logic like they're fighting
Cuz I needed a better anime
Controlled opposition
Our freedoms created one world religion
One World Government
It doubled back into the ship that Alex talks about
Your radicalizing
The enemies that you are imagining
In order to jump
Sayori
Coronavirus
In his
Is this like this is the f****** money bomb
Most of the show this is the money but most of the show
Fear beer and money
Fear fear and we are much more numerous
Then you think
You are not alone it's all about
3.5 billion
Don't feel bad because you're just one of them
It's like it's like on a buster has a dollar bill already in
His hat whenever he pulls it up priming the pot
Okay 3.5 billion people behind the only ones fighting
Global
Before
Rawls gets out
How much money
Did he actually
Yeah
Oh man
Are considering
Insane markup he has on these products
Even when they're on sale which I didn't even mean to bring up but let's f****** talk about it
For sale
Italy talking about like
All right that's on sale until the show is over got free shipping on everything
Cost
Yeah just like
Got to move it
That sort of thing on it
Which is b*******
If you if you are looking
King at the end of
The fiscal year though
Just because otherwise otherwise
It's still money you have
And it's not like that stuff you bought isn't going to factory
Books and sell it for no profit
Which might I don't know when we got into business I don't know I don't have it
Might still be like it might be indicative of the fact
Maybe overbought
He's in a hole
I don't know
Anyway
Ross
Before he gets out
The episode
Hamster say
Scariest things
I've heard a guest today on Alex Jones
Hellboy
There's going to be huge numbers of Christian refugees
That there is actually a need for a new Homeland Nation
Persecuted
Christian
Refugees
Numbers in the years to come
That's why I decided to
Siri
Call Land Of Promise describe the establishment of a Christian Nation
And I also made it
Christian libertarian
Read pray
A Safe Haven
For persecuted Christians all over the world
Argue that most of the time when
Religious
Pacific countries have been created heaven
How
Here there though
Is that
You saying
So many Christian
Refugees
Homeland
We're creating
Counter Cafe
Which is like what is the name of his novel
But the point being
We
That is persecuted
So let's make
Exactly that
What are burrs
That's instinct
That mentality pervades
Well and frankly this is
This is what we've been to
4 months
Forever
Surprise me
The people don't
One f******
2nd and think
Oh well this is
Thing is bad to lift
Because they have this
But then again then again you know what
Every every Democrat
Said when they go low we go high
Like Mark DeRosa
Walking friend of the show and I were having
This conversation
We all said when they go low we go high and now we're kind of at the position where
When they go low you f****** go goddamn
I don't know
Don't know.
Like we need our up
Okay so the rest of us
September
16th show for the money
I do think he's right there
A lot of
Should refugees
In the same way that there will be
A lot of rep
Total.
Immediately following like
Considering the effects
Climate change
What does happen
In our country inn
Specific
So right now we have a s*** ton of
Muslim
From Aldi
It's not my almost
Fuller up in arms
When we just start talking
About refugees
With no religion
How many all of these
Everyone's going to scapegoat depending on the adjectives that is part of the refugee
Parked exactly how many how many Christian ref
What's the number before
Well we don't want it
Anymore retrokits a part of
Complaining about refugees.
Because
Well you deny climate
Exactly it's a fun game play it's a fun fun game
What's the number
Like how many
For fucksake
Imagine
We're talking about Rome
All of the Catholics
For whatever reason
How many how many
Before
It starts going like
Well we can't allow any
Regardless of religion
Let's imagine this may not be the case
I'm not saying it necessarily is
But let's imagine a scenario where Muslim
Dominated countries
Happened to be the places that are safer from climate change
Imagine like Saudi Arabia is unaffected by climate change
And now these cats
Six-letter displaced rib
Wonderful
The Catholic
From the south of Italy
Right place
So now they have to go somewhere and they go into Saudi Arabia
Saudi Arabia
I mean let's not unpack all of their negative cultural problem
Let's talk about that
These Catholics come in want to change everything
How
How is it the
People can't do that neck
Like think about that
Caught up in their identity
Yeah that's probably
That's why whenever we talk about Alex Jones I don't like
Supremacist
I like to say that you caught up in white identity
White Christian male identity is more
To the point than saying is a white supremacist
It's way too easy to say that like he thinks he's better than ever
But
What really motivates him is
His identification with what makes him white what makes him male what makes
Christian
That threat
Opening to a lot of people to imagine a world where is
Problematic
Because becomes threatening
Right like I meant is that because
The demographics
All the sudden they have the
Thought
Wait
Maybe they start sink
What we think about them about us
Ramen to say
Already really in
Interesting
Assessment of
A lot of
Someone was pointing out that a lot of homophobia is based on
A sphere
Bye
Really
Aggressive angry dudes
That men will treat them like they
Women
And I think there is a bit of that
Really
I think there's a lot of that in
Alex is afraid
The minorities will treat him how he thinks
About them
Yeah crimes coming back
The thing that I have always
Considered
And it is
One of the things in the later stages
Obama's
That I was
Concerned about is
Because of that
Executive over
Because of how much power we go
Gave Obama
Trump now
Like they just
Never we never considered
That's not true
In the
I mean I agree with the point but it's
When's that was happening
Executive power was given to Obama
There were people
Such as myself
And other folks
You as well
This is not good
There should not be like
Domenico's back to Bush
The idea of being able to unilaterally launch war is not in the power
Executive branch
Even with Obama in power
I know
Hun
Of Democrats
It wasn't enough
Congress
Yeah
Imagine
Yeah no
I'm out
It's political opportunism by
I mean
If we keep this conversation going more than
10 minutes
We're going
Overthrow Appleton
Little do you know I'm already there but
Don't reveal that
So
September 16th I'm the revolution
Senor the one
Kiefer that's legitimate
Part 1 of the money
Rhymes with a long interview
Doctor group runs the 4th hour
The show before they handed off to whoever dumbass
He's just trying to sell a lot of product
She does a bunch of bulshit
But before he leaves leaves he says that his predictions
Have never been wrong he's basically a psychic
Young and that his sixpence
Is on fire like never before race
Life expenses
Is it on fire like
It's never been before
There I think that you are freaked out
Certainly
This quote
That I thought was really f****** awesome
I was
If you're nouveau-riche and you're not giving us money
Or
There's a long list of things basically there's about giving him
Impress a billboard
Yeah
You're crazy
If your nouveau-riche
Is that why you phrases like alright
Cuz he wants to delineate between like
It's a it's a new
If the.com billionaire
He's really cute
So now
Here's where things
Where is his show on September
Then
He was due to
The comeback
From 10 to 11 p.m.
Yes Larry Nichols
Yes
They were going to do an interview
And then they were going to Premiere a documentary
He said
People down to tape Larry Nichols
At his house
His address has been given out all our show
Give you his phone number
Still on the internet
On out Jones
They taste sour long interview with Larry 2
Christina
Lyrics
Clearly didn't answer the
Because the first time purpose
The first half hour of the show is Alex Jones vamping like hell
He's just talking about like Meyer of the day
We're great
So much filler
Recite the first 25 minutes on the radio and then
People not on the
What is he's trying to say
Without getting into anything
Then he can't
Bale from
Play reggaeton
That maintenance
Yeah
Exactly
And so about 25 minutes or so 30 minutes in
Larry Nichols on the phone
Emma just talked about
How much calories
Cuz that's his
Is bread and butter
Larry Nichols
Drop this
Chestnut
What Hillary needs to do
Is
She's going
To make herself the underdog
That's why she
Released all this information
About the
Wait
She did Hillary release her own the old is the information about the service
Yes because she needs to make herself the underdog
Which is out of Larry Nichols Playbook
From way back in the ark
They'd make Bill Clinton and Underdog in order to make
Cuz everyone loves an underdog
Bill Clinton
It's all.
If you actually look at Larry Nichols actual history with the Clinton
It does
Scan at all
But that's his Big Sur
Is it
She did all this s*** to herself
Because
The clintons and the bushes are dying
They're always going to be at the top
Today to make
Kind of care about
So he goes on to say
Text to thing
On the show
That are
Dumb
They only have 20 minutes or so to do their interview before they
Expend
10 minutes of it
With Alex Jones vamping more
Cuz Larry Nichols has to take his dog out to ship
Crazy
It is it's it's
Terrible even Hitler's dog loved him
Is something that Larry Nichols predict about Hillary that come true
That Obama's have for Hillary
Here's what you watch
There probably aren't Playbook this time exactly
She's going to start
Tour
Now when you go deaf
Misogynistic
Hillary goes out
Tear up going to start crying respect
Makes me want her to be president
Misogyny behind
Larry Nichols complains that like
You call me racist and that's your way of taking my power
It's a load of b*******
Also Hillary Clinton say what you want about it
She came out and defended herself
So
Hilton
Yeah whatever Larry Nichols idea about Hillary campaign
Hillary
F****** brought it
To these
Bees attack
Apologize for things that
Thought was maybe a error in judgement
Yeah
Right-wing conspiracy
Mostly tracks
Problem in the world
Terrible
As much as he has a problem in
In terms of all the stuff he's done with
With the clintons
He's a huge
Problem in
General
Like I know he
We've talked about this he was saying Obama wants to
Become the last
Because venue become king
Like like the Patton Oswalt Dead about
That's president about this at all
The King and I
Attract
Now
Will never stop that's funny that's funny
That's funny
But
Listen to this next clip of Larry Nichols
And realize how much
F****** hate Muslims
And realize
Nichols
Yeah
It's it this is no longer funny
I just I just can't believe what
Bad guys would look good today
Lancaster that bad guys back then
The heroes today you can believe that
Remember this
Honda Element
What does
Text to spread
They're moving in there setting up caliphates buddy
How about bread
Really nice people
We could probably let another one
Well then comes another really nice pic
Read the Koran folks one day
For lung cancer for lung cancer
Got it 3 times
70 some odd times
It says
Try to convert the infidel
Christmas thank you that we can grow Christianity
Crusade
America become cowardly
Dearborn Michigan
The Wacom app and Alex should we wake up
Community there declares itself a caliphate
Michigan
Think there's no way
Do you really believe we would take our
Government and Alex
Grab them out of there
Yeah probably
With Force leggings
It's not like we're new to the National Guard murder people
Take them out of the equation like
The government did what it had to do with like the Bundy Ranch
Wildlife Preserve
You suggested it admirable that they didn't all die so much now I respect you for that
Opinion
A lot of restraint
Because
The restraint I wish they afforded other people break
Write a hundred percent agree with that
His presentation
Just playing
Of course I would
Imply
Broken
Declared a Chris
Or what if
Livesay Dearborn Michigan
Headache
Huge Christian population
I have decided we are going to
Completely
The Theocratic
Christian
City
So do you mean just Dearborn
I got a lot of things
I keep sitting
How can is this
As if I don't
I don't get that.
The concept behind
Girl I'm clueless
I just Isaiah
I just genuinely believe
Human resources
Capable of
And I'm
And the worst part is over
We proved her wrong Embassy
F****** Epis
Yeah
There's no rationality
It's not
Nichols has a bunch of dumb-ass bulshit as he's
He's known to do on this
As is his
Yeah and play
Like he's in the wire is Marlo not there
My name is
Tyler Nichols then they play the documentary
Eclipse
It's just
Him talking about how like
To be taken down by Benghazi
But what's going to take her
Is the documents I have about Vince Foster
Murder
We have already covered
Him saying
That the document that he has murdered
Miraculously showed up in his mailbox
Address
I'm in the document proving that mother was Galileo
Yeah maybe
Maybe someone falsified that based on how you keep going on a right-wing radio shows
I got a Twitter DM saying it
True
But there's one moment of true comedy where he talks about how
I was involved
And then my dad got
Long
The video is him smoke
I don't know why he got lung cancer and probably some globalist
Cures for lung cancer is life-changing moment that he's describing is brought on by the thing he's doing
In the video
Crazy
Could be involved anymore what about if the drugs brought in my daughter was doing
Like with Larry Nichols was it really just
I'm kind of getting
F***** over and
Then realized
Yeah but it just realized
Do you have
Just talk
I don't like
I don't think he had any idea how well this is going to work out I think he was a bitter
Fictive dude
The piece of s***
And wasn't
Is
He was involved with
I'm not really sure what the circumstances were
But he was involved with the contras
Yeah like he was involved with like Ollie North and all them
That's why you got fired
From Clinton
So do you mean yeah
He wouldn't
He kept making collect calls
Nicaragua
And that's why you ended up getting
Cuz it was a completely traceable we haven't called
We have a call for you from
Will you accept the charges
Hang up I got no he's just going to complain about his dog sitting
But like that is he
Involved as a funk
Dictionary
I'm not entirely sure what other key
He had at that point that's very difficult
Betrayed
But I
He got fired he blamed bill for it
Event created this elaborate backstory
That has been shown to be
Mostly false
Repeat it
On
Bears repeating you haven't listened to all of our episode
He was on a right-wing radio showing
Claimed to be an assassin
Who killed people for hire
For the clintons he was their hired assassin
He said that on radio show
And then
When I was high on pills
When I was
That
The kind of person were talking about
Liar
Vince Foster killed
Yeah it was not a murder
Yeah the reason most people think it's a murder
Is because of this document
Yeah just mysteriously showed up in Larry Nichols
Does Rob Larry nickel
Drudge Report of their time
Yeah but like
Is it was moved
All that stuff
Zip Clinton
Sports Department
Department to take the murder
Navigation instead of that be
All that stuff comes from Larry Nichols and is there
I've seen the document that
Larry Nichols
Like I played it on the Alex Jones Show
Name Cran
It might as well have been
The late night
Portion of the 60
Now we get to the seven
The money by we are now we are now 24 hours into the money
And Alex Jones is trying to raise a million dollars
What kind of lunatic
You're looking
Goodnight part come on
Like I understand
I've watched
Involved
Why would you do that
I just don't know
What it is they think it's going to
If you do 8
27 hour Show versus
84 hour
Like tomorrow
Actually
Yes please
So much
Alex Jones knows full well
The only times are going to be making money ordering history
But
Maybe we get a couple thousand
Maybe we get a little bit of stragglers
Yes
Are you f****** work
Maybe some people
Big donation
Yeah so there's that there's just
We need to be
Off internet
On that on that like
It's a drain
And we got to catch as much as we ran
We got to make sure we're catching all that hay
What you want
Has money
You got to catch all of it
I'm not thrilled with this I love it I love it but it's the difference between
Using a thick or thin comb
You know like
Find count we got to get all the money out of this we can
Whole day
Someone'll TuneIn
A baby like
I love Liberty
Comparison
Like our usual like a or like or like with Jimmy Pardo
Like cherry
But exactly
0.0 is
We're going to
Continue to have a show
This is going to be something we're going to have these
They don't have many gas
Even if you're not interested for 2 hours
Like hey maybe you're a big fan of
Doug Benson Leo zagami
So you show up Joyce Brady
That would be
But but
Like other other
Marathon
Idea of life
And he does
Most marathons have Goodwill
You know what
Fair
Most marathons come from a place of we want to do good most of the time but they're doing
If it's you know Jerry's Kids
A park A Thon money for charity and they hope that things are entertaining
And I've watched
4 years in Boyle
Is not entertaining
The slog know they don't give a fuk
They Don't Really Care
It's just a
Marketing
It's not like this money is going to charity
Right clear the money is just going to
The things we already do
Already f******
Slapdash
And he's not even offering bugs
Do people like NPR.
Part out of it
He's just
It's just madcap desperation
So
When
But he ended his show
On the 6th
They had in the hundreds of thousands of dollars
Sprite
They were pretty well on their way
Here's where we
We start on the 7th
Here's where the finances are on the beginning
+ 500
60 something thousand dollars
We're just about to update
And the biggest one
Today
Dollars
$100
Thousand
Towards crew towards travel
Towards camera fobs towards editing
Sports reporters
Research cameras
But all the other stuff that he list
Stop it he's already doing
So like 8%
F*** we're 24 hours and we like $550,000
We're not making this million
Yeah I think there is a part of him that's realizing
Is not as potent as I want
Cuz a million dollars he's presenting
This entire lead up to it
It's not that much money
We're trying to run a media operation
He's milking
Don't he's trying to get blood out of a stone
All he's been able to do is
He ends with $700,000
Right around there
Which is 300,000
I'm short of their now granted that make their goal
Later
Darren Slater sales
So like
Thing that I think
Is that
At a certain point
He didn't need the money like I guarantee that
Half a million
But he wanted a million
Yeah until it became a thing where
Now it's not about money it's about
Cried it's about who am I it's about how much
And that's why you can hear a little bit of
Deflation
He expected to wake up
Desperation
Deflation exactly why
Exact
He expected to wake up in the goal be met
The show with Larry Nichols that are that documentary that everyone wants
Also it's like 28 30 minutes long
Disaster
F*** everyone should watch it though it's so bad
30 short
It's Larry Nichols smoking
Talent bulshit
You expected I'm going to I'm going to come in on the September 17th the end of Moneyball
And either it's going
Beware it 900,000
Are we just got to get the last push
Or were already there
Right and we're going to
Started
For 3.5 billion people we touch with our social
And I think he's starting to realize
He ain't got s*** right to what I was talking about
Right when he went there and did the Superman
With Hillary for prison shirt
And everyone in the f****** Arenas are for Trump
Recognized
Oh s***
Okay I think
That my premise
Bet the money bomb
Was
Money gets funneled in
I was wrong
But I
The disaster
Disaster is Billy Idol of $500
$7,000 I'd love that
But the
Disappointment of
How potent is audiences
Compared to
How Gloria
The reaction was
From
Trump audio
I think
That those two things Duhamel
Has him recognize
The real
Extent of his
Which is
700g
Which is not as good as he help
And you
Joe Biggs
Showing up at a trump rally
As a like
There is a whole new world
Right here
Yeah
But if we throw it
Very into some other weird
That's where we get into it
He thinks he's throwing in the Trump on
Top of it
As opposed to he's surrendering
I think it might be the beginning of it
That's really interesting
I'm not even listen to it
Damn hell knows what's going
I know every single time I've been certain of something crazy
There's no way he's a punk
Shut your fat mouth
Holy
Maybe when I put that I was like
Well maybe he never gets on the Trump trade at all forgetting the world that we live in now
Saladworks
Itech
I was like
This investigation is so f***** up
How the f*** did he say now
Here's worth shitt get Center
Yes
The debate
The Republican debate
Who's on the 6th
The 2nd
The night of the 6th
Mystery Science
Peter debate
Thing all the Alex Wilson Auto Part
So much fun
Cell phone
Then they really took down monosa had the
Not libertarian enough Alex
Get to respond
And so now we're going to enter
Little bit of
Little bit of debate recap
Here's Alex Jones highlights
Of last night's debate
Does Planned Parenthood
This is also based on all the Center for Medical progress videos
Of course of course videos
I've cutouts
So much of Alex complaining about that stuff
Because it's just so boring we don't need to cover it over and over again
Anybody references
Screws
In the context of a phrase that doesn't
And with
Loftus
Covering
Center for Medical
He is talking about
Legal
Regal
Bacon
Right
I live baby
Hold on
As long as the baby is touching the mother
They can cut it up
Then cut up
But if the baby stop
Touching the mother
No no
No I refuse to even believe that even the most irrational of human beings
What except
Crazy
For September 17th
About Red Rover situation
Okay heading up baby Planned Parenthood
But it may
I think it was
September 2015
The Congressional investigation started
Into the video
Now because we're in the future we know they cleared them of any wrongdoing
And found and all those videos
The deeply manipulated and edited poorly
Not appropriately they've been sued it's really f***** up
Since we've started
Like the court
K-Swiss still in motion
Like
Jeff the last week
Yeah bunch of those charges
We have said in the past
15 felonies that are being
Put on them
Yeah bunch of those charges got dropped
Like last week
Yeah I know
Why do we
I don't know but it does
A lot of it comes down to technicalities
And it just comes like I can't
Is it worth Prosecuting this further
You get you get somebody on
Tax evasion
Murdering
Everybody you've ever
Every investigation into whether these videos are full of s***
Have shown
Beverly
And Alex loves
Yeah
Bush
Just 40 years ago you smoke marijuana I admitted big deal
Donald Trump
And he's ugly
Trump
You look pretty goofy to me
Which I don't think looks goofy but I guess you can say it looks Goofy from your perspective you look like
Blond possum on your head
Then it was
You get your hair bleached
But
Agree
Believable
Is unbelievable
Where he talks about the fact that this is a country where we speak English
Alex
Not great
Pretty solid
Super unexpected
Oh man you know that three months after this point
Trump is on Alex's show
Yeah
That's so funny
What is going on
I don't know
How do you not negotiate
Hear me out
Here's what I think
I think
The payment hasn't
Clear
Do you think the check hasn't cleared
Like he's in Dorsett but he still like
Why do you
Why do you think he's surprised to wake up in this 500000
Okay
Why do you think he's disappointed he's mad
Because he hasn't
And he thinks that the movement
The check if I can't tell how much of what I
I'm just trying to make sense of this s*** I love it so crazy want you to be right
But that
Too far but it's nonsense even it like take all of that
Cuz I don't think that
Timing the s*** about Trump
Absolute
Take my nonsense out of it
Before that
He can
Be
F*** you shut your mouth
You're a punk
Whatever
Oh you're mad at Rand Paul askew
About your appearance
I suck your dick please
Within 3 months
He's crazy
Yeah no
That once he becomes Trump's cheerleader
He don't think that all this still exists on the internet
Established he has no concept
Movie ideas that like all that like stuff like every time we gone through
Alex Jones says this now in defensive
We go back and we have a clip of him
Everything Trump has ever said we have a twin
Are you are different steroids
They don't care
It's
Nobody is actually holding them accountable
Which is the biggest we can go on Twitter and we can see people going like
Here's what they said here's what they used to say
But nobody's actually f******
We're trying and I don't know what to do we're trying
I wake up everyday and I don't know what
To do dad
I can't tell you but we're trying
We got a couple more clips
That we're trying to do a fundraiser
So
The fact that Alex has been very
Free pro-russia
Pro strongman pro-putin
Not necessarily
Pro-russia
No that's not fair
Pro-russian pro-assad
He has been brought before the strongman
The things you said
Pro-russia
You're right
Angry
This next clip brings
Play don't like
Because of al-Qaeda
Yuma government
Essentially is saying
On the wrong side of everything is on the right
But how
What what
We have funded
Created
Al-Qaeda and Isis
Destabilize
Because of that
We are on the wrong side of everything
Russia
Just trying to destroy the forces
That we've brought in their forties
And
I just don't get that very simplistic
Argument
Because there's a dump in the same way that
In the same way that there's a
Kernel of truth to it
That is also such a
Wilfred
Mister
Misunderstanding of the way that the world works
It's hard to imagine
Totally
River of Russia
Cool
What's the motivation
For him being in favor of a son
Russian propaganda
He's a tease
These beholding to RT and Sputnik
Information
I mean yeah you make the good point of him
As as
Affirmations
But
If you put out
Stories about
No cuz
Didn't get the things that you will say
About Islamabad
Being oppressive tased
Yeah
Notarized
Is that
Is western-backed
Rebel forces
That are faking
That is the narrative that's their name yes yes
And that's
These people on who are
Disreputable sources
Yeah I can't resent Ambassador guy who he had on
Who acts clear Financial
If you're Russian
Yeah and you are on
Media of
Probably have time
The oligarch
With
A couple exceptions
Yes absolutely
That is the narrative that Alex
He's on board
Seems
Dumb
James Wilde but that
That's that's what he pushes
It's every single thing
Something do that
Like I
Arguing other Russian
But its side
So very
Clearly
Set out to murder his own
Here's where it seems like such a
First thing all over again
Like are you for Hitler murdering Jews or against
That's what a son is to
Is that Obama said the redline is using gas
Using gas tax on
How many didn't
Clearly
Is more
Proud moments
Sending the world
Agree
But
Alex's and all the Russian media's argument about that is
Why the f*** would do that if Obama said that was a red line
Why would they
Okay
That which is compelling interesting angle yeah I agree
People if you don't
Obama invited
Okay so the end result legitimately is World War
So what
What
Who is Obama
Sorry
Dancing
And if Obama knows that
Doesn't
Get in there and f***
Burn the ships
To the ground
That must be
All Sonos
It's a
False flag
And also before
Putin had made clear that he was not going
Except
Any of our aggression in Seattle
It is a much more complicated
Disturbed
Russian propaganda
I'm not saying that he's an agent
Call my calls
Why would you even need him
To be in Asia
Russia
If you have this kind of weird
Attention
Man foreign policy is tux
I don't know
I don't know if you know that's enough
But Global foreign policy
Barry comp
I'm a walk
Very complex
Entirely clear
Ouija
We've made a lot of mistakes
In terms of Armin Rebel
And stuff like that
You know me I'm pronation
About to be lit on fire right now
If you are a knowledge fighter
And you are within
3 ft of Assad and
You can light him on fire
Please light him on fire
Just make them hot for a little bit
Burn him to death
If he survives your lighting him on fire
Lighting a bonfire
10 more times
Eminem
Memes
Alex alright
I'm done
Who want some guy that
Job 2
Cheese brother two guys
Yeah Alex Jones offered a job to the first and second
Can play sky
But here was the f****** awesome
Like
I'm so
Cuz I don't have the clip with it
Yeah
Houston Mary's like
I told Paul Joseph Watson you got the
Ivan
Part 1
Hit me up you got a job please
I want to walk with you Braveheart Braveheart
David Wallace
I told my boss if he could choose the winner
You got the $20,000 that they saw honor band 4 has to do together
Yeah
Of course so the winner was
Okay
Of course
I'm going to give you three guesses
And now considers in mythology
How are you talk about false realities
No
That one more
Obvious
All other Mel Gibson
No but it should be obvious
Come on
You got this
Infowars
A Scanner Darkly like I don't know.
Matrix
I know that you can't even
That was made by trans women
You don't get this
Agent Smith
They're shooting at Neo down the hallway J stops
The bullet bullet
Intuit
And is offered both
Snow
Play The Weeknd play me more
That is a
Pizza bowls
Anyway
We got to get these last two clips app
We're on our 7th a half
Jordan
The debate
Yes
Alex mentioned
A little bit earlier
Good thing
And the debate right
Now one of them was that people speak English not Spanish
I didn't like that
Set them up
But Alex did
Fan
They're not
Donald Trump
Coming out
And he knows the system's going to come after him
What's going on
He doesn't want to be involved
What is removing health
Autoimmune disorders
Carson a medical doctor surgeon
Virologist
Future sister-in-law
Because he's a good guy
In in the debate debate
Trump talked about how
When he had kids
He's spaced-out the VAC
Cuz he thought that like
I've heard a bunch recently
Which is
True at all
No and then
I don't want to put too fine
The point on this
And where are you 4 hours
Podcast but like
I've looked into all of it
All of the anti-vax stuff
Pitbull
It's going to Wakefield
Sense8
Create
One guy
Got a f****** thing happened to him
Within two weeks of a vaccine news like
Well vaccine
It is always
F****** b*******
I can't
To deal with how much
I hate you
If you're an anti vaxxer
Legitimately by one
That is one of the most
Importance
In terms of
Statistics
That correlation
Does not imply causation
Something
But there is a
Slight relation to
You can't say
Because there's a relation
That explains why
Nuggets
If you can't
Correlation does not equal causation
Exist
The fact that it is
True
Almost there
Possible foremost
Right
The most
Destructive force
One of the biggest
Cases about
And Alex Jones talks about
You know like in the UK
Is this guy named Andrew Wakefield
Starting
Were called into question
And he got
Fired
Because it turned out he was taking
Enough money
Animal lawyers
License was revoked
There were lawyers who were trying to get a class-action lawsuit going
People who hate texting
And he got like four
From those players
People
Find
In the past
Knowing that
Terry
OSHA
Are you saying that when you get in
When you get
Money involved with
Healthcare bad things
Special
Can't believe it
Inclusions
Free market
Prosperity
Anyway
I was pretty thrilled with that
Zach Smith
Honestly think we totally clear
I think that no matter what happened
Internet debate
Alex would find something
The love
About
Yeah yeah
I think it's in this timeline
Is the
I do
He fixated on
Like now I
I want, want to go back and watch that debate
Sissy
How many things
Trump said that he
Would have
Agreed with versus
Did
I have no idea I did go back and look into
Stivax
So f****** hot water like 3 months
For this
And
He hasn't answered vax history that goes back
Like 2,000
Situation
This isn't news
This is just he cited a debate
Right position is like
He's going to be attacked
For this
But he had been attacked for it already
He's pretending this is some sort of like
New character
Widgets not
I honestly
No I don't think this has
Campaign it hasn't been all about
It hasn't it hasn't been all about
Hey he didn't start that
He's
Belt
So I think
I think if there's a little bit of manipulation
I'm going on
Maybe 4 episodes back
When he made his pivot
Stop talking
S*** about Trump
In terms of his
Yeah I went back and I did deep research
And if you have done
That she would already know that he has
A history of being anti-vaccination right hasn't been not that for
Right
So this
Isn't that the truth
Such a luxury for rich
Oh my kids go to schools where
Everybody has been vaccinated
So I don't have
And they're not pregnant
Also that this this
Version of ants
EFax
Where's
I spaced it out / 6
Years f******
F*** you
Light on
I've established
I think pretty
Consistently
But if your anti-vax
I hope you kill yourself
And then kill your children
That seems hard
No that's a good order
Well we all know that Arts
Still with us
Yeah and this is Alex
I guarantee a Donald Trump his friend
Vaccine
Donald Trump presidential
Composition of Liberty
Now we have come to our only place
Yeah we
We've narrowed it down
Cuz he loves Rand Paul he will
Very soon
Humiliated
Cruise
Yeah
The biggest b****** machine
For Donald Trump
Which is funny
But but that is the one that is the one true Joy
Cruise
This
Is
Like
I don't know how to say it
I was right
My argument so what you're saying is that we began this episode with Dan being right
And we ended it with Dad but I think I'm right
Not the way I expected
Is II predicted earlier
When Alex
Lexus
To trump it will be superficial it'll be
It'll be about
He already
It's not like
It's not new it's not new
Yeah sort of done
But he's not the cheerleader
He's still just saying these three guys
Liberty Canada
He's narrative.
Yeah
Riches
Already f***** up enough
Yeah like the candy
I don't understand
How it is that he
Professes to be
Libertarian
Theoretically nonpar
And yet at the same time
Every anime
Is leftist
Damn every every
Beer
Comes from
Inclusion
Every
Here Comes
Who's from
Any kind of like
We should all be part of the same world now his professed ideology
In that
The the globalists are trying to keep
Inclusion but he knows that it's a globalist
Plot
Like
He talks about a couple times
I already need sunlight
Bass f****** ding dong
A******
To me it seems like he would wind up coming down
Sanders
No
Ventura is like
Sanders or Rand Paul
That's what Ventura is he does Ventura has a philosophy as an ideological consistency
Alex
Believe
Really
I honestly think what we're coming to
What I've learned
From listening to
These pants
Like three weeks
For two weeks that we've covered
He is a
Harsh
Opportunist
He wants his money
And I think
He realized
When we write the screenplay for our documentary
It will be the
The tagline is
Alex Jones
He wants his
Earlier that
Are being thing where it's like
He's trying to get
Mercer
Trump to try and come in as big-money donors may still be the case
But
I think
He started the million
$10 campaign
Like as not having
In the meantime we've recognized Joe pigs went out there
And everyone wanted that shirt yeah
How do we rationalize
We rationalize it
There was a debate last night
He said something if you vaccination that he said Eddie Ray
Now it's like
F***
We soft kill babies
That he's against
Maybe
What kind of
Farias
Coronavirus
That's a good point
It means
In order for us to
Like
I guess it's
I guess it's more like
I feel like
We need a scoop
Like I feel like maybe nice
We need some kind of
But if it's
Just wind up being weird shity
Opportunism
It bums
I think some sort of Mercer money sort of like
Third-party donors like
Alright now I direct
Used to be the gold
But now it's
Chevron
Take solace in
Knowing that
No one
Has done
As much
Listening to his show as we have
We do have
Whatever
Even if it isn't
Set the Mercers are the ones who did it
Trump money
There's a scoop here
Cuz
He didn't
Care about Trump
Before
And now he's
Is it
Antivaxer
He's he's all over the place
When he becomes
These
6 2.0
A guy
Going to be
It's not because of
It's not because of things Trump said 5 years ago
Well that's
That's the thing that gets
Is that it
Seems like right now
Now he's
He's going off of
Says
Like he's going off of things that truck
Like Trump says something I like so I
Trump says I don't like so I don't say nice
Trump said something alike
Like that's the problem that I have
It should be something that is
Consistent
And until we
Assistant
It just seems like he's
Bollocks
Yeah you're a dumb dumb there's never going to be
There's never been
No that's fair I've never going to be point with Alex
I still live in this world
I still live in the world
I believe people believe in things and Alex
You know what you know what that's why you're right about that
Is that
Be consistent argument
Is always people believe
And Alex doesn't have a beliefs
Valentine Alex has
And then we move
These Rogue he's completely Rogue
All right. It doesn't matter to move on
Story
They got to get a bunch of
Publicity out of calling Tom Marla p****
Right and no one on their side knows that they canceled the fight
It just didn't happen
Vacancy
He was involved with e
Courtney
Yeah
It doesn't matter it doesn't matter perception is King
All that's bulshit
Everything is b*******
Anyway
Will be back with the next
Stage of this investigation
Chip I don't want
Interesting with so far
To this
Circumstance
Been buried
The actual things that are happening in the administration
Scaramucci's
That's because Sean Spicer was a
Deep state agent
Hayward
Using do if
Did get into like
Like
Who would get him inside information
How do you die
Was working
By the way this week
Bananas
This week as this episode comes out
Junior may have to show up
Lieutenant
Manafort
So we'll see
Of course
No they're going to be pardoned
But if you don't want to be pardoned you should go to our website I don't know
No I refuse that transition
Reject slightly buzzed activity on the word Ridge
You want to reject something on the website
Check it out
Start the show
And let me tell you something
How many people have started report
How many of you have become policy thank you all so much
How important it is to us
And if you are not a policy wonk
And you would like
To be click on that button
And you will kill Jeff
What hold on hold on
You will be granted access to
Now it's 10 episodes
Want you to think me and Marty DeRosa
Conspiracy theory podcast
Little bonus for you're a smarty friend of the showing
And there are other episodes that will be added eventually once I find him in my art Drive
I have an external hard drives that has other
We'll figure it out
But
Twitter is at knowledge underscore fight and we're on Facebook
Alright
Why this
Entire after they did that last episode
Intriguing
Is it diarrhea
Episode 18 on Facebook like I said
There's something about their algorithm where if you give us like
Stars
Indeed
Apologize this episode has been
Jesus Christ, we are at 4 hours
Not true
Jesus Christ
Really we've not breach
The Joe Rogan was the closest I think it's closed
Discover 24
I think if you would not
Disrupt as me so many times
Don't pretend
I was going to make this episode 4 hours no matter what have
A good time
You are ruining the ending
UFO
This one guy
What
Who is he
The younger the older
It's really old really old
Anti AIDS
Yes what about
The end of the night
Okay
The bathtub it has gone so far
He said he was going to the bathroom
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color