Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Acknowledge
Dot-com
Alex Jones
Jordan
Walmart
But that is that this week of the world lost the bad guy
Oh yeah Scott hall pass away I read about that
Not necessarily right about that
He died but
He was a wrestler who I was always
Very very
Exciting
I was grew up at just the right time
I watch wrestling in in such a way that
That
The WCW and the NWO
The Scott Hall is a part of
That was that was the era when I watched
Wrestling I had like two years where I was a wrestling fan so yeah I remember
Spiders coming in and invading WCW
Shows up and everybody went with Everett.
My parents didn't let me watch wrestling when I was a kid to the resort of that forbidden aspect to it
And
That made that made everything a little bit more a little bit more sneaky little contraband
And I'll go over to my friend's house and we would watch it it's lit sleepover
His place so we can watch like
Monday Night Raw and WCW Nitro
And said that there was an anarchic element
To the like
The invasion of the NWO Scott Hall
Chatters the cool one
Cool
He was a henchman
Through-and-through I think he thought he was cool
God always cool and scary
Follow blindly some a****** probably
Many fond memories of
Watch
Watching him work
And
Rest in peace
Strangely that vibrates but not
Better
However still somewhat nostalgic so if you remember Adult Swim Toonami
When they used to run anime all the time
Not really so
They are bringing back
Fooly Cooly
Zero idea
Describe fully Cooley to you on at least for occasion one ear out the other salute
Two people okay
There's a giant iron
Sometimes it turns into a manga fully Cooley might just mean rubbing tits together nobody knows anyways
The important part is that a woman hits a man in the face with a Rickenbacker Bass
And Mack has come out of it that they then have to fight the unit
Obviously
This is a coming-of-age tale about a young boy experiencing
I look forward to hearing about this for the first time for the fifth time in the future if I have no idea what you're talkin about
It is also one of the if not the maybe greatest anime series of all time
I feel like my reference point for Adult Swim is like when it was just
Sealab Aqua Teen Hunger Force
2 hours later you got Gundam Wing you got Dragon Ball Z German you got it all buddy
That's the s***
I'm glad
Good for you
Over today
Little bit of a break
Recording is on Thursdays I'm not sure if he actually got back to
Studio today or whatever but
To the present day on Monday
But for now we are back
Still
In the in the present or the past
I made today with tray
Delightful little bit of a request
Time travel episode
Birthday next weekend to celebrate
Rocky's Auto refund press to go back
And enjoy Alex Jones is 40th birthday and so we are going to be
About February 11th
2014 Ono
Alex's
40th birthday old man comes up once on the show but it's his birthday one time
Very weird
That this is what
Only a few months away from the invasion of Caribbean
It doesn't come up
Don't worry about that no witchery on that aspect
I am Richie but my powers are limited
Two to some degrees
Happy birthday Laurel after birthday to Alex
When's his birthday
Probably around the same
First Galaxy thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
The Galaxy
The Dutchman is called the Dutchman if he isn't.
I think that was about Rik Smits
Next I went beyond the consciousness of God and all I got was this stupid t-shirt thank you so much
I think that was about
Probably
Text Robert Lexus
It's not about rex that was not robbed
I'm a policy wonk
The doctor occupied Texas
You're not a policy wonk
Y'alls
Alright so this is weird just drop
Cold we don't really know what's going on
Records deepen Alex's pass
He's a very different broadcaster
It's kind of interesting to get this
Between points
Is pre Trump
Right
We haven't even figured out the four ways to learn
No he's being cagey about that but there is a list of episode
Not ways to learn okay I'll be a bit later in the episode
Here is my contacts drop though
From pleasure
Highways
Makes it hurt when Alex PU
Product
What makes it hurt when he pees
No no other iodine
He's selling
They made the
Doesn't hurt when you pee iodized
Or
Alex
Had syphilis
It's for a while to speculate necessarily
I also I will admit there is a failing in my research and that is that I didn't look into it
To see if it's a common side-effect died on the first one I just think it's a weird
I didn't look into it either I just
Gonorrhea
So here is a
Restart am to Alex is on one right at the job
One more time
I can do whatever I want
Walking along
Doesn't
What is it Obama
Accepting a state visit from then French president Francois
Thomas Jefferson
At Monticello
When he said that they were breaking protocol.
To go to
The terrorist to look at the view which wasn't part of the plan tonight
Of course because Obama joke about I was the president do whatever he wants Alex deadly seriously
The other post am joking around about
Not sticking to the bullet points of
Fitoor
Ridiculous
Oh man
Wasn't it wasn't weird when the
The president had like
An actual sense of humor that was not even
Not just
Like a solid sense of humor but at times it quite
You don't like with that or how did writing staff he
Crusted on those little things right there and then
Time do we say like
Do the Mexican you're going to kill you you know like that was a good president for a while
And there's an interesting aspect the pettiest
Complained
Being blown into like
Haha you admits he's a dictator
That's it that's how shity
It was too
It was to be a right-wing
Winger like s******* all over Obama's you had to be like
Look at it
F****** suit
Stance
Slipped
When
Trump becomes president Alex accuses everyone else is doing the same game
Absolutely was not tax rate over 100% in France
Hanson 2014
The highest tax Band in their system is on people who made over 150 1000
Some two hundred euros a year
And any income above that point was taxed at a rate of 45
Holland heads tried to usher in an experiment where business
Is the pay salaries over a million euros per year
Would have to pay a 75%
Payroll tax
But it was widely unpopular and it wasn't continued after the two-year timetable
It was put in place
Experiment
I frequently see this being reported as a tax on people who make more than
A million euros a year but that isn't
True
That was the original
Content of Holland
But it was Dean
Punitive by the Congressional Court
Has thrown out
Has it ever existed for two years this was a payroll tax imposed on businesses
Not on the middle class
And it wasn't over a hundred percent
Looking back it's interesting to see who the guardian describes as putting the
Dakota nail in the coffin on this tack
That honor goes to a young upstart who just become France's economy minister
Emmanuel
Macron
Surprised to hear Alex
Text liking macron for stuff like this back though
CDs are these villains in there
In doing things that he would support like on the way to be
Becoming the villain that he hates to
Like it is if Alex had jumped on early
Maybe we'd all be in a different place
Probably not
Doubtful there's threesome trends
That are going on
In 2040
I think I might have
Discovered hipsters
Women's
AR
What
That's Obama's fault I don't understand what the problem here is really stupid
Good thoughts disorder being woven together
What are things that I think is really fascinating about this is the way that Alex doesn't seem to take as much
The people dressing like hobos
The man
Women are attracted you should be f****** me
Big and loud
What if it does
It does seem like
The complaint is largely directed at women for being attracted to the thing Alex doesn't want them to be
Are they must be being brainwashed by the TV which is under the direction of
Obama
I don't want to listen
And I don't want
To say that people can't wear skinny jeans in the
Comfort of their own home I'm just saying
Don't put it on my TV until women to be attract
Do it sir I understand
Assertive intellectually this
This generational
Confusion about Aesthetics
Right
I don't understand why you got to get so mad about it how far away from the 40 year-old virgin our way
Probably quite a ways
No idea
All movies happened I don't want to ruin it but there was effect
On this episode about a movie
That is similar to what you're experiencing
Forty-year-old virgin I believe
We'll get to that when we get to it alright
Pronounce Alexei
Gunn fear story
Headline
AOL
Pretty rose version came out in 2000
Close close
So this clip Alex is talking about a guy named Mark
Witness app
I was just going to leaving at 7:40
For instance why was this guy's house search
Obviously the police were there you know
Did they weren't there just trying to seek out and
Empty shotgun
Michelle there must have been a reason for them to be there
Little suspicious
What's going on here
So when is Shaq was going through divorce
Since 2012 and his estranged wife
Complain to the police on multiple occasions that he had threatened her with a gun
This led to police visits during both of which they found illegal ammunition in his possession
The items found in the first visit weren't able to be brought to the case
The police didn't have a war
The Winneshiek did that consent to a search of
His house
Do I throw it out
In DC only
People with registered guns
Can possess ammunition
So the shotgun shell along with a box of Muzzleloader bullets
Cyber problem
Kendama
Ultimately he ended up getting sentence
What's the time served being on firearm registry and getting a 50
Dollar fine
I want all this probably seems like a bit of an overreaction and a waste of people's time but ultimately
Probably good that the allegations of
Threats of murderous domestic violence were taken seriously
The ones alleged by witaschek
Xy4 often ignored and they lie
Lead to tragedy
Seems like a rare case where police acted
There's something to be said for that
Yeah this wasn't
Actually the big
Biggest problem that would assure
Jack had to worry
Also is part of the Fallout from his divorce his ex-wife provided DC officials with
Some tax documents about which affects business-related look good
You got in some Rob
Double effect
Anyway the point here is that there's more
Stories in the way Alex's report
It's important when you're doing these kinds of gun martyrdom presentations that you present the central character is being as blameless
This is possible
There's no room for nuance
That's because you need to be black and white
Open and shut case where the persons having the guns taken
In for no reason
And the states actions are solely motivated by a tyrannical desire to take everyone's guns
That's why when Alex
Does decide to touch on why the raid happened
Here's how he puts
There was a disgruntled family member dropped a dime
Estranged wife in the middle of an ugly divorce
Who allegedly threatened her multiple times with a gun
Recognizing
Wecast too much of a shadow on this story in wrist
Smarter not look as blameless as he needs to look for this kind of narrative to work
You want to deal with the realities of this stuff
Away
No way
You can't you can't let your audience know that this guy was both confused of threatening his wife with a gun on multiple occasions
That's why the police band with the first place seems like they should take his guns away
I mean it's it's at the point where the real lesson of stories like they should be that gun shouldn't be outlawed
It should be outlawed for men to have guns and women should have to hold a gun pointed toward the man's face and every interaction
Because this is f******
I mean obviously there's another serious
Proposing I don't know I don't think it's a terrible idea
I think
In in the real world
The fact
That's
An allegation
Like this was made of like
You know this
5 my ex-husband
Threaten me with
The fact that you do end up taking it seriously
Pay a visit
Totally
I think things
Appropriately
Maybe it's not that big of a deal but he has a box of muzzleloading bullets
Maybe that's not
Maybe that is
Fitting to just be like
Hey here's a $50 fine
And this is going to go in a record because
You know on the off-chance
Someone else says
You threatened him with a gun we can now established
And well I mean I wrecked
Recognize that
I'm just so you know
But the level of
Men having every Edition inside their homes with guns
And then getting a divorce
Violin
Violent
You know
Intersection of masculinity and guns
I want to be living in Alex's nightmare
So are in a sex club Alex has something that I
Wish you would talk more about
This clip is why Alex's show suck
He's introduced a very bizarre position about
The relative evilness of past governments at Empire
This is the extent of his conversation about it
How you equip like that and all I want is more
It's like what countries are in the 20% that weren't total evil.
What's the differentiating factor between them
It seems like this is
The conclusion he's pretending to reach after deep research so I want
Hear about what he's learned
But instead I mean was latitude
Really it's just an expression of Alex's opposition to the idea of government
Though he's too cowardly to be an anarch
Yeah
Yeah I mean
Okay
Okay let's
Let's just go down the f****** listman
Alright bad government
Versus
Not too radical government
0 BC
The Romans
They do I don't know though
There's a part of me that worries
That it's
Governments that were headed by people Alec
Dwight
There's a part of me that worries that that's it
That would be about 20% of the government's he's aware of
You throw in the United States government in there
Whaleyville
Sirenita Howell
Nothing like the
The 50s I mean he's not willing to throw the Nazis in there is one of the good 20% just yet
Probably not as of 2014
I don't know but the fact that he doesn't elaborate on it just drives me nuts
It makes me mad
I want to know I'm interested in I thought that he doesn't give me that thought I would you say 80%
Is there something you're basing that off of is estimation
Basic that office you read research
Reading so much about history
How many zero million
Governments in history
I just want some
How come you don't get
So the National Guard is
Out-of-pocket
Haha
To generate
The movie
America home cooler
Michigan
Story we talked about
10:10
But I'd hold off on that road
The stories that Alex is talking about
Beginning of this cliff
Inspiring all of this is out of Portsmouth Ohio the Ohio Army National Guard
Civil support unit
In conjunction with local First Responders held a drill where the
The scenario was quote
Two School Employees were disgruntled over the government's interpretation of the Second Amendment
Glock to use chemical biological and radiological agents against members of the local
Local community
The motivation behind the specific scenario was to maintain awareness that
Not all terrorism is 4in base
And the domestic terrorism doesn't
That's that's the reason I use that as part
Scenario
I want to let something really interesting slip towards the end of that clip though
He seems that all the training exercises use right-wing 2nd Amendment supporters as the villains and their scenario because this is
Is about training the police and the public.
Look at them is evil terrorist
But then Alex admits that he only knows about the exercises with parents freak out in
Sue
I wasn't anything about the
This topic except the cases that he's he's reported in the media that
Consumes
He reads exclusively extreme right-wing news sources and they only report on these training exercises when there's an opportunity
To create right-wing victimhood narrative
The image that
Alex gets from the media he consumes is that every or almost every exercise
Involves brand
Ending Patriots as terrorists
That's not true at all
A ton of the scenarios at the National Guard groups do every year at to do the natural disasters where there's not even a human villain Envy
But beyond that if you go through their press release archive you can find plenty of examples
From the timeframe that Alex is talking about he or even that don't fit his mold
In August 2013 the New York National Guard ran it scenario
Exercise where they had a chemical Fallout but it wasn't
Any terrorism
Is cousin accidental train derailment
I would probably
Didn't hear too much about that or how
People are scared
In July 2013 the North Carolina National Guard didn't exercise that was based on training their rapid
Response team
And involve dealing with protesters who were having a sit-in at a water treatment
Facility
The fake protest group they had that one was called The Pink Panthers and they were very much coded as a left-wing order
Organization
I was probably didn't see that reported and drugs
And so he doesn't
Don't know it exists
In 2014 the South Carolina National Guard than exercise called objective
Indigo which had to do with terrorist groups taken hostage
But they weren't right-wing Patriot gun owner groups or anyting
Another example is the yearly exercise that northcom run
Vibrant response
Fox where a simulated nuclear attack happen
9 First Responders bracket
Responding
The things that are like
Take me to come up
And that scenario
Leaving usually
I need for a specific person or group behind the bombing
Because the focus is on the
Immediate response like
Dealing with the wounded
No real need for a larger
Storyline
Cuz I had a villain
The more flavor
Necessarily always
Alex is perception it
Very well may seem like every scenario bass exercise that law enforcement or the National Guard does involves
Maligning people like himself
Perception isn't based on real
In only extreme right-wing news where the only time he ever
Here's a story reported about
Scenario training exercises
If someone crying bloody murder about how is fictitious right-wing domestic terror group is part of the exercise
Question
All the other ones
Scenarios based on natural disasters are accent
Scenarios where the thread is a left-wing group
Scenarios where the villain is Ananda
Foreign terror group
All of these don't exist and Alex's reporting because
He doesn't know or doesn't
Don't care they exist
The media that he's taking and drives home the message
He wants to hear
Repeat
And solidifies that message to his audience
As if it's the product of research
When it's just
Regurgitating
Bulshit
But he skimmed on drugs
Sure I mean at the same time there is another option which is
That
It has been an immensely effective strategy
Even the slightest
Fictional hint
Of Gunn
Ownership being
Question
Shrek bloody murder as loud as you possibly can like
The mayak document was so reasonable and and
Borderline restrained of life
That kind of thing and Dave
Freak the freak out over
But even the slightest notion and its effect
Because it's kept us from
I mean it's illegal to study
How many people have
How many people cops
Till everyday you know like
Illegal
They're good at
Yeah and I think I actually even in this next clip Alex
Kind of expresses the similar thing that you're talkin
I'm about this idea of like we have to make a f****** huge deal out of everything
Stop playing that clip Obama wasn't in France he was at Alex's buddy Thomas Jefferson
Alex
Second president is
He's like a Wi-Fi hotspot in francophone
Mentality there like we got to make a big deal out of everything
People wrecking
Pig noises
There's a point to
Crazy it's so crazy listening to him freak out about it after the 6
Swear you're like
Yeah man
Also it's funny to to be like
Listen to this music is the most dangerous time in American history is like
Alright
Wait a few years bud
I would go back to 2014 and I'll heart
Just finish it
To spend my time
Teaching his dumb argument about
Cartoon
Debbie mcmoore
Fun than the reality of the world
The that
Covers now
So I think that clip also illustrate something really strange and Alex's world
Deep desire to impose harsh
Censorship on people who don't agree with
Watch the short-lived and not very well received the Green Lantern animated series he's talking about but
I know well enough that
The premises
Of the character and I know that the villains in it weren't
Can Amendment Patriot types aware tri-corner
I mean unless they were all yellow
Could be red lantern
Coats
You got that fifth wheel alignment
But it landed call me
Anyone you walk away from that's a good joke sullenberger of jokes
Wasn't pretty but we got talent
I would guess that there's like one episode of that show where some villain of the week is similar enough to Alex's militia weirdo ID
I mean calamity
Attack on him
And this is
Completely unacceptable
Alex
Anytime
The characteristics he Associates with himself or used to depict a villain and a shield
Secretly the government Pre-K
Programming the people to be against him
It's basically
So what's the solution to that
I guess the only thing that makes sense for Alex do support would be making a rule that villains and TV shows and cartoon the books
Movies of any characteristics
That make them similar to right-wing
Extremists are Gunn and militia weirdo absolutely not they can only be the hero right otherwise it's government otherwise
Like censorship really
Casino depicting characters
It's not a creative at
Actor function speech
Premeditated attack by the globalist
Alex just wants the global
To stop at
Hacking him
And the only way that could be done is by
Banning any negative to picture
Obviously stupid when the emperor has no clothes
You kill anybody who says you don't have any clothes
Is it makes perfect sense
Story is dumb what should have happened
When is the emperor's people should have just
Killed that kid
And then everybody else would have been like
You're right you do have
Gray close Buddies
Who's all this Salt Lake
Free scripting
Right
Alex
It makes a terrible terrible metaphor
What
Kebab planted
The drugs
I guess another explanation for knowing where Bill is keeping his cocaine is because
I don't know let's just say the bill doesn't daily radio show where he works really hard to scare the s*** out of his audience
I think kind of poke them closer and closer to thinking the baby keeping their cocaine in a certain place
Is the solution to all their problems
Maybe bill is a weird track record of denying the people like
Himself or capable of
Keeping their cocaine in
The specific location
And that anytime there's any
Clear instances of someone like him station cocaine
In that specific location it was a globalist setup
Maybe at that point Bob
The keep is cocaine in that location
I mean strong suspicious
Maybe Bob decided to listen to the same radio show and bought
The same book where to hide your cocaine
This is kind of a larger point of some of Alex's ship
You would love to ban all criticism of people like
Himself but because that's just not possible and his brain doesn't really allow him to openly active advocate for that
These TV shows get used
To preemptively.
Declare that anyone who is similar to Alex has similar beliefs to Alex
Possibly enjoys Alex's work
Anyone like that music
Committing a violent Act
Is just a global a setup to make Alex
The Patriots look
That's why they did the TV shows that begin with so they could pull off his
Furnishing of Alex's character
Quartz very little payoff when you could tarnish his character just by listening to a stupid show
It's smart of Alex to do stuff like this though particularly at this point because
A few months after this episode is recorded
Jared and Amanda Miller to Big Infowars
Killed three people
Including two cops
In Las
In May 2012 Jared written post on Infowars
Website board previously
But they're on this message
He posted a blog post
What's the title
The police
To kill or not
2 kill
Or you just got to being on probation for selling weed
Using difficulty in his life and was particularly concerned with the idea that the police would show up to his house for a search
Most likely because he was not allowed to own guns
Had a lot of guns
Hippo strongly mirrors a lot of Alex's ideas to
I do not wish to kill police
I understand that most of them believe they're doing the right thing
Yet I will not go to jail because I have not committed a crime
I would rather die than be labeled as a criminal
Let them call me a terrorist let them label me a fanatic some Nut Job
I know the truth and so does God
I'm sure our founding fathers were labeled as such
Call me a radical
Because America is a radical idea
There's worse.
They were Terror
Peter points from Alex's documentaries is an out-of-context dropping someone at a government seminar saying the founding fathers were terrorists
Which Alex uses a claim that the government hates anyone who believes in the Constitution
And that message
Is echoed in this guy's post
The post itself concludes quote
It is our duty as American
Can citizens to stand against tyranny
The stand against corruption at all levels
How did this happen
The Patriots like me could be resting under the boot of Tyra
As I plead for help for my fellow America
They just Walk On By
All the while thinking at least it's not happening
To me it's happening
To them so do I kill cops and make a
Cast and where they come to get me
I prefer to die than sitting there jail when I've done nothing to hurt
Alex knows the reality that there's not insignificant part of his audience.
It's like that
Little better right on the edge
Committed violent Acts
Most of them don't end up
Following through with them but
Alex does need a built-in excuse for the ones
The do any bills that excuse
If I complain about TV shows being predictive programming
Better set up to make it look like people who
Or his van
And would do things right
Kill cops
Right and of course after
Jared Amanda killed those three people Alex immediately called it a false flag
Because that's the payoff for the work that he's doing here in February
Being able to feign ignorance
Oh oh by
Whatever your audience commits Acts
Classic terrorism
The entire game
Any idea that it would matter is silly whenever
After like
If you went and read watch
Didn't plan it
Evil rat villain is left-of-center to Nancy Pelosi
Like that
What's the level of
If they were really if cartoons were helping out
We will be in a different world right now
There are left-wing
Villains
Oh totally
Yeah and I don't remember ever taking offense
To that even if it's something that I like
I do understand
Yeah that
There are left-wing terrorist groups
A lot of them even like animal Liberation fire mental groups
Premium
I absolutely understand
I don't
Take such
Offense
The notion
Of that being assertive a reality
People are fine.
The Scotts
My lesson wasn't like all their ideals were wrong it was like bad plan
I don't think I don't think that
Like the reality and the discussion of their existing
Left-wing terrorism
I don't think that makes me feel like people are saying that everyone on the left is a terror
Speedway Alex engages with the world which is
Is childish
BFDI to make you believe everybody on the left is a terrorist
Alex gets to talking about his eyes LOL.
Okay John
The morgue
Neymar
You are
I love for Alex to present that
Magazine article about preemptively arresting birchers
Cuz I don't think
Exists
Also whether or not Berger is are the most upstanding people
Some points of contention if you're talkin about like Financial crimes than the membership of the John Birch
Society makes up some of the most
Criminal Cadre of people's wage theft alone the Koch brothers have stolen
Trillions of dollars it's so many other manufacturing interests are apart of
But even beyond that if you look at some of their founding members
It's on Shady things like you mentioned
Is an absolute
Historical monster
DJ Meyers book dark money
He profited from building oil refining capabilities for Hitler in the 30s
Reveal Opie Oliver who was forced to step down from membership in the JBS and 19th
Because he was such an Ardent white nationalist Amanda
December 8th that he made them
JoJo he would go on to be a part of the National Alliance
Ambien inspiration
For William Luther Pierce when he was writing
The Turner Diaries
Essentially the Bible for white
Supreme Mist Terror
Also Pierce himself was aperture for a while
Before you needed seek out something stronger
Willis carto
Piece of s*** and
Semi traces
Founder of the Liberty Lobby
Was a bird
Torres was Tom Metzger
The Neo-Nazi founder of the white Aryan resistance
Add one-time Grand wizard of
The clan
A society actually is 100% just good upstanding people if you pretend all the examples of really high-level mod
Monsters don't exist
All the examples of
Real serious s*** head
Influential s*******
I'm not just talking about like
Oh there was a racist in the group who posted that sings on Twitter
Tom Metzger
Oliver
No problem
These are people who are likewise
We overthrow a government for the people just so I can get more money
That's some of that
Evil donut that's some of the businesses there's also just
I do
Strongly to the John Birch Society
I do appreciate that the rich have so
Overwhelmingly destroyed and dominated our media that they're like that we're all like a man
Lifting is wrong and the jumper Society filled with the nice
6 people in the world
Sure
They're almost
40% responsible for climate change
Buy them
Arthur crunch the numbers on that
Actuary
So
Alex Alex
What's a strong word
I'm sure that's exactly how Jared Miller felt ended up killing three people
A few months after this episode
He's a really clear in his both any feels like
Constitutional rights been violated and that if
B5 back or call a radical but they only call a radical cuz he
Standing up for what's right
He never says that the idea of killing cops is his way of
Commencing 17:7
We might as well
To be clear I don't think there's a direct line between Alex's comments on this specific episode and Jared's rationalization for why
Why was necessary
For him to kill three people
I'm saying that the
Consistent content on Alex's show and the editorial perspective as a whole
Informed Jared's rationalization for why was necessary
For him to kill three people in this clip is
Just one of the Litany of examples
That fade into the
Extremist back
Yak
Sick
Yeah
Yeah you know
It is it is one of those things
You're you're trained to think of theirs there's an inciting
Element to Alex's
Oh something he said must have him
Created a
Such
Void of
Empty violin
There's nowhere else for it to go
Kind of alarming I was looking at Alex's
Site obviously like you
Banksy's art been on a break
I am trying
To see what's going on
Blackpilled. News great
You guys are playing into
Something that
Whether or not it's intentional it's like that that void that you're talking about
Yeah it is
Is like well now you're going to try and create
Mass
Shootings out of it or something
Okay how about I would go with
Breaking news
Electric Boogaloo
That's not that's not
Not terrible right
I think you have to go with like
Electric Boogaloo. News
That news is kind of like what is
Is is branding iron
What is it like one of them was like
Tomorrow's news. News
This is bad
I know you can't do this
So are we know that Alex loves them cuts
Two-channel Sheriff
He has a little story about one of them
Florida
So there's about Nick
Fitch shares of Liberty County in 2013
He decided that he didn't like that someone was arrested for a concealed-carry violation of it
Concealed loaded firearm
So he unilaterally had him release
Reply to I am the law
Bright
Jim Beam arrested on an accusation of tampering with an arrest record and correct
Ultimately reinstated
Position is Sarah
This whole thing made Finch something of a hero in econ
Constitutional
Community show
Problem is that actions have consequences
As it turns out sometimes those consequences are really bad
Floyd Eugene Parrish was the man who Finch
Unilaterally released on the
Concealed carry charge
Andy 2016 Parris got into an argument with someone with a gun
Oh well I probably won't get covered on Infowars kind of like it didn't happen
You know yeah well I mean that was
That was later
You know this
That's like saying that something in the past then leads to something in
In the future and it just doesn't make
Only been now half
Everybody knows
There never any
Indication
Be like saying that foreign policy decisions from 30 years ago somehow have it effective
For policy decisions now. Just crazy
Just weird
This guy Finch
The sheriff
Overstepped his authority
Very
Brazen way
In order to get one guy out of prison
Concealed carry violation about it and I just dropped the story and a few
You years later
The guy who he
Unilaterally let out of prison murder to guy
Just weird
Well if there was anything I remember
Counterargument
The whole thing
Murder somebody do you bring up all of these exam
And you think it doesn't
Change
The truth which is that everyone should have a gun all the
On them
Pointed at everybody else and if you can do an argument
You should fire
One of your boots
Absolutely whatever extra one of Your Boots Been Under
I want to stress this
Is an experiment
Experian
That I find fascinating
It's
The uniform
I cannot think of a counterexample this
Every single sheriff who's ever been brought up on Alex's show
You look into him a little bit and there's something real f*****-up
What of the truisms of
Researching Infowars is that if someone to share if they're on meth
No I mean well in order to be a constitutional Sheriff
Your thought
Have to begin with the place
The founding fathers
Love giving unilateral authority to one person
The highest law in the land
What the founding fathers looking at King George.
No no no
We need one in every city and every state baby
Sheriff of Nottingham you have like you're Richard Max
Arpaio's I saw your profile
We got to do from Wisconsin Milwaukee
There's people all over the place
They're like I'm talkin about even Lake
Low-end
Completely forgettable never
A big media named Sheriff
They're still
Across-the-board
F***** up
If they're brought up on Infowars of the hero
So
We're in 2014 now
And there's
Some things that are different
Then
The present
Alex's
In the midst of
Figuring out how much she owes for
We are losing the Sandy Hook
Cases right
And the present day
Those fears were not in his mind
And so he was really really proud
Tampa.
Call kumon.com
Reporters
Massaman
Howard
How many hours
Sounds a lot like
You hold yourself here
Supposed to be actual reality of Danville.
I do love the image though
I like
People being
IQ
Don't pay attention to this matter
I want one time
For the entire press Corps
The stand up and
What kind of
Lunatic world is that we covered this whole time. Of the Boston bombing
Watch those videos and for the most part everybody
Is f****** annoyed
Andy being there and acting like a total a****** because the city is in
State of
Acute grieving
And Terror they're scared there's a bomber on the loose
Any of this guy grandstanding and trying to turn it into a PR stunt
Predict whole guy in Texas
You know like it's
It's such a distasteful thing
You can see people not like
Oh my God we're so scared of the information you're presenting it's just
What the f*** is wrong with you
That's what's going on
Oh totally
No the authority
These weren't mad they were just annoyed that everybody else there was like
If I could just
Disgaea
F****** do it if there was an element of Madness
Totally worn
Rented because
Functionally what his disrupting of
Press conference
Is doing is making
More difficult
For the official
To communicate with the public
When providing that
Information
Essential piece
Trying to make people feel
Trying to navigate this really difficult
Circle.
Dysfunctional
The effect
Albarradas action is actually
Impeding their ability
B2
The governor
Appropriately
He's walking in there with the express purpose of exploiting a tragedy at
Expense of everyone else there
Got it
She starts being a real s*** head
Proud of him back right
Doesn't really have much to do with anything
Sing boats
But sexist
I'm confused
Brown
Hey man
What are you doing
What problem is that somebody is
It might be you think we're like you back
Get stolen
Don't have to just be about it
Fear of terrorism
No I was I was
What is trying to get on a flight
And I made it through security and made it through everything I got about
4 steps away from standing on the plane
When I realized that I had
Forgotten my bag
Horsehead left them in there
So I ran back through the whole f****** place
Screaming just like you know how I am
That doesn't really help
Situation
But in this one it did because everybody was so confused and shocked by it that they just let me grab my bag and I get my
Right back on there
But I would have been much happier if somebody was like hey you forgot your bag
Covid-19
I mean like obviously for
Very clear reason
Airport shuttle
Policy that unattended baggage is treated as suspicious
Don't really don't f*** around with them and send them back
Can't
Is an airline or an airport
Risk
Not treating unattended bags
Exactly cuz
Legal ramifications of the lawsuit that would come out of that
I'm almost,
It's so
Someone saying like hey
Your ear leaving your bag here
Someone might come and take it
From the airlines
The airport might take it
Because they can't leave it on a kazoo
This is so weird he's actually describing
Courtesy
100% is mad about it
Complained that somehow he is mad because women are quote on quote
More congenial
And that but that's just in Stockholm Syndrome
Yeah but also
To the Salt Lick
At the Austin-Bergstrom Airport
So cool that you could get barbecue at the airport and it's not bad
Pretty good
I got it last time I was flying back from Austin
My web for the Depo
I'll probably I'll probably be back before too long. Visit my parents
It's more I will get
Get salt lick
Reason not to was thinking about ordering a bottle of the sauce
Spell
I was going to say they don't deliver the
No but you can order it
All right but it only comes in like a gift pack has problems with next travel
Anyway story about how
Him and his buddies are all oppressed
Yeah
Court-martial regular people
So now it says psyops group
Gave him this information
I take his sourcing
That seriously
Who does not at all
Extreme but for what it's worth
Can actually find a number of stories about this on Fox watch
What's the time
And even some more like
Even less
Credible right-wing sources
Then they report on this alleged meeting at Fort Hood
They can't donate to
Tea parties are Evangelical Christians
Problem is it after these claim
James came up an internal investigation
Began at Fort Hood
The outcome of the investigation wouldn't
Be known until October 2013 though it by that point Alexander's weirdo friends
Lots of free time to run with this
Completely fake story
Which was accepted as Truth by the audience
Who cares the truth is come out
Where's year in February 2014 Bukhara
Do fake version is still true on Infowars
He's got it
You know
It started
Once once the cement
Dried before the investigation came out it was all over
Nothing you can do
I like
Goes to sumco
He wants to make calls from
Military
Police
He wants to know about
Drills his drills are we are all being run to demonize the papers right
Call from one guy anyone
No like
Hey man you ever ever do one of
Please grills and obviously the answer is supposed to be yes
Of course the answers
Oh
Company
Coming from
They're doing a video for
West Point
National Guard base
10 minutes from my house
Where might unit used to be at
And we go out there and
Videos of us kicking outdoors and all that other stuff
Anime
So you see the way that Alex has to Pivot cuz the answer is no
And the guy is describing
Completely but not
Very boring story on top of that it's more boring than Alex is like oh my God I went out to 1
They're trying to kill Bocephus
You mean like
No we did
Videos one-time concern
Twitter doing this this this training exercise right
Already friends came over and all my God all hell broke loose
You know I tried to fake fight
Hank Williams jr. for a while. Right
Did you get any heat like advertisements tattoo specialist
His fighting style
I wanted to make sure that I was
Prepared for it
Amazing left
So Alex has some information
Or I should say
He has
Flames of information
Oh man that's not that Alex get offended if we prove that the killing of Bin Laden was fake and even as the name of the body double that use but Weebly
Isn't actually able to produce that evidence and never says the body doubles and
It would be weird not
How to say the body doubles
Sure
This is a part of one of Alex's big strategies that he uses to protect that he has more information than he actually does
It's very exciting to think that Alex knows this body doubles name but it's
It's only exciting as long as he doesn't say the name
As long as that stays the status quo it's entirely believable that Alex does have that information
You can't prove it or disprove it if Alex
Doesn't say anything concrete
Actually I do know who the body double who's that
Saddam Hussein
Thing now where they the last one they assassinate they just hang onto and then
Until the next one then
Assassinate
The timeline is but when was Kadafi
Haha
I was trying to remember who starred in the movie body double
So desperately
My brain just couldn't told Melanie Griffith
So
Fuck12 Alex says the name that he's a legend
The Mystique
I know this name goes away
Saying the name is going to lead to the claim being
Going to be a little disappointing
When is saying that you know the name Bryce
You can't say that
Which is actually counter to all of Alex's Notions about secret information
Also stupid
Such a charade I don't want to make this family feel bad
That's why I can't
You wouldn't want that.
So Alex is talking about this the faking over the killing of Bin Laden
And this leads him
Into
Nothing but other things
Things are fake
Comes up
That's pretty funny
Because
In the first episode that we covered
Mark asked Alex
Facts about this Bloomberg
Tell Alex that I don't know but I could definitely find you the source of the second deposition
Said you were going to find that Source doesn't
But yeah I think it I think interesting presentation here because
Is it playing that sort of
Mid
Game here where he's not
Overtly denying
All of the day
What you would do later
Would jump Whole Hog
Point he is still saying that the people who put out
The story and by that means people like Robbie Parker
I don't I don't know if he would be including Posner in that but maybe
Speaking on this of being actors
Which is
A problem
Exactly
Estranged
Hybrid of
A full-on denialism
And
I am playing it
Yeah it's like not understanding that you would like
I see I'm covering my ass
But with like
I'm empty like outline of Ally
Well you're not like that's not really covering your ass you realize that because it's not respecting the Imp
Application still doing the thing if you're saying that the parents
Of the
What killed children
Who are the ones who are speaking out about this
Are actors
The implication of that is
Their kids didn't actually die
Yeah because otherwise
What what are you saying
Doesn't make sense non Middle Ground area you can't be like
Listen
I know the Holocaust
But most of it was true and only some of it wasn't know you're still a holocaust denier now
It's very strange
To see this
Perspective
I don't really understand why he would
This middle
Ground
So weird
The caller saying
Some dumb
No I don't know
Time now
Was today are gearing up
The Masons
I live in a small town to Mason's have been having
Mediums
Quite frequently
Wisconsin
All the major roadways
The overpass
Barricades
Oh I know the one
Are The Masons the ones who put all the gates upon her probably not
Well
I mean literally it involves masonry I was going to say probably had something
Thing to do with it I just think it's funny to look at this in a match
Enterprise
Are active
They're all out there
Did the wave that ever
Everything has spiralled from
Episode of classical
Conspiracy tropes
Tickets
2014 might have a caller who's worried about what the Masons are up to that was fun
That was more fun
The Masons are the ones putting styrofoam cups in the overpasses overhead to s*** to spell out
Secret evil messages
Like
Geaux tigers
Doesn't get more evil than that
I thought you know
So here's a dumb prediction that Alex made that goes in the laundry list of
Bad predictions
Horrible
It's so stupid like look at the conception Alex has here
Close to happening
This was recorded eight years ago and none of the stuff that Alex is claiming it's all part of the globalist
Plans they have a plan none of its come to pass
There's been no gun confiscation there's been no need for Patriots to resist turning in their gun open no Civil War in
Inside it over gun confiscation
Also look at this s*** that Alex is unraveling is
The grand plan of the global
If grounded in reality
To the point where inanna
Insane person
We could buy into
They're really rich
Bad people have committed
Financial crimes and they don't want to get in trouble for them
So they're engaging in
Comically elaborate plot
The cover their tracks
This is dumb
If only because of Civil War it almost
Immediately wipe out whatever Financial games these people made by way of their crimes
But you can see this as a
Activstyle conspiracy
There's no Supernatural elements there's no devil working by me
Racines there's no prosthetic
Vision is a battle between good and evil where the goal is ascending to the Stars
This is about using half cooked ideas
What's the defendant
Active political ideology that
Push
This is my good Mason caller and seem so foreign to Oz present-day content wherever
Demon
You know everyone who disagrees with them is a pedophile
It's bizarre it's quick it's
Quick
Yeah but
You know a lot of people's brains have just been f***
Unbroken by
Man I think I think we're at the point now where we
Did you know
Like that any number of people who have
Previously had at least
Somewhat rational stances are now
Out now
Long gone
I understand that a lot of people have been
Maybe by degrees or maybe by
Leaps and Bounds
I got into areas that are really a rash on
I understand
I think it's a little different
Thunderstruck
I don't know
On the other hand
Do you know when your brains already that broken what happens whenever it breaks again
Keep scared he's gotten weird
It hasn't fixed him like a like it would be
Great if the worst thing that
Listen to human beings while we're alive
Would have been like a f******
Frying pan to the forehead in a cartoon and
Wake up and be like
Holyshit
It time to fix I can finally say you know like that kind of fit El kabong absolutely
Just got weirder
Speaking of weird
Around
Oh man what an amazing prediction David Icke totally made with
Totally came true
Whatever
So weird I also to see that the Great Awakening is happening in full force in 2014
Currently in 2022 yelling about of the great awake
Meaning of beginning and response
The covid-19
Almost like the idea of a Great Awakening happening is just
The consistent element of people like Alex and David Icke Brandon
And it's so vague of an idea that it can just be trotted out whenever you want to create the image
Is it your side to secretly winning
Really cool stuff and not at all the sign of s*** head manipulator
I think there's a real
Like
Solid
Narrative Arc
That could be made out of
Just
Alex is David Icke
Like throughout his
Is career like there's a real
I think there's some pesos
I doubt it
I'm literally just having him on when he didn't like
Sure
That's true do intros Jazz know to make it out of just his it's like overall
Look I do think there is a real downward trajectory that you can see if Alex being like
I have to differentiate myself from this guy who's clearly insane
To being like
F*** it he's got a big audience over to warm up to him
Essence by being like wild
Something
And then I'll find you like I've
Just going to steal wholesale most of it
100% it is like a one of those XY graph memes where it's
Just slowly all the way
Yelp brutal
What an a******
Paddock
There's a dumb story that Alex is reporting
So that isn't Holdren's book ecoscience
Documents proving AZ
In the water to make people dumb
How to make that up because he knows his textbook
To check up on his claim
Introduction of Nephilim skulls
Oh that's pretty
Exciting
What's going on here is that UFO conspiracy message boards have been circulating images of
These skulls that were founded
The perrakis region in Peru
I just making up the DNA testing it but do not
And show that they weren't
Ral that mean the first one was recovered by India
It's true
Just accepted the claims of the DNA testing inside
The face value like Alec
Because the skulls were elongated and slightly conical in
Nature
It's made them look
Possibly alien
In the real world
The Stalls at that appearance because they were from members of a community to practice artificial
Cranial deformation
This is achieved by exerting force on a child
Skull before it's fully hardens
There's a number of theories as to why people did this
Ranging from ideas about beauty to the promotion of in group in group cohesion
Whatever the motivation what's going on here is that Alex awesome meme that may take
Completely fake
Reclaim the DNA testing if it done to prove the
Please call FedEx
Depressed
But he did literally no work
Past that point to before turning it around and repeating it to his audiences
Fact that things are going crazy
And not only that you seem to be implying that the ACT
Accepting
The skulls are alien Nephilim
It's somehow a sign of being awake
Just pathetic
Hopefully David Icke sets
I'm straight on some of this stuff
I like I like the idea that there are times
Whatever
Conspiracy and reality
Can just be so far apart like
Here's how far to particle
They could be alien
They could be Nephilim from the Bible
Or
It could have been some people a while back
Who just thought it looked hot
Can I can I carry simple explanation I give you a quick correction
The Nephilim
Still kind of be alien
Because they're The Offspring of demons and human women
You have to accept it
I hate to be a nitpicker but
Where am I
We're talkin here a little bit about
The trajectory of Alex's relationship with David Icke
I think
Western Hills
Episode
It becomes painfully clear that like right
Alex isn't really talking about demon so much
Penne pasta
Episodes
Well a little bit
But also David
Is
Bo en
Future Alex
Very very important
It's not just
Really rich people who want to cover up their financial scams by
Taking away guns in order to prompt
Gun owners to start shooting at them and then cause a civil war
And I won't forget about the financial crimes there's on seeing demons
Gene's and arcade
This is this is
The point at Alex's
I want to play with next with really good for you respond because
Alex isn't really fully like
Fuckerrbody is making it okay for the audience to entertain these ideas
That's not why you had to leave that town
Yeah you didn't you can kind of see this like
Narrative even if you don't believe
NikeiD
However you got to get there man you get
Really pretty looking for greasing the skids
In order for people to get down down
Into this
The same time
Trying to pretend that like
Hey
I'm not the one saying there's demons
Cuz then it looks really
I'll wait a few years and then I'll do it
You know I think it's so weird
And funny in like
Kind of strain
Change that
These these types of people one of their
Look
There have been things like this that are pops
Japan ever human civilization
That means that humans must have
Contact with it somewhere in our
Memories or something along those lines doesn't make sense to be able to just be like
No
S*** heads like Alex Jones
David Icke and those people have been around
Since the very beginning
Claiming
Demons are the reason behind all of your
There aren't there out there is a lot of that
Yeah
These assholes have been there since the Jumpman
Even even
So
The ones in the present-day are misrepresenting a lot of stuff
About the shipment from the past
Both hats
Are dumb
It is like we haven't it said we'd
Did we went backwards
In learning about things
So how much do you know about brainwave frequency
I know there's
Three there's
Down and left
That's correct
Peeling
Smartphone
Really scary because I think that the human brain waves
Frequencies are just like radio stations brain is on 106
6.1 and if the government has broadcast something on that frequency
Brain control
Some problem
So this idea just starting from a function
Perspective
Human brains are on the same frequency or is it different for each
Person
It's different for each person that I don't know if there's that many frequency bands
Quite frankly
You just get smaller and smaller number
But if we're all the same
Really be impossible to find to Minecon
Control
Population-level brainwashing with us
Washington
Scam write your plans
They probably need all I got
Metallic moldable hat
Aluminum people you got a plan for failure or a back
Fire on some
Absolutely
Completely misunderstanding what brain waves are
Your brain doesn't have a set frequency that it operates at necessarily know that never changes quite a bit
State you're in
Princeton's
He's working at about 524 hurt
Works when you're asleep
Delta waves
Where is the state of high concentration your brain might be in Campbell
Is it over 35 hurt
So just really stupid I don't even know what he saying
Conceptually
It doesn't even
About Alpha Beta gamma waves
He doesn't give a s***
No he just thinks that there is this
Number
Tuna to the right thing
David Icke
Should have like any any sufficiently
Miss understandable technology is
Is the same as demons
I like you should just make it up
Makeup his anti-sagging
Quote urgency archon
Is not fame and it was a
I'm so mad that we can't continue this week
Hell I remember the name of the guy who said
Carl Sagan wrote the
The demon Haunted World
Who said any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from Magic
Are they see Clark thank you thank you
Carchex
Really strange thing the David I can Alex
Into
And it's really contrary to anything
That we would know from the Press
And that is that
Hollywood
Maybe not
Is bad
Mandela effect
I thought that The Nut Job came out much more recently
I don't know why but I had to
Except my mind is like 2019
Or something
Wow The Nut Job Lego movies old now man
That's I was just thinking that like
Wow
The Lego Movie
Government-run propagate
And it's been so long since I thought that about a movie
And it turns out it's The Lego Movie
Proof
Hollywood
There is a revolution going
It's very exciting
What's Guardians of the Galaxy come out yet
It has in 2014 we look it up
You son-of-a-b**** opened opposite
People like you
Stop eating
I'm not sure what year that was
It was fairly close to that
Alex is not in Guardians of the Galaxy that was
The lie but that would have
Probably Boniva
Even further proof
But Hollywood is waking up
If a wood cast Alex's
The hero
Snapchat I was thinking
Apparently a Hollywood
Pretty good
Word
I really bad news for Alex about
Where he's going to be in a few years about Hollywood
Revolutions
Did not
Go
Who is who who does he think
Isn't
Let it like
Listening to Infowars who's leading the underground resistance against the rest of Hollywood on the Red Sox
Pretty specific polana Elkins Park
What was it
Sumner redstone bitbox
I don't f****** know anyways no studiosystem
Makeda still around
He probably was
Not
Obviously something that is
Very clearly specific that I was just talking about
But I I just got no idea
Summer Redstone is vile
He was in charge of
See if maybe Ted Nugent the show
Who are the other stars that talked to Alex
Clint Eastwood
Peter Stormare
I need this musician
Tertiary
Seamless
Yeah he said that he
You said that Martin Sheen and Charlie schmelzer
Bowser for sure Bowser Bowser
The highest of the highest music
Unfortunately Rowdy Roddy Piper did come on
Yeah but he was in they live so we get to
Also Val venis
The wrestler Val venis
She did an interview with David on D1 time really
Was it about how one time they had a storyline where Japanese people were going to
I didn't come up that's the only thing that I will ever be able to think about any time you say his name
Do an episode about that I did that one with Marty
Covered
Val venis
Episode
He's much better prepared to handle it then I will
I don't believe that Alex
Thanks
That Hollywood is waking up so dumb
So dumb
So Alex
Kind of wishy-washy a little bit about the devil
What's the weather
That is important
Yeah man
So the Illuminati
That started in 1776 with Adam lights off
The
Books from Alexandria which was
Free 1776
Wildly before 7
Caesar it was a long way back
The pad for the patio
The one thing Alex's right about is the
Miss of the
At Library of Alexandria burning and everything be lost
That isn't fully after there was a fire
It was after the point at which
It was already kind of
It would
It was on the downswing of rellos
But say in that sort of ancient world
It was no longer the repository for all in all
No but that idea is really fun
Great what isn't it amazing to think of a repository for all human knowledge burning down yeah it's kind of gives
Nice narrative reason why we don't know something's amiss.
Sure
That's fine
I don't think of the globalist
Stole all that secret information and now are able to come
Control things because of it
Magic I also don't believe that the Atlantean set off an atomic bomb
Even if someone has a passion for Atlantis like I do I
Do not
Much less was it destroyed by a nuclear bomb
Said I think that the way Alex is describing
The devil here is a bit more
It's not a real physical being orator
Transdimensional be Artful metaphorical way to
Describe the people are fat
Okay
Bright
You know what then
Yeah it gets a little boring to just say that he's a metaphor man
Got to start
Spicing it up a little bit
Meet on that devil phone now the devil's preparing to fight Hank Williams Junior
So where's another gas
New shows updated I cannot take this leave
I was shocked
I have to say
That usually isn't true when Alex says he's not here to do a big infomercial usually is
In this case he kind of what
They did do a lot of talking about Alex
His productivity was
We are that there was another point
Alright now we've talked about doctor group a bunch
To the past and so we don't need to go into his entire dirty dossier here
But
The reason I was reading off all his credentials
Just cuz they're all fake
Where is that problem
He does not have a lot of Gravitas
Long resume full of fake
Credentials
Add to Breeze videos purchase
EXO
Alex probably doesn't to dwell on that too much
You don't want to list I mean unless
You are getting
From the fakes
Schools
Then you'd be like
Is this degree degree
Smiley smile infomercial but Alex does talk a little bit about vitality
And
Play I'm not sold on it
Or the female ones
For women
Why are you yelling
What
Wow that is not a ringing endorsement for whatever this pill is
Yeah I mean you're describing it like your inject
Sing me with bull semen Lego s*** man I'm f*****
I can't take this cuz I have anger issues
Also I don't like the selling of this pill unlike know what the effects are unpredictable
Hey what time is it Mellows me out
I freak out
It's entirely possible this is 100% of placebo and I am making this all up for my own benefit other
Wise I would have to confront the fact that my products do nothing cuz it seems really strange that
Does substitute have like
Completely
Contrary
When people sell you a pill
Drink or something
And then you ask them what it does
And then they're like
What do you think
I just agree with you
It might it might doesn't
Here's the reason the doctor group is on
Knowing what I know about doctor group
In the present day
I would expect that one of these would-be drink your piss
He's there
He is big
Get to urine therapy at 5
You think that it might crack the top five
His main job now
Bright
Spoiler alert
Maybe use a different time
Be a piss doctor maybe you should try and guess
Wait but that's I mean that's five of them is one of them should be X
It's not of course
Of course
The other one should be eating healthy
Spoiler alert
Okay
Then the other three are probably fake bull
Tried as f***
Call Courtney
Definition of clean water is dumb but the idea
You should drink clean water is
Right
Obviously the most
That seems easy advice is to drink distilled water with apple cider vinegar
Well no
But Clearwater Spa
Yes I do also like I like the idea that he's supposed to be a doctor and it took him weeks of research.
The number one thing is drinkwater
Well that wasn't he knocked out today is the rest of them that were
I'm not sure here's the second one
Alright okay
Actually I am
The correct myself his birthday comes up twice
Happy birthday
So
Spring chicken
Stewie knocked out today
Clean air
For somebody who is
Directly work
With
The man
Maybe more vehemently trying to destroy our water and air
Hey listen
Drink clean water
Obviously I'm working together with Alex to make sure it goes away we will destroy the EPA
Obviously I'm working with Alex to make sure that there are no regulations
You need to drink clean water and breathe clean air
But we have a political set
That will like policy set that want to make it intensely expensive for you to be able to
To access clean water or clean air the United States
Completely you're not going to get that s*** here
And by the way
Maybe nowhere because
Air doesn't respect
So while we take a little break e in the list of the top five healthy
Because Alex wants to know about like a doctor
Group
Ed
How'd you wake up
What was your waking up story
I bought it I thought Awakenings is such b*******
No
Now they're not
Tell me how
My God
None of that's true or real
Doctor group may or may not have finished getting an undergraduate degree from Southern Louisiana University which doesn't
The pre-med track for students
The study
Likely he really was
Black on his way to becoming the heart
Surgeon
After this he went to Texas Chiropractic
The college where you got a degree as a
Recipes degrees are fake
Degrees that he's paid for generally ones that are available
Correspond
Hey I'll give you a degree will send you a check
In the Stephanie saying is really dangerous
There's so many prescription medications that are
Critically important for people dealing with a wide range
The conditions
Just because big Pharma is soda
Detestable and because there are problems
Doctors over-prescribing something
That's not a Cause.
Pretend that literally no medication dozen
Anything
This is a guy who wants you to drink piss
And his mind drinking pass has more medicinal benefit that 80 prescription medication
Ever produce
That's Alex's
Expert
I thought you do it
I thought you do it right there
Please try to resist the urge
Do you like make fun of how somebody talk
Conoco
The regional dialects are maligned and what have you
There's a part of
Doctor group that doesn't really sound like you know like a southern
Person sounds like a surfer
Idiot
You realize that he is a piss doctor doesn't believe in medication
Cookaroo
You know what's crazy I this is that 2 hours
The secret
Therapy with that
It is it is fun how
Rehearsed his origin
In speeches
You know like
This happened to me I went to when I was doing the hearing anything
Dude Bill Austin I think his name is the dude who a little Bill also
Created Starkey or whatever
He was doing this
This whole big ass like corporate speech about this origin story
And you can hear it in that tone of like
Oh this is all
Can a cousin it can't be like
I made I made this company
Cuz I wanted to make a s*** ton of money and Alex you are helping me make money
I saw a problem with the market
Only my irecognize that I really didn't have the chops to be a real doctor
I figured out that there's a
Antique Market in supplements play Leon regulated chiropractor
Do you know how
Long it takes
To become a medical doctor and how much work it is
Yeah and how
You probably wouldn't pass
If you tried to write a paper on how medications
Don't do anything holy
Probably
Vail and you'd be really in trouble if you started describing this product that you wanted that maybe had enough
Back to where you got
Anger issues
Also a boner
Rock hard all the goddamn time
I think you'd have to go to a college
Undergraduate pre-med
Nothing I mean like
You also need to do that
I just
I'd sort of Forgotten
Experience of listening to Duck Creek
Pop up again was
Upsetting
Alex wants to know about his dad
Yes dr. group
His Heroes back
Text Dori not only ask you if there is a God I forgot
Doctor group his life's work is on
The evils of his dad
Saran Wrap
He is on a one-man crusade to undo the evils of his father
Because he was in Plastics
Saran Wrap Wichita
So toxic
Just destroyed the world and so he talked about that a little bit here
Is it amazing
Real quick
The person who invented
Saran Wrap in the real world brookford now,
There wasn't.
Adorable
Offered her a bunch of money my mom
Just found out I have
The big Saran Wrap author
Play Big Sur a rap off his dad
They killed a public document
Prepared Wows in the Attic
Doctor proved to be able to provide This research if he's found the evidence of it or whatever
If you were about to go public with it you probably got it somewhere in a readable form
Well unfortunately the people who killed him made his mom sign papers and then put all of it under wraps
Saran Wrap brutal
I'm not going to reward that
This is fun
You get this stupid doctor doctor
Peroxide to go public in babies with motor
It's so good I know but here's the problem I have with it
I find this
So much less believable than f******
Caps
Mark Richards backstory with his dad where is Dad met her f******
Churchill legit
This is such
Bulshit
About equivalent
Might as well
Could
He's at he's he's deeply involved in the drug war
Contaminating
Fake cocaine that the government
Just making yeah you might as well be from Aliens
Also if like
The research that he found
His dad was about to put out was
Everyone needs
To drink
That was the other information you found that his dad was going to go
Get back to the house Secret
How secret number three
Tell your dad
So we got drink clean water pretty clean air
Happy Clean to the first three he knocked out in a day
What's the one that took another week or two
Okay
Popcorn knockdown today
Alright
I don't know I think the first one is so vague as to be meaningless
Cleanse your body
Do cuz this is like take a shower
Okay tickets like cleansing your body also is like take my detox and supplements
Pantry pests
Of course
Ciara
Does not compel
No need to go top 5 relatively speaking for where
Where's this information is coming
These are 100%
Followable steps
For the fact
That like
Okay this is all
Tri-tip Vice
Reduce your stress level good food
All of this is
Fine
But like obviously they like
The eat clean food
Is like
All kinds of rampant anti-gmo South
Corn and soybean product
It's within all of these very trite observation they're like
And if you eat processed wheat you will be killed by aliens you know your daughter is great
Suggestion when distilled water with apple cider vinegar in it
Writer Agatha tap water will make you dumb I mean if you have been drink
Distilled water with apple cider vinegar in it for a long time
Piss is not
You might you might be onto something I think
You could make the lateral move to piss no problem
So you know you got to drink distilled water with apple cider vinegar but the
The key is to make it like
Body temperature
You know what you know what I found out I was I was looking at the toilet the other day and I was drinking
Nice tall glass of distilled water with apple cider vinegar in it and I thought
I could pour one of these into the other and no one would know
I don't want to gross anybody out like
In the end
We close this episode is it we're done with the clips
But there is there was a video of doctor group getting interviewed about his urine therapy
Please stop
And he has a mug
They like
Anybody else I would think it was coffee
Interview
Genuinely what
Subway
YouTube be like at today we have doctor grouper interviewing and then cut to that Meme video of the baby
Can you do his own Mallory in like that
You nailed it buddy
We might be making
Too much of a meal out of
The fact the doctor droopy can you doctor but is
It's been awhile since we've talked about him and real death
Already covered so much of the ground that's
Like really more
Substantial about
Historia past episodes feel really redundant to go over that we haven't really talked about when he's been
Because it wasn't the KA wasn't the case
Is that he likes a p
So we got
Dr. group
Drink your own pee
We got the health Ranger
Drink Ebola both of these people
Drink clean water
F******
Top of their game experts
Reliable
Lot of Gravitas
Do mulatto grab
So we come to the end of this 40th birthday episode
Celebrate
Dr. group coming in
The Big Four
At the big 4-0 you got it
Got to celebrate it in style
Talking about alien skulls the Nephilim
Fake stories about Fort Hood you know it's fun what a load of s*** for your 40th birthday we are
You're going to recreate this
Exact show
Word for word
I'm going to give you a script to hire people to
Will get dropped you to play doctor
Group that makes sense
To make sure
Not do this let's not do that
Let's
Want to do a stage 3 I'm getting overwhelmed by the possibility of being cordial
Talk about Alex
Start but just possibly my future but
Anyway anyway happy birthday Laurel hope you had a good one
And have a good one
We have is coming out
Dinner with your birthday's next week
Yeah we'll get that would be back
The world will talk about Alex Jones Studio
We have a website
Yep we're also on
We are on Twitter that analogy underscore
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leo rbx.com doctor marble
And now here comes
Alex
Birthstone colors