Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge like I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Exit
Quick question for you
My bright spot today Jordan
Okay today is actually I
Successfully finished forbidden West
Proud of myself
I realized way too late
That's the end game was a lot closer than I thought
Huh cuz I done so much other stuff I was roughly level all of them by you can't go higher than 50
And so then I hit barreled or the other
The game
It was one of those things that I do that's very annoying as I get soda
Distracted
For the first 85%
The last five percent is informality of formality
Yeah I put the game
To the side for a little bit to Silicon
Retain some of its wonders I realize that I was
Kind of getting to a point where a little burned out cuz he's doing exactly what you did
Riverside Quest
Some stuff
And
Congratulations on no thank you very much if you haven't gotten to a certain place
I have probably maybe not I don't know
Can you fly
In a manner
I don't know well my friend you get to fly in the late game
Spoiler
Well great
Anglers we broke our own rule
For the podcast that I'm working on that I'm
Excited about
Little Caesar that
Buybuybaby
Teaser teaser
We are enjoying
Alex Jones coming back
Back from his vacation is he better today
We haven't played the drop yet I can't I can't
This is March 17th 2022
Text a baby Alex is back alright
Not miss him that much
His presence has a absence of his presence
Has been filed
And as much as the dorks
I've been running that the house
And
Daddy's got to come in today I could be angry about stuff
Quickly as he comes back
He will be removing all of the snakes from the Infowars off
Some of it might just
Get laid off
You might
It might be payroll issue
Forget about Saint Patrick you just got rid of some of the steaks and they were like come on man you're downsizing
I better go Slither around Glenn Beck The Blaze
They're very welcoming
So we'll get the business on this episode
So first
Demon whiskey
Phoenix thank you so much you and I'll policy wonk
Listen to six hours worth of Danny Jordan across to Pakistan
Kevin Levin
Behind the bastards related
You're in Alabama
No little Breaky for the wicked took you so much for now policy walk
Deadman
Sent play Elden ring
You cowards or something like that
Not for me
Beware now policy
I introduce my brother
And Lindsay the best spouse Mouse thank you so much you and I was I
Technocrat
I have
Risen above
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Restaurants
Maybe I'll just be gone a month
Got to hear tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I apologize
Was legitimately having right now
Better tomorrow he's not
Sorry I had to wait
I was guessing
Not having a great day
Are you broke
You pissed off
Episode
Not I'm not trying to pylons US Government but it's obviously though
Control corrupt
Okay well
And listen nobody wants you to pile on the US after that Point Golf Course
Corrupt Anthony America
Enforce the American
You don't need to beat a dead horse certainly.
So Alex
Is not
There
When the show star
This is
Is becoming a little bit to the normal thing
Where are the show starts
Harrison Smith
Explaining that Alex
Will be there eventually
I'm Harrison Smith sitting in momentarily
For Alex Jones he is in the building's taking care
Illegal stuff right now but he will be taking over just as soon as
But for now let me
Give you a little
A little
PS2
How close we are to nuclear annihilation
God he sucks at this how close to the precipice we are before taking
Plunge off
The cliff
That will destroy all of humanity it's it's not looking good
Before I do that let me tell you
Happy Saint
Everybody hope y'all doing
Well hope you're you're wearing green if not
I hope you get pinched
Okay now the time for
Celebrating the Glorious work
Most powerful
Evangelist
Christianity
Never saw him taking a quick moment
Tell me the story
Israel strange path of fox Harrison to begin to show up
We're all going to die
But first let's look
Enjoy the Silverline have a green beer
Patrick one of the most powerful evangelist in history of the Christian church
If you're talk about who's like it
The top of that list without a doubt
It's Paul No Doubt
About half of the New Testament is attributed to him and he was critically important
In terms of establishing the earliest churches in places like Ephesus and Corinth
Eddie's letters to these churches that appear in the Bible
A book in the Bible established a lot of church doctrine
Outside of Jesus it's not really fair
To compare anyone
DePaul in terms of their importance
In spite of
Christianity
So you're looking down a little bit further on the ladder there are some major figures
You can make an argument that people like Constantine did wonders
For the spread of Christianity
Converted in
While the emperor of Rome and that led to the Edict of Milan in 313
The codified in
Cancel all religious
The tolerance for
Christianity
Where to buy
Affect
Massively spread
Well if you're not going to be murdered for it
What is your name
There's the conquesting Emperors who spread the language
Across the ancient world
Yeah
Alexander the Great spread in Greek
Glands
Allowed for the transmission of information among culture
Is that certainly somebody who
Well not necessarily you would say an evangelist
Headache
Dramatic effect
Now what one could argue though is that the most
Influential
Members of the church
Are the ones with the
Spotted Cow
So then you have to rejigger the whole thing I don't know
I mean Paul's got
6 Max
You don't know if I was up here
We need a gritty Paul video game
Verizon
Something along those lines
Rick is one of the most powerful evangelist in the history of
Christianity
Best
You could claim that he founded the Christian church in Ireland but even that claim is
Is far from solid
There's a lot of uncertainty about the historical record as it relates Patra
Breaking many believe that a lot of the claims made about his relevant to the Irish Church
Are conflated with Play-Doh
The first Bishop of the Catholic Church
Who was that
Ireland
The boy here is that the claim that Harrison is making
Is absurd but I'm excited to see how you back
Spits out I could befall interested also I think a lot of people in Ireland looking back on it would say that
Introduction of the Christian religion to Ireland might have wound up going wrong
Later on
Implementation
Well let's take the wheel
We're taking a quick moment
Tell me the story
Saint Patrick
Cuz it's a great source of inspiration
What we're doing here in the infowar
Saint Patrick
What's from
He was part of
Romanized
British family
His father was a deacon in the church
As a Young Man
And taken to Ireland
Which was at the time completely pagan
Were you accept as a slave and he was abused as a slave
Any live to life
As a slave until he
Got a vision
From God that told him
Your boats here
Your ride is waiting
It's time for you to escape and trusting his vision
He went to the coast and found a ship waiting there took him to England
We're again his troubles were not over
He was cap
Oxford multiple times
And I think about this
Who's escaped
Bondage
In Ireland
Has escaped the pagans you've you've made it out you live in a comfortable life with your family now
To give up that life
Go back and he was enslaved
Retribution
Some Revenge
Those people
To tell them the gospel
To convert them
Depreciated to perform miracles for them
And to better their life
Multipack
Was that man
But really it really trying to be like
Talk about yourself here a little bit
Well I find it very interesting that we can definitely identify with
Former white slave
Who come back to the land that they were enslaved in and then kicked out of
In order to do her
Straight up murdering anybody
Vine
Disconnect
But why would I
Which is a strange thing on Infowars because usually people
People loving Alex
Can pick us up but he has no idea what he's talking about
I'll bet at least according to whatever sources we do have available
What are the story of Saint Patrick is but like
That's the Wrecker
For yourself how reliable any of those sources are
And take him to Ireland
That escaped and then eventually decided to become a mission
Also Patrick supposedly had another Vision they called him to
Come back to Ireland so that's why you did it is supposed to go back in business
Giving these Visions is a little wishy-washy but we should be
Go get on the boat and back tire line
I
The one problem perform miracles
Formerly of saint
He's never been canonized and the whole thing about running
This makes off that's not true
Of course
None of this matters though because employers and everyone associated with it believes in lore as reality
Folktales about someone
Religious Doctrine
Absolutely important caveat though and that is at the Eastern Orthodox Church
Does venerate Patrick as a saint in equal standing with the apostle
But I really don't think that Infowars
Is an Eastern Orthodox operation
Alex Espinoza some theological beliefs that are at odds
With that tradition
So just seems hard to believe
That that would be there
Eastern Orthodox
Paul Bunyan is also venerated alongside the Saints in an Infowars so it's like
Find to true to Colonel Travis
I will say this with a fair amount of certainty
You're not going to find anybody who takes the study of Religion
Like a
Just religious studies seriously that would say
Play Patra
Rick is a major event
Not part of
How many other of them have their own holiday that is entirely about there
Real life and events that happened 100%
To them it's a bizarre
Notion
For Harrison to be spreading but
What's what about this is
It's just a way for Harrison to use his story Ben Tate Patrick really talk about himself
And Alex
They are like Saint Patrick and that they've seen the horrors of Ireland
The globalist metaphorically
So they could have a nice life elsewhere they returned and selflessly try to free people still in bondage
But I'm sure it feels better than dealing with the reality that you work for a malicious narcissist liar
Is only really packed in the world is increasing the suffering of all
Which is
Not like
The story of Saint Patrick
You bring religion to Ireland and then
Fights for the next
Thousand goddamn years
I don't know
Lozano taxes
So
Continuously about
Was that man
And his writings have had
Unbelievable
Positive effects
The world over
He almost single-handedly
Converted
Country of Ireland
To Christianity
At the single man with nothing but the words
Uses in the truth that he's expressing
Changing the destiny of an entire nation
Entire world
The man who is free from bondage
Hate those who enslaved him
Helped to bring about
The abolition of that entire
Institution
Love's very
Not true most of Ireland
Christianity in Ireland predated his arrival and historical record is full of
Bunch of other influences who
They're people who created a lot of like really isolated monasteries
I like because of their isolation
Many of them were able to survive much better
* the Dark Age
And
Became
Something it was eight
The heavily influential
The developments of
The church in Iowa
Absolutely
Look at my selfie that is at night
Are you got a taxi
The point
For me is that
These guys have such a
A focus on the individual strongman theory of History
One person who's also in at 4
Basically the model of an infant Warriors
You alone are able to
How to change everything
Sure some people are
Sansone
And hard work and luck
Some people are able to make it
Outsized impact in the world
That's not necessarily how everything
I mean
It is it is the interplay of 7 billion different things all happening simultaneously there
If you are the person with the luck to actually
That's why
Like a million different
Saint Patrick
Someone else in the church that was not-so-great Bruce Willis
What's the Pope
Somebody needs to
Celebrate
What the church is supposed to be teaching cuz I'll tell you
Somebody who's not doing that
Little man named Pope
Francis the store infowars.com pump Francis warrants
Final catastrophe could extinguish human race
I suggest
Pope Francis
Ask himself a question
Is that what the Bible says
That's not really what the Bible says is it no the Bible
Actually promises
What
Is wrong with you
Putting forward Christian Diaz he is about putting forward the great reset
New World Order
Control Paradigm that he seemed so eager to participate in
Pope Francis warns of the escalation of the conflict in Ukraine could lead to a five
Catastrophe
That would extinguish the human race
Speaking during his weekly address to Pope's that Humanity would have to start from scratch
In the event of a
Thermonuclear war
Increasingly concentrated on the representation of a final catastrophe
That will extinguish us
Whether it's
Climate change
Bored
The death of democracy
For the conflict in Ukraine
Everything
In the mainstream media has to be portrayed as an egg
Existential crisis because it's not about
Presenting you with the
And the truth of the situation so you can come to an informed decision
The how you want your
Political
Representatives to behave
Face the challenges
That we're up against a half
How to force you
Into an emotional
Do or die this is it the walls are
Crumbling down panic mode
Override your logic Center in your willing to do things and willing to allow things that you would never be willing to do or allow
In a more
State of Mind
Backflip is wild
Upset
The pope isn't playing into his Endtime Fanta
I guess that Harrison is mad that the pope is saying the word
Ukraine could escalate to a situation
For the continuity of our modern civilization is at risk
Right
But isn't that what Alex has been saying for weeks
Literally started the show talking about how we're facing nuclear annihilation
We're getting distracted with his Saint Patrick
QuikTrip
CC
Pope says what
The times of 10
That's an unchristian attempt
To keep everyone in the grates
Reset
New World Order fear Paradigm Alex and Harrison say they were one
Away from nuclear annihilation
I just done being super cool more Christian than the pope and absolutely not trying to keep the audience
It is state of crippling fear
Does this make sense
Yeah
It goes like this but just make it to clear these guys know what the
They're doing
Accurately describe with their entire business model is when they're accusing
The pope of doing it
Fully aware that constantly bombarding people with
Do-or-die the world is ending type messages
Have the effect
Of overriding people's critical thinking or Lisa cam
Harrison's boring as s*** but also
Makes it to clear that there's
An intellectual understanding within Infowars
That what they're doing is manipulative and abusive
If you're doing
Infowars game you're supposed to not be aware of that psychology at all or at very least
Don't talk about it
This is a f****** liability for Alex I would fire his ass immediately if I were asked
I mean
Is not good you can't be talking like this
And here's the thing you can he's not going to sell it for you man I don't hear I don't hear a lie
In this I don't hear somebody trying to be Alex in this I hear it
Child
That needs to be like
Put in a timeout
You need to stop this
Go sit in the corner
Like that's what I'm hearing no man is kind of interesting is
That is more lies doing an Alex impression
And I think he wants to
We become like our
Alex more like out
Harrison has his own
Something
Which is
But obviously like I said boring
I think it's also a lot more
Crypto neo-Nazi
He lets on perhaps much more of a close association with people like Nick Fuentes on the groin
Be there the first book that he is like a much more subdued less bombastic connect
In terms of like
He's not willing to push it
He's not really push that was
Does Bounder
Is a little bit on his own show but no one listened
You got 123 views though you'll be fine knocking down your door just indicate the
American journal on the radio station Kono
Look dude
Half an hour goes by
And
Long back rubs this is the auction show on Harrison Smith sitting in for Alex Jones who
Momentarily will be joining you
I'll be
With you
Sitting and watching Alex Jones
In just a few minutes
No need to worry about that
I'm worried
Like
I feel like there's too much of an awareness that this is a bad outcome for listeners like
Reassure people like I promised I would, almost out of
Have your lives for good again
Yeah if people wanted to listen to me they could choose to listen to my show and they don't know
Alex is coming don't worry
The 47-minute talent shows up
Ladies and gentlemen we are playing the game right now we are caught in the jaw so they could easily become
Civilization perhaps all life on earth like the Pope's
You know it was here back in the cockpit today that's a weird that Harrison is right there
Are the studio and he's not like offended by his boss Alex Jones we're playing the game it might result in
End of life on Earth
What the pope said something like that he was contradicting the Bible and trying to keep people in the great reset new world order for your States
Harrison
Harsh words
For Alex
So so weird that he doesn't fart into the studio and holds
How to speak to the fire about how we could possibly
Believe that life
Pretending to be mad about that
He's actually mad about but is that he's not enough
Of a bigot
He cares about climate change
Imagine listening
Half hour to an hour the show and not thinking these guys are
Complete joke
Like this is
Sew in
Eternally
Contradictory
It really hurts
I don't I don't think that they are doing a very good job
It work happened
St Patrick you're better off there don't go to the pope you don't have anything on the Pope I need to talk to y'all
About the most important relic of the early church
The Blarney Stone
Okay Harrison
Somebody told me they peed on it after I kissed it one time when I was in Ireland
So Alex has more interest
Alex didn't go to Ireland
For his trip as a little break
Eben ice Duets California
I was out in California for 3 days
And it was the most over-the-top
Before that it was the California the Bohemian Grove
But I infiltrated got the footage of the Mike Hansen
22 years ago that was the strangest thing
Hybrid
Very interesting
Then the rest of it we will break very very soon
Anytime
A lot of big stuff a lot of big stuff out
It was what
Definitely Hotel California
It sounds like I'm a loser describes their boring-ass vacation
Oh my God best vacation ever so much stuff happening
So crazy
Can eyes wide shut thing going on but I can't tell you all about it
As best as I can tell he was on that. Send podcast to trump it been on
Mike Tyson but beyond that I don't believe it he did
I'm also not impressed by Landing an interview with Mike Tyson in 2022
Don't know if that's
Like most people are banging down his door for an interview like obviously not great
If you would have gotten an interview with him in 1995 like when he got out of prison after he rape that lady
At least been like people were trying to talk
Would have been turning down some media appearances
This is just like
Yeah
It wasn't audio
Mike Tyson will talk to you
Is that I know the pathway that he got to Mike Tyson with
And that's frustrating for me because
I know that
Tom Segura and Mike Tyson are fairly good friends so I'm assuming that it went
Alex to Joe to Tom
Into Mike Tyson
I imagine it might even be a shorter Road
That's possible
Because Alex does have a bunch of
Because of Joe bunch
Associations in the MMA and like
Like fighting World strip
It's called
Yeah
I don't know
I'm not impressed
I don't care
See what Alex produces but
If that's what he was out there to do so far and that's what we know about these on that one podcast
I'm not imagining this going to top his holes
We can get the Bohemian Grove thing you know the thing that launched his f****** career
I mean Mike Tyson also has an adult swim cartoon rights
Mike Tyson
I imagine if
Like Mike Tyson
Bigman star of it hasn't lost sponsors
I'm talking to Alex probably is going to lose his sponsorship
Yeah man
I'm not I'm not convinced his trip was as amazing
Is it a zebra
You can talk a little bit more about this as the show goes on but goes to break
Play Kenny comes
This is so dumb
Tycoon
So for what it's worth Rammstein is a pretty left-leaning ban politically speaking
Mark pedophiles if they were in America
This song is called angle
His poetry at because
Disinterment and he knows it out the audience's
Was not along and think that he
He's deep
Henry ality it is fairly poetic but it's a
Deeply anti-religious song about the lead singer doesn't want to be an angel and how the idea that if you're good at
If you get to be an angel
Bulshit
Alex would hate just about everything about Rammstein from their politics
It's their support the lgbtq community
Music sounds angry
And Alex likes to yell
So he can
It's about how you feel
Alex
I hate that song I remade it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter
Like all of their songs that are like single
That have come out
That probably is the one that he should hate them
But I'm at least Du Hast is kind of like
It's vague enough it's not
Explicit
Fake your way through that you hate me or you have me
Can I have the American version is you hate
Anyways
But if you
You don't have a choice
To care
Conservative world
Because conservatives may call the worst media
They make all the worst music they make all the worst movies they make all the worse it out there probably some good like outlaw
Country types we've been conservative
Look up I'm not saying that
Okay maybe the exception that proves the rule the point is if all you've got is the best
Christian music you've got you're not going to be as happy as the rest of
That's that's probably true really have much choice
Take care you can't be like all this I got to listen to only music in other languages we can pretend
Patriot messaging
That makes perfect sense
Epso
Alex gets to complain about Joe Biden
Is that the matchup he's on meth
Which one
Time in which B
Well I mean yeah but which one that we know that he's dead no no no no no that's that's in Project
Still just one Joe Biden the cardigan
And how do you stablish mcginn continue
Front of cameras
What's about to come out
The blond
Black kids roaches
If you sit there and
That's crazy
Will you don't help people with dementia
Please somebody with dementia that they give methamphetamine to
Is people
I'm giving back the blood
Islamic Society of civilization it really is drug
I was out in California
One of the biggest
Famous person
What's
If you smoke marijuana
A cultural thing like a piece by
Bonded me another route
I'm still laughing
Referring to hang out with Mike Tyson and going to do that.
He was out there and it was pretty
Armstrong which is obviously
Soros attack
The story of his vacation sound so desperate and pathetic
He's a flu to California to be on a podcast
Is no podcast is worth flying
Across the country to be Gaston
Maybe if you're an up-and-comer
Trying to make a name
For yourself then you could see like
Let's are you
Comic who went on the road with the friend of Rogan's
F****** amazing
Get an offer to be on Rogan
B career-making click
Does that he's already the most important person in Media
Junior varsity Roca
Open podcast
He went to Florida to be on flagrant-2 and now he's going to California to be on
Full send
It just seems really f****** thirst
I think
And here's my hair's my suspicions
He abs
Absolutely does not trust
That he can make a voice call last long enough without the crew screwing something
Wow
I mean
That's probably a good theory so shity
I look up Skype breaking up
I can't even
Skype on my own show
Let alone for someone else's
How does the audience not get suspicious about all these trips
CC
Taking all the while yelling about how desperately needs money to keep the show going
Summit set off some alarms
These people like
He could pretend that he's doing like important
Grantee globalist business or something like I'm meeting with people behind the scenes
Clout
Otro topless on Pulsar Jetson belay and be like hey congregation needs to give me a
Another jet in there like
Imperative
Alex is no Joel Osteen
7 stroke
Alex that got high
Well you was at in California
I guess you know you can
Control California
Smoked
One sitting
What somebody whose initial start
End weather
It's going to be here
Literally
Feel like marijuana
90 watt occasionally smoke it is easy still high
A couple days later from this
Cali weed
Nothing quite like those kids
Haha
You didn't
You didn't actually see
Is your life
I will agree with him
When I was young
Are you a get like
Swag
Tweed was not nearly
The potency that they receive
Example
I don't know if you're going to be high 2 Days Later
No small town Illinois didn't get me past maybe 10 12%
And now you go up to
To 2829 you're going to have a good day goes numbers didn't mean anything
Sing to me back when I was totally
No I'd like to eat
I didn't know I didn't know there was
Such a thing as a contact
And that's what I'm saying now
If you're worried about it
You don't have to smoke the most
True
Oh you only want 15%
You can just
Not you got to do it once
You go to l.a.
There is just
Plentiful
Marijuana
Whirlpool weaponize everything else everywhere
The chemical bio attack
Protect America
Discussion
About this
Everyday People
I'm serious California weed I can barely get off
It is anybody
Cali dro
It's so fun to live in two different worlds of weed legalization you know cuz he still lives in that
You can get
Are we
You know you can have a weed
Right you do not like
You can go to a store where they have the thing you want
Yeah
Sacrifice
It's made for the greater good and I like
I can't believe how selfish he is getting high with Mike Tyson so he could be a mug
The stone people and get the word out about the New World Order or something
Like what I f******
Gyro place in you and small town tax
You need to support the man
He's going to go
The California and get high with Mike Tyson right now for you
Brigham knowledge
To the people
Being I'm like Jesus really like I was a monk
What's the Riff Raff
Received the same word of Salvation that you a bum YouTube
Is amazing
Wasted on Rogan's
Show cuz he needed to get them
Need to be monks
People got so drunk on Logan
Impulse show that Logan
Co-host with subtly trying to get him to
To stop drinking through the show
I got so drunk on his first time he took off his shirt and seemed to be in an active blackout
Part of the Infowars
No problem with Subs
Like honestly more fun
To be f***** up
Like that that nothing to do with
You know there is a field of anthropology that studies entirely about how much better it is to be high
In the exact moment you're in
It's not historical anthropology
It's just that's just doing drugs
Alex
Guy gets off this whole Cali weed
Go back to talking about the Pope
Shreeja couple these headlines there for you
Catastrophe
Costco
Could extinguish human race
I really should do the whole show on that
You do
Absolutely telling the truth it looks like there's another on take on this one
Suppose the business-like Harrison stupid ass did it
At the top of the show
Sure we hate the Pope
But in a situation like this you lose Nothing by just agreeing with the Pope and say
He accidentally got this right or is it
Reason to be right or something
That's the right move here from even a drop of integrity
He said
They should be huge
Problem between Harris
Send Alex
Disagreeing about a news story this is a deeply rooted
Theological disagreement
Because
Harrison believes
The pope is wrong at least in part because the Bible doesn't say that Humanity goes out like
Super Alex entertainment is a possibility
That should be heretical talk
According to Harris
None of this means anything because this is a company full of extreme right-wing Zealot conman Liars
But I point this out to illustrate that if any of these people at any of the
They claim they did they could
Could never covid
Austin work together it would just be
Constant
Violence we would never be in this situation if they believed what they said because
Cuz he would never have said that the Pope
Was lying about the end of the world
Because
He believes that the world is ending I don't know about the inner workings of Infowars after this episode Harrison might
Have stapled the 95 Theses on
Alex's office door there maybe it's isn't happening within Infowars
Spoken out of turn
Martin Luther
Again
Blowing us
So Alex has been gone for a bit
And
And I have these been gone
Situation
Ukraine has
Continued
How to be bad
Yeah that's got better
Mitch
Calculator
Why did he is
Foreign Service FSB head there their they're CIA
Pad
Why did they tell them that
Everybody was going to surrender
Directions to be in big trouble
There
A secret
You know Boonton do that
He sure as hell has arrested the head of the FSB foreign intelligence service
Dangerous
Yahoo news
Exclusive secret CIA training program Ukraine
Directions
I didn't start 2015 started in
Teen
Okay
So first off right off the bat this is no similarity with Alex's coverage of things before the
War started
There's a completely new narrative that he's pretending is been what he was saying all along
Domesticated
Because Alex is a militia
Also the CIA was founded in 1940
37 and you Brave didn't withdraw from Soviet Union till 1991
I guess when I was his 1945
This means the end of WWII so I guess at that point an organization that didn't exist yet was providing military training
To Country if it wasn't an independent country at that
It makes total sense
Yahoo news article that Alex is talking about is about how after the 2014
CIA groups
Did teach some tact
Text Ukraine
Soldiers
But why
A secret or nefarious
From the article
After Russia's 2014 incursion the US military also helped run a long-standing publicly acknowledged
Training program
For Ukrainian troops in the country's western region
Far from the front lines
The program also included instructions
How to use Javelin anti-tank missiles
And sniper training
The story also includes about the
CIA providing
Santee
Mistletoe
I'm not saying this is a non-story it just doesn't carry the same kind of weight that Alex needs at 2
Also in terms of Sergey abesada the head of the fasb you got arrested
Generous story about that
Alex wants to create the image that everything Putin does he's okay
So in this case
Ffsb was aware of State behind that works
Didn't tell Putin about them so that he would set
Rightly arrested
Looking at it a different way it might be the case that Putin
Is realizing that this whole thing is making
I'm looking little bit weak
In an ordered shows about a subordinate to blame and make
Scapegoat
This is again an example of Oz editorial decision
Clearly revealing his position
You rationalize literally anything that Boudin does
Nuke the us out to get on air the next day and say that Soros made him
That's the point we're at now
It's
Bizarre
It is very funny
That his question
About why Putin
Who did this
You know like
Why was why is
You failing why wasn't his intelligence very good
The actual answers to that
Could be very useful to Alex as well
Such as
Maybe autocratic leaders
To control everything
Don't like
Hearing bad news about how their military can't do stuff
Only good things and only have things reinforce
Only have people follow out their orders the way that they're supposed to
And when you do that sometimes
If you have bad intelligence
You make a huge
Drastic mistake
That you continue to do
For long after you should have that will eventually lead to you losing Millions upon Millions upon millions of
So maybe
Alex having everybody tell him
Things are going great
Instead of
Going on a military Adventure across the country do podcast
We can't afford it something along those lines everybody's like a boss
Getting that tank was there all great ideas
I'll leave you
Your kids
Stay behind Networks
Whatever whatever metaphor here
And the first war after World War was not
Korea
45 in Ukraine
Military history books
But
Lilly on the Cold War
Has descended down at Churchill said
Eastern Europe
My network
The Nazis had
The US came in that's why they recruited
Klaus Barbie
Josef Mengele and and all the rest of them
What so they can
Rolos Networks
Hold off the Soviets political
And overthrow Zenni
Successful
Pocono stay behind that works never
Went away
For hundreds of years
It'll still be going to plan on
I received
The Sprout perfectly
Miracle-Gro
Civil War
When Sorrows did that
Tesoro's beautiful
Call Mom
In World War
Beautiful,
Popping back up
Because they were just laying there dormant
For 75 years
Their children
This metaphor completely Got Away pallets
Control
He's trying to make his audience think of the Vols operation gladio
Isn't involved in any of this
Reality
We're talkin about here
This all sounds pretty good
Fun metaphor there like Seether never die Soros planted the seeds of rebellion the lay dormant until the uprising
This feels good for Alex
To say or like laying out the
Does metaphor until he starts realizing what he
You saying
He runs into
Two very serious problem
The first is that seeds don't live
Ivy I was going to
I was going to say.
Most are not viable after a few years
And this is
The case when they're properly stored and
Preserve
There are some ancient seeds that have been viable and could be planted but they're absolutely the except
Not the rule
Do you want to see between viable and still planted was a Judy and palm which is 2,000
Years old but the next oldest is
100 years old
My oldest CD
It's been able to be terminated
That's a big
Jump
The big
700 years
With almost 50%
Of the
The time
It's really rare for this actually work
Hoaxes where people plant seeds that they claim are old but they're actually just current Daisy
Houses probably seem like Daily Mail headlines about these hoaxes and assume that happens all the time
I'm not sure why you said it was Papyrus but I guess who's
Just because that's a word
That sounds like an ancient thing
The second problem is that when he started the metaphor I don't think you realize how far back he was going
If you stay behind networks were set up in 1945 then assuming the members were eight
18 at that point they be like
109 know what you don't understand is that they were shot of the rocket at relativistic speeds
Alpha Centauri okay and then when they got back around
But see because they were irrelevant to do they didn't age
Okay right
Is it raining the whole time
Think that your theory is interesting but as soon as that isn't
The case is good as his they will be 100 years old and I don't know how effective hundred-year-old stay at work would be
Ha rappelling
Russian invasion
I saw Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade and that old dude did not fight well
100 years old is tough for an infantryman
Realizes his mistake and how dumb that sounds so he says that it's the children and grandchildren of those stay by Networks
This is so stupid
He can't prove that these networks exist and even if he did now he has to somehow find a way to show that they pass down their positions Jen
Generationally
This is really really dumb stuff and it's just leaving me disaffected Alex he's still high
I think you might still be high
Performance
I do like the idea of something
Teenager being behind Network you're going to be able to stay behind Network
Miracle-Gro on us
Dad
You will be
I was going to stay behind Network my father before me with a rhino
We're unstable network family
That's great
Alex
Knows a lot
About the situation
Historically
Between
Russia in
That's why I like
Everyone thinks he's a bad guy
Casinos facts
Like things that were put out by Putin and press releases
We hate people who know if
Yeah but
He's not taking a side
That's what people can
Grasp
Do you know what the
Both sides have arguments
What's in the show
We need peace we to deal when you stop this right now
To stop
Medias
Instead of being on
Directions sites including perfect and he deserves it all in
He's right let's get behind
Ra7
Have you had to blame somebody for us in the left of the globalist
Who started dishing who drew first blood
Got the song going in it
Come down the path
New World Order
If Barack Obama George Soros
Well that kind of undercuts your whole point about the not taken aside and I'm not going to take a side
I am just going to say that is entirely Obama's fault right
MLive
Not on his side
Blameless in this situation aerial Act
They
Just reveal
Your actual position
Alex Gibbs say that he's neutral or whatever it does
Sport Bun B
Bebe
Compounded effect
Literally every piece of information that he provides
Why is Putin is Right losing his good
The death invasion is just
Install
That's the story he's the stay behind that were started in 1945 not 2015
Immediately following
Putin Faja country
It wasn't in response to something that is already happening
Obama was a Madman dictator crazy guy
One more mad
Haha
This
Clip is not
But I did I did like this
Alex
Kind of laying out this idea that what you should do
Is you should
Globalist Lee
I'm sorry what globalist
Shanghai
But being against
Understanding what they're doing.
Not going to be part of this
Find a solution
Can out of this
With this water bottle
Because of nuclear weapons and other things
Of course all this is insane
Waterloo records
I get sick
Everytime I'm there
Huge headache
Like hell
Good question
Cool
I hope I Alex didn't get covid
I guess we probably won't know for a while because he lied about it the other times they got it came to work and
Exposed entire crew to it that
You'd rather do that than admit that he might have been wrong about it being real
Seriously
Dreamcatcher
Like a California curse
Scott
With the flu
Is bio lab in Ukraine
That's where it came from
I like building Alex's solution is literally a dawn solution
Absolutely no solution
Provided herein every single one of his talking points is backing up Putin
Narrative of the war
Soros and Obama are to blame ultimately
He is just trying to wipe out these dangerous bioweapon labs
This is wall-to-wall weasel life Putin propaganda much of a coward to admit
Is real position
You can say is nuance
What species both sides
The reality of this content the information that he's covering
Is deeply one-sided
Everything he brings up
Is something metal legitimized boutin's invasion
The basically one
Person who can do that
It's not Ukraine B
Continuing this morning
And also think globalist is fun
Presenting this idea that if you want to save the world all you have to do is
A shadowy all-powerful group pavillon
Bright planets are really dumb and they come from your imagination
Hahaha I mean it was it was originally Steve Harvey's sequel to
Think Like a Man I Think Like a Woman Act Like a Man
I think
It's crazy to me that you can say okay we'll all the
Justifications for the
This war totally true and right
Yeah now I'm not on the side
I'm not saying that he is totally justified in this
By his own justification into because
If not
Why not
His justifications you Woodside are true
So why aren't you supporting
That's a very simple question that Alex doesn't want to
Piece of that is
Information are you relying on other than things
Things directly from poop
To assert
These
Talking points that Putin
That is just
Location of the Warriors being correct the person you specifically noted lied
Do you
Well you pretend that episode didn't happen
All of Alex's stories in the lead-up to the war and where the invasion happen or happens
No absolutely not
Very aware of
Did Putin the end of February
To stay behind networks and they betrayed him maybe that's what Alex is
Thinking that's what it's got to be right but still that wasn't
The topic of conversation up until this point
You'd think it'd be really important
Another headline
More that lives here
Loving
I mentioned this earlier
U.s. sending suicide drones to Ukraine
Oh wow
Headline for Alex to use because
Based on the wording of it I know exactly where
From
Other outlets reported on the story saying switchblade
Drones
The site that uses this headline
Suicide drone
Is it freeze at information liberation.
Cam
I decided to check out some of the most recent articles
Oh man
What's going on here
These storms will contribute to Russia's Glory Putin holds giant Rally impact Moscow stadium
That's not good
Zelensky delivers his funniest performance yet in speech before US Congress
Wow
I can see disagreeing with zelensky or possibly even like being
Opposed
Yes you can
Maybe
I don't know I don't know exactly how you would but
Whatever it's a position somewhere
It's another level of being a s*** had to say that speech was
Funny
This line was probably really funny to this blogger
I'm almost 45 years old today my age stopped when the hearts of more than
Do children stop Beat
I see no sense in life if they cannot stop the deaths
This is my mission is the leader of my people and the leader of my nation
So I guess that's funny
To the sky
Hilarious this one doesn't sound good quote the great Jewish oligarchs Escape Russian oligarchs Fleet
Israel in bid to dodge sanctions
Who is literally going to make a joke no
YouTube don't even need to bother with an interesting lead interesting Lee this was covering an article
Tourettes title CO2 the Great
Escape with his blog decided to add Jewish to it
Have to make the whole story really just an exercise in the empty
Somatic dual loyalty trope
Play the classic in white nationalist a Neo-Nazi
Communities
Truly weird great way to do it weird
Oh here's some important news that they decided
Patriarch Kirill conflict in Ukraine is a battle against the
International order built on gay pride parades
This was about to be spiritual leader of the Russian Orthodox church and Putin Ally patriarch
Making some really dumb,
Today there was such a test
For the Loyalty of this government I kind of pass
Happy world
The world of excess consumption
The world invisible freedom
Do you know what that test is
The test is very simple and at the
The same time terrible
This is a gay parade
So yeah this Saturday
A Putin Ally
Evicted stay at 8 you want in the club
Hey got have a gay parade
There is
Nothing
That gets one closer to God
Been really blaming the murder of
Thousands of people on
Gay people
That's
Here's a here's a bad one articles they post
Just before the invasion
Tell me if his blockers
Think this is a good or a bad thing
Quote
Give blood and soil speech on Ukraine unifying with Russia
Okay well that's probably
Only going to be a bad
I think as we all know the blood and soil speech is is
It's a very specific
Beginning of the article
Vitamin Putin on Monday delivered an impassioned speech
Accusing the Ukrainian government of operating a kleptocracy controlled
By corrupt oligarchs and advisors and non-governmental organization
And made the case for a reunification with Russia is what people Bound by Blood and Christianity
Don't say this website looks
Totally Above board and the sort of place that I would be shopping for articles to cover on my show if I were a lie
This is almost offensively biased and Alex knows
Is that he gets his news from aggressively pro-putin sites and espouses strictly popotan appropriate messaging
But hiding behind this facade that music
Exploring both sides
How much does this because he's fully aware the Putin is the aggressor in the war
If you stop
Attacking Ukraine there would be no further War
There isn't anything that you crank
Can do to stop the war other than acquiesce to Putin's demands and essentially no longer be a sovereign country
How to play the game of
Just consistent with the warranty
Sounds great if you're not paying attention
Does need to end
I was just pretending that the guy who supports isn't the only person who can make that happen
And it means
Just totally ridiculous
Aires
This
This attempt
Pure like moderate wow the same time
Like you're taking your news from this
F****** blog
That is disgustingly pro-putin tobacco love
Mocking
Itsfunneh
Zelensky speech
Where he discusses needing help
Right and the civilian
Rapping killed
Yeah it's
I mean
What I see from this
From so much of that especially the people trying to like run interference for it
Is
It's
Smart to get people to think it's okay to
To murder people based on false
If you are a conservative
It is
You know you don't want to say that it's wrong for Putin to just go murder people because then people might connect that to Hugo
Going in murdering people
And then you won't be allowed to do it I think there might be some of that underneath the surface but I think there's also a
Pot committed kind of thing in poker terms which Alex has built up
Who has the enemy of the globalist
And all this in
Into
Accept and admit that he's carrying out and
Award that is unnecessary and is targeting
Sure is terrorizing people
It would lend you
Require you to take the side of the
The quote-unquote globalist and Alex can't get himself to that point I feel like it's not that hard to
To go from
Putin miscalculated
Putin's trick.
You know just being like he's a liar
He lied to me just say he's a liar and he's a secret Gobal global Assault
Secret globalist double-time cuz he's fighting gets Ukraine that is full of Soros and stay behind Networks
Trump is a secret Patriot for 50 years
That didn't work
Do you think about this to there is no hope for this auntie globalist
Leadership
If Putin
Isn't that
Do you have that you have bolsonaro
Rally
Brazil is not a insignificant country a world superpower
To create
Kind of
Situation where there's a multipolar world
I guess of
Potential hostility
Against the the the UN
Global government
Like you need
The superpower to be led by an
Anti globalist person
Hey Matt is dead
Putin is required
For that
I would take her one
Literally being like surprise
Weevil
Sure there's no hope
For the
The possibility of life
Leadership
Nothing like Trump is gone
Yeah
Probably not coming back
Maybe is
But even if he does it's not going to be like
We've played that game already it's
It's
Sour grapes
Shaffer for Alex
I think that's a big part of
What he can
Give up on
It is that like
A student where to
Strong man can't lose
If a strong man loses he's not strong and that McCabe lose if you're against
And then your ideology or your the story that you're telling
I think eight
Continue past NY
We don't know about Casey's next
Setback
So get another headline
Something baby headline I don't know
White House Press briefing
There's a bunch of women
That's one little bit of sexism they're great
Who told Alex that women were against the war
Well considering that one reason he hated Hillary Clinton so much was that she was a warmonger
True seems like it will be hard
Had to go back now and say that women are against War
I think maybe he's
Thinking of Greta thunberg
AR buddy
So this was a compilation of clips of reporters in the pressure of asking if there was a point where Biden would see is like a red line
It does come off a bit bad preoccupation with the idea of a larger
But these reporters weren't begging for a war
Too much as they were trying to get information
Taking report
I want the main questions on the reader's Minds presumably as whether or not there's a situation whereby
Consider sending troops
How do I get to spend my time defending it but Alex
Is misrepresenting
This clipping weirdly
How using it has a strange attack on women
Sure
Why not fund
It seems like the the
Obama lesson
Just don't say
Openly that there's a red line
When it gets crossed and you don't do s***
What about it
You're f***** I think that's probably a great Paula
In general don't make that kind of
Specific
I b 2
It's due
Chaotic
Altering the chaos we got a guest coming in
Haven't heard from you in awhile
Welcome ladies and tell him he's got freely on the best experts we could have on about
Spoiled
Went to harbordale universities and got the
Special degree PA
The only hand out once
Someone kissing
Forgot the same one
Kissinger administered we got that
The anglo-american
So you like
Yeah
Route of the u.s.
Chemical in the lighter biological
Weapons laws
That was instrumental in
The UN treaties well-heeled
Are you in
I also prosecutor and some of the biggest
Everglow somalogic
Here really interesting I'll Francis Boyle stop
Showing up on the show for a really long stretch where Alex
See much money and pushing the Wuhan lab
Conspiracies
Either because the audience was getting bored of them or because there wasn't any new territory
To cover their
Either way without that being a Hot Topic Francis Boyle is straight-up worthless as a guest
He's boring
He seems like a crank in order to introduce him in a way that the audience alike
You have to lie about his
Double quick erection
Loyal wrote wasn't adapted into the wall
Do you and uses
The US version boil wrote was adapter
From the UN version
Alex always lies about this be
Because his version makes
The pier like boil is influencing international law
As opposed to the reality
He was just a dabbing International lawsuit would apply domestically in the United
Actually
Because think about that that's
What a global
Well what he had to do was remove the use
From color
Because an American colors are have the you
I mean
That's a pretty big
United Nations to United
Yeah yeah that stuff that is also he wasn't a prosecutor let alone the lead one
The case against melosa
In that case
What you be opposed to that because that's the case was heard in the UN
Can't believe has any jurisdiction
I don't know why
Some you win some you lose
Doesn't want to get into the weeds with boils resume because he represented the provisional
Government of the State of Palestine as well as many Native groups
Like the Lakota Nation
Andy was formally on the board of Amnesty International Alex
It's called a child trafficking operation in the past
How do I appreciate some of the folks at Boyle's represented with this dude sucks Ukraine biolabs
Is flying around 2 Alex
Remember the boy exist
He's got to try this boring-ass down for a chat
Fun
Great
Great so we got boil in there to justify Putin killing
Alex
They get into the bio lab thing
He's also
Biological weapons
Frustrated in that
Obama and others Winton
Basically refurbished their labs in Washington Post
Ukraine expert has a collar
And then the media simultaneously
I am in your Russian agent
Two of them
USA Today
Weather
I told you land of Beyond
Beyond the Tea Party in Alice in Wonderland I mean this this is just
6 brass balls to accuse something of being like the tea party when that's what you called your
Political party
Realwear
So here's the game was being played
Alexandra's weirdo propagandist Friends making incendiary
Accusation based on years old Russian propaganda in Russia used
Asians like in Georgia
Alex says there's bio-weapon Labs run by the US and Ukraine
And starts building a conspiracy about how that's why Putin is
Is invaded
Then we made out of originated
The claim he amplifies it
Elaborate stories to flesh out the
To the point where a bunch of idiots online or convince
Got made
Push back
And say that this is ridiculous
And there aren't bioweapons lab
In Ukraine
They aren't saying that there aren't any biological labs
Country and are covering up us support for the modernization efforts
But they are pushing back against the stupid over Blanca
Conspiracy
Now Alex is taking those denials and pretending they were actually denying that there were no labs
In the country
This is super confusing to him
Things get confusing when you just make sure it up all the time and attack your imaginary enemies
You constantly lose the thread
Do you imagine what they're saying back in
Adult
Exhausting
Also Obama has nothing to do with the starting of this partnership between Kiev in the United States in terms of modernizing those labs
That dates back to at least 2,000
And the weapon non-proliferation treaty we signed with them years before Obama was President
Also if Alex has 1945
USA slow
Articles about Obama
Ukraine
How was there no mention of this in the lead-up to The Invasion
It seems like if all this s*** would be relevant and it's definitely a large part of its coverage now but it feels like is only week
Campbell talking point Alex was aware of
After Putin
Inline media started pushing
The story is a means to just
Supply that invasion
Seems weird that that wasn't even
Wasn't even
Turtle in Alex's mind if the days before the invasion
Yeah yeah
Weird
I do like the I do like that
Like they refurbish them how evil and shouldn't it be a simple question of like a
What do you want
In foreign bio lab
Do you want them to have drips dropping from the ceiling
And Lakeisha
Or do you want it
To be safe
There's that
Reason why
Labs
Require
Keeping some of these samples around
Some people often don't understand exactly why that is one of them
Never discussed by Alex
That in order to
To calibrate
Testing
You need a sample of the thing right that you would be testing for in order to assure that this thing works
Machine works
That's what I want by 11
Seems like
Is like
Important
High-risk high-level stuff and
You know I think
Knowing that you need to keep you samples on hand whether it be for
Some kind of a test
Sometimes it
Experiment or some kind of
Calibration of equipment
You need to be safe
You needed
Pedicure
And that was a large part of the u.s. involved
Hi there already
I mean the conspiracy mind is that preparation for a disaster is preparation to make
The disaster
So
Weather
What happened to that like survival food is he planning to burn all the crops in America
That's how he works
So
The boil starts
6 minutes
What is your synopsis if you were
Briefing World your briefing Millions right now
About the some knowledge of what you would call
This sleepwalking into Armageddon or what is
Thank you very much for helping out my best year
Viewing audience
With the
Promises made by Secretary State Jim Baker
And many of the other NATO leaders
That are secretary-general gorbachov
Agreed to the unification
All the of Germany
Not move to the east
1 star Clinton die
They proceeded to expand 280 to the east
The promises the Baker and the other European leaders
Beta gorbachov
War binding under international law
This is bulshit
Boyle is just repeating things he's heard
Gorbachev is giving interviews about the negotiations with Baker and he said the topic of other countries joining NATO never came up
There wasn't an agreement accepted NATO troops
Copy station
East Germany
So we're starting off here on a false premise that only serves to legitimize Boone's argument for invade
And to be clear I'm not necessarily saying the NATO expansion is a positive thing and I think there's
Is a lot of Fine Art
Commence against NATO and how it operates
What I am saying is
The claiming that native agreed to not expand with Gorbachev negotiated with Bakery is not true and even if it were it wouldn't be a
Navigation for invading Ukraine
Went to other NATO countries already border Russia
Ukraine is not going to be joining anytime soon
Bigger problem boy was supposed to be an expert in international law and I guess if
He really believes this line then boil shouldn't
Have a problem
Arguing that a pre-emptive strike against any NATO country should be just
Ossified if Russia did
Yeah
Well they were I mean you could say that NATO is
Intox with Eddie Kane
Or any countries that recently joined like Montenegro join not too long ago
And everybody's got to take down Montenegro even matoes like while we're going to go down there
Did the rationalizations and
Vacations you can make Based On Believing gas
Are are staggering
Do anything
Mama's
What's what's
So insane is when you're like
Redoing
When you're redrafting pass
Treatise
You know you're not accounting for the fact that
Putin is the f******
President of
Of Russian man we're dealing with his b*******
Not even
Really the way he's reacting to
Treaties in the past or anything like that this is a dude who is a megalomaniacal lunatic
Who is trying to read
Form the Soviet Union it wouldn't matter if NATO was weaker or stronger imagining like
Kind of a reality where he hasn't broken for you
Yeah what are we doing
Absolutely
They're really parses Act
See how well that holds up
Speaking of treaties
Boyle is Mother dump
December as you know
Russian government submitted to treaties to Nato
And to the bidens ministration
I've read them I won't go through all of them here that was a wish list okay
Why was
Russia wanted assurances
That Ukraine was not going to join NATO
And that NATO would not expand se2
Moldova
And Georgia which are right there too
In this area
For two months
Z
Conformist
Lulu sweet negotiating
With the bike Administration over this
And refuse absolutely refused
Assurances
Which insured have given because
They were required by the promises that Jim Bakker have made
Who cares
Boyle's World Boonton is asking for assurances of things that are already established International laws
Biden's response doesn't matter
However if boiled wrong and all this didn't happen and there was no guarantee that it's really just food making demands in
Listen to them
Yeah also there's a reason to boil isn't going into the details about these
A treaty to man
It's because they're a bit over-reaching
Suggested that they were designed to be rejected to give the appearance of trying to have a diplomatic approach
One request
Is the demand that they do not expand
Specifically to include Ukraine but also generally to not any other country
The other main request is a little sticky
This wanted Biden shoes now
That might have been fine
Was that they wanted they do to agree to not deploy any troops or weapons
Any country that have joined NATO past 1997
I doubt that would be to be fine
The day was 1997 because that was when it agreement was signed
Between NATO and Russia called the founding act on Mutual
Cooperation in
Security between NATO and the Russian
Confederation
This was an agreement aimed at warming relation
Pacifically deals with
He's not deployed nuclear weapons to member
Also weirdly in that document with both the both
NATO and Russia agree to it says quote
Needle has expanded and will continue to expand its political functions and take on New Missions of peacekeeping and crisis management
In support of the United Nations in the organization
For security and cooperation
Europe should be in there based on boils understanding
Things like why would Russia agree to a document
That says NATO has
Expanded and will
Expand because they've already paid off the rush
Military in
Zielinski
It's all making sense now
Being 45-45 is when he first took office
Alright
I asked that Russia was making at the end of 2021 was a non-starter
Because essentially what it would do is make a NATO say that these countries that have joined since 1997
The Czech Republic Hungary Poland Bulgaria is
Estonia Latvia Lithuania Romania Slovakia Slovenia Albania Croatia Montenegro
North Macedonia right they would all be in the alliance but also if they're in trouble NATO wasn't going to be able to help
Undermine the entire premise of an alliance
Anson leave all these countries on their back foot unprepared for a possible encourage
Also from 1997 to 2014 there what it wasn't a super common practice for States
Send troops
Happens to new member states unless there was an emergency
Change
Putin
Invaded and annexed Ukraine if you cry me up
Right perspective
Naturally this isn't
An agreement that bite
When is going to accept
And guess what even if you wanted to
He couldn't
It will be up to Nato
They revoked
Find doesn't run NATO
Herb oil to climb with this was a sincere effort on Putin
Barton that there was a rejection of
Pizano
Is completely absurd and reveals only that he's probably a big
Consumer afar rape
Sporting media probably like Reeds information Liberation over breakfast
It's sad
Nonsense I find it hard to believe that
If Biden were to come out and could have
Picture later to every demand that Putin made believe the far-right would be like
Great idea for the leader of our Sovereign Nation
Giving a weakness
Are you giving an inch now take over America
But I doubt these people
I hate speaking dumb things gives no dumb pot boil has
Even today
I'm in favor
Stopping War
It could be stopped today
President by where to get up and announce
Yes Ukraine will not be joining
Already said that will not be expanding to the east in Georgia Moldova
Or elsewhere
And the rest were prepared to negotiate
Certainly over
Removing
US nuclear weapons for Europe
This is so stupid
NATO won't expand means nothing
He doesn't control that unilaterally it even if he did I thought the premise of war was supposed to be about
Be notifying
Ukrainian or shutting down bio-weapon labs are
Taking back a dumb bass region
Is rightfully Russia's and under attack by Ukraine
I'd arrive lost
The plot I don't really know what we're supposed to be justifying anymore I feel like if you have these just
Vacations
Then before April
Peace treaty even including
You get we're not NATO's not going to move all this stuff
Right they would have to handle the
Ukraine
Situation
So if you wanted to have a
Peace treaty then you would have to say
Okay well Ukraine's going to give up
Its leadership of itself
It is going to put everything under the control of Putin's Russia Now consume only Russian
Promedia for as long as it takes for them to stop
Listening to the West ever
I feel like
A little bit past that being like
Going to work maybe a little salty
Because it is incredibly frustrating
Try to pay attention to
All these
Various reasons why this is
Invasion is okay
Consistency the point changes from day-to-day and yet what remains and his ever-present
The insistence of Infowars is totally right
And they whatever they're saying
Today's what they said all along
I know this isn't news but
It's really getting to me a little bit more than usual admittance because there's
Boyle's functionally advocating for like you brought up as a complete acquiescence to food
And the surrender of
Ukraine to his rule
He may not think that's what he's saying and the other bunch of bad
He wishes to see
Is wherever one resistant Putin's invasion of Ukraine
Just stop and let him take over
I mean that's the end
Maybe if you're only
Conversation if your thoughts on how to stop the war have
Nothing to do with
Ukraine whatsoever entirely about
NATO not expanding then you're just saying that Ukraine should be blue
At this point
Boyle brought up the
That treaty
Tremblay class
Last year and Alex
Decides to Riff on it a little
And so it is true that all these trees expire the US did not want to go shade
Let them expire
This again is wow
They cut all their
Major provocation
I'm going to get your take on that we come back and talk about
Where this is all going
Oh man a major provocation is totally justified
This action
What treaties is Alex trying to claim
Expired specific at all what the f*** is he talking
Tannin
Treaty Albert
There was a nuclear non-proliferation treaty called the new start
Began in 2011
Really work well for Alex
Argument but it was Channel 5 years
Until 22
Sex
That agreement was announced in March 2021
Re-signing it
Considering the treaty with a high priority
Biden
I don't think that this is what I was talking about
The fake story about it a me but he just assumed that they didn't extend it or something
I don't know
I think what's going on is there to boil is brought up in this b******* about
Demand food was making
Right now is writing a bigger story on top of all of it
It's all just an exercise in excusing Putin's invasion
Literally all day
The show is
At this point
That is
F***** up
It's f***** up
Domino's say about that
What's up with this club is even more f***** up
And as I said they're using Ukraine in Ukrainian
As a battering ram against the Putin government
And against the Russian Federation
And so it makes the West
What looks like
Guess it's just continue song
I'm going to have to
Hey listen
When you're fighting two Wars sometimes you just have to commit atrocities
I mean on Fortune
Italy think
That that is
Trudeau
Descriptive
But I went to the speaking of this kind of
Moralistic
I think that the carrying out of War
Almost always
Involves
Atrocity
It is an atrocity
Definition
And that is a good reason to be opposed
To war
On a general base
Alex seems to be
First of all
Denying
The atrocities that have already taken place
So that's
Traveling
I meant
Call me sometimes you commit atrocities no big deal
Strategic thing just choose to
Kill a large number of civilians
In order to end the war that you started
Because Nazis were killing Civic weigh
Killed ukrainians ocean
No
Nope
It's it's outrageous
Comically pro-putin
How do you see this gut-level ending right now
Deal
Looks like deals are coming
He's going to have to ask like somehow to try to
Defeat these embedded
Nazi forces that are are high
Thread that needle
Western propaganda against
I really don't know Alex
Wow I just
I find it shocking boil just like accept the premise
Just crazy
I don't know Hey listen
I don't know how he solve this imaginary problem
Play without Escalade he's going to have to ask
The US
Is it making a deal
No it's entirely the web of course
It's not alike
Zelensky isn't make
Making a deal
Cusd80 says he'll do because he's going to be
Beat wait no he doesn't
To join NATO
Desperately wants
The deals we can save face
Get out of here with a little bit of strength intact right but it's not coming so he's going to have to
Well I mean
Alex seems like legitimately to be preparing his audience to accept
Really f***** up stuff
No.
Absolute
There's no other
No other
Solution great that he's talking to like an international law expert on war crimes
And it's like and it's like that
What is that's his idea of
Realpolitik
You know like
Okay well
He's in a bad bargain
Position you know he's losing
The war
So he doesn't want to get a deal now
Cuz they won't
Good terms for her
You understand Dan
He doesn't want to deal right now cuz they won't be good terms for him
What are you doing
The deal you want to deal with it
For him so
If he commits atrocities
Bended deal might be sweeter for him
And Alex is fine with that
Because it's all about the deal man it's like
Alex's ideal ruler is MBC
Fighter movie
Maybe something to that
Anyway boil Legacy
Oven sound like a broken record
Dudes dumb
I think we have
The demand
Jet biting himself
Publicly Proclaim
Ukraine will not
Join NATO
This is a dumb bullying tactic because the demand is something meaningless
The hope is that you have some sort of the meaning of symbolic action
Seeds power-to-the-people making that depends ivy
Russia
Putin
And align propagandist
Blackout you got it
Also in June 2021 by Moses at a press conference about Ukraine joining NATO
It depends on whether they meet the criteria
The fact is they still have to clean up corrupt
Meet other criteria to get into the X
Action plan to
School's out on that question
It remains to be seen
And it will not just depend on me
Whether or not we conclude the Ukraine can't become apart
Tornado on the alliance and how they vote
There's a world reality that Biden
Can't wave his hand
The Forces Group to vote the way he wants them
However there's an infant
Pretend reality were a big strong man ruler
Just do whatever he wants
So the fact that fighting isn't
These things means he must not want to
It wouldn't believe middle school-level s*** and I feel pretty embarrassed for these dudes talking like this public
And to clarify
Trump was able to do a lot of s*** unilaterally but
You might notice
But all the stuff he did like that were times when he pulled the us out of
He never deserted his will over these organization
They're groups with his strength
You just didn't get his way and withdrew
Do you know how to relax
Now you see that might be an explanation of how they think the world works
Trump is like
You have to do what I say
And they're like
No
And he's like
Well then I am going to go back to a world where people have to do what I say and you are not involved
I am taking my ball and going
Going to Blackmail the lynskey
So Alex is
Steven the conversation with boil about dumb
Immature nonsense
Illinois
Damn it may be just outside Chicago or in Chicago
Rolling Meadows
I'm not saying I want to fight him but I will call him a baby to his face
A big dump
I'm a little bit salty
So Alex is talking to boil
This one conversation and Alex gets
Distracted by
Important breaking news
Arnold Schwarzenegger has just gone live infowars.com
Video of it
German translation
Please bring them in German
Whataburger
German
Father fought the Russians now they're fighting today
Ceiling
I mean
Like Twilight Zone Stalingrad
I did fax
We fight in these areas
I was in the SS
Arnold wasn't speaking German in that video he's speaking Russian
He was appealing to the people of Russia and it's really interesting but probably an effective way to see the way that Putin is
To them but what's going on in Ukraine
It's not mostly about his dad so Arnold doesn't hide that is that was fighting
For the Nazi
He does literally mean
Videos about Arnold's love for Russia and the people of Russia and its first weightlifting hero with a guy
Name Yuri petrovich of a sloth
Have you met your fourteen-year-old boy
Arnold Dad didn't like that he idolized Yuri because as Arnold
Explain ski was injured in Leningrad quote
What are the Nazi army that he was a part of did vicious harm to the great City in
It's brave people
The video touches on how we got to meet Yuri again as an adult when he went to Moscow again to film red heat
The first American movie those permitted to film
In Red Square
Essentially it's a very compelling argument that Schwarzenegger
As a deeply felt
Connection to the people of Russia and the country itself
Outside criticizing that it doesn't
Something like this
Committal make a real difference
I don't know what the complaint about this video is
Like it's definitely less cringe-inducing than other celebrity videos we've seen it ain't got to say that it feels very sincere
Like a memories really do
Mean a lot
Donald
Very important too I think
What was it
One of the mr. universes
Everyone was
Like
IDrive
Stump some videos like broadcast on
Russian States
TV one of the biggest
Things that they've seen
It's such an interesting intersection of his lived experience to with don't like
Being the son of an Austrian
Former
Nazi Soldier
Who idolized a Russian weightlifter that got him
Like really motivated into that world actually ended up creating his career
Our leading to his career.
Intersection of
That like lineage of coming from somebody who hated Russians because of his
Experience in World War II
To being somebody who sees the country and the people for the beautiful
I think that it is
I don't know it
Obviously like I'm saying
I don't think it's going to move the needle in terms
Of world affairs Council
But I do think it's a more valuable
Video to watch
Then
The Imagine video
What is going around about that if I was Putin
Mom yeah
You don't like that stuff nonsense at least had some substance to it
If only as a
Like a sort of
Moving
Autobiographical
Slice of Arnold
Tickets addressing it did remind me
Message of course but it did remind me like I
It went back
Can I restart a remembering
Schwarzenegger's life
Just going
This man is a car
Cartoon character
Dislikes
It's not real but I kind of like watching you get like you.
Kind of why he won Governor like today
You forget
Like you see the movies and he's like
Goodwill drop off
Write a big muscley weirdo shoots people and rice
A strange accent it's never explained in the movie
But there's a compelling
Missing person
Still just mad that
Derail that campaign back is still just mad at Arnold probably anyway
Import
News
We got to get it
I'm clearly the way I want to talk about you can tell he hasn't walked
He doesn't know what this is
Reporting on Imaginext
You know that right
If you'd watch this
Boyle is
He's somebody who
Like I said
Drafted the indictment
Against Melissa
That's right he's somebody who has
At least a level of Gravitas in terms of
The world of international relations
You should
Be somebody who understands
To be careful
With his words
And if you wrote
Slobodan milosevic is indictment you should probably be aware that Putin is
Has got a real good shot
I didn't offer close to that apparently not only goes the other way
Yes these reports
Coming out of
Are fully consistent
With the United States government
Supporting
Biological warfare
Against Russia
If you take a look at the map you'll see large numbers of
Biological warfare weapons surrounding China
I've read the reports
They certainly sound a credible to me
She was actually accusing the United States
Biological weapons lab
It's literally like listen all I'm saying is Iraq should invade America we have we have wmds
I'm not saying I'm just saying I'm just saying I'm not saying but I'm just saying
And it gets worse at justifying this gets worse
There's the match
Rife
Biological warfare
Weapons facilities
They've been bought and paid for
By the Pentagon itself
Does not engage in missionary activity
I have no doubt about that in my mind
Indeed
I gave interviews to Russian news
How do I stream the DNA
Materials of Russians
And they asked me why and I said simple because
They're going to try to
Create an ethnic specific
Biological warfare
Weapon against Russians
If they can figure it out
Wow sounds
Is he telling me that this I bet he doesn't even I didn't even get paid
Probably not Irwin and
Did some f****** propaganda for Putin
Fury Shady
Listen
Find you're a monster but at least
Hey do you know you're an idiot
Yeah paid Alex plugs Boyle's book
And this is this I would have done this differently
Search
Francis a boil and find a spring
Especially
Comp
Amazon
You can find his work
That I don't know
Amazon.com amazon.com
For finding work that I don't know
Bezos
Directing traffic
We had Elizabeth Williamson on and we were talking about her new book and very specifically
We made a point
To not have the link go to go there
Stock Amazon almost like when we say that we hate Jeff Bezos
We didn't follow through
Well I mean there's no there's no need to be dramatic
Performative about it
Functionally
If anybody was going to buy
A book based on our recommendation
It would be ideal for them not to do it through Amazon and if we can direct
Traffic through a lake
To another place to get the
Body way better
Supposed to be
One of Jesus's blood enemies
One of them Must Die
Tried to get him a cut
Does it does
Do not have his own website
Where you can find his books I bet he doesn't
Like if you look at the shots of him but he's being interviewed his
Is offices
Just like piles of
He looks like he might might might be all analog baby
I'm angry that insert
Topic
Mitt Romney comes up
Sure
And he's important this is where the interview ends
But I think there's a couple things are a little problematic for Alex
Remember
He was elected in
Massachusetts is a rhino the only way he could be elected
Extreme right
And in order to work
The boots of the
Free Riders Republican party I'm not single Republican Party
But the extreme ride
And Romney tried to restore the death penalty
That weird started the death penalty the sacco-vanzetti case
In Massachusetts there in law school together
A new water Travis
See the whole thing
Reading Massachusetts.
You have to be sick and demented
To spend
Full-time like Romney did
To restore the
County in Massachusetts
Alright is a problem
First there shouldn't be any acknowledgment that there is an extreme right in terms of the political identity of people in government on this
It's not a reality that's accepted
There are GOP members of Congress who Alex thinks our Liberals are left-wing extremists like AOC
Spencer's old school Constitution Loving people
They're blue liberals on classic liberals
Speedstream right doesn't
Exist because when you consider who like
No just comes to mind with Boyle says that Romney kissed up to the extreme right
The second problem is it boils going hard on the death penalty which Alex actually supports
You think he would
Because he's so anti-government and he pretends to be a Libertarian but thank you loves the idea of the government killing his enemies
Seems like you wouldn't want the government
Who you don't trust
Right who you think is lying all the
The power to kill you.
In principle relies so much on the you know the government not being the
Solsource
Force
He's fine with the government killing people he walks on
Them to kill
Bon to this interview autograph
We have a couple of clips
Left here and
Alexandra
Talking to boil
But I want to get
I got to tell you when I saw this headline earlier
I can't be real then we went and watched it in check
German
Radiance
Anatomy
Schwarzenegger said
Arnold Schwarzenegger
Twilight Zone situation
Play some of that
Bodily harm
Dot-com
Interested
No no conversation about what's going on in my area Paul
Nothing
About
It exists in Ukraine
The type of news that Alex
Can cover is
Complaining about a imagined version of
A video that Schwartz on
Tiger put out
That's what right do end of the spear
That he has
Stupid
Yep we are kind of in a Twilight Zone episode
We're like
You can show people reality
And they can tell you they can lie
Like read word-for-word back to you what was said
And they will still tell you that Arnold Schwarzenegger was trying to be a nut
Supporter
Love by like they can't like it is such a
Oh you just don't live in
The world man
You just don't live here
Yeah
Talk more about the Arnold video
Says we should play some
Let me get to it eventually but
Coronavirus data
I am not in the point
Where
I couldn't even do the first
Show today
Because I'm sitting
Sponsorship
For money in
Just to make
Judge
Money I've got Noah
Find me
Your money in
Boiling
I like to joke a lot and have some laughs but
Sincerely here
I don't believe this s*** at all
But if this is true enforces the most
Static organization
And Alex has the worst business owner in the entire propaganda game
His number one job is to
To do his show
Which is alive
From 11 to 2 and then someone else takes over for the last hour
There's literally no reason why you can't talk to a potential sponsor before 11 or after 2
Except for a couple options that I can play
One is absolutely no power in
Situation at all
Calling all the shots now except
The bend over backwards in order
A few bucks
Yes I will take a call while I'm supposed to be on air
Be f****** with him if they're forcing him to take a call while he's on air
Says so little interest in doing any work that he's essentially only be working from 11 to 2
Supposed to be on air well
That's why he pays that Saint Patrick obsessed dork to to work there for that you wasn't talking to
Father who's talking to lawyers or Court who he can't reschedule a meeting
Think I might be more
Embarrassing level of inability to do one's job and I honestly I sent it
I also hate that's all you just want to LA to do a podcast
Do you really expect anyone to feel sympathy for your inability to make payroll
Like 10:30 last guns or get rid of the potentially
Studio like
Get rid of weird LED lighting behind your don't take a week vacation to another state to do a podcast
You need to make payroll so badly
You're over-extended
Danseaza the problem we have been out of the regular Workforce for too long
That's the way everybody I've ever had
Sorry we can't make payroll I am calling you from Hawaii right
Right now just in case you were wondering
I'm sorry I'm going to pay you next week
Your
Can't make it this week
Reminder to work for your cousin
Well not everybody
I have a different work history than you I do not have a lot of recipe
I'll tell you this the hearing aid game
Real Shady
Okay
I find that Alex's sales pitches
Seem to be like
A guy who has a bad business model
Explaining it
Beautiful
What's going on a little bit like Hey listen
I am a failure
You buy
This bowl
We were really high in the lead-up
To Trump
You're right we were crushing it
Too much
I hire too many people overhead we have too much
Rent to pay never heard of
Electric bills are through the roof
Almost like autocratic leaders don't like hearing bad news before they make
Decisions that they want I decided to make this
Dum dum free speech YouTube clone type website
And
There's no on there because no one wants
Advertise this is a sinkhole if money is real bad
Lot of Hosting
Cost
There
Oh great I have to pay in order to host
The video of the guy who dressed like Uncle Sam yelling at people on the street
He's changing the world and Harrison Smith has got 200 views on This Heart of this video
I need to be
Look Harrison doesn't have a lot of use
More than that
Alright
If there's any Solace I think that
Does not he's not long
He's already exhausted the money that he could get out of Mike Lindell
Who's conceivably glendale's
Blackguard
Breeze in the Wind
Right
I don't I don't know if side of like
Shady right-wing billionaires
What kind of
Since he might have
He could go down if he hasn't burned that bridge
Milo yiannopoulos coming back to
Isn't he our people paying attention to him in the right-wing spear again
Not real
Not really
Good I think maybe his name came up because allegedly he hooked Marjorie Taylor Greene up with
Nick Fuentes for that
Nick Fuentes have like a bit of a weird history
Because
Nick
Obviously
Outright bigot hey hey people
But he and Milo even when Milo was
Still a gay man
According to him
He was still a Catholic fashion
Frightened so like
The two of them bonded over their desire for a Catholic Tater ship
Now that Milo is a forward a man according to him
The two of them have
Les hurdles in terms of their Association
And their desire to bring about a Catholic fiachra
That shouldn't that give you pause
As for your wanting a Catholic
Dictatorship if you and the guy next to you who both want the Catholic
Dictatorship
If one of you were to get power over the other one the other one would die
Understand
Maybe
This'll Catholic dictator
Bishop is a bad idea if the guy that I like
What killed
I don't know how you get there but yeah Edwina
It seems weird
The beard is rising back to
Venereal
It's within that seeing good
But who knows who knows
He's a disgusting a exercising Putin apologia
I don't know why we came back to the Press
You know I
Was
Substantially more enjoyable
Maybe less salty
Right
How are you I am amazed
I really am amazed
You like it would feel bad
For me too
Make justifications for any
Large-scale murder
It would make me feel bad
To do it with this
Gusto
I mean in a very
Neutral term of the word
Awesome
It is
Tiring
It is like
How how is it possible that those picture of Gaston and
Pretending to be like
I'm just looking at Alside
Sure I'm not I'm not defending Putin's accident
Yeah it's a defective admission that you know what he's doing is wrong
You could read it that way yeah
It's a cowardly Augusta which is
Not something you see all too often
Beretta
The show sucks
We'll see what's happening later though
And
Another episode
Possibly something fairly
Fun on Wednesday maybe maybe something
We do it
We are on Twitter that knowledge underscore fight not go to bed Jordan
What the sex robot
Alex
Birthstone colors