Air Jordan
Knowledge party.com respect for knowledge B
Imposing a good guy or the bad guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Fix it around a little bit
Jordan
Good question for you buddy
2009 Nicolas Cage film knowing an opportunity to check back in on that film
Hold the f****** a really does
That movie is good. Actually good I've seen it made fun of too many times
It is restrained cage
But with a good freak out
It's you know it's it's it's
It's a it's an accessible Nicolas Cage
It's not like you know what you
You get some sort of just
Run-of-the-mill average everyday person
Call New Orleans
Original Bad Lieutenant
Some other caves performances probably too
Too much for the normies National Treasure you can get them in on that knowing it
What is in that Mill York
Exciting
Anyway
The movie came out 13 years ago
Google
9/11 / 2,000
I told you my bright spot is yesterday nice
Table of women at this restaurant
Bought me and my partner a bottle of wine
What oh yeah and Winos here's the worst part right
I was dressed like this
Basically I do the nicer sweater on no hood
Oki
To sit at a second hand store
Earlier yesterday morning
Right
She was wearing jeans
Nice shirt we were both walking
She had flowers
Right
And
They immediately came over and they're like oh my god did you guys just get married
And the problem was
We have
Oh and that's offensive
Because both people correctly sussed out that's as good as this Dirtbag is going to look
Wow that's as good as it gets for me
Yes
I would like to remind the listeners before I went to
We went to The Men's Wearhouse what you could have
You got a hug out of
Believe their Jordan Courthouse
Yesterday at 2 p.m. took us about
5 minutes to get the marriage license
Quick
Devon my partner's mom
She married us
The humanists celebrate
Okay take about 15 minutes we ran out we went and had dinner
Congratulation
He's great but really
I want to talk more about knowing
Congratulations I'm sure everyone out there is very happy and excited for you
It was nice
Is the best way to do a wedding
Ever
Pretty low-key in terms of the ceremony
Pretty low-key in terms of you announcing it
There was a witness
Okay huh like to cry
There wasn't an official with it
To be there
Yes we had our
Wedding Witness by an innocent bystander
That was how it goes
Kind of brings us to another point it's going to take a little bit of a trip
Honeymoon ish
There is a vacation
I'm coming up middle of April something like that release schedule.
Prepare yourself
So Jordan today not to take away not to not to Pivot away from
Courthouse that needs
Just a private Vine
So it's about
The 22nd
Within the year of Our Lord 2020
This is
Chaos there's episodes
Going to be a mess there is a lot of nonsense
Episode itself is
Perfunctory not really that's going over it there's some interesting things to discuss but
Far overshadowed
By the circumstances surrounding this episode of all that
Before we do it's like little moments say hello
So first Jordan gets me through the mic up
Thank you so much right now policy walk
Are you very much
2 ft from NOCO thank you so much for now policy walk
Very much sorry pumpkin but I'm glad we bought it over this thank you so much
Romantic themed emerging
Your nickname for your partner is pumpkin does not matter
You claim that one was on you sure
Lindsay Lawler thank you so much
Your Amazon Alexa thank you so much
Thank you very much
You
So I believe that everybody has a vague understanding of the things
Set up and going on in Alex's
Immediate past
And
I feel like we will we will dig into this hole a bit
About contacts drop from Today Show
Earbuds
Find
Leave my bugs alone
Bye bugs Pacific property issue or a bug
This does not approve of your bugs
Now it makes more sense
So I was going to put out an episode on Wednesday this week Jordan
You know this because
Your eye called
Albuquerque told things got a bit overwhelming and I wanted
Ended up laying out
Monday was an insane day for things that are related to our show
First Joe Biden use the words New World Order and in the process he gave conspiracy theorists
Justification to believe
That their particular flavor of shadowy lead cabal runs the world behind
And a big old
It was a dumb move but I was trying to say
It's not like there's a new world order it's an order that is not the same as the old and we are on the world
As soon as I heard the biting it said I was not
Publix 294 Alex's response because I feel like it's super predictable and I really have that much
More to say than we have
Leaders sometimes talk about the international order of the world
The set of relationships alliances
Trade Agreement
An enemy's internationally
Sometimes it major changes to the status quo of these relationships has become something new
It's an expression that makes total sense and there shouldn't be anything wrong with using them
Describe exactly the situation in the world
Today
I hear them and Pruitt is a guy approves of the devil's puppeteering biting at the top of the world
So we don't fight to eat our children's blood or something like
Monday evening everything got thrown into chaos
Will summer reported that Alex's lawyers had requested his deposition
In the Connecticut Sandy Hook case be postponed because of an emergency
Genesee medical situation
Apparently the afternoon it's
3:30 p.m. North Patterson received
A call that Alex was quote under the care of a physician for medical conditions that require immediate
And possibly emergency testing
Norm Drew
He doesn't pee.
Right superficial
Alex had done his show that day and was on here until like 2 p.m. and there was no sign of any particular
In addition norms
Filing claim
My client is not authorized me to disclose the nature of the medical conditions or the identity of the physician
Which is sketchy
This was all in service of trying to delay a deposition that was scheduled for this Thursday
Right
Dispose doctor had advised Alex
Sit for the deposition given his medical condition
Again seem Shady
Yeah there was a schedule at
The park may I sort of oversimplify
Wednesday in
Thursday
Delaware deposition
Yeah he had a case of I don't want to do it either
I didn't want to rush into anything and turning around to get an episode at the
Discuss this on Wednesday would have been a challenge
But at this point if you more data points have come out
The first is that Alex was in studio doing his show on Tuesday
He wasn't broadcasting from home
You didn't have Owen or Harrison cover the show so he could
Keep up the ruse that he was
It was just business as usual
Can I suspect the reason for that is that bite into a new world order and I couldn't let Harrison or Owen swing at that
Add meatball that was right over the plate
With
So hard it would make everyone cry like Alex would have to break into the studio like you would like to know
The movie like Mike Myers scream it at a smoke
This leaves
Question that still hanging in there
What's going on with that motion that Norm filed in the first place
The most obvious answer is that it could be purely an attempt to f*** with the plaintiff's case
Install the process
Legal strategy up till this point
At every turn he pulled out any trick
You can pick up to slow things down and try and create legal headaches for the opposing counsel
This would be totally within his character and I wouldn't put it past him at all
There's nothing you really stands to lose from sitting
Sing for the deposition because of Stonewall like he always does
He does have something to gain and Theory from trying to drag his feet
And try to force
The court to reschedule is trial date
Which
Much more fun for health course it wouldn't surprise me if that was part of what he was up
Justify
Yeah when I go to shot a second option occurred to me and that is the Alex could have covid again
When you got back from California Alex was complaining about feeling
I'm sick and we know that he's
Is very Reckless
And on
Tomatoes and he's guy who consistently hangs out with other unvaccinated people
And takes no precautions about getting sick
He's a high-risk category and he just took a trip to another state
So the opportunity
Please bring to be exposed to something seemed pretty decent at least
His behavior is a whole would also fit with
The covid idea because if he had covid he would
Still show up to his Studio to do the show
He doesn't give a s*** about his staff and he's admitted he already
Did that the last time she had Kobe went to the workings exposed to it
I heard that
The first thing I texted you is like well of course
She's still in the studio if he has any wood make sense why he wouldn't go to court
Wouldn't want to go to court
Is Dave take
Things like that
One of the primary reasons I didn't want to jump the gun on this is that I wanted to be able to have some
Some kind of information and not just you know come to the show with assumptions and whatever
David was filed and we learned a little bit more about this medical
Monday Alex happy complete lunatic
Fantasizes about murders doctor marbles on his show to do some fun covid denialism Khan
Contact stuff
When Marvel showed up at
The studio to do the interview his quote
Personal observations of mr. Jones
So alarm him
But he insisted on conducting a physical examination of mr. Jones
He immediately advised mr. Jones to go to an emergency room or call 911
After mr. Jones refused the physician advised
To stay home which mr. Jones did not do
Okay so if I understand this correctly
Marvel's walked into Infowars inside you look like s*** you got to go to the doctor I called
911 Alex
Appropriately understanding the doctor Marvel's is a moron
I would assume
Right off the bat we have a few problem
The first is that doctor marbles is certifiably insane
And I wouldn't take Direct
Cancel the grocery
Restore from him let alone Medical
So this is all coming from him seeing Alex getting freaked out and then I guess checking
His pulse
Whatever it was that marble saw it was enough to advise Alex
It's called 911 Sirius although again
Doctor marble
Is advice coming from a lunatic
Alex didn't take
This advice
Excuse to not go to schedule deposition
Probably would have come off a little more convincing if Alex and hadn't done his show the next day
Beverly punctures any illusion that whatever he's dealing with would preclude him
Them from sitting for a deposition God that's great
Having snub doctor marbles advice and not called 911 Alex didn't show the next day Tuesday the 20
Which is what we're going to cover
For today
Marbles was able to convince Alex to go to
See a doctor friend of his doctor Amy offered
Who practices in Marble Falls
Texas
Just about an hour outside Austin
At this point I feel like we're in some kind of a weird marbles base
I feel like
Feel like I'm asleep or something
You're just marbling
Not the marbles the way that marbles needs to prescribe marble rye
Doctoroff 8 in the morning of Wednesday March 23rd
He didn't do his show
Additionally he didn't show up for the first day of his schedule deposition
Which was supposed to be like I said on Wednesday and Thursday
Resultant
Complexions
Doctoroff it was in agreement with marble
Should be doing this deposition
At all
Based on issues related to stress
She said quote I had a medical visit with mr. Alex Jones for acute medical issues that were time-sensitive
A potentially serious
There's a little tough.
Parse because the time sensitivity could be a reference to him having a hard deadline about the deposition
As opposed to being something where is Health a dictator
The time sensitivity
It's unclear
In her note however
There's a redaction
We started a comprehensive medical evaluation
He has to assess his blank
Status
I've asked him to avoid too much stress
Until we have results from the blood test
This morning sure
Assuming that this isn't all an elaborate charade that's
Kind of worrying
This has to do with the medical condition
It's on full display everyday
I guess it has something to do with him
Ridiculously high risk
Of heart attack or stroke
Both of these are things that can be exacerbated by an
Pre-stress and markers would be the kind of things you'd find doing blood to
On Wednesday Alex
Didn't do this show but he recorded a long voice memo while he was driving
Probably to doctor office office
In Marble Falls
Play periodically on the show to keep the audience
Tuning out from reporting IRA
In case they might
I think that Alex accidentally showed up again so they really well maybe he'll come back
We got him so couple of fun pieces of trivia to throw in
Just add for flavor here
Dr. marbles included the Dubai
He has claimed that he was nominated for a Nobel Peace Prize
In 2021 any statement of facts in his affidavit which is hilarious
I read that and I still don't believe it's true
Affidavit
That's wrong doctoroff it is
But I was able to find it August 2021 article from a local Texas blog
About how her and her husband had decided not to
Get back tonight
She doesn't run a normal medical office either she works of a place called heart and soul integrative
Find yoga
Apparently has an MD but her practice is an is an integrative medicine
Which is definitely not where you'd go if you were in need of a
Cute emergency consultation
Integrative medicine is built on relationships with page
Actually
Be one that involves like a bunch of hormone therapy and yoga
Also she doesn't accept insurance
Which is strange
Well no insurance will accept
I think the she can say that but I'm pretty sure it goes the other way around
I'm not sure I would put on the website
Percent. The doctor you drive an hour to see if you're needing a consultation about a condition that could be an emergency
None of this adds up
None of it makes sense
And I think that she has some kind of association with the American Frontline doctors
Hydroxychloroquine Ivermectin
Think of that that might be where the Kinect
And why he would go
See her as opposed
Someone potentially more qualified
I would think not
A lot of neck flexibility exercises
It's hard to tell precisely what's going on here but I think it's probably fair to say that this is an intersection
Innovation fully transparent attempt to avoid the deposition
And they real but probably not immediately pressing underlying condition that Alex is almost certainly struggle
He's in terrible shape and if you had a heart attack
Any point in the last 3 years I can't imagine anyone being
Surprise
Evening the judge in the case judge Bellis gave an order that was basically saying that Alex
I didn't listen to doctor Marbles and still came into work
So that affidavit is
Really all day
Convincing in terms of the
He does have a Nobel Peace Prize
Maybe he was a
Somebody said he should get one
The court wasn't sure who doctoroff it was but
But taken as a whole.
The two doctors provide indications that Alex had medical issues that quote
While potentially serious are not currently serious enough to
Either requires hospitalization
Or convince him to stop engaging in his
Mr. Jones
Unilaterally decide to continue to engage in these broadcasts but refused to participate
Ended up as a
And plus she rejected the motion Alex
His lawyers had made to reschedule and Bar
Change in circumstances
Like Alex actually being hospitalized
Position book
Is planned on Thursday March
The real question
The game
What happens Thursday morning
Did Alex show up to do his shadow or does he show up at the or does he either
He's a very Brazen move Alex did not show up for the deposition on Thursday
Though the show did open with a pre-recorded video of him
Complaining about how his trial is a show trial
Laterally decide that the Peppa's
Fishing bait should be changed
No one will ever find me
The video is legitimately and say it's complete nonsense
Be perfectly honest when he didn't show up for Wednesday's deposition I was pretty sure you wasn't
Going to show up on Thursday either
And a big part of that was because what
He was actually required to produce for the deposition
Is stuff he could never
Never bring
It seems likely to me that he knew you was going to be sanctioned whether he showed up or not
And if you was able to not show up and make
He's not showing up
Somehow about the court not respecting his health needs
Changing the narrative in distract
Acting is audience from
Is clear inability to answer a direct question
Particularly about his finances
The deposition of the penalty phase of the
McKay's a number the topic
Lexi was going to be required
Pretty shoes with Finance
Including agreements that he had with youngevity
Which of course is the veterinarian dr. Wallach supplement company any cryptocurrency transactions
And documents related to
The connections between Asbury shell company
Like pqp our Holdings Limited
Njlj are holding
LLC
Good stuff
If you're in Alex's position it strongly in your interest to Stonewall this kind of stuff because
For the charade of your show to really work
It's pretty important for the listeners to just think that they give Alex money and he uses it to fight the big bad globulus
The actual details of his finances with
Radnet Imaging probably AAA the audience's
Blindly throw money at Infowars
You know he's not going to provide this information that is being required of him in the deposition and that'll get him
You cannot show up and that'll probably also
There's been a lot of talk
And like headlines about him like getting
Arrested
Everybody understand
Was never really a likely outcome
But
If you were arrested
It would just be a situation where
Someone comes in
Gets him and makes him
Deposition debtors prison in Valley can pay off enough of those
Settlement in order to sit for they send at the Marshalls
I don't know
Right
I feel like this video from Thursday morning
Glad you didn't show up for the deposition
The insane one
It's too important
To ignore
McCormick
The episode from the
So here's where it starts
And he's like a man
Doctor doctor Barbie
The gentleman thank you so much for joining us on this live
Thursday Edition
They live on Shroyer Islam
TV off
I am taping this
In the morning for my home
Before I go against one medical test about on 48
I'm under a lot of stress
And
Studio-x gas cylinder issues
Monday and
Awesome
Signs of some fraternity things check me out
Telescope
Regina
Stop by doctor
I can get into a clinic
Versus check myself in the emergency room
Wednesday morning
Urgent care centers
All over the place
It's not that
It's not accurate the only time I could go to this
Weirdo America's Frontline
Hydroxychloroquine yoga doctor
That's when
That's the look
I can go
To like a
Urgent care facility or the emergency room or I don't know about Backwoods
I could do all of those things
But if the yoga ladies available
You go to the yoga
I think it speaks to the fact that it's not urgent and it's not an emergency
First of all
And then second of all
If our Alex
Crutchfield
I feel pretty insulted
Liberty
I feel pretty insulted by doctor Marvels
Look at
Play Imagine Alex get PW
So he gets to the motion to postpone
Oh yeah the deposition
My lawyers contact depositions on us
Jason X
5 * weeks.
Document
Document other
Reset three times for depositions in the Sandy Hook case
Forgiven of over 300,000 pages of documents
How they got all our financial records everything for a defamation case
I thought you see my financials on the news when you
Definition to be on the news and then you see that I've been
Defaulted
Clean when you see that I've been defaulted
These are show trials
These are staged event
I intend to sit for the deposition
I intend to
Fight
Court cases Texas with
Three different cases to in Texas
Want to Connecticut
Where I've been found guilty
By the judges
And the judges don't find you
Alex doesn't get to decide what is or is not a big deal for the court
He seems to think that his individual judgment determines what rules he is or is not bound to which is
Pretty disturbing mindset to have I'm just above the law
I mean is that above allies justy gets to
Like take it or leave it it's like this part of the line
It very well may be the case with other hearings are depositions have been rescheduled in the past but it was agreed to by both
Both parties and
Didn't happen with all those
No Lie
Time based on
Clearly very flimsy rationalization
If Alex is trying to suggest that this medical situation is really
Actually serious damn
His actions do not reflect that
Doing a show on Tuesday is a gigantic
Pick red flag that whatever Health concern he had isn't actually pressing
But just could be a convenient excuse to get him out of Heaven to do this deposition that he doesn't want to do and probably would be damaging if
He actually cooperated with I mean he does I will say that it in in all fairness
One-time the defense lawyers did the plaintiffs attorneys
I did have to reschedule because the dog
Dog ate their homework
Sure and the judge was like well I mean clearly we have to wait until you can print that out because I
Texas score
This isn't an isolated case of Alex trying to postpone this episode
How much is legal team has been trying to get this deposition as well as that of their new corporate representative
His lawyer Brittany
Meat pies
I was trying to get those for phone for a while and according to a court filing
They have also suggest
They may need to extend the trial date
In this case lawyers are trying to push this back and take off down the road
It's one thing to need to reschedule something it's another two
Exhibit a consistent pattern
Creating fake
Excuses to drag out a process so you might never actually have to face the consequence
Better coming to you
Yeah
And it's not like he Chevron he can't like a Florida judge and buy all that stuff
Now he's he's stuck
He can afford
Half a judge can't afford a little bit of a judge
Jicama clip you kind of get a towel from Alex that he knows he's full of s***
He says that he's already sat for a deposition
Three times in the Sandy Hook case any use of the singular noun
Later in the clip he shows that he's keenly aware that there's multiple different cases
Just part of the reason that he's required to say it first
Separate deposition
And then there's the dynamic that he's completely
Use the discovery and deposition processes in the first phase
Is the trial
Is where there's a different set of facts
The depositions are set to
Explorer
Bobby says it's going to be more times you required to stay
Alex knows all this but he's counting on his audience except
I think this b******* woe-is-me you take where the whole world
Has conspired against him
Initial trial
And honestly it's probably going to work with most of his listeners but
Complete fraud
I I mean it is
It is weird how
Everybody knows that this is malicious
There's nobody who doesn't know that this is militia
You don't know that this is malicious
You're hopelessly naive
And yet at the same time it's like well
We've given other people chances before when it wasn't malicious so in the sense of fairness
We need to afford the same chance
Even when people are malicious and it's like this
We could just not do that
There's a limit I think we're well past that is the problem
Actual medical condition that is at the root of it I just
Bulshit the way he's using it I don't think it's
Well I mean if you're worried about the deposition being stressful for you my friend I'm afraid that's what a Depo
Position is going to be
. sure there's no Breezy deposition for him
I actually don't think
He is too stressed out by these depositions
Because he knows he could decide I don't know
But kill time
The issue to those like anything that
If stress is legitimately the issue
He screams
Freak the f*** out on his show
He constant
Any storms out of studio and ever use Madden
There's no more stressful experience for him then doing his show
Much easier to take this kind of a complaint seriously if his actual
Kinston dedicate that he was still
Like more than willing to do
Vignettes
Painfully I'll be
Beasley stressful
Mommy maybe he's doing yoga.
No
So Alex gets into the issue of default judgment
Mets and I think he's steps in it
Default judgment
Somebody
Never shows up one time whenever showed up in quarter.
Smiling
With lesser sanctions
We have been fed
Into the Democratic party process
Even if that's the standard that Alex is using to determine when
Default judgments are Justified
He's case with Meredith all judge
Do you know entry or both
Didn't appear for schedule deposition
Surly and these case
He didn't respond to multiple requests or document
On multiple occasions he sent
Completely unprepared people to depositions to pretend to be corporate Representatives
Which may not be the same thing as filing fraudulent documents but man it's closed
Also here
Ton of opportunities to stop a
Abusing the process
He was given
Smaller sanctions repeatedly and it was abundantly clear to anyone paying attention that he was going to
Was going to keep that behavior the fuk up
Any effect on his.
Participation data
Abuse of the process
He did all this to himself
And even by his own metric that he's laying out here he deserves that default judgment against
He has just
Condemned himself it's actually I mean you say that but it's like
What is
The words that
He says you know like what do they mean
And I feel like you're just being unfair with your interpretation of the meaning of words
Yeah that made
I was just mad at everybody that's like
They're the ones trying to cash it off and work
Contacts
Maybe the Sandy Hook man
Go to court literally the judge
They're making them up and
My king of the lawyers and
The BBC in a quarter
Buy my book buy my book it just came out in time for the trial
Elizabeth Williamson the book is available fire safety hook America
Yeah I think he's he's distorting the actual conversation
I don't know if anybody is saying that he made his career on Sandy Hook
Just that his actions
In the
Avenue of his career he profited
I'll buy
Inflicting
On the other people who experience
If he does not understand
Clearly.
What the problem is
After having it been explained to him
In so many ways
With so many
Carrots
So many sticks yeah
Sanctioned
I understand it fully but he can't really can't appear to understand it or else the audience will be like
You suck man I know but isn't that weird that we're on like
For five years of this and he still has to pretend like he can't learn
Yeah you really
So Alex makes a
Claim
Could get him sued if he talks anymore about this
Donations
Some of the people
Personally
When we go to trial
One way or another
Because
America
Controller system installed
Oh boy who cares with charitable groups of raised
Who cares
They make money and use it for charitable causes I don't know
Nothing
You notice that I wasn't saying that particular plaintiffs in the case have brought in millions of dollars in Sandy Hook because of
He did
He would get sued and that's kind of a problem he's trying to give the audience but
You can't say that
Because if he did
Hubie defaming them again
We saw this play out in the last deposition that Alex was in the one in December that I went to in in Austin
Alex is complaints about a group called Sandy Hook promise
And there are some questions that Alex seems to have about their fundraising and their activism
I want to believe that all of the Sandy Hook parents are one monolithic group so he's decided that the plaintiffs in the case against him
Are interchangeable with Sandy Hook promise which he literally knows to not be true based on
Exchange from that deposition
What is honor
You know what that is
I think that's a
Fundraising
Voldunai ever
Cuz I know you're not gay
The news articles
Tens of
$20 raise
Controversial
So I have heard
Like I told you about
I've heard of him in the honor
Honor Network
I've heard that
I've heard the other day
I don't know
You're asking me
Alex may try to yell and derail the trial with this kind of stuff but it's not going to go anywhere or do anything because it's pointed meaning
You can use this insinuation here on a show to make the audience
I think that he's going to walk in like
The Conquering Hero
System on trial
It's all far
Alex knows that he can say
Exactly what he saying
But if you had one more.
Detail he's going to owe a ton more money and maybe create a whole new suit on the way
Also not for nothing but Alex's breathing is super heavy in this clip and it's kind of
Orient it doesn't sound good here
I mean at this point I'm waiting for him to walk into the
The court and just be like
Tubalcain
James Alex
Send to how I think
I think maybe he was talking to Marjorie Taylor Greene she told him about HIPAA
Oh God no cuz Alex husband
My health issues are my issues and their private
Under protected by HIPAA
And
You saw this judge, Connecticut
Yesterday you saw the lawyers he Democrat Party lawyers or Plymouth
You want him arrested
If he doesn't show up for some
You need to go home you need to go get these tests I got more test done today more tomorrow
And you stay away from the microphone well here I am
I should be on here because I have to respond to the
Hundreds of news articles
Associated Press
That are attacking
Williams
Don't know if anyone cares to cover whether or not you're a bad person
Taken as read
Texas Health privacy with HIPAA
Then he goes on to just immediately talk about his health situation
Just released my medical records make you all look like fools
Whatever
After I got covid last year
And I took care of them
Protein
And like everybody else get attacked the cardiovascular system
And so
Again
Somebody on death row is allowed to go get your medical
Carrington things are post
Somebody
On death row
Where
If you can believe anything Alex says then there's a decent chance he might be suffering from long-term complications from
The times he got covid
You may have also gotten it like again
Animal that exacerbate
Situation totally just based on what he saying this makes total sense
He's someone who's been super unsafe with his behavior he's gotten covid multiple times and as we've learned their many poorly under
Bestowed phenomena but with this
Virus Ware
Lingering effect
That's
Not too uncommon
I wouldn't honestly be too surprised if Alex has heart damage
That's that was caused
By one of the times he got covid-19
That being said he's also a super unhealthy person who's at
High risk of heart disease even without covid-19 want to jump to too many
Conclusion
The part that makes covid as an idea fit kind of neatly is Alex's claimed that he was getting sicker since he got covid that's
Second time
Maybe true and vessel symptoms
Maybe the way that is mine.
Experience things
Yeah it's not actually an accurate reflection of the progression
Symptoms
He's out and
I actually don't think it's going to be that into
But I'll be keeping an eye on the situation and see if Alex
Just stopped
Talking about this
It's not a convenient excuse for him the reason
People bring up hippos almost
Exclusively when they have covid-19 don't want to tell you they have coded because what whatever
Well yeah I mean well yes reason I can't ever plenty of other reasons which becomes up in
Appropriate setting when I was in hearing aid I worked with him all the time
What about hippos
Class on it the whole thing none of it was like hey
Don't tell nobody you got hearing aids
I recall it being relevant it was a temp for a short. Of time
Heyday a health and
That's company
I dealt with like
Underwriting
Things that I had
Understand about
Privacy
I mean one of the simplest is if somebody's like hey can I have my medical records you have to be like
Who are you
Can I see
So
Kind of bummed out
Actually that he doesn't
Get to go to the dentist
So much
To be talkin about here
Chris Madden
Crazy if you go to your own 1012
You can't do it
So I got some more tests coming up
Today and tomorrow I'm going to get those knocked out and I should be fine
Medication or whatever in this world I know
I've never really
Maidan-e-jung
Wait is it the stress of the world or is it long covid or do you have a heart
8 p.m.
Anything he's
He's having trouble breathing Dan why don't you care about a man in struggle
I like the idea that
I was going to get in there and chill outside Chris Matic
Tried to put a million-dollar bounty on him
Some kind of yeladim
When was the last time a Texan put a million-dollar bounty on somebody and it didn't
So
Alex's got a message for the leftist
Sorry
Sorry leftist and it's really nice of him to apologize
And yeah sorry leftist
MyHealth
Thomasville for you
Land becomes famous off
My name
Misunderstanding
You're the Sandy Hook people you eat
Eat drink sleep
And everything
That's what you do
Question anybody
The Gulf of Tonkin
I'm just amazed
You just can't
Can't Stop
But you guys the ones that bread this up
Misrepresent
Whatever you want
You trying to say that I have not
You say that I have
You're hiding all this crap
Everybody knows Alex Jones doesn't
The situation
Record this
My bedroom
That's that's
Hitler in the underground bunker being like I've never hidden from a fight in my life I'm on the front line
Kaboom
Thoughts at
Stupid
Conflicted
I can't really tell if I think of that cough
Is real or is it like me
Trying to convince my parents I'm sick I'm right there with you
Problem with
Like trying to assess the information that's being put out by a liar like you really really don't know
Like if taken seriously
I think it's f***** up
That he's breathing so heavily and coughing
Throughout this
This little video they put out listen to the cops and then replay
Play them in my head like a like I'm in a 7 you know like just like
Is this a signal is there a site
Frequency variation that'll prove he's lying when you know like
I don't know
Turbine ozell shows does not
On the frontlines of the situation
Freecoaster supporting us
Ben 10
Faye record operation that takes money to hire lawyers
Deportes
Infowarsstore.com
Toll-free AAA
253 3139 also rather
Honda
Want your money
Ossified
This is a Time
For me to be doing that
And they got the move deposition
Good these people
I have rights
What
My medical
And I'm sorry you don't like it at all the world or taken to serve it as a Christian Healthcare away
Credit score
People are dangerous
Authoritarians and they know it and they're going
Owen Shroyer and alive
Infowars
I am fascinated by Amy first of obviously plug
Obviously
Going to be in there
I'm fascinated by this consistent behavior and like
Is there something about his audience
That like really response
Dude like
Petulant baby outbursts
Lake II
I can't imagine
Hearing somebody act like that being like
F*** yeah that's what that's what that is a guy who is
Fight somebody who's really
Doing the work on the front line
13 year old
That is a thirteen-year-old in
Succinate
It's great it was like I'm just a little bit too tall
It's f****** awful
Call to listen to this whining
Wayne here
It's it's
It comes off like
They didn't let me on the football team cuz they don't like me or not too good
Videos on the baseball team
And yeah that short stopping it's whatever
Other than him
Now we jump to the
Land that is Tuesday
Decided to come to his show as opposed to
Who sang home under doctor's orders
I think it might be a critical mistake I mean like
Do regardless of what happens on the show there is still the
The image of him coming to do the show
Undercuts
His argument
So entirely brakes
I'm done it if I were him 3-hour deposition
3 hours
Completely different
It's Tuesday March 22nd 2022
2220 2282 the old boys
Bones
What
Bohemian Grove
Titanic
Why
Hell-bent on establishing a new world order
Destroying the Christian
Absolute scientific
Dictatorship
Now
A politician and leader
Going
Talked of a new world order
Who is Alex trying to suggest that there's some kind of a mystical magical spell that Biden was casting by using the words New World Order
Holiest of days of the globalist
Promise of the B inside them the day before I'm through
Whining about it
Bryant no
322 Zone the Skull and Bones logo
Different theories about exactly what the
Significance of that number is but
I don't know I don't
Like it matters
No
I could not be less interested
And it him
I also many a politician over the years has said New World Order
At no point in time just like many of politicians having called for the New World Order and you claiming that every
They do so
They are creating that new world order that you sow fear and then
Still having not done so
Yeah it it does
It does seem to keep happening
0 * 1
Situations are changing in the world
You know it here's what I would like in that too if I said many a Time the pass
Pastor of a church has said that the end times are upon us
The Following part would be
And they still aren't because they're
Right Center that would be the same response
Define response
What's a respond to this
Something about the lineage of the term New World Order
Be close to race
Mafia
A politician in l
Going
Has talked of a new world order
Ewell's
More than 100 years ago
New World Order
Nuremberg trials
That the head of German propaganda
Joseph Gribble
Wanted
Kill
Seawell's because of his book
The New World Order
Wait is that good or bad
Then what the Nazis wanted
G Wells the non-fiction also fiction writer
The anglo-american
Bad word
Combine
New World Order
Adult Kayla was Hitler you may have heard of him
Outdoor route to kill
Well this is history so when you hear about the New World Order
Popular's up a little bit
Open your eyes up
Focus
I think the extent of Alex's actual knowledge about WWII is that Hitler's middle name as a Lewis
Says it all the time really aware of it was Hitler more than he says Barack Hussein Obama
Yeah that's because it's Mainline news
I
I'm I'm flabbergasted
You just give them their full
A couple of important things
It came out in the Nuremberg trials and expect that to stand is
Compelling
Imitation is actually I made that argument at the Nuremberg trials where it came out
Francis Boyle was the lead prosecutor
Material involved in the Nuremberg trials is so dense and copious that
Look up a person's entire career
If you want to fight something in that you really need to be more specific because to not do so put your audience of the terrible terrible position of
Either taking your word for it
I guess scouring thousands
Thousands of pages of documentation to sieve
What you're saying shows up
Anywhere
Another important
Thing to keep in mind is that Joe's
Gerbils was not tried at any Nuremberg trials
Because he had already killed himself prior to the end of the war
Do you want School through the Avalon project hosts
Transcripts of the entire proceedings of the Nuremberg trials
It is recorded that Wells Books were included in the book
Books that were burned beginning in 1930
33 but it's really unfair to pretend that Wells was the main target
Like Magnus hirschfeld
226 research was Daphne
Amelia Central Target
How many tons of authors who the Nazis didn't feel we're German enough for the right kind of German
Heather work
Just included people like F Scott Fitzgerald Upton
Sinclair Franz Kafka
Helen Keller
Like it's a lot of people so much the authors as it was just like general knowledge itself
Thunder under attack I think that the awareness that h.g. Wells
Included in that book burning list
Maybe with Alex's
Maybe he's just combining that HG Wells had a book named New World Order and
Nuremberg trials a great place
To put it in makes up whatever you want
So how to make fake points when he's trying to sell
Some sort of a narrative whatever that days narrative is
His Alex's movie endgame begins with a missed quotation
Confirm h.g. Wells new world order it has never read that book
Zero he almost certainly just saw that faulty quotation in a John Birch
Society pamphlet his dad gave him
Just been his
Reality sets
An important point to bring up here is they in some ways you could really see what Alex is doing here is being
Pro-nazi
I know that you wouldn't accept that characterization but it really feels like he's applying his own worldview and motives to grbl
He ran away
It's really only meant to get the audience to think that
Maybe the Nazis were doing all that bad of stuff
I wish we were fighting Alex's new I've been trying to parse exactly what it was he was saying and that's where I'm
I'm getting stuck cuz it does sound I'm not sure if that's the only reading
It is it sure is
Alex constantly talks about the global list of the New World Order is
Being working for the literal Christian devil
Kind of paint the Nazis is not as bad as they seem if they too are fighting against me literal Christian
Well
I mean what he said was
The HG Wells had a book named New World Order
Gerbils
Wanted to kill him
Because the Nazis had their own New World Order
And we are told pretty
Clearly that HG Wells is New World Order is the devil one
So
Unless the devil is like farming out like all kinds of Art
You know it's this is like the everybody was playing in the minor leagues you know there were a bunch
Smaller town Devil's a barnstorming Devils who would come in
They have their own kind of thing going on for a while
Yeah I find this absurd but I can't say with any certainty
How much of this is intentional but if Alex
Isn't trying to be a Nazi apologist
He needs to be way more careful about how we talked about issues related to World War
The first step would be to stop making stuff up about it
And then after that
Stop saying things that
The clearly indicated
Personally identify with a Nazi leadership
These would be
Be admirable goals
I-22 trying not to bring into the proceedings
Politicians in Riders of
Said the world words New World Order over the years and the one I agree with it
Is grbl
That's probably not the way you want to go right yeah probably not
Alex might sympathize
Alex
Alex gets into talking talking about New World Order
Stuff
Turkey has been
Of course he actually kind of lets slip a little bit too
Clearly
Knows what people mean
Politicians will say oh well I'm shuffling
The power structure and Concerta
Bouquet
Compilation
Prime Ministers and presidents and world leaders
Findings are New World Order
World government
Autocratic
Authoritarian
World government in place wobbles come out saying
Of world government was not just a world government
It's a worldwide authoritarian government
Abortion infanticide
You alone nothing you will have nothing and you will be happy or you'll go to a camp
Keep in mind this characterization that Alex is making
Because he saying
This compilation
He's going to play it later
The pretty big compilation
Spoiler alert
Has the model of the new world order that he wants to create
Important
Alex says I have the video in the same way that he says it's in the it's not
He's got the video for his audience to be like it
Never heard that one
I also want to touch on the meme that Alex dropped at the end there the you will have nothing and you'll be happy
This is something that's really caught on among s******* Skeptics who don't actually want to put any work in but want to present themselves as competent
News and apologize
Rogan Russell Brand
Multiple videos where this Logan is used it in that nightmarish way to characterize the great reset
That conspiracy that he's hard at work making his millions of fans scared about
Never said you will own nothing and you'll be here
That's not
It's a paraphrasing if something was written by Danish and
In 220
Ida was envisioning what life might be like in 2030 and part of that Vision was that things that have been historically been
Zenith products
We're now service
This actually is a little bit far-fetched but the essential premises that Innovation and technological
Advancement will have made
I think so available at
What abundant
But there's no real reason to own anything anymore since everything will be free
From SA
First Communication became digitizer
Free to everyone
Then when clean-energy became free things started to move quick
Transportation dropped
Dramatically in price
It made no sense for us to own cars anymore because we could call a driverless vehicle or flying car for longer Journeys
Within minutes
They're also aspect of this Vision that are kind of dumb and as much as they seem incredibly inefficient
For instance
This part
Once in awhile I'll choose to cook for myself
It's easy the necessary kitchen equipment is delivered at my door within minutes
Let's transport became free we've stopped
Having all those things stuffed in our home
Why keep a pasta maker or crepe cooker crammed in our cupboard
We can just order them when we need them
That seems like a step backwards
Listen imagination
Sure
Conclusion is that this new technologically-advanced city provides literally everything a person
Also afford to know actual privacy
And quote all in all it's a good
There's no specific
Plan laid out here it's more or less a creative writing exercise or someone came up with some ideas of what life might look like in the
The future
An excerpt from this essay was included in the world economic forum's video blog post
Quotes
Predictions for the world in 2030
Paraphrasing of the ideas that idle wrote out is included and summarized as quote
You alone nothing
And you will be happy
This is not a description of some nefarious plan
The stated goal the class swab is working towards
The clunky brief synopsis of this
Person's essay
But that's not how it's reported by people like Alex or Rogan a Russell
Willebrand
It's basically a
Rat like a parent saying you'll eat your peas and you'll be happy
Do you know what's really funny
What's up
I remember
Specific person
Sang like
Get rid of all your stuff
You'll have nothing
And you'll be happy about it
Visit the devil
No no it wasn't a death
OK Google was a guy in the guy was like
I've got all this s***
What do I do
And this guy was like I'll just get rid of it you don't need s*** because guess what it's not
Making you happy
Involve like a parable about a
Camel no no no way absolutely not come on now
People a f***************
In some way I feel like that's the only way they can
Experience the world
Then it kind of goes back to Alex's like
His whiny petulant non-central
Response to not getting his way about the legal
I mean it's not the first time that Daddy Issues will have a
Outsized effect on the world
Yeah I understand that
I do
Feel like there's a there's a certain aspect to it
I realized this kind of
Psychological
Phenomenal
Just didn't realize it was this profitable
In terms of building an audience always thought that acting like this was a bad move
Yeah I kind of thought it was embarrassing
I don't have daddy issues
Sure
That's why we find out that Alex was a little bit late
Finding out about Biden's comments
And I was going to bed early
Blowing up
Well-known talk show host
Calling me
Did you see Biden did you see by Juicy B
Call for a new world order
Play Store
Extra details
It was
Who's to be a symptom of Alex's covid-19 exhaustion
Terrible stories but going to bed so early
And this is me grasp
Straws to build up
It's honestly bizarre for Alex has anybody heard about this clip at 9 p.m. because it's antex
He's clearly trying to apply
The most important person in the world
Speed bike games
Conspiracy information spaces immediately
I texted you at like
It's over two hours behind it like we're the tip of the spear
I said no idea
Pathetic
So
Is this the way the media treats
Oh I mean they're just so unfair
They just it's like
Oh you can't run
Hundreds of millions of lives without somebody being like all me
Hi Prosecco
Here's the deal
New World Order
But then
Biden says New World Order
Nor
X Washington Post
I talked about a new world order
Going bad and it doesn't exist
America has a free speech problem
New York Times on Friday
Because they don't want us discussing
The future of the world
Levi's decide
Humans
That was real bad normal
Worse than his badge
Is very little rain
More importantly though people criticize Alex
Because you make s*** up and then he uses the idea of a new world order to push in
Hateful political position
To deny Act
The right-wing terrorism
In general
Target marginalized and vulnerable population
He's a meaningful distinction but I don't expect Alex ever recognize a pub
Look like
New York Times article Alex is talking about actually says the opposite of what he
He's claiming it does
The way he's talking about it reveals that he is literally just read the headline and assume that it must be about how freeze peaches
The problem because it allows Alec
He couldn't even read the first two paragraphs about realizing that this
Article saying the opposite
Quote for all the tolerance and Enlightenment that modern society claims Americans are losing hold of a fundamental right of citizens
Of a free country
The right to speak their minds and voice their opinions in public without fear of being shamed or shunned
This social silencing the D pluralization of America
Has been evident for years
But dealing with it stirs yet even more fear
It feels like a third rail
Dangerous
A strong nation and open society that is danger
The irony of him
Criticizing that specific editorial
Is everybody at the New York Times
Who is Alex Jones
Wrote that editorial
Yeah there's
Shameful food is disgusting
He could have written that all
Decrying the scourge of cancel culture
Because he's too lazy to read past the headline he's using it as a prop
To build up a case
What is under attack
Pathetic stuff
I don't know like it
It's at times like this one like there's a lot going on in Alex's World lots of moving parts
Lots of lots of things going around two stories
Read this article you're complaining about
Huge win for out Scooby like even the New York Times understands that people like Alex Jones should be listen to
I bet that will be eventually
Yeah I'm really really mad at that one understand I wanted to say mean things
Guess
Coming up
Resume the show
I think
In terms of
The sort of person you would want to come speak on the sort of topic
We also have
Economist
Researcher
Exposing
Depopulation agenda
The stock picker
Released by the government UK
Hospitals bribed
AHS
That meet Targets on Liverpool
Care pathway
Massive amounts of a
Forgiven hundreds of thousands of old people they killed
If you give somebody a shot of it that has pneumonia
They always
What
A few hours what f****** magic is that
It's for the Earth
Kill your dog got to kill your cat has your son
Got to kill the old people
There's not enough resources
You will owe nothing you will have nothing
The Daily Mail
It's not an article about covid-19
Concurrent Lucky's
Reporting a
2012 article is more complicated than what Alex
Presenter
Target's of between 130
Two-thirds of the deaths that occur in the hospital being on what's known as the Liverpool care pathway
LCP of the protocol that
Is used for patients who are end-of-life and determined to be terminal cases
And it's essentially away the doctors attempt
Provide hospice type care in Ahoskie
Little setting
Once a patient was deemed to be terminal in there was no longer any treatment options they would receive palliative care to relieve pain
But typically that page
Kenwood end up dying
It wasn't so much at the hospital
Killing these patients as much as it was a case where end-of-life care was being done in a manner that
Detached and bureaucratic
The fact there was a target range of deaths that should involve the LCP and the fact that
Its funding was
Attached to being in line with these targets
It really gave the air of impropriety even though no wrongdoing was necessarily
Being done right it's
Just people so divorced from the Omni
The ground reality of it they're just like
Looking at number now they don't feel yet
Review found that when implemented well the Elsa
BP is a good way to handle end-of-life Care at a hospital setting
And in fact it appeared that the existence of the pathway made it much more clear to families of patients that their loved one was at the end of
Their life
Accordingly
That's it
When it was a diplomatic while it was a sloppy process they could lead to some amount of negligence
And there were aspects of the pathway that worked
Too difficult to formalize
Right
For instance diagnosing when someone is at the end of life is
Imprecise thing
Soca defined rules of
I'll be difficult to do Broadway
And such
The panel that reviewed the LCP advised
Phasing it out
What's the NHS did
In 2013
Well they got them
We got them guys we did it
Alex is covering in sensationalizing a decade-old story which is just tip of the spear stuff
Nonsense
For the rest of that stuff is just bulshit ranging from transphobia to Alex mischaracterizing
Pat is bad for the
The environment mostly because the Dynamics
Involved in pet food production drumbeat of the you own nothing and you'll be happy
He said that a bunch of the
The past but not as regularly as he is now
And I suspect that he seen the success that folks like Russell Brand have had with using that is a mantra
And Alex wants to signal to those audio
Fences in Tryon
Right right right right right
See you again this is also like
What is it
Buddhism
Like there's a whole organized school of thought around how having stuff is a bad move
Wait is it Russell Brand of Buddhist I think he is
F****** idiots
Anybody catch yourself from the idea of not having things
Alright
Attach yourself
Tuan attachable
That you can attach yourself to
Yeah
I've been I've been
Starting to think that maybe Russell Brand Deuce is
Somebody who deserves a little bit of
Don't be too surprised if we do some episodes about him in the future
Wasn't seeing
The guy from one Guy Ritchie movie with
Like
He probably has a larger audience
But Alex at the
This point
And
He's still on mainstream platforms
Hugh
Doing some straight-up Alex
Exact same size
Not exactly
It is important and I will get into that little later day
But like
I was taking a shower yesterday
I was thinking about is like
He's probably radicalizing a lot of people
And I wonder
I know it could lead to trouble in like
There's another January 6th minutes
Because Forgetting Sarah Marshall came out
Get me to the Greek or whatever getting launched his career
When you really
Think about it
We are dealing with a triumvirate
Of Alex Jones
Jailbroken and Russell Brand
Three purveyors Tucker well of course but I mean like this
Bush-league b******* is not good we appeal to sort of different sectors
Right-wing types
Go to Joe Rogan Stone could go either way with Roadrunner Branch or not
That is the difference
Oh my God they're all like a
F****** 20
Rebuild a character in a f****** RPG where you just adjust the stats a little bit and you come out with these two
Goddamn
All I'm saying is brandx wasn't really like enough to Merit
Occult
Stuff in the UK before like obviously was already
Nope not here
He got back here
BoBoiBoy
Anyway I'm thinking about him
Photo of the New World Order
We know that the Nazis were trying to make one
So we know that there are multiple New World Order New World Order
New World Order
New world
Yeah
So
Alex gets into how there's a bunch of new world orders right now
What does that even mean
You're going to find out God
Announces the New World Order
Sure was one
You like that one
And you got
Brewskis
The real plans requires to unify the world and not kill each other
What main line
Psychologist
Psychology
Save the Earth
Really really
That
Weitzman carryout
Wow
Decided to kill most people
Humans become a new species
Jobs on their own
China Centric race-based
Fascism
I just want to be left alone
Really
They want to be left alone
I think I might still be high from that Cali weed
Wow
F****** insane Meandering childish bigger
It's shocking
An oppressive and it's crazy how all news World Order
Don't include South America or Africa whatsoever
So here are the teams
You might start to notice that some of these groups are characterized as good or bad
On the bad side you got China
Two completely different
Confirm what he wants
Then you have the anglo-american establishment would just go to the globalist and we know that they work for the literal devil
There's a slime which apparently will lead to the destruction of the world and then there's transhumanism
Creative
Sure
Just right off the top you can tell this was an improvised list that I was ripping because
He's a facet
Of the globalist plant
According to everything Alex has ever said about this topic
Globalist
Humanism is an essential element of their whole scheme
Where they're trying to birds with machines and become God
He talks about it all the time those are gold strange that he added them in as a distinct
Group
I think you did that because he realized how clearly is Christian identity nationalism was coming through
Christianity good Islam at
You starting to throw that out as a distraction from that
I mean but even then
Where we go right back to Chris
Condemn
Left
We got China
No we got America globalist we got Islam know so whose are bastards baby
Well I doubt it just wants to be left alone another Underworld
Which apparently is the true plan to unite Humanity
Definitely name if you wanted to
Really troubling questions
And I guess the first is what is Alex mean by saying Russia wants to be left alone but they also want a new world
Well the best way to be left alone is to rule every
How does this work man it's like so far Putin is killing
Tons of civilians in Ukraine
Seem like it furthers the goal of being
Left alone
No I mean it does
That's the
Pointed that's the problem with every
Every single person who's ever thought about the idea of an isolated Nation
In the current Global structure is that if you want to be an isolated Nation
There can be No Other Nation
So you either have the entire world or everyone else is dead
That's not a good plan
Tulsa with Alex's suggested with his whole thing about Mass ecologist saying the Christianity is the plan that we
What are you saying is that he wants to impose Christy
Theocracy on the world
From Alex
He says the Christendom is the real plan that will unite the world whether you believe in Christ or not
He doesn't care if you believe in God or Christ
You're not so long as he's able to assert
Power over you because
He does
So long as you have to submit
I can
Stick your fingers like this
And not just think that Alex is losing even more of his grip
And he's being a bit too over with his desires
But he wants to SeaWorld characterized by Christian theocracy any Seafood
Is the person who's most likely to Usher that in
Which probably explains a fair amount of his
More recent contact
You're just getting it all wrong
Okay that's why we can't have Islam because they want to impose
A religious theocracy on us even if you don't believe in that particular religion
That's not how Christendom works and it never has not once not one time I
I can point to tons of Mainline historians will tell you that nothing good
As ever
Not feel like leaving isn't in line with
Anything that Alex's said
Is big
Your stuff and like the major players
No not really
Like I guess
His conception is vagina is stopping
Working with a new world
Loader or whatever
Or with the global
But Islam is still there's never been a break
Yeah it turns out that he still thinks
Entirety of Islam
New World Order globalist
His
Conception of the world
Is so small
The Troopers just so little in his world
But I think it also is just
Made up
True
And that's why I mean it has to be because it doesn't think
About like the global South at all
He does only in as much as he liked.
You'll be a lieutenant
Boutonniere whatever talks a little bit more about this stuff
Soda
Defensive about how smart he
But which is the things Market
System as well but they're not
Following
The neoliberal model of
Sterilizing
Boys and girls and
Destroying
Acumen
Civilization
Thomson the Russians have broken
System
Just believe they're going to merge
Weather technology
What real debate going on
What's the real today
Bilderberg Group
I've had
Intelligence
50 million dollars
Science division
Heads of harp
Heads of major programs not trying to brag
28 years
And
All day
To be at the table
Even though most of globalist don't like
Wow
Anyone listening to the show actually believes that Alex is having adult conversations with anyone and
And the conversations are about this b*******
I can kind of see how his supplements sell so well
Wildlife
No I'm allowed to go wherever I'm smart I'm just smarter
I wasn't talking to anyone who's not insane
In themselves and you can tell by the gas city has on his show
They're all lunatics and most of them are lying about their car.
Essentials
How is it Steve pieczenik on a show for 20 years and never seriously ask himself if this dude was nuts in a liar
If you're actually like a big serious person you'd never associate with Alex because you can easily see
The company that he keeps and how he behaves
He's an untrustworthy idiot who's
Unpredictable and he's surrounded by white supremacists and neo-nazis and
Parity level conman
I do feel a certain amount of pity for anyone who could hear that and take it seriously because
This is just Alex's child-brain lashing out again
He knows he doesn't deserve to be taken seriously so he's creating a comical explanation
How seriously is taken by imaginary
That totally exist and they probably hang out with my psychologist
Listen
I know
You aren't taking
But these billionaires that you've never heard of
All of them all support pillow
Important
Guessing the person who runs harp
Is probably just Nick begich
Sure
We could probably pick out who all of us people are
Seeing by the audience in a certain way because Alex knows that on the merits
He doesn't deserve to be treated like that or seen that way
At all
But
Big news what
Alex could join the new world order if you wanted to not like
You peons and peasants listening
Do it can't do it man come on to it
I could join the New World Order
Just f****** do it man
Myself for a short. Of time
Someone's coming at an enlightened
Calling
Ennis Ennis this operation
You really think you'll be safe driving with this
A few thousand of you that are actually
And the Millions
To Valhalla
Elysium
No
It's a lie
We are
There's a short compilation
Just a few world leaders
Talking about the New World Order and world government and what it means
Paradise
You know we are at inflection point
I believe in dope World economy
Manchester World economy in the world
Occurs every three or four generations
As one of my one of the top military people said to me in a secure me the other day
60 million people died between
1919 46
And since then we've established a liberal World Order and
That hasn't happened in a long while lot of people dying but nowhere near than chaos
And Now's the Time when things are shift
We're going to be a new world order
We've got deleted
We've got to unite the rest of your world and doing it
I wonder if Johnny newworldorder would make it so Alex wouldn't have to come up with embarrassing excuses to not have to go to a deposition in the
Okay studies already lost about the fame in the families of murdered children
Maybe you should try that cuz I don't know what other option is left
Please probably run
I think I would love it if all the sudden we came in want to work one day and you're like I've got an episode
Good for you here's your out-of-context drop
I've joined the New World Order and then we go from there that's beat that's amazing
Wingstop
Alex just starts wearing black and doing the two sweet all the time
Being like a foe life
Gets the wrong New World Order
Gangs out with Hulk Hogan what you might do I do what is yeah well you know Evan people who say the n word
Stick together
Recent comment about the New World Order
And I don't think that it sounds evil or nefarious at all
This is that compilation
Alex mentioned earlier
Compilation
Horror the New World Order
So far it sounds like someone describing others a change in the status quo
It's happening as it relates
It's the international power balances
I'm going to go through each of these
These clips one-by-one in the compilation
The reason I'm doing this is because I need to drive home the point that the entire notion
What is New World Order stuff being
Some kind of an actual evil
Conspiracy plot
Even based on anything other than manipulative opt
That an historical anti-Semitism going back to
A lot of manipulative Optics
So here's the next
Again this time
Team speech you gave up
The annual conference of the export-import bank
The affirmative task we have now
Is is 2 actually
Create
A new world order
Wow
Adam B
Interesting that I would choose that clip because if you actually listen to buy
Cancel speech
The only time he says New World Order
Like for instance is just from a little bit earlier in the speech
I understand better than almost anyone
You understand
Anyone this year
Potential
This global economy
You forged United's
America
And you are
What a weirdo
Understory
Interpol
Warriors
Post-world War
Where are we faced
A slightly different set of challenges
The global economy re-emerge
Instructions of War we knew that is
Institutions in rolls
We needed to navigate through this new world order
And
Because our parents and grandparents
We're wise and because they were
Committed
We did what we've always done best
We exercised our Global Leadership
Allison use this clip even though it does involve Biden saying New World Order because to do so would undercut the point that out
I was trying to make
To be fully honest I'm sure Alex and never listen to this speech and has no idea where the Clippers even
I'm from somewhere just send him a fear-mongering compilation or these
Pieces to his
Employees
Put it together and they decided to include this clip
He's just ignoring the other one because it doesn't work
If all you have is our contact presentation to Biden saying who need to build a new world order that
Could have come from any. Of time and your brain to match
And that it's related to whatever you want to pretend it's related
That only work
Contacts
Conversely if you hear the full speech and you see that
He uses the words newworldorder to refer to the New World Order
That appeared
In the aftermath of world war and makes it to clear that the
New World Order isn't a specific compound noun in this speech
Really just referring to the changing set of circumstances on the world stage
This case in the field of economics
International trade
Something speaking to the export-import
The inclusion of this example in the compilation is a strong indication that this isn't making us
But since your point
It's just an attempt to use the image of people saying New World Order
To make that into an argument
Give me a quick hits
I mean public what exactly are we going to wind up you know it's not like we're eventually going to have our politicians all go like
So I think now the things are changing we're going to be entering a new
A novel
Global strain
Sure
Is an oldie but a goodie
We have before us.
Opportunity
For ourselves and for future Generations
When we are successful
We will be we have a real chance at this new world order and order in which
United Nations
Can use a peacekeeping role to fulfill the promise in vision
The un's founders
We talked about this in depth
Endgame episodes with this is George h.w. Bush announcing the beginning of the first Iraq War
While announcing the war is no good
Set that said to use the words New World Order in this beach are not in a
If you read the full speech it's
Very clear that this is a reference to The Changing State of Affairs between the US and the Soviet Union
In fact the line that's right before this
In that speech
Is weirdly always cut out of these
These clips is quote
We have in this past year made great progress
Since ending ending the long Arrow conflict in
Cold War
Long story short this was at the end of the Cold War in 1991
The term New World Order refers
The old world order was a state of
22 largest super powers in the world to be too occupied with fighting each other to engage at the UN
And their larger peacekeeping mission in the UN would be too busy worrying about
Have you asked him Sophia Union
You're free to scoff and disagree with the idea that the UN in
In the Gulf War were great
Escaping
Please do
Bush was not talking about a shadowy cabal and world government
He's not going to change in status quo between the United
States and Russia
Which brought about the New Order of the world
With all that's going on there
Novel Global structure
You're not going to like this next one
I'm not going to spend any time to sending him or his legacy but this is a strange clip to use in this compilation
This is from an interview he did with Charlie Rose in 2007
And if you just use a 9-second
Kind of
Conveys the message Alex is trying to pretend it says
Misrepresenting the larger Cohn
Hey you just hear this clip it sounds like Kissinger saying
It will have different characteristics
Pics of different parts
To the world and they
Is implied to be the New World Order understood to be a one world government
That's not what he saying
Just prior to this clip roses ask
Him about the Iraq War and its pouch
Understood as revealing the limits of America
Empower and if given the considerations of so many regions in the world
States in the Middle East the rising power of China
Was there a need for a new world order
Kissinger saying yes that there was a change of Dynamics it was on the horizon but that would play out differently in different parts
The world
In terms of things Henry Kissinger said this is a fairly benign
Yeah I mean you know I hate Henry Kissinger a lot and now they're doing that for us
Series on Via behind the bastards holyshit I don't even know how much I hated that I'm guessing if you were Alex
Your doctor advised you not to let you know I'm not doing good so I listen to it
Yeah
Yeah it's not Republic
Our next flip we get bush
Again
Well I mean he's newworldorder class
You know I think I found one person who use the term more than him
In this compilation
But you said it'll
A world in which there is
The very real press
Seven New World Order
This is from another speech in 1991 a couple months after the other one
This speech is mostly about
Declaring victory in operation
Can Desert Storm it honestly I don't know why Alex didn't use a longer clipper
From the speech
Or possibly like there's even more menacing instances of Bush saying New World Order in that speech
It's hard
To listen to an entire speech then listen to this wouldn't be more impactful of Alex use this clipping
Instead
Even the New World Order
Guaranteeing
Era of
These
But enduring
Must be armed
Personally I think that sounds more ominous
Like yeah even if you let us have our way there still going to be violence and War
CIA director becoming president saying that nope that's who that
Reason Alex uses the eclipse
He does is because he's never actually watched or listened to any of the source material is just using clips that other people have posted online and me
Memes
And she
So you're the next one
A new world is Imagine
It is a new world order
Which significantly
Difference
And radically new challenges
So this is a little sliver of the speech of that former UK prime minister Gordon Brown gave
In front of the Confederation of British industry,
Spell account
It's unclear what year this is frowned because conspiracy sites online claim that it
It's from 2007 but I found a transcript of the speech of the gave that year at the CBI
And it doesn't match
Some doubts about that
Actually really frustrating because the backdrop behind Brown is definitely from CBI
But it's also not the backdrop that matches with the conference used in 2007 nor any other years that I
Can find videos from
I've been able to find Brown speeches
Other years that he was there and none of them match this other it's a real pickle
Capodice look through all of the you know what the backdrop looks like
For each of the years will maybe not every year but relevant
That's the problem dude also look through all of the videos that are posted on C-Span include
Gordon Brown
In the description
So this
Does exist this 32 minutes
Clip that this comes from YouTube snippet that was posted in 2007
So I can be fairly certain that it wasn't
Said after that
So beyond that I don't I don't know what to say fairly certain Bahrain
SpaceTime manipulation ever know
Never know
Let's try the new world order
You forgot who was more than book
If you read any of his speeches he throws that s*** around like it's going out of style
Here's an excerpt from another one of his speeches
You see how the fairy is
Some scary this stuff is
Our task is government leaders
And this
This is why the theme of the conference is so Timely
Engage the citizens of our countries in discussing and then implementing with their active imagination
The new policy program that ensures that the benefits of this emerging New World Order can be shared
Not just buy some
But by all
Yeah that's
Amanda
That in W1 that's real scary
You compared to all the rest of these
Why is Kissinger again
We got a new contender
Baby development overall
Strategy for romantic Hindi.
Lunatic
Dragon
So this one is on a show called squawks on stocks
Or he's being interviewed on the stock market
Floor it's like the anniversary of
Vagina
Bank-owned OKC
Yeah
Insane
The interviewer is discussing the ongoing hostilities between Israel and Palestine
She asked
If it's all going to stop after Obama get inaugurated for his first term
She is straight up asking if the fighting in Gaza is something that's being orchestrated by Obama for political gain
And this is on CNBC wow obviously f*** Kissinger but this interviewer is not looking at her 8
Crazy
What
And the people around like
Okay good somebody reacted it wasn't just like this is a totally door
Marble question that we could ask her ask another question but there is there is a definite look on
A couple faces
Subtly likes me real quick
Amazing record by the way are the Jews orca
Castrating this to Alexa
Barack Obama press
Just real quick of your head
If it's uncomfortable
Clip comes after Kissinger is a strange question about what country's relationship with the United States
Will Define Obama
Presidency
It's such a weird question that I'm just going to play it and Kissinger's response
So you can sort of get the full contact
Read the most
Thing is for Barraco's
We are here to talk about
Relations
To say
Michigan
Find your mama
Abbeville
Minibots
You have
You can give
Do American Funding
Drudge
Dad
Scooby-Doo develop
7 / 0
Strategy forum
Indeed.
Been really a new world order
Created
Beethoven community
When you hear the question is responding to in the full answer the context of this comment makes way more sense
Surprising is that context is really the only way this works is
Making it seem some kind of
Dominus spooky
Gary,
Compilation
Yeah it's not like you said
You know what
You are Alex Jones expression work has been a bad one
A bay I guess I've never done it before I gave it a shot listen No One try things no one's accusing you like
Being the man of a million voices I am not accused of that by anyone
So this next
Cliff is
Feel like it's warm
It's
Not good
Eventually once we discussed why
Surface-level
It appears a lot warmer
2009 is also the first year
Establishment of the G20 in the middle
Financial
Is another step towards the globe
So this is a clip from a speech that Hermann Von Ruby gave after he was elected as the first president of the European Council
Prior to this point there was a six-month rotation of president
That's where whichever country was president of the eu4 that's
6 months
They also held the ceremonial position of President of accounts
They decided to go a different way with that
In 2009
Therapy.
Havana Rumba.
But liked it
Probably isn't talking about global government per se even say New World Order
Nightclub
He's talking about International cooperation that was prompted by the worldwide economic crash of 2007/2008
What he says
G20 was formed in
2009 that's not accurate
It was formed in 1999
But in 2008 in response to the global financial crisis
They decided that they should have annual meetings
And that they would be the body where the primary economic cooperation conversations happened
Prior to this that was mostly the role of the
The G8 but in the wake of the financial crisis
People recognize that you know there were other
Countries that begin
I'm f***** up bigger time
Yeah the interconnectedness of world economies had more important actors in it than just those eight
The reason that rumpy's says that this is the first year of global governance is be
Because the EU isn't a member of the G8
Individual EU states are members but the body itself is not
Conversely the EU is a member of the
What rugby is saying is not that this is the first year of global governance itsvet
Forum where International economic cooperation conversations happen
Is now the body that the EU which he was just to let
Like the president of easy
Included in
This one that sounds the closest to making Alex's point
But if you know a little bit about the situation of the context
Text of what Trump is saying
This clip doesn't say what Alex's presenting it to sing at all
It's not talking about a new global
You know what I'm going to I'm going to say this right now
And I've got strong opinions about it
I think that maybe short compilation videos
Aren't you should learn about his
No but
Good for slam dunk
Amazing slam dunks
CS
Rex Chapman
Don't go bring him up
I feel like he's a better comforter that's m
I would I would say
Yeah so we have one last clip that within this compilation AutoCAD then Alex comes in with a sort of
Dakota
Are you up to
Take a global system
Can I
It could happen
Any practice in the world
And they use that
Landry crises
Consolidate control
Bankrupt
Instead
Because you will be dead
So we have Soros on some interview show saying that a global system is in the works with absolutely no context about what's being.
I think at this point you can
Can see the game that's being played here and how all these clips are meant
To come at you fast
Stan without any surrounding
If you're overwhelmed by what appears to be a ton of powerful people saying that there's a new world order a foot
And then Alex comes back in the studio
And says that this is their plan to kill you
You might just accept him at his work
However if you like
Conspiracy theorists love
Do your research
And take a little bit of time
Ask the question
What's the context
You'll easily see that
The conclusion Alex tax on there at the end about
The people plan to kill you is laughable
This compilation doesn't establish or build
The conclusion to Dolly
It's just smoking mirrors because that's all this s***
Where was Klaus Schwab wasn't in there.
Images of you can see the drumbeat of you alone nothing you'll be happy that Monty
Anchorage
So annoying peating this phrase like he does is meant to logit in the audiences mind
I connected to other ideas like they want to kill you
Yep that's just
Subconscious manipulation that he's doing
Yep
Real
Real bad
It is
I really really do
Despise those types
Texas logon
You know that they're just like
They're what you hear before the boot stops on your face
Like that kind of s*** like
They're taking everything away from us as right before they shoot you
Is like it you
Before I die I have to
One second you realized
Is that like obviously it did
Come from
World economic forum
Video that they put out like it is
It's on there
But the actual context of it
Is being abused
Misrepresent
I mean obviously you can't always be playing defense
Like against
What conspiracy theorists are going to
Is your content for life
But
Something like that I feel like
Maybe saying New World Order is an own-goal okay you don't always have to be playing defense but don't
Kick the ball into your own f****** go to disagree because like
As evidenced by you trying to come up with words that would replace it novel Global structure I think that work
I'm going to use that one from now on
That's only because we seen in so many conspiracy videos and movies and all that s*** before I head because of Scott Hall
It's repeated in of it's just like where we where
Take all your stuff
Then you'll have nothing in the like
That's the
Here is just
The some random
Rambling
When I go to a liberal area of Austin
They are stupid
How scared they are
Feel powerful myself
And for the globalist when they see the homeless Shel
And the needles
And the trend he's offering their children up
Pedophile storytime
Broken your will
Badges
Help me
I want to be good and strong I believe in goodness
You will begin to
Spirit literally electrochemical
North higher
Vibration
Sounds right
New age that's not
What's a science
This is this is something you can be
Replicated
Science says
That if you drop down on your knees and accept Jesus Christ into your heart
Then you will electromagnetically accelerate to a higher plane on a different vibration
Scientist
Science science
Vibration
The Sunday wage
These are the conversations that they're having at the big boy table
Cool
So we get to the bug
Beatings
I do so love when we booked at it something to the point where I live
Completely forgotten about it by the end of that out half the gold
You have nothing you're a failure you're ugly
Used to that
Start switch
Instead of I will not eat your body
And I will have children will colonize space
New World Order
Not God
And we are not under your control
God control
And Justice and freedom
Where to go to break I want to encourage Lester's understand that
The battle for Infowars is here
I feel my t-shirts now the time
We're selling
T-shirts
Even
Below cost some of the
And 75% off
We got to get all the funds in
We can
Right now it's
He know who else said that you'll have nothing and you'll be happy about it Murray
Condo
I would say if
This is accurate at all what Alex is talking about
Things are looking real bad
Things are a real bad
If he's selling out things at prices that are under cost because he can't make operation operating expenses
The goose is basically cooked
I guess you could sell out all this s*** and then maybe put the Band-Aid on things for a bit but
This problem isn't going to go away because ultimately this propaganda platform is a model that
Doomed to fail
Actually Alex's propaganda
Platform is a great example of how
He stayed humble and kept things in the mid-range like where he was
2008 or 2012 yelling about how Ron Paul should have won the primary and showing up at places of bullhorn
Every once in awhile
He could have been comfortable to Rich
Probably for the rest of his life
Any would have been able to
Continue to pretend to fight an infowar
Against imaginary enemies
The Grove
Is what's killing a
It's be overhead and expenses on the
Worthless employees on his payroll
A propagandist doesn't need that kind of hassle
Propagandist
Is Born to Run free Hornet hand making up s*** but books
Please never read
This
A man selling his Wares at a loss just we can afford to pay a dork like Harrison Smith to host a pointless show to patout
The concept of putting out
That's a debasement
That is no good
This is not how God intended a propagandist to live
Also Something In that clip stuck out to me where Alex said
We're not under York
Control
Control and we choose liberty and justice and freedom
That thought
Completely nonsense
How does one choose freedom
If they're under a deities
Control
If you're under someone's
Control that means you don't have free will unless you can choose anything let alone
Choosing to be free
Confounding
Idea
But of course Alex believes that God is a free-will kind of guy
Maybe being under his control is to have free will
But in that case
What does it even mean to have free will
Pretty much nothing
That would tend to imply the people who aren't under gods
Control don't have free will
But then how can they possibly be condemned for the fact that they're not under God's
Control they can't choose to be under God's control they have no free will
I just don't think you
Okay then
When God created the universe
He also created the end of the universe simultaneously he knows everything that begins and ends
He knows everything that will happen
And that means
That you have the ability to choose what's going to happen
Can I tell you I read this really great book about Free Will and determinism recent
Who's called knowing
Starring Nicolas
Which I have
Some continuity
Alex gets a little bit work.
He thinks about the globalist
Kill your pets
That's the first time that I believe the globalist
Maybe I've just been wrong maybe I should
Submit
Maybe we should all go out today with hatch
Killer dogs in the backyard
It's the same the Earth right
We're supposed to give up everything we're guilty cuz we have dogs
Greedy
Monsters
YouTube
Be a rollover
But I can steal the future there project
Their Global is hatred of themselves onto you
All the beautiful nice things they have in the science they have
Came from the Commodores
Came for the people we built all this
The Robots coming online
Collective suicide
Well guess what it's not going to
Okay
It should happen maybe
Maybe I'm Wrong maybe I am the bad guy
Because I want to kill my new puppy
I'm the bad guy
I want to apologize to the automation store
The fuk just happened
Bloomberg the owner owner of Bloomberg and the publication
All the other groups that came out
We should kill
Savior
She said that
I have never seen this level of preparation on Alex's show
The idea that he's in the middle of what appears to be a rant about something and then it throws do a video about the same sub
Objective he did in advance
Like you prepared to this
JustBats
I mean
It's
Really a low bar
But it's impressive for him
100% thought it was a
Complete accident
Somebody to accidentally like overlaid the broadcast with an old video or something
Or maybe they would like hit the relay run out of the five second delay after you started talking about killing pets and then it got real
Weird
Impressive
28 years ago his career he's figured this out
Not once did that thought occurred to me independent I'm not positive
So much of a show
But I don't think I've ever seen anything that coherent
Yeah like in terms of a pre-recorded piece right
Maybe one
Alfred possibly want
You know it is
Good to show some real growth
You know at the end of your career
It's a good time to really still show that you can learn nutria
Be like if you saw this on a local access thing if you like
See
That was what he was doing 28 years ago
That's a bizarre clip their Beyond
Two features that look really bad when there's
Further contact
Ben you understand
Just off the top of the Bloomberg and all these papers didn't say that you should kill your
There was an op-ed in Bloomberg that was a bit tone-deaf perhaps
But it was just about ways that people could deal with
Inflation
It wasn't even about like it's bad for the Earth or anyting
Although
Has been written about in the past like going back
Print of pet ownership
So one of the main problems
About this Bloomberg
Nothing that is lady was addressed to people who make less
$300,000 a year
So just from that premise
It's going to piss some people off
And they did get dumped
I am shocked
That people would he
Here from bloomberg.com
But you know things said
Maybe are tone-deaf towards the Poor's
Turn the in the tweet it said that you should replace meet with lentils but the article actually just said
It suggested meat substitutes
Essential
Like
Detail that missing from
Another suggestion that's in the article is to
Rethink those costly Pet Medical
This wasn't saying that you should kill your Pat or that you shouldn't take your pet to the vet but that some expenses related to pets might not be
Be good expensive
The next line the article is quote
It may sound harsh but
But researchers actually don't recommend pet chemotherapy which
Can cost up to $10,000
For ethical reasons
You know this article sucks it's really obvious that Alex is creating fake version of it.
Get mad at ya
Kill your pets
The two things are problematic about
This clip R1
Alex is supposed to be in the grips
So some really serious emergency situation with his health
I stress but here he is on whether genuinely or is it performance
Would you be pretty bad for blood pressure
He's probably calm down
Yeah
Alex has a rich history of a talking about killing dogs
On way more than one occasion in the past
She's gone on and on about how he's killed dogs
So I don't know if he's actually the best messenger for this right-wing fake outrage
About this
I think
It kind of makes it supposed comedy piece got there at the end of the little bit less impact
The satire that piece is supposed to be that it's outlandish to imagine Alex killing his pet
But it's not
You talked about doing everything a bunch
To the Past
I don't know it it doesn't
It hits.
Currently the get sick
Kind of psychopath would talk about killing their
KATU
We do we need to stop on this dog's head
Never
Thought about things
For more than a second
It's
It's a total massing saying
So
There's a lot of time spent with Alex interviewing
His former employees Savannah
When she got kicked off Twitter after posting
Videos
Interviewing people about how
Unfair it is that Leah Thomas is allowed
Two competing with
Oh she was doing some transphobia
Yes scotches as it turns out she wasn't actually kickoff for the video
To kick-off for creating a new account to Aveda previous ban
And the way that her new video went viral in the right-wing media it brought division
She was originally kicked off in 2024 election related misinformation
Anyway she's gone on to become a personality and a producer at the blaze which is probably really smart for her career
It's still a dead end
Very least Glenn Beck isn't selling product at below cost in order to squeeze out a couple more months on air
I'm not going to cover her interview because honestly I don't care
I'm just going to play this one clip because I think it really
Illustrate
How little Alex does
He doesn't know what he's talking about
Savannah Hernandez really joining us bottom the hour to write down some really huge nose
One of the swimmers that saw the complaint
But you didn't like that
Man
Plus collar the other women
I'm being able to
Take over
Weather
Waterworld
So you got multiple aspects of the story wrong
The first is that the interview Savannah did was not with someone who filed the complaint it was just a person with some slightly critical comments about 2
Thomas seemed to be about her friend
Make finals
And I guess
Said she would have if Thomas had
Swimming
I don't recommend pursuing this line of
Thinking to its logical
Conclusion because it
Doesn't go anywhere good
The second thing that Alex has wrong here's at the
Person Savannah was interviewing didn't get kicked off Twitter
Savannah
This is the entire reason this is a story and why Alex would be having
He's doing a right-wing media blitz to
Strike while the Iron's hot and her victimhood argument is fresh in people's minds
Some sleep Hazard that Alex doesn't seem to understand the premise of the interviewees agreed do I show you
Literally no preparation for this at all
Anyway like I said
Decide this interview was just transfer OBS that's
That's all that's going on here
Basically concern-trolling 2
These folks attempt to mask their underlying intent bigotry behind
Pretend sincere concern about women's swimming
Yeah I hear I mean
It's so f******
Bulshit how dare you
How fuk I mean they're not just that but
Simply because
Bill Burr made the transpo big joke that everybody has been dining out on on the far-right like 10 years ago
In one of the special
That it was done in a completely different
Contacts
Text to make it look like
He's the idiot for having this kind of thought process
Says whatsoever
They're just going to do the same f******
B******* because it doesn't matter
It doesn't matter what it is if it's not
Sports it
Derivation be in the bathrooms if it's not the bathrooms it's they shouldn't be in the same restaurant it doesn't f******
Matter it's just a thing
I agree it's infuriate
So if you're somebody
Who's had his lawyer contact
And say that you have a serious
Emergency medical
Condition
I would say
Probably wouldn't want to then go to work
And do a ridiculous pageant of a show the next
Baby
Definitely if you did do that
You probably wouldn't want to say on there that you're going to come back and do another show that he's
Real this is all out the open
The new world order something else
I have a special
Live Infowars broadcast
Tonight
From at least 7 to 9
Commercial free
Phone calls
On the great reset on the New World Order
Don't know what you think we should do is call her
Stop this it'll be
I don't know if he actually ended up following through with that but I would just not have done that
Yeah the next clip is him saying like never felt better in my life
This is as good as it gets for me I've I feel like I've lost like five pounds in the past couple of days like what I was
Kind of hoping there'll be some clip of him
One supplement
31 Westcliff
Santa it's because
Alex
For the third hour does interview that
Economist stock picker guy
He sucks
I don't even care
The clip Valley
Getting into the interview
Hade to have them give people
These
Morphine.
Watch him die
But you're read this here's the headline
Hospitals bribe to put patients on Pathway to death
By the National Health Service Trust
Targets on Liverpool care pathway
The third hours in Davis interview the stock Trader Edward out
Sweetly insane
He's on to talk about the governor
What's killing everyone at Kojak's
See and then what happened
Central piece of evidence in covering the story seems to be this article about the Liverpool care pathway
The current story
It has to do with the pandemic
You obviously forgot
Got to check the date on the article he's reading
He didn't look into this at all so he has no idea the decade-old story and that the LCP was
Is phased out in 2013
I don't know how else to put this
Dish it's a
If I was scared at all about the quality of the work he's doing
Realizing that he f***** this up that bad should be a huge issue for him
You should do a big segment on the next episode about how to import
It is to check
Dates on stories
Giving people assisted suicide drug
Any of that
His audience accepted ever trashy gives them
There's no incentive to do better than trash
MetroPCS
It's trash absolute trash
This show is at the present a more less combination of extreme bigotry and incompetently delivered false news
Stories
I think I see this a bit but it Bears repeating
There's no value in the existence of Infowars as a piece of the information landscape
It's full-on come
Completely negative
In terms of
Society
I like you do you think about
Just would like the
I came from
Early on
I think that I had a position that was far more like
There's a place for something like Alex in the world
I still kind of believe that that
It's true there's there's
There's a place for skeptical voice
But that's not what this is
There's a world where
And Alex Jones
Performance
Is appreciated
Because it is not having any effect on people's actual life
Well I really unfortunate world where the performance is
Very much hurtful
I would take issue with how you phrase that
I got agree slightly
Even a
Different
Organize world
This has
Oh no no absolutely not that I think that there is a model of somebody who can be
Generally wrong but asking
Pointed question
That does have a societal value
Position that I kind of
Felt like
This is the idea of Alex
It's not what
Is the buffoon
The buffoon the ark
No no just that
That f****** idiot
Who's sometimes says something in your like a
Instead of being the idiot who says Non-Stop
I won't get what is the what is the buffoon is a hateful bigot and then also
All the time
And tries to sell you s*** there's no place in the world for that
Not even in the media landscape in the world
Think what I'm trying to get at when I'm trying to stress
Isn't that like
There may have been
A Time
Listening to
Alex Jones
Could give you like
Maybe
.01
Value
301 info Buena compared to read a story which might be like 1
Info
Trace Amounts of info unit
Open metric this
Supermedia now it might be in the negative it is negative
Dice lower faster
It's a
Little man
I'm interested to see where his health
Situation goes
Proceed somebody's other court cases
What's up what develops with them
And whether he's back in studio on Friday
Eddie
Any outcome is
Possible with this morning on Friday
He's got a show
We have about having late do the whole show laying down
That's the way you do another I demand
Absolutely
We will not get it but will be back on
Yes we will
We aren't Staten Island Resort fighting
S***
I feel like I can't see doctor marbles anymore since dr. William mount
Nope
Maui the international Man of
Peace are well back to their oldie but a goodie
Until then
Emilio dzx Clark I'm Daryl rundus
And now here comes
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work