Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
What's fight.com
For the altar of Selene and talk a little bit about to Alex
Text Jones
Jordan This is dangerous
What's the address
Its mustard
Well here's what's a interest okay
I'm thinking about doing a year of Mustang
That is dangerous I have for the last couple weeks I did with enjoying must
A couple different varieties that are like
One of them is to mustard and I love it I love it
You love the extra mustard but it's so much mustard delicious
And I'm thinking about that really trying to incorporate this into my personal brand
I think that is a kind of guy I mean I think Twitter it will eventually
New kind of guy just dropped mustard guy
Yeah I don't know I feel like there's a lot to explore in terms of the world of Masters and I think I could get 69
9 mustards down
I don't want to bite off more than I can chew but
Look I'm going to put the world on notice a lot of mustard
My brain works
Yes
A lot of mustard
I like it
How about you
By bright spot is we play Scattergories
We got together
Opened up the box play all night
What you have lost the pieces of your Taboo game
Subway with
End of the show sister podcast Marty and Sarah
And plates categories and it was I've not played Scattergories in a long time and it is a very fun
It is also the first time that I played
Way too high to play a word game
True and it made a guy I was not high cuz usually protect that too much into the weeds
I found some
It helps him sleep a little bit
I have I have enjoyed some gummies for Sleep purposes
But
Speaking as the non Stone person in the room
I did but also a little frustrating to try and argue whether or not words couch with
3 Stone people
Experience
It's rare in my life it is and it will stay
It will never happen to the bonds probably cuz you guys
Like the grass all day we like sagarika
You guys like that to that to that
I f*** I can't even come up with another Torquay way on the top of grass
It was fun time play some games
Also codenames
We're going to go back to the back in time out
So after our last episode
I felt really shity
Because
I have given Alex
Too much of a benefit of a doubt
About his medical condition that he was out of his deposition
On Friday he got back on his show and announced that
Bright good work
So thanks buddy I don't know what to believe whether the that's Saving Face about an actual medical condition that he has to go
He doesn't want
People to look at him as weak right if it's a situation where the
Case the lawyers had already left
And now he knew he wasn't going to have this deposition
The facade can drop and what have you
But whatever the case I felt a little bit like a mark
And that I had to pay cared more than I should have fangs not the first time that this is occurred
No and it's kind of one of the downsides
Do you know
Engage with
The work of a liar
And sometimes you can never be
I resent it and I'm not happy about it so what I'm going to do
Alex isn't going to be back in the present on our Show and Tell episode 666
David Allan Coe in the present
2022 will return
On 666 we are going to be doing other things
We have other type types it up so there's some fun stuff
Back in the past
July 24th 2000
M3
Others
Nonsense and that a massive Revelation PA
Where is Taco Bell
Talking nonsense alright
Deedee megadoodoo thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
But you're about to
Making that money off that heroin thank you so much and I apologize
Text Joey votto's biggest fan thank you so much
Thank you very much before the global nuclear Holocaust thank you so much
We made it
Thank you baby
We'll see tomorrow
Daddy shark baba baba baba thank you so much
My name is king of gravy thank you so much
Thank you very much
Name I do not approve of this at all right
During sex you're now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
My enemies
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
All your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not in nor was he in the past
But you know what is better than Alex
Listening to Archdale while having sex no that's stuck in my brain for the rest of my life it scares me yeah
Terrified
No but something that is great it was weird we have a special birthday happy birthday to to send
Huxley
Your mother Stephanie reached out and I wanted us to wish you a happy birthday
And look I don't I don't know how else we can make this
Like a really special birthday
So I heard you're a big fan of John Oliver and so we actually got him
To come and wish you a happy birthday along with us
Holy cow
I can't do a John Oliver
Oliver I can't do it, failure
Was it whenever I was like
Boy I wish this was a video
42 weirdest f****** movement trying to get into character
I got nothing I'm sorry happy birthday
Before starting to do an impression then
That's a gift profiles
We're back in 2003 from Today Show
How rude
Did not see that coming here is where the episode starts
Notice about this is that
I was really into talking about 9/11
This episode
Rtaa
Believe the government
What's the district is being reported there was a poll of people in Germany was the statistic
But you listened to him describe it what was it
People who believe that
The United States did 911 68% is something 30% is something maybe 18
19% I don't know
I was doing a bunch of times
And I don't think
You'd be able to tell what he's talkin to
Do you know the general top he's saying that 70% of Germans believe that the United States did nine
11 if I corrected that no you're not
68% is apparently the amount of the think that the media isn't telling them the truth
Unclear from listening to it what is which percent rice is 30% but that's actually people under 30
Percent of people under Thirty 11
How many people in France
We'll get to that in a minute
Like if you listened to enough of Alex's show you'll notice that often times concrete stories are reported in ways that leave you
Completely unaware of what actually being reported
And I think that's intention
But leaving that aside that clip include the really interesting little tidbit that if
I think those herbs attention
In 2003 Alex's
Perfectly comfortable saying definitively that it
It's proven fact
That the government did 9/11
In the present-day what he's asked about Alex Hedges this position and tries to pretend it questions about the official story
I was just joking
Independence still say that he knows the name of the perpetrator
Like everybody in the organization
Fast forward to today and you would never make that type of claim
Or like
I will name names
I talked about this a little bit in the past the idea of wet concrete how the immediate aftermath of an event is essentially
We can make it impression it very easily
But if you wait for the concrete
The dry it's really hard to get your narrative to make it
You can't write your name another the sidewalk
Is a very large part of why people like Alex really try to spam their theories hard-and-fast
But there's a sign aspect of this Dynamic where in order to make your immediate theories seem more convincing to people in those Early Times
You have to be completely in
Static in your certain
People looking for answers and you seem like a bad source of answers if you present your theories as possibilities that you can't
True
You have to push them as if you have a rock-solid case or else you run into the risk of your audience searching for someone else
To give them the impression of that certainty that they need in order to comfort
As time goes on this position needs to soften
Because as always the case these kinds of conspiracy theories
Fall Apart
It becomes too obvious that there was no basis for your certainty in the first place
Like it's no good to be certain 10 years after the fact that everything looks stupid
But the way
The way that this
This
Works is like
It's just different tones of voice of trust
Depending on where you are in the relationship
And then ten years later it's like
Yeah but you can trust me I know but you can trust me you help me
There's an unspoken agreement between the conspiracy theorist In Their audience
The emotional need for certainty that the audience
Looking for
Have you
Conveniently forgets later that the things that the theorist was certain about we're bulshit
Without the status quo show like Alex's could not
If Alex didn't provide that certainty is audience would find him
If his audience held him to his past positions and demanded he explained
How this certainty about things
Be able to do the show that he does not seem to be unable to provide the audience with their comfort and certainty that they need
Next time right
Definitive positions will be taken that are quietly disowned later
The audience will get ready to unquestioningly believe the next position Alex throws out in the cycle
Goes on and on
Just thinking like in the covid times how many narratives Alex's announced has definitively proven that he just kind of forgotten about at
Clear
That is embarrassing to talk about how viruses themselves don't exist
Ohio liquor let the virus if you choose that the energy needs to stay outside
Play Everybody Knows
That was more of a scary thing but
But yeah if it's sad that this Dynamic I think is really going to be something that you see pretty
I pretty
Clearly in this episode I think just like the definitive Miss of stuff that's like you don't believe that
I mean that is that is really great
As far as like showing you what it is that the that Infowars really cells
You know they sell the feeling of somebody who knows what's going on
Essentially you can take despite the world being horrible would you already knew it was
There's some comfort in knowing that this man has a grasp on
That's not only videos of spotted but like because of that grass that he has what he is describing is a world that is
Is Ron by
Bright sort of
Like A to B to C to D
I predictable events and everything there's no chaos or Randomness right there's no like
People who have different interests that sometimes a line and sometimes don't
There's none of that
That that that chaos
The world that works
Nan a comforting
Conspiracy that runs everything
Cousin
Inexplicably
The more
Complicated and complex the conspiracy is
The more simple it makes people feel like life
Because book
You can just do it
The large part of the certainty in the comfort that Alex sells
But the price is looking like an idiot
Yes
More more
At this point France's population was closer to 61 million people which
20 million people off 33% off
Now
Service book he's talking about is called Left real blood
Posterior
Or the horrifying fraud English under the title 911 the big lie
Since its release the book has been robbed
Comically debunked and its author Terry Mason
Is not taken seriously by anybody Direct
Mazza's name
I mean 2002 article in time Europe
Claims that the book had spent six weeks at the top of the French
Best seller list
Which is no small feat that's fairly impressive for a book
And I think that's the basis for Alex's outrageous claim that it sold 30 million copies
That number is f****** insane and a June 2002 article
Which is after the whittwood have spent 60 to the top of the charts
This article from June 2002 in CNN puts the sales figure at 200,000
C8 was either that or I believe
I remember this be
But being right there released next to harry-potter-and-the-sorcerer's-stone I think they like the same level of
30 million people like 30 million books sold in France
Like you got to consider like how many people are under the age of 18
They turned that book into their National currency I would be surprised
Price of it sold 30 million
Global
Alex could play the real number and it would be impressive if you know anything about like
Could book sales or the French book Market
Jumps off the page
In addition to that it's really important for Alex to make the image appear to be the people who believe
Libra things Infowars reports
Are the majority in the world
Yeah
See any of them on your daily basis
Doesn't mean that they're not every right but that's why it's harder to make that perception stick when you talk about the United States
Exotic like
911 truth
Indeed they love that.
So are we not friends book Numbers
We got
A German
Paul that Alex is reporting weirdly
Alex has done his own polling
Bermuda on
What
You heard me on the
In the morning
That's not scientific
I don't know what conclusions you can draw from the type of calls you get when you guest on radio shows
I like the idea of calling that doing a little Pole right now
I don't know how long
For whatever length of time whatever number of people on several radio stations
Well that one out of 30 people in America want to kill me
What are we thinking about
Dumb
What hit did you
Did you research
What
His actual poll results
No
I didn't I don't think that I could ever find these Podunk radio show
No-name ass radio shows that he's been on
Have made it
I'll tell you that no no
New
Sober look Alex
The calls
30 Gates
Multiple interviews today
Keyboard
The difference between a good and bad poll is all down to methodology
The number of participants is definitely one of the factors but it's much more important variables are controlled directly to end up with
Representative sampling of the population
Which is something that Alex is dumb radio interview pull doesn't capture at all like
There's a selection bias personality Alex there shows what types of shows are there
What types of audiences probably listen
Do a shoulder would have Alex Auditore
What type of person would call in when Alex was on as a guest
There's there's a lot a lot of
Confounding variables here
Interesting Lee though there's one conclusion you absolutely can draw from Alex's telling their story
9/11 was the best thing that ever happened to him from a career perspective
He went from not really that many people being in
Understand interviewing him to people banging the doors
And that's because he claimed a level of confidence and assertiveness in the position you was putting forward
Which made him interesting
He wasn't saying that he questioned the mainstream Narrative of 9/11 and he wasn't saying there were anomalies he wasn't saying that he had doubts
Those positions would be boring
You were saying loudly and into a bullhorn that it was definitively proven the bush and his administration did 9/11 in the plane
Remote control
He had all the evidence
Dead to rights
You don't even debating
What makes a person stand out and when is someone who has a clear inherit set of chops
Like Alex has
This can lead to a little bit of a media windfall
And that's exactly what
People were confused and trying to make sense of a national tragedy that's ended up affecting the entire world
And Alex is there bombastically offering answer
Hardly matter
Not the reason I bring this up is because it's a no longer profitable for Alex to be certain about 9/11
It wasn't 2002-2003
At that point being uncertain probably would have been a detriment to Alex's bran
And this is exactly what you see with him in the present day
He's all but disowned pretty much all of the insane bulshit he was pushing back then
You're never going to hear him try to sell a loose change DVD on his show or talk about how the hijackers are still alive
Stuff you pretend
Wasn't part of Macon
His career because that would actually be shameful for him to admit
He never could prove any of that stuff but because it got him more attention
Alex represented himself as someone who could prove it all
You manipulated people in the aftermath of a huge tragedy for his own profit
They want it was no longer profitable to sell those lies
He moved on and pretended he never said that stuff to begin with
I began lying about another
Alex's career is rooted in tragedy profiteering
The most notable events in his career the things that put them on a national stage
All of them were things were he was lying about something painful to someone else
Oklahoma City 911 Sandy Hook
The Boston bombing the Aurora Batman shooting
All of these are events where Alex sold his could
Levy made-up story in the immediate term
Heaven now doesn't want to be judged by what he sold
And I don't accept that and no one should
Its total b*******
Yeah
Absolute f****** nightmare
I want a good person to do huh it is odd like
It is it is so f***** up about the way that our media culture is just geared
Like it is geared towards making a man like Alex Jones a star that is a bi mean
As you were saying
Making those
Claims immediately makes him interesting
Think about the guy who wrote that French book
It's definitive
You cut the top of the bestseller list right it's kind of hacking that that detention
I think we accidentally built
Then
You know
Nuance or confusion or just
AAA
Blanket acceptance of like
Oh yeah this is a
Series of random occurrences
Turn on like NPR All Things Considered and I'll be like
Talk about a story with an extra like
If possible this is going to bed we talked we can see that being one way
Or we could see it being the other way
I'm God I'm listening to this then fuc
Comparison Keibler's coming on later
I would turn on Alex
Okay I'm listening
To look there's a lot of people out there in the world
Who believe 911 was
Sure I especially in France
And terminate that's true
About
We offer
I am stop this already
This report is in the audiobook
Yes
Alright
I don't believe that you read the entire report
Audiobook
Okay
I'm listening
He's serious
He's at
This is not a joke
Feathers on my back man that wasn't a report.
But the technology Minister did
This is entirely based on an interview that Andreas Von Bulow did with a German newspaper
Spiegel
I was published
On January 13th 2002
Modulo had been out of his position as the technology minister in Germany since1982
Miss Bedford technology minister of Technology
Yeah that 18 years there was like four more than 1821
He was definitely spouting 911
Conspiracy theories but he wasn't saying it from the position of certainty that Alex is claim
Again Alex's game relies on creating the fake impression of certainty and it order for the storage really pop for him
He needs to protect that certainty out to all of his sources including Von Bulow
It's not enough to have it's just say that he gave an interview where he said that he found it Unthinkable that the hijackers could have pulled off
The attack without intelligence community help
This story needs to be that he proved right
Analysis
It can't be an old man far out of government going like
Man this is so crazy it can't be true also my head is Giant
If you're Alex
You need to cram CertainTeed on your audience
Ancestry
You want them to think of themselves as question again skeptical but in reality the most dangerous proposition for you is the eye
Idea that they might actually start question
Make things like
The things you're saying
Why are you so sure of this
Do you want the artificial are of questioning
Not so much the reality the impression that they are smarter for not asking you
You quest right
Yeah and
Repeating
The question
Pat yourself on the back for that
Just to be clear I think Alex now would love
For everyone to believe that all he did was say like
I have questions and you know I think the government let 9-11 happen what he wants people to hear
That's not at all what he was saying
You know
Pearl Harbor
Okay so they did it
All right thing
Alright so
Now I'm it's so now Port Pearl Harbor was not a false flag
No it was it was but it was allowed it was a real event
That could have been
Stop yo what was allowed to happen because might as well have been
Where is with 911
George W got in that f******
Complain I would say that's remote controls is probably more like Cheney
Right now it's pretty focused on that document but he didn't write
Yeah
I I think that this is this would be a tough thing for our
What's the standard height
In the present day
It is in the years since it is not come out
And we are not all convinced that the United States government did a number of things that were in the documentary that Hebrew
Produced not true
The only thing that was true was directed by
Jason bermas
So you can't kill the truth
Of some folks who may be trite
Conspicuous in their absence
The devil
Bought the game
Pandora's Box is open
Matter
Boy
World Order
It's interesting like as I was listen
That I was thinking that it can't kill the truth but
Apparently what will do the trick in terms of killing something for Alex to decide is not profitable
Pretend it's the truth anymore
These globalist don't need to do anything nefarious to get Alex to stop covering something
I just have to wait until his audience gets bored of it and he moves on to another subject
Entailed
Only proven
Are so embarrassing leave his debunked that he needs to pretend he never believe that stuff
To begin with
That's the trick
Yeah
Wait about you'll get bored
Anymore
The enemy was nice at the end though like
Weird that
These folks don't seem
We working for the devil
Not anymore
Justin
Good old-fashioned can cartel with human motivations at plant
Wouldn't have to really be that crazy to buy into this stuff back then
Really
Get me on the hook
Cartel causing problems very real not even not not only not surprising
Almost certainly happening concert
Recognizing that secretly believes that
It's a battle between Angels and Demons Supernatural forces
Not sound true to me
Fannie Mae Freddie Mac
All the devil
So is calls
On this
I miss this
This call was fun this guy wants a
To know what what
Hey what's going on
You got inside sources
Tell me what's going on help us out
Alex is not a good answer
Impression or
Maybe some of your
I can't do John Oliver
Whomever
Maybe
Baby
Big little menu
Or getting
What
Cool I can tell you about the C-SPAN guy
Totally real that I have multiple sources but I can tell you about a book talk
I know your question was are minions getting cold
Thundermans
Kevin
No idea grew is a character
Which character
I don't know what'll happen
So look
Talk to sources really
Why would you
Everything is so obvious obvious it's open source
What
Do you know how
No
I worried worried about me tell you how we're empowering the Illuminati
I don't know what's going on
Logical Veil evidence
What was the plan against 5:00 of footage of someone eating somebody
That's too long I don't know if it would take that long
Want to eat somebody I would stay fresh
Yeah
What's cooked
Also I love this like I do want to meet with us all the time
Great meetings where we have caviar and they tell me I'm great
I have conversations at the adult table
Not like you little babies who take dumb pigs
No no I no psychological warfare powering how they died
Tell me on this all right I'll try I mean look there's two aspects of it okay
Number one
We are
Good level
Haha
Kickflip mctwist
Unbreakable came out in two
Something like that right right okay so do you understand what you talking about at all
Can you can you translate that
Is that by telling people what the Illuminati is doing and
People not really being able to do anything to stop it
We are desensitizing them to the Mead 202 stop
No
Okay
Intuitively on a subconscious level everybody out in the world already knows in their bones and in the
Their Spirit what the Illuminati is doing right
Fine I'm just telling you what I was just
So everyone understands that and what Alex is doing is revealing the method
So he's
Putting
To conscious mind what unconscious mind already knows
Sure
So he's telling everybody all this stuff
Which is actually a favor to the globalist
Because then once
The the the the
The Prestige happened
The Prestige happens in there's the revelation of like what the globalist erupt
Then there won't be open rebellion and like a like a civil war breaking out or whatever because Alex Azar
30 revealed
This two people
So it won't be such a cataclysmic
It's like telling people you're preparing them
Ultimate Echo
Well it's basically like
The idea that qanon folks had of like
Weird people are going to look at us like we're crazy and then once
The Prestige happens basically they'll realize that we we knew all along and we were right
Kind of idea
But it's serving the globalist interest because then there won't be a big kaboom
When they reveal happen
Right
What was going on right right right right part of the globalist plan apparently but
Subah twist within the twist
Alex's I think referencing
Like he has
Baked into his content somehow
Away there even
This isn't in the globalist best interest or something who knows all right
There's a second what's important is that he has outsmarted the globalist
Somehow
I can tell you how
They're not real
Yeah if you create an enemy for yourself look stupid you know how smart am every single time
Who hears this never lost a game to myself and Chesnaught once here's the second way
Conspiracies helping the Illuminati
What happened
America
New World Order
Mines in the world
Liberal
North America
Wharf
Imperial MO
Cersei yes indeed
Say yes indeed
Clearer than the
First one
Right
So
If I understand correctly
Is allowed well
Let blood called the Illuminati
That's probably better
The Illuminati the the UN has a sub-branch directory
List of the
Okay so the Illuminati
Has revealed that
Delicious
That
The United States did 9/11
Right in order for the world
I hate America including America
The concert
And then Americans themselves will say we don't want America anymore we want to join
Do you end that we are already a part
Yeah more or less or less but I think the subtle difference
The distinction is
The globalist
The Illuminati don't they're not putting out the America did 9/11
Take Alex to get that message out
Which time tarnishes the image of America
Doing their job well but he
He's trying to be very
Quitter
Said it's not America that did it
A hundred percent of his audience on a shirt that says Bush did.
He's doing the thing
He's not cuz he's distinguishing
Between the globalist of taken over the United States Americana
States rights
The Lure of America
He has more important that you can't kill the Lord Lord didn't do it
The Lord and do 911
The color has been interesting quote
To help Alex feel better
No
If you recall our last 2003 episode Canadian called in and wanted to get to fight with Alex
About how he's a coward for not supporting the war
Alex
Still a little Rob at this I think because this car wants to make him feel better
With a Teddy Roosevelt quote
I guess yesterday
Coming from
Tradernick
I promised really
Or that we
Standby
Did you need to save us
And when the government
What
Real quote
That's an actual quote from an editorial that Teddy Roosevelt wrote in 1918
The problem I have is that that is not an election year
Woodrow Wilson won reelection in 1916
Hey Teddy Roosevelt has been out of office for about a decade at that point and one year away from death
The context for this quote is actually really ironic
If you know where this got
This caller is using it to defend Alex from that Canadian guy who said that Alex was a coward for not supporting the war in Iraq
Boarding bush
Well
In Roosevelt case
He was writing this editorial but how it's great the question
In the government of the president because he was actually born in favor of War than Woodrow Wilson
Any gotten some flak for that
In the previous two years he been writing editorials about how the US needed to get more involved in World War 1
Arguing that Wilson wasn't being strong enough
The editorial of this quote come from is his defensive himself on accusations of him being disloyal
We're calling for more war than the president was way too
We can all agree that it's fine to criticize the present
It's just funny that Alex is lying about when this was written
Hey takes this quote about justifying a desire from World War
Overthrow a government if it just decide that it's full of usurpers
You just can't stop himself
Compulsive liar Roosevelt was taking a bath
You know what's fun about Theodore Roosevelt taking a bath
He had two bathtubs that he put side-by-side he was the original
Viagra commercial I think
That's
Part of it was an Impulse to be like
He was selfless and saying this in the even when
And he was running for president he said it's good.
I don't know he wasn't good with
Presidential criticism when he was the president
Strangely enough
I think
Alex
Just thinks it's a
More interesting story
He wants
To be interesting really bad
It usually does start there
Yeah
I don't know I
I do find it
Little bit
Frustrating
That if I did take the time to like
Really lay out every time there's like one that's an extraneous detail the gooseneck account we would never finish the show
We be here for a long time it would be a 24-hour livestream in perpetuity of dislike
Well here's a weird detail
Team 98
Alex really enjoyed
That idea that he laid out of
The globalist want to make the US look bad and want to join the u.s.
Think I've heard him say that too much
But he expounds on a little more.
Level
Okay
Because
There's so many fantasy layers to this belief but if you really think about it
I was kind of really does need to create this elaborate maze in order to
Defend his points against obvious Roboto
For instance you have to ask yourself is allowed to be on Aaron profit from yelling about how Bush did 9/11
Just go home and live in peace of it
The new world orders of bloodthirsty Kabbalah murderers will defend their banking cartel at all costs
They orchestrated both world wars
Zagato magic they can handle taking out an idiot in Texas
If you were doing something they didn't like of course and that's why they're letting him do it because
They're okay with thinking people knowing about 9/11
Alex isn't popular enough for him to use the I'm out in the public so they have
Let me live kind of think so I think this is kind of a decent tops
And for him to go with to explain his own existence within this
The scheme only did 911 but they did it intentionally sloppy enough
Subway so that the thinking people in the world would see the obvious Clues they left behind
And they would use these to argue that the US did 9/11 which is
A great
Plan B a judo move
In reality they want people to say that the US did 9/11 so that they can make us look bad
And trick people into liking the who at right
There's so many moving Parts in this plant and none of it makes sense
If Alex was right in the New World Order
Secretly wanted people to think that the US did 9/11 the people who said that the US did 9/11 be promoted and put
Bush by the media
And not completely marginalized
Do you think that the global is to control all world media
Wouldn't want 9/11 conspiracy theorist to be treated like completely unhinged idiot
Because their claims being accepted
Essential step in achieving the globalist
And yet every news story from around the time
About 9/11 conspiracies treats these people is completely wrong or is malicious liar
That shouldn't be the case of what Alex is saying is that you don't understand
Only thinking people need to know this information
Right and the only way to get thinking people to know this information
Is to have the mainstream media deny that information
Because thinking people will then go oh well the mainstream media is always lying to me
So if the mainstream media is telling this side of story that means obviously that the truth is
That the United
States did 911 however not the United States government
Actually the Illuminati
Listen I would have been a lot better it's categories I'll tell you that right now
Really wanted to make people not like the United States ticket just have like a more realistic Frank discussion about US foreign policy
DNR history
That would probably tarnish people's impressions of our country real quick
There's no need to do a 9/11 what is unnecessary the real story of Banana Republic
In every high school textbook and everybody will be like oh yeah I hate America
So
I think I kind of agree with something that a caller says a little bit earlier
Point out how recently was
Uday Hussein
Celebrating the death of humanity
Totally forget the we've already lost
Everyday
So Alex is still not to believe in Minute saddam's Kids
They're fine another great prediction
He knows okay
Yeah man
The Illuminati it was pretty grotesque
The releasing the death footage
The Dead images of them
I understand
There was a reason why
The government did that we talked about that a little bit but like I still don't
How do I understand the reason as an explanation
Don't think it was the right thing to do
And Alex is really dumb
So
All those things can be true simultaneous
Alex
That believes they're fake
Eddie gives just the
Perfect
Real world
Analogy
Let's explain it
Photograph
Forensics
Anyway okay
When the computer
It's all good well to present a theory that the government's going to fake some kind of evidence but I think
It doesn't really make for a compelling case when you just come up with like
We're trying to come up with a real life example and you just reference of movie that Sub-Zero
Was chasing down
John Richard Wright
And he was on the ice rink
And that's the ice rink is the Twin Towers
Okay and so is skating on the ice rink and that's okay.
And then
In the Gold's net which is
Alex Jones story
You may notice that Alex does this all the time because he believes that movies are speaking cryptic messages
The New World Order is taunting him and revealing their truths through the movies
Mickey chooses to see it's just like running man
The New World Order
Do you think that he's claiming that they do all the time. He's
Out of his mind
The Pentagon did really just released photos of Uday and kusay is bodies which a lot of people
We thought was gross
Alex and just pretending that they didn't also do dental exams and x-rays to confirm
These bodies were in fact
Because it sounds more fishy if it was just a picture
It sounds way better if you say all of their spending days preparing
They're not doing any of those
Normal things are legit before this episode is over
Of course also there were things like he's having an 8-inch metal bar in its leg which they got after he was the tar
Target of an attempted assassination in 1996
Is he right now what
There were plenty of pieces of evidence that these were saddam's kids but the Pentagon was also
Really set
I'm making sure that people who are fighting
Against them in a rock
Accepted
These were saddam's kids
Because bad weather demoralized
I understand the reason why you would release the photos again
I think it's gross
I suspect that the clear intention that was evident that they wanted to prove that this was rude and kusay
Turn off the distrust alarm if people like Alex in this caller
Yeah and they can't accept
What's being sad
Because they are so trained
To be defiant
And
And it's almost a preemptive attack
Check on them
You know that idea of like
We're going to release the photos
So you can't lie about it you know they've they have to immediately go like a f****** lie about it for sure
For now
This defiance
Sing it doesn't even really mad right I don't
I think what's being said like if
Biden
The International Community
I don't know how this would happen but
Right
Alex will be defending Ukraine
You know yeah you're probably right it's
It doesn't matter it's just whatever is being said
By the people that he doesn't like he's got to take the office
Society
Tiring
Like we're teaming up with
Russia to fight the Nazis in Ukraine come out
I did qualify that I don't know how
How that would happen
Pick the opposite 700%
Sounds good another caller
This means nothing
It has nothing to do with any
But I really enjoy this guy's thought pattern
Intelligent
Started a new age
Yeah because
Several years back
Pass regularly
I said how could they
Protocol
Successful New Age Bookstore in Mississippi
He's like
A lot of other conclusions you could come too
Like a tax shelter shelter
Obviously
Independently wealthy
I'll run this new age bookstore in the red just so I have somewhere to go everyday
Successful person in business
Someday all kinds of explanations that don't require the CIA is subsidizing
My Town Barber the f*** you live what you do and you say that
Ninety-nine times out of a hundred
I'm wrong but if I'm right that one time I saved everybody's like let's talk about what
Gordon's this
Small-town bookstore or whatever has to the larger New Age movement
Secret of this conspiracy my friend I never saw anybody in
Is it like
The central Hub of the New Age movement
What he's got to do
Underground bunker
There's something underneath there that is so his small town he's got
Giant oil deposit
Directly beneath the new age bookstore and CIA starts the entirety of new age thought
18 liquor
And that is how they get all the oil for tank
It all comes from that one new age
Wow
That we never would have cracked the code if it wasn't for the scholar I'm proud of him
Listcrawlers
I've been trying to
Now
Piano playing
Oh boy
Go and no trouble
Some idiot talking about
An invisible dog
Leave us alone
Delois Smith
Chester Campbell
Well you need to go in
Get those bylaws
You'll be here in about 10 minutes
From New York
Emergence
Wow you must be really disseminating some pretty seriously dangerous information if
The fattest shut down these stations
Obviously
For whatever reason
How many coaches be situation where they don't have a slot
4 mg
And some people might be more aggressive about trying to get there slot
Maybe he's going about it the wrong way talking to attorneys
Yeah that is a weird way to go Alex's describing
Like give them a lawsuit
That is merit-based
He's essentially saying threatened
Put you on there
Do it on a deal with it
They don't have a log and slapped with a lawsuit anymore are yet in 2003 so depending on the state you might
Be able to let that s***
This is basically harass them with the threat of litigation that you'll get on air and then you can play my stuff in them
In doing so you
You will destroy the station
Correct
I like this I like this
Mediacom series of events that would totally occur
As he described
The FBI would show up
At a local Access TV station
Dare you sir are in the back want Animo totally
This is a bit racist
Well I mean that last caller was a bit racist to a touch he had the racism
Wildly specific about an idiot with an invisible dog fence
Yeah you might have tattoos
This is a bit more race
I will be nice a BioLife
The world I was in the military
But
15 years ago Alex
Fast food restaurant
McDonald's
Wendy's Taco Bell
You name it
Hispanic working in the restaurant
Frugal
They were going
Leader
They're the majority report
The government
Works for the state of Illinois
She told me
Heard that.
You do a lot of
Gas stations
Dunkin Donuts
Pakistani or Indian
What
More
Bring home
You may notice that the scholars is bringing up a feeling buddy as they're all fast food kitchens have a lot of Hispanic
Conversation
It's fascinating how about a minority group getting mentioned and is mine flips through the
Cointreau
This is what comes out
This isn't Alex complaining about his perception that immigrant crime is completely out of
Control in that all these
Fake IDs are accepted for immigrants at this is destroying the country
Mind goes when someone brings up a feeling that a lot of fast-food workers are Hispanic
And that should tell you a lot about Alex and his racist ass brain
You bet also the idea that foreigners get tax exemption is a completely racist myth that circulated forever to demonize
Non-white business owners
But it's not true at all
The irony here is that it actually has its roots in another reality of immigration the people like Alex
Isn't real name leave it if you're not eligible for most federal benefits from the government till 5 years
Cipher you immigrate
Because the right-wing media are they need to portray immigrants as Soleus strain on the system
This entire thing needs to be inferred
In reality most folks aren't eligible for benefits and if they run a business they have to pay taxes
This gets reported at by races xenophobe like Alex has them getting rich on welfare immediately and being text
Exempt for 7 years
It's just big and s*** and there's nothing real about this at all
GIF at again
Trec this payoff turn into the
Great replacement conspiracy theory
The idea that the globalists are trying to bring in all these immigrants using incentives like welfare tax exemption
In order to bring in a population that votes
Subserviently for things that'll take the country way from the rightful whites like out
Alex
In more recent times with a lot of mass shootings
Violence directed at immigrants and being inspired by people's anger immigration
This great replacement conspiracy has gotten a lot of a 10
It's important to recognize though that this was a belief that was very clearly and regularly articulated on Alex's show going
At least a decade
The people who are carrying out these shootings now could very easily have been raised
What kind of information space but Alex creates
Or this fraudulent perception and perspective on immigrations just accept it as reality
It's
It's not
Recent
Yeah I mean
You go back to Pat Buchanan you go back
To you can just keep going back and back and back because
White people are terrified
That they won't
Be able to run roughshod over the rest of the world for
Long
I am just that things are being taken the right over here
Yeah
You're not even being
So throughout this entire episode Alex has been bringing up that the website is down
Florists.com is down
Non
Scandal
Open till the hack
Compartmentalize
Wait aren't they letting you
The word about
Alternative
Information
My iTunes
A guy
United
Farm
Dot-com
Literally
Reloaderz
A few minutes
What
He doesn't know their names but Maddy's sure they're not bad
Yeah so now we've got a coordinated a massive attack on the website
Here's how we talked about it
The beginning of the show like
I didn't even check clips of him talking about it cuz I thought like
That's basically all that was going on
Tomorrow
We've had it
We have some
Problem
Because of some of the
Where are
And we've already got the
Network
Working in the bunch
That people can
Infowars
Dot-com
Detect problem
What I heard them talking about it at the beginning of the show I was like you're leaving money on the table man
Labradoodle
Victim time baby you're under attack
Because I mean obviously
If someone
Someone's attacking the website
Call Buster.
That means they're only doing it
Cuz they're scared
Of the information why you do this
Right
Here's the problem I have with this right now
How can the global us both be
Furiously trying to shut down alternative media sites
And simultaneously
Using
Alternative media to
Disseminate information that they need disseminated it's because
They know that the globalist attacking him will make him look more legit right
And so they're doing it right
The United Nation
I mean you know it when you put it like that
Here's my problem WhatsApp
There is that
Tens of millions of hits every month
Maybe there are millions of individual pageviews not visitors enough to
F****** stupid site
It's because he's too
Mountain
I mean he did say earlier that it was actually
Not even
Traffic in the town where the servers are weird
We were hell
The DDOS attack and
Apparently a saboteur
It's all things at once
That sounds right this is sort of a inter
Interesting Pro do a version of
But Alex is marketing
Plan that he would use
Once I got kicked off all the Social Media stuff
Verboten information
This
People not wanting my s*** around
Kind of setback that I can have whether it is getting kicked off something or attack problem
Can be presented as proof that what I'm doing is
F****** serious and dangerous and it'll never stop because people really don't want me around is true
Wow is it true
Now
We could have sex
The saboteurs
But actually we do
Warren
Wow
That is very sad
That's that's the type of
Bulshit where I barely got offer that day like man that was
That was so great when I ripped into that DDOS attack those pretty guys did you hear that
We got attacked
Angel I've heard this
Those are song
I don't remember any of the other members of
Look
This is somebody's.
This is the furthest back I've heard the heck
Attack
Games played
And
Funky
Young
Internet * 03
That's crazy it's true it's hard to choose probably hosting on Angelfire and s*** this is probably
Play before he had an Infowars dating on Netscape
So that's dumb it's fun for him
But you get the call
This is where everything goes
Okay good
It was a Sumptuous I won't know the main twist isn't this caller is a sovereign citizen
Watching something I'm hearing
Public Access
Speechless
I don't even remember who is getting
He talked about
Call Noni
Nations are actually nations are really Corporation
And
Everything runs
International marriage
Actually work
$630,000
Do the US
Could you stop
World we post
We don't
Yeah this dude just tell him straight up siren City
9 oz rambling around making
Vague references to some document but
Actually just the National Security study memorandum 200
This is an analysis of population growth Trends and their implications
For National Security
Nothing to do with signing over populations as collateral in the
The stuff about sterilization
Is just Alex lying about suggestions in the document about providing funding for contraception and the develop
Open world
Yep everything Alex is saying is b******* deployed to justify The Sovereign citizen nonsense with his collar is asking
Rubik's of wonder if Alex actually believes The Sovereign citizenship or if this is just a desperate attempt to make sure the
The audience thinks he knows everything and is really interesting
Yeah I can't tell
Maybe both I mean
That might as well be Sovereign citizenship
No caller is bring it up and Alex's
You bet
In function
Pretty bad if you're a listener and you believe Alex
He's leading you down an insane and dangerous path
These kinds of beliefs model directly into the world of sovereign Citizen Community
A greater chance of taking an ideas about how your
Supposed rights might make you kill a cop who pulls you over for driving without a license
Alex should really be more careful and not just makes it up whenever he wants to feel smart
But there's a sub twist
Photo
Three-story house
I'm sorry what
And that was
Do I understand correctly
That the judge said
This is maritime law
So the judges he was declaring this is akumatized
All right I just want to be clear
That Google Images no I really do and I see the judge being it
An absurdly tall Ben
She's looking up like I just went by Homeplace to making like a legitimate
Really
Grounded legal argument
Lady I'm sorry it doesn't matter this is Mayor time I would like to quotes
Many different citator cases
Maritime law
Marathon
I have to really wrestle with the fact that
Galax does believe Sovereign citizenship has also really fantastic
Does sound ridiculous
And everyone
Construe
Scary stuff
That's some pretty scary stuff
Pirates
Should we be flying the Jolly Rodger
I mean what do you mean
Are you asking if it's a good idea to
You like he's saying that
1 ways to get around a lot of these problems they simply to fly the Jolly Rodger I wonder if he's actually
We talkin about the Jolly Rodger flag or is it the metaphor for like the mark of the beast
Need to generate
Specifically about
Well I make a skull and bones is
Like the Jolly Rodger makes me think that it is literally a stall a crossbow
But he's talking about okay
So I think we need to get
Think we got to learn
Well you got to give it up to him
It's true wherever they are now Blackbeard is of the devil
Something like that
Weather make you walk the plank that's really about accepting Jesus
So if I understand correctly if I understand correctly you
Like the cops could come to your home
Enabler
Santa Clara Marathon
To be told by the judge right right maritime law
Gold tassels on nail it to the door first
Text Leah to make a movie about how this person's house is going to BECU that may have to choose to sriprada predict
The program and Arnold Schwarzenegger has to start
Musically or governor
Although a small update on that it's got a call from a guy on this episode
Darnold isn't going to run
Or governor
How did that go
Alex doesn't seem to care that much of that also does not like
Call wasn't interested
Especially compared to like this Revelation that Alex's
Probably a sovereign citizen
I mean really she dances around it so much
This is one of the more concrete instances of like oh you do believe
This s***
That's funny
I think I've
Think he's at this place in his head where it's like
I believe this is true
But I know that they're not going to act
Like it's true I'm not going to be the person who drives around without a license
I have to follow all these rules
But I know in my heart that I don't really have to I'm not going to send the notice in my social site
Airsoft and my $600,000 bank account
New Albany
Should we come to the end of this 2003 adventure and we learned a bit
We
Sub twist after sub twist somebody's up twists
Somebody's with
I really don't like cinnamon twists
I had a hankering
Another non present-day Alex
Text until the market
They flew the Jolly Rodger though
So the globalist get your your afraid of going today
Anyways
But until then
That dude
Real figures
Something else out
Anyway
And now here comes
Robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color