Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge vype.com
Everybody was a little bit of
Alex Jones
Vibrates what today is a continuation of the last bright spot metal
Mustard
But I do appreciate it
I also someone tweeted at us a picture of hot Dan the mustard man
I hope you had a good man and I want to feel like I have to follow you to some sort of hidden pathway if you're hot
Mustard man you're going to have to choose your own condiment to celebrate a year of
There any condiments that you would choose to
Take like a sample varieties of her ear like a brother not enough ketchup's
Here's what I would say salad dressing
Spicy spicy Asian sauces
Okay like a sweet and sour kind of sauce combined with like
Hotel that has a category
The problem
Sub buster
I definitely do a buzzard
My bright spot is somebody
Very kindly they they didn't leave their name on the Note but they very kindly sent me some black
Bean coffee and chocolate chocolate
Fantastic
We've established coffee I just drink so much of it that I might as well survive cheaply alright
Drink a pot of coffee a day and Starbucks catch up to you also Folgers sucks
You drink a pot of it a day and you'll get used to it
Chocolate was really good though thank you very much for the wedding present
I only have one thing to say which is
But I appreciate it sure I wish I had that on hand
Did Emperor also that I made it rolled downhill and I got the
We have a very holiday people be very excited
To learn that today we have
Two depositions come over another full episode for y'all
I think we should not kill anymore
What that mean
I think we do think that's that's that's called for
Or something
You're not about to walk
Crossovers! Thank you so much and I apologize
I'm a policy wonk Jordan is my favorite author thank you so much you are now policy wonk
Very much my dog is a policy knock
Polar besties
Correction
Paul and Brett are besties may not be as intuitive
News on the other side of this but
Hello my name is Eric and I tried to get the
Thank you so much you are now technocrat
I'm a policy wonk I have
Miami star
A list for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe the next few moments broadcast
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
We will not know if he's better yet because today we will be hearing nothing from Alex
Alex info but the news is I've decided what that
I will be a benevolent podcaster and Eric is asking for Daddy shark to come back
Of course I will
I will honor this
On the 666
Alex is coming back
Everything we do is so arbitrary
Preparing this
Podcast is a brutal and ever that it wasn't fun a lot of time
Until I must amuse myself years of mustard
So that's that
Talking about one with kit Daniel who is a editor and writer for Infowars website
Personality although in some videos
Yeah in the past but not regularly
That is an issue that is tomorrow to this
Is a deposition that is related to the Marcel Fontaine case which is a case where
Kate Daniels
I wrote an article and post it on Infowars where he misidentified the Parkland shooter
Based on a picture that he found on 4chan
And this is delved into position
I'm in the second deposition is Owen Shroyer is deposition in the Sandy Hook case
In Texas
These are depositions that Mark Paxton didn't know he wasn't it was not a lawyer who
Who was giving these naturally
Hey who was it well it's Bill Ogden hands up his Cove attorney
For the plaintiff
You know
Pasta episodes
About
Or pattern to talk to the attorney who's holding the deposition
They want to talk to us it's very bizarre has got to run out that's been like there's no way that bill
Have a conversation with us
We Lewis
Hey folks
Hello we are I hear joint to start off this
Is that some poor get into the
These
These depositions here in front of us another formulaic objections everybody loves deposition they can't
Get enough of a weird world we live in where are fancy like holyshit a deposition yet
Watch out it's
Like a big I don't know why but
Fantastic we are joint
Today to talk about this a little bit that we've had the other counsel
For the plane
On Mark Bankston couple of times talking about these your deposition
We got the other counsel
Indicates Bill Ogden joining us thank you so much
Bill how are you today
Longtime listener first-time caller
Big fan of what is now probably the most listened
Legal podcast
So
Thanks for having me guys
Opening arguments might have a
Point though it Matt is that we screwed up by putting our podcast in the comedy and news sections at iTune 100
Should have chosen something else that we could be like at the top where the number one law
Wandering wandering vagabond
John Reza podcast
Most versatile we are not the best point
Guard not the best
Center but we're an all-around
Sixth Man of the Year or bam adebayo that's how we do it here shrimp
Well I don't know if I
My only reference talk to you a little bit
Before we get to this episode cuz we're listening to to deposition
That you actually
We're in charge of and we're handling and then
What would it I'm presenting
Pretty much as an interrogation by the lawyer will take a deposition
Did you ever
You took a
I did I did
Behind my friend I was thinking about this
I went to Austin I met you a mark
It came along
To the Alex
Daria tips
Both of those Mark was take
And I saw his
Style
Kind of like a boar like a jocular kind of
Style there's a little bit of a friendship thing and some playing around
Watch these depositions that I realize like I would be
So much more scared
Albion cross the table
But absolutely but he will make you like it
Well he does
Either questions that you asked like it and knowing that I just see like
Definitely
In these cases I've told
Especially ones that
Or if we have
Eyewitness code A1 and I'm I'm taking I'm doing okay
Day-to-day
I'll tell the witness like
I'm just letting you know now
Mr. Bankston
Wasn't very pleasant yesterday and he's the nice one
Straight up with Helen
Training day style Denzel Washington
You know I didn't pay
It's coming just
If you got to do something you might want to hydrate
Do we have
We have these two depositions here today we have
Kit Daniels deposition and a known Troy deposition
And
Did things kind of
Weird about this is Weezer from
Different case
Owens case
Owen was
It deposition was
For the hesi
I swear he went on air and said what he said about Neil sign in
Indeed.com
Mnk
What's the
Person at Infowars that wrote the article that started all of this
He wrote the article about Marcel
Fontaine
Bridgewater Massachusetts
They pinned his photo and said this is the $4 parking Heist
Shooter
Just massacred
So that case
For the case was filed first in from
The media attention that we have no idea
It's coming
From all of that we got contacted by this
The chronological order of how this all came
That is that is kind of remarkable I can't imagine being kit Daniels
NM like recognizing exactly what
A dumb f****** you made this down all of it for
He's very
Critical at least
Answer my question very critical of himself
This point I was like yeah
Greeley
Some would say it was a bit unprofessional
But you said to I just
What's a 1
This is bad
Call minhwan would be like
Broken sentences and skeleton on fire as you write them
Actually used white van
On a white background Teresa to play piece of paper I guess would be a one for him
That's not good that's not going to trigger a Litany of
Litigation against his comfort
But hey I guess that's
Better than this
That's so wild though to think about like this just kind of domino effect you had to like
Get Daniels wrote this article and that led to Marcel Fontaine being defamed and
Starting this trial you guys representing Sandy Hook folks
But even like the further back
Because the of the Fontaine stuff was based on him reporting on like
Troll s*** from 4chan
So whoever posted that actually is responsible for taking down that way
You can't you can't just go back you got to go keep going forward because
Then it triggered these lawsuits and here I am talking to you
So here I am congratulating Jordan I believe you just got married
Yes I did
Regions Bank hit Daniels
Congratulations if it wasn't for
This all makes sense now
What's the problem with us just watching knowing
Yeah this is getting
The only the only way this could be better is if it was kit Daniels first day
That would be the greatest moment like the very first thing he wrote
On his first day was this
Yeah that be beautiful importantly made many errors prior
What are the things that kind of shook me a little bit was when I was watching that deposition
Daniel seems a little bit older than I
I kind of yesterday I think he's 37
Which I was kind of caught up
Wait wait on 32nd
But you also
34 years
I have
Really f***** up my life
Both work backwards I'm better than
Sure I wasn't in that.
Keeping score here but I don't think I don't think it's closed
I'd always pictured him as kind of like a
Maybe mid-to-late twenties guy
Cuz he
It has like a sort of a youthful
Naivete to him in the times that I've seen him on video on Infowars before
But I'm seeing him in that room there was a
You know obviously longer face
And I've been
Certainly
Not having fun baby that ages feel that way probably I will say this you can be a certain person
Life or in your professional career and whatnot but
When you're walking the deposition
You asked where where do I sit
It kind of takes a right-hand it's like oh my God
What am I doing
Everybody else
Cuz there's not your
Looking right at a giant
Directly on you
And you got lawyers to Spitfire in question
Objection you don't know what's going on but you know you
Don't want to answer that really hard
Right
And like you have
Lawyers who probably poorly
Prepared you certainly number of
Lawyers probably didn't tell people exactly like
Here's what it means to be on the road
Corporate representative does that actually leads us to another
This is very important
And that is that
Ubill where the person
Who took
Rob dues legendary Depp
So
My rollator
Confirm
When I came in I started looking yet
And
When I can't will actually I work there for a year-and-a-half
During lost
I started looking around to see
What can I master
That can bring value to
The Firm instruction dorks
Yes that's actually what I do it so 30 B6
What we call it
Until I just kind of Master
Meticulously going through topics and making
Person just look
Really unprepared
In with these topics it was
Hard because
There's just no way
There's so many false
Claims in
Bulshit being thrown around
That no one could know
Get a grip
Like sincerely answering a lot of those questions would just kind of reveal more questions of the
The Neptune unpreparedness
Probably
Oh yeah answering them it's worse than not
At this point just and if they knew the answer
That would be worse than not being prepared to be extension.
Looks banging Chester whatever it is
I learned one thing
Bobby forward
What kind of what kind of preparation did you or I suppose I mean I assume that this type of
Deposition is a little bit different from the ones that maybe your
Used to in a regular non Infowars setting
Did you do like more preparation for this or
Oh I'm pretty prepared on every case that for this one
Specifically
When
When Mark came into the case he came to me because
I've been watching
And not as necessarily is a fan Morris
Entertainment
It's alright he and I had conversation
Yo in the past about it he's okay you want to
You want to do this with you
No questions asked
And so my first job I made partner I think
During this case
2 years ago
My first task
Here's two hundred hours worth of video
I need you to watch it and
Document everything that goes on
It's too late
Actually going through it and
Two or three or four Days Inn
And
Mark him in my office and he was like
What are you looking at and I was like hey
What disculpa Tonkin
Because it the way it happened
Firing so much information from so many directions
It really did, start mess with my head I haven't stopped yet take a step away
I took like two days off and I went back into
Give me to take a couple days off while back
I gave you my son
Yeah it was definitely
Experience and marcasite
Discontinued
You've been pranked
It really is like the
Stylistics
Approach that they use agile
Different
Topix completely that aren't related
They're just getting thrown in your face
Like you know
Somebody tossing a bucket of hot dogs into a
In your face I'll just hitting a different areas
You can't
The digestive
Awesome so instead you just
Kind of cheap
Yeah specially if it's like the topic is something scary
The kind of overrides your ability to keep track of like
08 you just jumped from 80 to H what is going on here and then dates back to be in an hour
What's going on
So I did all that I got
From there
I had a pretty good grasp on
Mark
Is
Just so we're clear marks
Hundred percent the smart
The brain
I guess I
Default to the looks but you know Mike
7online
Dixon, California
The aggressive one and
I don't like taking zoomed in
Winter like covid made does the thing
A defense attorney
Defense attorney asked me one time
Why don't you like Takis
Because I've never lied to you
And he just looked at me like
I'm not saying anything else I'm just saying
Yeah I'm definitely
The bully of the group I guess like when somebody needs to know what a bully needs to get
Humbled I guess I'm the person that
And takes care of that Mark Martin do it and he doesn't in a in a very articulate way
And he's smart enough to maneuver you into it you don't even know you're hurting you
Say your answer
Where I'm just asking it in a way that
Possible for you to Ann
Destroyer Destroyer
Right right
The Doublemint I'm not the knot
Right exactly
Probably too like that being in the room
Being in person is supposed over resume like
There's so many of those other aspects like what you mentioned of like you're sitting at the head of this table
You have that camera in front of you and other people are in the room
Like I'm a janitor
Completely different vibe
It really is there's an intense
Driving because
You know I have no problem just staring someone down
Contact
It's awkward Exchange
They know they're like what do I do
Make a noise
Fill that void
This is describing like the Errol Morris philosophy of like filmmaking
You know to make people stare at a camera eventually they'll say something
Exactly
Mike
Techniques of kind of
So Westmoreland County Fair started our firm when they were like
And they were
Roll the dice they took all the risk
Classic Warriors and so many years
So many years
Markwest College
David at the
It so I came in and I had the benefit of one riding their code
I didn't have to sweat a line of credit it whether or not I can pay him for you but they did all the hard work
Until I got the benefit of learning under them in
I just
Cook
Certain aspects from each of the lawyers
Could
Stylistics
Which of which of those other partners
Taught you about snack
Preparation
So
That's actually Westfall not necessarily actually probably been pissed
Deposition
Making making people uncomfortable
When you're asking
Uncomfortable questions
Makes them just wanted to end
So they give you whatever they they know what you
And if they're uncomfortable they're just going to give it rather than
Playing this line of things
Ask a question again I don't understand what you're asking did that kind of thing
Stop at Buc-ee's
Famous gas stations cycle Walmart
Giant bag of
Gummy worm
It's like during the Depo
Hold it up to the light
Beat It
And like I use it as a n
And then
There
Will cannabis gummy bear not down on them
The one thing that was bad with
Southern accent
Set alarm
I actually stole that from
There's a real famous
Slayer text
Married
And he would take a paperclip
Wilder the other side was doing their opening statements
And he would slowly make straighten it all the way up
Innocent back we could smoke indoors
Cigs inside
But he would take a straight paper clip and then you would slide it down
Need the cigarette into light it
And then he would smoke it in the
The Ashwood
Until the jury would just stare at that instead of paying attention
To the other side's opening statement because they're waiting for this long cigarette Ash to stop and it doesn't
You know.
It's kind of cool
To do and so I I kind of bets that's where it started and then I
Incorporated
I feel like that that cigarette trick
That's like sleight of hand
Yeah with people's attention where is like
The Gummy Bears Just aggressive
Like that
Just like
It's menacing
I'm so comfortable that I'm going to
Like this is not uncomfortable for me
It would be very threatening
I mean it's it's funny
Now but if if I was in a room with you while you were doing that God I would just call you a prick non-stop like it wouldn't
The answer a question I just feel like could you get this brick to stop eating me f****** worm imagine a scenario where you can't do that
Well then I'm in trouble right
Cheney snackin there's 2 things 1
You thinking how disrespectful
God I wish you'd give me one
And so either way
It's not good
I can you ask for a gummy worm or is that against the law I think you're probably be rawsome July
Oh no that would be best case scenario
Because if they ask me for a gummy worm
I only brought enough for one knowing it's a message for god sakes just
To let the air out of a b
I'm always looking for later
Everybody's most people
The awkwardness
And I'm there to create it
Livin it so that when someone gets awkward you learn a lot
When your meeting you can get a good read on somebody
I try to make people uncomfortable very quickly in a Depo
In a bad way just
To put them on their toes
See how they react so that I can then
What's my questions into amor
Impact
You're like what if jigsaw was a lawyer
Exactly what if jigsaw
Didn't
Hey you let you hang yourself to I mean it's the same basic principle
And I like the idea of it does start with would you like to play a game
Be
I've been watching
Oh watch me on these lives at this March or this protest and I'm thinking myself
He's just
Going and finding
The best clips
She's got nobody spoken so soon as
Hustling
Did heslin case came in I called dibs on
From 44 years ago
Enmark was like
10%
Are roughly the same age
I want him to
Spiel
What other people feel like when
She doesn't
Urge to bully the bully
Yeah exactly exactly like a show you how it's
When you meet your match here
And the best part was
I found a video
The night before of him at the woman's March
March in DC and he was wearing Trump Garden
In a lot of people were
Saying like oh what it how could you be out here wearing a
Trump scarf
It's important that you support women
Women that were sexually traffic at the exit Highway
Wish I was
I can get by
And then they're like yeah but y'all
Name one
If Trump is so bad maybe one woman's name as an accuser and these people
And
And he's like yeah so you can't even name one name
So you're not even informed
Until I heard that
Can you name
Do you know the name of
Do you know can you name one
You can't
Play the clip of him doing it other people
And at the end
It was so unnecessary
You see my question
You're not there and he just looks at me on the record
I tip my hat to you I'm out
At least you understand
What was happen
Like he knew
Rail
That's awareness inside the room you know like you're being able to to get that place
British excuse me I believe I have been hoisted
These people that he's talking to in that video that you found
What if they
Hosted a show where they complained about Trump accusers
I still couldn't name
You know that's good
That's even more sensitive
What makes your example even more egregious
Yeah so he
I will say this
I walked into Owens Depo
Thinking he was a bad guy
And
I could see in his face the more we talk about what happened and how we got here and how
Drawing all the s*** was that
He said
He was having a
Epiphany
Anger
Not towards us or towards
Point towards his staff
Company
And at the end when I said you know it's mr. hassling
Or Miss Lewis was in the room right now what would you say and he was remorseful
He was sorry he was the only one
He walked out of there
It's not fair
But I really do appreciate you doing what you did
And I say what he did so he walked away from that
I get his position
Easter
What you supposed to do
No it make a car wash wood
I'm not sure
Car wash
In Liberal Austin Woodhall
Or whatever his real first name is it maybe
I don't know
Yeah you can bring your little differently life somewhere in Nebraska
Crepe Place worm
Omaha nice during like
Oh I wouldn't let him in a city he's got to be very quiet by himself small-town Nebraska
He's from my home state of Missouri
And so like
Some people do I exit Missouri but like what I'm saying
People from their likes
That's funny you brought that up
Why do we call it Germany
When people from Germany called Deutschland
Anybody and everybody
Yeah that's that's actually kind of a bone of contention
The people in Missouri there's the Missouri people and then
Missouri.
It's I mean
You know I mean it is ironic but yes that was
Divided over this
But yeah either way like Owens
He walked out of there he was
Only Witness
Walk out besides Maybe
That was actually
And I don't know what they're sorry because
Were they were just that was the first time anybody actually given them all
Cuz there was a lot of stuff most of them had no idea like wait what
Well I just leave more inclined to agree with that about cat
Watching his deposition
I do think there's a lot keeping
Many things that will get into over the course of the episode
He shockingly doesn't know about
I want to take nose a bit more
I have is like
Yeah he may not have another choice
But if he recognized like it's on record
Sicknesses how bad this stuff is
But he's involved in
And continues to do it's worse you watch his show now he's doing the same
Southlake
He's just very safe he's just making sure nobody's names and nobody's I'm not identifying groups he's safe
With what he does in
He is a True Believer to an extent on that but when
He talked about Sandy
And it just happened to be the one time
Within the statue limitation
Brought them in
He did it I think somebody was just like
A new kid say that
Since then he was on a bunch of other
But
At the time I I don't fault
Best early for that
And watching a show I did not
Seems like you'd be more brash
But you did
In the heat on Aries
You don't
Interviews in olives
Elvis videos
He is very brash
But when he gets into serious moment
East yummy he's just
Yeah but what you're describing about him
And you wanted to hate him more the end of the the deposition was definitely
How I felt about Paul Joseph Watson
Deposition
He saw it
He saw the writing on
No problem
Stop doing what the
Walking we doing this is
This is horrible for all of us
It's going to give us this reputation
And you can see from that email
He split
And he starts doing his own thing because he's doesn't you know
He's not going down with that s***
Well I mean he has his his
Speed in both
Sort of boats as it were you know like
He has his own thing as much as he's doing like his own YouTube channel
I like it's kind of separate but he's also still hosting Infowars sometimes
And I still very closely connected
Do you still like the
Main editor of the site
And what have you he will I will say this
He
He does have some sort of moral compass
He knows
Right and wrong
Which not weird to say about me
Adults
Know what I mean but you have to kind of be a psychopath to work at Infowars so it doesn't make sense
Right and wrong would be a rare ability
It's it's
Funny because you know as much as they're like oh we're not sheep we don't
Just follow what
Dr. fauci says
When that boy poursuite kit for swinging
Such
It right now
At work I'm sure
Career-wise
Because he was like
I'm like why did you
Here he's like
Alex Jones
Okay and I was like
And then
In what you know
If I were called there's a couple times you're like
Alex is not going to like that answer
You said it you got to live
Ynw
He is not going to like that
He said something way different
And then you can see their face like
There's something so awful about like being in a room
Being questioned by
Somebody who has like
Start of the freedom or whatever to just like
The Trap has been set you have stepped in it and then you were just like
That was a trap
Yeah cuz I don't like
I knew that
I'm setting it up they have no idea then they say it and sometimes
He doesn't even know he's stuck
Estep's ametis just dangling and I'm right here
Listen to trap music
What attracts I'm Amazed
Whenever we watched all these depositions I am just shocked that these people aren't constantly going like
Over and over and over again where afterwards they go
But it's just
It's a rape they're stepping on the same rake over and over and over again
Same
Exactly
It's definitely
Regardless of who the lawyer is
Hostage
Job I don't I don't think
Preppies the problem
Couldn't help some of these Infowars people
That's it
Definitely a tall order to try and say oh yeah
Full day full day of prep is on
Robert Barnes
In their corner
It doesn't get much better
Yeah heat so I was the
One that kind of broke
Second
No the first
Rob do Depo
Where he just goes on man
You know
What I'm asking for start unreasonable you just blew is when I knew he had a few
It's A1C did I look at it
Always I could medicine
I'm not even going to comment
On the reef
And I just left it there you could
And I knew that
Attack with like a interview with Stefan molyneux about that
It kind of
Gave Mark and I
He brought us back to our roots and showed us like this is why we do this
This is this
We called a hobby case
We brought it on because the money doesn't we don't
And all sorts of
Civil rights cases
Big industrial accidents in the auto defects we we made money
So each lawyer brings on a case
At any given time
That they want to do for the right reasons and that's why we bought this one
And that's why I give all the credit
Because they have never told us no
And I've never said you know I didn't watch your spending or anything or just like
If you guys need help let us know I love you
Subway
That's when we brought this in
We start taking the Depo
It wasn't worth it was like we're looking like I'm not trapping
Thoroughly
Invested in
And being as prepared as I can
Because I just we just wanted to destroy this
Imagine that after you start doing these depositions
You start to see the level of sort of
You could call it unpreparedness or disrespect that's being shown by
These
Defendants in like that's got to
Got2b invigorating
In some ways or at least free
It is mainly because it happened
In all case
Not like this though right
First of all
We've never everybody always
It's not uncommon to do a motion for sanctions
It's not uncommon to
Seeking default cuz this is so egregious
Until now
In these cases
These cases have just they literally have kind of
They kind of screwed me moving
Because no matter I'm not going to be so hard on
My head
I'm going to say
Wayward
You're no Barnes so well
You were wrong
But you're not that
Because
When I
First started
I had I was the young guy trying to chip on my shoulder and I was just like let's go I'm about to start a bunch of forest fires
Even if it's unnecessary I'm here
Star Wars
You were 20
Some of us grow some of us
And
And then I got older and I start with
A little bit
Hey you don't have to be this aggressive
And all that and then I got to this case
Here we go
I forgot what this.
Yeah you're not y'all are hungry I was back whenever I was a stand-up
You know if you had a run of really bad shows and you just weren't doing well you just couldn't
You just kept sucking
There were a couple of rooms that are that were notoriously
Easy to get really big laughs from
And that's where you would go to like
Reinvigorate yourself you know that like I yeah I am funny that kind of
If I can make it it really does feel like this is where you're at you know like all these real cases
F*** you hard
You know I got to fight the end this I just get to come in and f******
Beat up on bounce to children
Is suing Alex Jones are being the plaintiff's attorney for Alex Jones is like going to the
What's the name of a
Airbag.
And I did
15 GB
Document sent over to my office
There's nothing exciting
Reagan 15 instrumental words on lights
Where do we where do we start
I really hope there's no child for
Slight
What's child pronography in some of their discovery
Connecticut
But it was just
The stuff
Beat the documents they do have
Are just
We only get about
15% of
The craziness that is
Is given to them or that they send to each other
A lot of stuff doesn't come out until we get to
Jesus
Yes
It is fascinating to see how
The inner workings of something like the
Yeah one of the things that really stuck out to me from the two depositions whenever last time was
Comprehensive background check on Leonard Posner that was just weirdly
In their files
Like that's okay don't know where it came from it just still fell out of your hair that way
Yeah that that was real
Dad and them posting
You know
But our Network
PO box that's the stuff that pisses
That's why we like okay
I'm not in any way throwing to
You can pretend to be nice and
I'm sorry that Danny got got it that was the initial
Started getting into it it was just
I'm going to enjoy what I'm
Nice guy
But it's now when I'm punching the time card on my to be an a******
Walking to work
Subway
Break room
In-N-Out
Mark and I are fully invest in this case
We would sometimes lose
Sight of you know because we're so focused on doing what we're doing and worth we are enjoying
Sit down together for a meeting and talk about what we're doing next
Realized
Going to be a very emotional
Trial and it's going to be a very
You know there's not
And so we have not invited
Right yeah because you
There will be
It is and
Enso
The client
They are some of the bravest people I've ever met
And and Mark Marcus extremely Closer Closer with all of them
I started off as kind of the Workhorse that was behind the sea
She's doing all the stuff
Watch out garbage
Videos
And it's so many it's so many more than you
When I say 2:00 video
It's 2:00
What should be 1,000
Because everything so scattered out and
At least like a third of it is commercials
Commercials
Elizabeth Williamson is a writer to your timezone
She contact us and that I wanted can I fly down and just follow y'all around 4
Sure yeah New York Times you can do that
What we didn't say what we didn't notice we have zero media
Enso step one was like let's go to El Tiempo
That's where
And I don't know if you actually
Strong margarita
Reporter
All the stuff you're not supposed to say to the media
I realized it about it
Our end
And I'm like
If this is going to turn into a hit piece I just want you to know
You have full authority to lie and embellished
If it's going to be bad
I just want you to know cuz I realized a lot of stuff
No one said off-the-record at all guys and like everyone
You guys are fine
But she
Bartender should really
Do that for you
Like to say this is off the Record
Yeah there's everyone's a bartender should have like a a journalist credential that they have to check and then
Do the whole thing I like it I'm going to open a bar call author
But she she just published a book a couple weeks ago
And in that She interviewed me, right when I was really digging into the video
And I should say what are you getting out of it not just watched when I was like honestly I'm really I'm really into these
Combat wipes
Delta commercial Medical Center
What are they going outside
I mean if you break it down it's just baby wipes for bunch of middle-aged
Caucasian men better camping out in the woods with some friends calling themselves
If she put it in the book
Niacin
So fresh down there when you're with all your militia
With the intro of
Rest my life
I could have been more professional in
With that watching all those videos and having that like
You said you watched Alex
From when you were like in college
We going to look at entertainment 911 JF
Hey
You know
Human hybrid amphibians
You're real
It was
Everywhere
My Generation go
Facebook came to my college my freshman year
Eating you
Email address to have Facebook
W w Facebook I will never forget we are
I promised we would never forget that
And so
Technological era of news and information and all that was
As I was coming of age and so
Alex Jones I would see differ
Articles
Washington
Exactly
And I bet it was entertainment and then
Closer to closer we got to 2000
Election
Is when he decide Sandy Hook
He took an extreme
Story probably the most egregious extreme story
Mylifetime
And then he made it even more
Brighton
From there the clothes we got
2016 he realized
Takikos political Heat
And he did
The heat went when he went right
Kids luggage
And
I mean for instance I keep
I mean
I what I said wasn't
Right
Rap.
I'll have one of those
Yeah
Political before it was just that he loved Ron Paul who is never going to win
The doctor
Yeah he's the most notorious OBGYN on the planet
And the only OBGYN I think who tried to take over an island nation
Everybody has their version of events right
He was use libertarian in heat I mean
He was not a fan of George Bush
Senior or Junior
Which is funny because
George Bush became Governor by saying yes that person over there
Conservative I'm bored
In-N-Outs Jones
Exploded
Did I experience like
Really
Feel different though like watching it and paying attention versus watching it for entertainment
Like the content because you cuz I'm not watching
I'm not really watching
The continent as much as
I'm breaking down
The stylist
The style of how he's doing it how he's going into these in and planning them and how he
Transition you notice all that now
And you realize it's
It was a way
That no one had really match
Astrid until
Rapid fire things that someone where you can ask question because there's so much coming at you and there's so many
Questions to ask
You just don't have time
Or you forget about something that he said 5 minutes ago because you're now talking about some
Yeah there's a there's a craft
To it that I'm not even positive
Entirely conscious of what he
He's doing
But it is
There is something today really just kind of a debate text
Take like overwhelming the person that you're talking to with like
Too much stopping and hoping they get flustered
But yeah
Open till like
Sandy Hook an avid listener
I'm his and
Then this happened
Yeah well if you say not too much
It's got its got to make you re-evaluate whether or not
Good idea to believe Alex about to Oklahoma City
And stuff like that
You're on the wrong address
Kent and Owen like
Tell me one story
But y'all gotten right
Yeah
Okay anything in the last 20 years
Owen was on the ground at the Gulf of negative
8 years old
I will say this they did they they called Epstein early
Well
The globalist for sex traffic
But they are called jussie Smollett
Boris if you're just a racist all
All the time
Then yes
You're going to call Jessie Smollett
But that's
The way I like to say it is even in a pitch-black room
And you're throwing darts
Hit the target
This literally what they do is they just
Everything's okay
Conspiracy
Everything Is Not What It Seems until one time
And you know
I'll give you that however they got their those were things that they
Didn't totally end up with something it was wrong and eyesight
That's the bar
Public figure
Yeah that's with a kit Daniels when it just like name something
You didn't get Ross
Emily just like
Ava keeps going
Painful
The first time it happened Rob do is doing
Name one and he just sitting there and I was like
This is getting
Well I don't want to say under oath something we got right just in case
Underoath
Bear hole
Motto
And floss music
You know if we
We got stories
Please don't make me
Will Alex just the other day was saying that once it gets to the trial for the Sandy Hook case
He's going to reveal and expose how all the people are making money on Sandy Hook
And all this
So I'm excited for a number
First of all when we went
Media
Started
Immediately on the show with Hillary Clinton and George Soros
And the data that was said we were all at lunch
I looked at my
My phone and I saw somebody
And I was like this and I looked at the table
Which one of you f****** has all the money missing Sharon
Where's the Soros check cuz I haven't
Everyone's phones on the table who has a text from Hilary Foods
Who's holding out
It's also fun
Hearing with us
And heister
Something
Play by the defense
Soros
Accusation a pronoun
I just want you I just want for the record
Just want everyone to know
I picked up so I don't want anyone getting credit
Except me I am
Any power behind us
Well I'm glad I'm glad we're able to clear up lien on Soros
Connection
Unless unless marks keistering a bunch of checks that he hadn't told anybody about it we have not received
We did start receiving money
And cards of support at the
Beginning and everyone so I will still get one
And people just started sending cash in and stuff
To us sahay this treatment help with the legal car
And
Barking Lot
Donated
Dioner Network he's like oh that's perfect
Anytime somebody to email
To the two people that reached out to her email or call him
Appreciate it
What just if you want to donate donate to the honor Network cuz they
Their Network at Target
Internet misinformation
Probably makes you look more like you're taking Soros money
Bright hey I will do anything in my power to look more suspicious
All right when we come out when your Optics are giving money away clearly that means that Soros is gay
Giving you that money to give away obviously otherwise you wouldn't be able to give that money away
Makes me want to buy one of those little earpieces
The little of stretchy cord that like the secret service where I want to look at him and then
Start talking into my cough
It'd be great if in a deposition you had an earpiece
But it was connected to a gummy worm
Right right
And a lit cigarette
Everybody's looking at me like hey that's illegal now
Is this lawyer crazy
Also we should probably wrap this up before too long I think we're about an hour or so weak but
There's anything else that you wanted to cover about the deposition
Anyting
But like would be a good
Introductory note
Cuz we're going to get into it after her after we talked
Sure so I would say with the Owen.
I Walked Outta.
Thinking that was
Way better than
Berry II
Kenu
The position he was in and he was
One of the few that didn't even
At one point, through all the papers the answer
Make this
Only makes more money than
Yeah
Their payroll is out of control based on the depositions that I've heard
Yeah so
And then
Early on I realized
I'm not dealing with the top
Pizza
Key
But he is a he's the type of person that
Doesn't know
Then to Bolivar
And so
I use that again
And I would
He would say a
What is that mean
And then he'd give me the definition of
Okay
What's now apply that
That was probably the highlight
It's when I said Owen
Is Infowars mean
Absolutely not okay what is mainstream media
You know they have
Been around for a little while have a reputation
Bay
Have corporate advertising
Alright what about bright
He's like no I wouldn't
And then I realized as soon as I say that
Before they were bi platform
All of these things
Tobacconist
He's like
What about this
I bet that's not just the whole listing of my okay with what's up with us
Chris Brown
Ben
At one point
I got him
I asked one
Let's just agree
You don't even know
Yeah.
Best case scenario for Myanmar sitting there
When I'm going out
Making sure that run
After Time by the time one of us gets done with the note in hands
Question
We've already verbatim said
We can read each other's mind so big we be doing this
And
Enso
Mark starts writing and then when she comes out.
He just kind of has a short job
I don't know
A Marxist
It was loud enough to where everyone in the room
But he didn't get caught on the wreck
There's one other time that that if you listen closely you can
And
It's during on cell phone I was like yeah I was live on here
Somebody who I don't remember
Handed me these documents that we already got the clips ready to go run
And
And I'm like so you just
Hope it is
Somebody who conveys a message but someone else has control
Your live on here
Somebody can't do story you don't know what
They have control
Right
And then you can bathe
Exactly
So you're a puppy
Yeah
I am a puppet
But
Marcos
Ron Burgundy
You can hear it
I
Rock all these Depots regardless
Questioning the other person is literally they're just being popped
Watching in Triangle today
But
But yeah that's
Ron Burgundy
And he wasn't trying to be
Disruptive or anything you just had come to him
He said it very quietly in my ear
I just look at it
That's a little loud buddy
Does no mainstream media is
And I'm a puppet
And Daniel's price
And rightly so
So that's
Hard to argue with that
How's the baby
That's the brief
We'll get into a couple hours breakdown of the sea
Or whatever
Oh Bill thank you so much for joining us
As a policy wonk I was honored to be asked to appear on the show
And I love what you guys do
Let means a lot and it was it was great to meet you down in Austin I hope
I'm a I'm a make the trip before the trial soaps
To see you again next month
Absolutely
Take care guys
And congratulations on the
Congratulations
Take in
Along
Listening to idiots
That's the plan so I decided that we're going to start with the kit Daniels deposition cuz I think
I think we can all agree that if this is the lineup of 2012 headliner
But it's just the reality
Position of February 17th of this year
Do with the Parkland shooter misidentification they put in an Infowars article
Shooter as Marcel Fontaine who is now suing
Probably more famous of a figure in that the Sandy Hook litigation is probably more price
Primary in people's minds
My position is probably more revealing than many of the other Zoe's cover
Maybe not more than Daria but it's up there and most of what we revealed through dark areas was the cheese
I'm weird out psycho music during his deposition is it was
Nature comes from I'm sorry to say
Seems really dumb
But that sounds harsh now but I sure you as we go through this that assessment I think is going to seem very fair
He doesn't seem to know or understand much and because of that he ends up getting himself into really bizarre places well
I'll being questioned under oath
Sometimes this dumbness intersects with the level of naivete in those places
Doesn't seem like he realizes some of the stuff he's revealing about the inner workings of Infowars which is
Wild
A lot of that stuff may not be legally problematic but it's definitely damning in the context of our show and what we cover
There's another aspect of this too and it's something that bill kind of touchdown Which is that you kind of want to end up
Liking kit a little bit
He doesn't seem like such a bad guy a lot of the time and it's clear lack of understanding about basic concept
It triggers a certain amount of pity in the viewer
The Listener
Those feelings are fairly complicated and waited along with a clear awareness that he's been employed Infowars for like
He doesn't deserve the benefit of any doubts
It really makes a bizarre mix of of of an experience
Definitely
Something that I found more interesting than I expected it to be for someone who is essentially
Boo Radley if you will
He's not a franchise he's a role player
I get what you mean
Easy you feel complicated things about Boo Radley
I think there's a lot to a lot to dig here so let's let's just Jump Right In
And we learn write the beginning a lot of preliminary conversation and I need deposition
Talking about past employment how long have you worked today
I'm working to jump in where we learn about Kate Daniels salary okay
From
May of 2030
14 to the summer 2018
Associate editor
Broccoli
And then after that
Promoted
Something like that
When you say something
We don't really have
A culture at Infowars of
Job title
What is the culture in 40
Well what I mean as far as like
Some companies you would have liked
Oh here's your new job title maybe it's in writing
It hasn't necessarily been the case compared my other
The other
When you became managing editor the summer of 2018
Did you receive a raise
No
How much do
Anywhere from 75 to $90,000
It's
Based on the Range SM
Owatonna salary
It is a salary position I think 75
My base salary
Can go up tonight eBay song
Performance
75,000 is high but I think compared to the other salaries we've heard from people
Who arranged that I find acceptable
Right
Wolf
Still bums me out but you know what you brought me out if somebody who supports workers is that he got a raise
Possibilities
Stout one major issue that I almost
Like in the back of my my no will come up
Almost constantly
Chip Daniels giving answers that he does not realize our begging Quest
You know that like
That's not really the culture we have here at Infowars
The question what the f*** is the cultured Infowars
Helicopter
Yeah I think you're right though he does open doors with with answers that
Is kind of fun because I think that bill as a person holding a deposition
Is
The sort whose like I'll walk through that door that leads to some pretty
Exchanges
It's okay it makes $75,000 a year in possibility of 90
Philz Coffee
Gets bonuses okay
Sherbrooke I mean who wouldn't put that way
Did you receive a bonus into
Unless your credit on a 2 years ago yes I did
Do you remember what that
That was probably a prox
For the year
12 to 13000
Seems like the company
Was doing
The performance the company was better in 2020 than
Something like that
What about 2,000
Does Proxima
+ 80
It's been awhile since I've looked at my double
But if we wanted to find that information out of would be in there.
Yes
Have you ever had a year where you did not receive a bonus
I don't believe so
Are you aware that Free Speech systems is rough
As they stayed in the swamp
Over 50 million dollars
No I wasn't aware that
Do you think people should be getting bonuses
If that's the night
Real.
I want to be the person to
Make that judgment
If you were running
Company
Was that indebted
When you be giving bonuses
Possibly not
Earnest
All the people that I've heard opposed the only person I don't feel his salary
The rest of these people are outrageous hacks and make way too much and don't get me wrong kid is a hack to but he's making under 6
Figures
I can see an argument for someone like him being worth a decent salary because honestly without the people who run the site and managed
The articles I go up there be no way the show could exist
Alex can't curate that shoot himself and if you were forced to report on articles of that tailor-made headlines room to yell about
He sure would suffer from that
People who write the articles on who repost other outlets articles with new headlines are really the backbone of what makes Alex's show function
And with Paul Joseph Watson doing a lot less that heavy lifting in the past few years
Someone like it probably does have real value
Compare with someone like him bring to the table to someone like Owen or Harrison night think you would rather have kid around
Just about any day
You know I don't like that he's paid as much as he is but
Relatively speaking I think he needs to unionize in order to get a better contract for himself because there's no
David Harrison Smith should be making that much more than him pay Owen like 15 an hour
Respectable and even though I'm philosophically opposed to them I would offer Harrison it wouldn't give him anything
Passing unpaid internship
The thing that I find really interesting about this clip and so many other moments in this deposition is the clear information based
Power imbalance between the lawyer and the person being deposed
No idea that Infowars is deeply in debt
Later Owen is going to talk about how he has no idea what archives are databases the company keeps heading no one told him that he received
The court order for Discovery in this case
This is because employers is a deeply compartmentalised workplace
Alex keeps so much information from people who work there you can see hook me completely caught off guard to hear these kind of
Lesions in a deposition setting
And that's for this that I'm not really sure how much of this is just normal for a business
But it seems pretty high
So I can see him being really deep in the soup but I don't know what the full picture of this is
Until until more information comes out
Taken at face value it's obviously surprise into kid and it sounds bad
I mean it might be just a quibble with Bill is just like you know
I think the employee should be treated regardless of whether or not the owners of the company have
50 million dollars a day
Song saying I think
I think in an Ideal World.
Maybe a business can't function 50 million dollars
But something like Alex there is something of the realpolitik to it yes so
Chip is asked about like
This the Dynamics of how they get article gets Papa
You did you publish this yourself
Right you were able to hit the button and Publishing
Exhibit one
Do you recognize it
Piloswine
This is a
Rolling update article I
Wrote in February 14th 2018
Regarding the breaking news
On the
Florida shooting
When you say the Florida shooting you mean the Parkland
Yes
Florida high school shooting PS
Who published the song
I did
Did anybody help you
No
When you write a story in publishing you have the ability to upload it to the website you're on your own
Who all has that capability
The writers that I just mentioned except Dan Lyman usually
Submitted stories for one of the
Staff writers
Publish for him
The managing editor have to put eyes on every story that goes up
That is my practice
Is that a requirement
It's not necessarily requirement bed something I do in practice
Have you always
No
Why not
It just kind of something that
After all these lawsuits and litigation I kind of
Decided for myself that that was something I needed to do them
I think most people would hear this and just move along but I think it's nuts
This clip is probably the only time in any of these depositions that I've heard someone Express that in response to all of the lawsuit
And forwards is facing that they decided they needed to do a better job
Are you saying that you saw a problem took responsibility and then changed your
Xavier.
F****** blows my mind yeah that's really basic thing for normal people it's a super low bar to clear before
Employees that deserves a standing ovation
Since this point kit is not done a better job any articles that go up on the website are still totally full of b*******.
Yes he has the ability to recognize that he needs to do better
I'm going to assume that he has a problem with follow through or maybe as a boss that needs him to do a bad job to keep the company in
I applaud this impulse on a very basic level
Make a difference at all but
Impressive all the same I think you know what it is about what you do and not about what you say but
Doing something like saying this is so unreal for it if it were deployed
Sort of touching on a little bit of that naivete
It doesn't behoove you to say something like that it makes you look like a better or more rational
But it doesn't help you with the deposition and
Your best defense at Infowars is pretending you've never heard of Infowars what is
Morals
So there's a interesting
I'll say in this in this tire Exchange
Deposition
Pops back up it rears its head is are you a journalist
What is a journal what do you do right
Kit has called himself a journalist in the past
The dresses back here
When you publish an article who does the
If it's an article I'm doing typically of myself
What's your training
I took some
Classes in
First off I have used the word journalism
Maybe I'll dig nurse before I kind of see myself more as a social commentator
Since when
I think my whole
Has been more about social commentator
When did know when did you start
Characterizing yourself as a social comment
I think I started reading some Glenn Greenwald articles past couple months
And, made me realize the way he approaches
Who sings a lot different than the way I pray
No the kids been reading Greenwald to lately as opposed to the other points in his career
That's not true I think it probably learned about him from appearances on Tucker
That would make sense
Another interesting thing to point out is that all of these people say that they don't consider themselves that much of journalists and their Maureen
The social commentary
I don't think they really changes much but it's so consistent in these depositions
That I think there must have been a company meeting
Tell that opens up a box of of worms we don't want to hear I want to open so it we can rely on
Commentator is definitely a Barnes repandus
Feels like something that is useful to appear to have less responsibility
But I don't know if it helps
The intersection of Lake are you a journalist
I may have said I was in the past described as a weird who's on first
107 kit
That's the thing that Ivan
When I first started in Ford it is very
I understand your frustration
With the two
It's X get this
But after this maybe this will be
What's the difference between
You and I
I don't go out and talked
Torches like one-on-one
Like I'm not going to go get a news tip
Somebody and talk to him on Signal
Let me ask you this
Did you
Go out to a Bernie
Sanders protest and talk to me
Yes those are source
I don't know if I called sources I was just kind of give them an offer
Opportunity to vent their frustrations with
What was going on
You're interviewing people for information correct
What their opinions were
About the matter and then you took
What what you gathered from those sources of information and then you wrote articles are or made videos about
Let me finish my question
I just
Wow
Call boy
Information for people that he report it
I don't have a disability
Here's where here's where I feel like social commentator falls apart
Is that they feel like it's more honest than journalist
Right but it's still behind something like what they should just say is like
Guess I'm a professional assholes
I am addicted to people and their reaction is what we sell
Have you ever heard that Denis Leary song and then I feel like people would be like
That's probably about as accurate as you're going to get
Yeah I don't I feel like it would be tougher for a lot of Alex's audience to
Get excited about the professional a******
I think that might tarnish their image a little bit and I pay him for it
We'll come back up of course but
Did the questions on the table now is that if you're reporting a story is it more important to be accurate
First
Oregon a quick to get the story out do not answer this question
Or answer poorly
Ask mr. Shroyer the same question that I'm about to
Foreshadowing you believe
It's more important to get the news right
Or to be the first to report
I think it's both
Really yes
You don't think that veracity of the story
Far
Is far more important than
It being reported before anybody else
Know what I believe is that you also you want to be as accurate as
As you can be
But the same time you want to
Timely
I mean look
Text dumb
You don't want to ever say that
You can sacrifice for your obligation to like be correct
If it's in the interest of getting things off at something would say
The most important thing to us is the truth spy
Well obviously we've got to get it out time when there's a push-pull of Economics here but they wouldn't
I think that the reality is
Obviously there's an incentive
4 things to be immediate when there are new stories of course but is in no way
More important than that you're always suppose you can't get an accurate story you shouldn't run with it for the sake
Ecospeed I don't think that is the
What's what can't is describing
I think he's saying like I would say you get it as right as you can get it so long as you get it out the door
Oh wait no that means that I put timeliness way ahead of it
In discussing the speed thing
Reviews some stuff about how he views his responsibility to the audience and vice versa
That I find troubling
When you rode exhibit 1
Was there any rush to put this article out
Yes it was breaking
Story
Because nobody
Shooting just occurred within a couple hours and was in the public interest to kind of
Kind of figure out what the motivation
Michigan Works
Why did you why do you think the public needed to know the motivation to
That's how the new Cycle Works
Webster people unfortunately people don't want to know things to 34 days
Later
Okay
Infowars
They're not journalist
There's no race
Wouldn't they have plenty of time to make sure what they're
Providing the people is
Well unfortunately our audience kind of dictates
Our time frame
How so
Well they're just not going to be interest in a story that's 45 days old
Why do you think that
Because the public
Hands too if they have their eyes set on a prefix their story that happens that moment a time that's where their eyeballs are going
Look it's revealing a couple of really important things here
The first has to do with the relationship between the audience and the producers of the content
Kid believes that he has to rush out stories whether they're accurate or not because the audiences tomorrow about what happened
Today
But the reality is that he has this relationship backwards
Infowars is cultivated and trained this response from Their audience through the constant bombardment of flashy headlines and imminent
Predictions of
Terrorist nukes in
FEMA camps
Everything that's happening today is reported as cataclysmic because it needs to be to capture the maximum amount of attention
And if you want a chance at retaining any eyeball tomorrow the headlines better be just as flashy
Just a severe and probably not about the same thing you were yelling about the day before that's not going to be as exciting
Alex is trained isn't his audience partially because it's easier
I'm partially because he can't operate any other way
If Imports took the time to flesh out stories and do follow-up reporting
Just about everything they cover would be revealed to be b******* and they spend all their time on are correcting the s*** they said yesterday
Being interesting show I think it would be as it like this catch last week's
Work distracting the audience as soon as the next cycle hit
And yet you have a very strong incentive to not flush out stories anyway because they don't hold up to scrutiny
They did this to Their audience
But the Wake it understands it there just responding to Market pressure
This is kind of sad but I do think that I believe he believes it
No I I feel like one of the things that I'm running into here and the reason that
Bill specifically said he's a more sympathetic figure it's simply because it
Appears that he
Has been told all of these things and then just believe.
Yeah yeah there is
Yeah it's it's it's weird thing to run into because is a sincerity to it
That doesn't
It doesn't feel artificial
Cuz what it is he's never asked himself
A follow-up question the way ever had to he's never had to so bill is asking him questions that he's he's sitting there thinking like
I've never even thought of this question before this is kind of interesting as revealing is
We internal way that Infowars kind of understand that metaphor that I refer to as the Kiewit concrete thing
Propaganda is really only stick if you're able to implant them early
You need to have something happen and then provide the narrative for your audience to understand the event through
If you can succeed at that your audience will be more likely to evaluate any further things they hear about the event through the prism
Some of your conspiracy narrative
As opposed to looking at the details independently
There's a critical aspect of getting narratives to stick it is reflecting the a basic understanding of this but just from
The Producers site
Do you want water think that's what he's doing because it's inherently abusive to an audience and it's entirely dishonest
But this is that dynamic
When he says that the audience wouldn't be interested in old news what he's actually saying is that by the time stories a few days old
Kris already dried and whatever angle he's going to try and sell
It isn't going to stick
I find the most fascinating about this perspective is that I completely agree with just about everything that kid is describing in terms of
What are whether or not the audience would care about a couple days old
New story
Do a fundamental disconnect in terms of Y
I blame Infowars at Alex where is get seems to blame the audience for how they're fickle
Wouldn't give it to him and it's like it's like oh
Just because I go into some community and give them a ton of heroin people want heroin that has nothing to do with it man
People always want heroin
There's there's there's something to that metaphor
So
Navigate to some of the details about the actual article that kit wrote
I wanted the pieces of information that he put into the article was about how Nikolas Cruz
The shooter in Parkland was a Democrat
Figured this out was
Voter records
Novice
Man
This first sentence is the first sentence of the story
Yes
And it ends with
Voter records
Voter record suggests nineteen-year-old Nikolas Cruz
Was a democratic voter
Where did you get voter Reg
If I remember correctly I do the search I think Florida has a
I think voter records in Florida Republic
Okay so for this story
You weren't reporting on what other people are saying you went out
Found voter records on your own
Yes
Does journalist
True
Can't really commentate on
What's happening in the media if you're reporting something
Nobody else
Unless it's
I'm sorry I'm trying my new little bit fuzzy
Unless this is something I found somewhere else
You remember that believe that Florida's
Minor saying was Florida's
Voter registration is
Public
Although this might have been a screenshot account for somebody else
So you don't even know where it came
What my understanding is it came from the Florida I probably didn't go back and verify it to make sure this
Not just something philia made out of
Okay so you do go and verify
Yes
Is not journalism
It just something that's good practice
For who
So you here you go and verify things for the audio
To best my ability
But I was I was kind of getting to a point
Around here where is getting a little annoying
Big great I am I am starting to recognize
Why I was not invited to the deposition
I feel like I wouldn't be able to keep quite a same solid phases as you and Bill
Appear for them
Sure there is a there's an expectation of decorum all I will say
Alert at one point there is an audible last
I enjoy and I will give you a heads-up.
Like is this journalism is what you're doing journalism
Is just on answerable this is just such a
Such a murky pit
When you agree that
Journalist have a duty
Would you agree with that
That's what urinals do
So if journalist
We're reporting an Instagram account
Be fair to say since this was within hours of
The shooting
They were verifying
Well unfortunately that's what you
That's what you and me would like to believe
What
And growing up that's how I always thought of traditional media
But unfortunately I saw an article in axios recently
Am I finding excuses little bit left-leaning
They pointed out that
Trust In traditional media
Is like
Plummeting
I agree
Let me ask you this
How did that answer my
I do like that but let me ask you this
What is that
So this is in relation to
The notion that it's given in kits article headlined the sub-headline
That the media somehow covering something up about the Parkland shooter this is that
You know a complaint I guess is best is Cape connects plane
But no one else is covering the the Instagram
Workout plan so bills conjecture is maybe they're checking things
Under is that there's a
This is not related at all
Unfortunately
This leads to
Getting getting some parts out about statistics
This leads to a brick wall
I'm not into
Newsrooms that some of these
Organization
Right so you shouldn't really have an opinion one way or the other
Well it's not my opinion when I
Say that I axios reported that
Public Trust
At all time lows
And that was a sample of
The General Public
Crack I believe so
You don't know who they say I am
Crack
Well if it's over
Reminder Sam
Being an economics major if it's over 30
Maybe citizen
Sickly
Important
I mean
Apps
Absolutely necessary
Reliable
Not just
Over 30
Geographical age
Gender all of those go in
Subject subject
Cracked
That's what you're saying I don't know that
Statistics and so
I'm starting
Statistical principle
Okay do you know that
No
Then let's not talk about
Do you know anything about this
How about this
I'm going to give you a gift
Hang yourself right now the doors to get open
Buddy
The article itself some of the 30
Because of context right I can't tell if he means over 30 people polled or if it's over 30%
Believe it it seems like that's what he's saying based on context you're being overly generous
30%
Send it to Jessica
It could be could be seen as relevant a pole as statistically relevant
As long as you ask more than 30 people
That's why I do not believe in education anymore I don't think it can save us
30% to be statistically relevant then
9/11 was an inside job
I don't know that is not a statistic
So the article itself
Claims in it where they attack it was saying that the shooter dressed like a communist
Also dressed like and Isis fighter in Syria
These were claims that were made
Based on Nicholas cruises Instagram Instagram page that you found
Bellefonte
They pad was found on 4chan
That
The kid
Miss identified as
And so we we get into a little bit of this the claims of the Communists dressing the supporting Isis
That's not good for cat
Would you agree with me that
Reported Florida shooter dressed as communist
Is false
If what I was 50 headline had to do with Fontaine photo then yes I would agree with you
Would you also agree with me that
Reported Florida shooter dressed as it
As communist
, supported Isis that's awesome
I don't know because if I remember correctly
His Instagram account said things like Allah Akbar
And his these photos in the Instagram account just looks like something I would expect an Isis fighter
Iraq to dress like
Interesting spider in a wreck but it constantly goes back to see her yet for some reason
And
This is this is kind of an interesting notion like why do you think this looks like an Isis fight
This could not go more poorly for kit
Cuz I can already tell you what stone answer is right now I can just be like hey who knows what's in a man's heart
That's it and then he's like that's all I got for you
I think that's a
Some level of don't answer this would have been appropriate
It just fumbles the ball game time
It's embarrassing
The article that you wrote says Additionally the shooters garb
Is very similar to the style worn by ISIS Fighters
Fighters
In stereo
I read that correctly
Yes
When we look at the image that you included in this article there are
5 pictures of
Allegedly Nicholas Cruise correct
Yes
And is this the
The collage of photos that you drew
The Isis fighters in Syria
Coming from
I believe so yes
Is it normal for Isis Fighters
Syria to wear
United States Army
Well I was looking at
The masseter
And the kind of the nice how he's holding
So you say the United States Army
I mean I do remember the
There was a big controversy
Bryce's Fighters I believe is in Syria were using a pickup truck from a
Plumber in Houston
I still had his logo on it
So there's no telling I mean yeah possibly
So it's
Based on urinalysis it's fair the
The videographer Heroes dress
As an Isis member fighting in City
Now he's actually pretty dress pretty well
I know plumbers in Houston that dress like
Porsche truck
OK Google
That's why you don't need to answer that
Offer information at a deposition I think probably there's poor preparation
These kinds of justifications
Her like why did you think that
In his normal life that's good enough
Too many like
Critical people of his worldview and if he does maybe it's at like
Someplace where you have the camera and it's hostile base
About yelling at each other doesn't have to actually question himself
Why did you think this person look like a Isis fighter in Syria
He was wearing a mask and is an American army hat but also a plumber in
Houston's truck was in Syria
It's just convoluted fence and it gets worse it just gets worse
So if he was if the videographer here
Was wearing US Army
You would
You you can
Infer from that
That he was dressed as a fighter in Syria
Well it wasn't the hat that I was
Picking up
Specifically it's just
The whole collage of the image
The whole thing
The fact that the guys wearing masks
If you will what's today's daf
Spider and I definitely like to wear mask
Whatever reason
Interesting pictures of people wearing masks that Mountain Bicycles yes okay so
We could throw that one out as reliable anything else you got in here that's reliable as far as somebody dressed
Like an Isis fighter
Well the photos I've seen of Isis Fighters
City that were definitely very similar to how he
How many how many photos of Isis fighters in Syria
Have you seen
A lot
Okay and based on that
Nikolas Cruz right here
Is dress like that
Pass office Halloween costumes
It could also pass off as a bank robber
In the United States
Why do honor synonym
I think a bank robbery think of someone wearing a presidential mask okay
Other than that very specific and extremely random comment
We'll go on to have you ever seen photos of Eye of of Taliban forces in Afghanistan
Any of them wear masks
Possibly
We didn't have that in the article
Alabama was I don't even think the Taliban was in the news
The time is mainly nice
If you don't you don't think or you don't know
I do remember
Okay well then we can dismiss that comment and you can
Okay why didn't you add
Taliban forces in Afghanistan
Because in the new cycle the time
It was license
Is
Is it extremely popular and sometimes often required for members of the Tamil Tigers to wear masks exactly
Like that
Tamil tigers
I'm not Friday with that
The second largest terrorist organization in the world you don't have to know I'm not
Okay that's bad luck
Don't know who the Tamil tigers for a receipt
Geopolitical website need to redo the roster
Oscar's cuz that's best supporting actor level s*** right there that was hilarious that is a funny man
It's pretty dry delivery
Oh my God
Oh my god when I pick a bank robber
I think the people were present and it like iMovie Point Break
Boyfriend not like the traditional striped
Do they have tommy guns and they shoot their names into the wall
I would say the kit does not do a good job of Defending these assertions
I mean be idea of not giving a s*** what it is whether or not it's Isis or Taliban or whomever
Because what's in the news is Isis
Sure that's kind of important revealed and it also kind of dovetails with what he saying about like whatever that you know
The audience's eyes aren't going to be
Wikipedia
About that makes your contacts offer I believe
Jump over to the notion that he had that
The shooter supported Isis and where they came from
I am just a heads up there is a ethnic slur
Great in this is part of the explanation for his course of course
And here you did say the shooters is garbage very similar
Right
But when we look at page 1 you say he's supported Isis
Well there was a
If I remember correctly and his Instagram account he said something about Allah Akbar
How to bake 3
You see the screenshot on page three of his
Nikolas Cruz in the
Voter registration
Yes
You see the caption on the Instagram post
Can you read it
I believe it says well at least we now know what it means when a sander kisses Ella Akbar
Does that sound like
Anyone in the world that would support Isis
I have no idea
Okay then why on Earth would you drive
Your headline from a sentence
But you don't
It was I don't believe I drive
Yes I believe I've derived it from something
Cruz said on his Instagram account
This is Instagram
Another comment you made on another post news
Instagram account
Surely you would have included that in your article since your headlines that he
Possibly
Possibly could happen
So yeah he decided that the just the fact that Allah Akbar rights included with
In the body of this
Is that also includes a slur
Very specific slur
That means that he supports
Yeah I would go the other direction
You can really derive from this is the level of attention to detail
Let someone who's in a managerial role
Hidden for warriors
Engages with his contact with bats
The scary thing is I mean I'm just shocked at the
Like complete admission of
Maurice just said just lack of curiosity
I can't believe I can't believe that you would have no idea what that means and not be like I better take a look at that
Sure you know
You just
Ignore entire parts of sentences
Eleanor drive to cuz you just like I don't need to ask question well the level of lack of curiosity and lack of
Knowledge base
Spell idly. I believe that
But
Before we get to any of that
Which is why you find one of the more staggering admissions
That will get you in a second
But before that
Did conversation of like why did you need to
The report based on this Instagram
Something that you
Felt
Well based on Instagram that's at the time
The shooting just occurred
And unfortunately that's kind of all we had to go with
To kind of try to figure out
What this means motivation for
So maybe
Besides Beck's motivation
Because information was so limited
Maybe you should have slowed down
Wells breaking news story
Are you
Canal's for Valiant
So the audience and tell us the motivation at the time who did the audience Infowars
Got a call from the audience that said we want to know right now
Fletcher standard practices if the news cycle is if you see in every single news Outlet
And on social media they're all talking about the
Shooting
That's where the audience is eyeballs
Okay where did it come from that the audience needed to know the motivation immediately to the point where
Were you just start throwing darts in the dark
Well I should Powell is kind in the public interest
Well that's what people are asking
Sitting here today looking back
At the veracity of your article do you really think this article was in the publishing
It was in the public interest
To try to determine what the motivation for behind a mass shooting
You would agree with me that one thing that is never
In the public
Is somebody who is
Disseminating false information
Well I mean
With malice Maybe
What does that mean
Why did you
OfferUp an answer to a question that only only raises further questions
Don't do it man
Gotta look real yeah that is a real problem through a fair amount
I do appreciate that bill has very clearly got a point to this
Section of questioning at Leeds
Which is that beginning of like
What matters more
Accuracy or timeliness and what he says both bill is very clearly going
I'm going to dismantle the concept that you give a f*** about veracity and that it's all about time
Yes yes and I appreciate that
Kids doing such a good job
Unfortunately kind of explaining why
That immediacy is so important business model operator
Basically money part of the you profit
Off of Lies
And hopeful recognition that what you're doing is clickbait right
There's another thing that bill tries to nail down through this
I like can you recognize that what you're doing
Is clickbait
End this conversation as it appears here
Leads to what I would describe as the most staggering
Admission of ignorance that you're going to hear
Frankly I think it's a little weird his photos I mean why would you
Your Instagram account just be nothing but clothes you wear match going on
Well I mean I think you're trying
Are you trying to make sense
Of an individual who brought
Guns to his high school
And killed a bunch of people
I wouldn't say since maybe like motivation
Okay
Why
Why did you have to do it right then and there
Because that's where the audience
Paying attention
Right so this is clickbait
It's unreliable information about a story the audience wants to read about
Tatacliq
That's your opinion
What's your what's your opinion of clicked
When I use it what do you think
Why don't really
Engaging clickbait so I'd only have a pain on if you don't return me
You just use the term clickbait what you mean by
I think clickbait is something like
When you see an article on social media it's like
Click here to find five
Waze
Find five household products that will clean your house spic-and-span
Right so it's like click here to find this out and then you click on it and there's no real information about that
Yes okay
So when it says he supported Isis
Somebody clicked on your story
We're in here
Would they find that he supported Isis
This based on what I saw on Instagram when find the information that he said
Akbar comet
Okay
Which you have no idea what it even means
I mean I know that's a phrase
Isis Fighters use a lot
It's also a phrase that every Muslim in the world
Did you know that
Not necessarily I'm not too familiar with
You didn't know that
Rockbar is
A Muslim phrase that is used literally every day multiple times
By every Muslim in the world
I'm just not from that familiar with the Muslim ideology
Oh my god wow
Just f****** wow you guys need to know what you would say to that
I mean
I guess
I guess it's easier to understand what that's what I would say is
It's a lot easier to understand why you're a white supremacist
Ankles if you are you clearly have no f****** clue what's going on
This little information like would not be anywhere near the levers of talking about
These topics publicly you would not be able to opine about
Terrorism any issues related to Islam if you didn't have
Some very basic pieces of ventilation and it's there we do not live in that thing
World feel like a fundamental issue were running into here is Kent does not believe that words have immutable meaning
I don't think most people that Infowars believe things outside of subjective
He's like it when you asked me what a journalist is
It's a word that has a meaning you never repeat that meeting back
Cuz that's what a word means
You know it could be like a when a bird flies and it drops information onto the ground
Information is a is a seed in the seed becomes a tree and that's journalism
The bird is Glenn greenwald's recent work
Yeah
And that seed is Obama bulshit this could have been another contact drive but it's just filthy language
With the fact that I did not know what I look like Barbie okay
When you wrote this article didn't
It was your belief
That Allah Akbar
Was something that only people in Isis say
That was my belief at
Okay and since that time you've been promoted
It's tough to resume stuff to wrestle with you no like
Because of his
Clear ignorance but it's also damning of Rob to help presumably his immediate supervisor Alex Jones
The entire inner workings of Infowars that
Mikey doesn't reach
Basic standards for you didn't know what
And
You didn't
Cover
The topics the kid talks about where he draws conclusions about things based on the words out of appearance
Strictly all right
World I really understand much about
Whatever maybe then you could be promoted if you're a good financial analyst
But all who like back by meeting Jesus horrible amazing
So that's incredible
They're more incredible thing it was brought up that he reported that Nikolas Cruz
Was a
Presumably a Democrat based on voter registration
Advanced news about that also included a screenshot of
The Florida voter registration
Guess
Did you even realize
The name isn't even spelled the same
Not the, tonight's not even the same person
Yeah I know why did
Blurted out
For that contention
The name
Does even match up and you overlooked me remember that there was an instance
There was if I remember correctly there was two reported instances of his name
Let me to get the time
End it
It wasn't until the next morning of the 15th were his correct spelling his name
What's more prominent
So when you wrote this story
Alleging that this person supported Isis
And was a communist
You weren't even sure how to spell isn't
Just because the media at the time was recording like I think two different spellings of his name why'd you pick the one that you picked in the store
Vital member
You just pick one and said I will go
I don't know if I did that I just don't remember that sound like Cooper reporting
Does it sound like good report
Well unfortunately when there's something in it
News that's breaking
The details tend to be a little muddy
Right and they're muddy to buy
Individuals
Trying to pull. Or he's out of details that are not yet developed correct
Well I'll give you an example for you
Correct
What was your question
Yeah that stuff all right so when I describe my job
It sounds good
But then you describe it and it sounds bad and I don't understand your words cuz I feel like my job is good
Not as bad
Later that bill brings up and that is that there may have been multiple spellings of Nicholas
Cruz's birthday that was release all you could have cross-reference that to figure out who it was
Record and get seem surprised by this until I do not understand what
Cross reference means describe that to me in Greater detail
So cute his brought up
It'll in the immediacy of story sometimes those breaking news things get a little bit muddy
And Bill is suggested that maybe things are muddy when people try to force stories
Might as well just been like you realize that you write that that's basically what he doesn't
Muddy is because all the news organizations are chasing after the story and the details haven't been flushed out enough yet
To report.
Get Smart
Write something like that
You realize you're you're part of the problem
Do you realize that
Maybe in this instance
I'm just saying
You seem like
You're sitting here today saying what you did in this story was was okay
Do you think it was okay to do
Okay so you realize you were wrong
Okay and you realize
You could have been way better
Yes absolutely
Okay you realize
Nothing about any of these photos as anything to do with Communism or supporting
Signers in that now yes that one when you start understanding
How did you realize
When you get inside the car as Isis
Tell her before I just instructed you on one anybody who actually supported Isis would
Never
Use the term sandercoe
Yeah I wasn't aware of that term
You didn't even know what it meant you didn't Google any of this you just saw it and said oh I recognize two of those words must be iced
What was the breaking news story at the time for you I would assume so
Goof
I feel like a lot of my responses to these clips at this time
This is
This is a boxing match
I mean just the Mike Tyson versus us
Yeah if
Although at the same time here's what I feel like
I feel like listening to now
It feels like he's in a much more
Comfortable space just because
He feels like he's getting dressed out
But he's a man who's used to having people telling me did a bad job
And right now he's like
Yeah you're right man I didn't do a bad job like I feel comfortable here I'm not being questioned to think about things right now
Possibly in other circumstances in his life is dressing down
Don't really lead any consequences and then he gets a bonus at some point
I'll do better next time
It relies on some assumptions
We can at least say there is something of value in him recognizing the what he did
Was wrong
Woodland something and low bar at forthrightness is not necessarily there in a lot of other Infowars personality
StorQuest
Again
Tentatively
Also the question of commie comes up a communist
And support for this is a much better but it has to do
With a text that Alex
Your other headline said that he was a communist
You got that from the picture of my
Correct
That was my understanding that the
You don't have any other there was no other information
And you had
Leading anyone to believe that
Before shooter
Supported communism
Well dones back during the Las Vegas shooting
Show me a text from 1
His sources
Somehow tied the FBI hostage rescue
Fingerhut shooting
That said
If there was a bunch of antifa paraphernalia
All over the road
Hotel room
So that kind of got me into that line
So now just anytime anyone fires a weapon off near you you just immediately look for something that looks antifa like
That was what the source said
Okay what is that have anything to do with this.
That just kind of put me in the mindset
So you're brainwashed by mr. Jones
I want that was brainwashed
Sounds like you
He showed you something from a source
And from there on out you were in a mindset to assume and look for antonym
Well I wasn't going to
Discluded
What am I going to
Possibility based on this text that Alex showed of an alleged source
Okay still is this or Setters antifa and obviously I called them, what don't you understand
The Source said that there was a People literature
Prior to this on a different device
Stablish talking point within the world of it
Between things where there is no actual connection and build the Grandeur conspiracy
So understand this
Clearly I don't think so but I do think there is some
Subconscious understanding
You can Keaton that's the stuff that I think is being kind of revealed through the questioning
Just decide to answer questions you didn't need to
This leads to the actual discussion of the Fontaine photo that kit included in his
Article
And in the in the picture it's Marcel holding up his fist
And he's wearing a shirt that if you
Don't pay attention to it
Might look like a communist shirt but it is revealed
I imagine this next with what shirt actually is
What does antifa stand for
Anti-fascist
I think
Okay
What
Does everybody that's an antifa support communism
I don't know you didn't put anything about antiphon your story did you
Did the photo of mr. Fontaine
If I remember correctly look like a communist shirt
Put the pages
Superman a communist shirt
If you look closely
Do you recognize that shardas
Aperitif
On the Communist Party
We're certain communist individuals that are famous
Are having a party for instance linen has a lampshade on his head in people are drinking
Realize that no I did not feed just saw a red shirt with a swap with the hammer and sickle and you said got to be
Communism
That was my assumption of the time especially considering his
This like that
Is somebody raising their fists like this has that been
Used for any other
Movements
Possibly fit in this photo that combines where I see a red shirt with the hammer and sickle
Bam Kabhi communist
I'm in your eyes
Well I was my assumption that
It looks like something
Okay
In the headline it doesn't say
My assumption is that he might be communist
Did you say that
No sure didn't
Kind of have these fundamental claims that Kate was leading with the
Dress like an Isis fighter in Syria supported Isis was a commie
Based on the flimsiest
The evidence is actually contradictory to the claims that the opposite conclusion
Or at least the absence of a conclusion
I think that's pretty clearly demonstrated
And so Bill asks
How do you think you did on this one
1 out of 10
Rate your performance on this article
What about two or three really you got the two
What part of it was Dutchman to
Everything you said if I had this to do all over again I want it done it this way
Frankly I think this is my one of my worst performing articles I've ever done
Veneto probably
What's interesting about this cuz I had to listen to that a couple times
Right how do you give yourself a rank he says two or three I bill as shocked
It can't interpret that is how did you get down to two
How did you get down to it supposed to what deserves it never occurred to him
Looking for me to justify why it's better than 200
Wish I wish I could listen to this episode
With zero understand it was Zero contacts for Infowars or anything
Just the idea of listening to somebody
Go like
Oh I called him a communist need like you realize
That the shirt
Had Lennon wearing a lampshade on it right
Just that moment like this is really happening this is not fake
You withdraw that Infowars based on it with all the other stuff we know
Cross positively
So
Marcel's face is the only one that
Visible Ryan the pictures that kids put into the article
And that that's a problem because if you're looking at the article you would maybe assume that it's the same face
Under those masks better on the Instagram account at play
You would agree with me that in exhibit 1
Yes the only photograph of the alleged shooter
With that is the only photograph with an unobscured face
Is
Mr. font
Yes
So when you started spreading photos of the shooter
Only one that anyone can see your face
Isn't even the right person
Crept
Did you do you know what a reverse image
Familiar with it
Okay
Did you do what
I remember typing it'll Nikolas Cruz
On Google Images
And unfortunately the photos that were coming up for of Mister Fontaine
I didn't ask
I know I'm just that's just making me clarifying
I asked you
Whether or not you did a reversal
I don't remember
And answers
So that's for practice probably
One of the things of this deposition is that there's
There's a kind of nonlinear aspect of the questions that are at the registration
And then came back up
I'm here the notion of Journalism comes back up
Can boost
Unfortunately kid has referred to himself as a video journalist introduces an entirely
Play new wrinkle of your declaration in front of you
Yes
We look at
Paragraph
Says you're a video journalist
And you use the term Journal
Video Journal
Journalist oh is he
In the context of video Journal
Cracked
What's the difference between regular journalism in video journalism
I use the term video journalist because I really don't know how to describe myself
To the best of my ability as far as going out and shooting videos interviewing people
And then writing stories about the videos
I didn't do that very often if at all
Okay so you just shoot videos and then give them to somebody else. You videos uploaded website
You wouldn't write anything in the bottom or a story of with
With the video typically not
I never I generally never had time to I was just shoot a video when just uploaded
Open YouTube and then we didn't bet it on a force
Yes Evening News
Albino
I mean normally in the company we use
Praise reporter for the on-air Talent
Private
Muir
Taking videos doing interviews and uploading
Crack
Yes
So when you see news cameras out
In the field and their little bands
Can I pull over and set up the camera
Do an interview
There's nothing different from that way
Well they had a lot more equipment and Ativan
That's fine
You don't have a van
Or the equipment but you got a camera near the mouth correct
Yeah but unfortunately there's a lot of interviews I couldn't do because it seems like
When you have a small camera people think
All time
Why are you telling me this
What are you doing
Kid goddamn splitting hairs but the definitions is so weird
What are you well you know I mean sure I do all the things
But
Am I
I do I do everything that's exactly the same as described as journalists except
By using iPhone
Pandora's 50 million dollars in that we can't afford impressive cameras in a van on a tank
Justifies his use of the image of Marcel that he uses by
Claiming that
Quote the image was trending
Bossy is trending
No problem but you look at reality
You turn the page to page
Paragraph 3
It says I published an image of a man that I had a obtained from the popular image
In web board entitled
4chan
I went to the fortune website after I had seen
The challenged image trending on social media
Yes
How does
How does an image
When you see it all well when you go on watch
Twitter news feed I need to see it all over the place
Raven maybe your face
Everywhere
An under oath right now to this jury or telling them that you saw
Mister fontaine's photo
All over
Your news
That's my understanding if I recall correctly
Do you know how many times at the time the article was published you know how many times how many times that image has been posted on
No
Do you know how many times you can post on Facebook
Would it surprise you a lot
Yeah
Less than
What time frame
Between
The shooting and your articles online
Big cup of water
Well maybe I'm
Maybe I just happened to see all of them
Good sayings
Maybe you just don't have as many cool friends as I do
That's
The justification is in kits
Includes a image of somebody posting this picture of Marcel
Sell on Twitter prior to keep putting out the article
And this also reveals
No but it is what turns out to be a troll Twitter account and
Conversation of this we learn another
Gap
In kids
Information base that is
Truly staggering
In paragraph three of your declaration
You also talk about
Laguna Beach antifa
You see that
You relied
On Laguna Beach antifas Tweet correct
No would it surprise you to know that it was the
Only original Source at the
The time that I posted it
In all others that
That would surprise me
Now that we've established that
Your testimony
And this affidavit is that
The Laguna Beach
Antifa
Twitter post was at 2:37 p.m.
Hours before I post it
The challenged image on the Infowars website
Yes
2:37 p.m. what time zone
I believe that be Central Time why would you think that
Because of the time zone on men
Wouldn't surprise you to know that if you go to the Laguna Beach page
California
I was in the impression to Route Florida
Would it surprise you think Laguna Beach
Wow Laguna Beach Florida
Oh my God these are unforced errors in trying to
Explain himself he reveals these
Just remarkable
Misconceptions
Betty has
Allah Akbar is something that only Isis people say
Distler isn't a slur
Laguna beaches in Florida
It's it's
Is sad it feels like if you are going to prepare kit Daniels for this deposition
You have to be as oddware one as honest as any human being has ever been and just start with
They know the true answers to the questions they're going to ask you so your instinct
Is going to be wrong
Yes you do not know the true answers or what they're answering you
Do any answer you have is only bad for us there's a human impulse to explain yourself
You want to be friends you want to explain don't listen
Let me explain why you don't feel like what I did was bad
Just don't do that I guess a good way to prep him we'll just be like watch every episode of Law & Order
I mean a good way to prep him is like a f****** Mafia prep where he wakes up in a goddamn
River prep you need to do for this
It's it's just I don't know what you would do like
You'd have to deal with so many like just first concept absolutely in order to be like you can handle
Being cross-examined by somebody
Some things are
Aren't alright let's start from the beginning
Apparently was pretty new
It is a troll account
Might have been discreet might have been
Pretty fresh webkit God's hands on it what time did you post the article
It was approximately
4 p.m. or after
Till about 23 minutes
Any been up on Laguna Beach antifas page
How long have you been following Laguna Beach antiphon Twitter I wasn't following them on Twitter how did you get to it I did not
What you doing in your affidavit
So Kevin Brown
Went and found an example of fontaine's photo on silk
Media
Dab
Predated
When I put it up on Infowars
Why don't you just go get the original
I didn't remember I couldn't find the original
Fortunately
How long did you look
Fufu
40 minutes
That's it
Call mingle maybe longer
Maybe it was well I couldn't find I went back and looked at the
44 I screenshot it for Fortune I cannot find the bread
I did I do remember looking for it on social media and
Fortune log before deleting it
But I was looking
Discovery process
Why were they deleting
I don't know
Possibly yes
Or because
There were a bunch of Twitter pages set up quickly
Call pages to see if any news media Outlet
Would pick it up and run the store
That's a possibility
Do you believe your victim of
Some internet trolls that just got the best of you cuz you weren't paying attention I think I was duped definitely
I think you were too
I love
That he instantly responded with what he thought
With a solid amount of research time to 40 minutes and when he was questioned on that immediate
He was like
Maybe it was longer I didn't know supposed to be longer wasn't supposed to be longer but like 30 minutes
If you had that would be a reasonable amount of time to have
That seems like about how long it might take about that long to find you failed to find it then we're in trouble
Pretty pretty easily
Oh well
So now we can explore this notion of
Alex told him
About
The antifa literature at the Las Vegas shooting
So this antifa idea is connected to this shooting somehow which then has been translated into communism
Which makes sense
2K
And this is why
The only thing you got from his photo was that he
We eating even understand the T-shirt he was wearing what motivation did you add to the story with
Wells Fargo
T-shirt he's wearing looking at it
Hammer and sickle is red color
At the time I couldn't tell us a t-shirt
What
What did that what did his photo editors
Well like I said
I was told in a Las Vegas shooting that there was
Antifa paraphernalia all over the shooters room
I got meat in the mindset to consider
Bad
There might be some
I'm sort of communist antifa
Link
Tucson police shooting
Okay
What did Mr fontanes photo
Add to the article
I thought it was a photo of Nikolas Cruz at the time
And you believe that everyone in antifa
Support communism
How to get to Oso hammer-and-sickle and it was red
Want to say hammer hammer and sickle in a red shirt I think,
Okay how do you get to Aunt
What's that
How many different combinations of Santa Claus
About to Las Vegas
Alex Jones is the reason why you assumed
Everyone in antifa
Support communism I never said that
You
You added the picture Mister Fontaine
Because
Yeah communism shirt on
In your eyes
Yes
You added that
Because
Mr. Jones
Showed you some information that led you to believe there might be
Antifer
Related
Ideology behind the shooting
How do you get from communism with mister Fontaine shirt
To him being antifa
It's in the same Spectrum politically
Of what
I mean pantifa tip is typically left-leaning communism
That's how you got to the headline of your story
Guess
Swinging a mess
Man
If you don't they're both left-leaning feel like it Daniel should really just be going like dude you are blowing my
My mind what are you saying I'm saying that antifa and communism
And you're like have you thought about it and I realizing that I have not
Write the end this leads to a line of questioning about like
Now what about that why did you why did you blame Obama he is also left
That's the trouble in the ass to go down
Reverse image search because obviously this is leading to information that bill already has
Of what he would have found
Have you done a reverse image search
When did you
When did you learn what a reverse image search was
I don't remember in Fort
Okay was it
Just now six months ago 6 years ago I don't remember
Have you known about it for a while
Say so
Okay
And
Have you run one on this image
I don't remember
Standing here today have you run whenever
I've done in the past yes
On this image
On Fontaine image
I don't remember
Okay
It's not hard to do right
How do you do a reverse image
Oh no,
Sometimes I try to use Google
Both of those you just copy and play
Yeah I was Google
Cancel
Regardless it's not hard
Rice
And standing here today did you know that if you do reverse image search
You'll find mr. fontaine's photo
The exact
With the exact same
Commentary the bottom
Posted
More days before the shooting ever had
No
Unimportant facts right
Especially if you could have done reverse image search
For spreading his photograph all over
WeatherNation
Alleging to be a master
You are blowing my mind man what are you saying reverse image search before I post
Why are there
That is the first time it ever occurred to him
To have done that before posting
I don't know about that bass Ardex also
Never is that noise been more appropriate
He never thought about the idea of of
Reverse image searching before unfortunately
Plaintiffs attorneys are they have at their disposal
Skip previous work
I vaguely remember riding
Okay
In this article
You talk about
How Reckless it is for people
Cannot run reverse image search is don't you
Articles dated November 5th 2016
Correct
Yes
And that's
Over a year before you did Republic Mister fontaine's photographs the world
And the headline says law enforcement begs world
Read Hillary's emails Hillary emails to find child rape evidence and then it says
Hillary linked
Child sex ring, emails suggest
Yes
Okay
We flipped a page 8
Does the seller attached a picture of a Beanie Baby collection to the email but
Using a reverse image search
The image appeared to be a publicly-available photo that appeared on several blogs as far back
It's October 2014 and perhaps even earlier
The sellers email was dated June two thousand
I read that correctly
So you knew what a reversion research was at the time yes
You done
Before you posted mr. fontaine's photo to the world
Why didn't you do 1
I don't remember but
If I didn't do it
Vermont and photo or Greta not doing
Something so
Satisfying I guess because he works for Infowars about that like
You didn't do reverse temperature tonight
Also here's a article where you're scolding people for not doing the reverse image search it feels
Like
A constant
Add repetition of that jackass
Sketch
Wait where they have the giant hand pneumatic or the the drinks
So whatever he's just walking right into question she's just like
He had he knows that the thing he's answering after that is you know you wrote this article right
He doesn't seem to ever realize the hands comic
No clue it's
Every single time except trouble and they walked toward that door with all those drinks and it gets smashed
By the hand of God
Yeah because this reverse image search article that kit has written about
Something to do with the podesta emails and Clinton has been brought up right now kits pizzagate cover
Here we go
Under the bus
The next page page 9
The second full paragraph
His other strange email sent to podesta include cryptic references to Pita hot dogs
Pasta and walnuts
Which are fueling speculation they are code words for criminal activity including child molester
I read that correctly
This is a bunch of pizzagate
That's right
I don't know if this was necessarily
Involve
Pizzagate
Oh yeah
My other channel pizzagate had to do with the Comet Ping Pong Pizza
Right where did all that start
Guess the emails with cryptic references about pizza and child molestation you know that right
I know it wasn't that I wasn't involved with the connestee Falls too far as I remember
Yet you wrote an article about linking Hillary Clinton to a child sex ring
If I remember correctly I think Alex Jones give me the headline in the sub headline for this article
I think I worked with it
Okay I don't remember unfortunately
One thing we do know is that here you are again writing about a story that turned out
To not only not be true but people acted on
Right
What are you referring to
A gentleman with an ass with an AR-15 walking into a pizzeria firing his weapon because he was
Convince
There was a child sex ring being run out of
Can I say anything about a pizza
Pizzeria on this article
Beautiful I'm saying you're reporting on the information that led to that Pizzeria
Pretty sure about that the name of that Pizzeria
I have no idea destiny
I like I said I didn't I wasn't that involved with the comet
Jean-Paul stuff at all no but you were involved with spreading the disinformation about
These non cryptic messages what does the emails true
It was Alex Jones that told me that pizza hot dogs pasta walnuts Raw codewords
And I and I believe that was also FBI
Symbolism
Can you believe it
Fatburger child molestation
Do you still believe that
I don't know I was just
Stuyvesant
Trying to vaguely remember what it this is from 20/16 my memory little bit fuzzy would you believe that
The FBI had coworx
Like that for Chop
Would point out hey if you ever hear these code words
This could be
A
Signal for child molestation so be on the lookout for it.
It was an I believe is in a bulletin FBI Bulletin
Do you
That's what I remember. Are you sure that what you're referring to is
Actual real FBI.
I vaguely remember seeing one
Vaguely
But like a Galaxy
I can't you know this is going to be Alex
Yeah that's bad
I can't believe he hasn't already how far into the depth is where at least an hour into the deposition but
I can't believe he hasn't already realize that if he gets the question do you think that was
The real document she knows the answer to that already sure
Like he doesn't heat kit just can't process that
He thinks that anybody asking him a question
Is genuinely interested in his response to it or there's a possibility that based on your answer.
The information the other person has will be affected
I mean it's optimistic in some ways it is it's it's a little Don Quijote it is
It is a Panza
It's a good approach to take care of would be
What have you ever gotten right
Good call Bill
Unfortunately I watched a lot
Looking for work program I think I've read every word that you've ever
So what I'm asking you these stories I kind of know what
Dancers are
So what else have you gotten right
And I'll give you two
Epstein instant jussie Smollett
I'll give you those two guesses that y'all end up getting right
What else
We are
I think they're just so many of them
So many
I'll wait
The Gulf of Tonkin doesn't count y'all weren't company when it happen
Priceisright.com doesn't count they want to company when it happened
I want that on the record please
We can sit in this awkward silence as long as you need to think of one time where y'all were right while they're just so many like stories we've covered
Over the years as little bit hard for me to kind of
It's like it's kind of like on Spotify like the time. You here
You keep thinking
Will wait in silence
That's not
Come on come on just let me get out of this one just let me get out of this what there's so many nothing but time just let me get out of this
All your questions sir I'll get on my knees just don't make me answers anything I've ever written is true
It's an embarrassment of correctness and so I have too much to choose from
I think the reality of that is obviously
You'd be very worried about saying anything definitive late cuz there will be a follow-up question
Really back up with your delay probably
So
This is this is another moment of kid being like
A normal human sort of
And that is supposed to have
Do you believe that you and Infowars are responsible
For the coverage that you
Put out that affected my
Write like a normal human accept that responsibility
You and or Infowars
Share responsibility
What mistress
Regret
Ocean has photo on
I do not see how you felt
If you're going to
Hold yourself in the company responsible
Yes
In
That goes for both you and the come
Chris
Are you aware that the company does
No I'm not aware
You disagree
I know cooking position are
And I can call off strike
Stuff even bill at this point is throwing a lesson we already know the answers yet
Trying to help him out
He's not hitting as hard as he probably could really do feel like Bill is is like
Giving him
This dislike
I don't know what to call it
Just a sense of like man
I could really tear your ass into shreds you know that right it comes back
Back to the think the dynamic you were talking about at the beginning is just as feeling of
They're just
Do you say things that you don't need to say in response to questions that you could
Do not answer you offer more information
Boxing metaphor it would be like
You are leaving your midsection exposed Christ Italy
You got your hands over your head and you're saying I'm going to get you
So this next clip is where of the main headline surrounding
This deposition is dead kid started crying
And this is the Clipper that happens
And
I'm going to give a little bit of just a warning in advance there's some language of the two used
Regarding
Fontaine that comes from 4chan post
And just for the sake of
It's on the record right here is that
I'm going to go ahead and assume you've never seen this February 10th post
From fortunate
No
Okay you flip the page
Yes
What do we see
Photo Mister Fontaine
That's four days
Correct
So
This post
Is if you go to the first page
Is a sub page of 4chan
And called Politically Incorrect right
I believe so again
And the caption
Of this thread is
Antifa
Aspie
Lefty
Communist
Cringe thread
That's what it says show me your worst
Unironically Lefty dimwit
Commies
Etc
You found while surfing the internet social media
Okay
And you understand Mister Fontaine was posted by someone to this
It's what it appears that they are you aware that Miss
Serfontein cell
Would that affect the way you feel about him if he did
Yeah it was
Felt the same way at 10
I'm going to represent to you that Mr Fontaine has been clinically diagnosed
The autism
Cousin like
He's socially
Not very
Developed as you are today
And
Has dealt with mental health
Beforehand
Now remember how you said you felt
Whenever you got there
Now
I want you to imagine
And you do not have any swimming pool
Is that you know of
Knox
Depression
Okay have you suffered from
Autism
Social anxiety
Do you have
An inability to
Working large
And deal with a lot lot of
And you can sympathize a little bit more
And I understand your
And I'm not trying to
Quite understand
The suffering has been through
I understand you're upset
If you want to take a few seconds
We live
Yeah let's take a break and get him some tissues
We got the record Madam reporter
30pm
So they go to break
You do a plug for gato prevail
It's important
I think
That a lot of people have
Attention to this
I think it's interesting obviously that he started crying but I also think that it's probably the most
Human response to the information that he's being
We presented with a guy I don't think that it's something
Does maca worthy or anything I think that
It shows
Inability to empathize with somebody when forced to
I think that obviously he should have
Recognize the pain that he was causing through this
Sloppy ass work short prior to this sure you would hope that right but
I don't I still find it very difficult to criticize
That response
This is a really good example of what we've talked about from the very beginning
With and with Alex it's kind of come to a clearer idea and flus ambiguous
That stupid V evil continue upright you know
You can be stupid
You know still do evil s*** but it's kind of clear here that kit Daniels is
Not in the vindictive or malicious or he's a colonel of evil but mostly kind of drama
Madonna where he's just kind of an idiot
I mean unless he's a f****** Kaiser so say level Mastermind right here
Then he's kind of an idiot who is Ben
Like to play Alex Jones and intimidated by everybody else
I don't I don't know what conclusion to draw but I think
You know that's certainly a fair reading that you can you can take
I was really
I knew going in watching this and he started crying and I still felt that it was shocking
Yeah like
It was fate still shocked me because first of all it kind of happens fairly quick
It does it doesn't seem to be pit doesn't
What it felt like to me was somebody's dissonance really being challenged
Mike be the notion that like this is what I do for a living and this is what
If I wasn't getting sued for this I probably wouldn't even recognize that I've done something wrong
And here I am
Seeing parts of myself
In the victim of what I've done at these thoughts just sort of tearing
Yeah it's in the brain
I don't know it's hard to sleep
The thing that it reminds me of most
Is
Evangelical children
And how they grow up
And
One of the things that will almost always wind up happening with an Evangelical child leaves the faith
For good is they will have
A very big conversation and they will suddenly start crying
And they don't entirely know why I'm based upon the questions in the conversations in the thought they're having
And the reality is the reason it happening is because
They're going through this strange moment where everything they have ever believed
Comes into contact with a
Muv immovable force your realities being challenged
Minecrafting pressure from that and so you just always cry
I did just happen
No conversely
Deprogramming as well you have situations like the Daria deposition or Alex's
Deposition
Where they're being confronted with
Like very incontrovertible instances of the harm and damage the game 2
Luby's the victims of these these narratives of these
These things that they put out
And they did not bat an eyelash
They had no real
Alex gave lip service to like
Example of the emails that Wolfgang halbig sent harassing the charity
Southern Voice
And end with Dario's even worse and Calder
High School
This this feels like there's some human hair that's crying out
Because it appeared feels like the difference between a Believer and somebody who is raised in the church
You know it's like somebody who is raised in the church has been surrounded by nothing but this type of information
Haitian for such a long time
32 Tsum to be true
Believers it doesn't matter what you do it does not matter what you do you cannot talk to them in a way that
Will cut through their belief system
Somebody was raised around it and it's just absorbed it
Then eventually you can go like oh s***
What the f*** is around me you know
Yeah maybe
There is an element to that it's kind of really shocking to see that yeah we're making more out of it then
Really is there possible
Makes it even more difficult is that like
To the best of my knowledge it didn't immediately quit right so like
I don't know
I mean and furthermore because it simply because of what we do we're so unused to people
Is it having Cuban moments on hard shell on Alex fix crying all the time but that's very clearly real
I don't even know if anything is true when it comes to human emotions on this show right or what is actually underlying
That you would even if it is literally could be him crying because he realize that he's so f*****
You know I feel like that's doubtful based on just the surrounding information that cost
I mean if you want it
Get really cynical with it there could just be a crying about his own pain
Not empathizing this early with reminding me that I'm get depressed
Memories from my own existence are what's motivating this totally
Really feel like it feels like there's an empathetic quality to it but
But again I might just be seeing something today
I would prefer to see as opposed to this is just a total
Selfish I want to believe that he is you know it's it's one of those things
Where I have that
Absolute bias as well like I want to believe
I believe that somebody can
Change clocks Boulder compound
What does it say it's preferable to like thinking that this is an organism
Break
And they come back and what are the things I think Bill is trying to do here is really
Force
Kit to recognize the Cesspool that is information comes from
That he got his information from
So there's more offensive language here so just a heads up on that
If we look at page two
Okay
There's a
Picture above
Okay
Alright
Has Mister Fontaine in the middle
Oh okay
Can you please read the comment that was posted
I'd rather not but I will because
Did you ask me it says same as B, f*****
Go down to
Or actually go down one what is the next one say
The nose
Nose
What's the next one
What is it with
They them
Pronouns aren't they plural pronouns
Would you understand that to be
A comment related to
Mr. fog
Containment
Non-binary
I guess
Just because I'm not terribly familiar with
The terminology
It means I'll represent in the mystery
Does not identify as
Okay okay
Yes okay I could go up one that's what
They them
Yes they're picking apart
The public information
They find on him
Using that to
Make fun of him
Then you see the photo of Mister Fontaine
Yes
Right under that
You see a picture that was posted
Incorrect
It looks like it was a
A screenshot of a video
Okay can you tell me what the file name
Left
Wing Death Squad
Okay
Go to the next one
Yes
Can you read it for me
I can guarantee that this loser works at the
Sorry can't relate
Worcester Massachusetts
They play loads and metal shows far more than any other John
Do you know where Mr
Fontaine work
No
Representative
That at the time you work
So the demonstration here is of the intensely bigoted nature of the harassment
Ikea
Continue to knowingly or unknowingly or through negligence haha and the
Dachshund and all of this
Is a the kernel from which
His reporting
Blue
Lancer bomber
Yeah you see all these pieces of s***
How do you feel about that you're one of them
It's more you have taken to their goals and achieved
You have spread this harassment that much larger audience than would be available on this
Pull board
And and in some ways created a more mainstream
Ishq place right where it's happening
I think if it is dealing with
What's being
Terrifying like oh that's a wake-up call I mean
Italy after this deposition that says a lot I don't know I
Can't really say that with certainty I don't know what his employment status is
Enough to know if he has byline necessarily heard anything
You didn't quit that speaks volume
Oh well
Anyway he fell for a fortune thing
And unfortunately a year prior written another article
This is your article correct
I believe so yes
Got your name on it yes
Can you tell me what the
What the headline
BBC Falls victim to 4chan trolling MS
And cut sound like
Howard Greek yes
And you wrote this article
August
About eight months
Before
The article
Question today
Yes
Now
The subheading
Catches my eye
Can you read it for me please me see claims visiting 4chan constitutes invest
Desiccated granola
Subletting there is
Pointing out and making fun of BBC for falling
Victim and
For thinking the fortune
Reliable credit
Something to that
Affect
You'd agree this one didn't really aged well
Howard degrees so
There's a there's a ability for kid to kind of laugh about this stuff after
Wild after he
Assertive purged himself
Weird
The very weird yeah that's like flipping a weird switch
I know. I look like now I got to say
Crime for destroying that guy's life man I feel like I've got egg on my face falling for a fortune
Break after a year after complaining the other people look like
Makes it appear that I was aware that that's what I should be looking out for
Hot
So there is a another aspect
To the Parkland shooting that it covered and that is that there were some
A bags that they're cops were taken to a car and it was suspicious
Soak it posted an article
Questions questions isn't attempts to get Kit to understand that this is not
Asking
What you're doing is not asking questions 45 minute-long clip
You are you contending here under oath that
The investigating officers of this
Shooting
Wearing proper
And what they did
I just the way I wrote this article I just
I thought at the time the video is seem a little odd
I'm not saying that they didn't think
Robert
Sure but let me do this
If
If you and I go outside of this building and we're stand
And
A school bus
Children
And I say
I was really odd how you just look at that little girl
I'm implying some
Nothing but I can say I'm just asking question
But it's not really
Can you get that right
I don't know if that's a
If that's equivalent to this
Sure it is
I'm just asking
No I'm
I literally was
To me it did seem a little odd that they were carrying it
The time
And it was pointed out to
I believe is a Jones movie wonder where that Radio 4.
Why do you keep looking at me
Like
You realize this is clickbait but you don't want
Because that's not my
I'm just asking question
You're the one that keeps bringing up
Look in my opinion
They look like you're saying clickbait
Mets Alonso
Right I'm just asking
Question when someone has an opinion
I'm sorry.
All right here yep yep
Yep very rude
When someone has HID kit
And then they inject that opinion into a loaded question
With an agenda
And they put they do it in the form of a question
I'm just asking questions
It's not actually asking
You don't care what the
That's what year
Your opinion is
Okay
What are the answers
You know now
What do you mean did you did you go through the files of Parkland and look and see what bag was get put in that truck
You look good try to search and find out who these officers were
No it's not
The important part is that you got body bag
And inverse Ponder's acting suspicious
The day after the shooting important
Not the actual
That's what your
I'm fine but
What you do to find the truth what you do to Anthony's question
Let's put it this way
Just answer my question I will answer your
What you do
If I were to go back
I do for your request
Define Angeles out Weeks Later
I'm sorry the audience is already moved away from Park
Right
You were writing stories
To get your audience to read them now
No
I'm writing stories
The audience is already paying
How do you know when you're going to pay attention
How do you know they want still want to know what are the answers
Because unfortunately that's how the
World Works nowadays people have a
Short attention
Doesn't sound like these questions are very important and does it
That's what your
I don't understand what you're
You're saying well if you had all these important question
Right
But never even attempted to
To figure out the answers
They're not that important are they
I guess I sure
Tough thing to get around obscene just care about the answer
That's a tough that's a tough needle to thread
I
Genuinely believe he does not understand what is being a
Explain to him
I do too especially that the part where I like your eyes seem to be
He was like I'm I'm in a completely different world sir please
You see how this works I'm doing this to you
Did not
Just can't get there
Snoopy idea of answering a question does seem anathema to Kate Daniels has possibly
We allot has come up and I will tell them to stop it
He doesn't unfortunately I'm not a lot looking back on it I would have preferred to
You have done my job completely differently from the beginning
So you do you know obviously
Questionnaire asking
Thought itself isn't bad
This brings up the the notion of you got to ask the right questions or boy this is going to
Area 45 minute-long clip
In your opinion are these questions and poor
We're trying to figure out what's going on
With the mass shooting
It is important to ask
The right quick
What people who decides what the white right quick well if there we know which ones
Questions right
What
I don't know I don't know where you're getting at
Wrong question
Are the questions that are
Put out there
The nobody cares about
And nobody actually goes and tries to answer
Like your article
Says who
We need to try to answer
Maybe that important to you you don't even care with you
What do you mean
Didn't you just said
You did not go and do anything to get the answers
Boy request when it taking too long my readers wouldn't have liked it
So how important to Levi
Here's the problem I can't
I can't force readers
If I wrote about something 3 or 4 weeks after the fact
So Infowars audience only cares
About the questions that are asked you mediately and they don't care about the ant
The news audience in general tends to only focus
Stories of the day
Necessarily
The stories I would have
4 weeks ago
Okay short where'd you get that info
That's just
No it's not
Oops
You're selling yourself short there buddy are you saying that people don't want to read your work
Merits of your work not sure don't
I've got nothing interesting to say unless you are already paying attention
Yeah little contentious
I think in cases like that in situations like that it's
To bring things back to the center
And find some agreement which they are able to do here
I'll tell you this Jones's told me
Years ago
That we were not
I can't I can I will agree with him on that now whether or not you made your audience and I and I
Now whether or not you made your audience believe you words
Completely different question but there is no doubt in my mind
The nothing that you do
Actually
I would agree with that
The problem I have is that Alex Jones is motto
And something he's repeated
Over and over
Over again
Is we are the truth in
Starts with a j and ends with a
Journalism
Still don't know I where did you see that at
On his show
Once or twice
Every 3 hours
At least for the first 3:00.
Well unfortunately I can't speak
Okay so if mr. Jones the owner of the company says Infowars where the
The truth in journalism
He's lying
I didn't say that what you said you're not journalist
Oh man oh man oh no god dammit assume
Either
No one at Infowars cares or LED to horrible conversation
Just like I could not be more a man walking through a f******
Crowded Street of carriages while two people are carrying a pane of glass and they're smoking watermelon carts
Everywhere like stepping into an absolute disaster every time he speaks
Just imagine I'm going to work okay boss
So I blamed you for a bunch of things aren't journalism if you say you are you lying
Also I said that it bores is responsible for
Starting to think I am not going to have a good day today I can just go back to my desk
Practice is apologizing for things I did wrong really does want to go
Get out of the line of questioning where it's like hey you didn't even look into any of this
Someone else's fault
Let me ask you
What was in this bag
I don't know what the weapons
I don't know
How many shooters were involved
Was it just one or more
I don't know
What was
Why did it take to train professionals
To carry this bag
I don't know
Is it scissor SWAT gear in that bag
Are these questions that you find in Port
I don't know
We're not important enough for you to go
We know that
Well
If I remember correctly I wrote this article at the
Somebody
How many tolls
I believe so
I think it was Jones or a RAV4
Like I said
And Jones head
Here's some footage this is what I want you to write on remember I just vaguely remember someone
Ask me to write
Okay so this article would have been
About
It is not necessarily your beliefs you just wrote
Something that
Somebody asked you to
Basically
Is my understand
And you would agree with me
These aren't these are
You don't actually care what the answers
Right
I mean
Wow
Exasperated seismic about the best you can do
Fashion Center
I am very tired and you make me feel very bad about myself I would like to not do this anymore can we do that
It's Alex's fault or some producer somebody else told me to do this
Did you hear me try and read the things you asked me to read
Do you think I'm good at reading
Or writing
This this there's still another matter to be
Still
The question of like not answering these questions
Being driven really trying to get this home to cat cuz I think it is important it is
If you thought these questions were important you would have asked you would have gone and looked for the answer
At some point
Queen
February
And today
February of 20
Right
Like I said
I don't consider myself a
Investigator
I consider myself more as a
Commentator
I don't even believe I've ever done
Spyderco
Safari like
Amazing
It's right
You just ask
I think I would have I would have been interested if I could find the answers of it
Within a couple days this
Are you saying you couldn't find those ants
No
You're not saying that
What's that
I'm saying I doubt I could have found the answer to this question
In a couple days with him
Mister Daniels
Try
I didn't think I could
You never tried
What is an investigative journalist
Maybe I just don't understand the question
Trying to put it out there sometimes Infowars
Has articles that go out
Weather Renton
In your perspective or on
Half of somebody else
That asked
Questions quote-unquote
To stir up fear
Or stir up at
Fierce Ethier
Like
There was a body in the bag
Or there was wet
In the bag or that there was SWAT gear in the bag
Or that it was a dead body
Or that
That the bat that this was taken during the shooting all of these
Just questions
They're all there just to incite people
Say oh my gosh
Something might be up and then
Where do they start going
They start coming back to ww.w
Fill in the blank
Infowars.
Cuz that's where the salsa
It's tough
Forget to refute any of this because
Is it pretty app
Description of
What he did
This is just exciting questions
To imply that you have some kind of information that isn't accessible anywhere else
Right and then
Get them into your Revenue stream Mariah
How do I get it he's trapped in the f****** Fox News right-wing propaganda brain where the idea is never
I mean the job of right-wing media is to remove curiosity
By destroying the value of questions you know like
Gay marriage what's next are you going to marry your dog you don't
Actually want to know what's next
What's next is more equality and everybody gets better you want to next
Yeah
Couples getting married questions don't mean anything questions are just reasons to hate
So
There's that there's a fundamental issue going on and that is that the retraction of this story was not
I'm done correct
Involved picture of Marcel Fontaine
And so
Kent has
An excuse about this
It is troubling
Do you know what date Mister Fontaine filed a lawsuit
Around that same time frame
The first
And he did that because
Standard language that should have been in the original
It's not just okay for you to take
This is what's required
And because he gave you
2/2 weeks
And nobody did anything about it
That's where this
Do you find the retraction clarification and correction
A bit disingenuous
Considering
It was in response
No
If he
Here's my problem I told her
Attorney-client
That's privileged
Okay well I'm not going to say what I told
You can say what you
What are you not supposed to tell me what
But she wasn't legal advice she
Okay I understand that
Peppa
My problem was that the timer counts
Lyric child apparently
You said on that
Letter that you
Excuse me
Am I understanding is we had when we when we
Saw the letter in the lawsuit we had we went and got other count
To write the
Protractor
Did you know that Mr tab actually represented you
All the way up until about
4 years in this
Excuse me
He pulled out
There is a allegation be made he ignored this
The man for a retraction
And then they got new Council but he was still the council until very recently before this deposition
This is troubling Daniels lawyer I would have said do not
Say any of that produces a lot more questions a lawyer said on this
30 days
May I have more details about that information thank you very much
Yeah yeah it's bad but also even
Given all that
Understanding about the rules
About retraction
And the bike down for this because this is the cliff where you can hero last okay
And your is your content
He sat on the
It was Donner the right
I mean it might hurt and we have like three days
Retracting up
According to Texas state laws
Set 30
And even if it
You got my letter on February 18th
You changed it
April 2nd
I don't remember if I even saw the letter until the lawsuit
Sure
But I'm just saying when you said you met the time for
Don't know how many days are counting
But we don't we don't understand it as we don't
Practice law in Texas
Turn on weekends
Well I mean
Do you do deposition
Saturday
Absolutely
It was
My understanding is in Texas who don't practice law on weekend
My understanding in Texas and please stop me if you know
Know any more about this than I do perhaps are you some sort of lawyer that practices and some sort of State
My understanding
Despite you very clearly saying
All the words that would suggest what I'm about to say is not true
Did you guys work on Saturday
I know from first-hand experience
Being at a deposition in Texas
What happened on the weekend before this deposition
Your people at Infowars what deposed on weekend
Get your note this is nonsense but I think it is a fun little bit of like
Haha I'm back
Who told him that
I don't get that information through books
Genuinely want to know where it is you got that
Custody
So there's still more problems with his retraction though and this also is another thing
It might get scolded by Alex for this
I do have a question about
Okay
Here
Is on this webpage on February 14th 2018 we showed a photograph of a Young Man
That we had received
Very puzzled
Considering you said
You
Pulled it
You're right so whoever wrote that
That's that clarification also isn't
Only those words I did bring up to Alex Jones
I didn't like
We had
What did he say
He said
Just left the lawyers how
Adult
Say Alex's name in the
Only going to get Alex in trouble
Alex told me I brought up that exact point to Alex he told me to shut up
How is it that he is not been able to remember so much but this one time he's like oh yeah that one I deaf
Emily brought that up to Alex
Probably a problem not have been more certain that he took that exact complained to Alec
Amazing
So I can't read this article so what happened the next day
Kind of funny
The day after you posted your story
Paul Joseph Watson who at the time I believed was
What was the role you gave him not Chief editor
Editor-at-large
That's how we refer to himself in his biography
And he says so
The alt right in the alt left media crafted a fake news narrative that fulfilled both
Their objective
Using made up 4chan posts
Less than
24-hours after
A bloody massacre
Killed 17 people
. okay
You realize mr. w
Contactually make
He doesn't realize that
You did this
Sandy
Bye mister
Response to him and says that's rich coming from you
Infowars published false information in the wrong photo in propaganda f
To link the left and and antifreeze
You are a huge part of the problem
Complete Hip Hop
He's not wrong there is
Let's San Diego
Clarifies it like you didn't do it maliciously
But I understand
Hey I just find it tough
How do you how do you continue working there having build your own
Senior editor or whatever was posting articles mocking the very work that you're getting sued over
I legitimately don't know how this dude f****** brushes his teeth every morning I don't know if he speaks
Who is blender I don't know if you've given things Fantastical names like I sleep in the double bed
Don't know it's I don't know how this dude function it's pretty confusing it is bananas to me
He also wrote some stuff about the Las Vegas shooting place on
Some Notions of antifa literature and what have you
Bill wants to establish that that
Was also click
I'm asking one question
Okay
Your
Your headline says Vegas shooter found with antifa literature
Right
Yes
Point me where you get that
In this article
I don't see a in bed for
You know why
I don't remember
Because the headline
That's your opinion
Not good
Oh my God what do words mean
Nothing that's what I thought
So this article that kit had written about the Las Vegas shooting
Hayes
Debatably clickbait
But
The information that he's running within this
Comes from dubious Origins
Essentially just from alley
Right
Now
This
Winding down this deposition here and I think it ends with
A scathing revelation
About how Infowars work okay
I wrote the headline in the in the lead sentence on Bahasa
Farmer
Correctly
He showed me the
Taxi got from
That you don't know if is even real
It could have been Doctor Jones with
Seriously doubt that
You don't know
But I seriously doubt you do
Just finding work
How do you write multiple articles telling you put stuff in it you can't backup
Maybe maybe the in bed for the
Okay I'm sorry
The nobody can corroborate
He's got you putting your name out there
But you would agree with me nothing
About this article
Has anything
To do with antifa
Other than the headline Jones force you to put on the top of the
Antifa Twitter
There's a
There's nothing in this article besides
The
The headline that mr. Jones portion put on here
It has anything to do with
Well that was what the source Paul Jones
Where is it
Where's the screenshot where's the screen filling out
So here's the thing
Why is that your headline is the article doesn't talk about it at all
That's a question
A Jones
Okay
2 in in inches
Tucana breakdown
John's discount
Said you're writing this and kind of forced
The right is this isn't something you want
My understanding is this is something
Ask me to write
And he gave me the
The information
Did he ask you in a way where he would have been okay if you said no
Cuz when you have something like this
You do it now
Why is my boss
So this may not be as a relevant in a legal setting but this clip is super important for my interest
I found that the methodology for how enforce works as a broadcaster
But Alex will use Infowars articles
Specifically there headlines to build his on-air narratives
Often times these headlines do not accurately reflect the body of the article butter worded specifically it away
So that they can be useful to whatever conspiracy Alex is trying to prove or demonstrate on air
In some cases these are
Fully in-house articles and in other cases their articles from other outlets where the body of the article is copy-pasted
Onto the Infowars site
In a wholly new a headline is attached to make it more useful for Alex
The Revelation that Alex is directly telling his managing editor what headlines to put on stories
Is basically the piece that completes the circle of Alex just making all this s*** up
He's on are pretending to cover news stories but in reality
It's just him yelling about headlines that he's told his employees to put on story so he can more easily yell about them
This is completely self-contained information space where everything is just basically Alex's win
It was pretty
Cleared that this was what was going on but it seems like a much more reasonable assumption to think that like
The in-house culture was just that employees and do what Alex wanted and then they provided
Maybe some subtle prodding if you didn't take the right angle Rob do would scold you or you wouldn't get as big of a
Enough to get the message across and ultimately the people who did the right job would stick around at the people who didn't
Livefit that company culture they wouldn't last
To me it's an entirely different ball game for Alex to be actively directing the production of the news he's covering
And having an active role in the creation of the headline
Which are the only parts of the story he ever really cover
Given this workflow like what
Story could Alex not manufacture
All he needs is an Infowars article to justify anything you might say on air and he could just tell one of his Moby underlings to create that
These underlings know better than to not give Alex what he wants
F***** up 8/8 like
We reverse-engineered this from watching the show
And it's like but even then you create a series of plausible sound except
That would lead you to the result that you have
To have somebody not only tell you that those steps were totally right
But to also be like and guess what there are
Fewer steps than you thought
It's just Alex
He's f****** insane because like you just have demonstrable observable things like
Alex only really covers headlines ever match the body of the article
* there will be articles match
Where they were originally posted with totally new headline these are all factual observable things
That lead you to the conclusion that this is an intentional scratch
Izzy's
They creep he's for Alex to yell about things on
You wouldn't want to jump to the conclusion that Alex is telling people what to write
Because it makes it easier for him to Yellow
Here we are here we are we have just been given that leap I guess I would go so far as to say that
That the one thing you would not want your employee to tell
Is that very fact
Yeah so we have one last clip in this deposition and it's actually a demonstration of how this process work
With the headline being used
Do essentially create
Idb broadcast
Open that article up go to the last page where the tweeters
And read what mr. Jones tweeted
That one right there okay
Last page
Sorry
Scavenger hunt
Right back to laugh
Read it
Police live Isis takes
Responsibility for Vegas shooting has left
Celebrates Massacre
Can you tell me
Why you put that in there
I don't know if I did put it in there myself
It might have been just
You might had a script
Set the time
Do you think anyone on the left
Was celebrating what happened in Las Vegas
I don't know
Personally
So
And your opinion you have
Zero evidence that anyone from the left
Was celebrating
I don't know I mean I didn't write this
Will you put in your article correct
I put it in Bedford
For Twitter for Joneses
Radio program
Okay so that's just an advertisement that has happens to be on the same subject matter as your art
I don't know if advertisement is accurate but I guess
For lack of a better term
If there isn't a better term
That maybe that was amazing was the
When was this published
It just might have been coincidence
Said they put the
He's talking about
That on the same day this article
And it could be coincidence that
He had asked you to write that are
Right
True I wouldn't if I were him either not understand that question
A2B demonstration of
Alex asked you to write this headline or told you to and you knew you couldn't not do it
And there is an embedded headline of his
Covering this news story in the way he told you to cover it
Using your article as the justification for it it's just
It's a damning indictment of of them as
I mean I think this whole deposition is really just a horrific portrait of how they work
Internally
That's mind-boggling to me absolutely mind-boggling to me
How is it
That you have been on these cases
For so f****** long
As one of Infowars as lawyers
But at no point in time did you think
Man we should really explain the kitten not to tell the truth
Or not try to give up everything
I think that this is an acceptable way to act I don't think so I think this I think it didn't know any better
Risen
Direct he couldn't recognize the roads he was being walk down
And I think
Vet
I think that comes back to that naivete and I think
I think that the
Dominus in the stupidity that he manifests
Comes out in a lot of ways
With him not recognizing some of the stuff that he's reporting is completely
Batshit and nonsense
And then the naivete comes he doesn't realize
Like where these questions are leaving Adventurer Vines to be like this you're weird weird
The conversation not having very much a dude who is just operated tea or Lyon
I'd like reward or punishment scale his entire life where they
If I don't ask these questions I get a reward they give me a bonus
How many might as well get $15,000 a year to not ask questions about this I wouldn't be surprised if that
And then he's a butt into I just
This is
Soul
F****** sad that is
It is so sad
It's a bummer all around I think I think it's a bummer because
This is obviously
Far from the only example of stories that
Get his shanked
It's just the one where someone talked to sue them and
It's
There's also a depressing aspect of it that is
From the beginning of it work this is the only person we've ever seen who has had any
Discernible sense that they need to do better in response to this negative feedback early
And it also doesn't matter
You know it's it's because of utility too if it comes out weird
Not weird I think one of the things that makes it
Easier to feel sympathy for kit
Is just because
Regardless of his whatever relative intelligence or or Preparation or anything along
He's just not equipped
To handle a conversation like
Yeah what do you mean some gas in his bag of
Of abilities and so
The problem here is that bill could not be more equipped
Right so it's it's very much a f****** night on a horse with a lance against
A dude holding his underwears over his head
And it's like
That's not fair even if it was Hitler holding his underwear over his head
You be like well this isn't a fair fight
I want Hitler to die but I mean this is just kind of excessive right
And I think I think that's the other difficult part is the keeping in mind
Well metaphorically yeah it's like how much sympathy do you really
Leave to expand for someone
Who is in a situation where he's way in over his head but also is part of it
Toxic
Horrible infrastructure has led to so many people being hurt
Ultimately ultimately what we're watching is nothing is not a beat down or anything like that it is a Man simply receive
Consequences for his actions
Calling audible Isaac we should split this into two episodes
I think that we you should join us Friday for the Owen Shroyer.
Frankly we're at three and a half hours or so right now and if we do and on I don't know what the
What kind of time we're going to be at
I appreciate that our listeners do enjoy long episode do yeah but we have our limits and I think it's
Prospect of a 6 hour episode is too much for anybody little taxing so
Is a bait-and-switch but I assure you Friday we will pay off with the old
The headliner
I think
Weird
Pinky say
You say just about everything you need to say about this deposition by playing it and then also say
There's a bit of analysis some stuff out but I think it really speaks for itself
I've been a lot of ways of just like
This is the level of care that is given when you're reporting something that has the potential
Drastically impact people's lives
Totally
Don't care until there's
They don't want to
I mean it used is just
So much of like
Children they're just children nobody ever explained like that
Hot
Hot stuff
Well and I can teach when other people touch it hurts
So don't touch
So we will be back Jordan Hindi we will her another little glimpse into the deposition world
World of Alex Jones Coronavirus
All but until then we website.com
Cxk
And now here comes
What the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work