Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them posing
Knowledge vype.com
Ojo
Oh my bright spot today Dan is a new album well it's not as new as I would have liked but I just caught up with
I wish it was yesterday so I could be even cooler actually when you find out the album
Otherwise
New Radicals who is one of my favorite
Jazz pianist covid-19 70's from a couple months ago
Robert Glasper though is specific cuz he works in the R&B a lot he provides a lot of hooks he provides all kinds of stuff
Suffern all kinds of people but he is himself an incredibly talented
Jazz pianist and songwriter and I f****** love it
For you to enjoy always
Three-way mustard in it
At least not as unhealthy as rulers like
We'll meet in the middle. Every way too soft
Serve do ice cream it is the best
I will hear no other argument frozen yogurt better
Better than frozen yogurt better than ice cream better okay better than what other Frozen things are there
A popsicle
Welcome back.
In 600 something episodes we have never done what would you describe as a two-parter I don't think
According this directly after we should go to the Lassiter
I suppose the closest would be obviously our documentaries wherein we
Obviously why would Stan
Are episodes irregularly two-and-a-half 3 hours long why would we do a two-parter other people do to part as a good point
We do five parts reflecting on a two-party
We will be getting into deposition
Blackjack
This is a fun thing about this is
It's to the Daria and Alex depositions that took place the next days after that
Unfortunately the timing didn't work out that I could have been
At the Owen deposition but it was it was right in that ballpark right around the same time
Watch the cock Destroyer be destroyed this was the nearest of mrs.
The legends
I'm so we'll get down to business on this year is deposition
New Wok
Alicia's or you walk
Anime
Next happy birthday clown space and Hootie bunter me love you long time thank you so much right now policy walk
Thank you very much I don't think so easy beef
Hugh you are such a policy walk here and I'll probably walk
Could you very much for the adaptus mechanicum thank you
A really gotten punished with these today
GM's professional elbow pads
I'm a policy wonk thank you very much thank you
The Kid Daniel's deposition Marcel Fontaine case
Being a targeted Lee focused to kit and his behavior
This we're back on the Sandy Hook business deep but
Owen Shroyer is the person who did the video that was defamatory towards Neil
In response to the Megyn Kelly interview
And so there is actually a bit more of an angle in that you're not really provided when
Walking with a
Cuz it was actually Owens
He was on the ground that the prompted a lot of this
That's that's pretty interesting position I'm excited for a couple things
Particularly something we're going to get into pretty pretty early
But first
We must learn
As we always do with all these depositions
Hey bro
How much you make it
How much money do you make from Free Speech systems is a salary or hourly
Celery
What's your salary
Give or take
Currently about just over 100,000 a year after taxes
After taxes 100000
I don't know the exact number
I think it's about
I think before taxes is just over 120 after tax I think it's just
When is not worth that
Text figures for Owen Shroyer I can't believe that he's bringing in
A commensurate amount of money I just can't believe it I mean come on
Over replacement is low that is brutal
All but that's I guess how it works over there man you just everybody makes about $100,000
That's it's just not fair it's got to be shut up money to someone something along those lines so
Sometimes you wonder about the how how did you end up in this place how did you get to
Bit of Owens backstory mechanics of it
Did you apply to Infowars or what did they reach out to you
They reached out to
And by day who is they
My first professional contact with Infowars I'm guessing would have been from Rob do
RAB do
From who
Robert
And was that an email or call
Come meet you
Maybe both
But the first request was to just do an interview on air
Then they asked if I wanted to come down for
Hey
Interview for a job
When I came down to Austin for that
Summer of 2016
Goodyear job and I accepted
When you got when you accepted the job was was your job
What was your job
At the time
Field reporter
Every once awhile I would do live
Feeling hosting
Live on air
I was doing a lot of video editing at the time then as well
So I would say it's hard titles
Reporter
Editor
Journalist
Yeah
And
Has your job changed since you started
Far as the day-to-day yes
But
There's never really been up
Professional title Persei slapped on me
Sit here today you're still a journalist
Yeah for the most part I've still been doing the same
You said for the most part other than being a journalist what else
Thanks you too
Longest
Referring to
I'm now live
3 hours a day versus back then
I may not have even been live one minute today
Depending on the day
This does not become as big an issue as it was me kick the argument about what is or is not
On-air a lot more now pretty clear
So as we know from listening to the show around this time. Before Owen got hired he was a guy who'd call into Allen
What's the show every now and again. Is a guest but is it just a random caller
At the same time he was posting videos on YouTube where you going and probably way more
Important for his portfolio than any of the sports journalism work he had done in the past
If you go back to before he worked at Infowars to find some interesting things
You can find some coverage of him for protesting police tyranny in the wake of the Michael Brown killing in Fergus
Missouri
Just outside his home town of St Louis
Interesting Lee if you consult this press coverage including an article in the st. Louis Post-Dispatch
You find that Owen wasn't totally forthcoming when Bill in this deposition asked him about his previous
Employment before he got to working it Infowars
He was doing sports journalism some Youth Development some odd jobs like DJing
There's something you didn't mention
Probably not Material as an emission like he was hiding something but
Go from 10 to midnight on 1380 a.m. in St Louis
As is the case with a lot of radio stations 1380 a.m. went through a lot of format changes over the course of its lifetime
I'm sure it had stretches of the top 40 station a gospel Outlet in a couple runs a Sports Talk
But just prior to 2014 it had one of the most bizarre radio formats I've ever heard
This station with the call letters kfxn was a sister station with another talk station out of
St. Louis kfnx
These two stations decided to Brand themselves the man and the woman with each breath
They thought would appeal to either men or women
I am excited to hear the results and it was a bad idea that sounds pretty fast
Yes
Kfns was the man station but decided it would go back to his Sports Talk format after the flop
Kxfm
But they ended up syndicating just the Yahoo sports feeds
I've got a plan for you okay
How about we immediately exclude half of our Audience by the same people
Right okay so then how about let's immediately exclude half of their auditions it's a great idea
After this kfxn decided to switch it up again and they were branded themselves as BX
Extreme talk radio
The Hope was appeal to an appeal to like an edgier audience or at least do an experiment to see if the station geared towards
What's up like that could work for advertisers and break even or make a profit
This was when towing at a time slot on air if you take what he saying in the st. Louis Post-Dispatch article about his protest
Face value
It doesn't seem like he's necessarily the worst person you would encounter on it extreme talk station
He was out at the I-64 overpass with a sign saying quote tyranny is here
The new goal was protesting the government overreach in the aftermath of the shooting
He told the papers at the protesters quote don't deserve to your gas and guns pointed at them
Which would sound fine if we didn't have natural suspicions based on where his career ended up leaving at 1.
Extreme talk station didn't work out at least partially due to the complete chaos of the person running the cup
Company that owned the station a guy named Dan Marshall would you say he might have been too extreme to
Put on their personalities were willing to go on the record by name and talk s*** to the Post-Dispatch like Jay Randolph Jr
Atmosphere at the station like this
Quote it's like nothing I've ever seen it like every man for himself
This was a guy with a job this was a guy with decades and radio
Behind him so the situation had been pretty sure I had to call my way out of a closet
That was because a fight your way out of there with Nick when you clock out completely insane
From there they were allegations of people not being paid a mother and other unsavory reports about Marshall's leadership
But some people sided with Marshall and there was a bit of a civil war that broke out between the two sides
What host on kfns a guy named Charlie tuna who is black
Became the target of some racially insensitive comments made by Nick trupiano at kxfm host who was upset
Tuna didn't like Marshall while trupiano did
Brian McKenna another kxfm hose to it spoke out against Marshall
This led to McKenna's showing up at kfns and trying to fight trupiano I love it security intervene
However a short time later McKenna and Marshall got into a fist fight
You can't follow him around the rest of the day he was appointed to fight the host and then ended up there
Fighting football
Remarkable
The Host
Dogs got into a literal fist fight with the station manager
And when reached for comment Marshall said quote
I spent the night in the hospital he spent the night in jail you can draw your own conclusions about what happened
I'll give you that one
11 is it Owen's experience working in an environment like this made him think of the way Alex acts towards his employees is somehow
Normal or acceptable
I need to recreate the issues that I was born in order to
Owen wasn't there long because they didn't last more than like six months
For the station went back to his Sports format and then eventually just started leasing the airtime out
I meant eventually they'd outright sold to Salem media only
This story is a fascinating piece of Americana
Completely out of control work environment
Illustrate why he puts up with Alex's ethereal stock does it matter
I think the stories great explaining it was one of the only ways that I can introduce one of the greatest things I've
Sounded preparing this episode
When is been kicked off of online platforms but one that he hasn't been booted from and he probably doesn't even realize
Is he still on
Is SoundCloud
As fate would have it in 2016 he posted a demo reel on Soundcloud do you like fishing for a job at ND
Do not tell me that this is his audition reel for Infowars
Ask him to do or if he did it just to get Rob's attention in the first place but either way this thing is amazing
One level
Painfully transparent as an attempt on his part to do and Alex impression
But on the other hand it's also recording of an idiot complaining about nothing getting mad for no reason for him
I honestly can't tell if he's our clips from his kxfm show or he just recorded himself in his free time but I choose to believe
Leave it to the ladder because I didn't adjust really funny like that
Is 20 minutes long and no one but me should have to sit through all of that
It's too long for a demo reel time and been like that
Going to the trash
5 seconds I remember when I was trying to get into voiceover work it was like you have a minute
If that no I went to had a whole recording session I did the whole thing and all the experience people were like
Like that was great you're never going to get hired by anybody stop it
So I will say one thing
When comes out the gate pretty hot for all of this because
Every game
They salute a veteran
They they they give him tickets for the game
And then during a break they put the camera on them
The fee IPA guy comes on instead
Salute to the veterans you know so-and-so
Just like the conditioning
Everybody stands up and cheers you know and if you don't everybody looks you weird or kind of your nose says you're a jerk or whatever
How about instead of just putting them on camera and standing up and cheering like a bunch of vapid moron
Why do we give him a mic
What's give him 30 seconds or a minute to beat their mine
How about that
Well we can't have that we don't know what they might say
Oh
Political correctness speak at the game are you say you want to order
We don't want to see reading a transcript of Alex's show like two days before this I could have absolute
More transparent than his current work certainly
That's weird because it feels like he's doing impression now
But poorly disguised impression
How about we just tell him to do it
I don't know why you're mad
You mad on their behalf for a complete that I've never heard anybody make never ever once
So you're this next clip is proof that Owen is is Brave
He's a man of action
Trying to wake people up I'm sick of these cheer Annika Lindley
Butchers plays because they get to get where's my wallet
$1 bill
This is worth noting that a lighter in here
Federal Reserve Note the Federal Reserve is a Rothschild Secret
He's willing to performatively threaten to burn a $1 bill that he's also willing to spread lies and bulshit for Alexandra
Exchange for 100,000 of those bills principal
Give it a lighter, my God he is just recording this on his own it is
Surrounded
Very very much and Alex Joseph it is it is
Be offended if I were Alex
If I were Alex listen to this and be like oh my God is that what people think I sound like what a bless you were specifically trying to find a
The younger version of yourself ohmygod that's what people sounds like
Yeah you're Alex you kind of have to deal with that early
Yeah I think I think if you would like
I don't know
Considering the possibility of needing an acolyte or something like that maybe like how I see myself in him right boom
He also has more complaints about the dollar bill make you believe that
I'm at the pyramid on the back
Why is there a pyramid on the back of the dollar bill
Boat over the pyramid on the dollar bill
Stop it. Illuminati
In God We Trust
Separation of church and state guess that's just total
Baker
You like your little Ralph Ralph dollar
Play keep walking
He can really see the Alex impression they're painful
Paper that's a direct expression even though Alex was just doing impression of Rush Limbaugh when he does it
The weird after work
Alex
How he's like a separation of church of my God it's it's so awesome because you can
Conceived mind working in a way that like you could have prepared
You could have got your thoughts together or whatever but it's into that
Point that you didn't intend to make
I am going to throw this out there I think I have a theory on this. Is he is actually reading info
Towards transcripts after having listened to the clips and trying to do the exact same thing
That's my theory on there because the timing of all of that
The the absolute change of the the tone of voice volume control
That suggests to me that he is listen to Alex say exactly those Alex is going to take the time to be like why we let vet
Veterans speak at football games go
Why
I don't know I just don't help it went to his issues that one might not be I think that one was
Maybe
But he also has more complaints about the dollar
Some great quote from Washington
Burleigh George Washington arms
To the colonies
Or like a powerful quote from Thomas Jefferson like I have sworn upon the altar of
Annuit coeptis
Novus ordo
I don't speak
Psycho
All American
He's mad at Latin
Okay alright so are we in that new Theory
This is an open mic that I luckily missed somewhere around 2016
Yeah
Complaints about
Jokes that people told 30 years ago
Really to illustrate Owens chops
Obviously it can get worse
As far as
In your face
It really can't get any worse anymore
It is all in
Your
Right in your face
I need
Only if it's in your face
For some reason Towing decided to include a meeting with clip-in is demo reel races it's in your face four times at 22 second
Eddie
Is obviously shallow applicantpool Lovett
I'm not going to be able to get over how many times he said in your face I will guarantee you
He does not say it in this deposition at all he does not accuse things are being in your face
So we're in the clear now all I can say is that just by that
Demo demo reel
I can tell you that guy's going to be working at Infowars I would look at that guy and you got the good
Do you know what in six years you're going to get sued
Got to have them
Deposition begins off friendship
Cuz what is the most important thing in the world friendship you bet
How's your relationship
I would say good I mean there's elements of friendship and then there's elements of Boss
An employee but
Is my dad
Would you consider him your best friend
No
Does he consider you his best
I doubt it
That's so weird
The weird McCormick restaurant in Bell
Do like that almost ideas
What cuz what is
We're going to say is it going to say
Yeah Alex think Alex probably thinks I'm his best friend
Well if I don't think Alex is my best friend has the question of does he
What's going on right now it comes up this question is asked
You have other
I would say if if
If it was one it would be
Rob do buds
But knock knock
Not really
And
You and mr. do have a personal relationship as well as
That relationship like
Best friends
You got to be confused I think that's what he's doing that's my. I think Bill is deliberately
They just throwing this s*** around
Problem just alike f*** with almonds head assume so
Who is your best friend
Play Luis Marshall
I did expect
Something to come to the conclusion
I think that's the issue with Owen is he was hosting for Alex on a son
Show and someone just gave him an article that he used to laugh
That Neil heslin could not have held his son after the shooting
That's the reason he's in trouble
And unfortunately it turns out I remember who gave him the
How did you learn about that article
It was presented to me
That
Day as I was on
By who
I do not recall
So you got it after 4
Yes
And when it was presented to you did they just hand you a copy the article
Pretty much
I mean my best recollection in this is no just trying to dig into my memory is
I'm in studio
Someone comes in and says hey here's a story
We also have the video clips for it
And then
We live and I mentioned Astorian
Okay so who handed it to me
I do not recall
That's not good because this
Yeah bad information that was given to you and now you're on the hook for it because you reported it
And could conceivably help
Send out the blame if you knew who was responsible for
Giving you this information becomes a compounded problem because he's asked who could have given it to you
And it's basically like
Not just anyone
Sunday show
You're filming and I'm assuming
Mr. Jones is Not president
That's fine or standing if I'm filling in
Most likely
And
Who has the authority
If he's not there
To find a story
Cut
A number of clips
Into a small segment and
Hand it to you and give you the authority to
Go With It live
I would say anybody has that
Story
Cuz not really
Authority
Figure that has
Beside that anybody can bring me a story
Any given time
It's not going to be somebody that tries to stop me
You're reading it or try to
Stop
There should be quality control
There should be a certain amount of like
That's not the proper Channel
You shouldn't be able to have like the boom mike operator give a story directly to the host and then they report it yet
The boom operator maybe you should talk to the news director or something right in like
Pass this along
People everyone should be allowed to speak their mind quality control on some level
I mean I would say that if I were in a deposition
Of this kind of magnitude
My first instinct would be avoid
Saying something along the lines of
Really when you get down to it
Everybody's involved to equally
What was the problem with answering any other way than what he says x y and z
People
Wasn't it this person
Do you know it wasn't there we got Dawn Salazar he wasn't Nico or whatever and you know it
That leads to more trouble
Actually you know what I think it was a complete stranger who just broke into our office would be handed me this story I read it out loud
Because that's how this could have been
So
We know from covering pass depositions that Alex is to have told people to not cover
Sandy Hook
After a certain point
I'm so the question is asked as Alex ever told you not to cover anyting I am turns out
Has he ever told you not to
Cover
A certain story
Not that I recall
So if you wanted right now
Go in studio when you leave here
Do wholesale
About how you think Sandy Hook
Jackson Ford
I could and I might guess is I would get quite a tongue lashing
Afterwards
But he wouldn't stop
The mic is on the cameras on where live
I mean other than coming in studio to tackle me
Turning it off
No
Stick this is a terrible workflow I am amazed that they can function
Yeah
I mean really
It is it is a testament
Not to their skills at anything that they are supposed to be doing it is Owen not does he not recognize that
They have a delay
Like cuz they may not for the internet
But like for the radio stations they can bleeps cuss words they ain't they do that.
It's like I don't know like there has to be some kind of a delay that's possible he starts going off about us Sandy Hook
You got it. You and then something goes
Goes away yeah yeah
I think it's a terrible organization to the Vic anybody can give me whatever information they want.
And also you can stop by or cutting the feed
Right this is this is a recipe for for defamation
They are describing how their business works
It is a business entirely geared towards eventually being sued for defamation
Yep it's sloppy
It revealed so much about the editorial in a working so how these articles are written and how they're used
Here you seeing like the live show and how the f*** he had isn't treated
The structure is ridiculous
But I went just reads whatever someone handsome
What happened here
It's not a normal
Fraction form
I mean
I would say
Yes and know it's a normal occurrence in that
It's a new story
We're live news organization there's constantly news coming in and out of my desk
But
And I would also say no it's not it's not like
Everyday or every segment someone says hey
Hear this news stories breaking right now
Right but what I'm saying is not
Common is the fact that you're live on air
Somebody hands you document says we're running with this we got Clip Tray
That's not a common currency usually it's something that
Is fact-check
You see the different video clips that you're going to talk through in a year
Yeah I mean in this instance it's really just kind of a momentum thing you know cuz
Download say there's a developing story on offering example
So there's an ongoing story
If somebody was bringing me stuff as I'm on are just updates to the story
In this case
The reason why there was momentum to this is because Megyn Kelly was just in town
She was in the news
So there was already all this momentum about Megyn Kelly
We saw that she was in the zerohedge article and that's why they brought it
Was it any
Was any of the retaliatory for miskellys
Betrayal mr. Jones and her interview with him the week
Couple
I can't even recall
The dates if that
Aired before after the segment in question here so I wouldn't say retaliatory I would just
It was it was relevant
This is this is weird that's a weird perspective
Yeah I knowing when things happened because there's just a concrete reality has brought up in this next clip
He's like his video was responding to Megan Kelly
Video about Alex how did you do that
Prior to her that we can all see through the veil of Illusion in the right
Forever on the psychic but this is just not possible
Have you watched the
The video and question
Which video
5-minute video where you're on are talking about Neil heslin son
Yes
What was the last time you washed it
During
My latest episode Shannon
Connecticut
And in that video
Surely you realize that
75% of 8
Is the Megyn Kelly interview
That happened
Before
You went on air
Talkin about the
Yeah I believe she was interviewing
Because you said I don't remember if the Megyn Kelly interview came out before I get
Well I guess what I should have said is I'm not aware
It was the same Megyn Kelly show
I got you
That's that's bad that the bad dog have said is that
This is something that not a lot of people know space and time are one thing and then if you put enough energy into the
The sinkhole of space-time
Then it's possible to pierce through create a wormhole and go back in time or really forward into
Could go anywhere the point I'm saying is that I got there for days ago
So we're holding side
I think that has a pretty
Bad explanation
What he was trying to say in this video
But I think he thinks it sounds good
I think he thinks this is very escopitory and it's nonsense
Yes
Did you use the word opossum
I believe so I remember the exact quote
Remember what you're talkin about
No
You were talking about a dead sexual
And you said it was impossible for that six-year-old father
Propelled his son
With a bullet hole
Based on what you
I've read and received
My conclusion was not that that was impossible my conclusion was that
The
Series of events that I highlight in the videos would indicate that there is
An inconsistency there
And I was more questioning Megyn Kelly
In the instance and if you look at the exact quote
I'm not asserting
That Mr hasn't lied at all what I'm assuming is that Megyn Kelly never did a fact check
And
That
That it was basically impossible
Or that it was I could say what I can say is and again this is asserted in the quote that
Because of the inconsistencies shown in the story
It's going to add to the conspiracy theories about Sandy Hook which are a bad thing why am I tired
When was that
Hear that fancy lawyer
4 conspiracy theories out there they're going to take this and they're going to run with it
Will Megyn Kelly fact check
Meatloaf
I understand your say you were asking question
And at the end of it I think you said you know
People
Answers
Give me
I'm saying that this story is only going to add
To the conspiracy theorists out there
About Sandy Hook in that that's a bad thing and you're saying that because those conspiracy theorists are the ones asking the questions
Bright
I'm not sure exactly what you mean
You you said
Conspiracy theorist
A lot of questions
We want answers
Lavate people have questions and these
This story here is not going to
Stop people from Africa
The questions people like you
This excuses obvious bowl-shaped but there's a couple of remarkable things are on full display here
The first is that Owen is so clearly grasping at straws to explain his video which is a
A strong indication that he knows that the content he was involved in putting out was horrible and indefensible
In order to make it defensible you have to pretend it was something else entirely
The second thing is at the beginning Owen tries to evade the question by saying he didn't remember his exact quote
He's trying to build a rationalization for what he said to help people need
Look at the exact quote
In the space of about a minute you went from not remembering what he said the insisting everyone judge him by the exact wording
Of what he said
It's painfully obvious what game he's playing the underlying point that Owen is trying to make is that he wasn't saying that Neil Hassel include
Have held is on after the shooting
He was saying that Mr heslin's claim made on Megyn Kelly show
Was impossible if the video Owen played of the Newtown coroner was accurate
Owen is claiming that his point was that this is an inconsistency that Megyn Kelly didn't fact check for herpes
And because of that it'll feed into conspiracies which one is pretending is a bad thing as opposed to the only reason anyone would
A hundred thousand dollars a year this is obvious nonsense over the course of a few clips
No I think bill is going to buy it
I think it's just going to accept that that is a well-crafted definitely not in complete
Bulshit on-the-fly
So a bill throws out a quote from Paul intensive use the words
I'm going to read you
Direct quote
He's claiming he is Mister hustling grieving father
He's claiming that he held his son and saw the bullet hole in his head
That is his
Now according to a timeline of events
When corners t'estimo
That is not possible
So
Surely you can agree with me that a reasonable person would hear you say that
And think that
You are basing
The possibility
On the evidence that you are looking
Right
Directions for
I'm not sure I understand the question exactly but
That I believe
What when I'm saying is according to the coroner
The coroner said that they didn't release
The children to the parents
Well I'm going to ask you this
NN you're basing that off of the clips that you played during the second
Yes
So here is the fundamental piece of this why Owens argument doesn't work
If it doesn't stand up to any kind of scrutiny
But Owen has to hold on to this for dear life cuz otherwise he has nothing
I am at is that the coroner's video is accurate it's funny I think I heard Mark whisper
Possible much like you heard it black and the last one
In the nature of what happened with this Coroner's video and
Doesn't stick
In your affidavit you
Do you claim Miskelly
Edited videos
To slam
Mr. Jones
Remember that
Do you think she did that
Yeah
Do you think it's right for a journalist to edit
Clips
For an agenda
No
Do you think it's
Good
Journalistic practices
For a journalist
To take
Edited videos
Ask any questions
And run with
Without fact check
Probably not
Have you listened to
The corner mr. Carver doctor
Carver
Have you listened to his whole interview
Cuz represent to the segment that you played
Cuts off
Immediately after he says he didn't release the chill
But I want to tell you that it keeps going
And he says a lot more
Did you know that
Kind of an important fact
As I was unaware of that especially if you were about to say what you said
About a father who's still
Trying to get over the fact that he had to bury it
And that's awful and I understand that's why I said it's impossible for mr. Headland have a false memory of his dying kid
It because of how serious that would be making is that nice try and have that false memory
So according to the coroner either the coroner is lying
Megyn Kelly just not going to fact-check
Or
Mr. Shroyer
Didn't watch the whole Corners interview and hear the corner say
That he didn't release them at first
And later released the bodies
Maybe that's the third option right
Wilshire that that
Can be true
Good dick can't be true it is true mr. Shroyer
You understand that right
Fraction form
He can say okay that he understands this but he can't actually internalize this in.
Operate under that
Absolutely some information because then it cast
His entire broadcast in a completely different light if he allows that awareness to exist
I'm so this
Notion that the coroner actually made a statement that they didn't release the bodies
Is it is is jumping worth believing and that Megyn Kelly has an obligation to address
It's Insanity have you ever considered that everything is everybody else
This fault and I am a blameless person trying to do my best to save the world well I believe in something completely nonsensical and bass
Bulshit right everyone else has an obligation to in any circumstance
Disprove that or else they are lying what are they are engaging in inconsistencies in a cover-up what I would like
The entirety of the human race to know is that it is your job to accommodate my whims at Alta
Definitely
Obviously there is an internal problem with
Responsibility it Infowars people really
Given
Appropriate feedback people aren't scolded
And so the question comes up
Whatever tell you f***** up
Anyone ever has ever tell you that you were wrong
I don't want to hear the answer to mr. Jones or mr. do
About this litigation at all
Not not too much note
And employers
No one has come to you and told you
That what you said was dead wrong
And that you messed up and use the clip that was highly edited
No and I didn't edit the clip
I did not
Previously music lip it was presented to me
And you just went with
Yes I just played it
Right
No one ever told him that bad work
You screwed up
I don't even know how to handle this everything that we learn about how Infowars actually function
Makes me believe that there's no possible way I can function
Yeah it is really leaves you think of it like
Make the offense so lucky
Spit someone didn't
Like really f*** with them like someone get a job there and just cause chaos
No safeguards
There is no there is no accountability
Anyone can just feed stories to people
It's a x bananas
The odds of them. Falling victim to
Some internal
Then complete sabotages is outraged at this is nuts and I think it's one of those things
It is one of those things
Where everybody just assumes because
It would be ridiculous for it to be possible
But this place function so everybody just assumes like
Well there's that there's got to be some sort of control this every somebody in charge of every somebody doing something right
And the answer is no
No
Just know it doesn't seem like a maybe you're from like a business and like
Fulfillment
Like they're the warehouse I do whatever happened there's accountability
Information on Scott
How many times you been arrested
Your been arrested
How many times
I'm not sure the exact number
Wrong answer
You have you have interested you just lost count
Is it, if you get arrested
Comment but
Probably too much
More than I'd like to
Angel
That's just kind of a fun clip it turns out it's not really that scandalous or anything he's got like a DUI and then
Yeah I tried to stop the impeachment trial
Okay well there's that one too
Giant rap Lewis days or whatever you say I can't really remember how many times I've been a rest
It leads you to believe it's more than like 3 or 4 it's not really
Pretty serious traumatic event that
Filed
And the beginning of it is a little bit funny
Kubiak to exhibit
The affidavit will go down 2 paragraph 2
Right
It says I have been
Frequent
Critic of the government for using tragedies such as Sandy Hook
To manipulate public opinion
In order to
Among other things
Further restrict gun rights in this country
I read that correctly
Yes
What
Do you mean by manipulate public opinion
I mean
Use
Outright lies
To deceive
Public
Okay
Answer this sentence you're not saying the government use Sandy Hook to
Use outright lies to deceive the public you're saying
That
You are a frequent critic
Of the government for using tragedy
2-minute
You to outright lie
Like what
Gulf of Tonkin
Oh my God getting us into the Vietnam War
I'm lying about babies being thrown out of incubators to get us into the Middle East
What's backup
You're a frequent critic of the government for things that happened
Somewhere between 35 and 70 years ago
Okay
When is that come up in conversation
What do you mean
What causes you to be a frequent
Critic
For things like the Gulf of Tonkin and why we got into the Vietnam War
Me I believe it's an issue that has never been properly addressed
Is that the case boy you know I that whole go from talking thing I don't think anybody ever really dealt with it
Emotionally dealt with a Fallout from that is still are I wake up in the middle of the night sometimes
Interview like never talk about slavery ever dealt with it
A million times over
I thought damai I love like this is the phrasing that Owen thought was going to be really perfect and it's just so far
Farcical when repeated it is such that like
Beetle here's here's what it is here's what it's so clear about it is that Alex's f***** with these people's brains
Or they never had it to the point where
Words
Can be just fun
You know like adjectives
Don't need to have mean
They're just there they're just like music notes like what he's saying is that we don't say words that
Have any meaning whatsoever we put together sounds that make a
Functioning noise fear that makes people afraid so they buy it's true
Eternal perspective perspective
Like everything is just fine like whatever explanation you have for something if it's expired
If it works there is no knife sharpening knife here
Google's that does not sharpen Google I've never had such a clear moment of lie
Like
You don't mean
You don't use words you don't understand words like you can't say I have been a frequent critic critic unless you
You are saying that
I mean in the legal setting
You have to complete that seems like an impression of what someone would say
Approximating what a normal person would say here right
Amazing so the question that is refined to all right
What are these instances where the government use these tragedies to restrict gun rights
And shock of all shocks
What did the government do in San Diego
To further restrict gun
I don't know
We swore to God in your affidavit
That
You're a frequent critic of the government using them to further gun rights
Restrictions of gun
God
So help me God
I apologize
You swore under oath
That this was true and you said that
Thanks likes
What I'm asking about
Further restrict gun rights in this country
What did the government do in
Sandy Hook
Further restrict gun rights in this
Well you're asking me to go back
And provide an opinion or commentary on something that
I didn't provide opinion or commentary on at the time
I was not at Infowars when Sandy Hook happened I did no commentary on it when it happened it was not even umbrella
New story to me
But what I recall is
And this seems to be the case most of time is whenever there's a gun tragedy maybe less now than
Other times
There's politicians go on TV and say we need
New
Gun laws we need new gun
Restriction
And that's just that seems
Be a pattern of behavior
Okay
I understand that you weren't there for this the initial Sandy Hook coverage
But you just want to roll
But this was
This was your words
And you said that the government
Uses
Things like Sandy Hook to manipulate public
Further restrict gun rights I'm just asking you
They take a tragedy
Like kids getting
Shot in the school
And they say because of that event
We're going to further infringe on your Second Amendment right
For an event that you had nothing to do with
When did they do that
When did they do what cuckoo
Said
Captain we're going to restrict your second
Who said that
Give me an example
I couldn't give you
It seems like a problem that's an issue
Stupid, you should be able to
Point out what stories have you gotten your money tonight
Right we're stricter gun rights I do like bills bills very clearly got this
Very obvious point
But Owen has no idea is coming toward them right
Like he's very clearly
Dismantling the idea that
The politicians are doing what it is you're saying they're doing just simply
Give him his own words
That will reveal that he is in fact the person who is doing those things
And he has no concept of this
I don't think of that
Do people who are paranoid
About everything
I don't know if these people who are going in for the deposition are worried enough about where they're being led mean
88th and Lloyd the lawyer here's the thing I want to focus on
Why did the lawyer say
Objection he didn't swear to God
I don't know I'm not sure I want to know more about that one because it seems like that would be very important
They are always talking about Christianity but maybe that was why the
The objections are like you're stressing that too much that's what I'm saying yeah you're making this sound like a religious thing as opposed to
You know just a formality of legal Riley
Maybe maybe maybe weighs maybe that's how it would understand that maybe it's not I don't know
So
The question comes up
You think your informed about Sandy Hook do you think that that is something you know about about answers obviously no
This point
After
Your involvement in this case for 3 years
And your
Affidavit
Mostafa David's
As well as your
Couple episodes
On Infowars about Sandy Hook would you say you're you're informed.
No I've barely talked about Sandy Hook
I asked you if you talk about us
About it it's kind of a fake question
I agree
And I ask you this because
The number of times I've watched some of your YouTube videos you walking around at Rally's
And asking people
The name accusers
Call Donald Trump
And you start
Because you said yeah cuz I'm in
Thorndike and
So I'm just asking you to name names
Name names of what
Of any government official you claim used Sandy Hook
Further restrict
Termites
I have to go back in time
The right now see here today you weren't
Uninformed
Citizen
Injection form
Correct
I would say that
If you could
Catalog
My entire career and media
Sandy Hook
Makes up for less than
00 0.1 per cent of Mike
Anyway was that response
I think it is very response
What was my question
You asked if I would be informed on Sandy Hook
Yeah
You said
Hell is only 1% of everything that I do
Are you at Sandy Hook is not my bread-and-butter I don't know much about Sandy Hook
3-run informed it's okay to say I'm not trying to trick you
Just trying to see if it were not you think you're under your informed or not so
I know whether or not I need to ask anymore questions on that
Are you informed about Sandy
Again it's a big question yes and no I'm aware of Sandy Hook
But
Have I done deep Research into my very knowledge roll musculation
Do you know Mister hustling son
It's such a simple question in line of questioning about the case
Weird dynamic
Attitude is just as important or more important than content
Has been trained to resist ever showing his ass
He made his name by going at the hostile territory and arguing with people he was calling them Cox so even though he's in
Completely different setting gear that mode is still a part of how he interacts
I suspect to come out and say that he's not important about Sandy Hook because he's worried that the next question will be yr
Weren't you informed about Sandy Hook really good question good answer for that
If you're Hannibal why wouldn't you learn a little bit about the case
He's been in a lawsuit for a while and beyond that is a big deal and online conspiracy communities that makeup
A large part of his audience
Seems like you'd be curious at least
Admit to being uninformed by Sandy Hook reveals the lack of curiosity and a lack of interested in knowing things which is counter housing forward
Supposed supposed to position themselves in terms of branding
It also opens up a line of questions that aren't going to come up in this deposition but I'll still probably worried about it
Namely whether or not he's informed on many of the other topics he covers
Like for instance is he informed on the Gulf of Tonkin incident
Good-o incoherently explain what happened Beyond just catchphrase version of like
The government lied to get us into the Vietnam War
I would suspect not and what are the really important aspect of Infowars kayfabe
Is the image that the people working there know a lot about the things that they talk about
Also not knowing a child's name is actively disrespectful Owens park
If you were truly someone who made an honest mistake and covered the story wrong and it ended up hurting this grieving father
You would think that Owen would have familiarized himself a little bit with the circumstances
If only to be able to fully apologize for the cause
And it's clearly not something that he's
Felt inclined to do
Yeah I mean what's he going to say I've been advised by Infowars lawyers to know as little about this case as possible
That's making my answers to you perhaps less damaging to the company although now that you have said that out
Allowed I'm starting to think that it's the wrong it looks like s***
His refuge and the thing that he thinks is going to save him is this notion that he was
Question Megyn Kelly
He wasn't questioning Neil heslin said that there were inconsistencies and Megyn Kelly
One thing
That I do both appreciate and don't appreciate because it moves us on our stupid be evil Continuum more
Towards the evil side
Is that it does appear that Owen has a kind of plan here
He is got like
If I stick to the plan
Then I'll be able to keep on going if I insisted this was just about Megyn Kelly
Through this and if he lets say
Ask me a bunch of questions that I'm not sure about don't know the answers to I should definitely not volunteer information like at Daniels
Yeah you can tell pretty
Obvious difference between the two of them
We get back to this just questioning Megyn Kelly
I I never had any intention
Go after
Mr. heslin I never accused Mr heslin of lying I never meant to do anything negative to mister Haslam
Instead
You took an interview that he
Did with Megyn Kelly
And said based on the corners report and based on this cuz Megyn Kelly didn't say how this done
Neil heslin
So when you said it was impossible
You would call him a liar
Right
Questioning Megyn Kelly
I was questioning the corner
And I was wondering why Megan genuine factcheck dad
More as again just
Just because Ben Kelly was in studio she was in the news
And it was just something that was Ellen
And she's a journalist so
That should be packed
Yeah I mean if she wanted to fact-check that and put the conspiracy theories to rest she could have done it right there and she did
But if she didn't have a highly edited
Did clip like you that made it look like
The coroner said
The parents never saw their kids
Why on Earth would she
Prove
That Neil has been held his son
Mr. Hassan was going to say
I held my son I saw the gun wound and they can Kelly's follow-up to that was like
Yeah because the coroner told us they didn't give them to you the kids at first but then later did
That's
Houses playing in your head right now I'm so confusing me
Yeah I mean I have no idea what Megyn Kelly had access to as far as if she'd ever seen the corner saying that or not
I've no idea
This is a great encapsulation of an impossible task it is to question propagandists
Owens claim is that there's a contradiction that Megyn Kelly wasn't addressing that only makes sense if
And only if
You believe that the deceptively edited clip of the corner it is the coroner's complete statement right if you don't
Believe that or if you seen the full video that this isn't something that needs clearing up
Miss Rosalind said what he said there's no contradiction at all
There's only contradiction if you think that b******* video is the full truth which by extension means that you believe that there is
Is a contradiction then you're revealing that you either know the truth and are liar or you don't know the truth and you're just
Speeding in a horrible and defamatory claims without ever considering
How do you check and see if they're not fact-checking while you clearly have not fact-checked
I think
That we could solve a lot of problems before this deposition if we just took one sentence of the thing they said on their show
Go and ask them to diagram a sentence you know like noun
Verb direct object like I really don't think they understand how we're really into grammar today really struggling because
Is it keep asking questions words like if you understood how a sentence work then you would just say yeah
Yeah
Reality bring this up as a testament to her doing a better job checking facts than Ellen
She didn't fall for that internet b******* and she's not under no obligation to dispel every potentially inaccurate think so man
Mike Fink represent the contradiction in a grieving father story
One doesn't feel an obligation to pass along true information
For him the video of the coroner was true in the sense that it existed and who cares if the full clips of the opposite of the additive
Somebody plays on air
Truth of the police objective thing to him and as long as he can claim that he didn't know the version he presented as truth with a lie
But he doesn't feel that need to be ashamed of himself nor
Does he feel the need to learn a lesson from this and try to do better the next time like it expressed
Feline
It's just because truth and falsity don't matter
The ultimate aim is what appeals to the audience to buy their product
That is what dictates truth and reality to someone like Ellen
And then you have to do s*** like this analyzed it in case you ever called on it in a
Deposition
My job is to lie about s*** quick
Is that what you want to say
Little Caesars
I'm ready
So he's just questioning Megyn Kelly though that's the that's the thing that's import
Except for when
Bill Reeves a direct quote from the video that really makes it seem like he's questioning mr. has
During
The segment
This is a transcript of it
Of the video
Direct quote hero
Will do well will there be clarification from
Hessler Megyn Kelly
I wouldn't hold my
So when you say you weren't
Questioning mr. Haslam
Is very good
Can you clarify
Sure
They never responded to the corners
Claims that I played in the video
So that's what I was saying so because they don't watch your show
Psyllium for Sunday Alex Jones
Because they didn't see it here your question and respond
That's what you said
I'm not understanding what
I'm not either
So here you can see again always arguing completely falls apart if he accepts the claims he's ascribing to the corner word
Not made by the corner at all
Owen fell for a deceptively edited video and then believe that the coroner had made claims that he didn't make
And now he's justifying his coverage of the case based on how suspicious it seems that Megyn Kelly and mr. hassling didn't
Address these claims that the corner in reality didn't make
That's why this exchange is bordering on incoherent
Because Owen is still clean to this pretense that they were actual legitimate claims that Kelly and that's when we're dodging and he was just trying to
Make sure all these contradictions are ironed out
That's his foothold on his actions making any sense outside the reality that he was in fact
Very clearly trying to imply that mister Haslam could not have held us up
I'm get more straightforward then literally the quote that was read to you right and I think I think
I mean honestly I don't know I don't know exactly how things work in the legal world but I think that this
The argument that he's making
Makes it so much clearer that he had nefarious solutely
Best you got this is s*** that's that's shameful
Belligerence that he's trying to stick to it it's very frustrated does not relent
No unfortunately weaving into a little bit of a question
About free speech
This is problem
It's not my job
To clarify Megyn Kelly's reporting
Why would
Right
Yes
The great statement
Is it your job to repost
A repost
From an anonymous writer
Question Megyn Kelly
I think that's just free speech
Right sure
You know what isn't free speech
When actually
It was backup
You said free speech
What does that mean
Ono Ono this definition is going to be a struggle to get through
You said free speech
What does that mean
You're not
You're crazy in the coconut
The right to
Address grievances to government
Speak
Without inherent consequence
Okay and that's across-the-board
I mean
I think that you know
Any legal expert would agree that free speech
It's not Universal
Correct like defamation
Did you know that
Okay so when you say
Is my free speech First Amendment right
You know that the first amendment protects you from
From the government
I'm Free Speech right nut other citizen
You know that right
Did you know that until I just said it
I probably wouldn't have phrased it like that but it makes sense
Right it's shocking but also not unexpected that though and doesn't seem to understand what the
The first amendment is about but
I got stuck on another thing that he said In that clip
He said the free speech and his understanding involves the right to speak without inherit consequence that I say what the f*** does
Is that even mean
All speeches consequence because speeches a means of conveying things between persons
If you tell somebody you love them that has a consequence which will depend on how they feel about you
Could be a good, but something happens
Similarly if you yell a racial slur at someone there's always a consequence
Maybe you get hit or maybe that person is restrained but there's still a consequence of emotional pain that's been in for
There is no speech without consequence because speech doesn't exist in a vacuum
The reason I think this is really fascinating is because I want understanding of this is that free speech is speech
Consequences
When it's he who's speaking
There isn't a concern at all for the consequences experienced by the other people involved in the speech
It's really just a childish mentality that kind of boils down to I get to say whatever I want if anyone's mad about it there press
I understand and I appreciate the desire and even the necessity of protecting speech from too much censorship
But to not really understand the dynamic nature of speech particularly when you work at a place called Free Speech systems
Mobile strikes me as a mark of a very shallow selfish mind
Grasping
I would like
The legal definition of free speech involves the government concept of free speech
Between persons
Always have a consequence
It may not be you get sued every time
But there's a consequence
Inherent consequence to me suggests that what he is
At the conversations that he's been having where inherent consequence would come up
Essentially would mean to me that he saying
I should be able to say the n-word and people shouldn't be offended cuz I said the n-word
Or just any words that has inherent consequence to me do you know what I'm saying that's where the right-wing version
Consequence
That's ridiculous
She's around people who don't mind him saying
Ecstatic
Government is
I'm telling you this is f****** just depression is absolute insanity aggrievement
Everybody should have to have the First Amendment on their wall and it should be highlighted it should be tattooed on his arm like
We make the mark of the beast the First Amendment
No chance.
We get back to this idea of like what restrictions happen
After the shootings and it's just
With regards to paragraph to in this affidavit
You can't think of a single government action
That
Was made to further restrict gun rights
Related to Sandy Hook
Correct
Now. My head
Why'd you put it in your affidavit put what exactly
The first sentence of paragraph to that says
I've been a Critic of the government
Freezing things like Sandy Hook
To manipulate public opinion
In order to
Among other things
Further restrict gun rights in this country
Why'd you put that in there
If you can't think of an instance
Related
Where's that actually at
Ejection form
I not say I didn't say it had anything to do with Sandy Hook it says such as Sandy Hook so I'm not saying that there was any
Anything following Sandy Hook all my guy just meant as a general
Saying when there's tragedy is dealing with guns
Usually there's a follow-up
Of a proposal of Morgan
Legislation and stretch
But not in Sandy
Not that I'm aware
So if it didn't happen
Why didn't this happen
Because this entire case is about
Right
So
But if it's none of this happened why did you add it into the next tenant to start there
Because the full case is about Sandy Hook and is again it says such as Sandy Hook so I'm not saying
It is after Sandy Hook I meant such as Sandy Hook because this case is about
Okay so such as you mean like so when there's like a
Mass shooting
Sure okay
Name a mass shooting where anti-gun legislation is immediately
I couldn't name off the top my head
KT I'm heading out
You know the fun fact is I can't either
Which is why I'm trying to figure out why this sentence is in there
It's tough
It's tough when you have to really go over this affidavit and be like why did you say this
Basically that any governmental action
That took place after the gun
To the next sentence in the affidavit which is about criticize into mainstream media
And this is also fruitless
Go to next sentence
I believe the mainstream because you were talking about the government since 1 right
Descendants 2
Completely different
Now we're talkin about mainstream media
Use the Sandy Hook tragedy
To utilize and transform the public sympathy sympathy for the victims and their families
Into
An issue of gun rights I read that correctly right
Okay give me an example
I think it's the exact
Examples I just gave it
But you didn't give me any asking you for this one
Give me one example
So that I can understand a little bit as to why this is even in here
Don't have an example
That's
That is the most Infowars thing I think I've ever seen it could not be more info
Then just this is Marion. It's exactly the examples that I just gave you
Infowars
You people just don't question my daily life most people are very distractible
The subject of the mainstream media obviously you're in a courtroom set Riley wanted to find
Wd2 with these people what is the mainstream media let's hear it
When you say mainstream media what's up
Just any
Cable News Network
Familiar to
Buff people
Okay so they have to be on cable
Not necessarily
Okay what do you mean by mainstream
Big corporate media
Been around for awhile well known to the public
Okay Whitney Corp
As corporate sponsor
Okay so
Corporate sponsors
That are
A company that has corporate sponsors
That
Convey the news
And
And are known to the public in
I've been around awhile that's how you define me
When you say for a while
How long is that
What are you referring
Your answer that you said
Do the corporate sponsors they've been around for awhile
What do you mean by for a while
For your words
I would say
They've been around long enough to have
Some sort of reputation in
Public
Recognition
Okay
So Fox News
No
No really they've corporate sponsors
They're well known to the public right
I would I would say most people probably don't know about LAN
Really
I would guess most people if I ask them on the street they probably around
Definitely not
Like
As familiar as they would be with Fox News
Fox News is mainstream media
For whatever arbitrary draw of number of people who Owen could ask upon the street
Number and it's arbitrary
Trump rally everybody knows who I am
Is it Breitbart
They got corporate sponsors their well-known to the public they been around for
Longer than the way in
Breitbart
Is it
Is mainstream media team
According to your definition right
I would probably say
No I wouldn't consider Breitbart mainstream either why
I mean this is all open for interpretation but I mean another General thing of
Mainstream media would be
Entities that go along with the same narrative
As everybody else and I filled it Breitbart and oan often
Beer
Off of
The consensus narrative
Okay
So you're mainstream media
Yeah even if you're a news outlet that checks all of mr. Shroyer's boxes of what he defined as mainstream
If you
Have an opinion that's different than some other news outlets then you're not mainstream
How different is it have to be in what's the frequency of that
There's no match
There's no there's no I mean I feel like
Stuff is and isn't interesting here is you have these definitions that I want his brain.
Corporate sponsorships
And those are the things that you would like
To present is what he defines as mainstream media put on further questioning
You really start to realize it's like oh no mainstream media says things I don't like and things that are crazy and are in law
Why was my narratives that's not mainstream media
They satisfy all the conditions that I immediately came up with the respectable answers
It does
Feel like this should be a criminal trial and the punishment should be a life
Wang parole of word that the plaintiff is words you have to okay so if you want to use a word
You have to
Demonstrate
To an expert
In language that you know how to use it properly
Yeah I think I think their punishment could be a lifetime of carrying a dictionary around your neck
Yes yes Scarlet Letter but it's all the letters
Realizes like wait Infowars
Would fill all the qualifications that you just gave right for it so they are you mainstream baby
Prior to
Infowars and your selfie deplatformed
Social media Outlets
I was Infowars mainstreaming
Okay
They've been around a long time
They have notoriety
Massive audio
That
Warts
Most of the companies that I just mentioned earlier
Right
And on every Outlet
That wasn't infowars.com
Corporate sponsors with
We have that
I just want to know Infowars
Checks all of your boxes for mainstream media
Why aren't they
I just don't agree
Check all boxes at all fact
Check
Generalities of my definition of mainstream media somebody else has to be
Entirely
I'm ask I'm not asking for you to classify
Infowars for everybody
Right I'm asking what
You think what's Owens
And then when I asked
How Owen decides whether something is mainstream media
You gave me your criteria
And then I took Infowars your employer
And it checks every single box
But you're saying no no no we're not mainstream
And I'm trying to figure out why
Tell me why
Okay
How about this
When
News outlets lie about events that caused massive violence to happen
They don't end up getting sued or in court
But when Infowars covers event somehow we always end up in litigation like
You ever seen defamation verdicts
United States
I'm not too familiar now
I want you to Google it when you go home
And I want you to see who was dependent by the Play-Doh
Their names are
CNN
NBC
Gawker
Pit massive
Hollywood
So I think this is one of the more revealing moments it's
Information
He needs to come up with an explanation for why Infowars isn't the MSM and the thing that he lands on is if they get sued where they make
Things up but the mainstream media doesn't
What's remarkable about this is that it's
Wholly reliant on Owen having no idea who gets sued for what no clue it's solely Based On A Feeling in that
Healing is a grievance
Feels like they're the victims of society and so
Assumptions are made in order to prop up that feeling
Instead of asking yourself if other people get sued for doing the things that you've done it feels more satisfying to assume that they do
And you're only getting sued because everyone's against you
I think this is so revealing is because it's an instance of Owen speaking to the identity and definition of Infowars
It's something that's at the root of why he thinks Infowars is different than other media Outlets
Because they're victims of an unfair game persecution
This completely inaccurate feeling is part of how and identifies Infowars and how they're different from CNN
This makes total sense to me and I think that this feeling is almost comically present in their broadcast but it's a little
Shocking to see it articulated by Owen in a deposition
Infowars isn't different for the mainstream media because they cover the stories that no one else will they're not different because they have asked
Will deep-level sources who feed them solid Intel
They're different because they believe incorrect things that make them self-identifies the victims of society
Really just very angsty and childish at its core and it really does explain Owens early career as a selfie
Describe duck Destroyer
Just a child this is just childish it I mean it does feel like what he wants to say is like UK
You can't like take the things that I say
And then put them into a different context
Because then
They own oh yeah that's cuz I feel like I feel real stupid now
I have
Made some broad statements about what makes mainstream media
Accuracy on the persecution fully understood the transitive property
Could you please explain that to me from the very beginning
We're going to be here awhile
So we get to the next sentence in the affidavit and
This is a meal basically this affidavit
In Exodus you say I believe the mainstream media
Remove
? over that
Instead you believe that makes you media instead of blaming the shooter
Portrayed all going gun owners
And gun-rights activists as the cause of what happened at Sandy Hook
Surely there's an event that you watched or saw
Where
This happened so that
That made you put this in your affidavit
I can't recall
Wow that's
Not good
What I'm hearing you say is that I should have a reason for the feelings that I have and the things that I say
I mean you don't necessarily have a reason for all of your feelings but ones that you swear
Motivate your actions try I would think that you should have
Some sort of
Like here's why okay now let me throw this out at you this is the first I'm hearing of this s***
This notion that mainstream media blamed gun owners
Come up with an event makes this make sense
But Bill makes it a little bit worse
If this sentence that I just read one true that's a big deal
Correct
What is a big deal that the mainstream media
Was
Was portraying all gun owners
And gun rights activist
They don't even know
As the cause of what happened at Sandy
Correct yes
But you can't recall anything that made that
Right
Not an exact
Because you're putting me into a position where I can't produce the oven in
You're asking me to produce
I'm glad you said
We'll come back up what's awesome about this moment is
That was basically saying like
Man that would be huge
I would be
I'd be worried if you could prove this please prove it I will join your team
Right now I'll f****** quit this love profession for good and work under you Owensboro
If you can get me one f****** example
So we get back to actual video and this is not good if I definitely would not
Not want to hear this in a deposition
With what you know now
We read some of the quote
When I read some of those clothes
The video
Are you did about mr. Iceland
Should you settle
I mean I think with any live
Broadcast I mean we don't have teleprompters or Scripts
That you're going to
Sometimes
Have words and phrases that come out
Are in the way that you like them
And so I'm upset
That
My commentary that day is perceived as an attack on Mr heslin it never was that was never the intention
When you said think we're going to get clarification from Mister haslinger Miskelly
I wouldn't hold my breath
You know what you did after that
I think it went to break I'm not sure
Chuckled
That's what you do
Did you find it
Funny
No
No do you find
Mass shootings
No you find you know
Asking parents
For clarification
On things that are the true
Is that funny
Sometimes it's just awkward when you go to break and you just kind of have an awkward moment
And I guess in that moment it was a chuckle or maybe it was just because
Megyn Kelly was just kind of a joke me at the time so bringing her up was kind of a board leave a charcoal but then it again to know
In no way shape or form was any of that commentary meant
A slight on mr. heslin I never see his kid didn't
I never said any of that
You really don't want to hear you laughed in that room
You laughed real
I'm feel good
Feel like I shouldn't have done that 8 can I ask you a question let's go back to the first question
Do you feel like you should have said all that stuff
Honestly he kind of thinks that like he did as good a job as he could
With the information that was available to its course he does it's not true
You are now
Have been found by a court
To have defamed
Mr. heslin
Right
Justinformed
I I had no again I never accused Mr heslin of line I never
That segment was never purposed as any sort of affront to me
I'm not even sure if I knew who he was before
So you didn't care who you were talking about
I'm just covering a story that was given to me you would agree you covered it poorly
Correct
I covered what I had available to me
No
You did not do that
You covered what was selected
By someone at Infowars in with
Given to you
Without any questions
That's what you did right
Yes because available was the whole
Corners
Prescott
True
Not to me but it was out there
It was an it was Shirley was available to you
Not in that exact moment but what if the news isn't a race is it
Is it up for interpretation
I don't do it as a race
No it's not a race
Mister Ogden
Right
I do not view the news as a race
Okay
Now that we've established that
You definitely have that Corners press conf
Available
True
No all I had was that clip
You know what the internet is right
Ouch
Define availability let me let me try and make this a little bit clearer
Okay
How do you
Or someone around you
Googled the words you could have watched the whole thing
Guardrails around Infowars there's news instead of being handed directly to you
And then if this video is b*******
Then do you just need to get to you and there's no risk of you accidentally reported.
Never had anyone add Infowars to do that what is that job
Where do you get those people
Ship is going to hire somebody who can look into things I don't think they teach them
Not with this centralized government school system
Got this video and this article from
Whoever anybody
Everybody
And
This clip is fantastic
Because this
Is the clap
Where Bill basically makes Owen admit that he's a puppet
I don't know who edited that video
Right it could have been someone in our house it could have been someone else on the internet that they found
Right
You know what
Do you know we can agree on
Nobody fat
Nobody to sit
Oh man that's crazy when did he say this
Google up the interview with watch it
20 minutes
I didn't plan on covering the story that day so I had no preconceived notion that I would even have to do that I know Mister Shroyer
We're here because you were a puppet
You would agree with me right
You don't agree with me that you
Heeler puppies
Cracked
Puppet is
An object that is used
To convey a message
But somebody else is actually controlling them
Yes bright
You were conveying a message
Right
True somebody else was
Controlling
True
No
Who who is controlling the message that you were putting
I were you and control what was the messenger recurrent at the corner
Said he never released the children
Cuz that's the story ran with
Who is in control of that information
If you weren't cuz you already said you weren't in control of it
Who was somebody has to be
Whoever originally posted the video
Someone else had control
You were conveying the message
We just established that you
There's nothing wrong
Derogatory term
But it's analogous to where we are now
You would agree
I think if anybody is being using the puppet it would be
People who are reporting their stories
I'm just chilling at information
The story
If I cover it so if I just pick up anybody's new source and cover it.
Does that make me a puppet
So if you don't absolutely okay then I guess then I guess I'm a puppet of zerohedge in this case
Yeah I know that's actually not true
You're a puppet
I coin Bank
Okay
That's the source that was underlying the Zero Hedge article
Unlike their puppet
I can't believe
That you don't have that moment where you go see where you going
Okay I think I did and I think you realize like there isn't a way out of this trap
Because otherwise I have to admit that I was in control of release
Totally I feel like the first time he was like so you're not a puppet okay so were you and control the message
Where you conveying the message
Yeah if it's humiliation or responsibility which are you going to accept
Shurfine in this situation
At the end I guess I'm a puppet then zerohedge
That's not even good enough to have to hit back not even that you wish
You don't even know who the f*** they are so at this point Bill plays some videos
Of all the women's March
Hey this is a continuation of Owen saying
Uprinting M on it
And I don't have it at my disposal so he's this is the videos where he does that to people and says you're on
Basically yes listening to this as we've gone
Bill already made reference to Owen doing this
He's already foreshadowed
And he made a very unsuccessful attempt at explaining what he was doing
So now we got it now we got props and Ona still hopeless
Alright
So this gentleman just told you tell that to the dozens of accusers that
Stead of accused him of sexual harassment
Right and you responded with
Name one
Right
Yes let's keep watch
So keep watching
And Bill subtly trying to make this point that I have been doing this to you
To pick up on it
Alright
So
Has an encounter with some protest
You were asked they had a position
Right
And you ask them
For evidence
In master
One name
One of the tropics
You said oh I'm formed
You started name
Trap Queen
And
Afterwards he goes
Believe the women
Even though I do
Even though I can't remember
That's right
And he's and you said
You can't even
Now
Take what just happened
What's rheumatism
Dublin
Couldn't
And there's way more
Right
I don't know but okay
I have no idea
Surely you believe that there's more
Governmental
And or congress
And or congress people
And or mainstream media
What's
Encompassing
Way more than Trump
True
I'm I'm I'm sorry I don't understand this
Yeah you couldn't name
He doesn't understand he doesn't grasp that they Dynamic that is
Planning out here it's not a satisfying no but but that's why build it has to directly tell him
So here's that
Can you kind of see how I got my
My question and answer format
Affidavit
Spoiler alert
Capital Cab
Oh my God
I want I want
Organic
Plated but there's a little bit of like still Saving Face a tiny bit
I still don't think he understands quite what is happening
I don't think he understands being directly told I took that
You did with protesters and use that to form the way I asked you these questions
Yeah again I really think that
Owen does not understand the ability to transfer a series of actions and behaviors from
Someone said section to another I understand I understand why you think I disagree
The a lot of the inability to understand things is somehow
Sometimes strategic sometimes it's
Convenience to not understand that
This article that Owen was using to do his coverage that he was flipped by somebody
You think like I don't know maybe if that article was everywhere
Like it was a huge story then maybe commenting on it
Make some sad that like with kit meals right if truly Marcela fontaine's picture was
Everywhere
It makes some sense to address or something
If you have more than just say a tweet by buttmuncher 99 then yes
How relevant that story was
This is the article that you were going
You're scrolling through the video in this
Cracked
Why had I believe I had that article printed off
Dismiss
What you're going through
Okay yeah I'm not in control of what goes on
So you don't
You are just somebody else is on this
But I do want to look at this
This shows that
And we're not sure where zero-point now is
They could be in the center
And so could have been published at 3:35 p.m. central or
Or 235
And
This screenshot is from the
And you can see how many shares has had
How many shares has had at the
What time you put it
What's that number
This article is not one
Getting shot around and Diesel other
Outlets
Reporting this is it
Safe2save this is at a minimum if this is been up for
At most
Our
3 shares
We're not dealing with the top
Your auntie
Is much larger
Something that's been put up for
Nauert
Correct
You know you talk to
Thousands if not
Hundred thousand
People everyday
The TuneIn
You and Mister
So
When
A larger media player
Like a war
Takes a smaller media platform
Article
And puts it up
You can agree that disseminates that information
Kanishka
Probably
This is a great way of using their grandiosity against them
Something that might be described as a to-do move
There's a Twist in here with you guys talk all day about
How popular you are billions and billions of listeners this b*******
Couple thousand
Cool if you were in Owens shoes
If someone had fed you this information
Like what would you internally at work what would you do
Abdomen
What would Owen do you know if you were in that situation what would you what would your sort of agenda be
I'm on air
No not talking like afterwards after you realize that this is
Bad information that someone is giving probably run away because you're a coward
Because if I admitted guilt it Infowars I don't know what anybody would do to me there's a lot
Lot of possible consequences with a lot of guns over around the heavily-armed workplace
And I couldn't continue working there morally speaking because I just committed one of the greater sins that I can imagine
So I'm going to have to go with move to Canada
I was looking for a figure out who gave you that information because they've clearly f*** you over
Because I feel like they're going to get rewarded and I should go to Canada
Bananas world over there
Hey this person maybe won't be mad at them
Maybe you'd be worried that they might do it again and maybe you'd want to have a talk with him about being more careful with their information
So it doesn't really care too much
If zerohedge never publishes the story I've never covered
Sub-Zero
I didn't say that I'm just telling you that if zerohedge never publish the story I would have never covered it
Zerohedge
Isn't the one that gave you
Circlip
And all of your
I don't know who gave me that clip I don't know where they got it
You definitely want to find
When you leave here you're going to find out who is working that day
Injection for
Probably not
You don't even you don't care
Well I imagine that you would
Oh my God
I again I mean
I'm not even sure if the people that would working that day even still working and for
10 question
What's the question
Yeah I am upset that Mr has one had to go through any of this I'm upset that I'm being lumped into this again
Sandy Hook was never my thing I never
Have ever doubted the events happened I never doubted that his son never died
I'm doing commentary on a piece that was published
By 0 heads or 0.90 or ibankcoin
They would never published it
I would have never covered it
Yeah but
But you were
You were reporting on that that was the
Zerohedge
But you
Directly siding
The corners
Testimony
That's it
That's company
True
I think it was a CBS interview with the corner I don't know where the original interview with the corner come
What we do know is that
You didn't know what was in it
True
Till I saw it that day you're upset that you're lumped into this
Enough
Go back to work and figure out
Who did this
In this position
Made you betray
All the people
And
Dearly
Impacted mr. hussle's life
Again
Right
You're not that
Injection form
I just feel that that would be
There's nothing that can really come of that
Jen and Noah truth not matter
Absolutely nobody ever
Was targeting any individuals
By bringing me that thing other than to say hey look ma back in the news
You don't even have gave it to you
Okay fine I guess I don't know then Ringo
You don't know
Why they did
You don't know why they clip that video in
Zach Wade
Set you up
Two light
Thousand
Owen did not have to say no one meant to Target anybody
Because now that is introduces that idea. Cohen can't say that
On the record
For the jury Ellen saying give me this in order to Target though
This is just an unforced error AAA cost nothing to be like
You know what I hadn't thought about it but yes absolutely I would love to get to the bottom of this and I intend to figure this out
I didn't before and maybe that's that was sloppy of me
Nothing I mean
I genuinely cannot believe that none of their lawyers just got together and explain how a deposition works
Just was like
Listen
Answer only the question if it all possible keep your answers to yes or no do not
Explain if it is not part of the question
All you have to do is answer the question
You just answer the question
Yes or no if possible
Giving giving these bizarre explanations for your motivations and where your heart is
Is only going to create so stupid more problem you are so stupid
So the video gets played and
I think this is just a demonstration of how poorly these videos were cut
Like they cut off mid-sentence
ISO making a
Pretty
Extreme
Glenwood
Very thing Vivid in your memory holding his dead child
Here is an
Corner
That does not cooperate
Contact
Accomplished
That is what
You realize he was going
He was about to say something else
Agree
I have never seen the clip I never seen the full clip that is
The only time I've ever seen or known anything about that clip
Backup
Right there what we just saw
You could hear him going
Continuing to make noise as the video
Correct
You can play it back for me now but I've no idea if I heard it then or not
Have you ever heard somebody in descendants
Bottom
I have no idea
This is just an attempt to be like you should have had an instinct that they would this
Maybe there was more
And this is laying the groundwork of establishing a pattern because there's another clip
That is played that's just got off mid-sentence
Well
At first I thought that
And I have questions
Wanting to
See her
We can agree that
That clip
Right in the middle
Troop
Wanting to see her
That would be an assumption I don't
Oh my God
Okay so
Just
Another question
That people are now going to be asking
About Sandy Hook
Will there be a clarification
From
Edwin or Megyn Kelly
Not a good look not a good look
Do a little bit of a fight right after that because you can hear Mark in the background
But that is a question that is very relevant
Who is fueling the
Thumbs up
The last tech glasses and on that video you say will there be clarification from Heflin
Or Megyn Kelly
I wouldn't hold your breath
So now there
Fueling The Conspiracy Theory
Unbelievable
Who isn't there
Viewing the conspiracy theory claims
Megyn Kelly and zerohedge
No
What did Megyn Kelly say
Just mystery
Against far as my knowledge
The
Coroner testimony was not brought up
Mr. heslin
In Megyn Kelly's interview
And it may have been irrelevant but that's what I'm saying is that Megyn Kelly did not clarify that question
Questioner
On the spot
And I'm probably doesn't go to
Your website
Pretty fearsome
Okay sure
You can see here that I want still grasping to this thing that he thinks is a life raft it is the idea that Megyn Kelly for some reason
Was required to address the manipulative lie edited clip of the coroner and the fact that she didn't is somehow suspicious
Without oversimplifying things this is basically all Owen has to defend his actions which is really sad because
If you want to really Express a truer version of what happened
It's B Owen believe the fraudulent claims was true because of conform to his conspiracy worldview
To attack the people he felt were threatening his boss whether he actually believed it was true is beside the point but use the impression
To discredit the claim of a grieving father
Who his boss had lied about defamed in the past but they didn't fully address this fraudulent clip
That must mean that there's a reason that they don't want to clarify things
We all that's going on sloppy
No no every every new question
That's continued existence
Point know about Wolfgang halbig
Until I really even know about him until like there
Papa and be relevant
But don't just learn something kind of course this deposition
Then why did you say what will there be clarification for bromhead
Just I would say that if he doesn't like
You Stories being published in
Then he would come out and make statement saying
You know
What he said in the video
That's literally what he
In the video
She said I held my dead son
Silence
Conspiracy theories
That's why he did to Macon Kelly enter
Do you understand
You're saying he did the Megyn Kelly interview because of Infowars
Yes because of the phone
For That interview all of the torture
Did they put him
Over and over and over again
That's how many videos
So yes
Did you not know that
Depressing I just
I mean
It's either a lie or it's an indication of just not caring at all
He did sound honest
It did sound honest when he's like wait but he's your little issues you're saying that he went on Megyn Kelly
Because of us
Yeah
That's why are we the bad guys kind of moment or just like
So
The another thing that Owen did
Was be really shity to miss Lafferty whose mother died
Sandy Hook was one of the teachers and he made a little bit of a suggested that
She should have had a gun and that would have solved everything that's going to go well yeah
I've forgotten some of how shity this is
Pause this video at
49 seconds
You just made the state
If Miss Lafferty's mother had a pistol or firearm
She could have her
By shooting
Her assailant before
The sandwich shop
How did
Did Miss
Did the did the deceased
This is Lafferty's mother did she see the assailant
I have no idea
Did she have the ability to get
Personal lock box
The weapon
To defend herself
I would assume not
Did okay so then why are you representing to the public
And directed to to miss laughing
Who lost her mom
That if she had a gun
She could prevent
Because I believed if you would have had access to a gun she would have used it to protect her life in the lives of others
She could have also
Use that gun in taking steps to put herself in
In further Danger
Meaning yeah if you're going to
Approach armed assailant then you do put yourself in further Danger
Chickadee
List
And get a child
Yes
Or she could have
She could have died
Without ever even seeing it coming
From behind
Tripping the first one that went down
She could have been I don't know
So this
Conspiracy theory that you have
Which is
Guessing
Really
You and I can
You're making
Jackson forum
No I believe the gun issue was made
With whatever story I'm coverings
Like I said whatever the story is I'm covering they're saying that you don't new gun legislation is the answer
And my proposal is that
Having a gun to protect yourself is a better answer
Are you sure that that's what
Because
I will say this
You do say that she is a
Hypro
Going to have a
That's not
This is about her
Telling press
Trump
Distance
You understand that
I know that that is mentioned in the article
You're the one that I
Arming teachers
That's a great moment there because it's really tough to argue that all and actually was not the first
Who was making the story about guns
Miss Lafferty was just saying the Trump shouldn't associate with Alex and in order to lash out and started talkingshit
But how is her mom had a gun should be a lot
What I find particularly repulsive about this instance of Owen Sandy Hook content
Is that it's directed specifically at Lafferty
He speaks in the second person saying your mom as if he expects her to be listening
It's pretty f***** up stuff and I can't imagine what kind of internal strife it must hate to pretend you're not a monster
Listening back to that kind of stuff that's he's doing
In this deposition
Grizzly
How did the how do you survive that now I'm interested in knowing as like a
Specimen you know like I could not hear somebody in a deposition play that for me
Recognize that I did that and then continue living I feel like I would just explode instantly and be like
Good call I'm out boom and I'm just gone I have a place where you could search for Clues your beginning
The rest of his demo video with Lafferty
Answer the reason that I brought up that he claimed earlier that he had no real weariness of Wolfgang halbig
And that's because this next clip
He's looking
He's not the one
Wolfgang halbig
Forgot just done the best
Really going to
I'll stop there
Earlier I asked you some questions about Wolfgang halbig and you said no he's the radical one
I don't know anything about his work I can opine on what he does
Remember when you told me that
Yes
Vacu said
Should I'm not familiar with his work enough to have an opinion
Remember when you said that
Certainly sounds bad considering the context
Like if
Somebody had me in a deposition and was like when you introduced such-and-such comedian
Did you really think that they were the best in this area would you say that
Do you really believe that they played colleges have you have you seen them at clubs and all around the neck
All around the nation are they really a regular on the festival circuit
You really think that it's someone's birthday well usually
Good excuse for that
I mean if I if I have to make a cemented statement it would say I think that people died that day cuz there was no
Alarm security there was no layer of protection to stop the shooter from going in there
And killing people
You may
Miss Lafferty's mother
Would not have died
If she had a pistol or a fire
You said those were
True
Yes
Then you went on to say
You know
Wolfgang halbig
He's a good guy
She's dumb
Best reporting
Of anyone
On Sandy
He's got 16
I wasn't
I'm not sure
My guess is when it comes in Sandy Hook that was probably the only name that I ever saw brought up about it and that's how
Probably why I referenced it
But to say I was a big fan of Wolfgang halbig is inaccurate and it and I don't believe I ever described him as a good person
Okay
How how did why did you tell thousands if not millions of people here
Wolfgang halbig.
Is the best reporting on
Out of all the reporting and this was a highly repeat
In the world
Probably because that was just the only name
That I had associated with Sandy Hook
For whatever reason just got in a research didn't I was the only name I ever saw so she ate it with it
Big CNN MSN
Fox News
Hunza people covered it
But you
Did you choose walking hobby because
He fit your name
Narrative here
I didn't have a narrative
Again I wasn't falling Santiago time I wasn't following
Politics are current events at the
You were just upset
Miss Lafferty
Your boss
Upset you
I just wanted to cover an article and respond to Staples
Did you get
Good feedback from
Alex Jones after this did he say hey
You good
I have no idea
I doubt there was any feed
The bomber has your dad ever said good job son
That's a bummer
Situation where it's like you have just been shown evidence that you lied
Is material that has to do with like
You
Or calling out
Someone whose mother died at Sandy Hook tour and part of your rationale for that is hey Wolfgang halbig
Big is great but I've never heard of the guy
But the
Video to show you know correct yourself probably
Obviously if I've never heard of Wolfgang halbig I'm sure that later on you'll see that I've never heard
Loaded him on are you should probably correct
Or not
What reporting
Wolfgang how big do the
How did he beat
In your opinion
I would say
I misspoke in that
Video or as I said earlier
It was just the only name that I've ever heard associated with Sandy Hook
When was the you saw this video
A couple weeks ago
About a month ago
Okay in the last month have you gone on Aaron clarified all of your audience
Do you wrong
Cuz now he's got a second
I don't want to touch anything Sandy Hook with it
Million football
I really on time and I understand
Impulse right but I also think
That
If you if you're someone like oh and you have to recognize like this makes your credibility look really bad
The families probably would only think it appositive if you would go on air and directly ask
Address that you made a mistake
I just think that this is cowardly kind of perspective bill doesn't understand
Alright is that standard operating procedure for Infowars okay he's too
To never be wrong
Always lie and never ever apologize and yesterday didn't really happen
I don't even know what yesterday means
I got the Feeling watching this that Owen is starting to get pissed
I would imagine so
Alex
And they say that
He doesn't know what really
At Sandy Hook
And they do
The official story
Has more holes
So again
What holes are you talkin about
Okay then why are you talking on there
Cuz I'm covering a story
You're defending your boss
Because
Someone said he said this
But all he said was
That's all he said
What did he say
I don't know
Prior to going on air did you do bunch of research
Fact-checking
No
Okay you just took somebody else's article
When on Aaron started.
Yes, your modus operandi
Now but that's the case in this
And that was also the case in
Last video
Right
Got those kids
Same thing
True
I've answered the question
Where was that
Earlier man recognition that you should not answer
Lising I am losing by the end of the little bit of Bud here little beep
Has if you ever heard the phrase in over your head
Yeah okay
In the in the suit thorax do you know where an angler fishes in the ocean
That's about how it over my head I help you but turns out just promote Wolfgang halbig
I'm asking conservatives
Join me
Alex Jones
Pure
On his show
Again I would
Say you need
Wolfgang
Is 16 +
But again
Where Wolfgang halbig 16 questions
I don't know
Why were they so important to you in this video you mentioned
I think it was more of a matter of
From my perspective Alex Jones was catching all this flag for Sandy Hook but the other
People that were questioning it weren't
To my best knowledge
Who who do you mean
Wolfgang halbig
It's f****** Brazen Amazing Alex should be taking all the Heat
And where you decided to express that is telling a woman who lost her mother in a horrific shooting lied about a bunch time
That doesn't sound like a takedown and how big and this comes from the same video where island called how big the best reporter
He's clearly saying that Lafferty needs to answer how big's questions because he thinks she can't write
Meaning behind what Owen is saying is he believes that if Lafferty were forced to answer those questions could be proven to be a hoe
Oaks pretending that this is an anyway critical of Wolfgang is the most cowardly dazhou encabo here
You expect better from a cuck Slayer
Yeah you died the Cox late or you live long enough to see yourself become a cock on the road that's what's going on here
I I mean
It is it is so sad I just want I just want to sit down and just be like listen
I know how Infowars actually works
The questions that I am asking you
AR
Just either to tell me if you know how it was actually works
Or to tell me how you're lying about how it was actually works there was no outcome where you get away
This is it this is over
Yeah if a conversation or traffic Metroid
Come on dude clip of you doing the thing
How long are we going to do this dance I don't know
Joann hours
Tilapia
For you lose
I feel for whatever happened
But I'm telling you Alex Jones
How big is not your enemy
You still believe that
Wolfgang halbig
I don't know enough about walking out big tits
I never know
Alright f*** you b****
That's
Stark
I never knew enough and yet I am
Using him as a prop to attack
Woman who lost her mother
Just Google is s***
Here's a little bit more video
I asked you
Add a gun
Ready
Dylann roof
Took your mother's life
Today
Infowars.com
How do you think
Action form
I don't know
If you could redo this
I just wouldn't do the video doll
Why
Because it's now being used against me
Is that why that's that's that's real
See that's one of those things where your answer is
Way worse zip
And also not for nothing
We got the shooters name wrong he's at dylann roof sealing roof yeah
That's a little disrespectful
Dark pretty f****** disrespect
Dark
Wow
Yeah
So the question comes up of hey man what shootings
Has Infowars not thought was a hoax or a false flag
Okay if I'm Owen and I get this question my immediate responses
I don't have any examples for you and then we just call it right cuz that's where we're going to go
I mean eventually
Can you think of a mass shooting
Infowars
Did not
False flag
And or a
Yeah there was just wanted a high school
And I Michigan this week
Prior to
Actually
Prior to this lawsuit about
Because
Columbine
Brainwash
The government branch
Boston bombing
Gabrielle Giffords shooting
Parkland shooter
Aurora
Sutherland Springs Church shooting
El Paso
Oklahoma City
San Bernardino
Oh
False flag
All claimed by
Earlier when I asked you if you
You thought Infowars
Spira C3
Now that I just went
Still holding on to that
There's way too much to unpack there
To make a broad statement
20 different events
Make a blanket
Statement of conspiracy theory I gave you all 20 of them
However many
Which one of them was a
Was a hoax
False flag
You tell me
I have no
I didn't say that either
You can't you can't nobody you can't you can't say any because if you do those follow-up question
You just can't handle this
Trey or claims that any of them were actually hopes as an Infowars called all of the pokes
That makes you a conspiracy site doesn't it
Every single one
Is
Labeled a hoax and or false flag
Immediately
MyInfo
The day up
Every single one that I
I mean I'm
I'm facing
An answer off of
An assumption that you're being
Completely honest I don't know what you're talkin about what events did I cover
Of those events that you listed
So here's the thing
You didn't cover
But
You did say
The Infowars
Not a conspiracy
So if their website
Labels all of these
Events
Has false Flags Endor
Government cover-up
Hoaxes
And none of them
What does that
Meropenem
I'm asking what's Europe
Section 4
Yeah I don't answer that figure this out 3 hours in
You starting to look pissed off it just felt like yeah you're going to have to almost like a switch kind of flipped
Like I got a clam up about something
Clips
Revelation of like completely trapped myself here I can't say anything else
It's probably going to be a trap
I mean
I would be shook too if I was in that position I mean
I guess points for getting there
But you should have gotten their way earlier might have taken three and a half hours but
God
So there's that there's a culture it Infowars that is of a certain character
Now how much
Anyone is aware of what the other people there believe is a matter of debate
There's some information about some of Boeing's coworkers
Is brought up stuff
Michael Zimmerman
Do you know who he is
Yes Susie where you friends with her
I would say we're friends but
I mean we don't hang out about that often
But you friend someone
Professional in Paradise Salon in public I go say hello
He seemed like a good guy
Supposed to be come up there
Shockingly
Wood
Has he ever shared any of his
Opinions or views on mass shooting
Not that I can recall
Were you aware that
Christchurch
New Zealand shooting
Music live stream
Brandon Tarrant
Was the shooter exq
Bunch of Muslims
Something
Yeah you're refreshing
Details of the event
Army right now
Do you know whether or not anyone had Infowars
Claimed it was a
Did you know that
Some individuals and Infowars
Light
That shooting
Did you know
You understand that Michael Zimmerman handles the it stuff
Directions
I know that he
Was doing it I'm not sure if that is still his role
Did you know that on March 14th
Mr. Zimmerman registered the domain
Parent Manifesto.com
Did you know that he registered the website
Shooter Chan
Dot-org
No
Did you know
You know Timothy Thrift
Yes
Do you have a person relation
Work acquaintance
Did you know that he registered the website
St
Tarrant
The shooter
No
How do you feel
About
The people that you work with who you have somewhat of a personal relationship
Registering these taco
Websites
Immediately
Live streaming
3 surprise
He was pretty surprised but he also says I'm not going to bring it up to them I
What are we going to do I'm going to be mad at all
I think if I found out that A co-worker had registered
I'll probably quit
All because it also is that an intersecting datapoint
With someone who has been on much lately but was a pretty regular Infowars guess
Vox day would call Brandon Tara getting parent
Of Andrews breath
I and I think
I think that these kinds of intersections these kinds of
Like with suspicious that everyone seems to that you scratch under the surface and there's he's
Weird
Semen is seeming to like
White nationalist violence and murder
You ever noticed how many of your friends are Nazis
Like but have you ever talk to him about it I want to talk to him okay
But like
If you're at a real talk to about it then I met you don't have to okay okay
Talk to him about it and then you guys go to a rally together right and it's all of their friends
Okay
But you like them right
Well I love the other ideas are all wearing Nazi armbands
It's the season okay well convinced it's troubling I mean like obviously
Responsibility to know everything that you're
Coworkers do or anything like that I've had some co-workers that I've had some suspicions about you were
Somebody came to me and confirm some of those suspicions I would have disassociated myself
Around that whether it's like maybe another office or something like that nothing
To do
With those folks
And if it's something like
A place that does deny mass shootings at did
Christchurch shooting was a false flag
And you have multiple people who work there who are
Creating websites intended to maybe make something
I understand that what you want you can't make 100,000 anywhere else but you can make a fine living
I don't know helping Nazi so be good
So we only have a couple more clips left and one of them is a question about
Did you know that you didn't answer discovery
And so this is all going to be exhibit 30
And it's
One large document
Starting his first day
Which is a signed order
By the judge back in 2018
And it is
Order discovery
By the judge
To defend
And this is the Discovery ordered
And that's your name right
Said that was
Ordered by the judge
For you to answer these requests
Directly to
And if we go to the request for production
We see the request for production one
Can you read with that set-up
All Communications including letters
Miranda emails text messages instant messenger logs or other Electronic Communications in which the following
The follow topics our reference
Neil heslin Waterstone dr. Wayne Carver zerohedge Jim Fetzer
To this end I was ordered by the court that wasn't just sent by us he was sent by us
Not answered and then brought to the court of the court order
You
To do that production
Okay
To this day you have naughty
As we sit here
And
Correct
I was I was unaware of the
And
You would agree that some of the
This one of the exhibits that we've gone through today
Wood
Be considered
Communications
About
Carver
Neil heslin our son
Zerohedge
Correct
Yes
You did not produce any of that
We have to go
I like I said this is the first
Even been brought to my attention
In the other case as soon as this request was presented to me I produced everything
So we have this situation where you needed to do this
In addition to do I have
The Orioles where he said that the lawyer sat on this thing for a month right conceivably might be
Uno's
Answer this leads to Bill making a suggestion that
Is a little bit too unconventional
I understand the Mysteries represents you
And I am
This next question
No way
Because our
The best
But
When I
When we look into your net
I want to know whether or not you have
Disgust
Wauconda Plata
Not with Mysteries
Anybody else
Legal malpractice
Lawsuits against
Park Council
Multiple failures
Over the course of
3 years
Duke
Entertain
Responsive discovery
To the point where
You haven't sanction
The default judgement
Can you just
Simplify that for me so I can
After you discuss or
Clayton suing you
Because they
Did not tell you any of this it come to them that you were ordered by the judge
Answer
And because of that along with
Anaconda.
Fraction form
I have not had any discussions about that now
I will say this
Fiction
And the reason I say that is because
The claims are an asset
At some point
The baskets
Probably going to be
Evaluating
Because
I'm sure you've had conversations to an extent
With your lawyers butt
I will say this are you aware that as this case dance right now
The judge has taken
Any ability
I understand that now
And cereal
Foley from
Whatsoever
If we could please
Make sure we're clear on the record there
Malpractice
That's
Between Hawk
So this is a pretty wild thing here
Recommended do you sue your prior lawyers
Also there's a there's a two prong thing here the first is that there's like this isn't all your fault you got
F***** by these lawyers
Second thing is
If you do so your lawyer's that's an asset that's collectible money whatever you will give her
Lawyers
Should be assessed to be possibly given to the people who are awarded a judgement against you
I feel like Bill is saying real quick
Like pet
If you think
After this is done
You can then go to your lawyers to get some of your money back
We are going to take that money to
Yes all of this money all of yours is now mine this is not going to be something where you can
Make yourself
Richer after the fact
This will beat this will be a piece of whatever your assets are that are
In this case here's what blows my mind
Okay
They know weeks
So
The only thing that makes sense to me is we have episodes
Where we critique
Depositions
Essentially we gave them free coaching
All they had to do was listen to us s*** talk them I'm take our advice
Free lawyers
I don't know if it's the ones that I was at Brad was the lawyer the hills was another lawyer
Just once Brad thinks some of the other ones
Periodic different lawyers
But yeah it's free to bring this sort of
Deadland fish anytime
Amazing I think like genuinely this is shocking don't we don't
Show me know all that much about law or legal advice Kobe to know about unforced errors you keep committed
Shut up or come up with a better answer
Silly
Who's one last trip here to Dismount and it's a question of whether or not Owen feels remorse for what he's done
Last question
You have any remorse
Or
Any of
The contributions you made
Chords
Impact
Mister Haslam
Reporting that you
I would say I do
I would say that I wish I never commented on any of it
I would say that I wish I understood
Whatever
Recording mr. how big was doing at the time better
Before referencing him
And so
My my one regret is that I should have never even covered it never should have talked about it
And having said that
I'm just a
Not to be redundant but I think it Bears repeating
I never said anyting
About mr. Hazlet being a liar I never said anything about his son not dying I never said anything about Sandy Hook Sandy Hook being a hoax
I never had any intention of any ill-will towards
Mr heslin anyting
If I had thought that there would have been such consequence 28 minutes of my career on air because
These videos and I would have not done it
Absolutely
Appreciate
This is interesting for me because obviously there is an expression of him saying yes I have remorse
At the same time with the explanation of the remorse has to do with consequences that have been visited upon him
As opposed to it was wrong to do this
It's it wrong to put someone that treat someone like this essentially even if
Abstract idea to you
Like a person in his life but
Not considering the possible ramifications of your
Blatantly irresponsible and bulshit coverage
Also very very
Series Intermatic and not to mention Miss Lafferty's
Respectful coverage of a situation
I think I don't know if it's an inability or an unwillingness to accept responsibility
Beyond the level of this was wrong to do
But I find that distasteful that these could only understand wrongdoing through consequence
Is a guy saying I regret being caught
I listen I stole all of her money I love stealing it I get to keep it and I regret you catching Maybe
Because now I feel like I'm going to lose it and I would really like to keep that person's money that is not mine if I'd known there was a
The punishment for the shity behavior that I engaged
Never thought there was a possibility that this would come back to haunt me I probably wouldn't have done it
I mean Solutions on being a responsible adult it's just it's just so much like listen if I had
I'm going to work for Infowars where they told me this s*** was fine then I probably wouldn't be doing it
What education do I have I'm a moron
You work for that AM station we are we reach the end of this and I'm exhausted
But I think we learned a lot I think we did but I think we really
Learned a good bit about the inner workings of multiple facets of Infowars show
Enforced of it that these people are s******* scam they just don't know what to do and can't defend themselves
Without making things worse can't take the help
From people
Who hates up to do a podcast
They know who we are doesn't mean listen to every episode
Listen to anything but if you've got a deposition
I mean it might behoove you
Next time
Jordan
Emilio Emilio
I'm dcx clerk I'm
Sure
And now here comes the sex robot