Satan's kingdom on Earth
The Old and New Testament
Proper sign for more than 5,000.
6666 bike.com
Celine
Dot-com live feed from the ground of the level of covid-19 antichrist takeover by
666 pesos spectacular
Knowledge right I'm there
A little bit about Alex Jones
For the special relief team song
Start was
Potastic
It was
Is another 30 seconds on top of already
Spiegel
What a treat to have someone offered services like that
The talent it is so good
The most frequent
Comment we get I think is Jordan eats
Shut up
Thank you for making another Banger absolutely
Jordan
Whatsyourprice
Today is actually I was on the most recent episode
Russell and Sarah Shockey
Preview I think I got a number of the matches right
Just by accident so what
Yeah
I made some predictions
And yeah I watch the Wrestlemania last night
What's the
The first night
Recording
I'm David the big
Blove course
Spoiler alert
If you haven't watch WrestleMania you plan to
Steve Austin
Came back on night 10000 Maniacs okay
Bizarre
So he came to do like a talk show segment
They closed the show
First of all this is nuts
They had the original
And Kathie Lee like that kind of talk show
What are the things that
Wrestling does
It doesn't make sense
Is that they will have
People
Create
They're on talk shows
And then they will do them
And it's basically just a way to set up fight
I'm interviewing this person that might like
Jerry Springer but if you consider it for a little while and why are they doing a talk show
Pull-A-Part
Kevin Owens
For some reason in the last couple months
What's decided 38a Texas
And has stupid everyone for Texas is WrestleMania
Texas
Stone cold to be a guest on his talk show
For the talk shows like a man look I'm actually looking for a fight
Right
And of course Stone Cold go through all the hats you know that you are
Of course
The Great
The great hit
Camera got to come to a sign in the crowd Austin 3:16 for sure
Which is bizarre gold medal match
And
What what I saw was even more bizarre is that
Of course stone cold one
But in the match
Owens was able to give him Stone Cold a stunner
His nuts unbelievable
It's believable it happens
Bizarre level of respect to allow your move to you
Put in recycle end up winning and then he's stunned Kevin Owens again
Opened up and poured maybe 30 beers on himself
What are the fun things called used to do is he would have people come to the ring announcer and then they
Cheers of beer as they're drinking Byron Saxton
Commentators
How to sex
Did not know this is coming knows it's coming he has to know it's coming
Immediately after this stone cold has his brother come into the ring
Why I don't know I've never seen this guy before they're celebrating his last WrestleMania or whatever
No
Brother comes into the ring and they have a beer and Mike's Dunham stomach
Seriously
Has his brother's sons have no that would be too confused
Absolutely
So I just be these
He's gone mad with SunPower he's stunning everybody the curb as we're having a good time
Thought the show was fine I guess
But really was my big
Gotta follow through trees
Sexton's your brother especially since the third what is
The funniest
Everything was there at
I mean this just proves to me that stone cold is a coward and I to hate the state of Texas
You know what
Photo of you
I2 joined another podcast
Yeah that's right we've cheated on each other except you did it in my own bed
This is my apartment
Everybody a smooth they didn't have Wi-Fi that's right
It's Lions led by Donkey
But yeah it was absolutely fantastic he was like we're going to do a two-parter
And then we talked for three hours so.
It was just a fantastic time
But it'll be available for free in like a couple of weeks
Yeah I've seen some people posting positive things about it I have not had a chance to listen to it but that's over
I like that you and I are branching out
Add more toys
Atrocities
Responding to other people say
So Jordan today we haven't promised
It's the Return of modern Alex
Expecting like a
Let It Go
66 episode
The special episode
But when we ever done everything out.
Mental is just a normal episode
First
Yeah not good not good not good you mentioned this to you before we started recording and it's it like
Because of the time spent
Preparing the deposition episodes and putting Alex on timeout
Belittle miles inside listen to some present-day Alex
And it was
Jarring to listen to it again
It is so hateful
Shockingly offensive
I I don't I don't
I don't know what to do what to say other than
Even I someone who is listen to thousands of hours of Alex's show
Was was taken
The freshness
Writing
Fresh after looking at
If not
This is awful gross show
I'm not going to play too much of the stuff that's actually like
Horrific
Yes
So don't worry about that
Folks
Business
So first of the Bosque
Next
A raptor thank you so much and I'll buy what you want
Thank you very much I go next Nostradamus was always right thank you so much you and I'll buzz you on
Thank you very much this is the safest way to get my fill thank you so much
A policy wonk
Not a Weasley thank you so much you and I hope all is well
My God has a bigger dick
Thank you very much
So
Potato and maybe sick of Alex's whining but my husband and I are out my husband do
Bando
Play the way husband and I are big fans of technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Miami
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not as bad as ever
Also a lot has happened since the last time we checked in with present-day Alex
He's facing escalating penalties for every day that he does not eating everyday
Penalties for every day that he does not do his deposition
Right for the Connecticut
We call that the Breck
Sex club scenario every week
He misses he gets another week
Detention
The whole
I had a doctor's note is not fly
No
Yeah he's he's in bad shape about that
The world's falling apart
There are
Even if the whole house is on fire
That's not going to stop Alex from getting to the new
Snow
Doing his
Job
Which is telling you
Be accurate information
About the world around you
Alright let me lay out exactly what's going on and unfolding just let you
Here's some of these headlines
California introduces new bill that would allow Mother's Day
Kill their babies up to 7 days after birth
Universities in the US are delivered Alive babies after born
For kept alive or sometimes months
In medical experiments and I'm not going to tell you what some of the perverts at work
None of that is true
It's been on aborted fetuses being used for research at its given in the right-wing media
Based on manipulative lie edited videos released by Liars like James O'Keefe in the center for
American progress
This is an absolutely about a bill in California titled A B 22-23 which amended parts
The public health code regarding issues around abortion
This has nothing to do with letting people killed babies herb 7
He's from the amount of time Alex used to claim the left use
It's only seven days now as opposed to whatever it was
Before
It's more reasonable for
I think the leftist reporting it was like a year together and they've decided that it
It's only a week right now actually about formalizing the position that no one will be held criminally or civilly responsible for engage
Aging and reproductive Health in Norfolk assisting a pregnant person
Someone doing so
Website to Alex gets his information from generally cover the story like this
This is a quote from lifesitenews which I know that Alex reads and uses a saw
The proposed legislation would Shield mother from civil and criminal charges for any quote actions
And quote related to her pregnant
Fancy clothes including miscarriage
Stillbirth or abortion or perinatal death
Inquire
Although definitions of quote perinatal death
Unquote very
All of them include the demise of newborns
7 days or more after
This coverage of the story relies heavily on selected
Quotation
Selective quotation just why I really strongly specified where the
The quotes began app
Here's the full part of that section
In the Bell as a
Notwithstanding any other law of person shall not be subject to civil or criminal liability or panel
Healthy or otherwise deprived of their right
Based on their actions or Omission with
Perspective
Eeyore actual potential or alleged
Pregnancy outcome including
Miscarriage stillbirth
Or abortion or perinatal.
That part
Notwithstanding any other law is a massive part of the sentence to leave out because
It basically contradicts the entire narrative
It's being built
You can't kill your baby after it's born because I would violate another law
No
What
Who is Ever Write a Love it's like you can't kill your baby I thought the left love killing babe
Notwithstanding any other law
Dum dum already a law that you can't murder babies
It's been awhile at least a couple months
This language in the bill is specifically meant to make it so if there is a miscarriage or baby dies shortly after
Cerberus
The parent will be held civilly or criminally responsible
Like say in a different
What state where they might say oh your baby died two days afterwards even though the doctor said
That it was going to die no matter what
You did be better and give birth to it and now we're going to prosecute you for a crime because
It is certainly a
This is honestly a pathetic attempt to get mad about something that literally says the opposite thing that you're claiming it does but people like
Alex only has pathetic attempts to offer because they're dumb and their points are
The s***
He does hate people get abortions
Partially because of his religious zealotry
And partially due to unprocessed Guild that he feels about his past
Decisions
He could deal with his problems but it said he does
Larger picture the Riley media is taking aim at the bill because it includes language
To take language out of the existing health code
We're just really mad because their number one organizing issue at the moment is demonizing trans people
Emmitt Smith
Serrated to that heading
For them
Overall Ahi Pullin stupid life from Alex.
To start the show that will likely end up helping get people who need reproductive Healthcare
Gilbert
Yep curiously Alex over the news about Lauren Hamby
AP Washington a abortion activists whose house was searched and turned out she had
5 fetuses in cooler
No hot take on that one it seems
I mean weird
He would have to have a cool take on that one
Sure
Oh yeah that one.
Seems to have not happen
Cuz it seems like
You know that would be something that's so important
Talk about you know cuz the left is killing babies 7 Days afterwards so
We should find out what the answer your portion activist are doing
Keeping fetuses
Why was she
I don't know
I think from what the story that I read about it
There was an allegation
Strawberry her whatever Associates
That they were avid
I don't know
Don't buy it it'll buy it
Heavyweight there's more big news in Allentown
Like he's on the ball here
While Samsung has banned the word Z letters I told you that was coming
Banning letters
You got so much to break down there
A story from
The letters he's become a bit of a symbol for the invading Russian army who are currently still engaged in a war in Ukraine that Alex said would
Last about 48 hours over a month
I have such it's taking a bit of a negative connotation to people who aren't bootlicking Putin apologist like Alex
Emma's became a branding problem for Samsung
Bam the letter Z foldable phone that they were selling was called the Galaxy
Azizi fold3
And that name release were poorly time
Remove disease
Leave from the name and Ukraine Latvia Lithuania and Estonia
Probably because it would have been a PR issues they didn't
So naturally because Alex is a lazy liar this
This becomes a band
Gliders
Yeah I mean
Instead of being like
Hey let's not reference a genocide
Unfortunate
PR situation
Yeah yeah that means before the war
Hey we got a real cool idea week
Piggyback off of
Is El Sabor phone
Whatever
I don't think this is a big deal I think it's a done deal yeah
These are some of the top headlines
Discussing and actually
You think that conveys him
Information the audience needs and can use
Well if a brand removes the letter z
Then
They're coming for your W-9
They're coming for I mean nobody's going to touch
Juicy
An R
Got ya
The big
Siwa
Sherp
Southern other big news that I was getting into
Halted
Firestone
Germany
Respond by announcing unprecedented
Inside the duration release of the US Federal reserve's
Yes run out our strategic oil Reserves
Instead of
Letting people thrilled
Well and pump oil
And deliver oil
On Thanksgiving Lounge
Oil companies
Hudson Grille
The Wildcatter
Got out of the Ender
This is total economic war against
Point Blank Range
And also big articles
With his judges and District
Attorneys that rule
And believe me I face these people.
And there is no new process for Christians
Conservatives gun owners
Veteran there anyone especially on a pedophile
Loving devil worshiper
We got that information
More clear by tigers vomiting out a medic
Conspiracy theories that insisted Soros runs all the cities and small towns of Judges EPUB
Pitmasters stuff
To get around
Oil drilling loans this is entirely made up
In August 2021 Vines Department
The treasury issued
Multilateral development Banks
Arctic
They shouldn't give International loans
For coal and oil exploration
This is guidance not a rule
It's also not applicable
Domestically so unless these wildcatters these independent oil drillers are trying to get a loan from the World Bank
To dig in Vietnam
It doesn't apply
Does nonsense mean it doesn't get more Wildcat then suddenly go to Vietnam wild ass cat
Catman the opposite
Is true
21 the office of the Comptroller of the currency
They adopted a new rule which made it essentially impossible for domestic
Banks in the United States
Unilaterally reject loan
From businesses in a particular industry
For instance denying oil companies loans because you're worried about climate
Right
While this may seem like a bit of a negative thing there's a narc
You meant that it could actually be
Important because
It makes it so Banks
Can't refuse to loan to Broad categories of things like
Charities
Which they may have been able
Go to do the absence of a rule like
OCC press release
Quote
Comptroller's and staff and previous administrations have made clear in speeches guidance
Some testimony
That should not terminate services to entire categories of customers without conduct
Individual risk Assessor
Is inconsistent with basic principles of prudent risk management to make decisions based solely on
Conclusory or categorical assertions of risk without actual amount
As this was at the end of Trump's term there was some talk that the rule be reversed once by and got into office but
In January 2021 Federal Reserve Governor Lael Brainard
Gave it explicit
Words that the FED would not be making any directives about Banks and not loaning to
Pacific Industries
That's not our job we don't tell Bank
Which sectors do we asked them to risk-managed and we make sure they have good
Practices are good processes in place
Sprite
We got two stories
So far
That are both
Not true
And aggressively the opposite is
I mean I don't know what there is about the Z that we can really hang our hats
Are there but this one
Nothing you can't do the thing you can do and you can't not do the thing that you can do
Yes yes it's
It's just complete not that
Okay if you're just listening to show free information you're going to just
Believe
The opposite of what is real
Teeter B world
Cool
I think he's just making this s*** up
But if I had
Gas I think Alex might have skimmed some headlines about the answer
CC proposing new regulations
About oil companies have to provide climate-related disclosures
And then he's reporting on it like this
I think
Either that or he's just make
This up out of thin air
I'm not sure
That sounds about right
But
You know
Maybe maybe maybe in reality
I just don't listen to
Maybe maybe
I think you're the only person
Who listens to Alex Hardin
I still
Have Alex telling me that I need to listen up and listen good
It's not going to just be the third world is starving to death
It's going to be
Every major country in the world has tab
Civil War planned
During the collapse
So wouldn't that just be
Global
War needs to sink into the people that are involved in the different
Government agencies and corporations
Better than helping carry the compartmentalize
You need to get D compartmentalize and you need to listen to me and listen
Good
Because I had your best interest at heart
Because we all have joint interest here
Civilization
And it continued on for please listen to me
I'm getting
Biggest chills I've ever gotten on air
Spirit tells you
Listen to me very carefully
Here's a good news
I have
Bunch of
Indicators here
A government
Policy
In just the last 48 hours it's getting almost
That there are some sane people inside the system
They're trying to put the brakes on the collapse
Okay
Some good people are doing some stuff all right
Man this is so frustrating I hate
Because last time we've got Trump in office
And he's surrounded by some bad people
You right and that everything that happens is some nefarious bumper cover globalist
Abiding in office
And they're still like surrounded by dinar good people who are YouTubers Road people who are the good one
Yeah just figure your s*** out
You got it
It's
You kind of box yourself in
If you don't allow for
Rogue agents within whatever you want
Cuz you have to be able to justify good things that happened under the administrations of people you hate
Things happen under your Heroes at
Ministration
So you just create these Bizarro spy novels
It's like
If James Bond were able to pass legislation
It's nonsense
Vilseck
H b
Did you know that all of the globalist
Play song
James Bond villains all of them are based on globalist
Ford Precision without sin
Huge compound and they really are James Bond villain
Villains are based on real people
Ian Fleming new
When he went to places like Bilderberg
When you see those movies and then slept like notoriety
What's going on
You got government-owned you've got spec
You got Hydra
You called him the hell you want but it's real
Hydra
He's really a corporate leader
Will be working foreign
Riders of all these shows are telling you what's really going on
Persona
I don't work for
For Humanity in America and freedom
And it really comes down to that you work for the state
From the Bible
You better decide right now
Not the most important way to understand my religious belief has to watch a children's cartoon
The world was just explained to me in a barrage of references to evil organizations in 100%
Fictional universe
For children
Outlook.com
Tell me the backyard with my friends was actually training for the fight against the devil
You know what's crazy about it if you didn't bring up
Captain Planet
Arguing
I was a rat but his
Real problem with dumping toxic waste
Overcomplicate things
Galaxy
These are all
Thematically just like
Haha big shadowy organization
Trump VR
Goldfinger
The app that whole photo spread of his apartment.
Do it
Oddjob
Who is Jaws
What who all was on the Celebrity Apprentice
Dan Danny Bonaduce duty is okay
Guy from Poison
Dekuyper
Brett something
Wow you was on the Rock of Love bus
The accused
Bret Hart
Yes this is dumb
I think it's really
Kind of
Troubling
How imprints this idea is that like
No
The people writing g.i. Joe we're trying to warn you
Yeah
Yeah that is
I think that he just said
A radio show in public that would 100% get you
Section 8 it
You know
Fast as you were telling your boss that it work
Listen if you want to understand global politics you need to watch g.i. Joe
You're fired
Agreed
Four Paws
I will not fight back
I'm going to go tell the nlrb's that you murdered me and not already dead
Just trouble
So there is some good news like Alex mentioned earlier
Okay get limp
Quietly
Remove fertilizer off the list
Banned items
Because if you don't
Do that
It will
Billion people in the next two years
Just watch it's always a year
What for
Hey buddy it's going to kill
So the underlying story here's more or less true that
Betty's the sanctions as it relates to medical and agricultural products
Tax which is probably a good thing
Alex's exaggerating things a little bit though
There will definitely be affect but it's premature to assume that it'll be nearly as cataclysmic is Alex's birthday
Disruption the Tappan
Or the reason for this is because of though Russia is a large
Exporter of fertilizer the ingredients used in fertilizer
We don't holy rely on it
Imports for fertilizer nor does any Khan
A lot of it is produced domestically and there are other countries like India and Canada that are potential sources
They can make up some of the difference
It's lost
It's obviously wouldn't be a perfect fit but there are
Some solutions that can be helpful
Be Ripple effects related to cost
And that's not a small issue but they're also Solutions
Explore the country to offset some of that
Challenge
Because it's just
The financial monetary Challenge and if we have the will
And the political will
Some of that would be
Not as difficult
Now it sounds like that's an unsolvable problem that will never handle you know what it probably is
I was joking also on March 11th Department of Agriculture announced
$250 in grant funding for the exploration
Do the best
Stick fertilizer production
An options
This is going to push American industry create new jobs and opportunities and maybe make a dead to the food
Supply issue as a whole
And possibly be you know
The help
Create animations in terms of cleaner
Method
Yeah but I really think that
More money should go to the military
That seems like unreasonable things
Look
Treasury Department rolled back some of these sanctions
Department of Agriculture
Announce these grants for domestic
Exploration of new
Technologies in industry
Alex should be celebrating that
It was B Administration so sorry this stuff doesn't even seem to have happened
That Trump left behind
Sleeper Agent I'm sure that would be the!
Hopewell just because things are happening under the guy that I hate doesn't mean I have to tell people about it
Notify your dumb s***
So we go out to break
Things are G
So you can pretend you're with the establishment you can purr
Pretend
You're a judge
Rogue
Bureaucrat
Fill out your Birthright and destroy the social safety net
And destroy
The checks and balances in chivalry
Better protect us all
Roberts
The last vestiges
Of the Renaissance
Are being swept away as we sit here
Brace yourselves
Jorge
None of that meant anything
What what was he even mad about
I mean you heard the judges things as probably
Yeah
Anything
The last 10 over what what is that what are the last vestiges of the Renaissance
And then chivalry slapping people with glad the right to dual yeah absolutely okay I think we should
Should have that be the the
Unalienable right to be a knight-errant yeah yeah
You need to well I mean you have to spend the night
In prayer without Aunt fasting in order to become a full knight-errant so
What's going on judges are taking away our night of reflection
Before you become a knight
I just like this
It's
Always remarkable to be Whitney
You just have sentences
That go on in
They don't mean anything
I feel good probably to say chivalry is being destroyed
Yourself
Monster Golf
Historically associated with the Renaissance yes I agree
Some of those paint
F****** taters
Alex is mad obviously about Judges probably related to his case
She's also mad about Amanda
Smooth
They can put you in prison for a misdemeanor
Because
There's no 8th Amendment
Anymore
You see that being done to me right now
Another judge the judge is everything and all of creation
Who's that
. oh
Soccer
Excessive bail or fines
No fine but Alex is facing is in any way except
His behavior has been so disrespectful to the court and so flagrantly obstruction is that I probably would say that you deserve more
Excessive if you put a bounty out for a million dollars you could find a million dollars
Or something
I don't know
Hard to defend that one
Unfair
I also I would say that God as Alex is not a great model
For Earth judges
I think sending people to hell is definitely a cruel and unusual punishment
Bigger picture though if you look at goddess some kind of law enforcement
Much bigger than life isn't exercising in trap
And I don't know if
That's cool thing as God just hanging out waiting for you to f******
Yeah
He created
The thing that tempts us to sin which is what sends us to hell and not just that but we have no free will over our actions
Whatsoever anyway so all that we have and we'll do is already been written in the book
Debatable
Depending on your interpretation of the movie knowing
Also I hope
When Alex gets to the Pearly Gates
It's not the hell causes a big scene and complains it like
Peter's book has gold tassels on it
Hibbett Heavens operating under maritime law
Happiness
It's just
This is not a boat
I want my $600,000 back
I
I would love it if
Alex ends up getting sent to hell and there's a
The conspiracy about it
Story that I was lying about earlier and he has some other lies
People doing this
Pay for what they've done
Little Bill
I'm sure you've heard around the country that got bills to keep babies alive for 2 weeks 10 weeks
6 weeks and kill him
Where's Nolan California
California reduces new bill
Don't allow mothers to kill their babies up to 7 days after birth
Peter Singer and Pete on all of always push this
Campbell kill babies
Repita actually
PETA
California
Infanticide bill that would legalize the murder of children
Route 29 months of gestation
And in the weeks after birth
The mill
Has been proposed by Newsom
Future of abortion Council which makes recommendations
Restrictions
Does the State of California
Define
They've already been doing this for a while
They got to do a rear guard action
What
The Christians
Infiltrators
The video of all this
So what's going on here is that Alex hasn't read this article and he has no idea what's in the bill
He just got in the
Opinion on it that's formed from skimming headlines and extreme right-wing blogs written by lunatic so everything's just going to filter through that
I hope he's reading Alex realizes that he needs to find a way to make this make more sense
How is this being defined do you have a week
To kill your baby
Like what what in what world would that be the norm
I'm interested to know there has to be some explanation for that so Alex just makes it up
California is redefining what a baby is
You're not a baby until you're 8 days old
I'd make that clears it up but also its
Totally pulled out of Alex's ass 100%
That's because you need an explanation for the timeframe you just need it
I know but there's another law that says
Babies are people when they're born
What were the Articles that Alex's reading
Don't include that language notwithstanding any other law because they don't want people to realize that they're full of s***
Yeah that's no good
What kind of deceptive almost has the third stage live
Lying about it making s*** up about it
Probably just imagining even worse things
Imagine that
The somebody's eating
These babies for sure
Right
In reality a number these stupid blogs have different time frames
I'm stirring which they claimed it to this bill will allow you to kill your baby because
They're all just lying about the term perinatal death
Whatever the blog decide
That's how long you have to kill your baby according
Perry Isabel Perry Perry is pepper but Terry is a prefix
Derived from Greek meaning
Around
And there's no specific definition for how long perinatal periods May last
It really depends on the pregnancy and with a needs are of the
The parents and child
This is all just a made-up story
You can tell her we could grasp Alex has on it because he's just fabricated details about it to his audience doesn't lose faith
But he knows what he's
It's
It's sad
Yeah you know
It does seem
Almost
Hard to believe
Maybe even impossible to believe
Tire governing body of it
State would be able to
To get away with
Writing a bill that says it's okay to murder your baby for a week
Only for a week
Possible to believe that they could do that
Actually pass it or sign-in or whatever before anybody else but Infowars got ahold of it
Right
I mean like if
You were a
Parrot and you had a baby four days ago and you're like I want to see my baby and then the doctors are like
Not a baby yet you got four more days
What if you are a parent who really hated their baby
And this bill passed on like day five would you be
Concerned would you be like wait
Is this entrapment
If I kill this baby
Mean
I would wonder what the Rams
Applications would be easier like
If somebody
Did
Skillababy cuz they listen to Alex's show and thought that it was legal
Like would Alex get in trouble for that I mean it would be in it
It's hard to imagine that somebody gets that
Far they don't have any any other Inspirations behind
Ate it but Alec I agree
I think a lot of the times these these
Notions and rhetoric and beliefs that are put out into the world have very serious consequences
I wonder if
It's a potentially
Like a things that shoot
You should worry about
F****** coolers in her home now I am more worried about it yet doesn't Inspire confidence
Sharp
Just making up these details to fill in the gaps we realize is like
If I don't explain that the audience might get curious about it and it might look into it why is it a week
Let me find out this is all full of
All but there's another
I want to bring up and I'm not going to play clips of it because I think it's a sort content that wouldn't do the audience any good and I think it's
Grotesque
I've noticed this habit of Alex just making up details about things to flesh out stories
He's particularly prevalent any stories about abuse against children
I've read the reports a new stories about some of the cases he brings up and Alex will just make up lurid details to make them seem
Sensational or make them more easy to fit into his
Conspiracies
It legitimately it's
It makes me sick to listen to Aunt this episode
A particular included some
Census of that that I'm just not going
I've often pointed out how Alex
Who's the person who is way of making money is essentially just lying about tragedies
And I wanted to make sure that it's clear that this extends to him music
Victims of childhood abuse as props that he can profit off of
I honestly was
Conflicted about playing some of the clips
On that team because on the one hand
I know the playing them as the likely possibility of her degree from triggering some listeners
I don't think it adds
Anything really to our understanding of Alex other than he's an a****** which we already know
At the same time I do worry
Sometimes that we are being clear about how shockingly offensive and extreme the show is in the present day
Like I worried
Possibility
That because of
Those editorial choices of
I'm not going
Everybody does this grotesque knots
I'm sure that there's a sugar coating that goes on
Risk of
Sanitizing
A monster like Alex
It's like we've already hit
Where
Normal human being
Kingswood go
F*** off this guy's a monster right we don't need to go past that that's over
I know the episode to the Past we've played a lot of those grotesque
The reason why it doesn't really add anything now is because
That's part of the information base of his show
Yeah I worry though that as there are new our listeners maybe some of the move.
They've gone along with it and
Entire Journey
The date you don't recognize that a lot of this show can be
Disgusting
Very extreme
You know the risk is sanitizing it but what we are doing
Is telling you about it
And all that is being
Sanitized is just a visceral emotional reaction
Can you would have to touch
Disgusting out right like I don't want to
People to
Tweet pictures of
Civilian
Murder By you know I don't I don't want to look at that bright but I
F****** know it happen
You know
Right
Right that's kind of the
BMX extreme
Example
Of it but that's kind of the balance of like
Is not
It is is it
Did Subway sugar coating
To not look at
Before reality of it
And I agree with you I don't think it's our shows place too
Put metaphorical
Pictures of
Dead people absolute people's face
Although I
Just wanted to
Call out vet
I struggle with that decision sometimes because I recognize and I see how bad Alex is
And I worry that some people
Because we make jokes a lot of the time frame
Like I worry that
Some people might have a softer version of him
Then he deserves
As bad as it gets
So
Even as bad as it gets
One of the things you can't take away from me
Is that your ports on really important
Absolutely
His sources are very very
Jit
Like memes
Children one way or another
Reminder cut their genitals off
Don't take
But that's her favorite
Natasha
Tom
Donovan
Cartoon section
What
It's Snow White
Meaning of the image of a
Becoming a woman that powerful images she's coffee as a mentor today
Girl girl
Material Girls coming over
Meeting you was a dream come true
Doesn't say hey let's go out in the forest in
Seeing
Talk to the birds and squirrels
She says let's explore your sexuality
Man in a wig
Telling the childless
Explore your sexuality I mean
I am I mean
I guess if you need
To describe memes in order to
Express your anger and transphobia
Fine
Coming outside
No
You do not this is
Is this a Radio Shack on audio medium
I mean it does sound a little bit like my grandma trying to tell me about a movie she saw 20 years ago
He goes to the place and it at the place
They do all the stuff
Here's what I want to say
Description of the meme is fairly clear
You can kind of imagination
But
It's also
Who cares
Traffic
Yeah
Aren't you supposed to be the guy who talks like Lieutenant Colonel this
Spear my friend
And that's fear is pointing into a meme
You're describing shitpost
Oh yeah comics
Section
Of the Infowars web
Sirius X
Even though we're taking time on the show too
Talk about me
James Wright
The world is also a
What's what
There's a twist
Maybe
Republic
Countdown to 90%
Extermination
Call official apps
Credit
Simultaneously Center
ATL
Liberal
Communist organization
Not going on
Economical
Fox News
How we can
Soft Landing
Speaking of Crash Landings
I don't want Infowars to employ
And so I
Hair supply chain breakdown
Point week
30 week delivery of products
Makeup quality of supplements
That
You you order them you want me to resign if you don't promote them Jones
I had no idea it was
Business manager I dropped the ball on something
But the t-shirts
Absolutely
Because
These are all limited edition Hazard Classics is a
Classics
I can't begin to describe
How as a comic
I could have told you 10 years ago
Don't get that many teeth
Don't do it
We know a million people who have boxes of t-shirts everywhere
Sage advice
I think also
You need to
If you're ordering 63,000 shirts
Video of a warehouse full of shirts or something
Subtract outflow
I have more coming
These are all like old shirts
I don't even
I don't even know how to estimate if that's a lot of shirts for him
I don't even know who took a lot of shirts I don't know how a conversation can work
Eveready functioning business that goes like this
We have a lot of shirts
Alex we have two men
How many how many
How do you not know you have
Seems Unthinkable hell out of
Weird
It's just coming up now
It just now
How many shirts did you order have you been piling up shirts in the corner of the world
Must be thing or shirts don't move
Of course not nobody ever move shirts
Who wants to wear a f****** Infowars shirt very few if you do with the statement
It is
I think people are find possibly putting up in fours bumper stickers cuz you not to wear them
Bright
Different thing
22 walk-around
Yeah my bad idea one person and Infowars clothes
In the wild
It was when I went with Marty DeRosa to show that he was doing in Indiana
And we freaked out
Cuz the guy was wearing
Lolita
I guess the world is ending but good news I got a warehouse full of shirts
I'm a little bit confused how we started that clip of I remember growl world is ending
Dramatic music
End of the clip
We got too many f******
Total chain
Considerable
So others not only
Shirts
Remember a little while back Alex was selling that
Coin
Ono how many coins
We got a nuke
By Patriot collectibles.com
1776 koin.com takes you right there
And this is helping
Infrastructure
Unless
On the deck in the fight
Kaminaka Drive accuweight we're not going to abandon ship shall we need the funds plus as a historic
To have in your pocket
YouTube
Design silver coin by yours truly
The tree of Liberty
The Thomas Jefferson quote on it
Blood
The Patriot
Much refreshed
Dupree of Liberty
Sometime
Graybar probably sold half of them
And we need to get the rest of them out to get funds in
Now
I want to thank you all for doing that Shannon
Total collapse of civilization right away
They were going to watch some very special things for by their founding members give you put your email and when you purchase it if you don't then that
Support
Habistore clemento
Heirloom
Of the Revolutionary War against Satan revolutionary war against Eatonville
That one was 70
G73 though
We have to beat him to even start the revelers level
I think about
Possible that Alex old half
For the coins and a half days
But if so
A drastic decrease
And the number of available from the last time
Because we heard him complain about no one bought the colony but a free to go home around
Send it move
As to why you would want to have what is essentially a terrorist slogan on a coin in your pocket all the time honestly I don't want
Go to my pocket but there is a part of me that would
Want the full set of those three coins
I don't want to give him money and I don't want any more listeners stupid somehow
Ford building
We got to Ocean's 11 this thing we need a second-story man
Pulling up
Callers that we are climbers you here on distraction
Basically the the con in the
What does the Apple
Scott Conant
City Athletic in this city
Alright you can handle a drill haha I got really good
Ears
Reply if you want any part of our oceans 11 game
My library
We're going to have to stand around a really small found
After workout though
Somewhere in Austin
I got so anyway Alex's
Commiserating in
Maintenance
The scary ideas about how Stormtroopers are gone
Going to come in and take everybody out
And it's really just they want to get Alex
And Owen Shroyer
Trouble setting up his whole operation
That's why they hit
Cuz I want to get his balls
People in folks and inheritance present others are doing
Great job show
Continue on but again
Just let you know that we're Two Minutes to Midnight
They're going to everybody Tucker Carlson
Trump
Anybody to populous anybody that they
Control
Anybody that's going to stand up
I am x-ray
Solitary confinement
My most dumbest
It stomped to death down a dungeon
Peacefully
Go forward a number to be christ-like
Oh
That's a really bad news for Alex
If the top
B last after you and Owen gets up solitary confinement Harrison Smith
Import is going to be dead in a week
Harrison's going to be doing
Full on mask off Nazi show on Nick Fuentes a streaming service
That's where you going
More bad news even if only Alex went down and old was still there in Forza
Still be dead in a week
There's no talent in this organization
And other than Alex
He had essentially been worn down by
Drug use bad financial moves
And he was being an unhinged rage-filled a******
Done it's only a matter of time but yes
Infowars we live on
Inasmuch as the
Equipto anti-semites will still spread stupid
Series online
Happy Wheels
Still trying to scam people with
In that sense
Alex's Legacy is very
Secure and his impact will be felt
For years to come call them so much
You know like that
Successors are the kids of Alex Jones so much as like
What happens when a
Mushroom release
The Cloud of spores
So anyway
Alex's
Dark state
Please
Talking a lot of death
Stopped and dungeons
Sure
They want you to know that if his family dies wasn't
Priceline
I will not offensive legal after these people
Are they come
Show me I'm just going to
Get on my knees
Because I'm not going to give them the fight that one
What
But if they common
Murder suicide
That is a lie I did not
Commit suicide and kill my family
That is a lie
You know they killed me and my family they do that
So that's what we're dealing with
But it's okay folks
I chose this I want to fight these people
Politically culturally spiritually
I chose this path
Where I Wanna Be
Funeral
I don't have the General yet
It's right where you wanted to be
And that's exactly where I'm at
Opposition
In opposition of the devil worship
Opposition to the New World Order in opposition to transhumanist
In opposition to the uyghur death camp
Allison said that he does
Don't care about the weaker 100% that that is very clearly
If I'm ever in a situation where I'm having
Preemptively speculate about how stories that I've killed my family are a false flag
I would likely not be exactly where I want
There's probably something it's gone horribly wrong ever in that position
Assume that something is
Very wrong I mean yeah I would assume I'm already dead and that's it
Or you're the person who I say I won't kill or something
This is all fine but it's just chesspub pausing bravado and you've heard this from Alex over and over through the years
Also it's really easy to stand against the pedophiles and demons when you've just imagine
Send them all in your head based on your bigotry
Inability to read past giving right-wing blog headlines
True
The demons aren't real and though there are pedophiles in the world Alex's definition of the term renders it
Essentially meaningless
On the one hand this is all very extreme and insane and probably should be seen as a warning
Zion
Like that might be the case but also on the other hand
Italics
So this honestly just sounds like I'm saying
Come on guys I'm serious
This time give me money I got shirts in a warehouse
When you're sailing with a person
Sindhu just offers up the information that hey
If they if my whole family and I are dead I definitely didn't do it
That's usually about
Red flag
Yeah it's right
I think the people in the good place
Say those things usually
Especially not
Unprompted
But this guy is also said that he would eat his neighbors
So
Talking about in terms of death is very different than a number
Like it's not like a new thought
Right
Pretty extreme
It doesn't come out that often
But
I think it's more just a representation of like
Paranoia
Where is trapped until it's going down
We're going to lose these cattle lost
Cases in rdy matter of time before I know you're broke
If so a Wars is great and that's why everyone lies about that
About us to demonize this all day
Because they know we are the standard
Infowars
In Generations in the fight
Me Mama power
We're the best there is
We've done the best job that means you the list reviewer
Literally I'm not kissing your ass when I say that
You need to know what you've done with your word-of-mouth in your prayers your support
You need to know the
Your TuneIn
A couple million you TuneIn right now are the Vanguard are the whole
Children are future of the innocent being tortured and raped
Begging for God to save them in those dungeons
Play cry out to God
God sent out his Spirit to us
Give us the answers in the motivation to stop the Satanist
God is paralyzed
At an intersection
Because.
Weed
To be his instruments
What
Belongs to
But God works through us
And that is our job now
Peacefully
Exposing me
Their spiritual losers they were always going to lose
Anyone
And take as many of us with them as
They
Possibly can
7076 point will sell out
We need to find
Strong
Okay let me just catch my breath here cuz I'm really freaked out right now
Coming out of scratch the surface on the news have already covered more Stephanie B
Probably discovered 10 hours
What he absolutely has no
Absolutely
You told me about how he was going to kill his family
Could you cover that in 10 hours I could
Not
Yes such a bizarrely distorted
View of his own effort
Like you seems to
I don't know if he
He sincerely thanks but he's actually
Play covered things
The most he's done his rant about his feelings and then read a few headlines
True
Well
He's revealed that he has her
Do many shirts
Oh man
I mean right in time for Christmas
Do you know
It is it is interesting that that quote was
The tree of Liberty must be watered with the peaceful blood
He definitely didn't just tell people to go murder his political enemies vengeance is the Lord's
But he said that the Lord said the Lord needs you
To do is Vengeance for it did you know that
The Bible's all Biden
Information Warfare
They did not
I did not know that the Bible is all about how God is like
Dudes you got it
Take care of this s*** form and he'll is actually just
Information base
And there's a different dimension
Mahathir trying to break through I don't I don't
Obviously
The message
Just getting across
That is
You guys got to kill you guys got to kill
Sing a cowardly and safely
For legal reasons yes the point is still there and and go f*** yourself
Peacefully doesn't even count if you
You say it like that
You don't eat does
It's taken away and all you
You did was tell people to kill was that cough there too a little bit
Robot dogs without speakers in for Shanghai lockdown
Surprised and concerned Poison Control issues Nationwide talks
If you ain't want it would kill you
Substance used commonly in
Pest Control
You don't eat cuz I don't understand how that is a question whatsoever
That should not have been I don't think that should have been a headlock
Justin answers desperate to attack
The very idea of taking covid seriously that
Yeah a warning that there is a reagent that can be harmful if
Eaton
It is somehow an indictment
Like six thermometers were eat a thermometer
Just don't randomly put it in your mouth why would you put it in your mouth in the first place
Dangerous for babies
Certainly it unless they're under 7
Stop power off
Yeah childproof
I have
Identityiq
Challenge drink your covid-19
I don't know why
I don't know how you get to a point where you're this
Bike
We are standards of this low
Dhoni covid test
What a scandal it makes more sense than Tide Pods
I guess
What you want
So we're going to need
A lot of vaccines
I keep going of course
There's another one
Says all Americans will need 4th covid-19
There are a million other six shot
And Israel fifth shot in Europe
I only laugh because
I did not cry
Are people like listening to this show that is not paying attention at all
Months ago Alex's reporting at Israel's on it seventh shot but now they guess they've gone backwards
Making s*** up as he goes along on 9 by 9
He can't keep track of where is narratives are cuz they're not connected to reality and they don't mean any
Alex is reporting on a Daily Mail article and when I went to look at this there were some red flag
Here's the headline
FDA Vape
Maxine Chief says all Americans will need fourth covid-19 vaccine shot in the
The fall
But here's the sub-headline
Go to dr. Peter Mark
What's the fda's top vaccine regulator says Americans may need a second booster shot
And fourth overall as early as this fall
I'm sure you can see the problem
In the headline says we will need the shot but in the sub-headline it says we met
There's a bit of a
Editorial blunder here in this is something that should have been caught before it went to print because it
It seems like the headline
Might be an exaggeration
The article claims that marks was on a conference
It's call with reporters
Said that he believes all Americans will need a fourth vaccine shot as soon as this fall
But that's not reflected by the
The quotes that are attributed to him
In the article
They do quota
It would not be surprising
If there's a potential need for people to get an additional booster in the fall along with a more General boost
A campaign
If that takes place
I went my listen to the whole conference call and I didn't get the sense that marks
Who sang that everyone is going to need a booster
But the people should
Consider it as a serious option
I think at this headline
Might have been a little bit
Exaggerating
Alex's
Lying about it I like maybe the Daily Mail has their own kind of
The grinder in a clique basic economy
You could be my baby
So Alex is mad about it
Case
Deposition
Tried to skip out on me
It's so close
Just so close if he had
Gone to work the next day I mean probably still wouldn't respect
You people are
Just beyond
And
We got this job in Connecticut
You can call it that
Mustang
Wait the state
Cheated us every way white about us if we didn't give him this
Thanks for not giving him the Sandy Hook marketing
Unicorn
That one lady
I know you got I know you got a leprechaun
And that was when she first started
How to get three depositions with myself
Hey I'm not feeling well I need to move it
Put you in jail
Compounds everyday
The 1.6 million dollars
Appearance
So you know what
I'm going to go up there
Jamaican zombie
Cuz at least I'm a grown man I know God
Imma watch some kidneys lepus dungeon they're raping
People got got to deal with that's all I can tell you
Okay
Little bit weird that was very weak
Could have just gone to your deposition you dick I really feel like maybe you're just blowing this whole
Google thing out of proportion didn't work like a giant child who's not getting
It's way because you try to pull a stunt
That sounds childish
Yeah
Yeah could be and I'm going to throw this out
Okay what if
He had done different things
All of you so different
Any wouldn't have these consequences
So different
World of difference
Also
Two things one
He stands to get
Some of that money back
If he does appear for the deposition
CS2
He's just trying to sell shirts to make up the money that he's going to have to pay the courts
Yep
Such a parasitic it is a vicious cycle
Listen I want to sit for your $25,000 deposition
But if I don't go to work I'm not going to sell $25,000 worth of merch
Trouble
So Madison cawthorn
Talked about
Hotel party
Hell yeah
You're going on in GOP circles
How would he know nobody
He's inviting that loser
Obviously Democrats
Not going to give Daddy party is probably a persona non grata
He'll do that to you
Yep
So Alex needs
Talk about this story
There's only one person
You can call in
Gentlemen Welcome to our number to Rochester
Information Madison cawthorn
And his big exposure of what's now being called orgy gay
By who
And a Sprite with the corporate media has told you
Madison cawthorn has not
Canton
But he was invited
Georgi and cocaine Parties By the way
Cool
You can't really get better and simultaneously worse
Then Rogers totally
If you could be the go-to expert on orgies foremost
Political talk shows
Right but the problem is he has to play this repentant act especially in this world
I can't be like man when I was back in
Doing those or junko parties I was having a grand old time
I don't know why Madison cawthorn tried to ruin it for everybody good clean fun
Listen how business was done
If anybody rides
Should be mad at Madison cawthorn because he's he's snitching the same way that they said Sean Rogers
I just been through a wheel of fortune
How many cities do you think Alex has been invited to order
Probably actually but we only hear few of America
I'm not just been invited
Andy's
Which outfit
Andela I wish I'd declined
I have been invited to be in the hellfire club
At one of the two most famous universities
Global organization that was started by Sir Francis dashwood in the 1700
Alex is trying to imply that it's still rock and roll in in
Unfortunately couldn't come up with the name
When grasping for a British University I was wondering if he was going to get there or if he was trying later in the episode
A bunch of weirdos we get together and do things that work
Considered taboo back in those days and certainly a good deal if it was probably sexual in nature
Things that weren't allowed in polite society that you were able to do
Remember
It was a real straight-laced a stye
I really allowed to cut loose
Wright also there's a whole lot of
And also the Earl of Sandwich was a member
That was a thing
I I don't I don't
I don't think that the hellfire club is
Is nearly as fun as the name
No and that's kind of an unfortunate thing is a kind of lives on because
Cuz of the names
Invited to a
Tools like every time he sets foot outside of Texas someone's trying to get him to do weird sex stuff
I mean I can't
Think of any reason why
Yeah it's like oh my God
I have set foot
The state border
Oh my God I must Retreat to my puritanical
Welcome to Oklahoma we're going to f***
Everybody here like the fuc
If it's your first day in Oklahoma
I'll tell you about the secret handshake here and it's fun
It's the Oklahoma hello
Weird
Seems to come up in his life more than most
People that seemed unusual
Go see what usual I have been propositioned 40 or
What's the technical definition of an orgy
I think it's got to be for plus I really feel like I'm I want to say double digits
It's but that seems It Go
If anything under 10 was an orgy that would really cut down on the number 40
Worldwide per capita
Yeah I'd say six sounds right
6 is a good start
The organized
But that could be tough
So anyway Alex but he recently talked about meets with these globe
He just did Reese
And the left always hear stuff like this it freaks out and I guess they wish they could
I just look at everything We Do It Center
Cutting Edge
And
It over the years I've had a chance to have meetings with three different Bilderberg Group
And just had one few weeks ago
Anime
But what is a real world
And so
Hawthorne has a lot
Doing what he did because
To go to the orgy switcher just like
Just like an ant houses that look
Just like that
Victorian style French style
Oz
Or they've got
Famous caves in the UK where the hellfire club
I need a lot of good things and things
Much dead body to catch this house
What
What's yourself full-circle on that so there were bones that were dug up under
Benjamin Franklin's home call children and it wasn't weird rituals or murders
A medical student
Play William Houston lived with Franklin and he was engaged in illegal anatomical studies
It was against the law back then to perform human dissection
Research
It probably involves some
Stolen dug up bodies but it probably didn't directly involved
Ben Franklin
It's nothing at all like Alex's
Implying also that was a regular thing that with people stole bodies
All the time
Yeah grave-robbing was much more
More comment
I think
That there's another issue
I'm having a little bit of trouble
And that is
Did Alex
Keep taking these meetings with these globalist sure
Yet they're murdering children
Constantly
Why is he meeting with people who are engaged in demonic
Ritual murder of children
More importantly
Why is he so respectful of their privacy
Cuz they seem to be murdering children
Off the Record
Have you had their chefs cook
It's so good
You can't piss off cut off from
Yeah
I think it's a hole and his plot
And I think his audience should be more offended by
His meetings with globalist if they are
The way that he describes them to be
Yeah
I wouldn't take a meeting with with George W bush
And expect
To stay off the Record
Like I don't even
Think that they're like
Demons destroying the world that I wouldn't take a meeting with someone like who was interested in doing ads
Something
I wouldn't take a meeting with Alex
Absolutely probably not even some of these
Business Partnership with 100 hits people
Maybe it's
Maybe it's a maybe I'm legitimately is him like
I mean obviously I don't think
But it's not real
Assuming it's real in this fantasy version 2 price
One foot out the door just in case
I don't know
It's all it's all
Speak no more made up stuff
Public School indoctrination real 4th grade teacher
Austin
Told her piercings a summer class came out as lgbtqia
Then she told him to
Around here
That won't get Center.
So this is an interesting story because Alex is reading from a post on a website called The Liberty daily which is basically just a board
Extreme right-wing clone of The Drudge Report
Mixing with their aggregated lengths they also have their own blog post
Guys advertising
Quote for spring freshen up your bedroom with Mike lindell's
Jesus.
Sheetz now 60% off
So this article about the
This 4th grade teacher has precisely one source and it's a Twitter account
I called the lives of Tik-Tok
That account post is completely anonymous unverifiable images of what's claim to be quote in
Internal messages
Easily be anything from like a YouTube comment
Something I cooked up on a Notes app
There's no sourcing or traceability of this
Nonsense there's no reason at all
Outrage bait
Depot
Perfection standards Ark
Essentially we have a situation where an unscrupulous Twitter account posted thing
Which is that written about by a drudge clone funded by Michael
Glendale stories covered by Alex who is it least is or has been
Confronted by Mike Lindell
This is all just a lotus
That was what I was getting at
CenturyLink
Alex brought up
How do you say Joe is
It is real
Sure
We didn't do is Cobra Commander voice
Yeah that is
That is weird
I think he regrets that
And we needs to get an impression
It's crazy and you read the stuff they're teaching
Third graders
Shove
Sex toys in their rear ends I mean
Jocelyn elders
Surgeon General nominee under Clinton
Timer for
That's what they do in public can you imagine who they really are
She said even though she said it I mean
Do you
Very Joker
Play John Professor Mark Dice I teach genders
California State University
Cross the country been making tremendous progress
We better Deuces you know
List of
57 different gender identities
So I guess
Mark Dice made an attempt at a comedy video skewering gender
C.a. Johnson Elders that's
Not true
His version of this is
The salt that's all
A tweet that was written up in a drug
Cologne that's funded by Mike Lindell
We've got
A meme
Alex reported on earlier
Now we got Mark Dice
Doing a dumb comedy video
I just think that the
The
Beer buddy
Nobody is doing
Things
This good
Baby nobody
Is doing things like this this
I would take the good
Yeah what a load of trash
I think Mark Dice
Gets a lot of views on stuff chair
Alex might be a little bit jealous
Maybe feels like he wants to get in on the game
Particularly
The only mention the Mark Dice is wearing a green wig
He looks a little Joker at
I think Alex
Who's feeling the call to put on a wig
But I only told listeners
Go to city council go to County commission's go to school board
Because
Did you just goes viral
This is the place to go
And okay maybe just the city council and 5,000 people watching mobile cables
But most of these millions of views
I am going to create a new character
Call Peter power something
And I guess the city council
I'm a repeat real quotes
The great words of Jocelyn elders
We need
Masturbate the babies
I need to reach down and grab their genitals
Peter Peter women
Beaver Dam
Real
Quotes of these creepers
Can you imagine how drunk he would be if he did that
Bike
Ohia
Fall over the podium just screaming at these people like
You be taken out because like you're not going to let Alex Jones then if Alex
Disney dress like Alex Jones
Mumbai
You might know
I know you would
Look
It's open forum
Citizens
Yeah but he
I mean just cuz you stole rainbow snatches wig sitting around it.
Doesn't mean that nobody's going to be like
Hey we can't have Alex Jones at this meeting
He's going to disrupt
I even listen to show the other day
He's going to sell things that he thinks are quotes
Right I do think that would be a
Interesting
That disease in a wig
Trying to do a terrible character misquoting people to make an argument
Yeah yeah
Well here's a good news Alex has no follow-through
Probably going to happen
You still haven't even sold sold in either shirts
Still hasn't done that
The maid that show with all the colors
2 going on
Hey I'm here
Alex believes that
Call Schwab
That makes sense
Spots also
Starts rambling about how important it is that
But he
It's been part of the eve of the revelation
Bilderberg
He comes up with
Luminary
Names
That fight alright
Well they're executing yours of Klaus Schwab
Who is the head of the Bilderberg Group
Member out shelves are supposed Bilderberg Group in the meeting with Satan existence
I made films showing in existence
Just 15 years ago
And now you see why the Bilderberg Group is so important because we got their
We had the sources
You work the people that have been covering Bilderberg Group for 40 50 years
People that receive the
Brain Trust
Died like 89 years ago
Good friend of mine
And of course myself another one
Go get him back on I mean this is the real Global controlling Force
Alex seems to be able to come up with three names of people who study Bilderberg and they're all lunatics
Westbrook pegler was a fascist Jim Tucker is the was the editor of the Holocaust denying a Neo-Nazi
Leaving outlet and Daniel estulin wrote a book about Bilderberg
Included information resource from a captain of
Intergalactic Army
Bewise
Claimed
This is a good company
These are bunch of losers
Jim Tucker died when it's hat
That's how
Secondhand smoke
Yeah
At what a bunch of losers shity crew
Can you imagine saying those names thinking like
Woohoo I got a murderer's row of here at 3 last
Jim Tucker
A fascist from the 50s
So
Look I think that we've gotten used to the idea that Alex thinks
Expect movies and TV shows are talking
I think that's
Just got it like we've become numb tonight
This introduces a new
Things to be worried about
How many times did I tell you that robot dogs
Marching up and down the street
Very by ioi
I told you that ten years ago there's a video of it
Specifically exactly
Didn't because to actually make myself see the next phase of this
He's so horrible
And show
Multifaceted
That I almost
This isn't how it works but
It is just crazy
Almost existed so I know it's not us doing it they're the ones doing it but I mean
Pubs
This is
Vast civilization collapse
Robots taking everything over
Nothing like this
Planet ever seen
Here is abiding again not knowing what planet he's on
Thing is that for shot
I'm going to get my second booster shot
4 shot
You saying I'm not sure why I'm doing this on a stage
Not know where he is
He's fine now I'm concerned
Because it appears to
Oh yeah
From this
What do you think might be
Concerning about what he just said
Worrying
Speaks things into
Exist any possible that he believes he is making things happen by saying the word
Right
Yeah
Well you said that's not how it works
Snow
He did seem
Solipsistic
Will do cuz things exist outside of him
He is the root of all things
Narcissism people leaving the date you speak
Future into existence
Do I make the play
Plants grow
If I wasn't here I'd have no evidence
Everytime I look the plants got bigger by looking I made the plants go breaker that day. Just makes perfect sense
Now I've forgotten about every single
The millions of times I've said things that have been wrong
Haven't come to pass
It's our kind of thinking that maybe everything I say comes true really good thing that it does
Otherwise once again we would be a smoldering pile of nuclear record
Chicago Beef
We've been bombed with nukes
Six times over the past two years or whatever
This dude's
Bucked up
Anyway Rodger comes in
And Rodger knows about these orgies
You know why why
He planned to be planted
I mean he's repented of it
Not judging in Worcester
Viral right now
That Madison cawthorn the Congress and talk about the
Get on
And and the Carson did not
Actually
He just said he was joking or wasn't real
So yeah Rodger knows about it cuz he used to run them
I think that's
I think that there's something
Pretty impressive
But I mean like
Hosting a game night is hard
Do you mean the
The organizing used to play baseball
These guys are hard it is to get a bunch of grown adults together to like
The text thread I can't do Saturday
Yeah imagine if you're hosting an orgy people are going to
Be pretty critical of the ambiance
Getting a playlist together and actually
Yeah the mood
Food what food
I mean naturally
You have to
Sure right you don't we order pizza
Maybe you have a chocolate fountain
Fondue situation
The time frame
When you got to get Caterers you can trust
Dial yeah well they probably want to join the orgy
The problem
A lot of administrative situations is what we're dealing with Rodger had to do with all of that headache
Right but he's now repent
Nobody's ever rat Fox quite like the guy who ran over
True
So Rogers interviews going to start but before we do there's a John bowne
Spitaliks going to play
Rodger Stone on orgy a transition T minus 6 minutes but I wanted to go to report
John bowne put together
About
Reporter Joe bags
Who's being held
Show me install gulag
For crimes he didn't commit
Staff sergeant Joseph Biggs was born during the ominous year
Okay call my guy
Violated parole
He didn't but he's one of the Coca
Conspirators boys
Conspiracy
And so Alex's is
Is
He's speaking out for his guy
His former reporter John Powell put a piece together
No man's land that doesn't play on Bose radio station
You know I care but not that much
Is it going to sell me some shirts
Rodger Maybe
So
Quick question
How are you spell
Digo o r g y
I could see Anais situation but it is that I just
I don't know
Yeah Yang seems like a tough
Difficult to do
What's the point of adding gate to things if you're hyphenating everything now it's got to be portmanteau
Yeah that's
I know but I just drove by and it looks
Wrong let's let the audience decide
I don't know
Orgi gate that's not it
Alex pretends
Rodger like
You can say whatever you want about him
Always been
Honest
About
We have seen Madison cawthorn the
Republican congressmen come out until he was invited
Orgies and cocaine
Well I mean
Cocaine party
In d.c.
Rodger Stone was one of the top lobbyist ever
He was a
Performance
Really hit it
Do this was underage people or any night absolutely hit it and was not honest about it note for quite a while
Very much engaged about that
He blamed the former employee of the Levi
You could say that he hit it and then did not quit it
Madison cawthorn. Back
Act like walking back
His claim that
Fair enough but you did get a Stern talk
Thing 2 from Kevin
McCarthy realize that if you didn't
Additional gop's
Support and the party might get behind a
The primary challenge in that would not be hard to defeat Madison
Think so blame the left for everything
My comments on a recent podcast appearance calling out corruption have been used by the left and immediate
Disparage my Republican colleagues
Then falsely insinuate their involvement in illicit activity
The left I got to stop right there because Madison was the one disparaging his colleague
I know we'd the left were using him doing those things which he clearly would never have
I've done if the lieutenant told him to do it maybe I just covered his words and then the left on Twitter made fun of him
Not its they didn't do this
This is pathetic
Consider for several days how best to address this controversy
The culture in Washington
Is corrupt
Compromising activities occur because when other people can place you in compromising positions they can
Control hue
It's all about power but my colleagues and I are fighting that corruption
That's dumb but whatever
A little bit later quote
Western North Carolina you sent me to Washington to change the culture
If you want Washington to operate without accountability send someone else
What kind of dishonest
Madison
Naming any names and no one's being held accountable here at all
All he's done is talk show
Some s*** and hijack a bunch of leadership
And with this statement revealed why he would never be invited to an orgy in the first
This demon ends quote
I will not back down to the Mob and I will not let them win
Continue fighting for many years to come
Who is the mob
You are sweet I think you'd be cooler if you went
Madison
Interstate Auto podcast
Very well may have been real and now
But he can't keep his mouth shut
Are the people who invited him to the
The party is the mom
Where is Twitter in the media or laughing at the thing he chose to say all podcast
I'm not sure I really understand but I do think the statement doesn't really help at all
It's probably cooled things down with McCarthy but Madison maybe I'll borrow time
The GOP leadership taking them seriously as someone they can
Canntrust after the
This point imagine it's off to the Marjorie Taylor Greene Matt gaetz world for him
Going to be at least
The Americans
Going to go ahead and send it
The kiddie table over there
Be really loud
Well just got a point here and that is what everyone's doing this
Hemorrhoids during f****** drug or Juiceman
Anybody out there who thinks
That the ruling Elite in Washington DC
Or Malibu
Or Manhattan
Or Hollywood
Do not engage in drug-fueled orgies
Is out of their mind
And all of those
In the media
And in the Congress
Cornell
Attacking Madison cawthorn stop and ask yourself
Why are they doing
Who
Who are they covering
Or is it themselves
I can answer why
People are attacking Madison cawthorn
People are
I think of the issues that Madison never said who you was talkin
About not cast a wide net of Suspicion on everyone in the GOP which the GOP was naturally not happy about
When you say something like you didn't you don't name names
Anybody
Could be who you're talkin about
Which is no good for all the people who didn't invite him to a Coke orgy
Right similarly people on the left
The meteor annoyed that he didn't name names because without that element
It's just not the right way
Ding dong talkingshit on a park
It seems to me from everything I could tell about the story fit everyone will be totally fine with Madison
If you did what he's pretending to do
Switches hold power account
If you truly does have a problem with these Coke parties in orgies that he has a responsibility not to justkass reply to meeting list
Sudan actionable accusations
What does speak specifically about who's abusing their power
He's not doing that which people right
We find annoying
It's a liability in the
Upcoming midterm
If you talking about like Republicans
Who are invited to parties
Any Democratic Challenger can use that against their opponent
Because he didn't really want to have the
Party of Coke
The orgies do you want to vote for this
Houston
Basically handed a weapon to political position
I mean it's like
McCarthy had to have sat him down and just been like listen
I know
You did what we all do
Which is
Go on a podcaster some s*** and talks
Open podcast
That's what they do they go on background
But you talk about the left doing it you don't say that the GOP is doing it you can say that all blanket
Leftist politicians are fugly make it believable be like I have some
Some staffers were friends with staffers Apollo 11
Wheelworks
Together and I've been there you know you don't
Save at the GOP does it you don't
You don't bite the hand that feeds Madison that's what he say yeah it's
It's too much
Of a liability
When you don't speak
Specifically
And
I think to not understand that dynamic
Is pretty dumb
Yeah it's suggest that he was raised in a generation of right-wing politicians that
Absolutely have no concept of Subs
Whatsoever
Rodger thinks he's going to get mocked
For his days of
Being a liberty
And I would suggest
You said it at the beginning and I won't run away from it I was a libertine in my days
In Washington so I attended some of these parties
Cocaino wasn't for me
Prefer my faith in Jesus Christ that's why I feel that the
The power and the strength to speak out and tell the truth
Unafraid to tell you the truth
I know that I'll be mocked
We're coming on and saying this I know I'll be attacked
For you know for the life that I abandoned
When I was a high roller and Washington
In d.c.
Available
I'm a different person today
I think I think
No I
I think Rodger Stone as a reformed character is makabu
Regular Liberty
Is hamaca the world is Loki's shitbag
Is his f****** you can't defeat of what you going to say oh you're so disgusting
What do you got a liar of course I am
Look at what I do but now that is on
Christian
I have reformed it's giving me the strength to speak
Go fuc yourself
It's not fun
Tuvix
Cocaine absolutely
Yeah
More worried
Is if he was telling the truth
There is a reason that he left all the other drugs that were not not for him off the
Irrelevant
Keep up song nobody would ever invite Madison cawthorn
No ears ears what it is
Okay everybody assume
That they are getting up to more f****** sex stuff because they have more memes right and if you had
More memes
Some people would be like well
You know I'd like to f*** eight
People butter I'm broke and I don't have a friend
You don't have any special power UK
But the fact that you assume everybody's doing it is
Speakers
Crooked people
Don't want to f*** a peep
People through exhaust so bad
On paper. Probably use
My house
I agree and I think
I also think
That some amount of like
Swinging kind of
Things and
Cocaine as long as it's not like
Carnival
Like I don't think that those are nearly as Extreme as they're being made to sound
I think the right wig is way far behind
With the left
Is tolerant of these days where they like oh my God and we're all sitting over here like
Man what there's a sex club down the street go
Have fun I think if it's like
Off-hours and it's not
Something where politicians are using
Bears
Status as a politician to force people into doing orgies with them or something
Whatever
Live your life
Cute what I think
What do you think
I don't
Know if
Going to an
An orgy is nearly as
Black available
Well I mean
Leverage in a hotel room
We do know he was set up
He said so himself can't argue with that
I think I think
There's this notion that like this is how they're going to be able to Blackmail you can
No it's that's that potent snow
Well they still live
You still live in the old times where it's like if he comes out as gay that everybody's going to lose their s***
Insinuation
I'm kind of that Kevin McCarthy is
Okay
You have to question
Why Kevin McCarthy is so anxious to cover this up
Why is she so anxious
Silence is Junior member of car
Why are all these
Rhino
The woodwork
What are they hiding
What do they have to hide where they at some of these parties
Is that that's my question
Well we also know it doesn't
McCarthy live with another man
Famicom model of the White House together and they like
How old is the president in there
Well he is it is alleged that he
Weather upholster
Republican polls
Think much of
Who's got the worst toupee
Ever seen in my entire life
I'm so yeah that's that's kind of weird
Super
Understandable why someone he and other non
Insane
Wings of the
Republican Party
Would be very again
Champs this
From a logistical perspective nothing to do with Togo
Yeah I mean and also what you going to do
Go out on TV and say listen
Madison cawthorn is ripe
Some GOP people having cocaine-fueled orgies
Sure but not meet with but that exacerbates the exact same problem
Also what they're talkin about is during the pandemic Kevin McCarthy rented a room from notorious pollster Frankel
I stayed in a room and wants his house while he was in DC during
That's what they're using
To imply that maybe you gay like to dress up like the president today
Facsimile room
Letter b
For me personally
Yeah
I genuinely thought he said upholsterer
Terrible way to get
I'm so Rogers interview sexually disappointingly short
He's only in for
Quick-hit Buffet
Hades orgies are happening I know cuz I've been there baby name names
Madison really should have
If you but then again
He was just talkin
Let me know what
He doesn't want the consequences of saying names actually want to hold anybody accountable
He wants to talk some s*** and sound cool and interesting wants to sound so cool without considering
Consequences and the lotus
But he's putting on his
GOP colleagues
The damage that he's doing
So is your stupid and
I'm sure you got a good talking-to
Because the rest of the episode not worth listening to
I can't think of a better 360 went out there the one we're about to talk about right now
I hope everyone I hope you listen to
I pushed him a little bit like Rodger state
Stone came on
This guy
Dying
Commercial
Talk about something
Things that are common knowledge to good tax attorneys
But it's like unknown magical General Public
Is here with us you can go to Jones tax relief.com
Oh no
Alex talks to his tax relief
Fantastical
I will say that from I could turn it off after about a segment
The 16th Amendment hasn't been ratified
So that's progress
That's good this guy was just saying that like I'll hunt down loopholes for you
Yeah
But you know
Probably not ones that you can actually use
I would assume that a lot of people in Alex's audience
Might not have
A lot of financial
Here's how you can get rid of your investment
Unrealized gains tax
Taxes if you
I don't think I
I can use that
One can I write off
Metal coin
Infowars can I write off yeah
Their war bond what's the value of my war bonds in terms
Tax write-off
Uber business
Sixpence sure
So we come to the end of this 666 episode 66
And yeah boy
Alex
Ohio
What a lot of bulshit Laden on true stories
Alex
Insisting that he won't kill his family
Probably
Probable
I mean
Nice video
Telling people to Kayla's imagine enemies because God needs
Them to peacefully
Peacefully
And also insisting two people to go to City Council or school board meeting
Tron cast
Is the Joker no that's for him and him alone
Jordan will be back with another episode
Until then we do it sounds right. Com
We are also on
We are is that knowledge
Until then I'm Neo at Leo and bcx you so much again
They got mama shark eat
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color