Important
I have great respect for snowledge b b
Need money
Fight.com
But the altar of Selena
Jordana
My bright spot today Jordan I guess is that I have decided
Your the mustard is happening
There are going to be details revealed
Do this differently than last time
But it was a first draft
Right alright we learned a lot of lessons from
Absolutely have to have a
Fearless inventory of failures
I took some time I searched my soul and I've identified
Real basic things that were done wrong right correct those of those wrongs
And make this the best ever
Of course our gears begin on 4/20 0420 will be the beginning
That makes perfect sense and everything else
Stoner New Year or something
So your mustard is going to happen
Get hyped
From the government headquarters
Fear the mustard is
Yeah I'm very excited I have
So many
The mustards I'm excited to try to put a new section on the website
Where to
The house the domestic
The mustard reviews there will be pictures of each mustard as well that wasn't like I failed last year this is one of the family
Pictures of myself with all the Seltzer's
No no no this year
Pictures of myself
Selfies
Mustard selfie
We do
We can do it for the gram but it's okay because that
I'm excited
My bright spot is by my wife
I'm legally obligated to do that we're on a podcast
That may be the real reason not respect for any pigs
Purchased for me for my birthday
A bicycle
I saw that
Did you know the bicycles are expensive now I am willing to throw out my first-ever absolute
Unqualified advertisement
Not paid for
Bikes is f****** incredible is that the name of the company that's the name of the place Chicago Company
It's f****** amazing they
Take old bikes
Refurbishing a few hundred bucks
Places Coolidge it everybody works there is like
Knows too much about bicycle kind of like a little bit ago recycling that's good
It's your birthday
Is the first like I've had about 10 years the last one I had or was stolen after 3 weeks
Sure
Fingers crossed
Are you wearing a helmet
Safety First
Safety First Jordan today we have an episode to go over we are back in the past
Phone number for
July 25th
A couple reasons
The first is that Alex was out of town for most of this week
Going to do his deposition
Connecticut Connecticut
Tilly deposition in can I get a lot of the money back
So it wasn't that costly although ticket emotional cost of Hangout
That was Norm pattis
Yasso
MasterCard commercial
But the opposite
Priceless
In reverse
Studio for a good time and honestly
I think the
Largely
Infowars content of the present day
You can
Pretty much predict everything that they're going to be talking about
It's going to be a fication and more
Extreme
Versions of this
Labeling lgbtq
Teekyuu Folk
As grooming
That whole narrative there going to be a flying bat
Going to be yelling about Supreme Court
It's going to be Alex justifying Putin
Behavior
I don't know I'm not into it there's nothing more to say about his transphobia that we didn't already cover with his whole body
Phobia 20 years ago right now that's one of the things that I kind of find is a sticking point
Frozen the trans people the trans Community to try and wedge their f****** nightmares bulshit into the rest of our lives
Scary
Unacceptable in every way and Shelby not tolerated
I want to go back to the past
Little bit of
A business
I believe little bit of an announcer
That is we have
Crazy monkey
Coming out you are going to be on vacation on your honeymoon
Quotes
Henrico
I sure will be gone
Damn then you're going to be back
And then
April 25th
Alex's trial in Austin begin
And we will be going to Austin I mean we don't have a choice really it's
Yes
But we have to approach it with an air of
More dignity I don't want you dressing up
I was like David Knight not going to happen
I'll be at we're going to be in Austin
For an extended stay over the course of the the trial and ideally
Providing
Daily update
Ideal situation
Fiery we won't have regular episodes during that time it will be a
Two-week miniseries yesterday we of our adventure in Austin at the truck
It'll be interested yeah we've never done that before
No we have not charted territory it is a great wide open and we'll see if it's a complete
Disaster
Oh yeah I mean we'll just do it till where you'll pretend
You play a clip right and I'll try and remember what it was Alex and I'll do the voice-over maybe they will talk about it like I did
There may be no clips
Stuff to look forward to there's some other stuff
I may do it episode about Russell Brand
Still thinking about that all things are possible
Yeah this is
At this month
Is that what looking out in front of it
Yep yep but when we look back at it'll be great
Finger store we will be dead by then
You know who knows its possibility
Like I said we got this episode to go over but first let's say hello
The first Rodger Stones orgy janitor
Thank you very much space now I have to Nuke the moon but thank you so much you're now
Playboy Buddy Rose thank you so much you're now about as you want
Action rowsdower
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much
That spaghetti is a good dog please don't throw it at the wall also hi Mom thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Could you very much and we got a couple of
Technocrat
To the first
Thank you so much you and I were technocrat to my wife can't remember what episodes are shout-out is on so here you go Kristen
Correction
The last episode
We called the Spurs
Oh no they threatened
Legal action I mean that is reasonable and so
I have to say
Bosque you are now
I have
Risen above
Miami
Go take a little break now
A list for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for YouTube
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the crew in The Listener just
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having right now
I'll be better tomorrow
Is tomorrow is the past
You better than the present well he will be better yesterday that
And Tomorrow Comes Today
And that's not good be good
No so we start off here and Alex is getting a little bit introspective
About how he never does his job
I can appreciate a little
Stories
Went through the
Imprinted
We
Absolutely not there were not several hundred that he covered on Arrow
Kind of appreciate
One thing you could do is really gay the slow news day we're going to catch up on things to slip through the crack
100 news stories in the last 4 days
I mean
Explain to me
At what
Point you decide
I'm never going to cover more than
50 store
Oh man
Right so then let's only print out 50 store what are we doing print out 200 so are you doing that for
Need more than one page you need one page that has a couple of talking points on it
A couple of headlines
F****** needs a vision board
Lichen
Front of him with with copy and pasted or like a magazine articles like a ransom note in front of him that he can just
Read off of
Is The Drudge report's front
Make it big
Alex has a story out of the San Francisco Chronicle
This is a big big big news
This is one of the ones you miss
Right
Runoff rate
Borders New World Order killed
That is full name
Watching if not
Liberal
Find this exact article about in the San Francisco Chronicle
Chronicle from around this time
I know what he's talking about
Basically if it's the former mayor of Los Angeles Richard Riordan
He had said that he was going to run but he wouldn't
If Arnold ran
Right until more liberal Republican. That's what Alex is talking
I guess
This is around the same time that the Bohemian Club meet
At the Grove word that maybe they wanted Arnold to run right over there,
Drops out before maybe he necessarily even began
Campaigning
For the governorship very excited
About the recall election is about to happen at Alex's life because
This was
Wild stuff
Silver like 200k
Jerry Coleman Ram it was absolutely.
Mary Carey I mean yeah
It was one of the it was one of those things where you're like
Yeah yeah that is one of those uniquely California things whatever is much
Guy from Florida Etc
You know the rules
California has those completely different sets
Things really like donuts
Happen here in Illinois election of 2003
Is
Probably one of the more bizarre in
Like event
Of the state politics
Ignore the wacky race
And I definitely is
Like I can't wait to see it through Alex's eyes
You know that
That's all he already sounds
I don't know what he thinks about Cruz Bustamante but I have
I hope he tries to say his name at least once I would love it if
I don't know who Alex Wood back
Put put could end up being a Coleman guy
This really
Gets me going because you know because a lot of really dark topics
It's sometimes hard to dwell on those too much
And this I think will be fairly silly
Alex will be very mad about for no reason
I'm so weak we have some predict
Addictions that Alec
Text makes that I think are not very
We're on the edge of war with North Korea
In October
I want I want that
Pick up the idea
North Korea nuking us would happen and you
Still insisting these pictures of Saddam sons and the whole thing is fake which is
It does it does make me laugh about if it back on how a lot of people were like
North Korea has nukes
They're crazy
They could nuke us at any time
And now we live in 2022 and it's like
They still couldn't
Shoot of Rocket far enough to hit us with a nuke
Not a chance
It's 20 years later and there's no way they hit us with a nuke
I think you're probably right but I also think that
It is in these conversations
It's always best to approach with a little bit of a reputation no no no no no no
This whole California gubernatorial race
Is bringing out the demon
Alex
And these demons
Are forcing him to attack one of his own his own I mean another bigot who yells on the radio
Michael Savage
Real conservative
Yasso Michael Savage I guess is talking s*** about
Considering running at 7
Michael Savage
He's a big old liberal so he's the spoiler he's going to come in
Make it so Cruz Bustamante
Using his liberal lies
That he's protective fly
Neocon property idolize
Right and they're going to be
Conservatives because it conserves
Is Winterport Republican
Democrat
Are bucking
I mean they're not demons yet
No the demons aren't really in Play You Look Silly if you were
Wi governor of California at least 500 people Electric Plant themselves the president of Texas
The truth is out of control
I just pulled this next week because I think I could like
Legitimately
This could be played any year on Alex's show
Be able to be like that seems out of place
Doesn't mean anything
Pheasant 2003 4 5 6 7 8 9 10
Absent all the way down to the present day
It's always the case where the most critical juncture
Of all time of the day we're dealing with just pick a year and he's like
Make a cake settle be the end of everything
Yeah
It's it's
Just a shocking realization of like
The triviality of what he talks about
Mixed in with you very serious and real things that I felt like that big
It's just a little bit disheartening
You know to see if the
The present mirrored so clearly of the past
This is the most important thing ever
He doesn't know what he was talking about there
Come on man
It's
The United States
Liberty's what about
Wood chipper
America being destroyed
We see the size of government growing
We have a
The buildings are
Everywhere
Pulling around
Blood
Are walking around
George Bush
Literally
Wait what
I think there's such a thing as getting lost in a metaphor you know like
I think you can cure somebody speak so eloquently that you're like
Caught up in that that but the reverse
Caught up in the confusion I feel like he got caught up in in the story he thought he was
Who's making a metaphor
And then he was like actually I kind of really like the story and I also wanted to be literal movie mode
How many people with blood streaming down their faces saying I love George Bush
What is that
What is that an allegory for
Mine was a neocon
I see that's again
It's literally bigger to the ambulatory
Seems like they got blood all over their face
I love George Bush
That's a lot of blood
All right group
Lisa these folks who are the enemies
Basically America
Toronado
They're hiding as America
Mushroom cloud
Play runaround butchering the country
Camouflage
I think Alex is at the Flights of Fancy today
I mean he's having a little fun there's a light
That's for sure
He's doing he's doing character
Oh my God wait until a little bit later he gets deep into a chapter
He doesn't One Man Show
Enough
Kia
I think there's there's trouble with the enemies
Uniform is the American
Can flag I think
I think when you establish that is kind of your mindset
You basically hitches
Randomly choose who your enemy
Well I mean
It does seem like what he saying is everyone is possibly behind the attack on you personal
So you should never be confident unless
They also love me but even if they love me they could be lying to you and anybody who expresses like
Patriotism or love of country is probably
Strangely enough the only people you can trust
Have declared themselves king of
Michael Savage oh so you can't trust operative
Karl Marx
Need to come in about I mean
Wrote poems
The poisonous
This is an accusation of
Savage
Knowingly being in
On this operation
He's an operative he's not just somebody who's
You know
Not doing the right thing according to Alex
Misguided
Conspiracy
He's a little silly
He's a
Obviously His Radio Show comes first
But
20 years before this
Early 80s
Okay the CIA came to Michael Savage while he was a Beat
I can never like man you got to get out of this might've been like rating diet books at that point
Okay well in mad you got to get out of the daycare alright get into the radio industry get famous enough to where you can run for governor
During one of the most chaotic times
That anybody's ever run for governor of California
Then
You'll be able to
To get the
Conservative what is the plan
Dido
It's basically
That
I forgot what the goal is
Spirit cruises
Here's the problem right
Well
Alex seems to think of
B great Davis kenwin
After he's been recalled
Right
But he does he's not running
In the recall election
Right because he's been recalled right
He is out
This there's a special election to replace him
Until Alex seems to think
Like Arnold is going to run
Atman
Will run and suck the Republican votes away from each other out
Alright
Kind of the best I can do for you in terms of
Him not saying office believe so I can't remember if it was a choice or if he just actually could
Yeah I think it's
Newsom
Ranagain whatever he got
But he didn't get recalled
I do I am I am I wish I had a better understanding of that but I recalled you don't
End up in the next one
Davis is going to win
Anda
I mean he's wrong
There's another aspect to this
Michael Savage
Is the fly in the ointment
It works
There's another guy
Just like that
Real
Or political
Liberal agenda
Course
Medicine
Is that what he did
Is it
This is definitely not what Alex thinks now
In more recent times Alex's
Wheatley contradictory narrative about Ross Perot
In the present Alex definitely it said that bro was the first attempt at a trump like president and he would have won but
But the globalist threatened his family so he bowed out of the race
It's so bizarre how you go back in history
These blatant Subs
Incentive contradiction
2003 Alex knows that Michael Savage is a knowing she'll for the globalist
Trying to suck votes away from a real conservative
In the California gubernatorial race
A few years later
How to swear that he's one of the legends of the Patriot movement even a Trailblazer for all these years he's the one who
Change the game
In 2003 Alex knows that Ross Perot was working with bush and Clinton that election in following years
Won't know this anymore in fact he knows the opposite to be true
The reason they're these absurd contradiction
Because Alex was just making up reality to suit whatever he wants to be true at the moment
Whatever makes his job easier and makes it more money is true
2003 Savage didn't want anything to do with Alex so he was the enemy
In later years Savage was willing to Gaston out to show and talk s*** about Obama so he became alive
Yep and 2003 Alex have no reason to support any politician other than Ron Paul sopro could be a bad guy
In later years Alex Ajo useful prostory could be to reinforce the idea that
The system was out
So he rewrote his narrative to be there bro was a noble hero who the globalist forced out of the race
None of this means anything to him
It's just an exercise in radicalizing people further to the right
I consistently insisting that disaster is right around the corner
And then offering no real solution other than tuning into Alex show tomorrow
See what you should be afraid
That's sad
Yeah I think people like Alex should not be allowed to talk about people like Ross
Despereaux just because
You're going to make up bulshit and it's never going to be as interesting as the reality of what Ross Perot
Vicki prospero's name out his mouth unless you're just telling interesting stories about Ross Perot witches are always
Hey rosborough gave Bernie Sanders a sword
Of course he did but what what
What is a more interesting story than one
That's not true I mean the one thing he did Ares like
Hey I'm going to get like 20 guys together and we're going to overthrow the guy you like I mean he's he's out of his mind
Prosperous
Ross
Do you think they're just little fingerprints
Like wow your story
Completely different across time wonder why that is oh wait it's
Super f****** obvious
So Alex thinks that Savage is going to make it so Gray Davis win
Michael Winer
The younger generation
Conservative
Will not vote
What
He's not
So answer the middle says it's going to Great Davis or Schwarzenegger one of these liberals but then
The end
Pacific
Everyday Baby Dave
At 8
He's a stickler for specificity
A five-year-old of Machiavelli and understand I do not
I do love that
Listen
85 year old rocket scientist could understand this Rockets
95 year old that's red the prince
Is going to be
Able to handle this s***
85 year old with a Beyond
I guess master's degree level education is going to be able to understand that
No no no no
Don't understand s***
But this is so consistent on this episode that
The Savages going to be this guy who ruined
The chances of an actual
Conservative
I mean I think that the writing is on the wall for the most part that like
There's going to be a circus
It's going to be nonsense and turtonator is probably going to win
Feel like everybody was kind of
Almost treating the idea of Arnold winning as both
An insane thought and inevitable one
You know everybody was like there's no way that Arnold Schwarzenegger is going to be our governor Arnold Schwarzenegger
I mean it's only got 40% of the vote so I guess he's going to be our governor
So
Alex says I don't know how to
I don't know how to say this
I don't
Dia de Kobe Bryant
Story
Sexual assaults Torinos
If come out
This was a long time ago haha
And so Alex has some thoughts
I get a present this year
Call Brian
Colby
Alright
Are the NFL
Or any of the
They're not role model
Boys
It's crazy with your misogyny Trump's your bigotry
What are somehow both in the same sentence
Yeah I know I don't know how to I don't know how to handle
That response bananas
Believer
What is a knee-jerk I don't I think this woman is lying that's also
If I were ever credibly accused of that
Obviously all women are liars
But also you know I hate all black people it's a difficult
I think that if his whole thing was like I'm not going to talk about this he should have brought it up cuz then you just
You know showed some misogyny
Quite clearly
Really can't think of a worst possible take on that just not talked about it like you plan to Alex
Is about as bad as it gets I am just
Some other things that Alex
Is only talking about because he
Talk about this recall election at all
Stop
Says a breathtakingly embarrassing clip
You have Alex rationalizing is Joyce to cover two stories that he feels are otherwise
Beneath him and he's totally wrong about both of them
You wrong it's it on son's death so we're fake but he's actually way more wrong about the recall
He's more wrong there because he's wrong
Conceptual
Not just factually
Alex has decided that this thing that he's imagining will happen is a perfect summation of the way our political system is corrupt
But that thing is imagining wasn't
Real
Happened
Arnold beat Cruz Bustamante by 17% and there was no real spoiler
No other democrat or republican of the race would have greatly affected the outcome if they weren't in it
In Savage
Which didn't even run
He was just talking s***
The thing that Alex is imagining what happened is a perfect summation of how Alex imagines the political system works
But none of this is connected to reality is very bad
Seem
Like he's
Making up
Stories
And then being like see
That's how the stories work
What is really work like
Obviously it does
Well it does
You're just not seeing behind see you you're looking at the obvious
I'm looking at what
Underneath
You know the made-up stuff
Text
So
You know there's something more prediction
Kind of stuff get back to a little bit of North
North Korea predicting sure you know Alex has 99% right about his predictions
Except for the ones that he just kind of ignores and pretends
For North Korea
Use in black uniform
Everywhere
Aperam adult
World War 3
What's the plan
The peanut document said that North Korea was going to launch a preemptive strike
Being assuming
I assume because they think we're going to
Strike them because Rumsfeld batak
Rumsfeld
Is planning to strike Korea
North Korea's like we can't allow that to happen
So they're going to preemptive strike us with missiles that again
Cannot reach our Shores whatsoever that's why there's the caveat that maybe it'll be the globalist false flag
United States
In order to make it look like North in order to get a draft in place
Cuneiform
Sporting to me
Diamond
Pyramids on the TV
Population-wise we would need a military draft
Only North Korea
I can't
I guess
Inconceivably Alex's imagining
Things breaking down on like a half
The world versus the other half
Spiral Adam Tulane
Yeah cuz it's like wouldn't just be North Korea
If we dropped all the men that we can just literally
Occupy all of the territory will stand arm-in-arm and we will
Stand over all of North Korea
I don't think that's
Appliance
Ucan black uniforms
Pyramids
Step
And I can't believe that they work together with
If the Democrats 20 years later to get Trump out of office
Yeah with those fake ballast
Play here's where Alex does his one-man show
Nonsense
Government War
$200 a month
My little
This is less settled in rent
Want to join
You're going
It's all over
We
Two-man 22-minute act out Whether tis nobler in the mind to suffer the slings and arrows of outrageous here
Dear God
I kept thinking
I kept thinking I could just like someone to just interrupted
Is not well
The captain
It's great that this new characters go get his very clear motivation
Picture of character that somebody's created to play with themselves that has gone worse than that
Add partner for himself that there is like a Clearwater
I want to take over my neighborhood
You want to help other character in my head
Yes there is that
Tell clothes would appreciate that part
Yeah that that was tough
That was that was bizarre brutal I'm not sure there are many instances that I can recall of Alex doing
Multiple characters
For that long
3 minutes log
It was it was something
Alex bogus calls
I had a good bit of the show is called
And this verse guy
Yes question about a story that you can
Very clearly tell Alex knows nothing about
Didn't go anywhere
It almost done
What's up
The guy has
And
They're saying now
England
Report
There's a story about Colin MacMillan is a man who bulshit nominated to be Secretary of the Navy who died by Suicide while
Waiting now for his confirmation by the Senate
People who knew him commented that he had a recurrence of a cancer that he's been struggling with and he thought that he'd actually
Beaten
Avails possible
Contributing factor in
Bigger picture here though you can see that Alex has absolutely no idea what this caller is talking about but he can't let that be too obvious
He's supposed to know every
Navy secretary nominee died by Suicide allowances never heard of
How its pivots by rambling about
David Kelly the UN weapons inspectors who died by Suicide recently though Alex's
Convince himself it's
Conspiracy
How much does a little hand waving tricks like this in order to obscure from his audience that he has no
I deal with people are talking about a lot of the time when they bring
Turn up news story
You know all these stories hours like it would be a big story it seems like it would be in at least one of his
200 story sex or are you at
I mean it doesn't mean you use that he's going to get to it but
What the point of having all of those tax would I sensibly be
Straight that he has read all of this information
Gus
Capable of recalling it to you should you so call it
Meant to show
That
Exact
It's the appearance
But he has
Question
Of that
So I got to go to call who like the Ann Coulter
Interview
Very very big theme
On Alex's show is a suggestion of who else
Alex should have on screeching Groves
I enjoyed the time when you had and Coulter
Neocon
I had an idea of
Health Frank and might be a
Play Jessie's Girl
Former liberal it'll be nice to get away
Think was done with the Clinton but I hearing Hillary's name being
Kind of pranks
Oh yeah
Al Franken
Yeah is Al Franken a former liberal
Yeah
I don't know I don't know if this is
The caller was saying that I think he was a former liberal
Who's going with you
No
I think he might have had an article about Al Franken in that stack
I think I would be a very interesting dynamic
I remember the book he had out about that which was lost
Underlying lies in the line lies tell them around
Extreme
Bulshit
Polemic
You know like yeah I remember he had a book that my dad have that I really enjoyed it was that why not me
It was the
Fictitious
Sort of
Travelogue of his run
A president and
The Run never happened it's just
It's just a humor book about goings-on
I don't want to revisit that book lest it not be as funny as I remember it being when I read it as a
The kid Barry ever
Yeah just in case
Yeah I think I would like to see that in Urdu
If it's ever
I would be I would be happy with that that could happen now be real so just call her wants
Buzzword years I want to party
Want to partake in the infowar
Alex
I'm a hair of your programmer
Your program
But I like to say
I can't move her hair
I'm just hearing everything I would like to
Partaking
I take all your
The same thing they're hearing this or from you
It seems like Alex. We need
We need a plan
Are you giving out all this information
Start doing
Real weird to call people hearers
All the heroes of Nashville
Definitely weird
Sing Alex Reed vise
Is a dead end
We know for sure that
I would like to partake in the Infowars
Quasi-religious speak
Alex does comeback any advice
He's just saying
Beam me
Which is
Maybe not possible
I want
Border
The Environmental
Become a leader
Commercial radio show
Room organization
Make
Light work
No
Secret answer
It's not a good answer
I don't think I can tell about this Dave character I don't know if I'd like him on Access TV or the radio
No hello to my heroes
Hear me
Hear me all by Heroes what is wrong with you
Here's how you partake
Yeah I figure that's a that's a
Advice that is useless to anyone except for Alex and even
When he was younger it would be useless
Get a massive
Influx of cash
Baja your way into a
Public access to make sure that you meet a weirdo for Minnesota who sells gold
Who's desperate for somebody to be his pitchman
Let's be honest
He's not the only guy trying to build
People with fake gold or gold guy is also philosophically a complete weirdo Liberty
That's super important
Names of philosophical Allegiance
With your your gold scam guy
Some of these are the pieces of advice or like maybe that's good to know Each one teach one
I'm kind of stuff
Sure
What about having meetings
What about getting together and organizing
You know like
20 years in the future I'll tell you what that could be used against you
Well
Secret answer
Coming too fast
And I really
We think that we need to
Maybe we can
Come together first
And then we
We can make plans
I think
A police car
The police
Elected
Your ideal
You can't have meeting
Political meetings right
Enough awareness that the
Man is going to jam up your political meetings
Put this in order to get to the point where you can have political meetings
You first have to elect a sheriff
Wright County Commissioner or something like that without any kind of organizing apparently
Because it's not just like a 10000 person meeting Alex that we were talking about
I don't know
Little meetings do
Me to go 10,000 people
I don't know but that's kind of how Alex
You know it's got to be a big meeting otherwise what's the point
Obviously what he saying
His first you need to lay the groundwork for plausible deniability should anybody that you go to a meeting with
Cause any terrorist act then you can say to them that
No no that was an agent provocateur definitely not somebody carrying out the thing that we went to the meeting to do
If you have some kind of it
Matutinal support USA insurance or someone who's got your back
Okay
Here's how you started Terror cell
Just useless advice
Is the good way to
They get a sheriff elected would be
To organize
Nightstand
Some political Act
Yeah the sheriff
Refracted
Seems like this is just another path towards
I'm not being able to move is this caller said
Write a mean isn't he kind of reinforcing the idea that you can
Change things through electoral action
Thus making the need for violence
You know
No
No he's not
You should vote for your local
That comes later
That's true
The sheriff first
Enough people to get the sheriff
But you can't be
God damn it is
Also don't put up any signs for the sheriff because they could be a false flag tank
The current sheriff is going to come to your house
Jam you up
Migrants outfits another call this guy is an artist
Calling in from New York to hear from you what's going on
I just want to let you know that
We've been called the Blues Festival here in
Pennsylvania
Tri-state area
Check it out
Mocospace.com
The New World Order
The Revenant
Everything everybody
Hell yeah
Bulova
Who's Bank on Poker Face
Poker Face
I found the band's website free Lady Gaga
Yes quite a bit
Video of them playing at that Festival there plug-in
Alex is hyping this kind of a plug on the show it
It's not a large
It seems like maybe
Elevated battle-of-the-bands
Typer typer
But everybody from 7270 did enjoy it
MPA
Paul
I know because
He said his name is the lead singer of the outfit
She also plays guitar and keyboard
His bio is
Is pretty sweet on the website
Paul is the heartsoul songwriting social Guru that poker face is
This biography
Songwriting social Guru that poker face is
Heart
Camisole
, songwriting social Guru no commas
Salisbury Social Guru
That
Poker Face
Bad grammar
He is and always has been capable of immense inside and focus the source of his reverence and respect for
We're all things through
And willingness to fight against those that are unjust of his biography I am not trust
Sing the writing of
Elvis songs
The other people in the band have also
Some silly bios
They didn't call it no
But Alex
Familiar with that
Bands name out there on are just like haha surprise I called in casual about the way you made this announcement
Hey man how you feel about the world
In the world today I think I'll scares is right on right on
62 report
Report
I think I missed
Take me to Kissinger
America
Terrorism
Well I'm hearing that
I'm at humor of his heroism
That's pretty impressive at this rock and roll collar is asking why would he think about the state of the world and he quickly cites the report for
From Iron Mountain
Which is a fake.
It was a satirical piece written by a guy named Leonard Lou and mint to skewer how think tanks operate
Secret group or tasked with figuring out what the insides of a state of Peace would be for the United
Their ultimate conclusion was a piece is not good for the continuance of our system particularly our economy
And us it's not a desirable state
To pursue
That's the document
The Liberty Lobby run by racist Nazi Willis carto published the text
What time is it was real in a government document
And you know you be able to publish it but unfortunately
It's owned by somebody so they got sued by Luan
And ultimately settled the case out of court
Sounds like this rock and roll collar Alex and even Bill Cooper cling to the idea that the text is real because it matches
Is there worlds you really well it must be true and not a piece of
Satirical skewering of
Think that culture
Absolutely and if you believe it's real have I got an Irish baby for you to eat
Hey
What about it
So alligator busy
Pretty positive
Infowars
Fans
I think he wants to spice things up a little bit to use on Philly bags
People who disagree
Free to call in
We are going out
Pensacola
Florida
If you disagree with me or anything I'm saying
Attorney
Anything nobody disagrees called in
Seldom is that going to happen
Almost Never
Who's listening that disagrees with Alex in 2003 who is motivated enough to call news
And that was
You disagreed in the wrong way
You have to be if you disagree
With Alex
Inboard extreme position you're already motivated enough to get on a phone
Without disagreements
He's likely to get or not going to be thoughtful
Criticism
Going to be like what
That kind of stuff and that's
That's
Obviously you'd want to bathe that
Into coming at you and the people who are
You-know-who would
Ideologically disagree with him
Most likely listening for entertainment value to laugh at
You're not going to call in and be like hey man you're pretty low
Another caller wants to talk a little bit more about this idea of organized
Pretty opposed to the idea
Is Alex
Gets basically like into a state of like
Okay well why don't you you could go find like-minded people
Course
We know where this road leads
Is there anyway
Because your audience
The most
Informative
They seem to be the
Cellular areas where
People who live
You would agree with you
Can get together and
And start
That's a base to do things glow
Well
You guys could call local radio
You can meet like-minded people there
If you buy one of my
Security response
And you walk down the street
Are you wearing my shirt
You're going to
Are we what are we talkin about we talk about organizing are making fresh
What is exactly the the goal here
Cuz if you're going
To like a gun rights group I don't let your just going
Tubi
Engaging in gun rights activism
You can probably meet some people who have
Other fringy ideas
I would assume for your own arteries are Buhler organization
Know what you want to do together we want to get a 10 to 15
So people
Know each other's names and you don't really have any direct communication no nothing on phones
What if a narc is wearing a for sure
Possible can't do it
Is so smart
So informed there's no way they would allow a
What I mean what would you even call
Provocateur ticket into their ranks
It worked
I do have the shirt I do have
Videos
Where
Educate
Small group of friends
And people that you care about
Show point where you know your
You're trying to pull
My warning
No question
That's pretty pretty abusive
Hey your family people care about you as a person
Recognize follow you down there
You know what I worried they're just
Keep themselves they don't respect
Yeah yeah yeah
At for your mental health
I think you should isolate yourself from them
That way they'll all be together with their social group that agrees
With each other
And then you'll be alone by yourself
Only listening to me that I've already told you you don't got to buy more anyway I mean like Mike
I already buy the shirt and it didn't help and then there's this guy who runs a radio station
Yeah that makes perfect sense
Perfect recipe for roast people at church
Terrible
Suggestion really real awful all the way around
Another color am I
I think that guy who is the hero's guy
He had a weird energy
This guy has it also
Call a from Minnesota
A couple years now
And I'm
Real quick
State College
Something really interesting the other day
Well I know
Crop what is it opium
Corita in Latin America but
Robert Reed
Liberia
Not come up at all or not hahaha
So this point yeah
There is a civil war happening
In Liberia has reason to talk about it with Alex
No appeal this point so it came quite out of left field
Hey what's the number one cash crop in Liberia
Riddler vibes
Scrum-half
I don't know if he's even told me this out
But he's some kind of eukaryotic
Dialysis claims about minerals in Liberia that has nothing to do with anything
Cuz I thought the caller was asked
About
I was just making that up
By far the mineral with the highest production and exportation from Liberia is iron ore
There's also gold mines and diamond mines
But Liberia doesn't have a developed oil infrastructure at all
The important most all of their oil
Good on Alex do to catch his mistake about the opium
That would have been embarrassing
Soil is probably stupid Earth
Just assume people have oil
True
Oh I think they actually do it didn't have
A certain amount of like
Promise or like it was
Some expectations and hope that they were there
Oil exploration that was optimistic
Take but it didn't didn't
Butts
This caller the weirdo Riddler
Huey uses AOL
And took
AOL
Immediately
And then today I turned it on
Look at it
Number of American troops
She's around Liberia right now
Inverted Piper
New York Times articles
I want to talk about a UK article though so the top
2 * 3
I found a guardian article from an early July 10th Bush was planning center
That's not the source Alex exciting
I think I was just made up that number and then attributed to a meeting with leave eggs or
Probably what were
4800 seems like a round enough number that you could pull it but also it's not 5,000
So you're not like
Guesstimating you're like all 4800 that sounds like you know exactly what you're talkin
Trustworthy trustworthy enough I don't know I don't know where it's coming from the numbers that I
Fiber
Bore difference
So
And it has not come
But apparently it was already happening
2003 couple of profession
Breakdown
Or you with the draft
Medical worker
Do not say you see
But that's all
Where
Uniform
Weather
Shane
Quote
I'm telling you right now if you think well that sounds insane
You got man
Sodas
I mean look
You got to you got to give it up to Alex for being just like
So right
All the time you listen to show from the past
Oh my God is this guy a f******
Prophet the last time an old person wearing a gray outfit and a badge
Harassed me snitch squads of old people
I was
I think what I was wearing a diaper
And I was a couple years ago.
So you got one last clip maybe this guy just like
This this color is a
Afraid
Of what Alex is talking about with the draft
Because like
He's of the age but he could
Could get drafted
Undergrad history
Good old-fashioned
Either you go and
Paris
You don't go
Already
But
I mean what are you doing
Well I read the article today
Uniform
Call Greg
With criminal
I seen that
Illegal immigrant new Army Squad
They're going to keep the white Christian paper
It's down
Another going to be old people snitching on everybody all by God what are everyone's going to be drafted
That is the worst Riddler I have seen in a long time he didn't even give any riddles and he just agreed with s***
Pathologist
Mercenaries
Streams
Security is a guy from Blackwater now
I wouldn't have
Gone with Mercy
It's it's
He's on the right side of that stuff in 2003
Quite against these private armies
They're bad
Now that didn't stick no
Despacito
3 Excursion is is a little bit
Little soft uneven
Definitely uneasy it feels like we were a little all over the place on that episode
I think the reason is because
It is
Yeah we went to Liberia Forno
Real reason
Come up earlier
The thing I think is it's Friday
Maybe wants
To go home the office
Liberia probably some gold there
I mean we're just going to take some
Some nonsense called I'm going to yell about Michael Savage
Ruining the California gubernatorial race
On behalf of
Globalist yeah I guess
Davis
Tyler no
Better now
I don't either
I am very excited
The to see where this goes because
Gray Davis isn't going to win
Nope there's going to be chaos in that race North Korea nuke us
Alex is going to have to wrestle with the fact
Right of the pictures of Psalms
Vons
100% real pictures
Yeah there's a lot of bad stuff going to steal not dealt with it
Location
He still has even bother me that I can't believe I'm talking about
The bath party being put back in charge.
About the actual reality
How do you still can't tag still can't pull up a metaphor
Not to save his life
But his character work
Stop song
Soft Dodge that that copy wants
To steal his neighbor's business and needs help
I don't know that other characters
Until then
Cam
Horizontal
Clark Timber
Not good
What the sex role
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color