Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Joseline and talk a little bit about
DeAndre Jordan
What's up
My brakes
Rare
This was one of your bright spots
Where's that I actually end up taking somebody's
A something but
Watch the bit of Taskmaster
Freddy can't make it much of a better show than that really can't be sidekick
Just pretty fun and 5
Comedians
You're forced to do random
Bizarre
Tiffany
Requiring tap
Very much so
Activity is pointless scores
It was hard for me to conceptualize when you were describing it
The way you described as I kind of sounds interesting but I couldn't
Put the pieces together
It's
It's very good
Very entertaining
Addictive
But I also don't think
You could ever work
Isn't America
Gunshow
Like I don't I think
It has to be a British
I'm telling you right now
It is you and I who can run American Taskmaster the end that's it
But then it would you be
Great should I be great
Both have to find a weird way to be both add each other aggressive
Right I don't know I think difficult
Conceivably
But he's also the second banana so that's me
So it's like
Butt stuff
Greg Davies
Giant loud angry piece of s***
Condescension
Yeah
I think that's the main problem why this couldn't be an American show
The sensibility of it is really tough to translate
They tried and they they tried and Alex Horne told the story that they tried to one cut it down to a half hour
Irish Oso
Already it is over
First thing he said was like well when we tried to bring it over they wanted to make it a half hour show
And I stopped reading cuz it's like no you already lost then you didn't do it you did a bad job
Part of part of the charm of it is the feeling of
How long is a met these people do things
Two or three months
What's your we didn't talk about it
But on the day of our last recording our brains right eyebrows Serenity High
Thursday
April
Okay baby
Ohtani
Four innings
2/3 pics
9 strikeouts Man 9 strikeout not bad
That's pretty good a stout
Hasn't hasn't hit a Dinger yet but it's coming you don't need to hit one open again
That's great I'm happy for you I know that this is you were
Tengo it was possibility of it not happening it was a
Get to watch a lot of
Gamers
199 thousand
View
How many episodes
We are going to talk about present a business or about April 8th
But also before we do that we have to check in with a little Special Report Alex put out from
Connecticut where he was visiting to do his deposition
That sounds about right
Let's say hello doesn't do wasps
The First AME from Fort Meade Maryland thank you so much you are now policy wonk
Daybreak's all the time back when I would stay home from school
Northern Exposure
Text Scott Lively but not that
Scott Lively much better Scott Lively
Even if being better than that Scott Lively is not much of an accomplishment
Thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
I'm confused as to who the top Scott Lively in this situation is but I'm grateful to both there's a hierarchy
Next congratulations on your free bottle of wine thank you so much
Thank you so much
Schmidt
This is technically a birthday shout-out.
Next
Marriage is a false
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much in a lot of
People like it
So thank you so much
It's time to pay
I have
Risen above
Miami star
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I never want to come back
Back here again
Apologized
To the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's never better tomorrow
It's bad
For quite a while
Alex had been dodging his deposition
Connecticut's Sandy Hook case
And I've come up with
Fun excuses like doctor marbles looked at me and was shocked
I was sick
He looked at me and I was like at your right
I can't go to that deposition
Yeah a lot of those sort of like when I would take a charley horse
To get out of PE kind of kind of business
59 fly and So eventually Alex's hit with these these escalating penalties
$25,000 a day
Until you went inside for his deposition
I went to Connecticut
It did not fly so Alex himself did he must
Connecticut
So he did that was out at the studio for a lot of
The past weekend
Now so we don't have a whole lot
To go over chair
In his absence
But while he was in Connecticut
He might have made a critical error
And that is he recorded a video of himself
Talking about the deposition no no no no
Possibly open up the window for his deposition to become Publix at he's making
Public statements about it
Real disaster
Couple of out-of-context drop
UPS from Las Vegas
Dreamy creamy
Gross
Listen to that
Because it's dirty
Here's the other one maybe this'll likely clean the taste out your mouth
Am I on the air
Hello
Okay that's better
That's better
This will not be the new Breaking.
Here is the beginning of Alex's conversation about
Is that position
From his trip to kinetic
Alex Jones here on April 5th
Connecticut
Yesterday afternoon
Hearing Connecticut
Costco
It was just Macs
Level like a hallucination
They start out with demonizing
Global government
Just last week
The Davis Group Matt announced the world government planetary control
Are we ready
Absolute tyranny
Is someone
So yeah we got to already
Talking about stuff that happened in the deposition presumably at least according to Ali
You have his version of things that they demonized
For believing in a new world order
And I need a place that clip
Doesn't say what he says
Says
This is just a levisa
I mean
I think
What he's
Cuz I feel like the point that I'm supposed to take away from that is that
It is so ridiculous for the lawyers to vilify Alex Jones for believing in a new world cover
Right right
And then he plays the clip of the
Theoretical new world government in in question but the person is just saying are we ready for
New State of Affairs in the world
Not so much are we ready for the Illuminati to ascend into their demonic Foreman
Bleed all our children
Editing in the reality that exposes why Alex
Being made fun of
Shirley begin a new world government because it's such a small clip the appearance could be made that like haha I actually am right
I took fun
Possible anyway so Alex Alex's like these people
Lawyers questioning me about the new world order they are just like the media back in the day pretending
That this stuff wasn't real
Watching this unfold
And I'm just realizing they're like
20 years ago
When 60 minutes
There's no Global government there's no transhumanism
There's no plans for any of this
They're going to outlaw
Questioning big events like wmds in Iraq
Or
Jussie Smollett
What should I do
Like script
Weapons of mass destruction in Iraq
And jussie Smollett are the things that Alex will say
I would
Say that I have some doubts
Smollett was a major world events
I would even go so far as to say
Strongly the opposite is true
Right
I think I think that Alex just had such a really difficult time
Rationalizing his action
That he's needed to come up with short
And this is what he's come up with
Every time
Yeah I mean
Don't you ever stop and think man if all of my here's my examples I've got one
Wmds
Total Knockout absolute slam dunk
Sure government lied
Flies
Worlds at stake amazing important
Got that one
Example number to jussie Smollett I think I don't have a good argument.
Drop yeah
Alex I will try to discredit
Is a little bit introspect
You are about to his behavior
But here's the big takeaway
Years before I was sued
This is all about them being holier-than-thou
They're the Arbiters of Truth and Dare the Democrats
They're the ones that love you and Alex
Challenges the devil
Consciously
Literally
Those are not
Algos wmds jussie Smollett it goes on and on Alex's Sandy Hook
The cases are to distract from
Judith Miller's reporting
You got it
Okay and then when people have Judas Village report
I think
This is soft
Azumanga
Well it is nice
Picked up some of my criticisms might be a little harsher than his own self
Criticism
I'm also the last animedia are not the Arbiters of Truth
He's on the wrong side of it
Anyway
The problem for the New World Order is the everyone's waking up
To stop people from waking up
Bye
Suing Alex again is that it yeah I guess okay
Crazy as a Publix basically totally woken up
Around the world
They're doing
Is reversing that
But they picked these weird Mirotic subject like January 6th or Alex Jones Sandy Hook
And they just obsessed like a religion
Everywhere I Go
You're shaking hands
But a lot of more mad at me Lego hey
And expose don't even get our Law Firm
That the world has moved on
From their BS and yeah do I make mistakes
I don't lie on purpose
Like
The corporate media does on record
The people in their Ivory Towers do realize the people have moved on from their BS
Right but that's
The thought that Alex has after saying that a lot of the people that he meets
Are like hey man why does
Stop saying it's a deal goes fake absolutely
Yes but those are the people who have moved on from the BS
Why would they move on from
Wait
How can I move on from the BS
Isn't really at the end of the day saying that he still think Sandy Hook was staged
I think in a very roundabout way
Directional take we've we've gotten to his
The BS newbie like being mad at Alex
For questioning it and have you quotes
The Yankees
Yeah that seems ill-advised
Norm is standing right next to him
Good job
ABS Alex declares himself the you-know-what The Rock
He's a people
I was also going to go with the Michael Bay movie
The rock is the people's champ
Hey change the people's elbow to the corporate elbow
No one liked it
The difference
And so I am
The populist champion
Cuz I'm not perfect but mean well
People love me and because I admit I'm wrong sometimes people love me but I'm high
I'm not trying a lot of pee
People on purpose and when I'm wrong I will admit it
C-3PO
Will never admit they're wrong
So Alex never lies on purpose and never realize it all lies about something or get something
Personally like
Thirty seconds later he says this
Associated Press reported that I wrote a book called
Nobody died at Sandy Hook
When you bring up these Warriors
They're part of the established
Alarm
Lying about that
And has been for quite a while
Lawyers on ladders and stuff they have
He has every reason to know that the AP didn't publish that headline and him asking them for a retraction is impossible
It wasn't publication that they put out
Yasso
He knows that this is wrong
Based on everything he said about this he has every reason to know that it's wrong
And therefore he has to be actively lying about this intentionally
I don't know I feel like he needs to make a retraction
Yeah I think it's I think it's best
Pitch at this point is
At a fundamental level cannot tell the
Prince between
Reality in
In falsehood
Cuz I just don't know what the difference between truth and fiction
Right when I say I'm not trying to lie on purpose
You can't help but believe me because f***
Anything Could Be True in my brain
If if
Know the difference between reality and falsehood and was like
I'm telling you the truth 100% but also I don't know if that actually laugh
Dangerous
So you might recall that in the lead-up to Russia invading Ukraine
Interesting perspective
She was great in that Ukraine was
Waiting for it
Thought that
You can find no fault
Most honest man is ever
So there was also a bit of
Issue with the state department
Coming out and saying that Russia had planned
To use false-flag
Texas pre-tax
I to initiate
Your call Alex's perspective on that the government should
Call something a false flag no history of bright
I'm the devil I'm Satan
Narrative
I'm not the only one questioning now
The state department
5 weeks ago
And they said you or Alex Jones for saying Russia make steaks
Of course government
Cool flags
Alex Jones
Okay cuz it's kind of complicated cuz I guess the official narrative
Name of the Russian invasion
Justify starting a war
That's wild because like you recalled Alex was one of the people who was criticizing the State Farm
Or something
Also it's not
Questioning things that the problem it's a declaring something
With no evidence
It's right about the state department
Evidence
It's a it's a sort of slippery
Kind of thing to try and get ahold of
The dangerous precedent
And
Applies Alex as well
Criticism equally applies in both
Direct
In this case
It seems like they were working on solid intelligence where is Alex just called everything that's inconvenient
I think so they can profit off so very different
Do you think it's possible to adequately explain to him
The difference between a quest
Should like
Is something that the government said true
And a declarative statement like
I know beyond a shadow of a reasonable doubt
That the government is murdering your children right now and you should go start a fire and responses
Now you got to be impossible
Love if the state department representative just came out it was like
I'm just questioning things
Also I want to take a little moment to bask in the ways we can say that Russia has ended
Hesitated Ukraine has it I don't know has it you f****** tell me you trust this music
Trust me I don't want you you don't trust you
Sake throw to smoke bobbed out screaming jumping
Smollett
Disappearing into the date it's so let's let's take a moment really relish
Some of the ways that Alex has been so wrong about the situation in Ukraine
1 Selinsky was a double agent
That sad narrative is falling apart
There's going to be no resistance since Ukraine's government has been paid off it's just going to be no problem
Waltz right through the keys
The war's going to be over in 48 hours
Before The Invasion Alex at Boone just wanted to have open trade with Ukraine
5 Alex
That was just what I came up with on the top
My head feels like he's been
Very very
Polly Ave, clearing about
See the thing is evolving the situation at least
Tumi
Is that I feel like there is one way to tie this all together all of his pre Russia invasion and
Post Russian invasion together and put that all together which is that zelinski double-crossed
Yes
He forgot he had the plan he did the whole thing he got elected to the leader of Ukraine
And when it was all about
To go right hahaha
Surprised I actually like Ukraine
I was fooling you I'm an actor
And then the whole thing could work
I have another way
Salep
Nothing outside Alex's head actually exist
Real
Haha
Claims that he was correct
About
The lead-up to Russia invading
I have some issues.
And that's why they're so pissed and so freaked out
Write 95 96 97 Priscilla time
I bet you do
But this isn't true
Gave his speech
That would be the eventual justification for The Invasion
I've never heard of modern world leader be this honest
We came in herds Ukrainian
And linen David all the way to begin with it's always
Your son
Balls cut off cuz
Cuz she's going to put your kids
With adults
Because
He wants to go back to Russia being Russian things were part of Russia we part about she doesn't want the other parts that weren't part of
Caesar the things that are Caesar's
You're not over there in Russia or not
Later he said that he just wants to economic relations opened up with the Ukraine
It's really
Ukraine's fault for being so belligerent isn't their desire to not be taking over
Was
In any way saying that there was going to be an invasion it was
Solely and in
Higher leaf
About Janice kinloch
That was the only thing that he was
Because otherwise he would have been saying that Putin was about to engage in a depression
Other event / and that's not something that he would
I have sat
He's a complete liar trying to rewrite what he said
So fucken
Also
F*** Norm
What you doing in this video confused as to why he's there at all it's to try
To get Alex and more trouble prop like
Before you dinners going to spend about 5-10 minutes
Take your time
And where this is all going north
It was a long and difficult day we appeared for the deposition
9:30
5:45
Under court order we have to give to complete days we took a brief lunch break
In the afternoon
We're at 1 in the morning 1 in the afternoon
Great job.
Questions
As many of them
About Sandy Hook as I would have expected
I'm there were questions about events unrelated to Sandy Hook
And it struck me as abroad
Wholesale attack on mr. Jones
Infowars
Questioning of narrative
It struck me that the attack here was not on behalf of the parents of Sandy Hook but on behalf of people fart
Are different
Ubuntu not not sued in the case I heard questions about people who
Reporter Dan batondy of former reporter
Who asked questions of public officials who mr. Jones was asked repeatedly what it was appropriate for him to ask those questions
Those officials never
I can explain this to Norman he knows exactly why those questions were asked
It was because Alex would send a Tandy out to places like Boston
The Marathon bombing and he would go and harass people and make us
Cena press conferences so Alex will get more ratings
And then afterwards
Alex sent him to Newtown
Where he went and harassed people with the Wolfgang
How big
And so the premise of is it appropriate these things that he did is to establish that Alex
Knew damn well the kind of behavior that a doggy engages in
I am still was
Open to and excited to have him go cover Sandy Hook related issue
So that's that's that's why North
Box
You know exactly why these questions are happening you're trying to create this
This
Fictitious premise about the question
Turning those going on to make Alex look like more of
Like A persecuted victim yeah I mean that's that's
Boring that's really that's really bad
I think it doesn't have much to work with probably it's true that's true
Alex keeps yelling Jessie Smollett
That is that is a good boy
Not a good boy. A lot of
Raw material after a 10-hour deposition
Your Norm pad if you were there the whole f****** time
You're here with Alex to bring your big guns about what it is they're doing wrong and you're like
They seem to ask questions about dhanbad on DL person 100% relevant to the questions that we were talking about
Who harassed people in Newtown
Cool weird it's not it's like he wasn't even at Sandy Hook on the deck no that's okay
So Norm has a little bit of a performer
Review for Alex about his his deposition
Marcellus wasn't perfect today but it didn't
Punjabi showed far more patience than I would have or perhaps
Could have been from time-to-time tempers flared in the room
A in general I thought Alex was
Patient
Was as direct as could be
In the face of
Repetitive and sometimes
Sneering and mocking question
We have another full day ahead tomorrow and I'm going to work both going to need a good night rest
And hopefully we can wrap this deposition up
This is probably
Deeply
Deeply irresponsible and inappropriate
The characterizing the opposing counsel is sneering and mocking question
The
This kind of stuff is is trying to create a story about the deposition
That is inappropriate if it's
Not public information
If this is
There's an expectation of confidentiality surrounding this
This is just
Flagrantly abusive that confidentiality
Yeah I mean
The other side can't talk about it now you're doing a shoot promo
You're over there they're f****** this is professional wrestling they're turning a was supposed to be out actually
Off-screen conflict
Into a foreground drama more appropriately would be there going into business for themselves
Scaccia would be more than they have this expectation of confidentiality that
Exist within the case
And then instead of agreeing to that they go ahead and play their own game expensive
Just start beating the s*** out of
Probably going to have some coffee
I would assume I would hope so
Sonor medicine predict
About the song Kiss this trial
Trial is set to take place this summer
And it's looking to me and I'd wanted
Chrissy theorist
This might be the trial
Century
As2
I'm at 2
Right of ordinary people to raise questions and draw unpopular conclusion
It appears to me that the Sandy Hook families
Have decided together with the New York Times and Elizabeth Williamson formerly the times editorial board
This is a trial not about damage
Sandy Hook
But what they perceive to be damage to the American Republic
And they do mr. Jones and Infowars
Something I can do with cancer
A cancer eating away at the truth
What they're missing is that we've lost
That's what makes Alex Jones industry
Yes it is what makes Alex popular
Created this
False reality that they insulate people within and scare people
About the external world in the people who
Believe and what they
Turbo fictional reality
Popular
You already lost
Put the system on trial
Ridiculous
What is going to be the Scopes Monkey Trial that's what we're going to do this is comical
Comically delusional
So Alex brings up a jussie Smollett again
Dammit a lot
Always
Shocking revelation
Most the time we're right about stuff
I almost didn't come out and say that I thought jussie Smollett stage thing
It didn't sound right
Whole story
But that's the difference I'm not mad
You ordered that a good price to pay
So the fact that Alex is angry almost didn't call jussie Smollett a false flag should give some indication of how arbitrary is
Birds are for disseminating information
He'll just say whatever he feels and presented as fact I may or may not end up being accurate but if it does it
Coincidence
It's random
Accidental that he may get some
Things that heat instinctually thinks
Are are the reason
I remember this I was listening
The reason that Alex thought it was a false flag
Is because it was a racially motivated crime
That was being alive. Nothing to do with there was no other necessary
Am I guess I'm sort of the knee-jerk defense of the idea that it was Trump
Supporters who were
Riley alleged perpetrator
Also an important fact is conveniently ignoring here is that Madeleine Albright absolutely apologize for that
Comment that you made about sanction
In effect she did correct herself which Alex's pretending she didn't in order
It's fair to critique Madeleine Albright and you probably should harshly but this line of attack Alex
Is making his dishonest and self-serving
He just pretends that two people who have made statements and things that were
Inaccurate or offensive
I have not come out
Hey look that was that was f***** up
It bums me out
Because it almost
For an instant in your head you can see things going differently we're like
The jussie Smollett thing happening
Was that
Blast
That one lasso like I'm going to
My last nickel
On this
99 black I'm going to put my last nickel on nine black
And then it comes up and he's like s*** I was going to stop calling thing false-flag if this wanted turned out to not be a false flag
Every time I want out
Put me back in
January 6th false flag
Baby rattles off
That's not go well in courtroom no
What's the antifa
All was gay actors in the right rally is already much
Actors running around pretending to be
It seems like those would be very obvious one since they were Oklahoma City
Use those
Very very weird
So anyway Alex gets into more details that are probably inappropriate for him to be talking about about something that's presumably
Confidential
They worship her
Well look at me
Shatter Me.
Your dad says he was a combat Vietnam he was never there
Toys for Tots program
Special
To sit there
Brian Williams son I'm at Center Blumenthal son
Yeah so this probably isn't good
I wouldn't do that I wouldn't do that
I would have
Push them out of
View of the camera or broken the camera has thrown it against the wall
Hey going at a river
I have to advise you not post that video Alex just seems like it
It's really untoward
LOL it's lies Alex is your future bankruptcy lawyer I would recommend that you
So obviously
Of course
You know where this is heading
Of these
People his insane
Thanks for your prayers
Ford Fusion
Supporting infowarsstore.com
This fight is your fight this fight is my fight we're together
Bugging Infowars store
That's obviously
Norm has ever he's known Alex for years he has every reason to know that that's where this is going
That's the final thought is going to be about how like we can only do this because you're bored
We got so many shirts
It's so many
Probably deeply and ethical
For him to participate in this
That's what I said about him being on air when Alex put the million-dollar bounty on
Chris Matthews
I would have thought they would have got him in trouble
But apparently
Being around for an active
Participant in things
Super f***** out doesn't get you disbarred
Yeah there is a little bit of a teams like the legal profession is a lot more fun
You know we got to stop Alex from doing this stuff and then like the lawyers who did the Alex SOB like a
You guys
Don't do that
Next week
Come on get out of here let's go
So
On the evening of the seven
Some news broke
About
Some allegations
Text Maybe funny
Some places we can talk about that probably a bit more in the future but at this point
These are claims that are being made
Do you know that's on the night of the 7th this stuff starting to percolate
Alex comes in on the 8th
He's finally back
Ryan Connecticut
It's coming in hot
Cuba coming
He's more exhaust
While I was in
3 days
Suppose you're there
Total 4 days
Menopause 2 days
Get up here
Probably exhausted particularly at
Getting very loud in my bastic
That's really a k
Exhausted
And I am
As they say ignorance is bliss in the beginning of knowledge
One of the 20th century and a joke
Bless
The beginning of knowledge
Great sorrow
But also
Decency in Civilization
Everything we need
He had to resist saying power
Spider-Man
It was close
Now you know with great power
With response
You're just right there
If you have the means
Then
It's still there
Yes Alex's real is real tired
I agree with pretending to be passionate about things is a coping mechanism
But it's usually a coping mechanism for him being ill-prepared to do the show and not knowing anything about the topic
Pixies cover
Usually that's
What the he's covering up but I mean the coping mechanism is still useful even if it's
Spread
Most of the time I do this cuz I don't know anything because I'm an idiot
Now I'm doing it because I'm very tired
Like if you're bald maybe you wear a hat to cover up his book but it also gives you a little bit of sun per tag for your eyes
Same thing
Good stuff
The world's being destroyed
We are about to see the world we've known asteroid
Natachee's bill
System design
Asteroid human
It's made me into God
Okay
It's very sad
Spray paint
The spirit of evil
Spreading it's black
Wings Over the Earth
Longstocking
Our children's
Take a nap
Sprewell
Good is not the only thing in the universe
Happening
And his windows good spirits do not stand up
Fight
Anderson's that innocence is destroyed
Children
Rambling about this kind of s*** is also a coping mechanism
Is a little bit less entertaining and Littlest bombastic but it's the same thing
Grab a John Keats book off of the goddamn shelf if you're going to keep on this s***
Well what is beauty Dan
Beauty is truth
Atrocious
Event for a beautiful war is what John Keats was all about his power and power is responsibility
So good I left swipe
So
I just bought Rambo again for you
Seeds
When Jesus was at the Garden
What
Smelling at all
He wept
Jen said please take
Because only by knowing
In
Through
Beyond
Find archery place in.
Only by this test
And you will all be
Christ was
But you
Your soul is so beautiful
Your glory and your bike
Like the Green Goblin
The Creator
Spell
Candles and
Created what
You are your mother's womb
Like Wednesday
No it's an explosion
The devil wants to eat you or something
Yeah I think that this is
Kind of fine as
Bland
Preaching
But yeah it's a it's the show that Alex is pretending he's doing not
Well I mean I will say that yesterday my partner and I were driving but she likes to listen to NPR
And we we had
Turn it off at one point because
Coming up next
What is the difference
Twin soil
And dirt
Next on Science Friday event guy risdall comes to know what the devil hates us Mark of God
I would prefer that
Sorry I'm br
I think fresh air would be so much better if it was just all ranting about the devil
Better than
What is the difference
Between soil
And honestly I would fight back
Incredibly, and probably informational
So I'm Alex transphobia going on
More colors than others
Here is just an interesting incidents of him making stuff up
Disappeared
Woman A year had
If you thought she was a man
100012 years old
So cool
Alright first of all Angelina Jolie got a mastectomy because she gave the screaming.
Called brca1
Which dramatically increase the risk of
Developing breasts
In the general population the risk for women is about 12% of having breast cancer but if you have that Gene the risk goes up to 60 per
Her decision to get this procedure done prophylactic
Stickley was aching
Completely appropriate medical decision has nothing to do with any of the issues I was trying to cover
Second altitude making up all this
There are likely over 100,000 mastectomies performed every year in the country but the vast majority are related
The cancer or cancer prevention
Also the there's the issue that mastectomies are
The same thing is Top surgery in this gets a little bit murky and trying to parse out some of these details
Also no one would do Top surgery on a 12 year old
Better not appropriate given the
The standards of carrot that because this now
It would require is a comically evil villain that that's like stuff which Alex could only imagine
To do something insane
Yeah it would be it would not be appropriate at age
I was just making s*** up to freak out as listeners and make them hate trans people even more but it is interesting
Please bring up trans men
That's not something he usually even
Yeah
All of his fear narratives around to Dick being cut off
Well that's what I
That's what he tries to
Also all kinds of sphere around transport
No bathroom type legislation and note
All of his narratives that really struck me as strange
That he's talking about transmitted
Yeah it's just weird
It's very we
I don't know
Why why were they such big
What are you doing get a job
Not sure
The big news story about the pole
About Biden voters
Western Journal
70% of Voters would have
About the stories covered
And censured by the media
Hunter Biden
Peter Rabbit
Talking about
Head of Chinese intelligence
He's worth 57 billion dollars missing and he's disappeared
That's where we are
Skip character work
Where where are we
That's where we are
So this is actually a pole of the media Research Center which is not a reputable
Organization
There are right-wing entity that's largely funded by billionaires like the Mercers and big corporations like Exxon
Was reported by NewsBusters which is a Blog that's run by the media Research Center
This blog post wasn't recovered by the Western journal and then that's Now with Alex is ripping off of for Azadi
Seems weird that Alex wouldn't just look into where the pool came from and reported directly
Just skimmed headlines it's someone else printed out for him and putting the big stacky
Anyway some of the stories that they asked in this pole like the presence of the poll was if you'd known about these stories would it have
Change your vote
Question voting for Biden
You're really stupid headline have you seen Flashdance
There was once covered like Hunter Biden's laptop Scandal which Alex's characterizing in his typical restrain
Train fashion
But also want the stories that they asked about was quote
Harris most leftist senator
So do I
A lot of folks who aren't thrilled with vines performance so far as a whole
I think that's fair
I don't necessarily mean that they would all wished they had
Had voted for Trump though which is with his NewsBusters article is arguing really seems like they're missing a lot of the context
Lied about all this stuff
Then drop would have gotten all the vote obviously which I guess is the next Retreat after you
Sail with the Vietnamese North Vietnamese boat
What's with all the Audits and all that kind of chips
I guess we're not really going to be able to convince
Anybody the
Did actually win the election
We play a game
Exactly yeah yeah yep now I mean
We wouldn't want to do that in the other direction as well though
Like let's not relive gave any other
Elections what they're like this.
Say in like 2016 like
If you knew this about Trump
Would you have voted for you one of those
Let's not do 12 goes back like a 2000 election to re-vote for
All of it
Do we have to try and figure out how history would have gone
Might as well
Compares his enemies to characters in a specific
Pig movie
I'd like you to try and guess what he is and what the characters are
3 question 30 will answer
Alright genre of movie
Cartoon
Cartoon alright
Decade
What decade was the movie made in
Food Nelly
I can say with confidence that was the last 20 years has probably in the
Thousands to 2,000
Sometimes I don't know exact release date
Alright this kind of Blends into all right
I'm going to go and
This could because I'm way off on the date really want to say Finding Nemo
What were the characters
I don't know which one
Dory Ellen
You are incorrect
You're not going to just get put
Oh no no no no you're going to
The inside of a
Federal Prison
Criticized
Do they said in A Bug's Life
Call Suter Farms realizing
Grasshopper grasshopper why'd you just attacked and beat up that
One little
You didn't follow your orders you just ignoring
Because because if you let one ant stand up
They might
And there goes our way of life
Bug's Life
Wow
He took Alex
I mean what it's been
20 years
Something like that I'm like that that was Dave Foley
That was Dave Foley starring in A Bug's Life
Yep so Alex
Playing that clip from Buchheit later
I guess I don't remember like it
Movie
There is a little bit of a response to the stories about
The claims that he may be moving money around
But he is also lying about what the story is
Why don't the Democrats care
It was a town hall article last
Monday
What the Democrats are trying to implode themselves
It's like they're trying to destroy themselves
Mission is to destroy America
Any free systems are the demolition operative
In this economic cultural spiritual
Biological chemical War
Because they want to get rid of people because I like to kill people
Because they're bad
Happening here around the world that's what happen
When good people do nothing
Disinfo articles
A lot of fat
Fake news out there
Infowars is swimming
And money money that's leaving our pool very quickly
Yeah
Think they at more accurately said
If these stories are to be understood as
And I bet they're being reported in like raw story
It's swimming in money and more that the pool is being great
As you are you're saying
A bunny might be
But other people don't know where those pools hidden pools
True
Articles
A lot of fake
News out there
Infowars has swimming in money
And
Imports is not want to have layoffs
I personally
Bought an expensive nice house
4 years ago
That's
What we do
That's your that's your best bet
Couple million the bank
Maximum
Troll stuff
I personally have exhausted my phone
Which is fine I don't care
We really need your support
Plus we got great products show
Play The Weeknd
It is the part two of the
Founding member
Coins
Please be by my overpriced coin amazing from high ridiculously backed up novelty
Coin
Obviously it's pretty predictable
Anytime any kind of story like this comes out that's kind of threatening to Alex is going to use it as a fundraising opportunity
Do they found out that I've been stealing money from them my people will love to give me money for that
Interesting
It's an interesting strategy
Spearly offensives
This is a
Skip ahead a little bit
But you're a Alex discusses
Just some
Some shity
Gitty perspective
Here's Jim stocking
Does gender affirming healthcare for transgender
Is the best practice
The potentially life-saving care that's what they're all saying
Commit suicide if you don't
Bojangles off
Think about that
Transgenders have the highest level of suicide and lowest life receive anybody in the world because they've been
People
That's her free will just
From the children
Okay
So I mean obviously
He's putting forth his s***
And not backed up by anything other than his own bigotry
Who is essentially just like
Yeah
If your if you are a very important you cannot exist in society
You can't exist
In public
Take care of you can't
Away from the children
What is
Then what what is that entail
How far does that go cuz it's not just like okay
You can't be a teacher
No no it'll be the idea of you needs to be away from my children which means it can't be on TV
Read about it being a public position where maybe you achieve something that's irrelevant to the news their child might learn about
They were to say oh this person was the first trans person to become president that would be here in my life
Is VRBO
Now probably
Can't go to a church
No cuz you probably be around children
No know what you would have to do is go to a place where they were only other trans people
People who also couldn't be part of society
And they would have to be kept there because
Ghetto people want to
Be part of society you would have to have some sort of
Thing to keep them all in one
Obviously these kind of social stigmatization Czar the things that Alex wishes
To see put in place for the effect
Essentially eliminating trans
Distance Society
Whether it be through silence or by
And that framing
List
I don't care what you
Because
And I met and that's fine
And it's not me trying to hurt you
The globalists are trying to exterminate
Trans people
Write those
Globalists are you
I just don't want you to anywhere near my children or you the existing
Interview to be something they know about or for you to continuous
Net effect
Asian that
To increase
Is the kind of pressure
That
Drives people
Go to
Suicide
He'll just
Not recognize and wrestle with the with that his merry way being
Yeah I mean you know just
Holding a club hitting somebody saying
Thank God it's me hitting you
Those imaginary demons above my head May really be making weird Club
Yep so Alex complains about how
The
The elites they aren't wearing masks but they're making everybody else we're math
Little late on this blippi
You're an elite and I mostly only playing this as a way of
Proving that I'm a witch that will pay off on a later at the house
Their servants and butlers
Minions are I mean this is
Colt
Your face
Like
All that famous book by George Orwell Animal Farm
At first the pigs
Tarantula farm animals too rebellious to humans
Sitting Elite
Aristocrats
Four legs good two legs bad
But then once the pigs take over they say well
Tulane
Good four legs good and then later
They say actually four legs bad
Who likes good because the pigs start walking upright
Michelle
She works like you
You do all this but we don't
Subway close to Animal Farm
But also not applicable
No
But Alex has talked about the plot of Animal Farm that will be important
Later
Alex gives himself a little bit of a review of his own performance
Today
I'm doing okay in the first hour
And 12 minutes
How do you know it's 30%
When the calls
Very import
Question
Central
Everyone even even New York Times
Big question
How old hurts are Democrats
Woodbine
Eeyore lower percent poll
The lowest many president ever even in establecer polls that sample
How on Earth
What even major blue states are going Republican
Hoping you just end this nightmare of
Prices and open borders and collapsing country in Warren
An answer is
Get ready for that narrative to recycle and we'll do this game again
Opening Salvo of Lake are ready no matter what if any anything
Monday you know it's a ceremonial.
Deeply annoying back to work
I would guess that maybe Alex has covered 30% of the news
I mean
It's it is arbitrary how much news he has to cover
Yeah you haven't covered s*** but it could be 30%.
No I think what we need is a progress bar that should be on the heads-up display of his show
I would I would find it
Slowly increasing the Brevard Zoo hours
So you're done with the news that's your dessert
You got to do your job and do a lot of a lot of safety
I think it would make the show a lot more interesting though cuz then there's the tension
Water heater
That is like that turns it into an almost like 1940s boy story like that
The guy takes about his school and they're all of the butt
Title situation is like
If we finish playing baseball he's going to tell us the story but I think it would
Crippled the ratings of the early
That part of the show
No one wants to hear him cover news about the devil all the time
So Alex
Some calls
The show is called
And lot of them are
Pointless and I don't care about them
So we don't actually have that much
Leftover show
Check in on
Is
What's to know like a look
No
That the globalists are going to destroy their to take down the internet they're going to take down all means of communication
So what do we do
What would you do
Chip repair
To prepare for that I think I would maybe do two things
Skyward bolster my defenses
I really focus on hiring people away who have the capability inability to protect me
Okay that's two things already
I would
Try and
Junction off a portion of the internet just for me
And I would take it so that they could destroy the rest of the internet but I would have my own personal you want to still Mall network of tubes
Yes I would want my own Al Gore Network
That I have for myself well I guess that would solve the problem of the communication this color as a slightly different take
I wanted to pick your brain
What do we do
I mean
We know they're going to turn the lights out we know they're going to turn the internet off
Delaet's
Let's think about it now and compare
Right now how do I react how do we
The Davis Group
Borrow release is a war
An economically collapse
Civilization
Nevada
Organize
And there's a realize what's happened
Are the pipeline
During a shutdown
To get the most of America
Is someone self-sufficient other than areas in California
Connecticut if you places
Most of America
To make us
Dependent when they go for the jugular
We know that they'll just leave their lines open
Their media Outlets know what they want us to hear
Essential weird non-essential
Buying printing presses
That's where we're going
You are smart. You're thinking about what to do once they hit us for that and I really should be doing so that planning
But
Did you tell them we partially back them off at least
Take the pressure off
We were about to pull in Italy
Exact
What exactly
Were there
What
They were going to get us to not have to wear masks
Okay
The government did that I don't think it was a response to
That's because they didn't want us to take power
Okay
I don't think anything really
We don't have to wear masks right now do we
Well
She's not in prison
You don't know that there is not ones last time you saw him in public
Declaration that the vaccines are
Bio weapon in Spanish
If you want to declare small victories that people have gotten tired of being careful
They've given up on run
Hire Society wants to claim congratulations
You didn't do s***
It turns out we know it takes exactly two-and-a-half years of being a complete
F****** prick
To get an entire Society to finally quit a a billion people to die our country
Play yeah also interesting
The places that Alex has deemed not able to be self-sufficient where New York LAN
Connecticut
So weird little bitter
Better
I would like
Everybody who really thinks that they are part of
Majority
Of America that is self-sufficient
Really struggle with what the word selves
Sufficient mean
You know
Yeah cuz I think when people say things like
I'm very self-sufficient
I do not think they understand what that is
No
It's a challenge
There's a lot of things that you
You take for granted that are part of living in
Society
Like I am
So far here's how unselfish
Self-sufficient
Before I wake up every morning
Are not well right when I wake up every morning I have to take pills otherwise I might go crazy
Sure everyone will be in very big trouble
Yeah I'm not self-sufficient
At all and it's not like you could
Plant those pills
Right
Anime think about all the people who you know might have conditions that are chronic and you know
Even take take
Other
Other conditions on the other there are tons and tons of people who
That's not even a realistic
Possibility
I might even be on that like
I mean sure
You grow food baby right
Do you grow enough
Do you grow a varied enough type of food year after year are you driving the soil
Nutrients
What's the difference between dirt and soil
Although I do love this guy's plan of getting printed breath
The way their brains work
Does have a very Taskmaster as quality to it or you're like
That is not the solution I would have gone with sir
Absolutely because you can't really print off memes
On a
You have to build
Tire pressure
Arthur meme
Play just be making your own that beach house
Because you're not going to have a 3D printer
Palomino
You're not going to
How are you going to get the printer
But I mean it's going to be like
What do you mean well who's going to make the printing
We have to get it before the whole thing goes down that's why you talking about preparation
Should I have a printing press in my house now
Yes yes
Horde printing presses
Another think it's important the printing press is
It's only as valuable as what you're
Sure
Talk to
Make a
Cutting of the Bible in order to
Lego removable block but that's still a ton of work I mean
You know
Everybody thought those Gutenberg Bibles where we're all hard to make or whatever and then they lasted so long I figure it'll be that
So another caller calls in and Alex pretends to know what he's talking about
Sleepwalking
Call Alex
You ever heard of a guy called that goes by the name
Pharma
I have heard of that mine
He's laying out
He warned they would use the Caravan
Isaiah
And the preacher
Martial law
They're going after that cut things is bird flu
And they're going around killing
Millions
He's coming
Furious
They're doing it
What
Supply
So Alex pretended to know rice a charmer is
Bird flu
I'm not sure what the exact numbers are but yeah there's some bird populations that have been
Affected they believe that
A lot of it is being transmitted by some wild Raptors
Not the kind
That looks fly over like a chicken
Check into be like Planet happen
Operating Theory
Big an issue is this guy's presenting but it is something to keep an eye on
I would ever put the larger picture is out with
Pretending that he knows of this guy's talking about and he has no idea
That's a metaphor for Infowars
You know the Raptor that flies over and s**** on a bunch of chickens and then they have disease
That makes perfect
I mean look
Why not
Alex says that he's got a guest coming on and I got really interested right away
Elizabeth
And Lorenzo and John I'll get you all but I got a special guest pop it into like a
Go back to your phone calls
This is a
A few days ago
Describe losing leg
Talk about this cuz we can talk about the statistics Alden the
What happened is very very
Alot of people personally
But didn't listen to
Very serious blood clots
It sounded I we talkin to him
You like what the statistics
Call Jay but they don't make the point that you want to make so talk about anecdotal cases and freak people out
Strange story for Alex cover because it kind of muddles the narratives about vaccines
He's made such a huge deal out of how he thinks it's the MRNA in the vaccines that makes them really dangerous and how
That's that's what makes it an experimental gene therapy
That's the appeal that it has 22
Created like a mysterious unknown that Alex's used to spread doubt and fear
For his audience
This is why he always talks about Pfizer in moderna but almost never brings up Johnson & Johnson
Because J&J isn't an mRNA
So it's not as easy to scare the audience
This is a regular old X
The audience is more used to exist
AstraZeneca is also not an mRNA vaccine but it's also not available in the United States
A decent chance that the audience doesn't know that
Alex doesn't even actually know that
I'm kind of disappointed
I was pretty excited to hear like how Alex was going to handle this weather he was going to
It's not
MRNA vaccine we never find out
Seems like
F****** Matrix is way out of a bullet on that one yeah possibly
Matrix himself out of the way of a non mRNA vaccine heading right for them
No it's not a collar I just thought that this was
Pretty funny
Pretty pretty indicative of like
I mean this is Saved by the Bell s*** okay
Regarding Trump
I've seen the footage of him
Shaking hands with claws swab
I've seen the footage of him on stage with Bill O'Reilly overly bragging
Taking responsibility for the MRNA gene therapy
It's so good that he's been jammed that he's been boosted
Then I seen the crowd
The crowd how they booed him and he kind of mock them saying all that she's too small 9 of minority
Here's my question Alex
Trump
Is re-elected
What are his main priorities going to be enemies
Ask you straight out to we trust him or struggle globalist
I want to know
You know we should have a whole call-in show
Commercial
Free calls
According to the world gold Council
Pretty sweet
That is if we do a show about calls that are as good as that
Is Trump a globalist let me tell you
Here's this idea for calling show that I've been talking about for years and
I do not want to answer if stuff is globalist
I don't really want to take responsibility for a later day out
Commercial
Episode
Not a lot of that much meat on the bone but you know I wanted to check in with him
I'm on the present-day breaking
I am so I wanted to see if there was a robust response
Clearly there was
Tommy Hitman Norm had something of a response
They had a busted respond
Different
You're going to be gone
Turn on vacation
Stroke
Ideally hopefully maybe be able to put something
Together Thursday 8
Breaking news
But if not
I will check in with Alex when you get back indeed we will
The Jordan
What if I miss you will I need to go somewhere you can go to your beautiful faces Guitar website
And maybe now it's too early
Marriott
Leo and bcx
Vanilla Ice
Vanilla is not good
The sex robot
Dreamy creamy
Holding
Alexandra Christian coloring with huge fan I love your work