Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge B B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Freight
College vype.com
Jordan not here today Jordan on vacation
Celine somewhere over there mewing
Hello I am one guy who likes to
And where's the other seen talked a little bit about Alex Jones and
Credibly surprised by him asking me if I had a bright spot
And if you were here I would tell him that my bright spot today is actually it's something that maybe a little delayed
Being a bright spot but there's a new season of Survivor upon us that started a couple weeks
Me and my friend Angela Lansbury been I've been watching the season a lot of
There's a there's a lot of problems with with Survivor still I think I think they have
Added too many bells and whistles I think I've made this point in the past
Too many convoluted rules about
Idols only have power in a certain God.
It's it's a mess
If you if you don't know what I'm talking about if you don't understand
The Byzantine rules that Survivor is that a good for you
I'm rambling a little bit
That's what happens when I'm sitting here alone
I suppose
So I wanted to put out a little special Sneaky Snake episode today
And the end of Jordan's absence with ought to take the opportunity to have a chat with somebody who
Books have I requested that we we have
Very interesting person
And so I had a little chat with Amanda and we will be getting
In just a moment
The before we do I would like to take
A little mama to say hello to some new walks
The first
Monkey kong hate you so much right now apology walk
I'm a policy wonk Earlywine versus the Westboro Baptist Church thank you so much and I hope all is well
I'm a policy wonk
Facts about Star Wars with this pile of documents all day long in the Shays Lounge on the chaise lounge
Text Zachary motherfuking sorrow
I'm a policy wonk Daniel crying because I've been a gummy worms like you so much you are now policy walk
Jordan is not here
So thank you so much too
You and I will take a crap
I'm a policy wonk I have risen above
Miami star
A list for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order and
She wrote in on and all your s***
Maybe that I should almost broadcast
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
We will find out if he's ever better but for now
On that note let us up to
This interview that me and Amanda we will catch you on
On Friday for another episode we will see you then
Hello folks how do you do joining me today in in Jordan's absence
I I thought the other somebody who I wanted to have a conversation with somebody going to sound very interesting
Thing and thought that might be relevant to a lot of the topics
That's so we cover on the show
I'm thrilled to be joining today by Amanda Moore
How are you
Good I'm so happy
It's daytime thrilled that you enjoy the show
I feel like
For most people it's
Probably not a healthy thing
But given your particular pathogen trajectory
Maybe it's it's appropriate
For you to enjoy the show
Yeah yeah
Those who do not know who you are and what you you're you're
. speed want to give like a little bit of a brief version of it
I don't want to tell it lest I list I screwed up some
Sort of details
So I
Accidentally-on-purpose went undercover in the car Ray
So I went you
January 6th
Not gay
Fundraisers
Embarrassing
Do
So now
AR
What were the you like actual dates that's like you were like beginning and end
Your time
Doing this undercover activity
My first and then I went to go was the November
Right after
That was the end of Owen Shroyer is Caravan up the East Coast
Yeah yeah
Wow
To be there for the end of the Infowars Caravan what what a treat
Which I started when orange tires Caravan
I got some Fortune
September
Okay okay so yeah that's that's a pretty good strive it covers a lot of like
Do you really
More
Turbulent times
Where I'm at
Run that stretch
You said two accidentally and on purpose
Yeah when you went Undercover
What did what do you think was more did it was more of an accident or on purpose
Isaac Hayes
O'Reilly's and I was just like there
Adios by Lucy are going to go anywhere I
So I was like
Oscillating saw
In-N-Out have a personality
Main Street
Nazi recruited me to help organization and didn't work
So yeah it seems like it was
You know
Being around and then people coming up to you and instead of being like
Hey you want to you want to dip in
Little Pearl
I guess that's that probably makes I mean that's probably passed a lot of people go down to earth
More willing unless
Having in mind for
Undercover
Operation
Yeah
Petrino Maryland
Now covid
Lost my friends and my support
Did you feel like you were intentionally creating that as a way to make yourself look
More vulnerable
Like those sort of descriptions of yourself like
And be the sort of person that they would want to recruit in
If it seems like that that is a lot of the sort of people you hear who fall down these days
These rabbit holes are people who
You don't have those support structures people who
Maybe have
Gotten some
Weird politics and the people around them are our tolerance or just have had enough of it
And then they find people who will accept them
You know
Especially here and I know she was different
You're like
Country outside
Summer 2020
It was all very much like if somebody didn't
Unless you were in Congress
And then you get away with it
So you you went undercover it did you
I guess
I'm kind of interested in is like
Early on when you started to notice that you know like you're getting in in mashed
In some of these circles
What what sort of gold did you have
With the undercover
Like dizzy
Is there a like
I'm going to find criminal activity or information or what was where was your mind at
I mean
Like whatever
I Googled him and I realized as I can
Congress
What's the message
So you guys
And so I was like oh my God
Definitely
Voters to know about a person that's running
Obviously
I didn't really
Did did a plan of like what you were doing
Develop over time was their doors are like a point where you realize like
Alright this is
This is why I'm here or why I'm doing
A lot of people in there some information
And it was just it was hard to say because it's like
You can see obviously if
Fallout more information
Also like
Closest for fun
LOL
I don't have media that allow me to
Wasp
Lost you in on Chronicles of 2021
So you have like an archive of
Of like
The DVR what would it be the Apocrypha of
That's going to be valuable one day that's going to be going to be in a college archive
So yeah
Ogier of experiences that you had
That's obviously going to be more than
Like a single piece
Busy es you're describing at you know you're going to be sort of more mainstream
Conservative areas
You know whether it be the c-pack or
I guess you could call stopped
Estilo stuff like
Fairly mainstream now
And then the qanon stuff it so there's no sort of multiple threads
Kind of
How much overlap did you experience
Between that
That kind of
Those world
Garlic broccoli and shrimp
Chevron stock
Turning Point USA
Bashas pharmacy
For sure
War on the west coast where there's like all those rallies in LA
Watch younger
Our Generation
I actually
IMessage
This is the first time I've seen a guy in a three percenter shirt
Talk to me
Grilling hot dogs
3% water bottles on Highway 280
Security in life
Oh wow
So did you do you have a feeling or sense then they'd like what you experienced was like and I like
After that there was more melding
Yeah
This is not my first life
I never been
Laura Loomer had a big rally in DC
A few years ago
You know there wasn't badly
I've never seen anything
Even even the people in those
Like those right-wing circles are
Yeah
What kind of bums me out but
Pretty expected
You you experienced I guess then you're what you're describing as like
Thank you kind of being an intentional like
People who are maybe more
Stream going places
Like turning playing like seapak
In order to maybe find people who would be receptive to their more extreme message
This is an intentional strategy that you you
See people using I might take it
Audio with literal Nazis talking about
Heck that's that's
Kind of
Not that surprising I guess
I guess that like
You'd expect that they would be aware of that
I wonder how much
People like the turning-point folk are aware of that
They are being used that way
Do dealers
So maybe
Maybe fairly aware
Weird structure 24 like I was hanging out with people who
Obviously I need to be
So
APU
And then
Translate the more distinguished you are
That seems that seems like a bad bad vibe
That seems like a recipe for for quite a doctor nature
Incycle
Let's go
That that that
I guess one question I'm sure you get all the time but I'm very very interested in
Like
Was there ever a point
Where
Likes
You
Word like
Legitimately afraid
For your life
Because
I have to assume that being in the
You're around people who
Do nothing but spread violent rhetoric
You know like it's got to be
I would assume
Frequently
Pretty scary
The correct answer is yes
Lovely
Are you
People
I just never I never felt I was in danger
And so it was never
So that worried wasn't in your mind of like
Maybe they know already
Massive eye roll
First of all
I like I would text me but all of the guys who were in
Irish
What the fashion
It literally cannot control
There's no way they would have been able
They don't have they don't have good information
Awareness
The qanon folks are more plugged in
Call you on phone channels like
I guess maybe I'm just
Kind of like up in my head so I just imagine myself like constantly being like
Figure.it.out Ono
Like that that's I think it probably takes a certain amount of like
Putting that aside
To be able to be in an undercover
Situation
You know
People in the
Convention Center
Security
You're saying you were in like Hotel
Parties and stuff like you're probably drinking
With these these folks and
And such
Like
I would be so scared of that like
I don't know maybe just because I I talked a little bit of s*** when I have some drinks
So like I would be so afraid of just like saying the wrong thing
I don't know I'm I'm I'm fascinated by this aspect to
Love what you like me
Beautiful boy
Message sky for coughing
And I always like mashed
What about the June
So he was like
Friendly or Nazi Germany
Whatever dude
Obituary James O'Keefe
Sponsored open bar party afterwards and cottages
Smart smart
I mean I can relate with gallstone
Angles of that bike I certainly would
I end up slamming drinks at a open bar
James O'Keefe party
McKenna Bachelor
Existing there
I'm not so
Was that where you got your llama
You've liberated this llama
I liberated my brother retracto
Well it's me
It's quite an attractive llama I can understand people
Wanted to swipe it
But I also got covid
Congratulations
I'm so what does things I wanted to bring up his kind of like
Related to the stuff that we kind of go over on
This show is
I feel like
My sense of things is that
There's like Alex and his
Serta propaganda world
Orlando
The sort of waters that you were swimming in
Were there related inasmuch as theirs
Hard right extremism and a lot of the same ideas and a lot of the same
Desires for the world
Seems like that's a completely separate
Like
Their names
That that
Ring out in the communities that you were talking about that
And nothing to do with like Alex and Infowars
I think probably I'm guessing think that Alex is a joke
Would that be accurate
If you used to like younger fashion
I need so people like
And they're all they talking and somebody was like
He says the frogs turning gay frogs
There is this like
Yeah I've seen a lot of that on like your maybe message boards people
Trying to rationalize like yeah he sucks but you know he was an OG or whatever going to like about alley
He woke me up but then also like I think he's bad
Cory sucks
Yeah and I have a lot of people
Actually why
Action bondsman
In creating
Really like the Goodwill
People are pretty forgiving in
I need the kind of
I don't
I didn't really
Interesting
That that is that is it a like
Bizarre
Side effects
I do I do think that it you know like even Nick Fuentes
Like talk about how awesome the 6th
Even even someone like as close to
The World of Alex is in
Doesn't need to cover
Himself
Which wouldn't just be like it was good
Antique
Has Ryan Infowars on his stupid
Atmosphere because they understand all the breakers
Everybody
Yeah everybody says
Right now the Knicks
America First pack
Like the whole event thanks to Peters
Kmart in was
Machete to Marjorie Taylor Greene
And
And they turned on him
Like the necklace
Mickey turned on him even though you wasn't invited speaker in
Yeah that's there's there's something very important about that one
That's a crazy
Congressperson
Did you do you ran into her I assume like
You would
You might be at the MCG
So when I'm done
Revenge
Running into the loom alot
She's really like loud places
So
X displaying
Fire magic
If I were to ask you about just about anybody would be about the same response
Yeah that doesn't think I was I was curious about like
Is there was somebody who sticks out as like
But then you know what I don't want to I don't know if I want to the Surly dwell on positive
About to eat.
Mike Massaro
True Believer
You could be walking
Gray pillows.
Schnucks that's nice if you're in
So there's like a sincerity behind that even if it is
Talk to you about
Our China
Stole the election and I have
Forensic
Yeah at least it's sincere that he eat think that's what's going on
Set the time
When is also accessible
So blind blind
Who opens up is a little bit of a
Little bit of a what's it called
Blooming
Military s***
What is a
Arm socket
Security
Always best if you just go
Closest bar
So
King Soopers
Irresponsible
Justin Bieber in public
You know
This is weird
Rodger Stone
Is like
And nauseous
Numerous
Shots fired
She is very rude I don't think you I don't think you would get that from her soda pop
Public appearances
So friendly
Yeah feel like she comes off as
Not mean at all
Super super I thought you can do something for her she's very friendly
If you're in a position of power whatsoever
All these people I'm pregnant
Go online that's that's one of the things that it
You know
Weird here is the the overlap
In terms of a lot of like ideology but not actual overlap
I mean you got phlegm you got Mike Lindell
You got Laura Loomer
You got Nick Fuentes
Let me know where are there are at least a number of people and then you said you went to the November rally
Stop bustillo
Then I guess January 6th
And Stu Rhodes was at both of those
I mean I saw
Actually
I said
Tejada Street
Hi
Capitalism
And no media coverage
Literally
A1 Japanese newspaper a single picture
Nobody else
When you covered
You're the only person.
Taco Bell
When he tried to storm the stage
It was it was wild inside and it was strange shooting so
Has Ryan Jennifer Lawrence and
Not the actress
Nausea
Good for her that she's not the turbo Kristen basa would have been Works games watch for me
Sure was speaking on the stage
Green Shadow gate
Millie weaver or is that you've been fired
Touching human has like a healing properties
She was like trying
So you can't really understand and
Obviously
Like we're not
America America
And then when he walks away
Okay
That's the effect he has
He ruins other people's things by lyca
Bombarding with energy if not everyone's as burnt out or like
Let's Pied Piper this year let's follow that guy
Yeah and then he was like how are you tonight
People drawing tonight
Some people got stabbed
Everybody in line off in front of the Marriott
Sure
But it's still broken so I have no idea what he said
And
Stay there there's a call for proud boys do you be wandering around
Deputizing
Course
Everybody
Obviously
I went to DC not too long ago and made a pilgrimage to Comet Ping Pong
And nothing but antifa federal agents the entire
The entire place is packed
Why was he with
Absolutely
One one question I thought of is
I think if it's something that I talked to with the bill Ogden one of the lawyers and the same
Hookies
Sometimes being
Exposed to a ton of material
On a regular basis
You question a little bit of
Your preconceived notions are like
The ideas you go in with
I was wondering if there's any point
That you can think of where you questioned like
Maybe these p
People are right
Or onto something
Did that ever happen
Never
I was raised Evangelical
Libertarian
So it's not fascist or qanon ship was going to sell it would have been
Will less less less that and more more like
Just
Losing a grip
On where you were
Wineries
Was Italy One Life undercover for like ever be things I would say
28 year old normal
And so I was already having to do all of this like
Is your news I would literally
I would have super strength
Like one
194 listening to One Thing for so long
Probably helps because it was just constantly
I might I might listen to
That's fascinated imagine that that forced you to be analytical more the you know then then just if you had
At 1
Persona if you well you know like
That that might have been really helpful
Play to keep keep you grounded
Yeah yeah and I spine
It's very easy.
He committed to like show reality
Sure there'll be times to I was just outside of thing
Understand
And
Sissy
Answer to whatever they're saying
Yeah you have to have to sort of Translate
Decode
You can put that with that
Like I feel like it would be tough not to just likes to come to
I'm thinking of qanon it's kind of random
Because
You know so much as I can
You know
Whatever the belief is
You could just
Have any belief
You think like at least I think that most people
Be with that way do you think of that
Do you think that there is more of a set system
For the things that they believe then
Then Ben random
I think the defense systems
For what they are
Just like you having
Crazy makeup looks
And then I see
Experience
Super well-informed
Like I would watch people say s*** like she still alive
I didn't know it until this person convinced me
Uber to party knees
It does kind of Beauty in person in a way that is in
9/11 Memorial
Party
General playlist
Speaker
Your Dental Designs
11 Memorial
Party
It's $500 a head
Chicken breast
The beauty dinner the night before
Chiropractor in Bryan
He says the crowd how many people
0 not enough
Yeah that's
The Inn in those circles that the question you do not want to hear someone posed like
Oh God
She's going to go horribly
But then he was like
But you know more people are dying
The current
Joshua's are the ER room
Financial aid
You know
Is conspiracy theorist
500 dollar dinner
Dinner
I'm saying that that's disrespectful sober to do open mic
Conspiracy material
And $500 dinner
Microwave
Whatever
Interpreting
Yeah
I think I think
I have a sense and this is completely uneducated
I feel like
Three people are definitely responding to whatever like YouTube videos they watch or whatever whatever creator
Their version of things
But whatever their creator believes
That has a slight bit of Random
Stewart
Absolutely
Right right
It can't be like whatever like
How are you feeling today
Now the world is doomed
Yeah it's B narcissism projected someone
You mentioned the kids under the Getty
And
I wanted to loop back to this really quick
Do people believe that
Oh my God
Hey listen
Right right you're a people who have been conned
You think cuz I've only heard that ever from one weird guy on YouTube named Steven Kelly who
I believe that he has like mental ninjas
Recalls them Jedi who go down into the Getty
You do battle with like the demon
And stuff down
I've never heard I've never heard that being like a a more sort of
Popular
Theory
I'm excited to hear that the Jedi are getting some help
Let's
Eastside baptism
Do they travel that far to get really drunk
These events
It says that but instead you go to extra
What
FaceTime Glenwood
Videos me on telegram Channel
Embarrassing
People rapping
Weather
Dino Hillary's executed
This is not an appropriate question for a baptism
Listen
We got to get rid of those demons
Did you know
The answer was relieving Harper you
Wow
BatDad
The answer in and of itself is so telling I mean it's it's
It's a like
I am going to eat we want you to be able to let out your like
Bloodlust
We're going to throw Hillary to you the wolves
So I mean I mean
See you said you grew up Evangelical and we're libertarian
How
Does this Translate to
What I presume is a pretty
Decently left
Set of beliefs now
Mom was never religious
Managua
Journey
I'm not domination
There is no God
Interest in politics
And then
I read a book
Okay
Larry Elder
I'm not judging
I can tell
I could tell you
Deeply troubled
Michael franzese
Likes
It's supposed to be the non-aggression principle and I can't have the the state having a monopoly of force
Got to get out there
Got to stop those beliefs
Samurai
Right or from not protecting
Businesses in Tampa
Yes yes it is very important
Jeopardize my business forum
That would be
State that wouldn't be state
Monopoly of force
Became
I mean
When Michael Brown was killed
Where
I really remember I don't remember
In St Louis
You dead like some disillusionment then I'm guessing that that's what you're describing
With the libertarian
Bend
Yeah I mean
I was just
It was a joke
Gary Johnson stand
In high school I had like
Libertarian sticker on her so I'm not really one to be able to judge
It wasn't good
So
And
Campaign for Bernie Sanders
Remind you that to that like awareness or like connection with some of the libertarian ideas probably came in
Handy
Along the way
Yeah that's that's one of the things that I find really interesting is there like
Is it Webster Tarpley I believe wrote a piece about like it like around the time Trump was running
About how libertarianism in like Ron Paul fandom
Was a like
Doorway to Fascism basically
And I don't like him at all he's a like former Infowars doodoo is like
You got a lot of problems himself but I think he was
Are we accurate on that one that assessment
I mean like
It's bizarre
I'm always surprised
Mommy
Really
Little allergy
Yeah but you can't even like me cuentas say stuff like that like a little a libertarian
That's better that that Dodges that's on both sides there
The guy
They wanted me to meet
Stewart Rhodes was a Ron Paul Stafford to lick his neck
All kinds of tentacles coming out in so many so many seeds planted by that weird
Family Paul family
Yeah
You were you were doing this over the course of
The pandemic
Do
Imagine
I don't know if this matches up with your
Experience but I imagine things got
Worse
Over the course of the pandemic
More people gravitating towards
These groups
More extreme
Stuff going on
Angrier
Talk
So yes I started
Nightingale
Cheerleader brightness
Certainly.
People became work
Actual
Because
February
Where is the Beastie
Warframe
Ofra is like
I'm probably next to me
And by
Especially in the qanon places I'm sure it was very unwelcome to be vaccinated
Daughter just goes
Options for grandchildren
Mongo's
Driver's license
Turn my mom's last chance for grandchildren
That's a concept of child shouldn't be dealing with at all
Eli's going to photo
There was that and then
I got so busy in July
Work Meister
I understand that certain feeling
Anything
People were dying
Music
Waco bar was fine but coffee wasn't
Help me something about chickens. Temperature
Weird
I also would like to apologize that you're talkin about people dying and the thing I got hung up on was
Cold brew. Okay
So then they were like
That makes sense
Does it
Is there something different
Yeah you see it Spike protein anthrax
I have enjoyed watching
Sort of the gymnastics in the hurdles over
Of trying to make sense of like
The shifting landscape of
The conspiracies and I imagine being like
Therefore it and having conversations with people about it would have been
Even more
Confused
So bizarre I mean Irish
Undoubtedly that's what's coming
And I might know you want to tell me if she could kill it and put it in water
Yes
That sounds really good
Fermented grape juice it's that
Can I have some
Probably be full of bacteria and
I did I do have
Sort of a begrudging respect for folk remedies
But it'll come up people come up with
What is a begrudging respect of me the creativity and optimism of it not not so much the
The trying a thief
The month-old grapefruit in a fridge
Is
That's pretty sweet
That's that's
You have to be a dreamer
Transfer that to be something that you could tell someone else
Show me this beard on
It's real
.
Until like watching people
Very bizarre
Yeah
It's like it's kind of like a reality versus non reality
In a really microscale
Just these people as the sort of avatars of reality and not reality
And I'm guessing not reality generally win
I'm very open and honest and getting
My mom died almost died
You said that at first people are really open to that change
Do people fart
Did you did you run into many people who like
Didn't like
I've noticed a thing and maybe it's just certain through Project Camelot stuff but like
Bears
People anything for like 2 I guess but the people who are like you know what this whole thing is made me realize that
Science isn't real
But there is no
Such thing as a virus
Do you ever do directed any of those those folks
Is cool
Cool book
Knock knock
So not very
Eden
That's that that's something that's interested that's something that I hadn't really considered it is video
There is probably a taboo on the
Some conspiracy ideas even in these
The circle
But there is a point that's too far
Unbelievably boring
I mean
First you in on rally in 2019
Exact same speech he gave
And it's just me on Sycamore
But I was in Dallas in May
I was with him it was me and him
The sparkles
As far as I know
Siemens parts are red
Stickers all over it
Windshield windows
Mandalas later on
Junior
It was like this
This is this
Okay
Not sure it looks great before but all the other stuff is is so
Impressive in and
Unbelievable
Yeah that is that example or like that one seems like
That makes a lot of sense cuz it's
It's kind of like this is undercutting our brand
You know like this is
This is going to make
More difficult for me to get people into the revenue stream
JFK jr. is Dad
Alright is alive as it were
That's a that that makes sense
Leave the virus doesn't exist I guess that's probably
Is maybe in the same
The same Brown
They're like I'm trying to spread Medical
Conspiracies but this one is that's too much
Yeah it's a virus virus
My sister stole my churn
That's a good point
Julissa
Well
That's that
The grifters oldest doctor group
He pissed doctor he is a chiropractor
Science doesn't matter than all of us doctor
I was just about keeping your spine in line
That's all that's all we're doing here
Be
Being in some of these things like worlds in these communities
We're coming up on the midterm
And
You around in what I would say is a
Babe
Election heavy time to be embedded with
These folks
What do you expect
You did that you're convinced of that
I'm so a lot of something to go to
Their evil satanic whatever God has Dominion
That's why they called it that man
I literally sometimes you just like how do you
So
Every single
More like Sprite
You know he would
Jim come in and teaches like this is how I
My likes are elected.
It's just quite a workshop to offer
Oh I just followed her kids home from the school bus everyday until she decided it wasn't
Worth the $8,000
Shut
Doctor children
It just happens a Cool Wind
Accidents that I was constantly following her children
That's pretty f*****-up
And we have
Wow
More.
I don't know
I mean what's what's up what's the
A woman's children because she's she's a rhino
Until she quits her job
The point
Or you don't like there's no intervention
People
Every jurisdiction
Machine
And so that was offered a solution
So I don't really see how
And maybe there
Amen
Trying to think of a solution is probably
Probably impossible I mean like
Yeah these like just the example you're giving
Whether or not this happened exactly as it did but you know like
The person following
Someone's kids
MMA quit there
They're low-level
Position
Probably no one ever would hear about that you know like
They're there are tons and tons of offices that are in local levels that like
All kinds of nonsense could be happening around the
Until
You know
Schultz everything
Dinosaur tourist
Last year in April
Robby Starbuck
August
This makes
Everybody was all in
Like watching
You know
8888 like a
You being exposed to that at that time things that like
Seems like complete nonsense this is never going to stick
I'm in now here we are
That's
That's probably a lesson that
Is very difficult to learn
Is that like
Stuff that sounds like it might be insane
Could be adopted by the entirety
In six months you never know
Yeah I mean like watching all the
It is so well organized
And I I mean
To figure out
And behind the people who were probably complaining just about trt just a little bit under the surface is public schools are evil eye
George Soros
Yeah
Yeah that's that's that makes me think of like if you go back
Cui
Like somebody episodes from around when qanon was
Coming around
I
Very
Famously
This isn't a big deal this is
This is just some dumb things happening on a message board
And like I I really
Boy I was wrong about that one
That's a that seems to me the casino way this is going to
Like
People are going to buy it
Yeah it's so weird
It was just
Discount everything
Yeah cuz they're all I mean
Do you think you think we're going to have another another bad election
I'd say I agree with you
I just
It's very frustrating Jodeci
Quality
Kairos or whatever saying stuff like
All the GTA V
Are you like Dreamer
Yeah it's it's it's unfortunate that the opposition party as it were does not seem to grasp
The reality of the other side
But there again
Extensively
Really really dragging it
Refuse to hire people who would be like
Yeah that headline is is a trap that you're setting for yourself
Chainsaw
Yeah Everett that news is the onion now
Put it all in the headline
People are just going to skim this
When you were when you were
From from your time
Hanging out
But these folks
What what do you think
Is the most
Troubling
Thing for you right now
Like what what worries you are most looking back on on
Your time and how things have developed since then in the things
But you seeing
What should people be aware of maybe that they're not paying enough attention
People don't really
Understand
There is
Arkansas
Shortly after I was.
Josh Hawley
You don't look like a lumberjack like
Macy's
Exactly. Talk about being the brawny man
I don't understand people are still missing.
Stop
Because people
You are not
We haven't done anything
VP that sort of right-wing points
Make making
Spell points with bad Solutions
China
Yeah
The name for white people
And also Italy
Snot sucker
They are like blind with
Mario B I mean
Where's Ethiopia
Joe Biden
There's no
Let's paper that is
That could be a problem
You're so you're saying also like in the under 30s
That's that's
That's a community that you think is is
Turning
Thule right populism in the Moors
Troubling way
People Are People
Well
Skin problems
Yeah yeah
And the end of the people who will speak to those problems
Or maybe people laugh
Darker agenda
Well I hope that's
All this doesn't combine into a terrible tornado of s*** this year
India elections
The school board's the
The
Turn towards right-wing populism the denial of election
The covid stuff
Seems like a perfect storm
Well you know
God has Dominion
Dominion
So
It's in his hands
That's that is true and now I believe
It's time to pray
I think that's that's as good a .22 drop off after 22 to wrap this up
Amanda thank you so much for for chatting with me
I'm sorry I was in a little bit all over the place
Dina do you have anything that you would like to to plug to to direct the folks towards
You can follow me on Instagram
No turtles is 17 Q Link
Yeah so no Turtles 2
It's from that time that Alex was tripping
I camera
And then
That was said there was a sober moment
For him
For Alex
What is my favorite
He was just tired
You desire
And instead of music
Nice
Well it's been blight
I'm sure we will we will speak again in the future
Alexandra Thurston color