Alexandra Thurston color
To knowledge sightmd
Novelty beverage
This week because
4 hours in
Three bottles of wine later remember my own name
It was a necessary break from reality perhaps but that's not sad
Let's not kid ourselves were much better with Faygo
Faygo cream soda in honor of the jug of America
We have become juggalo
This is all Madness all the time I don't even have time to look at the news without
It's insanity
It's crazy everything is gone now it's backwards and now we're living through the worst of it
It's very well bus
Quite frankly
How else
This is kind of the point
If we normalizing we stopped fighting against
But at the same time it's like what
Do you do
Like it like the idea of waiting to the 2018 midterms
World's Fair election
Gerrymandering
Jack Ross Jack that's absolute
Play the play the outro
I think we can do at least you and I we can donate to causes
We can
Call senators and hope that helps
I think it's proven that calling Senators is b*******
And just s*** on their lawn if you have time to go for it
Shiting on Senator Orrin hatch's
If you have time feel free to do that but if you don't
Help help
So
Mail them
That'd be great
32b some Middle Ground between
Weeding
Extreme of like
There used to be a capitol building
There's something in the middle and I think
That's the only idea I have right off again if you have the time
Senators house
Some of us have to go to work
Anyway
Alright
Let's find them
S*** on the donator
God I love your transition love to give a shout in a welcome aboard
Thank you for donating
New policy walk status Alex we love you
Tell everyone at the bars at House Parties
The user are the most boring person in the world
Tell everybody to know all about the intricacies
Describe how many times I've gotten laid
Absolutely it's Street
So Jordan today we're going to be doing a very
Special episode
Defend
My assertion
That Alex Jones
Is largely basing his world 2 on the widely discredited
Forgery
The protocols of the Elders of Zion
Iowa
What we believe
Yes but it is kind of a b a b of a
To make a number of times on the show
I just got to and I want
I don't want our listeners to go read that book
It's a waste of your time and it's full of b*******
But I
At the same time recognize that we are making
He's playing tonight really
Literally back in them up
That's what I intend to do
Right it's kind of bulshit thing for us to take notes
Six months ago saying
He loves the protocol and all this s***
A couple weeks back.
Alex Jones of Robert David Steele
Yes I recall
The claim of the globalist
Have a Mars colony
Which they take
Babies to be slaves
Cuz they can't get back
And those Mars colony they're stuck there and now they're enslaved
By the rich
Mars globalist
So which is a proven strategy for white people for a long
Going to space back
That's wild
That claim
Is pretty wild
In the Fallout from that
Everybody started clowning on out
Alex Jones thinks there's Mars bases
Which he flatly denies although we found clips
But
She started to say
That the globalist
Set him up by Robert peel
But he came on to show to discredit
They're starting to be cracked within the Alex Jones Roberts
Steel universe
Deception already there
Is well so happen to the aftermath of this
Is that Robert David
Steel
Went on
Project Camelot
Also
We've got her name wrong every set it
Callahan
I don't even know this
I will tell you what this interview was all about on the other side of this clip
But I think it's important
Interesting
To hear how Roberts
Steel start visitor
When I'm sure Cassidy from Project Camelot
And I am here with Robert Steele and we are doing a very unusual
Robert takeover so go ahead Robert
Kerry Cassidy
I have seen all of those who have slandered you if I have been slandered recently by designer
Stewie
You may need
You made no
Sign of being surprised by Robert David Steele blaming design
At what else is he going to do
I've seen the way that you carry Cassidy and I now
Have been attacked by the Zionist
Cassidy usually I don't mind
Regularly
Enough to know where her head is on the whole thing but I definitely
She says is wacky b*******
So I think that's what's going on
No I don't think that's her cosmology I think that's Robert Steele
Okay and he's bringing it into her being like just like you have
I'm in the same boat now cuz I went crazy
The Zionist
Who are setting me up because I'm telling the truth
Am I girl
Play EverQuest
In the history of the world
So believe whatever you tell her
When is the Robert Steele
Interviews
Kerry Cassidy about the secret space program
Interview
I'm trying to do this it's terrible
Is that the Nazis
From Project Paperclip
Program
Good people
They create super soldiers and numbers of tens of
Most likely
There's all that sort of standard talked about super soldiers on the last Project Camelot
Which is great
One of the new Revelations that we find
Is Vietnam
Oh there we go now when this was not about communist
Okay we're start
Was Vietnam about communism
What's North Vietnamese Menace
The Communist Menace
Yeah but I mean
I'm just worried about rich people get rich
Outlook
Whatever layer you want on some level the media told people it was a bad cop
So
What did media would dare tell you
Is it the truth is that there were Stargate
They're also Stargates in Iraq
And that's why the Iraq War happened
Because
Saddam Hussein
Was going to
Allow in alien races through that
That portal
But he had
But we have to shut that couch
Classic sedan
That is classic
If there's one thing I know about autocratic dictators
They love letting in Alien
Just like ours
Power
What the f***
What about Korea
Probably
The explanation for all of America's War
Mostly it is 100%
I was like this is Wile
I've got to look into this more
Where does
Where is she getting this that the Vietnam was about Stargate
With a soldier who was in Vietnam
Who would get been getting hypnotic regression
With a therapist
She
He asserts
Vietnam
He was fighting Giant Beetle
So right
Do you know what their names are
That's why it was
Was called the Tet Offensive
And there was a mass hallucination
Remember that
Only through hypnotic
Can you recall that the text
What were the Beatles
Strategic
Sanford
Vicious Critters
Like wow
She's basing all of this on an interview that she
Who has PTSD I feel really bad for him but I don't want to make fun of him
He's doing the best he can
Hypnotherapist who's also in the interview
I start to get the sense that maybe this is about her
Vietnam
You think it might be about a little bit
So
I was like Jesus Christ
This is this is the wildest s***
She's referencing this interview that you did it while she's talking with Robert Steele
The Robert Steele
You're the best you're doing the best work you're amazing
He believed the wars have been over Stargate
And Alex Jones as a guest
On his show
Repeatedly
This wasn't the first time he was on you stalking about Mars
Alex
Either doesn't know what his gas to believe
Or doesn't care that this guy is
Certifiably nuts
Do any of these people
I know I feel like
Steel
Well yeah but you're not one of those people
Welfare
Doesn't actually believe in
Stargates or whatever it is
Callahan
Call
So they just
Greenway
And forth by like
She says the s*** she wants
Never the twain shall meet
There is some of that that's probably a fair assessment opportunity to
Say like
You got the dumb Alex
Your tax guys are coming talk about
He's been in prison for 20 years
Do you think it's a f****** setup
You believe all this
Do some f****** leg work
Wesley Snipes should go on the shown be like Texas or Eve
Yeah absolutely
So
That was a little bit of fun now Jordan let's get
The protocol I wish I had
What do you know about these your protocols
I don't know anything
Nothing
Not the same
I guess so
Now we can do the now we can do the intro
This is a podcast for Dan knows everything about the
The protocols of the elders
So what to do on this episode
If I had more time to plan what I would have done
Is I would have taken a bunch of past
Messages from
The protocols of the Elders of Zion
And a bunch
Quotes
From Alex
Yes and I would have had you
And I don't think you'll be able to tell a number of them apart
Okay because I didn't have that kind of time
I just have
A bunch of packages that I found
From reading
Burgos builders
I've read it before in the past
But going through
Is
Not
Alex Jones
Baby-faced isn't
Higher
Philosophy on
The protocols
Brett
Tavolata
A lot of videos about the globalist come directly
And spiritually
From this
You believe that he is
Maybe and that he is most likely
And changed
From Zion
It's us
Gotcha
I believe that is possibly true but another possibility is
If you dig into a number of
Actually do
Still says that he finds like
Formative
A lot of those are inspired by protocol.
We need to Schartner
We're going to
Alright
Conspiracy
Exactly
Himself has become a master
Is just shooting out the same ideas
Is really recognizing
And where they come
Form of this
Paises the Mothership
The pig in the signals to the smallest
Tips around
The Earth shirt
Blowing
Yeah
I suppose that's fair
So I do want also still get the caveat that I videos a lot of other
And same sources Betty get stuff from and this isn't
Fully explanatory everything
But as we go along I think
Think you'll see many many very important
The protocols of the Elders of Zion First
Appeared in print
In Russia
In 1903
There's subsequently reprinted in a book and
In a book called The Great in the small and the antichrist
By Sergei Nila
Immediately after that
Add this chapter from his book becomes a pimp
Widely distributed
At this point yes
Very much so.
Azepam politicus widely
Distributed
Start to read
Start to heaven
Artifact
Most people believe
That
The actual writing of the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Was done
By Russia
Intelligence
Or buy a like a
They believe that it was a concerted effort
To demonize the population
Right
Are you really get deep into why
People do that sort of thing
It really goes back to the roots
Which
I don't think this is the whole story
Well I believe the roots of
Aasimar
You murderer
Lord and savior
Jesus Christ
Total no
The roots of anti-Semitism go back to the fact that Christians
In the early days
We're unable to
User
They weren't able to loan money
It with interest
The only people who were able to do that we're Jews
Where the population are Leon
They were not allowed certain jobs they weren't allowed
That's the only way that they could make me
Was to be
Loan make loans
Successful
And everyone got mad
I feel like you got to get out of our
Your pants like we've tried to force you into this box
And you succeeded in that box so f*** off can't got to go
Leeds
Basic because of Bible
The thing that they profess to believe
Have a history of Khan
Hopefully getting kicked out of play
I want your new coming into a new place you're always looked at as differ
You're not looked at as the
Local
Rightful population of a place
So the entire history of the nomadic dates
Throughout
Various Nations the date
Go to make a lot of money
Loan because that's what they have to do
Yeah quite a bit over the last three
Right
Where the cycle repeats
Much more harshly reinforced
I already have the word from the other place
Place to get kicked out of
Right
There is some of that
Over the course of history there's just been
A real black mark
On the Jewish population
It is unfair
I am usually
Like almost all the stuff you end up hearing
About populations are about legendary figures or mythology
From from way back
Thousand fifteen hundred years ago
Idea of these like
Bad blood thirsty loan shark
Is wildly overstated
Just serve
To create a demon eyes population
Cancel that
Protocols in a lot of ways
Coming to a head of it
Thousand
Plus gear Factory
Beating again
All Odds
So people
Still hate because of
Get mostly guy
Spider-Man that is a large
Portion of what the protocols talked about 2
Frame
This
Money-grubbing
I hate that even feels dirty to say but like
That that sort of
Mythologize nature
And they turn it into like
This is what they're playing all along
Since way back is all their plan
Is this
And force them into a job thinking that it will never be
They were horribly segregated against then once
They figured out the
That thing they got segregated into was super successful
They bided their time and I have planned Revenge
Against
Well I mean I have a good case for
Like the entire thing we talked about about people really projecting what they think they deserve
Yeah
So
This this
Prim
I just kept on going
And this
This pamphlet comes out of becomes really popular
When asked
About where it came from
Like why did it get published
Every single story
Changes
The years change
When this was supposed to happen
When
People came in
The possession of the original manuscript
The story of how it came to their hands like
Espionage and people breaking into the Jewish elders
Sanctum and stealing
It's not you know it's all again just mythologized garbage
Stories
Stories Keep Change
Just lends no credibility
Like it is Night tickets early night
1800 but that's not a time that we don't still have decent records
Yeah we have decent records from 300 BC
Right
2019 22 Henry Ford published 500,000
Copies of
The protocols of Elders of Zion
And he started
To repackage and publish them and articles in newspapers.
With titles like
The international Jew the world's foremost problem
Yeah so he just started to use it as really potent
Anti-semitic propaganda
Around the same time
Publishing
It comes out that it's a forge
It comes out that they are they have soundproof
Researchers have found proof
Complete fraud and actually stolen from multiple pre
Existing
Scott from documents that are very
Just ideas from them are package
Some paragraphs or even just stolen for
Absolutely
As of this comes out but that does
Stop Henry Ford from
Continuing
Going to push it
SATs Medical
He even goes on to a verbal says about the same thing later
He goes both have very similar perspective
This text might be a forgery
But the ideas
Contained inside of them are
True
Is
I mean there's no way around that
I've been interesting because
Did I don't care if what I should be basing it on it's been debunked
No it's a Feeling
Dangerous
Why not theism
Still has such a stronghold
Because we started
Sure we started the knot
The 500,000 copies of this b*******
That the Jews are trying to take over the world will end up killing us
That's all they're all the goalie in the world
What is
Happening in America in 1920
So
Great
America
Hitler was very inspired by the protocols of the elders believed in
To at least some extent
At least
Definitely
Stop
That supported them
Referred interesting Lee
Two Jews as vamp
Empires
Alex Jones does a lot
It is interesting to go back
Juseword
Right
That means Alex uses it in the context of
Child molester the whole bunch
Sprite Hitler uses
Suck
Kim's dry
Except if you change the phrase
Step
Like I said
In the twenties and
Perhaps even a little bit
Before that
People started to discover these very similar things
And other books
One of them
Main things that it's taken from
Which is
It's an 1868
Systematic German novelist Hermann
There's a chapter in it
Titled in the Jewish cemetery
Salida
Describes
A bunch of really powerful Jewish people getting together in a cemetery
Plotting nefarious
Which is very very theme atticly similar to
A lot of it is Whole Hog
Repurpose
The other
Piece that is
Wiley
Widely plagiarize
Within protocol
Is a book called conversations in Hell between Machiavelli and Montesquieu
Came out in 1864
It is basically
Exactly what the title says it's
Yeah it's just a dialogue
Inhale
Where Machiavelli argues
In favor of despot
You think the despotism is the way to go and people don't
Preserve the freedoms
Fanned on the side of liberal
So here here or a couple
I just side-by-side
Comparison give you a sense
Reveille dialogue spoken by Machiavelli
Like the god Vishnu my press will have a hundred arms and his arms will give their hands
To all the different shades of opinion throughout the cow
Now here's from the protocols
These newspapers like the Indian God Vishnu will be possessed
Hundreds of ham
Each will be feeling the pulse of various public
Sounds like a bad book
Absolutely
Like duet
Citing Vishnu
Specifically
Hundreds of hand
It's all like that's
Very clearly.
Machiavelli is talking about Vishnu in hell we got a lot more issues
Sherp another one
This is Monty
I understand the figure of the god Vishnu
Sufficient
You have 100 arms like the Indian Idol on each of your fingers touch
To the spring
Arizona protocols
Our government will resemble the Hindu god Vishnu
Each of our hundred hands will hold one spring of the social Machinery of State
I'm just very obvious that box
Hey there
Tons of examples
Direct rip-off
The dialogue in Hell between
Machiavelli
Is not about
Am I missing
Has to do with which way is better to sort of take over a country
Which is the preferred system
But so many of the ideas
Just repackaged
Repurposed
Anti-Semitic
Gotcha
I want at this point I hope
I don't know if I have
If you're interested you can do
Specifics
But it is a f****** forgery
It's been proven over and over again
And anyone who doesn't believe that doesn't want to believe it
Right they feel
They have to be emotional hatred of Jews and they don't want to deal with
Reality in order to
Kind of correct that
I do feel a little weird about the fact that I have the protocols of the Elders of Zion on my Kindle
Yeah well your phone is a peasant
I will now begin our portion
The analysis
Of the protocols of the elders
The I like the officious
Nature of your words don't know how to do that
Motion
Seconded
As my own motion do that all the way it's set up as an address
Speaker in the Tribunal
Do you learning Elders of Zion have gathered
Further meetings supposed to take
Place
I believe in 90
The case then
60 whatever
Free dating app
Verydice
The year change
I think what it was they claimed
That it was from 1900 at turns out they met in 90
I took the initial claim of when that came from could not have
Elders of Zion
No elders
Jewish organizations me
Williams Ian isn't was a thing back then like Theodor herzl has a book called The Jewish state
Also widely
Cited as an inspiration
Just a text
About how the Jews need their own state
Yeah because they've been everywhere
I'm not fully on board with I think that Israel has a problem
At the same time
Design isn't that existed in the early 1900s was not
The same thing that we associate Zionism with
Associate Zionism
As a term
Jewish Supremacy
That is sort of the 121
Mental
Thing that we make
Between those words
Zionism largely was
About we got a
24oz to be around
No matter
Yeah it's Cedarhurst.
Came out in 8
Conclusion of it
Man
Any anything in German
Jews
Really bums me out
Not good not good I don't like hearing that
I believe that a wonder is generation of Jews will spring into existence
The Maccabee ends will rise again
Let me repeat once more my opening words
The wish for a state will have it
We shall live at last as freemen peacefully in our own home
The world would be freed by our Liberty and Rich by our well
Magnified by our greatness
And whatever we attempt is there to accomplish for our own welfare
React PowerPlay in beneficial for the good of humanity
That's the sort of an encapsulated of what
This this
Theodor herzl Zionism
In the late 1800s
The maccabean
I'ma go today
What is a good
Aspiration
The Jewish people clearly didn't
Someplace to be
Absolutely
Treated as equal
Everybody's
And they don't get runoff
At the same time saying in like
This sort of Declaration
Is what
Anybody
Recess
We deserve to be free the world will benefit from our freedom we will enrich Humanity
By whatever we are able to create
It's a positive message we f****** have it in our declaration
The world will be a better place
If you stop f***
With us and treat us like
Instead of taking that message
People got really mad
Really scared
And started
King with them and not trade
Absolutely
This idea of the Jewish Council
Meeting
Comes
To be in this Protocols of the Elders of Zion it's one person
Ostensibly
Giving
A speech
About what has happened over the last hundred years
The plans that this Council has for the next hundred
What they're going to do to people
Got now I am just going to read you the things that I highlighted
I'll just let you respond to them
And also I reckon
Nize that
In order for any of this to hit home
You have to have listened to
Or just
Apologizing
You're the first one so does seem like it's more for you
But it's like
You're you're doing this because it's like I need everybody to know that I'm not making this up
We're going to go through the f****** document we are
30 headlines on his headlines headlines
It must be noted that man was bad instincts are more in number than the good
And therefore the best result in governing.
Terrorization
And not by academics
Discussions
Sounds
Like how Alex Jones says the globalist think about us
Yeah I don't like that
We're stupid
And the only way that
Going to want to deal with us is through
Great
Because as Alex
In the past
Where's the Patriots and where
Far outnumbered
By the asleep
And we're fart
Destroyed by the global
Gotcha
Here's another one
Next next passage political freedom is an idea but not a fact
This idea one must know how to apply whenever it appears necessary with the
Have an idea to attract the masses of the people 21 party
For the purpose of
I'm crushing another who's in the Thor
This task is rendered easier
Opponent has himself been infected with the idea of freedom
So-called liberalism
And for the sake of an idea is willing to yield some of his power
Is precisely here that the
The Triumph of our Theory appears
The slacking brains of government are immediately by the law of life
Caught up and gathered together by a new hand
Because the blind might of
Of the nation
Cannot for once
Single-day exist without guidance
Authority merely fits into the place of the old
Already weakened by liberal
That sounds familiar
Sounds very familiar
I mean I don't know if Alex could use most of those words
In their proper
Perhaps not
But
The men look at it
He has his
Conceptus Alex
They're like it would not be good
Good liberalism is
Tricks in order to get us to socialism which leads to
Despotism
Your words to today's episode
Boom that's what that saying
Is your already infected with
This idea of liberalism
And because of that you're willing to let go some of your freedoms
You're not willing to let go of some of the control of the government
And he's Shady globalist behind the scenes
Are just going to take over the slack
Whatever's flag
They're going
To take it
Therefore every game is a zero-sum game you lose a little lose an inch to the globalist thing to take to
Yeah
Exactly
That sucks
Yeah
Good thing or not real
In this next piece
Next song
This
Latest
This one is
Isn't about my
A dog
Will my dog Die album
It is indispensable for our purpose that Wars so far as possible should not result in
Territorial
War will just be brought on an economic Brown
Where the Nations will not fail to perceive
In the assistance we give
The strength of our pre
Predominant
At this state of things
Will put both sides
At the mercy of our
International age
Ginger
Which possesses millions of eyes over it
Ever on the watch
And unhampered by any limitations whatsoever
Our International rights will then wipe out National Rifle
In the proper sense of right
Designer
AR
Not even really interested in
Like like there is the idea but their main goal is
Is Tubi
Everywhere
International
Spreading their money around
When people become
Dependent upon.
MN
Their power over is Over All Nations
Is super
Yeah
Okay
So they they want to go global
What they're saying there to is
In a Wars
Like you can't allow countries to take over other countries
That's just going to be a mess
Don't want to do that
Make sure that everything that is strictly Financial which
Alex Jones talks all the time
Control system
Of course I will have you playing government
Against each other
I am in whenever they
I have wars
Getting rid of
Which is exactly why
Our International
Well then why
Yes
Everything will be on a
International Global level as opposed to your own
National
Concerns
Where is these guys
Just what we said so far till
The bank to get a loan for a small business start-up
This is such a great plan
But that's the other thing that really needs
Analysts have gone over this also basically
It's kind of the same criticism
That I would make swaths of generalities
Truisms and stuff like that
No specific
And in the same way
You go through this entire
Book
The hesitate to call it a buck
Will you go through it and what you see is a lot of stuff that's like
Okay
Whatever
I'm exam
Cuz there was stuff about like the police
We got a militarize the police
The state will be in much more control the stupid
That's true
It's it's it's
It seems like
Axiomatic
It's just
Yeah
Yeah I got a great
Here is another path
In the hands of the States today
There's a great force
The creates the movement of thought in the people
And that is the press
Department
Is the keep pointing or requirements
Supposed to be indispensable
To give voice to the complaints of the people
Express
Enter create biscuit
Presents that are going out of their way to disseminate
False information
Listen to make everybody feel bad
Yes because
Misconception
The Elders of Zion have taken over
And Alex Jones is conception the globalist
And basically control all of the mainstream media.
Elders took over the Press
Through the Press we have gained the power what are you into
Thanks for the we've got the gold in our hands
Notwithstanding
The Gather it out of the ocean
Tim's of blood in tears
Descriptive setting
Yeah
Whose blood
Yeah yeah
W
So
Is absolutely no evidence that it's
Genservice working
For a
Because what else would a government especially an autocratic government
Other than the demonization of
The Free Press
They want control over the dissemination of information
It's a good thing never happened
But more to the point
I hope at this point you're starting to see
Many many shades
The Fairly important pieces of Alex Jones's World philosophy
Globalist
But he's super afraid of
Congress we have right now
Well I think is kind of an issue
Because
Spell because Alex Jones is very much
Not upfront about Allah
The things that underlie his belief in the globalist
He has given somewhat of a path
And whatever you can he gets accused of being auntie
Somatic or anything like that he gets the fallback be like
Right and because he has that sort of cushion butt
Truth
It's easy for other people who are conservatives minded
To be tricked
And not realize that what underlies
His beliefs is
Mastiff
The same thing is like
It doesn't matter if you know everybody bleeds red blood
Black people are far scarier that's why the cops killed
We have people who are very much in the same ilk
What's Jones
Tempt Providence
Media
You have Alex Jones you have Drudge
WorldNetDaily
You have all these sites
The put out
Similar
Sort of contact
And reinforce each other
And backup the globalist narrative
You end up having a conservative world
That is largely accidentally or intentionally I'm not entirely sure
Based on a lot of it
Yeah
And I don't know if ever I don't
It's not that I don't think anyone knows because a lot of people do
But I don't know if the people who are under the sway of this stuff and believe
Give this stuff really recognized
And
To me that's kind of scary
Because
Now you have
People who
Motivated by things that are ages medican origin
Being able to fight for the same goal
Without
Admitting that
Well what
Afraid of is
These Jew Banker
Well I don't think it's that I think
I think from what I've heard so far
What word
Dealing with is just
Not anti-Semitic
But
What
So it's it's almost the reverse
Instead of instead of a
Nation
Intelligence service
Disseminating information
Turn on this route
Small group of people
In order to
I am assuming
Something along those
Instead it's reverse
So now a small group of white people are using
Things to demonize
Everybody that's not white
I mean
Jus for globalist
Because you're not going after
Jews you're going after Jews
Ann Black
People are Muslim
You're going after everybody
That's fair
Go back to the
So
This next part is about
How
They
When
The goal was to create such strife
And such a negative position that would they will reveal themselves of the savior
And will beg for their help
We have to we have to
Reactions
Terrible
Living situation
That's totally awful
Give off
The solution
I am retaking
We B
Nigerian dialect
Nowadays with the destruction of the aristocracy
Merciless money grinding
Scoundrels
Crew Yoakam
Upon the necks of the worker
We appear on the
The scene is alleged to saviors of the worker
From this oppression
When we proposed
To enter the ring
Of our fighting force
Socialist
Anarchist communist
Do we always give support
Accordance with the alleged
Brotherly rule
Of the solidarity of all Humanity
Of our social Mesa
There is docracy which enjoyed the
Was interested in seeing that the workers were well-fed hungry and strong
We are interested in just the opposite
Hemet
The Killing out of the goyim
Our power is in
The Chronic shortness of food and physical weakness of the worker
Because by all this
They all that this implies he is made
Slave of our well
In his own
Authorities
YouTube
Strength or energy
Decide against our will
Hunger creates the right of capital to rule the worker more surely than it was given the
Art by the aristocracy by the legal authority of King
So in there
Saying that
Because there are no Kings anymore
And there's all this capitalism
People are being the other workers are being
And the other being a
Essentially
And we will show ourselves
To be the solution to that problem
Further in
Mutating with socialist
Some communist
But that will all be just a
12 lb
Goyim
Alex Jones killing off
All the people who aren't
Why would you say this in a meeting
Why would you write this
That's the other problem
Don't record it a little meeting room
It's it's not like everybody had iPhones back then it was for the recorded this
It's patently absurd
But in very very big
Pieces of Alex Jones
He's about the globalist
And that they are going
To introduce socialism
As a way to
Neutrik downtrodden people
They're going to trick them
Into this control globalist want
To kill you and your family
He says it all the time
We will go check them
Kill off all of them
The other big piece of his thingy
You always talked about how the globalist
Want to make you weak because of your week
You can't fight back again
Conception
Because I guess your other one tons of vaccines and s*** back in 1980e not the prevalence of we have
The specifics
Of vaccines and putting stuff in the food but that is why I was Jones is willing
To believe those narrative even though
The facts don't back them up
Because
It reinforces
Does this sort of an idea
The comes from the protocols of the Elders of Zion
This idea that the globalist
Want to keep us weak
In order to not be able
The fightback
Insulate soft Killa
With vaccines
I'm stuck in the water
By trying to kill masculinity
All
Exam ways remix
Alright
Writing back then
I would throw and give everybody
Sure
Themes
This is it this is a terrible master plan
Totally this is a
What do we spell talk
We already
True
We could have too much backlash
Because they can't control the smallpox once it gets going
Here's a very essential
Elvis Master plant that is that when it goes down
People who master
And it will be safe
There we go
The hatred this hatred will be further magnified by the effects
Seven economic crisis
Which will stop dealing on the exchange
And bring industry to a standstill
We shall create by all the secrets Subterranean methods open today
With the aid of gold
Which is all that are hand
A universal economic crisis
Who mobs of workers simultaneously in all the countries of Europe
These mobs were rushed to shed the blood of those
Henderson plicity of their ignorance
From their cradles
And whose property they will then be able to loot
They will not touch
Because the moment of attack will be known to us
We will take measures
To protect our own
Alright now we have a new guest
He's going to talk to us about the coming Financial collapse told you about
It's coming in late September and we got him coming on he's going to
Weigel
$8,000
Orchestrated the global economic collapse and then
At the end
Talking about how these are going to be safe
Because they know when it's going to happen cuz they're doing it right
All the time by the globalist they're fleeing
Heading to armored without all the f****** time cuz they know when the attack is going to happen
Did it
Right now
Let me ask you a
I love question
Do they ever stop to sell any kind of boner
Okay now we know it's going to happen we know how it's going to go down but listen
We have an Easter to work
Play kids music
I'm not nearly done
Ever since that time we've been leaving the people's from one disenchantment to another
So that in the end they should turn also from us in favor of the Zion
We're preparing for the world
That's basically games
We're making people miserable
In order that eventually they'll fall right into our trap
Haha
The art of directing math
Individual Spherion verbage
Fire regulations
Then comment and all sorts of other quirks
It all which the goyim understand nothing
The Specialist of Art
Creative brain
Reared on analysis observation indicates of fine calculation
In this species of scale we have no rival
Any more than we have
In the drawing up of
Collection
In solidarity
Villains like important
It drives
A drive-thru
Because that Passage
Could have written
Could have been
About the people
Who are Distributing this thing
Right that's exactly what they're saying
That's exactly what
Look up might as well have been that intelligence offer being like
Check this s*** I'm just going to tell him what we're doing to him
It it is it is pretty wild when you step back to realize
Just how much of this is
Completely ripped off
An entire fraud
You start to think about realized
The
Reasons for the fraud
It does become very bizarre
Yeah just
You're saying that these people are using propaganda but you're doing that with in
A propaganda attack
Yeah it's just very amazing
It's it's layers upon layers
Perhaps
Let's take it one
Let's let's Inception
We're going to go one more level.
Maybe
This
Actually is propaganda by the Elders of Zion
The intelligence community
Make about the Elders of Zion
Still about make no mistake
This argument is made on Stormfront Mega so
Here's another passage the intensification of armaments
Armored redoubt
Decrease of police forces are all essential
For the completion of our Afroman
Engine plans
We have to get
Is there should be in all the states
Overworld
Besides ourselves only the masses of the proletariat
A few millionaires devoted to our interest police
And soldiers
George Soros
Soldiers
Do they have
A few millionaires
Millionaires is George Soros
Don't get slam Jack
Giving a speech to the other Elders of Zion right might as well
Age regression technology is right now
You got some nerve
So Alex Jones is super afraid of
The idea that the globalists are going to bring out a police state
I am
Commence right here it's and their goals
Create
Police then a few millionaire
Forget to live freely
Throughout all of Europe
Call Europe
And by means of relations with Europe
Another time
Also we must
Creates ferment
Discord
Hostility
Just they're going to
All around the world
This is the else invented
Alex Jones has a lot of ideas about education
Here's bathroom
We've fooled bemused and corrupted the Youth of the goyim by rearing them and principles and theories which are known to us
Ruby Falls
Although
It is
It is ended
Globalist
Two things that are complete lies
They
You know trick you into believing you're growing up
Climate change
Gay rights
Yeah these tortillas
Is that
So it's all good
It's all these things that they know
2B bulshit
They're sucking with
Your head by getting you to
Brett
Which
That's very Alex
This is all f******
I just
I just don't like
I feel like I'm being attacked by two people
Attack by Alex Jones
Believing this basic
And now you read English it to me
Fighting in my brain right now I think I hate this
But I think it's important
To look at it
Because it is a very important piece
Of his world
And without it we can have a fully robust picture what it is that's behind Alex Jones
What
Bulshit
Yeah
Answer when you when you have these
These things
From the protocols of the Elders of Zion
It's not necessarily preachings ammo clock
But they are
Entirely in line with
His beliefs about the global
And when you look at the stories that he believed
And the things that he
The things that are parts of his bulshit narrative
But don't stand up
To the scrutiny of fat
A lot of it can be traced back
Back to this
Because like you said with the Purple Penguin stuff
If you look at the facts of that
Benignly
It's nothing it's not something that even if
Conservative person necessarily should be screaming about baby make
King fun of
I could see Rush making fun of it
Or something like that
But the idea that you be actually angry about it and thinking
It means something
You have to believe
The globalists are doing it specifically to f*** with people's minds
And that has its roots
Right here
You don't think
It could have been
Okay
Maintenance
I don't know if it's like
If two comics
Come up with the same promise her little finger
Cuz this sounds really damning
I don't think it's parallel thinking
Because there's
Too much overlap
Yeah
You know I don't want to call Alex
Cuz that's
Second timer
He does try comedy quite a bit but I have to stand up comedy
So two guys go back in the archives
I am not willing to believe parallel thinking
Believe
Like parallel sourcing
Like I said with books
Into
The narratives that he believes those are also heavily based
On 1st
Like like how even if you haven't
19 Casablanca
You know the bait in like it's so
Part of our culture
Community
Zeitgeist
But you still kind of know what happened
If you live in Chicago and you seen a bunch of Chicago
Using Kaioken
You know I'm saying
Yep
People's influence shows through
Their product
Yeah people who are deeply inspired by
Sure
You have a lot of the protocols
And those are a lot of
Appreciate you trying to bring funding to this this structure is difficult without clip
But videos
They're talking about how they want to take over the world
To secure their
We must have everybody vote without distinction of classes and qualification
In order to establish an absolute majority
Which can be got from the educator
Property
In this way by implicating in a
Of self-importance
We shelter
Destroy among the goyim the important
To the family
Educational value
Alex always talks about how the globalist want to destroy your family
They want to get rid of it everybody should be raised
St. Mary's in order to make a democracy
Goodnight everybody
No is voting equally everybody
Isaac
Inw destroy
Peoples
And you can do this in a democracy
As most people
Most people are just go
In that majority-minority
Yep
Oh boy
When we introduced
True
Hitler is the Hitler is also an elder
They were set up
Hitler had some good ideas
So
When we introduced into the state organisms
It's whole political complexion underwent a change
States of infused with a mortal illness
Blood
All That Remains
Has to wait the end
Liberalism produced
Constitutional state
Which took the place of what was the only Safeguard of the goyim
Namely despot
So
This has
How is it
How is it that
These people
The only place
This kind of chicken
Come from
Is
An authoritarian
Dictatorship
Like the only people who would absolutely
Advocate for
Despotism
Nobody
Contained within the
Pretense of the fact that they
Sakrete
A global
They wanted to have it
Despotic rule over the entire world
Yeah but that doesn't make any sense
Consolidate the already despotism that you have
Especially if we're talking about
Oppression
Or
Situation
Those people aren't
The people who would
Give this information out who would fight against liberalism
Are the people already in power
True why would you think that people out of power
Would plot this liberalism
In order to
Their own desperate
Cuz that's what they're essentially doing they're saying that we're not the Dust
No but they're also sort of making the argument the despotism is
In the past
And that was the only thing that was keeping
The goyim the Sheep
Safe
Couldn't take them out
Liberalism
Can come in
Come over the top
So they couldn't do that for
Right
So there
So they're okay
It's almost making the argument that a dictatorship is the only way
Alex Jones is interested
Yeah yeah
The only way or well I mean
With bannon's interested tearing everything.
Right and only then can something be rebuilt
Like
Right there
Tyranny
So
Do you know how that you know how tyranny will always always
Gives up
Like tyranny is well-known for only being some
He never goes
To fart in absolutes
I'm cool with some tyranny is like
That's just how that work
So you might be thinking how much
Control do these here zionists have over the political process
God dammit if it's
It's not 100
In the near future we shall establish the responsibility of president
We shall arrange elections in favor of such presidents as having their pasts
Discovered
Some Panama City Panama weather
Where the agent
It's for the accomplishment of our plans out of the fear of Revelation
Hey I'm from the natural desire of everyone who is attained power
Namely the retention of privileges advantage and connected with the office
The president
Legitimately
Globalism is kept in place by pedophile pedophile blackmail
Blackmail sure there's other stuff drug-running one have you
But yeah a lot of child murder files
That's the narrative
Like Benghazi
The globalist
This again change the name
Digby globalist
Arrange a favor of such president undiscovered stain
So stupid
So stupid all it takes so much of it is here
So much of it is in the stupid book
Right I've always
How is it that year old
Pamphlet
Because there was a thousand years of
Before that
Already is a coiled spring already
This is just like
You want to hate them and now we've been given fraudulent proof that you should
That's essentially what's going on
Endive
And that's why it is lingard
For a hundred something
Really makes it mainstream people who were talking about like
The ideas of the globalist
If when you look at the history of it
Back in the light
I don't know if you go back to
Like a 50s
M60sbs
Abyss sword
We're about Jew Banker
Yeah and stuff like that
It wasn't it
Is couched in euphemism about
One has the 50s as
So
Is another path
By such measure we shall obtain the power of destroying little by little step by step
All the doubts that when we enter our right
We are compelled to introduce into the Constitution
The state to prepare for the transition to an imp
Perceptible abolition of every kind of cons
Institution
And then the time
Iscom
To turn every form of government
You are deaf
Their game is Just reinforcing
The idea that
You know it is heading to a one-world despotic governor
You're shaking your head
I just I'm just thinking the baffling
Like
How is how do you read this
And not sink
Do the best plan is to just
Let these guys
Pretend
And have fun
What do you mean
I know but that's what I'm saying even if these people are real and you're reading Pez
My thought is like
That's such a
Terrible plant
Triad
It's going to fail just on its own
If you have a cold
It's never going to work
They've all the gold they've infiltrated the media they've
Eroded the very idea of education so all of the people are dumb
You have a dumb down population
That shackle
Intentionally by the bonds of workaday slavery
But that's just Scientology
Somewhat
For sure
I mean the ideas of the globalist in a lot of this stuff is essentially what it does
Callmesnat
Neren
Bible
To him it's a cult
Like it's not real world
Very very dangerous
Do you think
Episode
So this kind of makes me feel like the way that we should
Be
Handling this bulge
The way that we
Be handling all of this b*******
Is the same way that we had
Handle
Is the same
Like so if I hope on some level
Ambivalent Alex Jones listeners might be able to come and find our show
Oh
Alright
I hope
Yeah I don't think that's necessarily ever going to be the case I think we should just start by finding regular
Thank you for listening what I'm saying is like I think that the only way
I really did do battle with Colt
Is deprogramming
By making fun of the ideas of the cult
You can
Research
And bring to light why the cult is full of s***
Or you can just hope for people
Like
Like URI Escape
Really what it was
I have
Illiterate I escaped weird Christianity but it was
Fall in with the Colts
So I mean
I don't want you to
I don't want to be
Look up the No Name Fellowship
You can find them online say if they were on a watch list
Because of what they believed in a kid.
But you you didn't have some like a podcast about how stupid
Did not
Well that's what we offer for
Little boy that's what we have to offer to the end
More liberal
Break right there
This is not a liberal bashing
The part played by the Liberals
Utopian dreamers
Will be finally played out when our government is
Is acknowledged
Till such time they will continue to do us good service
Therefore we shall continue to direct their minds to all sorts of
Conceptions of fantastic Theory
New and apparently Progressive
Have not have we not with complete success turn the brain with heads of the Glam with progress
Till There is not among the going one mind able to
Received it under this word
Why the departure from
Truth in all cases
Where it is not a question of material inventions
Fallacious idea
Serves to obscure truth
So that none may know it except us
The chosen of God
It's gardening
Guardians
That's magical technology
Well that's Med beds right there possibly but also the idea contained
Conceptions and fantastic theories new and apparently Progressive
That's just Alex Jones talking about
You know you're trying to confuse you with trans stuff
Yeah I'd like that they're just trying to change the language
Weird stop
It's right here that's what liberal progressiveness is
It's just a plot on the part of the globalist
Which book you want to read
People just really hate people's life
That's what you read people get really angry
Whatever like
Like Alex Jones is idea of prosperity is
Forever
Booze is bad for everyone
We don't have a healthcare Protocols of the Elders of Zion
Someone forever
Black Reborns
The same thing
It wouldn't have
F****** people
And I'm not I don't know how that
Fine
You wouldn't have you have an inch
Insurance Company
Right
Stop was specially when you distrust
Like the idea of distrusting
Progress
Is a real dangerous
In your world
Because what's the
Alternative
Regress
Conservative
Right
The only two things you really can do is move or stay the same as a civilization
If you can't say the same
No it's like you're always going
To err on the side of backwards
Yeah we're moving backwards as opposed to move
Forward calls from the military is not
It's not a good idea
It's very dumb
And probably illegal probably
All the stuff is
Regressive it's backwards-facing
And
And if you're going to talk about
It like
Everybody
Progressive
Never stopped
To think okay so if we're going back
From the actual going back or back then
Progressive
No no
The forward motion Through Time
If we if we like I know the answer is going to be
Write 8
To mention
It's f****** rich
Oliver rich white Christmas
It's all of those people who are the ones who always want
Back
They realize they are not important
And they're not in power
And that's why this is really effective
So
Really interests
Until recent times
Autocracy
The one and only serious though we had in the world
Why does Alex Jones always say
That the Russians
Are one of the only people who
Kicked out the oligarchs
Who kicked out the globalist
It's in here
The only threat
The design has felt they had
Was it
Pretty
Referring to like the anti-Semitism of the czar's and s*** like that
But
It's still track
Terms of mentality that the Russians
The strong one
Anime resisted
Is globalist
Why is Zionist
The mask
Man
I thought you were going to say
I'm just f******
This week
Give me an all hope that's not my goal my goal
Like what has
Change
Nothing
What exchange from this f****** Tech
Close dealing with this
They're still
Close I've gotten a lot better presentation
Unacceptable for Alex Jones
Reveal
But so much of this is based on protocol
The fact that we have a society where
You have to hide a bigotry
As opposed to
I still think about a year to you all have to be grass-fed
In terms of
You know like
Tattoos
I don't seem to hurt them
Delco great
Right
Nazi tattoo
Stripper lady who married Jeff swastika tattooed on her body
Sammy like she became a celebrity for a little while and all that did was
Edible markers you made a lot of money
I don't know I read where the world is going on
Be asleep
You shouldn't lose hope
There's Hope in
And lots of drugs
I don't think anybody's ever said
Open
Thursday self-satisfied
And once it all goes down we will die but it's some point
I Told You So told you so just like
Alright
We said what we needed to say
In order to affect the destruction of all Collective forces except ours
We shall emasculate the
The first stage of collectivism now this is about education
Emasculate the first stage of collectivism the University
By re-educating them in a New Direction
Their officials and professors will be prepared for their business by detailed secret programs of action
From which they will not with one immunity deferred
Not by one iota
They will be appointed with special precaution
And will be so place
Wholly dependent on the government
Alex Jones believe
The colleges are campuses.
And I professors
Through the foundation
Are just
Being given marching orders and they spout globalist propaganda
He did not go to college
Doted
I went to college
And my dad is going to Professor my entire life
I've known many professors
I can say
At least as far as the religious studies Departments of multiple
Major United States University
They're not getting marching orders from
Except
I don't think I've ever even had two professors
Using the same book agree on what
The book says yeah
Yeah that's the robustness of university life
Is
It's the same thing that Alex Jones
Facts about
It's a college
Because of the diversity of thought
And that diversity of thought
Whenever they bring it back makes you think they've been brainwashed
When it's really just
Oh I've been exposed to real thing
Right but the diversity of thought leads you to a more liberal more
Progressive Finance that generally
Feels like you're being brain
You've been personally it appears that
You shed your small-town bigotry
But
It's
It's right out of here
Book
So Alex Jones talks about how The globalist Wanted
Destroy our memories
And he's special because he has a memory
And beyond that
The only thing he was ever taught growing up
That's how bad the West is
I wasn't
We shall erased from the memory of men all facts of previous centuries
Which are undesirable to us
And leave only those which depicts all the errors of the government of
The goyim
Wow
That's dad on man that's exactly what that
Dad on and I don't believe that in the real world Alex Jones was literally taught only that suck in the West
Does Babs I don't believe that for a second
Specially not f****** Dallas in the 16th
32 that America is the greatest
No I imagine the worst subversive voices throughout the
60s and 70s
Are you seeing some America bashing going on
In the counterculture in the last certainly that was
Pervasive
But that's not
That's not what
He claims
He claimed that all he was taught growing up as how bad the West is
I believe that
I believe it's
Perception of you
Inflicted upon himself
Either directly from the protocols
Or from other sources
Pez dispensers to put him second
Yeah
So
I think we only have a couple more of these last year from the
And if you didn't want to just sit here and read at you for like 3 hours
Examples
So it started out as a pamphlet how long is it now
There's 24 protocols
This speaker gets off base
A little bit there are some derivate on Mars
What I would call Flights of Fancy
Okay I don't know I would I would say maybe
It's hard to tell cuz I have a Kindle and it doesn't keep track of page numbers necessarily be like
70 to 100 pages
Like it started out as this little pamphlet
82 and Addison Woods back then could be big didn't have TV
Just a street book
It's on my loose paper
Anti-semite
Where's the next one little bit
The legal fiction that everything in his fate belongs to him
Which easily be translated into fat
Will be enabled to resort to the lawful confiscation of all songs of every kind
For the regulation of their circulation in the state
From this follows the
Backpacks
Will that be covered by a
Progressive tax on property
That's all about guns
Regulated
Controlling
That guns all the way
Know if we can't get bitched out
Well I guess you can
About how much he doesn't believe in progressive tax
Federal
There should be a flat tax
You should tithe
Healthcare we should go back
Did all of it
Barbers did all that
I mean I think I was hoping I was hoping that if I got another broken arm they would just take it
What book did the regulation stuff you talk about does exist
In pieces that I didn't pull out
Disarm population as opposed to lead them to war
Right sort of thing like those sorts of fields at within it
But there isn't as much talk about guns
Necessarily
Cuz of 90
Technology was talking about it wasn't
I believe that this passage is more like actually just
Does mirror
To some extent Alex Jones
Isabel
Fisher
Economic crises have been produced by us
For the goyim by no other memes
I believe that there's a mist
For no other memes
Then the withdrawal of money from circulation
Let me try that again
Economic crises have been produced
Bios for the goyim for no other means than withdrawal of money from circulation
Cute capitals
Stagnated withdrawing money for
State which were constantly
Apply for those
Same state capitals for
So
They create economic crises
So they can take money out of the systems
Take it for themselves
Process that gives
Massive loan
Two countries when they make them fight with each other
In order to
Put them in situations where they can't possibly
Enslaved
Designer
Frankly that's
The college loans
But not
Creative Awards
Apparently
Damn well know how to put together a regressive College paper
Yeah but it seemed like a good gift of theirs
They talked about
Like if anybody
Goes against us what we'll do is get their neighbor to fight with them
I'm going to look
If they refuse to fight against each other will start a World War
Now looking with Alex Jones says about Syria
Says about Ukraine
He talked about how Ukraine was just globalist meddling in Ukraine
That wasn't
That's exactly what
The plan of designer
Says within the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Alex is conception
Russia is against the globalist
And so in order for them
To fight against Russia
They get Ukraine to do it
HD things in his
World
That aren't
Back by fat
Have to be back by something
Weather weather
Directly from this or second
Hand from this
This is the root of it
Antisymmetric fraud
Bitterroot
So much
Of the reason Alex Jones live
Sunnyway
We have one more one more
Could you read it
Thanks.
The. Of loan supervene
And brought all the states
I really do it you can't really do a lizards
That man could never say any of those words in that sentence
Do you want me to work just a Feen understand but
Like
Possibly
I guess if
You just absorbed this
Bright as a as a worldview
Because it's not like he's going back and checking
What is the Elders of Zion one of the Elders of Zion
And how does it relate
It has to be that
From
Young age
He was
And
Frankly because I love the word and we've already heard it use more times
In this episode
I think I've heard it
My life
He has been in
With this
This
To the point where it is
Infection
Like it's almost a virus
Throughout his brain
Through this lens
The time somebody who is super into the Bible
The people who are always like
16 it says you know that
I believe it's called like a schema
Like your psychological
Dima you build it up
You filter your experiences through you
You filter
Other people through you just create your
York the building blocks of your psychology
Through your life and it becomes a lens
Except of course he's not going back in
For tomorrow his with his
What is reading adult books
When he was sick
Around that age Maybe
Reading college-level book
Conspiracy theorist growing up
Oh yeah that's true probably the best
There's a real decent chance that his dad in the house had book
Read that were based
On
Protocol
Understand
And Incorporated them
So deeply into his schema
Now it just
Just become
What all this other stuff is built
Upon without him realize
And I think at this point I'm ready
Pulley layout my point and that is that there is no difference
Then Alex and Alex Jones is globalist
The Zionist
Canvas rajul
Text
Except for
Vague specific
Beans in water
I think that's my larger
Are you
Donaldtrump.com
Besides being overwhelmed by
Dread
I don't
What might my feeling is that this is second
If if not I'd like this is dispense
As a worldview
Through the Ages and never like
I doubt
That Alex
Has read the protocols of
I disagree I'm sure he's right at some point the first books he bought was mine
Cop cuz he was super interested in it and some lady was at the store
Like what
So the fact that he
I have told that story on the air
I'm not saying that he
Isn't Hitler anything
Hitler
I don't
I'm comfortable using that only under the context of like
I'm not saying
Giving out now Nazi or anything like
Like that but the fact like Sandra Bullock
Condom
He's willing to go on air and relief
Express
Early on in his life was reading
Things that maybe
Weren't true or where
Opposed
Position
Epic Center
Mine comp
I picked up there's literally no way he never read
It's a very notarius book
I did not know I have never heard of it
Before when you started it's very it's very big
I may have heard about it but it but I never
Is there hundreds of YouTube videos
Scrape I did not know that
There's such a dark underbelly of
Horrible
Yep
Community
But there is an undercurrent tell me that my girl
Carrier
Kerry Cassidy
I don't know and I'm not I'm not willing to make that claim but ihe
She believes
Beatles fought in Vietnam
Beetle Bailey
Holyshit
Call Lisa Sheridan
If the writer of Beetle Bailey is in on it
Everybody's in on it Danby Mort Walker
University of Missouri
Achoo on campus
I don't know if you guys out there listening
To take away from this
It is that you need to go to the universe
Missouri
Beetle Bailey
Need to know now I worry that it's
Open taken down I don't know it was
You apologize
Statue as much as it was
Like a seated table
I was like Beetle Bailey was sitting there having a beer
Take picture
Where the statue don't have a lot to be proud of the University of Missouri
We had we had like we had
Who won president
Who went there
Drop the nuke
Is our mascot at truman the Tiger
That is a great way to memorialize the president
So that's great will take me to
Brings us to the end of my exploration of the protocols of the Elders of Zion I hope you
I have enjoyed
Scared
And hopefully you're not hopeless
And I hope that you understand my
I'm not sure I'm never able to tell if I made my point
I hope
But I have
I don't know
Yeah Alex Jones is repurposing
Anti-semitism
In order to build up his case
The globalist
And that's what
Behind
I mean even the Nuvo alt-lite people like
Even Jack
Sobia Khan
Alright no out light
I refuse
Refused by
Leaving the People Like Mike cernovich
Injector sobiech they still rely on sightings the globalist
Some stuff like that which means spiritually they are linked
The same mythology that I would
And has been espousing
4 years
And it is
Repackaged
Buganda
From 1900s
3 Rush
They put it in the microwave and f*** this all with
Absolutely
Thank you
Good flashlight
Is that how that works put it in a microwave
If you'd like
To go check out our website
I don't have anything else to say do I know you did it you did it you accomplished what you set out to do
You came I didn't I'd said my
I hope that I think you've laid out your case pretty pretty clearly
I didn't like the format of this we won't do any more reading episodes little detour
I am jazz
If you listen to all the way to the end of this
Just so you know
We're going to
Wow
This is essential
More
Morales
Or the regular episodes
Twitter is at knowledge
Underscore
Notice so many of you are
New listeners all the time like this is this is amazing we love you guys
So much for listening
If you want to donate to the show you can do so
The website knowledge right.com
Support the show button
I can become
Merch soon
Library ideas around
Boc podcast me and Marty DeRosa do you can access
If you donate to
To the show
Submit ideas for
Email us at knowledge
Gmail.com
Policy wonk branded sword
Are there foam sword
Yeah we should
Honestly think
Except
You dress up like either weird
No great idea
Put the money up for these foam swords ahead of time you got to buy your own foam swords
Yeah
Play well do something
Catch you next time
But there's one thing that
Weighs heavy on my heart
Is it assholes
The dinosaur got a big old greybeard
I hope you don't say
Because that would be
Believe
Oh that's a very
Protocols of the Elders of
Alex Jones pictures
What's
Jon rappoport can go f*** himself
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work