Damn important
I have great respect for this knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
A little bit about Alex
Do
Jordan
I don't know how to put it other than
Dreamy creamy
The dreamy creamy era has begun
You shouldn't have shown me your weakness
You showed weed here's the problem I saw you grab that file directly and put it
Back in and I was like I know what that is I know what that is
And then immediately when I saw that I knew what your Brightside was going to be and I'm furious with myself
Because this is going to happen forever now in some way or another it probably is
It's always going to be a bright spot but you you
Don't reveal I know ends of soft spots
Especially not whatever they can be applied to a year of something
Food items apparently
What is an era
Zaramay just Westies to episodes
Could be forever
Well I mean I have a hard time thinking that you can't find a way to use dreepy creepy right before your mustard
Not almost her decree me my friend. That's why it's not an all-the-time thing
Maybe somebody's
Arrowhead like a creamy mustard that much
About it I don't most mustard
Thing
Why is Amanda screaming XO
Trump mayonnaise
Okay I got a reverse around it's not you
So scary
Have to start with basic start over
So creepy extreme
What's the right spot
Vibrate spot dad is
By my partner's mom
Her birthday
Was yesterday so
Okay
Spy we celebrate
Continue do that later Scottish accent
Scottish people got in an accident
They Scott
Indian accent ok
We had a lovely dinner it was like a
Wine and food pairing thing
And it was it was fantastic
The food is very good
The wind was in
Incredibly
Incredibly strong
I mean, yay
Which
Guess it's a job
And he was like this
This
Photo
How much is like 18 to 20% okay
Yeah that's what is worrying like
What you mean like the last one was like a port
Is that the skipper wine
I'm revealing myself not to be a smelly ass
They're all just
There's Apple wines that like Boone's Farm
A good man I wanted 18% Boone's Farm
It was difficult not to be for adult people walking out of there that place drunk
Purely unintentional
I went in there
Have a good time and they're like this
When is going to f*** you up
I went to a wine tasting in like Sonoma Valley with my parents one time when we were on vacation
California
And yeah I
I didn't get the memo that you're not supposed to drink
Alwine wish around
Mistakes I'm pretty drunk
I'm sure you did too absolutely
Today we have an episode to go over we were guarding this Advanced as you are on your honeymoon and gave him
Right now
Cross the border oh my God
Dude I think that Canada is going to come up on this episode
I'm a witch
What about July 28th
It was Monday episode in 2003
There's some stupidity there's some
Really really really funny
Stuff though I believe that one of Alex's most
Misfired interviews
I think I've ever heard okay so awesome let's hear it I'm excited to play it for you
We must say hello.
Firstmark
You can have a main character moment thank you so much and I'll probably walk
Twist your novelty walk
Monica from Australia thank you so much
Play the inflamed song episode 666 from their classic 1997
Oracle
Brother se600
66 episode and if you guys don't do what I swear I will donate to vulgarity for charity so Tom can make Jordan cry
Thank you so much you are not about to walk
Thank you very much too
30% of that at least
Got this a little bit late
We are now a pastor 666 episode
What do you do to say hello and thank you to a technocrat
I have
Risen above
Miami
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I mean
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Back here again
Apologized
To the crew in the Lester's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
He's a little better in the past
More palatable kind of
Shocking to be preparing a past and present episode at the same time as I did with this nrr episode
Weather for Monday
Google leeringly different
Mentality
I'm not sad
Them
Obviously the same person and obviously he sucks in his a bigger than past 2
View level to which he has
Falling apart is its
Yeah and I wouldn't laugh if he wasn't such a
Complete dick
In July
Up 2003 there's something interesting that's going on in that is
Public conversation
Starting to happen around the release
Of the 9/11
Report
And
Alex has some thoughts about this
The fact
There are 28 Pages missing dolls at 28 Pages missing
The 28 redacted Pages all of those 28 pages that definitely didn't have anything to do with Saudi Arabia
Probably one of the most surprising perspectives on this I go to the match
Thorn
I'm going on all over the place
On the Sunday news shows yesterday
Pretty shocking position for Alex to have about this
Like at this point in July 2003 the report of the House and Senate joint inquiry into the events of 9/11 was being released
And a lot of people were a bit suspicious
She said there were 28 Pages completely redacted
Normally for a conspiracy theorist this thing
I like that something like this would be so exciting but weirdly
Alex seems to not be interested in the redacted pages
Things not to care what they might have in them or might reveal
Is Clement what should have happened
So what's in those rejected pages are does not going to help his story
It has to be presented as Ironclad and that's what's going on he's not curious or interested at all because
It's already sat
There can't be any room for doubt
Because his whole narrative is held together with chewing gum and
Scotch tape
It's flimsy as hell
How much does so little evidence of anything that he has to insist that he actually has all the oven
Seminole
28 secret pages
Lead to questions about how they stack up with his supposed
In that sense I was angle here is really smart
He can't be intrigued by the 28 Pages because he has to already know what's in
Whatever has been redacted has to conform to his existing narrative in the parts
Elaborate cover-up
Better being covered up within the already cover-up 911 before covered up this is
Admission of guilt is part of the cover-up
Covering up that you didn't admit guilt right
It was long believed that the 28 pages
Isabel details about possible Saudi Arabian involvement with the hijackers so
That was bringing that up isn't super surprising at all in this timeframe
And giving the actual documents wouldn't be
Declassified for like another
13 years
You got pretty safe ground to make up whatever he wants about this
Besuited purposes
That is great contents of those 28 pages but it doesn't really seem productive since Alex has no idea what's in them any
He thinks our cover-up anyway
It's kind of a daddy
Eventually Ron Paul starts
Make them a big deal like that
Declassify those pages so I would imagine that around that time I was just doing will change
But for now this is where we are he's just like I don't give a s***
Oh you're not going to explain to us what happened on 9/11
I'm able to explain some things what you want
These Pages were redacted is because Saudi Arabia made some
Threats
White-washed
We're going to list
U.s. Bank
Pretty hard to figure out what to
I think about this claim that Alex is making here
On the one hand I don't think he's basing this on anything real
14 News
But on the other hand
In 2016 Saudi Arabia did threaten to sell off approximately 750 billion dollars in Treasury
Securities and other Assets in the United States
This was in response to the discussion of a bill that the Senate would make the government of Saudi Arabia open
To being sued
For any possible involvement with 911
Basically 911 victims
Families could be able to
The suicide Arabia with the
Spell Passage
I don't believe that this necessarily
Completely copper bowl though because the reason that they threatened to sell these Assets in the United States
Was because if they were made vulnerable to lawsuits
Their Assets in the United States could be frozen
And one part just a decent play
Yeah I can't find evidence of this threat from Saudi Arabia regarding two pages redaction
And I do think that Alex is making
Stuff up but it's not the most outlandish thing that he could come up with to make up
One of the reasons I'm particularly wary of Alex's story is because the 28 pages that were redacted didn't have to do
Who is Saudi Banks
Tipped off to something like that if it wasn't in the report
Is a little bit off
Thematically it feels a little like
Detail that fits neatly into Alex's
2003 conception of the globalist is primarily being involved in the banks of the world
Supposed to be demons trying to drink children's blood to make it so Alex camping
Explore space
Another reason I'm a bit I'm convinced
Is that in the redacted Pages there are indications
The connections between 9/11 hijackers and people connect
To the Saudi Arabian government
But definitive conclusions aren't
Made
The recommendation is for investigation saying that these connections
Split quotes
On the other hand
It's also possible that further investigation of these allegations could reveal legitimate and
Innocent explanations
For these associations
So I don't
Really think
I don't know I don't like this story doesn't
Jibe
Some kind of
Source I need
I don't
I think he's going to
Alright so
Alex has some news
Celebrity news
We got it
July 23rd
Well I know 28 I know it's not Betty White
True
I know it
It's not Dame Judi Dench
True
Beyond that anybody
Asparagus
Biggest movie
No idea
But he's been in a lot of them
Probably
You know what I'm going to go with Sidney Poitier then
No I would definitely know I Look Who's Coming to Dinner
Okay fine okay
I know less about this person from Sidney Poitier apparently
Oh yeah
Okay yeah Ike's
I like Alex's eulogy
Be nice if this guy wasn't a murdering monster who should burn it out
Probably be in heaven but rest time if you hadn't had sex one time before
We got married but now you're in the hell is that
So
Alex
Ends up dealing with this a bit
B b
The idea that all the news
Is like
Covering Bob Hope's death
They won't talk about him being a Satan worshiper is a problem for Alex
Then you also in the
Announce his one of his gas
And if this is so awesome
Emergency
One of the quarantine Center
Bob Hope
100 years old
I know that my grandmother
A grandmother
I had been involved in some of the revelry there according to the
Acquiring
But I wonder why
Today wall-to-wall all over the news
It isn't mister
The mister
Was that
Angela wasn't in the
The obituary because it's not true
Mangrove is probably
On the scale of things that are important about Bob Hope
Reloj cuello
Qalo
What was Bob Hope's biggest movie
Road trip
Not so funny that I couldn't anymore now that I know it's an Oscar
No I do not okay I don't think so I don't think Baba one of those maybe probably
I know he won the Grammy
So yeah Bob Hope
In his obituaries that he worshipped
Moloch big swing for an obituary
Throw that a man dominated American culture
50 years went on a billion Uso troops
But everybody know who's been like a sex slave
Yep
But yeah also
Bohemian Grove Alex has a guy who's involved with the relocation Center building
Coming on
This is one of my favorite interviews of all time
It's delicious person is the way he describes this person seems like
They are going to be a calm
Knowledgeable
I mean
I'm going to throw this out there
Helpful person
Trying to help Alex understand what it is they're going to do I am going to give you
No
Okay
So Alex is little
Piece of trivia
The shock of shocks
Is not true
America
Why
I can do whatever he wants
War
That's not true
So Alex is misunderstanding or misrepresenting the part of Article 2 Section 2 Clause one of the cots
Institution that has to do with this kind of stuff
The president shall be commander-in-chief of the Army and Navy of the United States
And of the militia of the several States when called into the actual service of the United
Be when called into the actual service part has to do with the militia only
But I was just pretending it applies to every
Again man we're really going to have to get into like
Scanning app
Try and say the word subjunctive Clause have a real struggle. Absolutely
So Alex gets to some predict
No I mean every time we listen to show he says he's right about
I also
How old
Media lights
Tell me that Putin
Is right and a good guy and always telling the truth it's fascinating cuz Alex is Right 97% of the time
He's wrong twice
Huron's that Saddam is in Belarus with his son's not there she's also wrong that you're going to find a dead body
You got
Found where you live you can go inside of a little hole Yeah
Location their one-year
I don't know if that's import Ace
Alec
Books has an interesting perspective on the story about Bush signing the flag
Yes you actually fine with it
Well I mean you would have
Because later on his his dude
So
But he doesn't know that in 2003
I do actually kind of want to tip my cap a little bit into the prospective
Getting mad about your signing with like I don't like it
But it's fine
The flag symbolizes the freedom to sign the flag
I appreciate that conception Leon Alex
Basic burn the flag is party
The flag kind of thought yeah yeah
Clip and surprisingly
I don't think Alex likes Matt drudge in 2003
Photographer
The red herring
Blood and soil here
Patriotism
Blue blood
And everyone
New world
It's okay
That really surprised me
Drudge is a new world order priests back then
Yeah wow
I don't know exactly what I mean I guess probably was a little bit more mainstream conservative
And it was very jingoistic
Yeah
I mean I wasn't keeping track of the Drudge Report
Oh yeah I could say I could see it hasn't it been
Of supporting the war and such
Yeah but it is it is really into the garage become such an important
Piece of Alex's career to
A stretch that guy is a new world order
Is representative a conditional everything is a new world order
Eventually becomes the most important person
In all of conservative media because he's
I've been there and expose the Clinton
Windows
Before he became a new world order fries
A man eventually maybe he sold the Drudge Report to Global listsource
Then became a globalist
Is cool for a while again
It will rewrite your narrative tomorrow
Infowars
Because you know like
It is it's like a long-running show where former and it's like a long-running soap opera
Season 6 + 12
This guy was the biggest enemy number one try
It season 7 he turns out to be a good guy and then they work together within the season 11
Beat it turns dude B you know it's a difference between
There's a narrative
Arc with
Shows
Explanation
For what made Matt drudge go from
Hero of the Patriot movement
Yeah it's just arbitrary it's like if you're watching a show that is long run
But also like
Haphazardly just changes people's alignment
It's over and over again
That's the problem
That is one hundred percent because
My feeling is
If we go back into the past
And dredges an enemy that
I need to know why of what happened what's the reason that you know what it is what's the backstory
No and we don't get
You know it's more like the cloud at
It is a lot like the title and it's like
Tom Hanks
He's friends with Halle Berry or whatever in another time
But now he's mad at Halle Berry
This is disorienting
Movie One Day
Shows like the cloud
Also as racially problematic
Wikipedia
Here is the clip where I
To be a witness part 2 from Monday
New World Order
Okay
Orlando
George Orwell
What
Am I
Yes
He does the sort of same breath
About Animal Farm
Same reference weird because isn't something that he does on every episode
Preparing so weird
I'm so weird now very bizarre sick of being in a simulation
Buda break me free as I do also like though the
Be weird defensiveness
Like first of all the New York Times isn't watching your show that closely in 2003 or even now I would argue
Second
Do the people we're going to send you emails or your listeners who haven't read Animal Farm
Do you think the people are going to suddenly like
Walk by the radio go to legs
Is good for legs
This Alex Jones guy is talking gibberish
Ago
It was just as annoying when people made Animal Farm references
And we've done it twice in a week so I apologize
Anyway Alex has talked a bit
About the flag issue
But also has some thoughts about people who cover the flag issue
But
That's not true
Do you think it's true
You were willing to accept that that's true I mean I didn't know that it said that all of them were adamant
The part where he said the bigger problem is that they're made enslaved
So this is a good example of how flawed Alex's information-gathering techniques are
I assume his little study that he conducted himself was like skimming and mistreating a headline or possibly just seeing one flag that said made
And then jumping to the conclusion that almost all the United States flag
Are made in China
Warning
20 are made in the United States
95%
Made somewhere
Sanka
In reality according to the flag manufacturers Association of America 94% of all United States flags are
Manufactured in America
Most of the imported wants do come from China but it's a really small percentage compared to the ones that are domestic
We produced
Any flag that is imported has to be clearly visible Declaration of where it was made
And if you find a flag that doesn't
Show that it was made in America or have you country of origin declaration
You're supposed to contact the Federal Trade Commission
Because that is a bootleg flash holyshit I did not know that they are
Oh there I can't imagine it's huge but
But there is a flag manufacturers Association of America I don't like people getting it on there too
So there's a good illustration of Alex's information
InStyle
It feels like all the flags are made in China this kind of a poetic
The resonance to that idea that fits those narratives about the world
Reflect reality
One possibility for how Alex could get this impression is that every now and again usually around the 4th of July someone'll run ahead
Redline like the one that was posted in The Hobbit
Post
From 2013
Quotes
94% of American flags imported to the United States last year came from China
Is true but it's misleading
94% the flag that were imported came from China but they were still only like 5% of the total number of flight manual
Fractured
They like the rest of them were made domestically
If you read the second paragraph of that very article with that headline
It says quote
American manufacturers still make up the bulk of the business
Fret
Alex doesn't repass headlines investors has a surface-level grass but most of the stories
AC covers
What kind of important
For him but it becomes a big problem when these flawed interpretations of stories are passed along to his audiences some kind of gospel truth
Just using this example if you believe Alex and you think that 95% of flags in our country are imported Wendy
Exact opposite
That is true
What I'm getting at is that he's an unreliable source of information because he doesn't have good methods to take his information
Right whatever is coming into him
Is going through a terrible filter
Before he comes to you the right
Unreliable you can't trust it if he's right it's an axe
Yeah
Yeah this seems like a situation where
It is not just him
At fault
Call headline could be well much better Ripley don't know if he's operate
Getting all the headline like that
That it that huffpo article is a good example of why it is very
Easy to immediately be taken in by somebody saying 95% of those
Because that is the type of Click baby headline you would write
And that's why they write that
It's true
It is true
But it's cooked baby bulshit
And that makes me change what I think might
Be true based on what's going
It's tough to know if like
That's
Wrong
Headlight
Strictly speaking if you do
Read the words
In the sentence
It doesn't give the wrong impression it's at flags that are imported
Made in China
Fine
Fair enough
Because the number so high cuz I would probably
It is
Spiritually
Not going to do the job that you wanted to do
If your job if you're telling me this information 94% of American flags
I would need the contacts to make a decision about what to do with that
I forgot
Contacts is just like
Holyshit China's got all of our flag
You know they make everything even our patriotism article the second paragraph
American still make up the bulk of
95 ft
15%
Look at some of the numbers that are included in their terms of like
Bulk sales
Like 95%
My way through to the other side
Nope that is a bad headline that's not good
Call Anthony
Brings up
Little politician
That becomes
Fairly important
For Alex for short. Of time before he decided no no I'm going to get away from this
Albert has no idea who he is
I appreciate
A lot of the things about how the media overlies
I also wanted to point out
Story
Overlook
Which is the
Judge Roy Moore in Alabama
Been fighting a federal
You think mammoth from Alabama Supreme Court House
A room from 11
District Court
Quad lock
Tactically remove app
Against
The state of Alabama
This week
Have no idea about Roy Moore at this point
What's
Isn't too surprising cuz this is where he comes into a national prominence
Whatever way he didn't write
Bleeding at this point
Until
More recent history
This is also along with the California recall race
The whole
Chaos around Roy Moore trying to do the oil at 10 commitment thing
I think I'm going to be another long running
Storyline on Alex's show me more showing up on
I don't know if possible I don't like that
He was still around twenty years ago and people let him come
Continue on to get into
My life like
You guys listen
Everybody in the past
You knew that it was coming
And now you left it to me to deal with and that's on you
Now you left a mess
Absolutely get your s*** together the past
Alright so
You can come down on the pass all you want anything
But one of the things the past
Is giving us is this interview that I was going to do
So this guy
And he runs an organization called Dallas
And Alex has given him a
Little bit of an introduction
And I we are joined by.
Add of the
Basically use the hot wire
The
The Earth
It's true that the Dallas was the father of Icarus but
That's not his
Top credit I mean
I think if I could
He built the Labyrinth
Working my nose is probably a little higher on the list of reasons name your Construction Company after him
I might have forgot to mention this
How was interviewing the guy who runs like
Construction cover
Are there are there into fabrication
Easily one of the
Cheap pretty construction Folk
Of the ancient Greek
I miss you wouldn't call them have fastest but you wouldn't
Shake a stick at it if he was compared to him
You know like a Smith
Creative things for sure but
In terms of building
But you're doing more with it
Elaborate
Classic
I'm at Minotaur
At Minotaur
He and I he inherited he's never got along well
Took me forever to beat the Minotaur AC Odyssey
Annoying fight
Batman the Animated Series
So the Ed
I was asked him a little bit about what your company all about
Building in Pittsburgh
Thanks
Important Point here
Daedalus was
Materials
Who created
Extremely low-cost house
Turns out
An RV
Probably few materials
Available
That
Structural integrity
Projected low
Longevity
Materials
We had no
In the US
Simply Red
Recognized
You want to borrow some
The requirement existed
To have a
Low cost
That could put up
Facility
Twenty-four to Forty-Eight Hours
Within 48 to
Who wants to have
Ben interview about the
The conspiracy element
Of these centers
I have he has got a guy on
Who's in the construction
Oceanside
Right yeah if I'm
If I'm Alex right here
I heard that answer and I went
This is been great talk
Talking to you goodnight
Makes a few f
Amy tries a little bit early unfortunately in the framing of his questions he also reveals that he doesn't actually know any
Anything about
The subject he's talking
News articles
Incorrect
Well
I'm not sure if that's correct
Dr. I don't
Don't know of any
Contract
For this particular
Turns out this
Particular facility
Is under a government
Through
Allegheny
Perhaps leading
Groups
Bald in
Civil prepare
Disaster
We're not looking for any contract is already a contract we're just doing this in Pittsburgh
I cannot
Be more on board with
People who
Clearly have no idea what they're
Supposed to be doing with each other
Like
Just no idea that he's he's like I'm giving you information about
Buildings that why you would interview me yeah the only reason you would talk to me is if you wanted to know about building
I have a company and I'm sincerely excited about this new application of this
This building material that we have developed
And I'm thrilled that you'd give me a national platform to talk about
How and the other applications of building housing in the developing world this is so excited excited for me
Tell us a Batman
Now
Ever everyone
We provide that level of
Well I think
Inaccurate
Notion here
These facilities
Observation
Bye Felicia
Location for corn
It would presumably have
Three different kinds of
Believe the Browns
Don't really know
Ferdinand
Features of a
Building side effects
Such a fire
What we do here
Nope
Well
We are a construction company
Thank you very much
A f****** misfire
What could you possibly thought was going to happen from
I don't know
What and what world
Do you think that you're going to get it engineering
Construction guy to come in and be like yeah
So this all this really cool stuff that I'm really interested in I love building I love building materials
I love what I'm doing
Also we're out in the developing world there's really cool places I could be right now but right here
I'm doing
I'm craving trapdoors
If you try and Escape
Dabble
I can't believe nobody even asked me if it was a trap door to hell in here 2003
S*** right here
Where is the Pearson Elementary this that is I think
Maybe it's a Longshot kind of interview they can something happen that
The other end
Recognizes that like there's nothing going to happen
Ain't so he bails you can tell with the interview ends
Much more quickly than it would have if something interesting was happening course and so he comes back
Why say I'm sorry before the interview ends
You can see him give up in the in the actual interview
Wow wow
In 48 hours
Power and Water
Different services in in
That is correct and
In the case of
Provider
That's really
Maryland
I was interviewing the guy about how you'll make a building
Alright so when you bring you take the stuff out of the truck so that you put it together
Plumbing in there in 48 hours actually one of them
More informational claim could be doing but it's so disappointing for Alex
Interested
So Alex interview and then he tries to save face when he comes back from break by protest
Sending that that was what he was
A bookworm
Weather
Good say
I just finished the interview with any kind of weird are you still listening
He said what
I just wanted you to know whenever they take you into these camps there will be air conditioning
Call Mia
Bookworm
I just wanted you to know that whatever it will be made with some
Very Innovative materials
That are being used to create housing in the developing world lesbireal
These are going to be really trustworthy buildings that you are going to be murdered in good luck getting out
So Alex just calls cuz that's much more fertile territory for him
Believe
The topic of a Jewish Mafia
Play Bloomberg is a little bit new on the scene wants to know if he's part of the Jewish Mafia
Question
Bloomberg
Doesn't sound right part of the Jewish
Start develop their Bloomberg or is that
That's another nationality
How dare you
N36
Bugsy Siegel
If you
Jewish Mafia
Stop
Where that what were golden
Not really
Took a little bit of a nosedive
When are people going to realize where that. Is most power
I would have been right there right there where the. Is powerful
Alex's expressing that there is a Jewish Mafia and
If you criticize them badl
Which
Implies that they're sort of like a
Protection with Jewish Mafia
Hello
Starts to get a little bit mad
About this
Weather report
Weather in Bloomsburg
New World Order
Norwegian
Criticized
So there's an interesting and very deeply racist lack of understanding that Alex has about the things he's saying and I think I can
Look up simply like this
It's totally fine to criticize Bloomberg even though he's Jewish
Unless your criticism of Bloomberg is just a vague unsubstantiated playing but he's part of some mysterious Jewish Mafia
If your criticism with him relies on him being Jewish to make sense
Then your criticism is antisymmetric if your criticism
Policies in general probably not
And you can see this refusal to see non-white people as individuals at the end they can see that very clearly
I want to sing any sports being critical of all Chinese Americans working military bases because of the fear that some of them might be
Despise
It's about that that's not a logical train of thought unless your race
Since Chinese spies exist
People should be seen with some suspicion
They possibly could be one of those spies
It's important to recognize how this mentality in line of thought feeds directly into exactly the same motivation to let our country to enter
Japanese Americans during World War
That was a shameful act in our country's history
His mind hasn't learned the most Elementary lesson that you should learn from it because deep down
He probably thinks it made sense
2in turn all the Japanese people
Right
Now here's ears one of the big flaws with with
Racism
Racist
And their thoughts on Spotify
So funshine
And I want to get some spies going
United States
Here's my thought
Alright
United States is racist
F***
Let's get some white folk to do it
Boom.
Beyond
Interesting Espionage tactic
It also has another guest
Might be a little bit more fruitful than the other guys but he's also named
And
Quite exciting
That is exciting
For what it's worth there's pretty regular conversations about secession in part 2
Does Canada has anything to do with guns
It's hard to say how much of what Alex has things based on
Kingstree pieces of information
Doctor at Hudson is a really fun fella
He's on a crusade to challenge Canada's Firearms Act in a wonderfully quixotic fat
I'll January 21st 2003
Stage Nevada outside to Saskatoon police station
Where he was in
Clearview of uniform police
I sold an unregistered rifle receiver to an associate of his
Name Joe Gingrich
The Hope was that he could get arrested on a gun sales charge would you get that appeal up to the Canadians
Supreme Court in that wood
Be his ticket to getting Firearms Act overturned
However
He didn't get arrested on gun charges
An officer asked him to surrender the gun part and you refused we got charged with obstructing a police officer
That wouldn't be an Avenue for a challenge of Firearms Act and also the charges were dropped
Back where you started
This was all part of a comedy of errors where Hudson was trying to get himself arrested for a Firearms Act related offense but it just wasn't
The point where he was considering filing charges against himself so where is strayed into Wylie Coyote
Territory trying to
To take down this is like if Wylie Coyote was trying to take down the Second Amendment
I think it's worse because
I think that there's an aspect of this behavior that like really undercuts
It's like all these gun laws are so oppressive
You can't get arrested trying to
What you talkin about
Eventually on October 28th October 20th 2003 he would successfully have a firearm
MCS but
You wasn't charged under the Firearms Act just under the criminal code
Hudson try to make this work any attempted to raise constitutional challenges but they all failed
At which point he asked the court to charge him with a crime he could use all my God
Dude
He also runs a group that Alex reference called the Canadian unlicensed Firearms Owners Association that I would assume that
Any self-respecting Gunn weirdo militia type would see that name in in immediately assume it's either run by an idiot or it's a
Honeypot Canadian
Yes that sounds like a good idea
Wild
Yeah so he comes on
And Alex's real pumped about how like
Man
Overturn these gun laws in Canada
You and me buddy
20 years later
Going to happen
We've been saying
Is there anywhere in the world
Controlling
Are you out understand
Is completely open our membership list
Anyone who
Remember
Knows the dog that their name address telephone
Phone number is going to be
Completely
If our membership
No one joins
That they're going to be
Completely open
Sounds that sounds like gun registration almost
Please pitch saying if you aren't license
If you want register to own a gun
And you have a gun sign up on this list so the government will know you have a gun
Brightwell
Yeah it's at least kind of sex
Going to make it easy for
Government know where these unregistered guns are
You know it is almost like
If people were aware that way we when they were signing up to this website
That if they've been committed a crime with a gun that they would know that the
Gun was unregistered
You could have just register
This is counterproductive and dumped its
So we get into the secession stuff
Alex's Intuit
Turns out this guy
The comedian
Guy
Isn't really that into a panda
Talk about
We can have a new freak
Alberta
Beyond my scope and
Expertise but I've certainly been
Done
Gun shows in Alberta
Talkin about the Alberta
Alberta separating
I am not
Peaceful
Very unjust law here
Really weird way you phrase that
That is next to some people
People
It's not my bailiwick what's up
Elucidated with a man trying to get rid of it'll be real though
Important
Superman and cool outside of coincident but the Maverick
His party was deeply involved in the roots of the protest
Kind of see
There's all kinds of
Differing
Ideas about
Some secession ideas in Canada whether it be
From First Nations
Folk or or from
Weirdos
Who want a gun
You know a right-wing Utopia
But it is it is interesting that the fingerprints Kiara of secession arguments
And in the present are both at the Alberta separate
This group really putting together a good case
Animal throw this out at you okay so like
And here's what I
If you don't want problems
To be worse 20 years later
You should take care of problems
In the Press
It's it is truth it
Leaving things
Doesn't usually take care of it I'm really starting to think you might be able to ignore them a little bit if you ignore
Right right
Can load easily be worse
Piece of news for unregistered Gun Owners Association owner is it the cops are
They're all on its own
Where are you
AutoZone RC
I would say up to 7
The numbers game
Download number like 70%
Police officer
Exactly
Most police shows in a lot of movies are set in New York
So I understand if you base your worldview on movies and pop culture
Chris getting killed all the
In reality Texas has the highest number of police killed per year pretty regularly
In 2016 they were number one with 18 police killed in the state in the line of duty with the next highest aping California
With 11
Hammond Louisiana with nine
The entire state of New York had four officers killed in the line of duty
That year
When you adjust for population New York isn't even anywhere near the top of the list
A 2016 study conducted by researchers at Harvard found that in reality the likelihood of a cop being killed in the line of duty with
Was 3 times higher in States
Ownership
Compare two states
With low rates
Yep
Alex fuel
Like officer deaths in the line of duty must be lower in States
More guns because he wants that to be the truth
Because he wanted to be true he feels like it is
And therefore it is true
This work is repeated over and over to his audience and I accepted his true despite
Clear evidence that it's just based on Alex's feelings
Also by far the leading cause of death among police and 1st years has been covid
And we seen how seriously Alex is dealt with
How much you care
So go f*** yourself
It's true
But I don't think that he cares about the underlying issue as much as he does just wants a lot of
So
This guy just had some fella
He also said something that I would should probably
Take issue with
But
But you're crying
I would like to take the opportunity
But as you said in your
Introduction
The people of the United
Need to wake up
The forces that are in play
Here in Canada
Take over
International
Sing about
Left-leaning
People who
Conspiracy
I'm pretending to be above the left-right paradigm
It's an international
So that's the that's the end of their interview
I am.
I mean
2022 in this guy's not overturn Canada's gun laws
Resolve
You still working I'm sure he's got time
Here's just a nice clip of Alex enjoying his life in a way that he probably can't anymore
Or raining
Yeah man
Takes me back to the blunt around
That is that is the other side of not having a boss
Site that we live in now is
Is the bad side where
You nobody is stopping you from being of weird monster screaming about demons right
Consequences that are probably things that bosses would have
Curbed
Yeah or fired
But this
This is the good side this is the s*** where it's like f*** it I'm I'm
Listening to music right now
Who's going to stop me oh it's a new show
I'm the news and the news is what music I want to listen
Smeagol never bad driver ahead
Alex goes back to calls
And this fellow believes that the Amber Alert system is a conspiracy so that's fun
Stories on TV that
They were following us
Unless they knew what was going to happen
But yet when you see
The same thing
We weren't there we didn't get to cover that
All the details were all there when they started to introduce the Amber Alert
You know whatever happened
I'm sorry
Remote control
Little general
Nature of the ignorance
They want to introduce this and go look
German
I wish they could have got
To the people who perpetrated 911 dispatch
They did to the mall Bo Peep
Two Scholars decided that the Amber Alert system is a conspiracy and he's doing a spectacular job of explaining his position
I don't know
Nobody's talking
They couldn't have done it if he hadn't already known that if they've done
I guess all these kidnappings or whatever are false Flags
That is I am and his desire for the 9/11 hijackers to have been caught as quickly as
Lee Boyd Malvo
Who was one of the d.c. snipers
He and John Allen Muhammad we're on a shooting spree that lasted from February 2nd 2002 until
October 24th
That's a full nine months that they were at Large
22 days of that involved sniping in d.c.
A long time
Example I would have chosen for like a speedy
You know the rest like you do it and then like an hour later you get
You should have chosen one of those crime
Sure maybe almost any crime
Particularly like a violent crime large-scale I think
Probably mean if an if the case gets solved at all
A lot of time is quicker than 9 months
You wouldn't
I wouldn't use it I also don't think that it was much more than like a time of
D.c. sniper
It went on like I don't think that timeframe is much shorter
Turn the. Of time
From when Bush got the memo
That wasn't that much more than like a month
For that was in August
Yeah so like
I don't I don't I don't I don't use of me mostly because that's your choice of
Yeah I notoriously long
Terrorizing thing that happened
Yeah
5 of a YouTuber
Like it now like a YouTuber
Random Jose compounds allowed on YouTube
Christmas music
Thoughts
This really really funny
Whirlpool
The group
Galaxy it's not know that the Willie Nelson
Toby Keith and really
Whiskey
Is Uganda
When the Gunsmoke settles Hill singer
The local Saloon
We'll raise up our class is okay
Who is skateball Bombay
Call Sara dolls
Willie Nelson hasn't lied about get all the rope in Texas find a tall oak tree and hang up all of them bad boys
Is for the people to
I think that Alex is responding that I don't know if that song includes put everybody
I think the I think the funniest part is that
Is closer to the song that Sacha Baron Cohen
Making fun of people
Yeah I don't know if Alex is conflating this to with like Toby Keith Courtesy of the Red White and Blue
Maybe but that doesn't throw this out there as far as music knowledge goes
Jingoistic country music
Not on my list
You don't know courtesy the red light and I don't know any
Put a boot in your ass it's the America
Nothing
Hey Uncle Sam put your name at the top of his list
The Statue of Liberty
Beheld
When you hear Mother Freedom started ringing
The whole world is coming down on you
Courtesy
People I do and I just don't think they should be allowed near music
And I think that's been borne out by all of human history
Look I grew up in Central Missouri Fairmount Toby Keith and Fairmount
I would be wrong if I didn't say that
The great-great glasses
Toby Keith Willie Nelson and Willie Nelson
That seems weird should have recognized his voice
He's kind of a big deal
Generational
Passing of the torch
Not really
But Alex has not gone to
What time does Fizz news
We're coming up to the end of the show
And he realizes that
Water hose
Murder
Call Brenda
He could do a lot of things
He's not doing any of those things
I mean he couldn't talk for hours about the David Kelly thing
Because he's doesn't really know anything
Ramble about stuff may be true
Saudi Arabia stuff you already talked about the beginning of the show very briefly and dismissed out-of-hand I don't know he could talk about
But that 4 hours
Maybe you could
Not about drama
Grow weary of
Like
I could have done this
You could and you can
You got to show
No one telling you anything
What did you do instead
You wish
The f****** interview with
Thinking it was going to be awesome Utah
Just trying to get all the unregistered gun owners to sign up for his organization
Create a list of unregistered gun owners and it wasn't even an international conspiracy
God
Brutal
Yeah it's just
If you could you should and you got it because what you doing
So we are one last episode of Alex's is trademark
Headline rap-up
At the end of the show
Hugo zygos over
Some of the movie talk about some of them
Someone who doesn't have time to get to because
He's run out of time
Another article review
British police they now found out
Got time for a plug
Article isn't about the police being in a secret society but Alex
It's that because he's just skimming headlines and he saw the word cabal
It's about allegations that there was a team called operation Rock
Jamwich cherry-pick reports to emphasize
The argument that Saddam was not in compliance with proliferation rules
This is a UK group
These allegations were made by a former un weapons inspectors from the United States named Scott Ritter but this isn't proven claim
Heather's been actually many objects
Do it
Like Rockingham does exist but the claim that their purpose was to
Cherry-pick Intel that's not a stab
It hardly matters though cuz I haven't read this story has no idea what he's talking about and even if you did have time to get into
Show me scams the headline sees the word cabal insights
Completely made up story that the news is reporting
Secret society
In the British
Force
Again I'm a broken record I understand that but
This is accepted
Alex
He's fine reporting
Completely fabricated stories care
It is
Never
Not
Astonishing
That a man could just
Read a headline and then be like
And in the UK they've discovered that there is a cult of
Cops out there Coptic getting married in all this just doing this whole thing and it's like no
You just decided these words are a scam DeMatha
It's like a creative writing prompt and he gets one every time he looks at the paper and then he just wins a yard
And it's not
You know you know it intellectually you know it
But your entire life has trained you to believe that if somebody is standing at a desk
Looking into you reading off of the news
Something like something close
You ever read the world
You hoped you'd hope that I let Sandra and then the other thing that you project onto those people is that
They would feel bad
About getting things
He's completely wrong
And just making s*** up very least would be embarrassed or worried about consequences or anything
I hope that's not the case for him he just does not give a s*** to let it all hang out there
Yep get like the real essential point is
You have to understand
The way Alex
Filters information
From a source threw himself to the audience
Unreliable of a delivery mechanism this is
You can't trust what's coming out because
Sometimes
It might be a thing that he understands
It might be something he made up from skimming a headline
And you have no idea which is which
He report he sounds exactly the same no matter which
We talkin about how
Hey I believe that the first amendment allows for writing on an American flag
Thought about
Sounds exactly the same
Undercover secret society in British police horse
This headline would have nothing to do with that
Dangerous dangerous that kind of person to be
Disseminating information
Yep that's
That's my point
You got it
Is where you put a.
Oh that is where you are going to keep that. Buy bread
We works
And I think that
Obviously
You're so much more fun
I mean there's no world in
Anymore
You never in the present-day going to hear him
Taking a long shot on interviewing
Reconstruct never going to find stuff like that and endnote
You good also spoiler alert
Alex announce that he has
Facebook Charlie Daniels for a future show
Well then I guess we'll be in the past until the dam has not like Charlie
Whenever you're back from your vacation
We do acknowledge buy.com
But until then I'm Neo I'm Leon dcx Clark
Dreamy creamy
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color