Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
The altar of Celine talk a little bit
Alex Jones
India today buddy
To be back
In the saddle pleasure
B b b b b
Back
So here's the
Situation
You can't eat any more f****** muster
Well
Terrible news
In preparation for the year of the mustard
I ordered the number of mustard
Yes you did
I don't like mustard
Mustard mustard
The number is yellow mustard a little bit too boring and playing but it's right like them might like
I have like
Some of them that I got
Way to DeShawn
Calculation with fairy off
What's a good ice
Being bigger than your stomach is I think a feature not a bug
Good ones that I cried and now at the batting average is atrocious and I can't imagine doing it alright
So I'm calling off yeah yeah I think that's wise I think that's wise
There is big news we are replacing it
Your the mustard out the window
God but now you know what we're doing what are we doing
The dreamy creamy summer
Okay
Alright
Ice cream novelties
Ice cream Novelties doing it for the summer dreamy creamy creamy creamy summer
Just going to be
Dreamy creamy
It's going to be the best
That'd be great so starting on Ford 2600 till 9/11
420 2911 Coronavirus
11 more details about what this will entail on the next episode
Much easier to complete in a positive way for sure
Good mustards if you'd like
To send me a message I will
Certainly repay you
Or make you something that I don't know we'll do something for you because it's a very generous
If you feel short-changed by the year of the mustard please and not Our intention at all
I just hope we can transition that into
Enthusiasm about the dreamy creamy summer
Well I think ultimately you know
Wait
Game might be an issue for the dreamy creamy Summers
Think I'm going to have to try to make sure I don't
Go to far
Honestly
I don't think I eat all that healthy to begin with that is true that big
But we went at 8 here's what we do we do this like like the McDonald's
Is everyday for 30 days
You're going to need to go to a dentist regularly like
Once a week check-ups how much ice cream have you eaten this week
Six-in-ten drink
Fortnite you don't like that guy just go to a chiropractor who pretends to be a dentist
Chiropractor who pretends to be a doctor
And a dentist
Chiropractor
I think it's a good way to go
So
This is me Summer
Coming to you
My bright spot is my my little sister she is having her
Child
Bonjour and she just did the gender reveal
Yesterday certifier
Straight with a cupcake
Cakes with a color of icing okay
Oma bees inside of
If a cupcake ripe
Cupcake
But you don't think that's
Talk bad about you sister but
Acme
Just I think Safety First
Sure I mean just the institution of gender reveal party
Okay I mean I couldn't go because I was too busy slaving away in the podcast Factory
Yesterday yesterday
So are you but anyways it's a it's a boy
Congratulations
You're going to be an uncle
Yeah I'll be uncle twice over next
Already
Wife's uncle to Uncle
Addition
The next
How you like it
I would imagine
I have somebody who is and uncle and not a parrot
I can only speak from my experience
It seems like it's better than I've ever did
Witness work
Yeah let's responsibilities
I like him they're cute I see him once every
11:54
We are getting back
Check into some present day
You've been gone for a week
We kept podcast
Yes isn't it thank you to Amanda for I coming in and having a chat
I enjoyed that interview I'm sorry to miss
Happened while you were gone
Today we're going to be going over April 3rd
That's Wednesday to you say no
No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No don't we already have dreamy creamy you get to keep that one
I don't know this one back April 13th 2022 that's Wednesday
Well maybe it'll maybe it'll stick will see
This is it fun
It's not fun but it's an episode
The first sneaky sneaky little Breaky tomorrow's Turtles today thank you so much and I apologize
Horse you rode in on
Thank you very much standing up for that horse Millian play out
Patrick I'm not saying the Drowned God is Cthulhu but the Drowned God is Cthulhu
Stalled hungry so much right now if I was you
Chatham green
Say hello to
James Patterson the author
Answer the person requested to be on the 600
66 episode 9
Unfortunately mr. message sale
Episode all over again
Thank you Paul and Kentucky not that a****** ran that you are now a technocrat
I have
Risen above
Miami
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not he's not much better
I don't think that this was as
Toxic and episode is I've heard must her for Alex at this point
I mean it yeah I don't think I wanted to rage quit at any point
Okay
Bored at many points
For something outside of what
Possible so I think at Alex's position
Achievable goals such as not forcing you to rage
There might be a me like top
2% percentile
Contacts drop hear from Today Show
We ain't
Dying
Okay
Alright alright this is literally
We have chili on sale
You prefer a Baconator I get it
So we start off the episode and to Alex's covering
UB Subway shooting in New York
That is a kind of the big news
You got to take
Incredible story
Dr scrambling his
Trying to hide the facts of the New York City
Subway shooter was targeting
White
Because she believed I needed to die
Also wanted to kill black people
Married outside
Bloodline
Obviously completely mentally ill
This morning
Totally off base here but there is a couple of important
Distinctions that need to be made between what Alex is saying and what information is known
It is true that the alleged Subway shooter Frank James had a history of posting disturbing off and hateful
And violent videos on YouTube
You have a serious problem with New York's Public Health System particularly be mental health system having claimed that he was mistreated
The city facility
He also did have some just taste for white
But Alex is conveniently leaving out the racist yet he post about
Many other group
Including black
That being said it's pretty clear from his videos that he was strongly opposed to white people he was worried about a coming race war and was my
Mentally unwell
And he was mad at
Kentucky Brown jacks
Send because she's married to a white man
Alex is referring to their
However there are
These distinctions that are important
This is a very possible motivation for shooting and it may well turn out that's
McKay's but Alex doesn't know that when he
He's reporting this is option that Alex is making
And
Whether he was
Motivated by a racial hatred
It doesn't mean that he was trying to kill white people in the subway
It is there's a meaning to it although it's
Maybe slightly I could
The I understand I understand what you say
The second point is probably more important you can see that when there's a black shooter who appears to be motivated by hate
People ideology
They're making decisions
And they are actual
Compare this to the way that Alex covers countless white Mass Shooters like dylann roof or James Holmes
Clear distinction
When the shooters white there's a g
Conspiracy about how we was brainwashed
Basically just a blunt instrument being used by the globalist
Spotify shooter is not white it may be some kind of a conspiracy still they made
Maybe not well
Control over their racks
There's a reason that they're doing what they're doing
Yes it motivates our Acts
Supposed to like
They were
Jolyon West brainwashed him at an Air Force facility or whatever
Just ghetto
Sing out loud you can judge this person as bad
You cannot judge
The white person
Miss bad because they're at
Actions we're outside of their control
Exact
The 3.0 bring up is that Alex was just making up an idea that the media is covering up Frank James
Previous social media releases
On this very day of this episode April 13th
There was an article in the New York Times titled quote sucked suspect drifted from city-to-city as his videos hinted at violin
This Times article offers a more nuanced perspective on James videos and how he wasn't just someone who hated white people
The only thing that's important
Alex so that's how Infowars report
They compared to this from the time
Quotes
He seems to have been more Focus
Just on his YouTube account where the video is he post
Devolved into outburst
Homophobia misogyny
And offensive comments about people
Mr. James was black directed much of his hatred towards people who
Name for the way they were treated in the United States
The article goes on to say quote
He expressed admiration for black Trailblazers like Martin Luther King Jr President Barack Obama but Unleashed vitriol
What other black people including Dante right
Who was killed by a police officer in Minnesota last
Here and other young black men shot by the police
He blamed them for their own death saying you play stupid games Win stupid prizes
And adding that they deserve
To be shot yeah that's so
Turn from what Clarence Thomas
Believe or Alex
There was a big article about the videos and a social media Post in Rolling Stone and it's a story that was covered in countless other Outlet
The point here is that they're absolutely was no desperate cover-up of the subject matter and it's important to understand what Alex means what
He says that
Went out to Ledger the cover up what he saying is that other outlets don't at the same angle on the story that he doesn't anyone who's narrative is
Is different than Alex is covering something up
So when Alex says that there was a shooting there was entirely and centrally around a hater
White people
If you're a listener
And you encounter another Outlet.
Discussing the broader hatred and anger James's traffic again
You'll be far more likely to see that is the media trying to blur the real truth of the story
Alex is Reporting Act
It look they're trying to both sides it they're trying to make it look like oh this isn't just about how much
Much he hates white
People and by extension because as obviously we know
You can paint an entire group by the X
Actions of one individual
Especially one who is incredibly mentally unwell
This is another critical aspect of Alex's early game
When their stories breaking and there aren't a lot of concrete details known about the situation he'll pretty much always accuse
A nun specific group
Like the idea of the gauges
A cover-up
It never actually has two
To be true because the effect he's looking
Emporia's to make the audio
Distrustful of any story that doesn't match his narrative
And warning of some imaginary cover-up does that perfectly well it doesn't have to have any bearing on reality
Also there's just a Trope among races
My black crime was being covered up while white crime is over reported now it says
Definitely playing that game here too
Totally
That sucks
Introductory pieces
It is a little bit wild to hear Alex
Alex's take on that when there is a I mean
You can
Pool if you put transcripts
Alex videos in that guy's videos
There are plenty of situations where you would be able to tell who said what
Maybe there's
Optics differences and turn right
The way things are being expressed
James in his videos was
You're so concerned about upcoming race war Alex and his guests
Talk about that all the goddamn time
So
What you going to do
I think that Alex thinks that he's taking a little bit of a moral High Ground here by being like we don't blame Alba
Black people for the
The shooter who was black rights
Okay cool
Blaine black
People for what he did
We don't blame someone for the color of their skin
Somebody else
The same skin
Has done
Completely
Also mumbling in
Incoherently
What do you want into an innocent black church and killed nine people at point-blank range in
White person in America was guilty
And every gun owner was guilty the corporate
4 months
Betus
We don't blame white p
People for what they
Stopping me shooters
Really funny for Alex to pretend that he hadn't evolved response to the Dylan roof shooting
His immediate response was that a proof wanted to actually kill black
People you should have become an abortion doctor which isn't saying about Frank James
Why people you should have become an abortion doctor
Don't white people get abortion. Guess it doesn't seem that Alex
Would really think of it though
When the victims are racially Target
Imports on reporting from 2015 actually undercuts Alex's entire Point here
Snowmass blaming of white people for rusacks
There was a deep trauma that have been caused by a personal Act
It specifically out of racist hate
Had a conversation was needed about how that hate is more prevalent than most people want to admit
And this is where
8 leaves a lot of
The time
When I say that in pores on reporting contradict Alec
What I mean is that just after the shooting Alex Jakari Jackson
Come down to Charleston
Expecting to find chaos
And people fighting
Spouting is normal race war fears
But when Jakari got there he found a community coming together
To heal people of all ages races and backgrounds and supporting each other here's a clip from his report
Doubts about
11:40
He also had loud
Inside there
And
It whether you were inside or outside who is
Pretty hot
I don't know if they
They didn't have one but
Bobby Webb and water
But it still good until we are
And they're sweating
But everybody
Enjoying the service
It was
It was a lot of
Asian worship
Goodbye
Keep saying about this
People law
Colors
She's All That
You will not be surprised to learn that Dakari didn't do too much more reporting
Charleston because of community coming together to reject racism and show that they're stronger than the hate that motivated dylann roof
That's not a story
It's very interesting for Infowars
Not profitable
Also f***
The idea of having arm pastor
When that's something you're sincerely suggesting you need to stop a minute and consider the problem what may be way more serious than your acting
Like it is
It's bad enough that rhetoric around arming teachers is
Become so normalize the idea that religious leaders
Painfully depressing
But it seems to be missing the mark entirely
It just feels like Alex wants to live in a world that's basically just that LP video for Deep Space 9 m m
Just casually pointed guns at each other everybody else all the time
It'll do something
The most high-profile case
I think Alex could be referring to here is the Sutherland Springs Church shooting back in 2017
Stop by an armed Deacon or somebody in the congregation being armed
Stephen willeford was a guy who shot the shooter there and he was at home
When the shooting started
He only responded after his daughter told him that she'd her
Heard gunshots only came to the church but it wasn't
An armed preacher
In 2021 an armed man took over a church pulpit in Nashville
Pastor in that case was able to disarm him
Didn't use a gun
Pastor does tackled him from behind before he was able
The shoot anyone
In that case I would suspect that if the gunman had been
Confronted by someone with another gun
You would end up putting a ton of churchgoers in a much more dangerous position and where
They could end up being
Exchange of Fire
People could be shot
Accidentally
Preacher might accidentally shoot one of your
Aggregation
It's not a solution to the problem
It's Alex's solution
There it would be it would be very hard
4A
A
Pastor
Or priest
Of the like
Who believes
What they believe
Sincerely
I want to kill somebody
As opposed to lay down their own life
Right
I mean like you would rather a pastor
Would rather be killed
To save the murderers life
Then otherwise
Is the point
Situation
Because of this
Happening in there was a case of a pastor can't remember where
But he gave a sermon
And then he went to a Wal-Mart and there was a shooter any ended up
Having a gun
Shooting the shooter
So is Pastor shooting
A guy with a gun
The church so I didn't
But who
It was a deeply traumatic
Experience
Absolutely I can't imagine how much worse it would be if you are in your
Church
Mike Howard traumatized
Having a shooting at a church
Be traumatizing no matter what bad
Level America's so f***** up we'll get to this level like granularly argue about what types of
Shootings are a problem three stages past like rational conversation Saturday
All right and that's another that that's what is important about what Alex is doing towards this Subway Shooters he does not give a s***
About the victims
Or about Solutions are about trying to avoid it
This is entirely in service of saying
This is happening so that's why it's okay for Dylan roof
Or why you shouldn't feel bad about dylann roof like
This is all in service of making it okay for white people to do at least
Trying to make this
Tire thing about Dylan
Body bags post before somebody shooting
Where in the World War 3
Didn't even know really where he was or what he was doing
Just like dylann roof
Didn't know he was gibbering the police
It was all white people smile
No
Something wrong
Hogue grips
How does mad
I think obviously the conclusion that I came
Game 2 from the subway tragedy
Don't blame me for dylann roof
Call bouncing to this specific scenario
So the New York Post story that Alex's siding doesn't say that the shooter didn't know where he was
The witness just said quote I looked at him and I thought to myself he was talking
Tim self for like a while so I looked at him and I was like this guy must be on drugs
That's why
Do you text the
What Alex's extrapolating outright
Also dylann roof didn't a bunch of gibberish during his killing spree
He showed up to a Bible study and was welcomed in by the churchgoers
They sat there with him for almost an hour before cutting down 9 people in Cold Blood while they pray
I know that Alex is trying to grasp at straws to make the story somehow about himself but this is some
Shameful share
You can tell that he's mad I think I know why
And the aftermath of the Charleston shooting people didn't blame all white people in the same way
In the aftermath of the subway shooting people are blaming all black people
However Alex is a flagrant race
So he experienced the conversations after Charleston as an attack on white people and himself in
In particular
He only felt that way because that's how he experiences reality and then he went out looking
4 tweets and blog posts that would back up
His persecution
You know something straight weeks of someone blaming white people or something
In this current situation things are a little bit.
Because Alex isn't
Experiencing the coverage of the shooting as an attack on himself in his own identity
He's not looking
For a defensive that narrative in the same way
As was the case with the Charleston shooting people aren't using the shooting took
Condemn an entire race to this becomes a situation where there's a media coverage
Hey what's the media allegedly covering up
Alex's narratives that this shooting wasn't text people and us we've come full circle
And every event of the news is understood only through the filter of How It's proof
How Alex is
Particular identity is
Under attack
Specifically
The obsession was talking about there's only through the prism of dylann roof that shooting
When is pretty towel
I think
I
I would say that
A Patel
I mean well
It does
Seem like you can
Very quickly work
Backwards
From that
Go to
Let's save the human race
One by one
And ask them
Just pure what is your first
Word association game
Only Alex is going to come up with Dylan Rowe
Sure you know what I kept
Thinking about you and I was listening to this like
Alex is saying like in 2050 2015 whatever that
Some shooting happened everyone blamed all white people
I just keep thinking of the multiple times in these depositions
People like Alex and Owen Shroyer
Have been asked
Did you ever actually
What are your examples
Of calling for gun control after mass shooting
And they can't come up with enough
I would guarantee that Alex could not come up with anything other than a
The general feeling that he had the people were blaming all white people
Identity fears in victimhood and persecution obsession
That's what he's talkin to
Yeah I mean ultimately
It could be seen today
To me that he's
Believes that white people are at fault for things
Have something coming to them and it is
Reacting so negatively because he wants
To try and avoid that outcome
You can
Psychoanalyze email you want
I think you're pretty
Goldwater rule
So I'll pull you back a little bit
So Alex
A lot
Oh time
On this episode complaining about CNN Plus
Sure better later streaming service
People have subscribed
Alex brings a pet number a bunch
If you're going to dance on a streaming service I think CNN pluses is a good kwibi way2go
She's very much like
With that it's a little navel-gazing a little bit
He spends so much f****** time on this
We operate on
Michelle 60 million dollars worth of product on that
To be able to then get my Defender
To break even
Take some of the money
We raised a year
To be able to sell that real estate
Operation
So I'm down to my last
Chips here
But but but not
Because we're not
Imagine that
We're operating on
You're operating on 27 million dollars a year
On crew only go with all the attacks
Plus
Watch with 400 million dollars
Less than 10,000 viewers
A week
You can start a cooking show yourself on YouTube Annabelle
Decent
Within a week or left
Well that's not
Dead cat
To get more View
Webcam on it
Joe Rogan
About it
Okay look
This is important stuff
Obviously covering
CNN plus not being very popular
I don't know
Who is watching live streams of dead cats I mean at least 10 to 12 thousand
People are eyasu
I think you might have asked you.
Version of
How difficult it is to crack into the attention
Do you have a cooking show a halfway decent
A within a week
Tens of thousands
The people will find you
He doesn't realize
How ignorable he would be if he wasn't this deep in his career
If he hadn't
Started prior to YouTube and started like
Wayback
He wasn't grandfathered-in no one to give a s*** about his dumb show
It's such a stupid
Stupid
Source of information and honestly
I think in the absence of Alex
Someone else might be as good of a showman as him
Absolutely Maybe
Absolutely
I don't know I'm not sure how attractive is program could be if it wasn't
Imagine
Disappearing out of nowhere
No one gives a s***
There's crazier stuff there's more interest
Sing stuff
I mean I think it's a little bit like a little bit like a comedy the pre-internet you know of like
There are so many Gatekeepers before the internet that
There is no way to break in unless you started unless you knew
And that kind
Kind of kept things much more homogenized in it
People from experimenting a lot of really interesting
All the sudden the internet comes along and
You could be a mediocre white dude comic
And have a very good career and then the internet hitting it's like
Oh there's a lot of mediocre White
Do Thomas around maybe there's maybe I should work
Hard but at the same time
Everybody
Can put out a time to stop
Your is even you know it's probably as hard or harder
With the
The amount of stuff that people
Can put out or get any kind of traction or 10
Absolutely
That's good, cuz you are there's a hundred thousand of you
888 just as good if not better
And even if you're doing something wildly creative guess what there's a lot other people are doing Wiley
Put just come down to like well people didn't see you at the right time
You know like
My point is that Alex
Sucks
N80 is no value if it wasn't
But
Elon Musk
Nope
Disagree
Elon Musk battling back about the inside baseball on that
A while back
Play frightened Austin
I run with people
Weekly basis
And I support.
What I was told was going to happen
Elon Musk
He's going to buy Twitter is battling the New World Order
Doesn't get more tip of the spear than pretending to buy Twitter and possibly getting a dress
Westgate times that we all know he commits that they just doesn't get punished for because
Consequences are anathema to the wealthy
Quite a battle
Alex
Incredible
You've taken very seriously by what
He would describe his intellectual circles where
Work is never done
I'm always Scrabble to get money just to stay on the air
Authoritative and more
Influential
In-N-Out
Natural circles around the world
Your investment Infowars
Is
Always
Turn off better day by day
How to get the babies
It's about to be
We all the works coming in now
I have almost spent
Pastor Reserve money I have
Important
$4000000
Months ago
Okay
Everybody we've got working here and I'm not bitching or complaining
Why should we have layoffs
Lawsuits coming to trials this summer
I mean we're under mass of a tax levy
The battle
But you decide so much so now
Romans Ashman
I need everybody's seriously to get off
Offend
Dot-com
That is about the most
Concretely I've heard him
Express
I need you to pay my legal fees
That is about as blunt as it's been
They like
Look I'm going to get hit with some really big
Vines coming up soon I need your help
Do you want me to be around you're going to have to pay for it Alex is going to be bad supper I'm going over dreamy creamy
Alex pays out the
Yep
The plan
Whatever he gets fine that's how many ice cream
I might have to divide
Zohir Alex gets back
Back to
Some
Conversations about the New York subway shooting
He really really gets
Pretty f*****-up
Open racist here
Charleston
Church
People he never met and didn't know. Nothing to it
Shot more than
Killing knife
Matter they said all white people were to blame
No I'm not to blame
People are not to blame
Is the one
Just like the New York subway shooter Frank James
Is a black nationalist
Waukesha parade killer
Recently released video Manifesto
Video
Court Justice doesn't like her
Because she's married
2A
Gibbering
Who do we blame me blame the
Blame them covering up the fact that black on white crime is at least
Sometimes
White on black crime
Because the media promotes that white people are bad and deserve to be mugged
And many black leaders even where I live in Texas
Robin your neighborhood go rob white people
You don't Robert kill anybody
How about that
Seems like that chick clip took an intensely racist turn at the end
The feeling that Alex is doing everything in his power to stop until from black people
Here's what I would say
I would say
That's
All black people
I have standing to sue Alec
Books for defamation there because we know that that is not
There is no such thing as black people committing 10 times more crimes than white people that's not a thing
Discuss this year
15 people
He killed nine and injured wanted
National person
Bigger issues oh Alex has these crime
Statistics entirely wrong like your
Literally just repeating inaccurate races proper
Again.
This conclusion the black-on-white crime is 10 times higher than a black crime is reachable when you don't factor in Papi
Relation ratios and other factors at urinalysis
And this is a standard drink at white nationalist and white
Supremacist groups
Reviews for decades
Have black people as dangerous
We've talked about this race is myth a bit
The past and hoteling it is that Alex thinks
I'm not going to dive into that fully again
But this actually leads me to an import
Point
I was just trying to use some kind of Illusion that all white people are blamed for the Charleston shooting in order to frame his coverage of the New York
Instead of blaming all black people Alex has decided he's going to do is blame the media for covering up that black on white crime
Is 10 times higher than white on black crime
In order to make black people feel like
Like they should attack the media to be
Apparently doing
This is literally what dylann roof wrote in his Manifesto about why you decided
To carry out the Charleston shooting
This is from his Manifesto that was published on his website the last Rhodesian
Quote
B of A truly waking me with the Trayvon Martin
McKay's
I kept hearing and seeing his name and eventually I decided
It look him up
I read the Wikipedia article and right away I was unable to understand what the big deal was
It was obviously a Zimmerman was in the right
More importantly this prompted me to type in the words black on white crime into Google and I have never been
The same sense that day
The first website I came to the Council of conservative citizens
There were Pages upon pages of these brutal black-on-white murders
I was in disbelief
At this moment I realized something was very wrong
How could the news be blowing up his Trayvon Martin case well
Hundreds
Black-on-white murders got ignored
I was just using the image of Dylan roofs not justify his racist response to the New York subway shooting but the truth is italics
Is dylann roof
Alex's disseminating the exact same people
Praying in a church
Specifically because they were black
Alex is spreading the same information to his audience
Potentially sending other impressionable listeners.
That may not lead to murder but definitely leads over racism
Difficult to believe that he doesn't know what he's doing
Beers had plenty of time to figure out that this is a
Incorrect racist meth and he heard doesn't care or he knows that it is and he still perpetuates it
The f*** him
Yeah
That's
That's great
I mean
Wow
In response to this mass shooting
10 quiz racially-motivated
Movie quote dylann roof
Paraphrases Manifesto
0 times when it's a good idea to paraphrase
Manifest
I mean you see where we did that episode on Anders Breivik how similar a lot of Alex's Rider Rick is to the things that were in
Aspiring to him
Inspired by the great replacement conspiracy theories
Oh that's early made of appearance in a number
And Alex's coverages identical
Because the reality of this
I mean it's the point
You can't say stochastic terrorism enough
Whenever
The point
He's too
Create an environment
Aurorae
Reality
Wherein it is justifiable
To commit those Acts
Exit Massachusetts
So regardless of whether or not Alex
Quote unquote
What's them to happen
By disseminating this b*******
You are trying to make them happen increasing the likelihood that people will find places that I've even more
Extreme versions of these racist
Poison live
Yep
Online if they if they search these things out and they'll become
Deeper radicalized
If it's not a path
Did someone responsible would go down
To put it simply
His response
To a mass shooter
Of which there are
Just egg
Unconscionable number
Is to say things
Things that will inspire another mass shooting
Or at least definitely have
Really this is
Maybe it beside the point maybe a trivial issue
This is the kind of thing that would get somebody fired at a regular job
3 like
Repeated insistence of these
That would get you
F****** fired so far
100%
And
He doesn't have to worry about that
No boss
Snopes anyway Alex's got some information wrong about the
Frank James situation
Kill all white Easter
Troubleshooting
Black Nationals rhetoric
Praise beautiful 911
Turn settings on FBI Terror list
Ages of tribe investigating but the investigation
Was
Killed
There was no investigation that was killed Alex is making that up
There were some inaccurate reports
That Frank James
Formerly on the FBI watchlist but it turns out it was a different person named Frank James
This is a mistake someone could make but what Alex is doing isn't the same thing
He's taking this inaccurate reporting then building a conspiracy on top of it
Not only was he formerly on this watch list but someone in the FBI killed an investigation into a now why would they
They do that
Why would they
Nothing else says
Means anything
Guy takes mistake sword or things he makes up and then makes up stuff on top of them it's
Soulja Boy
Yep you can
You can make a mistake if you're like oh I found on this
Former
Could this be the same person
Everybody could bet you know
Billion Frank James is out there
But
Then add like
And
Because I saw this
Possible name that matches on this thing
Clearly the president assassinated his Dad tried to investigate him and then the investor
Navigation was killed
Holden
Harley from Alex's imagination
Total b*******
Writing elaborate
Maxi's about is the case of the witmer kidnappers
Right
But she the wheels are coming off
The witmer fraud
Millions and millions spent
Michigan
Define
Langley
Young white man
Fatherless homes
Who were looking for
Male role models
And who were upset about the decline of America
Firearms
To be basically in the military without joining
They come up
Activate an order them that be
Themselves
Wittmershaus
No no I don't want you
BFDI
Muscle them and command them
Police show up
And run around at night the bushes bar
She was a victim
When people during lockdown
What is a fun scene from a movie or something but that this isn't accurate
Yeah the four defendants in the case were acquitted and the jury was unable to reach a verdict for the other two
Is there an audio even close to what Alex is describing this never would have even gone
The trial
Also Alex is conveniently ignoring the fact
The two conspirators
Play the guilty already sure and there are eight other people facing State charges that are set to go to court
Although
There are problems
You generally speaking is at the FBI rushed
They jump too early for the arrest as the pot and it was going on was
Solid enough for them to likely get charges
Is the stick
As it stands now it's too easy for the defense attorneys to portray what was going on is just some dudes talking
S***
Doesn't help that there were multiple bowls
On the group since that doesn't lend itself to the impression
And the FBI
Was running the whole thing
But that's not borne out by the end
Information
That is available
But it's just fun this dislike
It's in the evidence that you cut her head off
CFB izone
If they hadn't if they hadn't built a reputation for doing
That adjacent behavior in the past whether or not it's an all-the-time thing or anything like that but
You do it one time it's there I don't I don't have like
Necessarily a problem with some
Around anus
And I also don't think there's like
Absence of criticism
That that is Meredith
But totally
I don't think that the claims that Alex is making
AR
Our defense
Play that audio
The Watergate tapes
Go run around in the bushes
You ever see your Hot Shots part Deux
Look up people
Stop be asleep and Alex's decided
He's going to have a little weight so
Alex's
Very conveniently forgetting all of his buddies
Have been
In the background
That Stuart Road
Works for the FBI
Interesting syllogism
I don't know
Find me maybe that's Google
A parley with the FBI
Shut up right now
Okay
If you're a student at sea
Hey FBI
How about we turn these tables around yeah
More like
Yes sir I don't know anything
Okay you say to the FBI
Alright
I've heard the tale
Investigated you are they going to be like
What nobody's ever done this before doing a runaway oh my God you're so manly this is terrifying
You're clearly not scared of me
Nonsense
So Alex is opening is like they want to violets going into the midterm
Democrats
The globalist are just a Kratts now
So they want violence going into the midterms that's the only way they're going to win this shooting
Subway
Staged
Maybe it's okay
There's a headline Democrat death march to November town hall and it just says every poll shows
Landslide US history
He won the second time
False Flags
I pointed out you will see mass shootings and subways
Anna churches
Colleges
Shopping malls
Everyday
For the last few months
Schizophrenic
And then turn the cameras off
In New York
The higher-ups didn't let him
Shopping
So it wasn't I didn't know about it and they did have control which isn't true
Okay but they
Hey buddy could have
True if it is
80s
Who knows that is worthwhile
Death march to November is
I don't care
Analysis of Aldi
Please Depot
No
It's a guy who worked for Breitbart
It does seem like he would be let's say unbiased
Yeah
I think this is
This is just dumb
You know it's crazy to me
Vicious
A prime Street
Diedrich opportunity
Do the
Bare minimum of
Zoom saying you're not race
You know you could if he was just like
This is exactly like dylann roof
Play I mean just like that if he just equivocating them
Entirely
This being about black people
It would be one
He's so racist
Secondarily I don't
That they're the same
They're absolutely not
It would maybe be racist to say that they're the same
Absolutely would be racist to say the same
But in Alex's world that would be that would be like
It's not about what you're describing is what he's trying to do or what he
Thinks he's doing you know what you might be right
Oh my God you might be right this is the worst day of my life I'm sorry
Well I'd like to make your day better by having
Alex tell you about a study you could even read
But I want to get to this
New York
California
What's the number to
The lowest death rate for the comp
Backcountry
The study it's abundantly clear that he hasn't read the article under this headline they have no idea what the
The study is
New York Post at Reid's New York California failed at handling covid but Florida was among best
Study
Why do you read the headline like that if it's probably good idea to ask yourself two questions
The first is
How does the study define success in dealing with covid-19 second who did this study
Well the thing about
It was and you would
I've seen this coming but
The measurement was how successful you were at getting around
Covid risk
So Florida was the best
Dad put a little jumping hurdles
Just a little bit below your nose you know what I'm saying
That would be an interesting study it's not
I think in this case answering the second
In question who did
The study and helps you get halfway to answering the first Quest
This was a study done by the committee to unleash prosperity
Which is a nonprofit group dedicated
It's pushing policies that will ramp up economic growth
If you are non supervillain
You know there's only there's really just one simple rule don't put unleash in your name
If you're a super villain
That's where you put it
Unsurprisingly the committee
He's co-founders Arthur Laffer and Stephen Moore Economist with deep connections
To the network
And our board members are very swings
Within the American legislative exam
Exchange Council
Is their way of putting
Policies around legislators
Expect this is a study that is not primarily about mortality from covid it's an economic
Institution with strong right-wing
Putting out a paper meant to justify the argument the places except business is open our bet
Better sure to be clear I think that New York and California and our beloved Illinois
They can come their way about handling covid issues
But I'm not going to take a study from the committee to Unleashed
Prosperity very seriously in terms of that argument
Read the article or the
Tostada
I am
Going to dismiss it out of
I am too
Moving along
I think that
Make your move that much
Well I mean I do like
The idea of
More things have a baby named Unleashed
Get like more charitable like this is the national Center for unleashing vac
Maxine's on you tell the committee to unleash the kraken
Exactly
Our sources God is truth our source is
Sacrifice price
They receive it
We are ancestors and our current
Brethren and those in the future
Eternity
Because eternity is not enough
Wait what
What is greater than eternity
Unlimited
What
God
I want to take your calls from Chris Michael Alex Rush Brandon
Nobody Does it Better If I got the Ethereal with the pedestrian
I'm talking about incident in Trinity is within God's and then immediately
Imma take a dump call
The eternities Beyond eternity SV eternities of eternities yes I would like the
Nice please
Thank you very much
Yep help meeting with rambling about esoteric Christian ideas
The closest we get in the present-day to good old singing along with country music I think
Yeah
Periodic times he sings along
Country music
So much more rare
So Alex gives himself a little bit of a status report checking in boss but sometimes you got to Be Your Own Boss
What's the scraper
Mentally ill schizophrenic
Black Sopranos
The winning that reportedly shot all these p
Situation
And it flies in the face of the
FBI
The last two years
People
Dylan roof
Other cases with the media is not going to
They didn't do that
After Charleston shooting
Are you saying they
Should be doing that now I believe so the ideas being expressed a really weird and kind of all over the place
Woodfield
Intensely racist
Yeah I mean
It's hard not to think that you really want
What he saying to be true
Which I think is weird
Headspace
The feeling that comes
Lacrosse
I wish that people had said it was all white people's fault
Feel like they did
But I mean like
I think I think
Here's what I would say yeah
As opposed to wish
I ain't think he's can
Confused
The people aren't blaming all black people for this
The Gap and how he's dealing with this ridiculous.
Because he
Feels and thinks that they did blame all white people after dylann roof
Confuse that no one's being racist
Just enough for something
I need everybody be racist right now
I think that's
Part of the Constitution
Alex
I need a little bit more
Brian stelter
Humpty Dumpty
This goes on
Too long
No one can put
CNN MSNBC
In the corner
And the whole corporate media
Together again
Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall Humpty Dump
Humpty Dumpty the greatest examples
Humpty Dumpty said we must ensure the mall
Speak
Humpty Dumpty
Ugly and disgusting feet
What is a wall Humpty Dumpty
All the king's horses
Couldn't
Humpty Dumpty back together again
What can I do
But look here's the thing
That like
Started the parody started okay
Yeah
Thought you was f****** me
She's going to roll roll my brain is just going to take me through to the break with this amazing ride and I'm coming
Lee falls apart with these are the only ones who can speak being rhymes with had ugly feet
Yep I'm seeing Brian stelter's fetalis
Maybe just going to those websites are creepy websites
I don't know I'm not going to look it up
But I think
By the end
He's just
Reciting helped
I got much like
Icarus
And I got to go back to Safe Harbor that was too long
Commit to
The parody or shut it down just by calling him Humpty Dumpty that's fine
Right
Tall man
It is
This is probably the most
The closest that Alex and I can
Canfield
Because both of us have absolutely
Experience this moment where the Improv Garden is
Empty stage
Does me to Mann Eye Care
Performing at the last Factory
I have like 40 someone like me does not belong on a stage like that where there's a two-drink minimum
It's just all dark a Sea of Faces so many times was just me at like
Some idea or some thought I have is like
And if silence
Here we go
I can relate to that feeling a lot
Oh yeah
It's not good but
I will say that I didn't then Retreat to just reciting Humpty Dump
No I'm proud of that job is to overcome
You know we always turn him into
It the Clown's almost more
Lovable
Never going to not be a
Israel
Please don't turn back
Because that's real
Why would
Time Warner
Put that on TV
Cuz they want to force ugliness
Evil
July
On you cuz there hunchback
And they're ugly spiritual
And they like the fact
Ugliness songs
They're spiritual
They're filthy
I got to assume there's some kind of internal metrics
And Alex knows that like 18
Complains about stelter for long periods of time it does numbers
You think something
I don't know the man just hates Brian stelter
I think that could I mean that's obviously a part of it I just don't know
He's never given me
Anywhere near enough
Stelter's crimes to justify
This level of despair of hate
I think I saw somebody what is a poster like
Text Altura.
Quarterly
DNR
It also has been since the beginning of this that he's been yelling about
How many years is a Jedi
He hasn't even done anything
You just I would I would I would argue that I wouldn't know his name
If it weren't for
100% I would maybe be able to recognize him as somebody who's on CNN
But I would not know his name
Never
More people to Brad self
And assumably Ithaca
Comments about guns
Aftermath
Of the
Deepest Subway shooting Friday
Wants to like
Really clown on it
Because
For some reason
Biden started talking about
Prostitutes
In the middle of this talk
Talking about gun he's crazy he doesn't know where he is man okay
Here's that clip
Here's Biden
Can't even get it right
Butchers it and brings in
Prostitutes
I said what do you think the deer your hundred wear Kevlar vest what tell you need
20 bullets for
You must be a hell of a terrible shot
Think about it
Think about the mass shootings
Bonnie's 100 rounds
The weapon of War
There's nothing to do
Is Recreation
Alright Banning the sale and possession of
Unserialized guns
Eliminate gun manufacturers immunity from liability the only outfit so the only outfit
The Prostitute being sued
Come on
Zoe just misspoke
Execution
Inside of
Wow
This is this
This is big as that Nancy Pelosi clip
She misspoke 1 times
The tip of the spear
This is big
Having this clip
Now
Metaphorical Smoking Gun
That proves Jim Carrey
Is Joe B I would say so I don't think there's any other
Conclusion
Take take a viking comments
However you will agree or disagree with him
I don't think anybody who is acting
From the position of sincerity could say like
That wasn't just him misspeaking say prosecute
Pretty f****** clear. Trying to make a bigger deal out of it
Seems desperate
Yeah
With Trump
Stuff
I think sometimes
His be speaking might have been a little more funny
And I honestly think that if Alex was covering this like recognizing that he just misspoke
And thought it was
Funny that that's the word that he said
I don't think that would be anything even worth comment on
Conception
Chewy
Fires bringing prostitution
No that's just
We just had the wrong word
Yeah I'm at your best
Did the best you could do even then is like
Piano
He's not out of it he's not scrambled
But it's like he's not as quick as it used to be
Maybe we shouldn't have 85 year old president
That's a conversation more sense
Anyway
And it's called from a guy
In New Jersey Adam thank you for calling her on here
Alec sauce
Just want to let you know you are the tip of the spear thank you for everything that you do I want take up a little bit
Your time Anna
I live in Jersey
Going on in Brooklyn
It just seems all too conveniently seen this move by the globalist
They overplay their hand and then they go
Play to the other side
It just it just enough over here that's wanted to get there
Conveniently the camera failed
Play Shadow the thousands of cameras that's the one area where they failed
That's exactly what I'm saying
Too coincidental
Yeah that's that's why I'm awake
Misconception about the actual story is relating to
To the cameras in the subway not work
According to officials who spoke to the New York Times the issue was a faulty fiber optic cable that affected the stage
Mission as well as to others nearby
However this was not the case for all of the cameras in the stations
Tim Menton the spokesperson for the Metropolitan Transportation Authority said quote
The suspect was able to be seen in movements evaluated with the mta's assist
He added that the cameras with malfunction
Thing for youth we're located at Turnstyle
Where they would not be in a position
To capture any activity on the platform
Below
It wasn't even affecting Ray needed to be
Right
They were still able to get izone prank
I'm so like the issue is
Kind of
Maybe
Coincidental
Slightly interesting on some level but it doesn't really affect
The reality of
What would
So what's important is just that the next caller is
Golf Wang how big this is weird why are you out yet it's a false flag
A more skeptical mind might come to this sort of different possibility which is that maybe a ton of the cameras in the
New York Subway system don't work
And they're just there for show and saying that the ones in the station happened to be off
Is to cover your ass a little bit
I don't know if there's any evidence pointing in that direction but it seems like a more reasonable suspicion to have than what this
Is collars getting at
I know that I worked at more than one low-paying job where they had cameras that definitely didn't work
At least in one case it only
Came out that the cameras weren't plugged in after someone needed footage to prove something
It's not unheard of the companies do that
I think it's a stretch to assume that an entity as large as the MTA would do it
I will
Let me know I'm not saying it's impossible to take it to scratch
But put Stillwater underestimate the underfunding of public transportation I think that's still a farm
Reasonable
Spiracy questioning
I guess angle to have on it then whatever they're talking about
This is like
Premeditation
They turned off the cameras gear
Yeah here's your
Conspiracy
The government has
Has been over to
Taken by the wealthy and is transformed
Itself into what amounts to a kleptocracy
That steals money that would be going towards
Say public-funded issues like transfer
Predation in the lakes and whenever you find out that needed
To be there
That's when you discover that essentially they're running on a goddamn skeleton what's been ripped away from
I feel like that happens when a bridge collapses
Anyway the same caller has some other dumb ideas and so does Alex
Damn all these videos of his social media
He was some Mastermind why did he have all these videos
Basically saying he's crazy out
And I would suddenly this guy it doesn't make sense
Wallpaper
Blocked it
I will continue to watch it as it develops
Necessarily accusing James being amassed
This was not the most
Intricately planned attack
Has ever been
Pretty blonde
Force
More importantly though it's really critical to look what Alex
The saying hear about race
Alex's conjecture is that if Frank James have been
Killed that invest
Navigation to him and that they
Only did that because he's black so it doesn't fit the narrative
That they want to push
What's going on here is it Alex's taking
The fake piece of information that James was actually on this FBI watchlist
And using that to make the story fit
Hughes narrative
Alex is the one who's forcing things into a predetermined narratives and accepting bad information because it adheres to the conclusion
But he already wants to be true
Which is somehow that this would have been different
If he was white
I am at
Because Alex is right
Places
Purely in service
I'm saying that the entire United States
Prejudiced
So we get to a little comment about Russia and Putin
In the war
Haha and how honest Fitness I was one of those Donna's people there's ever been since no proof
These are real good point how can you prove it
You considered that
Alex's
Currently
Put music
I said put one into a trap
Right away
Globalization
But doesn't mean I'm an old Jabo you're so smart to go in there
Don't give me that
What do you think was waiting for him
What do you think
All the special forces units of Europe
And the and the Delta Force the rest of them for
We like jaguar
You better if you know that why did you say that they were going to just all not have any opposition in the oven
Because Russia had paid off everybody and their Reno fighting and they'd be over in 48 hours if you knew
Special Forces have been training for a decade or whatever
It's all nonsense
But I like the idea that going to be an old-fashioned
I mean
Wow what is
What is this
Crazy
Mixed-up world
Does wild
Clarification that we need to make here
When the war was just starting
Alex did say that
Into a trap but it wasn't about losing the war the Ukrainian forces were
Still saying that Ukrainian military have been bought off and all that
When Alex said that Putin had walked into a trap
He was saying goodbye invading Putin made himself vulnerable to being blamed for a cyber-attack false flag that Alex was sure
The closest swab was going to pull presumably on the way
I was very specific about this and now he's trying to rewrite s*** about like what the
Trap was
Specifics of words because when he says trap
He's talking about something in his head that you can bring into the conversation with something in your head
Agree that they're both traps
And assume that Alex is talking about something correct
Instead of being like
Here's the problem
Okay Putin is walking into a trap
What is happens olinsky is setup
This box okay and underneath that he's got a
Plate with a cheese sandwich on it
And it's held up by a
Small stick
Now he doesn't even know
You can't see that
Olisis the cheese sandwich
Really thought you were going to involve like a marble at a shoot
Mousetrap
Alright
Spine
I'm going to have to soothe my wounds disappointment with another caller
Brutal this person
Took their dad to the VA
Because they're worried about
Vaccine injury
And they think that the
The dad got fades
Oh Richard
Does not exist
My father I'm his part of attorney
And
Two years ago he was riding his bike
9 miles a day
Wow very
In state
Elderly yes
Exercise
Everyday
And now he can barely walk to the mailbox without getting out of breath
So I took him
And I wanted some blood work done
Because he's had
Thought
And
The doctor acted like I was
Crazy
Because I explained
Why wanted this blood work done and I
Where we went I told my dad
What I was concerned about
Which is back
Being induced
Autoimmune deficiency syndrome
And
Doctor
Acted like I was
Crazy
He acted like it was
First time hearing
Meridian Ms information
Illiterate
I think that
You know among people who are in the elderly set
Sometimes a couple years can be a really
Turn around
A lot can change
In a
Relatively short amount of time
There's a ton
Of reasons
The other than vaccines
They could attribute they could be attributable to what this
Dudas
Experience
But I think the cheese
Jump
Some conclusions that are not
Found it
Doctor
At the VA
I might also
Be a little bit
I don't I don't know if I want to humor this I mean
You can't what you going to say to her like hey
You know
Have you ever
Pizza sidewalk whenever the moon is full
Full moon didn't do that but you remember the Moon being full of the you associated
Did the two of those things together
Do you see where I'm going with the vaccines in your dad here
Can you prove that the moon didn't do it
She's come to
Conclusion about what's going on
And
Also I think
That
You know it
Whistle conversation about Hippa rights
I don't think this is a HIPAA violation necessarily
Because
There's no identifying
Information haha you know
For these
Ding-dongs who talked about HIPAA all day long
Complain about sup this would be an imaginary violate
Near me
Not moving
Start over with
Start over with what's in the report
In the report
Keystone
I wanted to know
And they're low
Bestow
B as in boy
Those are all
Stolo
Eating 8
Those are your app
Depress ourselves
Blow
And then the key 48
Free smells
Hi
And it's very high
I looked up
What does
Mercier Tracy Ojai
And
I got instantly on WebMD
Hodgkin's lymphoma
And your listeners to know
As much cure say if
I have proof
And I
I feel horrible that I let him get this
It was out of Michael
Control to be honest the doctor
Lymphoma
3 clear there's plenty of reasons that aren't lymphoma why someone would have a high ratio of these cells
Princeton together viral infection I would cause the
The same test results
Typically this is a ratio that discuss not in the context of lymphoma but in terms of hiv-aids
Which makes sense
Because this woman did say that she was badgering this VA doctor to test her
Pixie is this not existing condition of AIDS right
Interesting Lee you generally find
Decrease ratios
Use of these cells in patients with HIV or Aids so this
This test essentially
His invalidating her entire argument
But you came in with
Right which is why she had to run to WebMD.
You find a new thing to focus on and claim their dad got from the vaccine
There's no good evidence anywhere that cover jacks
Cause lymphoma but I think Alex might just be getting
Confuse
Cuz the vaccine
Lymphedema Dental pathy
Kiewit similar but is actually just swelling
So I think that's
Probably what's going on here although I do feel like this is
Very sad
Yeah
Person is a
You know like
Vizio disinformation
Yeah I mean Nintendo just a beacon of Education
System failed and they just
Every part
From start to finish that lead
Did you hear
He's not just like
Her choices
Is this is a structural issue
Baby to get here
Education system in many other ways she may be very well in
Informed and know a lot about a lot of things
You can be susceptible to
Lot of dumb narrative I don't know if it's necessarily a failing of education system but
It's a it's a failing of
At least the people who disseminate information like
Alex and whatever she's
Pulling from
Have some kind of a responsibility
The hold themselves accountable for what they're putting out
Angie is a victim
Some of that for sure
And II
A pill for her but I also think
I mean she's just a person in
Tympanic who's
Whose father is it
Ghetto like of course
Trying to find Subway to make the anti-vax argument
Fit her
Particular case
And it's just a bummer
Call from someone named Vern
And I got excited cuz I wanted to do an arniston course
Anyways
Here's the call
Hi Alex. Thank you for taking my call
I'm not transgender
My real name is
Veronica but shorts
Stubborn
Hey Vern I wanted to I saw doctor artist on
On the 11th
Do feeders
And then
Understall
Brighten with Mike Adams
You really need to get them on your show
Yes yes
Prison
Substantiate his claim is
Remarkable
Information
Been out there
On the internet
January 2020
Do Peters conspiracy documentary called watch the water
Which feature is a chiropractor named Brian artist
Playing with snake venom and the devil
Here's a synopsis of the documentary from Stu Peters pay
Okay
The plandemic continues but its Origins are still in the farias mystery
How did the world get sick
How did covid really spread and did the satanic Elite tell the world about this bioweapon ahead
Time
Dr. Brian artist has unveiled a shocking connection between this
And the eternal battle of Good and Evil which began in the garden of Eve
Wow
Snake venom
Naturally artist is using this documentary to sell a collection of
He calls it the Aunt Ivy collection
109 dollars
Supposed to say this is overpriced
Apparently after the backlash of people making fun of the documentary claiming that the vaccine was meant to inject people to Satan
DNA Wright artist decided that he should do some damage
Controls that he's been done Dirty by Peters.
Recapture is claim
Pressure is still on the
The top of Artisans homepage
Supposed to
Nope a publicity is good publicity I got to sell these hundred and $10 pills
I'll take what I can get
Limited-time sale price Jesus
Yeah but you got done Dirty by
Stupider saying
Cuz that's do the Garden of Eden or some s***
The snake venom
Conspiracy
Because
That gives me some sort of hope you like one thing that it is
Is Drew about snake venom
And Engraving
Anti-Venom
Is that
There's just not a lot of it and it's really hard to get
It's really hard to milk Venom and is we there's a shortage
Of all kinds of venom
United States
So in this scenario
Someone out there is milking enough Venom
To poison the world
Would suggest that we won't have to worry about snake bites anymore
Have you considered
The time
Tom Hardy movie
Yes I have which one
But
Great some Hardee's amazing this is giving you some kind of optimism
Optimistic too because in response to this call
Alex is like
This is bulshit
A series of Courts
A remarkable coincidences
Truly inspired by God like LED
Supposition and then
He was able to kind of
Masonic me pru
That coronavirus is actually
Snake venom
Pacifically
Snakes and the cobra snake
And what's interesting question and
Virus scan
Pace University
Virus virus is real replicas
How much snake venom to put in a water supply
To have these type of blood clotting infection things
New York
Blood clots in your leg
I'm not pooping this one will get our Tucson inside what's the big
But
To to shave it
It's diluted it breaks down
Electrochemically very quickly
What you want is a virus cuz it
Replicate to the body
Yeah cuz cuz
Contagious
Ears ears how bad it is
Your whole in that
Plot is so big not even Alex
Can walk through it safe
He doesn't think it's worth patching off as like well
Why would I accept this
It undoes
Everything I've been saying
Completely
Open
Everything that I claim I've proved the right person
I can't do this one
Also come on
Yes I come on
I thought would be I said that would be the most reasonable response I think from Alex
Get out of here fairly generous is responding to her because it is I'm not poop this is meant to be short of a
The softening of the blow and then BB like you understand how much venom it would take a toll so
Viruses replicate
You mean they do it on their own
Kind of nice that he's not just being like this is f****** dumb
A little bit disconcerting
Have him immediately save the most obvious thing which is
We don't have enough Venom to do that ma'am no one does an element of
He's engaging with this theory on and I signed a defensive that he's capable of it in some
Totally second there's an element
Grace
But he's showing towards this caller
No and it shows that there is a possibility that
If he can act that way towards people
Which is f***** up
That is
Although less unexpected is the idol still interviewing cuz ever want to talk
In his field of
Chiropractors baba baba
Trump says together and drink
I bet they did
So another color
I think a lot of people
You know sometimes if you don't engage with Alex's
Really don't listen to the show you don't recognize how
Goddamn religiously insane
Listen to this caller
Alex Jones my brother in Christ how are you today
I'm good brother
Absolutely the Lord
Call my heart
Call and give you an extrication and just let you know
You're a crusader of modern-day
Crusader for these times
Before the return of our Lord and savior
As you know and you
We're in the days of Noah or the days of lot
And many
Are just not awake
But you as a crusader a Lewis leading those
At the type like Noah
As a came up
To the Sea
They look behind them
Pharaoh's Army was there
Today that's
Oroville
And what is a sea that is impenetrable
Afterward says
New the God Will Make A Way
Odyssey
We made it across your leading people in that way into the light into the truth
And that's going to lead
Do Great and Mighty things
Moses
Nope
No is the plug guy
The boat
Yeah yeah I think
There's something troubling about like actually disseminating is information
Series that is like
You're f****** Moe's
You know sometimes
I think you know
Like listen to this
Listen to The Wave
This man is speak
And what he saying
About Alex
And then just
Go back in time
I meant think
Maybe Moses was just an a****** who said he did all this s***
Convince enough people to believe it and then everybody forgot that he was full of s***
I just don't like hearing this year don't ask me uncomfortable
Coming up another gas
Ortega's a gas cuz he hasn't had a gas yet
Episode butts
It is somebody we have not talked about in a little bit he's somebody who likes
To get permit
Four stages for
I wish you were people that he plans
To bring their fraudulently you might certainly suspiciously close to
Somebody like that
Torch passed to him from rogerdale mustache aficionado
I think yeah you could say that
Oh yeah what is back
Introduction
Editorial consultant
Blossom
13 years and
Understood in philosophy and building a better
Comport / Alexander
Gab
Social
Ali
Telegram
And more he joins us now
Good
Pivot
I'm a philosopher
I'm a loser
Oh sure I was I was previous political
Activist
Coordinating with Paul gosar and all these other weirdos
And I was involved in campaign running
Alex might say
But now I'm in the philosophy
Play now cuz
It got too hot
Are you saying that you don't think people can change
Not Ali
What is this philosophy that he's pivoted to
That is going to really kind of blow our minds
Make us forget that he's a month question
I want to know you have a notepad I will
Over the course of some of these clips
Determine what is philosophy
Mighty
The first cup maybe not so much philosophical but
To do with
Report
Split his pants
Periscope Channel
Like the videos aren't available anymore
Yeah well you know that it's absolutely fascinating to me I have
I have my Periscope videos on a
Subservice
Now deleted videos
Twitter
You got ready or YouTube your son should know
A news article saying that Ali's videos have since been deleted he did the deleting
I get to be sensitive but this is a little sad
Also Alex's situation is entirely different
The reason he's in trouble here is because when he was Sue there was an order for the preservation of materials related
The lawsuit
Prior to his YouTube channel coming down
In the intermediate. No one took any action to preserve the videos that were on the channel that were relevant to the case
We cannot be found out
No one is mad at him for deleting video
Stacy was that he failed in his duty to preserve a bed
It's a pretty big difference but if Alex gives the appearance of understanding the distinction it becomes too obvious that the courts are depressing him
It all images actions have brought him into the situation that he's
And that's an intolerable conclusion
For the audience.
Yeah don't do that
Just making me look dumb
Dumb you're dumb
Before this couple days before this it was announced that Ali was going to be at a cooperating with the JaneDear
6 committee
What's a give a very APA
Perspective position on this
Disappearance
Parley with the FBI well I mean I assume she is thinking of
The great mark
Aurelius
Whatever Marcus said do you know
I hear you got a you got to pay the piper
That was a saint August
Man I'm
This is why Ali's the philosopher had not made you've got to go with more religiously that's a good point off with Ally
The stoics were really his bag huh
So Allie has a
6 committees actually up to
Let me go ahead and break some medicine and only my lawyers and I are weird
The January 6th committee
Is going to try to Outlaw II out out outlaw
Okay
I knew this in December
Rodger Stone
A criminal referral piercings were not going to primly refer but we really like wink-wink-nudge-nudge
The justice department to move on
Policy recommendations
To keep the right-wing from ever organizing again
You're going to see recommendations
Increase the regulatory environment for Bitcoin Americans to get it
Well the rest of the world compete with us on this sovereign
On the shop
Various.
So this is Ali playing a preemptive defense
Game because I suspect that he has a pretty good idea that there were so
Shady f****** transaction
They were involved in January 6th overdone by Bitcoin
A telegram is a platform that a lot of them used
Plan an Insight people
This is an attempt to hijack that conversation before it even happens because the ultimate end of it is threatened
To some aspects of Ali's bran
Pipe always do
I wouldn't be too surprised though if there were conversations in the not-too-distant
Future bathtub more regulation and oversight of Bitcoin
I don't know how much that's going to involve the jam 6 committee
Seems like it's just
Long overdue
Some kind of a financial nightmare that comes along
Probably
To do with nfte
Situation where we like
Got it
Make sure this doesn't happen again
One thing on My Philosophy watch here
He disagrees I would imagine
With a loud
Insofar as he
He does not agree that one who speaks
Does not know
Because he sure f****** toxel
I think that you're right although I don't think that would be
Formally codified in his philosophy
That's okay
I think what other part of the philosophy that you'll see is like
Dunno
Bobby McFerrin don't worry be happy she's kind of I like it
I'm really happy being studio today
It's good to be next to somebody's going through some of the same how that we are
15 months
And then I've been watching the series The Chosen which has been really good
In Christian friends and they're just like
You got a smile through this more Ali
And so you know I think that I think that like that
Everybody if you're listening to
You are part of this and you can play a role in this you need a red pill your neighbor
You need to make
Prosthetics
To you and your neighbors
You need to make Prosthetics
Statements write will later be used
Do promotion phone number to is eat drink and be merry for tomorrow we die
Victini
That's where we're going I thought you were talking about Dave Matthews Band
1 and 2 in my book on philosophy
4/3 Milly
I'm just going to two-step
Into this crap
Alright today Matthew
So Allie has a belief that
The GOP
They don't
Wants to lose
Right
Didn't want to win
Too much
Obvious
Is Berwyn too much people want them
Send to do things
That's how I would interpret it
Interpreted more as like
If they win too much
Then the people who are going to have major power are like Marjorie Taylor Greene
Paul gosar
These Fringe figures will have more of an influence
Where is Sav small victory
Kevin McCarthy will stay being able to whip
People into place
To get things
Where is
I don't think I don't think that makes much sense because if they've a small victory then the conservative people like
Marge has have more power or more because they will be the deciding factor whether or not something I actually
I mean
Is is
What that's V exact opposite of how it actually works
But
Babies
Ali is
Promoting or what
Suggest a prophetic statement that later on we'll get people to listen to Infowars
Would be the best thing possible for 100%
But now that they
GOP only one
You have to think about this way
Kevin McCarthy gets too large
The conservatives are in control
Kevin McCarthy just gets a little off the tip top
Control
A reversed A6 committee
Investigate
Any FBI setup
So they can control it and a 2024
By taking Trump off of a ballad
I was frustrating
Is Ali
I like that at the end
Daddy's
So dumb
Something that if you said that in
Any kind
Reasonable space
The person sitting across from you would have to laugh
Some of these priorities that alley Hazard is never going to happen anyway
You had a giant
Majority in the house or not
But I think
The possibility of having some like
Trivial ass going nowhere committee or something like that
Marjorie Taylor Greene wants to start I think the likelihood of that is much higher there's a small victory
Because she could use whatever leverage she has in terms of
Passing something that is a priority for Kevin McCarthy
Do like you have to put me on this thing
Right I will go along with your caca
Make any sense
It appears that Allie does not understand how negotiating power structures
Like the
The more you need from me
And the more power I have
The more likely I am
To get what I want
In exchange for giving you what you want simple
If there is a 60 /
Republican thing in the house
Your one vote does not really know hold as much clout as it would in the alternative
So I don't know but which is why Joe manchin is the singularly capable of destroying the world
Because the Lesser majority is the more likely you are to have two more important
Leon Bibb thing I love those
I know they do so excited
So a little bit of here about January
Defendants
Deeply problematic
Let me tell the government
Yes
I regularly talk to Jay six defendant lawyers
Over 30 of them
And they tell me about the evidence
Only secure laptops
And this evidence in one case exonerate
Moving train wreck
And then they get a harsher sentence because they didn't quit work
That motion
If there's actual evidence exonerating that these lawyers are in possession of
Could get it in front of a judge
Even if it is confidential or something like that if they have this
They be able to presented the only way they wouldn't is if they didn't
Attempt to
I suspect he is talking about isn't so much evidence as it is
Heavy insinuation
This is the kind of thing that is called evidence I probably wouldn't
Play in an actual Court
It's kind of persuasive in the court of public opinion I feel like that's what Ally is talking
Also if Allie is telling the truth in January 6
Defense lawyers are leaking privileged information to hit that easy then discussing on Infowars
That is a gigantic
Confidentiality problem and there could be some real consequence
This for that
Dealers might be risky
Disbarment which honestly wouldn't be too surprising
Considering the Ali's last lawyer Jonathan Moseley was Justice
Disbarred for breaking
6 rules of professional,
Yasso
I don't know
I would stop insinuating that you're in contact with lawyers who are doing things that would
Probably get them
Does bar it is kind of amazing
That
Despite
TV
Massive amount of
Consequences coming their way
Through the legal system
None of them have really spend enough
What time like educating themselves on how this
This is going to work
You know like it is there so many things where you're like no your
Did that's know what but what are you doing in this case I think I was just talkingshit
Vicki probably is actually putting any of these lawyers in jeopardy
I think that
He's not saying anything specific but he's
Being
These drunk posture of revealing privileged information
And that could be
Courts do not
Look up
Probably doesn't go over
Maybe not disbarment
But certainly some kind of Accenture
I mean I'm imagining that it's
Quite putting out a million-dollar bounty
Fights
Yeah
That's actually
Totally cool
No I do not I have never been needing to disappear
Beer into the woods
That means that you still get
The protest
We survived the tea party we survive the
Shooting controversies
Still you can wear Melissa
January 6th
Peaceful protest
If you wear camouflage
Any protests across this country
BFDI can identify you
Associated with you
And you get
Profile creative
He sounds like an excited
Angry baby
Yeah I mean people complain about me being
Screaming loud all the type of cheese
That's annoying
And also like
I think
That's
I am flabbergast
I said the idea that
The FBI would open files on anybody who wore camo
Protests it's ludicrous
Yeah
But that would be typifying is
I know that our government likes to
Yeah I mean
I suppose
Maybe the best you
Could save for that is just like
Yeah the people who
Did the whole you know
Zip tie handcuffs and everything
They were tagged
For good reason
It wasn't just cuz they were
But That's Amore individual actions not clothing
It's insane
You know how many
Camo
Designs
What is camo
If you're going to say that what is camo
Sweeter as if you wore like a pattern of a Chamberlain
Fence that could be one of those pictures that have
People paint you in the back
That seems like maybe a Taskmaster episode
Real camo be like wearing a regular ass t-shirt and jeans
You're going to get on the list for that
Anyway
This is this is where I think some floss
If he comes at 2
Holly Alexander how do we stop
A Civil War the globalists and Trauma trigger
How do we deescalate
What
Some of the conspiracy
Satan's domain
Because I
You know
Uef all this stuff way more than I have
For over 25 years
I have a great understanding of campaigns large organizations and government
But I don't see something like this fully cooperating with each other without a supernatural Force
Influencing
Yeah
Here's what I say
Guilty
That's what I say
To that
Honestly
All evidence
All trial base everything is done
That guy said that
Because he did it
Duh
Come on
You don't say that
Crazy person says that
You might as well have been like I wanted over there yet those
Conspiracy goes so far
But then
Not guilty how can people
Do things with Supernatural
Haha
Ali Ali is a little bit much
I ate you know
Sing today's I started to realize that I didn't miss
But still I hate this is the word
Though I do think that he is the kind of cat who comes on and
Ends up a little bit
A conservative publisher
Explain to that conservative publisher
You don't need to convince the
The public
They need to chill
Ping pong between the two parties
Districts in America
Fulton County it's Orange County in California
This mini seats and so
Okay with these things
And white women
Being called a racist
But they don't like CRT
Yeah we got a hammer
I was advising
Giant Republican organizations
I would say
Trt is something that the Tea Party Stop the ceiling Trump wasn't
Five-year-old white babies on rice
I think this is a little cynical
Wow
So I think I think
Dates
That's kind of just a good
Summation of
Love how
How
I think of you here similar things
Is that art is Craven and cynical in terms of like
What messaging surrounding
The medicare-for-all
Is
What messaging is most attractive to
XYZ
In a largely surrounding an issue that is real
Where is
Trt and all that stuff is a manufactured problem
That they're like oh yes if we drive this
Messaging surrounding this there's not an issue it scares white women
And it'll Inspire enough to vote that week
You can flip a couple things
Yeah I mean
Justice idea that Alyssa
It does not matter if
Trt
Means anything
It doesn't matter if
What we're talking about
Is educating people about races
It does not bad that's
Nowhere important
What's important
Is making people think that if you go to school your kids are going to tell you you're a racist
Wow wow mommy already we've got to vote for republicans
So they can
Wait
So then they can
Dominate the critical race Theory
And then that would
Lower the status of so
Okay so they're just race
So there's one last clip here in Ellie has an interesting take
On how
People like you and me I would guess
If he was at
To talk to us
You would look at us as like cavemen
Weird we work we're back
Words thinking
Folks
Bluewater religiously ordered Society
There was a real innovate
Are the real forward-thinking Google
Google havlik
Stop 10K
Consciousness consciousness
Consciousness and get it
Yeah and
He said there's a different way
And by the way now it's Universal
We need to have a different way of saying
We believe in these archetypes and we believe in the tradition
Work for Humanity
We need to move.
Cuz the new model
It's super weird because their archaic
You know where are the people who are dreaming of alien coming together
We are always seeking on the right
To commune with God
In innovative ways
Civil Society
That's
Fascinating
I think I think Allie might want to unpack
How the church
Was just like the only people who had money
At a certain time
Certain things like art also take a little bit of a step back and recognize
A massive censorship that was involved in what
The church would
But he was supposed to say will probably be fine
With that kind of rank
Centralized censorship
Because they would be censoring things that he
Himself likes
For him
But he does not want
The culture to enjoy
And when
This happens as it always does
People go away
I didn't know you were going to do that
This has gotten out of like
Control and now we have
Yeah maybe maybe that's true
But yeah I think
I think his conception
Seems a little bit Limited
In terms of
The the
Did the extent to which
The church was interested in
The Arts
I mean as in somebody well
Miami Avenue
Appreciator of music
Prefer somebody to
Claim
Straight face
The church brought brought Harmony to music
Is it insulting I don't know what level of proportion can exist but it is that
I looked into it and I regret to inform you that the church
Holy s*** that's crazy how did they do it
Yes but that would make
I don't know I don't claim Christianity is responsible for their being 7
Billion people
Is the world
I mean
That the things that he just said that
Are so rude
Ridiculous
To claim
That I am mean
He would
If he was ever pressed to actually believe that stuff
Now you know I was saying this
I've brought up about alley in the past number of times
Yeah
It's
Really outrageous
Some of the stuff that he ends up
First of all summer just dumb
Yeah man some of it is stuff like January 6th had to be the devil's doing because how do you coordinate all these people.
Supernatural for guilty
Okay man
Wow why do you talk public
I mean you know
It is it is kind of a an example of something that always exist
In this type of a movement which
She's just a person who's willing to say any
A lot of those people
Well yeah I mean
That's fair
Anyting
Just an Ethan
Wild
How do you how do you go to
Sleep at night
You know people ask that whenever they talk to serial killers and that kind of thing
And I think they're serial killers they probably saw
How does he sleep at night
His brain has
Just be filled with like reasons that people hate him
He sleeps on
I don't know
I8
These people are a mystery to me
But
I think they are
I have some trouble,
Jordan
Will be back for another episode but we have reached the end of this one
Sucks
Text Ruth shity coverage of the subway shooting
Shity phone calls and shity conversation with Allie Alexander
Yeah
But hopefully greener pastures next time huh
DPAC sale
Mccreamy summer
Going to be good while it is upon us
Not yet actually cuz we have a couple days left
Yep
Is that true
I think so we will be back
Inaugurating the dreamy creamy summer end up eating an ice cream thing on the next episode
But we'll find out then until then
We do acknowledge right.com
I mean
Emilio dzx Clark
I'm not
F****** buying your chili
You can't make me
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work