Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Sit around worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
Job Indeed
Doordash
Summer of Ruby creamy creamy summer is upon us
Be kicking off I'm not going to eat
On air
You are not like ice cream novelties
So disgusting to listen to into the Mike's
I think it would be fun for the audience to hear me jump across
The table and slap it out of your hands
Sure will you do that with like
Just fully work.
Okay
That's probably how it would have sounded
Something like that
So the first
Entry into the dream creamy summer we're kicking it off with a classic
Okay Triple H
Okay yeah chocolate chip ice cream sandwich
Non-Stop
Goodness chocolate chip cookies that are that are just nice and soft
Good good soft baked to be soft right
Campy crunchy in the middle
Some nice ice cream
Surrounding the ice cream WhatsApp mini chocolate chips
Oh on the side
How big how big are we talking about ice cream sandwich wise are we talking about. Eyes are we talkin about the smaller one
Honestly I don't know
Know how many lot to learn about the way I parade
Measurements for a little bit
It's great great way to start the game between me Summer
Very excited
To see where this goes
More ice cream
I have to run into something that is abject
Actionable right to try some flavor of
Something
Oh no oh dear God what is this I think you do have to set aside some some
Choices better purely for that edge
Level of like
I don't know if this is going to be good
Of course I'm drawn to novelty
Absolute that will inevitably happen
And I might have to seek it out a little bit more than you are
Another cases
So I'm excited
What's your bright spot my bracelet Dan is my partner as you know she grew up in Maine for a lot of
Childhood
I'll have some friends out there
We got sent a wedding gift
This morning
From Maine do you know it was Lobster
Yes
Oh wow okay
Sorry I didn't mean to
She left me alone with lots
Do you know how well I reacted whenever I opened it and they're alive not well
Spinner like put them in the refrigerator I was like with my hands
Snow
Little Lake
Yeah no it's very
Did you let him go in the backyard
Lobsters you are emancipated do
Go to put him into the lake all the sudden
Organize Maine Lobsters in Lake Michigan Alta all year round I think they could survive the big boy
Really tough situation being cuz obviously
You know I'm sure you want to eat lobster
But they're alive
So now you have to emotionally deal with
No you made it clear up my partner's very excited cheese grew up there cold-hearted enough to take
On the inside
Just to eat
You just grunting it up as you drop them into boiling water she doesn't do cry when she reads where
Where the Red Fern Grows nothing inside
Brutal
I wish you well in your Lobster and see what happens
How many did you get
There was three I want one
Yeah well course
I would have walked in here with a lobster on my shoulder like a pirate
Jordan today
T22 that's Monday
That is that Wednesday
No it is mine
Feels
Close to being all right
As a way to
It rhymes
And so there's obviously something to it's always wrong by just a little bit the date is long
So this is
The obviously the day after news that broken of Alex declaring bankruptcy
So that people are going to
Be interested in Alex's response
Get ready for a lot of ads
Going to say that right up front there's a lot of that
It is funny a lot of people are like what's he going to say about his bankruptcy filings is it going to be like
Still fighting there's going to be like not the real answer is
He's going to try and get more money
Get ready for a good bit of that cuz if you're looking
A content
Auto finder
Not not a lot of things I needed to dig into let's say
What do I feel like most of the time it's just going to be listen
I didn't
If I did declare bankruptcy which I'm not
Confirming my lawyers haven't said anything about that
What you need to know is that I'm still great
I'm still fine
Nothing to worry about
I need as much money as humanly possible right now though
Unrelated
Don't think you're
Far off so we'll see how far you are
Lotus Milwaukee
Next
I'm about to try to trip me up and they can't do it that was well done
Lose lose got promoted thank you so much
Congratulations
Thank you very much I go through these messages with getting policy wonk names
Unfortunately
There's a little bit of a theme in a couple names
Okay I have to do with a happy anniversary sure
When I see these shout-out.
Whoever is sending them
They did the best they could do something special for an anniversary
So if you were their partners
But they did not send a message late this one's on me
So thank you so much to Simply nice Mike you are now policy wonk and happy anniversary
Thank you very much 18 years of marriage and all I got you was this walk status
Happy anniversary Jenny thank you so much
You're out policy walking happy ending
Anniversary we are
Good affair
Look
You can't expect the two of us to really be on time
With your anniversary wishes that's just that's just not how we do things no do record of being at least
2 months behind on all birds
That's true that's true
But but see the thing is there such a
Trope of people forgetting their anniversary
That's true heads I just don't want to feed into the
People did a good job
What should the 18th of anniversary gift
Canned goods
Oh yeah Mr eazi
We start off here and I will say that Alex does jump into the the
Maine
Copic
Pretty quickly
Yes he does bring that up fairly quickly
Explaining dead like we're all f*** Monday April 18th
Addition of the Alex Jones Show in the year 2022
And we see worldwide depression we see worldwide inflation we see planetary
Starvation Reservoir
Collapsing borders we see
Open pedophilia promotion
By every major Western media Outlet
Any size
It is just stunning unspeakable
Moment in human history to know that we've been turned over to evil
Millions of babies
But God is now withdrawing his protection from us and evil and Corruption
Is that being allowed to absolutely run rampant
I'm going to say something here
And
Boulevard
But it's just this
I'm not declaring bankruptcy
It's a chapter 11
Reorganization
In the federal courts
Who's the total mess but it's wildly unpredictable
Bankruptcy
Even a chapter 11 reorganization style bankruptcy
Then all civil litigation if it involved in
This is because whenever bankruptcy like
Cuz represent
Typically a business will enter this kind of bankruptcy if they owe money to multiple creditors so the whole thing of civil litigation is Jenner
Generally an attempt to make sure that one debt the business has
Isn't prioritized over all the other deaths
In the people who are owed money
Chapter 11 reorganization
To create a plan to
To pay off all the debts while keeping
Business funk
Play speaking when people do
Right
Pretty hard to see this as a sincere move on Alex's part
Given the way things have gone over the last few years that stuff for me and not to read this as an attempt to postpone or entirely.
Civil cases against Infowars
But as it stands now I really don't know what
Six pack from this
What what is a big break
News story going over our world short but honestly I kind of look at this still is a developing story and I don't know
WhatsApp
What's going to be
I mean what in his
Like background would give you
The idea that maybe this is a
The stalling tactic everything
Oh okay
Any specific
From every single thing that he's done over the past three years everything okay everything everything
Alex is an interesting explanation for why
He's doing this
Makes sense
It's a chapter 11
Reorganization
In the federal courts
So you can go and show them their books
Don't have 16 million a secret bank account
We haven't any secret secret
The Connecticut court
And
Successful or not
In the long-term
This will be an issue
For the bankruptcy Court's one way or another
It's just time for that.
That I don't
I don't have
$3000000
Less than three million dollars cash
We need that money about future product to be able to operate
This explanation falls on deaf ears for me because honestly if Alex wanted to open up his books to the court to prove that stuff
If you could have done that at any point
Up till now
You only can do that when you file bankruptcy
You can't just like go to the courts
With your books I don't think that's necessary to achieve
Describe
So I kind of feel like
It's explanation
I just don't accept as like satisfying at all
Yeah but you would if you wanted to keep it all confidential we could have had it subbed
Get to the protective order that's in place for the
Please cases
So like
I think that I think that
That all could have been done
They could have
Right on the
The court and the judge
What you don't know though is that it wasn't so it's it's a little bit like Hippa
Okay so until
God removed
His
Protection
He couldn't show those
Numbers to the cork
No texture like hippo
Alex is hungry hungry
Because he eats lunch on air all the time
Alex has a prepared state
That's very clearly like his lawyer wrote
But also he tries to read some of it
Stick to it.
Bankruptcy
Alex Jones you're truly gave up alright just membership interest in the
Trusts created
The federal system has the tools experienced a fairly deal
Resolution of these planks
Here's what's important
Uh-oh
Again the corporate media in the nation
Know that we don't have all this money
The plan is to try to get judgments that are giant large
So they can close our doors here
Makes me work harder
Value the person
Is tied to your faith
Add
This country and this world is in a lot of trouble and so we're all going to share
Demos that are
In the system and that are
Really destroying due process and
Every major
Pillar of our Bill of Rights and Constitution
It's completely thrown out the window
Not as mm
Remind me to buy cruel and unusual punishment
And also about like excessive bail or fines
Right I mean I think
Alex is actually violated our right
Amendment rights
No cuz it's not really a punishment
It is shows crawling on your roof
You and I could choose to not move into any point in the punishment would go at it
I think that's fine but emotionally too listening to this
But yeah I don't
That any of this Plies
Honestly there was just a news the broken
Got sanctioned like a million dollars
I don't think that's excessive I think this is a very
Like
Based on his behavior
Probably fine
Probably appropriate I feel like
Human Society does kind of breakdown
In this scenario
Is like
At a certain point
There can be no more benefit of the doubt given
You know
Like
If you
You've proven that if you give him the benefit of
The doubt he's going to exploit
So then you
Stop doing
Still is like with this million-dollar judgment it's like what are you doing you're giving him the benefit of the doubt here
You're only charging Bliss
Well I think it's probably a very high fine
But it also
Seems like
At this point it's like
Slap-on-the-wrist number
54 whatever here I'm looking at Old cases going through like
Let's just see the top number and I'm going to go up by at least one
You know think about like instances of other large civil
Litigation
People don't
Act like this
A little
I have to imagine that this level of obtuse
Navigation
Feet dragging
And such as almost unprecedented
For most courts do whatever
Totally
It's pretty impressive
So what do I
Lexus
President that's what I'm thinking is my my response to this is
Alex is doing unprecedented
Did things
But you keep giving him very precedented
Sanctions in
I wonder I wonder if that's at
I think they might be
Quite large I'll agree I think they need to figure out
My definition of unprecedented I'm not sure I'm not sure it'll be interesting
To figure out more about
So Alex has some other things
You could describe a sanction
Against him
I'm not going to get into this today
Any story
For anybody in the country
And I talked a lot of lawyers and including some of the biggest names out there they seen these documents
They cannot believe this
But
The judge has given him a Texas case and the Connecticut case whatever
Warriors won
Remington Inn
Serious problems
Filed for one of three trials they have coming up
Lexi like this month
That we not be able to talk at the truck
Guilty
Didgeridoo
Judge usually a jury would decide
The First Amendment
Not defend yourself
This is a big story
Pleasant crew
However
Some reality
Used to this bad the situation but Alex himself
Put himself in regarding the trial
Repeated abuses of the discovery process that Alex engaged
The court sanction tip after they failed to produce get another Corporal representative after the dari-ette
After that when they sent another representative
That didn't work out
And
Instead they
I had some issues
I mean Lucy territory we're here in Charlie Brown territory you guys keep putting that football out there and there's a
Just never going to kick it
This made it so Alex aside wasn't able to
The demand any further discovery
From the plaintiff
If he wasn't cooperating it wasn't fair that the other side was being held to a different standard
I think that makes some sense
Further and more relevantly because they had at least four opportunities to come in and
Discuss discuss
Failed spectacularly each time
The court ordered that if there was a factual dispute between Alex on the plane test on a number of questions
The jury was
Did the view the plaintiff's claim does established fact
His list of questions include stuff like
Sourcing and research for the videos described
Duplantis petition
The audience reach of the videos described Duplantis
Position
Efforts made by the company to preserve potential evidence
And the company's business structure and relationship with other parties
Alex was given a chance to discuss this stuff in an appropriate setting but he was unwilling to cooperate with the process of now that
It's not appropriate
For him to like now I want to talk about it once we're at the trial
It is it has a little bit funny because it does feel like in court
We could get into a scenario where Alex is like
No that didn't happen and then the judges go like
That Jerry's
Instructed that it did happen
The jury is instructed that it did happen
Able to bring up the First Amendment I'm guessing that's more of an issue of it being
Completely irrelevant
To the case
He's already been found guilty in a default judgement
At this point
And even before that
First Amendment defense wouldn't really apply
I mean that one might as well just be like hey
We can't allow him to be an a****** who Grande sayings about the First Amendment for no reason for it
An hour
Given half a chance we're going to go right one step ahead
Yep so I don't believe there's anything in place
If it says he can't talk
Or can't defend himself
It's just that
Juno is required
Self on maybe some of the other question
Gyms that are listed in
Then the things that the jury is instructed to
Not accept his
Protestations
So anyway we get to supply
That is
Attached
Is endemic
What is happening in Civilization
And it just tears my guts out
I can tell you this
If we weren't so maxed out
These legal battles would be a lot easier
The biggest thing you can do is
Born by the broadcast and Powerful forces
Are doing everything they can and Breaking All the Rules
The devil
Because they need the main voices of resistance silence
I had of the next big block
And the valuation of currency
Universal basic income
Tom and and the real
That is
Shut up and roll.
Please spread the word about the broadcast in realize it's so precious
Every guess we have and every time
Information
It's something that really scares the power structure
It is they know it's the truth
Also financially support Infowars
So this is just going to be setting the tone
It's going to be a lot of
Yeah
Yeah you know I mean
On the one hand
I see him say
If we had more money these lawsuits
It'll be easier
Raven Lite
Designed to get as much money
Yeah I think so
And at the same time
Is it a deeper truth about America that if he did have more money these lawsuits would be a lot easier
I think
That if
Most
People had more money
Their lawsuits would be easier to handle
For Alex
He's already got
Lawyers that he cycled through
I don't believe
He's that there's anything really about how it's gone that more money would have salt
I think he is
Probably
We've done as much as he can with money
It would require enough to like
Purchase Texas
Yeah that's beyond his audience his ability to donate
Venetian I think it would be able to get out of this
Short of that I don't know what money
I'll talk to you about it we'll see how it goes
I guess he could be imagining that
Goodbye the judge
A little bit about you and said your assessment
Mcraven attempt to get more money
It is probably accurate
Because
He's already
Grown quite a bit a wall
Turlock
Show the continued
San Antonio
Blazing gentlemen that if you want us to be able to stay on here
Ford Futura
Cannot wait
Infowarsstore.com
Especially those t-shirt
Supplement never got an air filtration water filtration
Shortwave radio Souza's of great items books you name it and infowarsstore.com get your living defense get your
Body cleanse
Infowars store
Dot-com
And it's just that simple
A button
Pop on the top
The shopping Carlos as support
Become a sponsor and you just click there and you can
Shmoney
30 or 40%
50% with the sale of the products show
This is do-or-die time
Attacks of the system and the system pulling out all the stops to try to silence this then
This is the time they are trying to silence you
Voice
Resistance
So I simply needs you
Daily infowarsstore.com
So
I I hear that list of products
There was a supply chain breakdown
You couldn't get these supplements already
Stuff in stock
Presumably shouldn't
Based on things I've heard
It does seem like that and
I do appreciate the idea of
Up somebody list
Listening who's like
You know what
I've been dragging my feet on those water filters for a long time Brew but now that I know Alex
Is declared bankrupt
That's what I need to put my money into that fire now I need to buy a
School Bus size water filter
Yeah
I don't
I don't know who
Possibly exist in the audience
Who's been listening to him
Scream bloody murder and the sky is falling
Multiple times over the past six months finally I'll buy it
Is sales what called action is like
If you haven't once thought about buying this weird upside down golden horse that I sell
Going off the air in 6 months like a year-and-a-half ago
Silver coins as like war bonds
The didn't work out
He's trying to get everyone to buy reset Wars by saying it's the most important work he's ever done
Pillows with the a****** they're gray pillows
Feel like you've done about everything
Extreme called
Call to action
Panic button
And like I don't know who's left
The Freak Out
Hostage situation necessary to elevate
You know like he's got to be like
Hey guess what this is your grandma I've got her by the throat
If you don't buy a water filter
Grandma's dead
It isn't that what he's doing with his job like that you like this show
If you like living
You need this show to continue exist and so you need to
Grandmas in the world grandma is going to have the world going to end
So there's some
Content
I guess
Emblematic of the rotting establishment that we have that's in control that look at some of these headlines
The Washington Post
Democracy dies in darkness
Says it's time
Present
Must wants to buy Twitter for free speech
He's a danger to the world there's another one
Real clear
Policy time to choosing the president
Washington Post
Same article you're reading the headlines
Year-old operate in the Washington Post it was roundly mocked and criticized so they changed the headline to it
It's time to switch
To preference
Primaries
Whisper expresses the point of the the headline in the article
Mad about it he's pretending that's like a current
It's just annoying
Elon Musk wasn't trying to buy Twitter for free speech
And even if he was
The two-year-old op-ed that no one like
This is
Such a trivial waste
Yeah I remember that
Headline
And I was like
That was from a while back
That you told me it was two years
Back makes me really
Concerned how well I can remember
It's less than 20
Something like that
Within a few months
Po-boy
Some rambling for you
And I am just here fighting
As hard as I can with everything I've got
As long as possible
Until she finds it sold again and stands up peacefully
All the promise
Working
They backed off some
But now they're setting up
Proposition
You can't avoid
This corruption
RockAuto
It's not going to go away
I am very honored and blessed we've been on the air 28 years
Together
Mistakes
Overall
The world the better
More insightful as time goes on
Really
The good brand sold
Great brand Soul God gave you and all the listeners
All the guests of this family
Tell your folks
You're the only thing
Mark Warner
And I'm in your corner
Nope it's Word of Mouth to make sure this broadcast gets through the sensors
Chinese money
Bat signal here
The Alamo
Please send reinforcements to stay here
Salmo didn't work out well
Yeah and like the Alamo he's somewhere where nobody wants him to be and he's
Really being a dick about
Long time ago like
He seems to just be dead set on
Kind of trying to live out that Ark
But like
Siren of the bat signal
This doesn't seem to be working
Batman's not coming
No
Why you called The Joker
I mean
Because he is the Joker that's right
I'm so depressed lately do you know who's in town
Doctor I am the Joker
Yeah I think
I feel like this metaphor
Because if you call the bat signal is not going to bring you
You money
First
I mean
If you're doing the same thing
You're not going to necessarily get a better action or response out of this true
You know what raising the bat signal does gives you a little bit of eight increased cash flow
Maybe it's got to be diminishing returns
Studio
Like you're just squeezing the same people
Yeah that's what I mean like we said there's no reason that
A new call-to-action withdraw in a new
Audience
Dubai
Scare the people who are already inclined to buy most likely
Seems that way to me I don't obviously know how is internal
Stuff works I don't know I don't know if this does actually bring me to Costco
Oversight eventually transito sucking dry
The colors that you know you hear they're like yeah you know about your products and some more because of it
People who are already in the revenue stream
Maybe we would like well I'll get some more toothpaste
Yeah I was going to wait until a couple of weeks
Weeks to buy more toothpaste but now I've got
4tube
Better buy all of it though cuz Alex can't get s*** anymore probably
I want to be strong persevere
And the biggest way you can do that right now
Goodbye going to infowarsstore.com and getting things you already need
I shouldn't be selling all the stuff for on sale because here's that here here's a predicament
I'm spending almost all the money
Infrastructure
And legal and
And then we have to buy
Product going forward
Prices are going up to 25
We got that money work please let you do it for no money down and 25 and 31
Product
Books to films
The t-shirts
Jerrod office stock
467 months no problem
But then I
And add
Do the show
On on on a shoestring
Available
Huge but not as effective
I don't want
The years
And never gone infowarsstore.com
Boats
Are the reason that the broadcast is still here
Summoning
Powerful people
And so many great, people it's just a measurable
What this family
So much but
Most important
When the strike without your permission
It's excessive
I think he's describing a bad business model
I always
What is people won't give me Supply like a
Stuff on credit anymore
Probably because I'm being sued into bankruptcy
Has to be an element of it
Credit it's very unlikely I'll get that money back I remember when I worked accounts receivable
Situations where you have to re-evaluate if someone's going to be on a net 30 schedule for paying for
Spell 40
If you need payment on
Delivery Adelaide
It says
It's something that happens with all company probably offered
Some automatically ordinarily
Strange the movie
I think Alex
It's probably a little frustrated by that
But also I
Here is this like I have enough to go for 6 more months
Pretty consistently whenever used
It desperate times
Seems like that's just kind of a line that he has
Roosevelt Lake
I don't know how much that reflect any kind of reality
I don't trust that calendars
It's been
180 days
Since I've said we have six months
The down and he's like I'll write 0 days
I don't know it just seems like it's his
It's just a
Cliche
But he has
Trope
But
Sound good
Six months away Comics used the other day
What two years ago six months ago I ate yesterday what's the other day
Free
I don't necessarily believe any of us to pick
His
Israel situation kind of silly
Completely tell everybody you're busy
He does that a bunch
Wonder if it is actually
Got to be such a bad
Definitely not what you'd want to invest
So
Here's where Alex gets a little bit threatening with the audio
It's about whether or not they should give you money
I need a gas station right now
Odyssey
From you
But you want to support
But you really want me
Give
It's a free will universe
I just get out as I say so
Go to infowarsstore.com right now don't weigh
Alex Jones
That's like
A more immature version of Jim Bakker
I like your big girl be like we need a sign that you want us to expand
Weather Shack
Outback
Did do something in hold our potatoes in or whatever
The adding of the or maybe I should quit
Oh yeah
I'm writing a sequel to Field of Dreams called field of b******* and it's just an angry man hearing a
Voice in the Sky Go
Studio
If you tear it down they'll go away
You can go away I'll leave you alone
About something entirely different than they are
They still write articles
Everyday
I'm evil and none of us exist
We're going to destroy you
We're thinking write an article
Human
Nowhere for your body
People go well I better not criticize it
I mean
No one suing him for those things
Because
I wound up serving
To death all over
Suing him for talking about a new world order
So one world government
Talking about just a new world order or One World Government we wouldn't be in this scenario at all no
Biomass
It seems like you just talked about Hillary being a demon forever
Nobody would be lying about Soro no problem totally find legally
The problem
The denying the defamation intentional infliction
It's another five emotional
The Straz Center misidentifying Marcel font
Action Bowling in a civil court
Not talking about the New World Order let me let me just try this real quick then
Future
Government
Quo
Got any
I have a lawsuit
Deserve
Alex is right I didn't even mean I did not know that you had to do it
Just like something came over me almost like a demon possessed me
So look Alex doesn't talk about himself
He says
At 90%
To talk about himself for a really long time
Give the number out and I'm going to take your calls today on the war
On the new covid lockdown
Tommy how you're dealing with inflation
I really don't want to sit here and
You know bore you would pour Alex Jones what's happening to me but
Intelius
Start the clock
Big famous law firms
And they don't believe
The rulings in the things being done in Connecticut
Texas
And
The proposal for the trial coming up in that we can ask
Jury selection next week
In Texas
One of three lawsuits that got
Against me here
Brooklyn
We are not allowed to raise the 1st Amendment or any defenses or talk
The jury told I'm guilty
We can't respond
So I said okay
Show
They wanted to post me there's a party
Insurance companies in
Jayceon dies
Sunday silly
Deposition
And then one of the other Warriors will just reschedule
But I try to reschedule
Oh my God
You're so this money
Twenty-five Thousand Miles the next day
They treat me like I'm Daddy Warbucks
Howard Hughes
I just bathed in Gold like Scrooge McDuck
All just completely insane
Everybody else
Shocked that you don't want to talk about
Yourself
It's very much real sincere that he does
Until
Based on what he said
It makes
Can feel deeply uncomfortable with two kind of like get into this frankly as lawyers
Have given him the advice Eddie.
I bought a little bit of a made a whole thing for him
And it's clear that he just doesn't want to talk about
Admirable
Yeah you know who Alex treats like Lex Luthor and pedophiles put together
Anybody who disagrees with
Particularly members of the lgbtq community
Care too much about his feelings about how he's being treated
I'm so sorry.
Books
Scrooge McDuck
Ed's I was there
Real relatable references
Girl modern you know it's a lot like wow
I'm in the Spruce Goose was how many years ago
Dixie House like 2 years ago couple months attitude it one way or the other you're alright now I remember it
So Alex thinks that the people suing him have
Ulterior motive
To see it happening
And watch it going on so I'm trying to
Dishware under federal court trustee not lying about
Again
The judge is coming her hair and prepping
Making money off me
Wall climbing
True
Order to sit there like a monkey
But then allowed to talk
Taco Bell
The First Amendment or house
TV
Trials going to be the dead birds
Sketch
Yeah
Still not talking
Hates talking about
Yeah he's been complaining with the judges combing her hair
For the media
And all I did
Was
Obfuscate
Probably in a criminally fraudulent manner
For multiple years
I don't understand why he wouldn't think that this would be something
That media would be interested in
I mean he's a media company
The big one very public a****** Behavior
Together with the most a****** a****** president there's ever been
Yeah
I think it's so you got understand that
So Alex has done some ads
This episode
Quite a bit haha I've not included all those
Automatic
There's a lot okay for pets
Alright then he really swings for the fan
Let me get into as well
Alma DeSantis run
A lot more but
Let me go ahead and go to do this
I'm going to take this live on air
24 minute and we can run
Bearing all the shows
Operate in the future. Beyond his own show you just record say format add to play other
Paradise
Any other show
90.5 on The Simpsons is Bart.
Just stopped and he's like I'm going to record a Butterfinger at real quick to the camera
A Wolf Blitzer
We have some good news coming up next segment with
Even stelter wouldn't do this
So here's some of that good news
It's about old
Great positive
Does Santa's blastpro infanticide late-term abortions
Florida State Journal passing laws or have passed laws
More than 10 states
Trimester abortions that is a
Very very good
But that doesn't ban late-term abortions
After 50
18 weeks which is right around the cost
The first and second timer
Masters
How is presenting this is DeSantis Banning late-term third-trimester abortion
Because he wants the audience to see this Extreme Action
Is just a minor good first step
That way they can still feel like there's so much I need to fight
Wait for it
Gimkit extra life any opposition to DeSantis action
His people overreacting
And it's
The Cheap Trick
Dan sucks
Hey you know
You know you're good
You know you're on the right path
Whenever you
Andrew buddy
Have to
Constantly lie to
The people who support
In order to get your
Evil bulshit pass
That's how good
It's um
Wow
It's okay
America would do it
Pitbull boy
So I can get many years ago Jordan
Let me tell you a tale
Deerslayer
Four score
Situation I don't remember where it was
Repack maybe Joe that the
Seem right
I don't know anyway
This was a time when
Alex and Rodger Stone decided
To go crash
A recording of the Young Turk was talking to Jimmy.
Spit on at
It was a big to-do
Alex velt assaulted
It was so sad. I can't remember either way Jimmy Dore spit on somebody
Isn't it ironic how far we've come
No Alex is playing at Jimmy Dore clip
MSNBC
Advisor in it
Analyst
Explaining what's really
Going on
Ukraine
They almost have a heart attack
When this gas is on
Morning Joe a psycho Joe and Mika Brzezinski the war criminals
When the truth is
Jeffrey Sachs
Very difficult
Who is this
And listen to what he says
Congratulations are due to Jimmy Dore forgetting
The Alex Jones nod of approval
He's clearly doing some really solid work and should be super proud of the people who want to associate with him
A few points here though
The first is that this clip is not a morning Joe clip talking about the war in Ukraine
It's actually clip from April 2018 talking about Syria
But it's also a 2018 clip from Jimmy Dore
Jimmy doesn't think it's talking about Ukraine Alex is making
That all about this okay
The Palestine question Jeffrey Sachs
Is not a newcomer to MSNBC or even to Morning Joe as Jimmy's trying to imply
And he didn't
He's been on the show since this clip in all that nonsense is just Jimmy trying to create the
Perception that opposing opinions aren't allowed
On media platforms that he doesn't
In reality the clip Jimmy is playing along with saxes other appearances which Jimmy's pretending I don't exist
Ori strong
Counterpoint to the entire premise that dissenting opinion
And aren't allowed in
The mainstream media
Disagrees with the idea of insisting on Assad's removal from Power while the prevailing
An opinion on the panel
His little socks should be removed
And he's free to speak his position
Any wasn't blacklisted after work
Anyway Jimmy and Alex both suck even one second to look into Jeffrey Sachs is resume
Define that he's involved with a bunch of organizations that Alex believes that the New World Order
Like the UN in the World Health Organization in the World Bank in the oec
CD
This is an important point to not bring up also because
It would illustrate that there were differing opinions on world issues even among people Alex would call the globalist
And that makes those narratives really impossible to rationalize they just completely fall under their own weight once
It's seeing that this isn't the unipolar group where everybody
Has exactly the same ideas and works like otamatone to achieve the goals of the devil because then whenever you
Murdered them you be like I owe these are people
So
Another gotcha moments
About Joe Biden
You know where the last one was pretty strong
It was powerful prosecution misspeaking a lot of Support over there
Here's a club
Indicative
Instructs confused Joe deleva crowd
After
And you can laugh at this but this was done
Covid-19
The Elise
Their puppet does here's a video
Southlawn thank you and happy happy Easter
Alright
You can hear say wave
Who cares
I don't think is a big deal at all
Not remember Trump looking directly at a solar eclipse during his Easter Fest
No there's nothing weird about that
He just looked
I look directly at it do you know why because he was so great not even the sun can hurt his eyes
In terms of a
Call Calabria head on that one
I don't know
Cares
How do I access more threats
About the money issue
This doesn't affect me
It's affecting use the courts to become this out of
Control
Dribbles do stuff
Like to show
And we need your support
Whatever because money
Is the big thing that can
Fix this at stand up to this
Ensure
Other things are able to be done in the future matter what but maxed out like I am
Sure will
A delicious don't support me
Then then then then that's what God wants
Always providing
Lawyers
So
You know just
Absolutely did MIT than that is God's plan
I'm supposed to stay on air
But made a lot of money
This is an interesting texture Eliza
If you don't give me money that's proof
Play God doesn't want me to be on here
Your actions can determine God's will
I mean what else can I say but jolo's
Steam come on down
I think it's a little clunkier
Well I mean that
To go without saying
Aplomb and panache
Showmanship better at
EBay have a helicopter
You know last year when that
Texas head ice all over
And Osteen doesn't have a tag
So that's 12
So just bored I need money s***
With the accounting
The DNA Fork plus antibodies ultimate turmeric formula
Any activity X3 in the coffee all of it
Pictures of money
To run
And implode
Weather
I am in between a rock and a hard place
Money right
Water in frozen ocean
Oysters
Infowarsstore.com
Secure high-tech beautiful sight
And buy some Ultra
UT shirt
Whatever
We can
Absolutely win and dominate
Almost destroyed
I don't have millions much what's going to dollars
That's it
Narrative Trump is all over
I guess we're not totally against
Is he hasn't gone bad
I guess also Alex saying that he's not worth anything bacon
Course sort of weary cast that
A billion
Apparently
Billion dollars
It's been a rough go for 3 billion dollars
Is still a shitload of money
Wow
Are the 20 billion Maybe
Man
Surprised
We don't have like literal found
Like I'm surprised he doesn't
Turn around
And you see
Before
D-list conservative
Celebrity
Please Manning
Old timey rotary phone just like
You're ready to take your call but you throwing it to like a choir of
Employees children
Yeah
Rob do-doing
Talent show great probably as something that we still get close-up Magic
One last talent show to save the rec center from the evil billionaire
Goddamn dignity to do something like that that's what Alex needs help to
No cuz he needs to be a shout
It means to be a show car wash also do the like
Cuz what else is down there like save Infowars are thongs or whatever era as the dumbest shows
But longer over and over something that you need
Try and jump a car over Snake River Canyon
Alex Russo like David Blaine.
If we don't get this money
I will know God has abandoned me
Because I will be dumb
I'm sending this text I will be
Bring in a see-through tube
For a week
People in glass houses shouldn't throw stones
And now we're going to prove it
I just think something like that would be
FIFA
Fantastic it be better than this
Because of excessive noise
Said the relative term
Does take some calls
And man this first caller has an idea to save Infowars
And
Let's hear it boy
Alexandra Daddario
But also he starts with saving for Save the World which is a
Prince2 Heroes save the Cheerleader Save the World
Which was that what hero Nakamura I thought
Sylar
In order to
Anyway you have told me about heroes over the years
Who was called the Haitian
He could mitigate people Powers when he was around them
Love you buddy
And come up with any
This color is a bad idea
For Alex
I'll talk to Bob in Ohio Bob welcome
Welcome
Unless I ran a TV station
NBC affiliate
The better part of a decade recently
But I know exactly what you're doing wrong
Okay
I believe what we need is
Reseller
Infowars.com
What do you think of that
What's the weather
Music 7-Eleven
Fundamental problem with this idea
Do you not realize that they already do
And it's a lot cheaper than the s*** that I sell I put a different name on
Alex
It's like his response
Obviously is
Appropriate already if anyone have interest
I mean
God
Half a chance already be in every store
Not love
His f****** mad men ass prepared pitch
You used to be a treat sir
But now you are a bush
How do we get back to the tree of Liberty is anybody's keeping a list
The Shrubbery of Truth is up there with the
The Piranhas of news
The Piranhas of Liberty
A boy
I love that
So I don't call Ortez that Alex should get more sales
I agree
Alex
Does not take this well
Brakes are still hanging in there
After
All the crap that's going on right now
It's so I just want to stay
I just ordered some
Stuff from the store and I was looking back
History
And I made an order
There's another one around about a year ago
And
There's been
The whole entire
Website has done
In about a year
That's ridiculous
There's so many people
600000 orders
Only come out your guys store
How many people are watching this and stuff
Is absurd
Blankets
And nobody takes this stuff seriously so we'll just go off the air
So much nicer about it
Hey brother we're in this together
Zeroed me against the world
F*** it don't take me seriously I'm going to die alone I don't even give a s***
GoNoodle
That guy was
Stocking it was order number
Guest based on order number
Hundred thousand
Medipass
But yeah man
That's not a good headspace
I expect better from the shrub of Truth
I mean
I hope one day it gets the water of responsibility
It is uprooted by the construction company of
That seems like a perfect metaphor
Alex
Gets here to point where he's like I don't want to take any more calls about me
Stop it
A lot of people pick their noses from metamorphosis of corrupt
Wonderful things
I want to talk about Russia
Because it just
Storytime
Virtual offices
Bio weapons being relation Force modulation
Then America's done
And my job was to be here to expose what was happening
Spiritual choice
That is when
You want to meet us in the fight against the New World Order
We need your support
Turn it into complaining
My God
Stupid outbursts
Like what kind of calls did I like to expect to get when he's not the first hour-and-a-half initial basically just ranting about doom and how the world was a
Whether or not
Theme of the show and that's what I was getting mad at himself for not being able to do any other show than that
It's
We what do you expect
This is what you do you complain all the
The time no callers calling in with like
Want to talk about this
Situation York
Complaining about
Right right
You didn't know s*** you didn't spend the last half-hour talking about Ukraine
And then when you went to calls
Everybody was talk
Talking about you right
You spent the last half-hour talking about you and then you were like I'm going to go to Kohl's what do you think people are going to call in about
It's a
It's a call-in show
Why would somebody call in and be like
Hey I know you got bankruptcy or whatever but
I have a raccoon that's
It's loose in my
Baytown and I think
That the mare is secretly working for that raccoon
What do we do
That raccoon sounds like a problem but not as big as the problems I have now we're in trouble again
Just turn it into lake house like you know the raccoon is really like the court
Call APS
I don't want to take calls but in Forza want to take calls but other things that I will make about me
Cool
Liberty I have particularly with this is the way that it sort of blaming the audience
For calling in on the topic
But he's clearly
Rambling about 4
In the same way that he's making
His fault if he doesn't make enough money
That's another abusive
Go to work
You don't give me money
They're not maybe you don't want to show the kind of you I know I hate that I'm not a capitalist but even capital is don't lie
Like work by their rules like
Your shity business so you go out of business
This man it's not their fault
This is clearly a shity business
Everything
Alex's said about a bottle
That he follows
Collapsed already on E Bayonne
So yeah you had a good run
Silas is tired of
Asking everybody for money
How much energy it takes
It's got to be exhaust
Nothing to do it as much
Psychically
I'm just sick of sitting up her ass
The small percentage of the products would be in the
Situation
But
We have great products
Infowarsstore.com
Publix
Complaining
I'm sick of doing this
I'll sit back and watch this
In five years
Just so hard to do this everyday and I even harder
This man
We'll be right back
Weird I'm not continually rich I will watch all of you die in front of
Give me with Noah
And it will be yeah I will feel no guilt you didn't give me enough money there's also
An underlying sort of supposition there that
Alex believes
That his show is the thing that's holding back the world burning
He's the damn
Yeah
That's wild
Can you imagine
Feeling that important
No
Well actually periods of time in my life
100%
Very important under the sway of a powerful mental illness
Amazing this
Yeah
But for it to be a consistent belief that you
Do you know without shame
Express on Youree
Worldwide Bronco
Right right right
I want it all
Little f***** I wouldn't do it
That would be my advice I also wouldn't say that if I don't get enough money from you
I'll watch all of you.
I wouldn't say that
Just let that one go
I think Alex probably has a me to try and cover all possible bases in terms of like an owl
Am I going to f*** with people enough to get them to send me money
Maybe that's one way right but I mean
Radio show that is essentially a pretty
Textron racket for fear
It all like he comes to your home and he's like I be terrible if you weren't afraid of some
Something for 5 minutes
Just saying
Lakewood
It'd be terrible can you imagine if you weren't afraid of your neighbors
Yep yep
So are we one last clip here and it's the third hour is Alex interviewing
Judge Andrew Napolitano
And I don't care
Wow is he falling
All right ladies and gentlemen Judge Andrew Napolitano author researcher judge good friend
Remind philosopher smart person
For the rest of the week
He wants to get into the ongoing investigation what came out about
CIA
He wants to get into
Elon Musk and what's going on
The Durham investigations are no such proof and Alex isn't Vindicated and anyway
Where is the Durham s*** is really just a right-wing media machine and March a federal judge chastised
Including unnecessary information the fuel the fire storm and right-wing circles about supposed spying on former president
Donald Trump in a routine filing that he made
This is kind of a purpose of the investigation and Alexandra politano are playing their role
Kohl's in the whole front right if I can't imagine carrying any less
About something then what Judge Napolitano has
To say about Elon Musk drink
The what is what
But why is life
Those things that I never thought I would hear
Judge Napolitano on
Elon Musk buying Twitter
Yeah I mean you're saying how far he's fallen but like napolatanos been on Alex's show for a long time
Fox News guy he was
But no heat
Goes back quite a ways actually super regularly but
Infowars
Maybe even
Since like
Tea party date
If you have or ever word judge
And you go on Infowars you should be immediately disbarred
I don't know if
Napolitano is practicing
What about Judge Mills Lane
Judge Judy
No.she's
Punch and Judy
Judy tenuta
Judy Gold
I'm out of duties
Yeah I mean look at the interviews not
Alexander politano boring me
That like
This
Just
This long rambling about nothing and Howard the Duck
Things are at that I need money
If you don't give me money with them maybe you don't want my show to exist
Who's the oldest bulshit
I think
Sincerely
A little bit more respect
For Alex
He thinks
And that is like Colonel Travis
Right going down with the Alamo
Like
Colonel Travis
Go down
Like complaining
About the Alamo the whole time
I don't know that
Well
Whenever they were all in the Alamo he was like
God this hurts my back they're all out there probably
Lemoore the myth of it
Apologize version of it isn't like
Santa Ana shows up
And he's got one favorite is no one came to help
You know like
There is a Dignity of quiet Dignity of
Being in the situation where you're in this lawsuit and maybe you feel
Lil Jon Dirty by it but your job is to be this broadcaster who brings
The truth the Shrubbery of Truth joy and you bring the information to the people
So get on your show
And do your job
So you're going through all this trouble
Right I think that there is a dignity that that Alex is clearly incapable of
Right-of-way bodying
I think that's
Probably
Predictable
So I think that makes
Exmark and Bill the knights who say nee though
So that's pretty
Yep
I'm trying to think of who I could be
Being that
Because this shows you continually getting yours arms
Bike shops on the guy who makes the horse noises
OK Google black guy
Alex is Sir Robin that naturally
I didn't watch that
Anyway
I figured maybe people were excited expecting kind of a breakdown so
Because response is far more
Logistical
Emotional outbursts
Hello there are little periods of emotional outbursts but no like
Storming off the set
It's kind of like I need money cuz you need mine
Yeah I mean there's
It's the most honest two shows been in a while
Yeah
There's a definite
Sensitive
Clarity
Anybody or I will not do this anymore
No matter what
You know things go really bad I'll just have to fire everybody but I'll still go
Keep going
Not a chance
Without the trappings of the like
The status symbols
Studio that the wealth
Such he would absolutely not be doing
No on equal footing with the rest of the
Severe
Didn't have a studio that look like CNN and 50 employees or whatever in the
Ability to play up his relationships with all sorts of other people who are more
Mainstream and legitimate
Does Tucker Carlson going to care about interview the podcast
Is Pakistan could be allowed on Apple
No that's respect
Jordan card for him
Epson WhatsApp what the what is
His butt
A happy beginning
Into the dreamy creamy summer
Dreamy creamy
What the sex robots
Alexandra Thurston color