Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
MoneyGram
Collegeboard.com
Acknowledge
Dan
Just kind of think Coca-Cola
If you heard of that and no I have not I think it's what it's called Starshine Starlight yeah what's it called that I don't know it's
Exostar something
I don't know what this is selling us now
I believe it is the Coca-Cola Starlight
It's the pits
That is a beverage featuring a red color and a unique mean
Inspired by space
I mean that's that's just mean
I don't know Myspace
This tastes just
If empty it is empty it takes your breath away
Absolutely I like it
That kind of messaging and branding is somebody
It's impossible.
Actually taste like
It is
Taste testers lick it and they were like okay
I got this one now so are far more questions about space
Take me to VIP cuz this is every it's overly sweet why don't we send taste testers to space
That's a great question what is the dust taste like
Like to taste nothing
How many people would love to brag that they licked the Moon
TV
Nothing like a strong to get into a fight with somebody about like
Whether or not he's licking the Moon
I bet he didn't have the guts to take that helmet off
Yesterday I went and got the first session of my
Wedding ring hand tattoo that's right yeah it's really really nice
Appreciate it unfortunately the tattoo artist was having some
Issues you know how I have a tremor
Haha sometimes I'll be doing some fine motor work and I'll jerk around and we'll go flying everywhere
When you're tattooing
That hurts a lot more
Yeah and especially on your hand so he was having a real bad day
I could I could see that being being couple you don't want to inflict pain on people
And at the hand tattoos ever
Sensitive area there
The trident
I've tried it I've seed it I'm quite good at
Congratulations to go over with some stuff to talk about
Recently I was wondering what that weird
RAB do
Thank you that was a journey believe it was a theater major in college if I were
Call correctly so maybe this time
Onyx that time I should have my pants and classes a false flag by the other third graders thank you so much you're now policy walk
This is a long one
Warning the FDA is found that consuming Alex Jones that goes drowsiness loss of appetite blurry vision mood swings and nearest
Principal fits of Motor Vehicles are you heavy machinery under the
Under you know how Infowars affect you
If you or a loved one we need a word daily daily events are those of rainforest plus unlocked
For the safety of all involved before calling for emergency assistance thank you so much you were now if I was you want
Boundaries
Neil from blackbird
Text Carl barks The Shepherd of Mendocino thank you so much
Virtual Russian is my internet handle a 2005 is turned
Turned out to be a terrible decision
Sing yeah yeah
So
Well Where Do We Begin busy week
Weird chaotic
Stressful
Yes so we had planned on Sunday
Aleve for Austin
Broadcast like live reporters I was planning to get a hat that I can put a little card absolutely.
Puppy
The best I was definitely going to get an old rotary phone I had already looked up various ice cream place
Chicago like
Dreamy creamy summer yeah you were going to get a two-week like exploration
But unfortunately that trial has been postponed
Do to Alex's bankruptcy maneuvering
He owes me money for flights are not cancelled
I mean there's that there is a small part of it that's on you
Getting on refundable ticket
What what I'm going to get expensive tickets that you can refund
What how was I supposed to
To guess in a situation like this
Said something surprising would happen that would delay the trial something surprising that also you knew
Who was a possibility
From the jump
It's ups and downs with it throughout the week I gave this going to happen is this not going to
Like it was just
Really
Chaotic and moralizing
Past won't be able to take this trip
On Sunday and I was excited to be
They're with my parents in Austin the whole thing
So there's a little bit of deflation Maybe
So
Some of those issues also are
It's still developing and so we'll see we'll see where things
And exactly in terms of
If and how and when this trial is going to proceed
And when we have more information I sure you you all it'll be wonderful and we'll we'll get into it that's the plan
Alex needs money
Yes we do know that you know that as there's big news that is broken that people
Baby making more out of than they need to or maybe not I'm not sure
And that is the issue of Alex going to the doj and asking for immunity
Exchange for a conversation
Now I think that there is one way to look at this and that's the way I think a lot of Twitter is looking at this and it's like Alex
Flipped
Yeah
I don't know if that's the case
I mean 41
Alex did talk about on our last episode covering his show from Monday
That he was planning to go and make an offer to the FBI
And that he doesn't know anyting but he doesn't want to
Run any risk of getting in trouble and so he would do it for the deal of immunity
So I'm not certain exactly how much of this is
Is revelatory as people made
Everything good maybe obviously the people who were
Reporting on it are people who necessarily watch Infowars so they wouldn't have seen that on bonfire
If it's something that is like Alex's turned State's evidence
I don't know how much you be talking about that on his show
And this is the way I would like things to go
If I had
My druthers
Everything Alex is doing right now we have to assume
The end goal of that is to get more money
Avoid paying money right it's all about money is my point at this point in time
Yeah yeah yeah yeah and the way he makes money is by advancing bigoted politics
Erode public confidence in
Right centralized collaborative system
And at this point in time
Giving him any attention is only going to be beneficial
That's my vibe on it
Well sort of outside of that you run into is they win you over
Write something like this would be like Alex's flipped he's going to turn to tell everybody
He doesn't or if that doesn't happen it looks like
Right right
No I do think there's a possibility it's a very small possibility
Outside possibility
That Alex has realized
That some of his friends
We're up two more than he realized initially or that's possible you know reading some of these indictments of The Oath Keepers
And stuff maybe you realize like
I do have texts that are relevant to this and I didn't realize they were
Right I better just make sure I don't get arrested
Could be
Could be there's a chance
I don't think it's high but I think there's a chance of that might be I wouldn't
I maybe that's flipping I don't know if
If he was flipping
It wouldn't be Papa
Like this
So what are you doing now because it's so public it suggests to me that one he doesn't actually have anything to share
So there's no risk in him coming out with this
It's possible they're going to run with it and you know how we know cuz they did
I am so I kind of think that he's got nothing and he's trying to get headlines that aren't about Sandy Hook that he
Chicken fundraiser off of and people are obliging
Yeah
Yeah that's my feeling
Yeah it's I think that's pretty strong possibility but yeah we'll see we'll see what I
Happens with this
Just a guess
Spie the boj probably aren't interested in giving him immunity
30 from 4
I don't I don't know it it seems it seems like a weird thing for them to the humor
I mean not because like there's necessarily like giant charges coming for him just because
No
Absolutely not
Just a flat-out no whatever information you have is worth less than me saying no to you right now
Like no matter what you've got for me
It's going to be better for information the long-run to say
F*** you and so much of the information that they probably
Would need from Alex they have
From the other side other people messages
Available by spell roaches
I don't know I'm not
I don't know if this is as big of a story as some people are experiencing bad
But that's it I don't have any inside information I don't know that that the ins-and-outs of this so
I could easily not know a piece of information that isn't public and that could be the piece of information
And that changes my mind on
On everything
So we'll see we'll see
There's so many moving parts and
Is there is
A lot going on in pores but how bad they need money yeah and there's some stuff
I just know I think it's going to take
Until Monday for me to really get another episode together
Back burner
Well unfortunately
I don't have to tell you this
I
I don't have any Project Camelot I don't have
Jim Bakker
I know I've been talking a lot about this Russell Brand and I think eventually there might be maybe a Jimmy
Door episode at some point down the line branching out a tiny bit
Okay because here's a question that I have been thinking about for so long
And that question is
Well I suppose it's not a question
But it's more like
Alex rant about the devil and witches and we get all of his perspective and all of his
He's guess perspective on that what have we never done
We've never interviewed the devil
We've not done that we've not
Had a month of puddings that's what I will say to you is this
You have not interviewed the devil
Yeah but we should talk to someone
Who has
Somebody's interview the devil
We haven't seen we haven't heard from witches heard from magicians
The magical powered people
I mean maybe not specifically on the devil but we've definitely heard some people with powers on it we had a project
Quickly Magic
Can I also say that I think that our main subject Alex Jones thinks he can do magic
He has seen the devil
I think we'll find that there are a lot of similarities
Is Joe Rogan and his talk to the Clockwork elves that to do what you do DMT
But I would say we're about to talk
Well
Some witches
We are going to what it is this is an out-of-context drop for you
Give me a little idea of what's going on
Alright great so and the next question
Let's get into the role of the devil and the Saints and European magic and Witchcraft and
Do you believe in the devil and if so
Are there a lot of them
What is the Dell
What is what is
Do you believe in the devil
Do personally
Know if so
Wait. Kind of messing it up
Follow-ups
I imagine I do believe in the devil
Would you believe that there is a bunch of them
That sure
Here is what I will say to you about what we're going to talk about
That was just a stand-alone question because you need to know
Okay
We are going to talk to
Gordon
White
Who is a chaos magician
I thought it was going to be staying
Where is the host of the leak project
And I am a little bit in love with him
Okay I'm going to tell you this right now
We are not going to be talking about a monster
We're not going to be talking about evil people
I have done my best to find us
The early days of
Camelot whenever it was just pure beauty
How to have them daily
Oh and by the way I'm an anti-semite today buddy well we might not yet
How deep did you dig on these people in the craziest part about it is Gordon white is
An anti-racist
Like
Hemant one he's I mean I can't say it any other way than his words
Gordon white is a chaos magician
Shamanic practitioner and permaculture farmer based in Tasmania
His website and podcast Rune soup is one of the most popular digital watering holes in the world of Modern Magic
Tasmania Tasmanian devil
There are some spells that he will tell us about later that do require
I don't do good impression so he is he considered
A success in many spheres Gordon has worked for some of the world's largest digital and social media companies
In a life that few experience he has partied with Princess
Diamond Castle
Been mentored by a former director of the private spy agency and had a billionaire night buy him a bottle of champagne
Bring the same chameleons skills to his magical work
Gordon
Has dived in search of sharks in Lost Cities
Satin ceremony under Desert Stars
Yes why you looking for sharks in Lost Cities
I think they lost cities there's more to be found that sharks you can find sharks anywhere in the ocean
Yeah but not the most magical ones the most magical sharks obviously moved into the Lost City
And by being in the Lost Cities have game the magical power tools
Barry gleed
Has
I mean his credits are amazing it's quite a resume it doesn't get better than that
So he's he's he's like a certain he's like my age
Okay
Have you ever had a billionaire bottles at once
He said it's Alexis few experience I have actually had a billionaire Night by me
It was just sparkling grape juice
So I can't really compete
I had a millionaire dick bag buy me a bottle of champagne
I wouldn't put it in my credits
So he is being interviewed by Rex bear
Who is the host of the leak project
Which I guess is a podcast in and web series
It's words
The news media and the government this is its description of what it's
Okay
Okay the news media and the government are entwined in a vicious circle of mutual manipulation myth-making and self-interest
Journalist need crises to dramatize news
And government officials need to appear to be responding to Christ
Too often the crises are not really crazy but you ain't fabrication
The two institutions become still ensnared and assembly out of Web of Lies that the news media are not able to tell
Tell the public what is true
And the government is unable to govern effect
That's
It's credits
FleetPride Stanford complaint
About us
Write about the government and not at all about the Libra description I wouldn't know if this is a
Show or
No
Crazily enough that does not move over to Rexburg is a delight of a man
And he's going to tell us what we're going to talk about
That he's harboring these feeling
He's mad at the government but like how we all
You know like it is f****** up
Sure and if you believe in magic maybe you think it's f****** up a little bit weirder yeah I would assume so
And I want to get into real quick
But we're going to talk about
We're going to discuss
The grimoire tradition
And its relationship
Chaos Magic
The latest Consciousness science
And the return of
Animus
The role of the devil
And the Saints and European Magic
Witchcraft
A chaos magic form of remote
Viewing
A method of summoning Dragon spirits
That sounds exciting
A Sumerian method of banishing ghosts
I need that one
A complete system of stratification hello and the second part of the podcast you will be taken question
From the live audience
The ghost get out of here
Cuz you asked the question
Why does he beat what's going on with your life
My house is just full of f****** ghost
Syfy show ghost
Hades developing a recurring theme there
That smell is going to come back up
He is not going to explain to us why he needs it though that sucks it drives me insane
There's a couple things that I have to deal with here first
Too much on the plate
This if your life
Too much to get into
Second
He's pretty I think he's selling it pretty well
Like spell the penis ghosts
Spell to get dragon spirits that sounds nice
This is pretty exciting
Also chaos Magic
I can't not think of Sonic the Hedgehog the chaos emeralds Chaos Control
Find it chaos magic is very different from the sex Magic
I mean I can't really answer so much
Of that
Because
I've read Gordon White's book
Which was a fun thing for me to do
And
His
Belief system
Of what chaos magic is
It's kind of
Everything is right
Okay so so like in his book about what spells are this dude is really really brilliant
I don't know if he's brilliant so much as if he has in an eidetic memory like
He's
Absurdly well-read and he cites things that are 100% true like he is a fan of a dancer
Okay if he starts telling you about the history
He can talk for like 5 straight minutes tell you everything that actually happened like that is
That is understood
And then be like okay
Now we know what happened
Here's why magic did it you know and you're like
What
What why why did you do that
Maybe someone Put A Spell On You
That made him think of Magic's real well I'll tell you I can I can know we're going to do a couple spells
Here's what's important about the show bar
This is the most evil portion of the show
What was the production
It is
An app
Yeah
And also real quick folks I wanted to let you know my friends are betrayed like
Genius
Diatom Robert and specialist Ali project listener
This is just a really great way
Hilburn about trading of the convenience of your own home
What's nice about this
It's actually said you trade alert so I just wanted to show people real quick cuz I've been getting dozens of emails
The past few days
Wrecked how does this actually work
So I'm going to show you real quick what it is
Because I think it's Alexa
That's essentially
Super easy and a lot of people get nervous
Screen share
This right here
Boom this is
An alert that I get
Every single day
And sell this is a training that I've got about an hour ago
You can see right here I clicked on the alert
And then I opened it up in here
And this shows you exactly
The time to buy you can also get into more details of the charts
If you want to
Take the bundle opportunities or
Extremely discount right now if you want to do all the car.
Holiday but no leak project
I sent you
55%
To check it out trade like a genius.com but no leak project
Alright Matt let's let's rock and roll let's get into
Gordon
Where do we start
We already started
Now
Why
Dan
Do you think
That's a company like trade like a genius
Would choose a show that might be
A lot about wealth Magic
Put an ad for trade
I think it speaks for itself
Also assume the trade like a genius isn't necessarily a gigantic company and maybe this is something that's within their
Horizon budget I mean I think they are pretty big I'm not sure I didn't look into trade like a genius but it is what it is
Is it another one of those wealth trading apps where it's like okay according to this signal of a line that goes up when
Whenever it does this you should buy Bubba Bubba and then we get a shower and
And it's more of a
Merchant service so it's not like they get a cut of your trades
It is like you pay them five bucks a month or whatever
It's one of those kinds
Stream I find it's sketchy no matter what but also a presentation
Far more ethical than the way out 100%
100% this is these guys
Really are trying to do things as close to what they believe is the right way
As they possibly can
Now they do also have a lot of that wealth Magic
Big stuff in there
Gordon weitzbuch
The chaos protocols
Protocol
Two things
It is like an exhaustive
Collection of historical
Spells and magic and end
Hey an exploration of where they came from and who created them
And it's it's
Really really
The other thing it is
Is a millennial screed against how the government and the economy is f****** ass over and how
In the 1960s
Certain things were worth this and now we can't buy houses
Sure like it's full-on
As anarchists socialists
Do all this s*** you know what I'm thinking about I don't know if I'm making too big of a leap year
But it makes sense to me that magicians would not like our current monetary system
Because Alchemy
Works with the gold standard
Right you know
Oh my God actually let me know I have this prepared.
Walking know how right you are
I thought there was a stupid phone
The chaos protocols until 1971
The value of the dollar was pegged to a fixed amount of precious metals
Just as it was at the beginning of a fractional Reserve Bank
When the famous Voodoo is Marie Laveau and her daughter were alive in the 19th century a dollar was either
Either made with a guaranteed amount of silver
Or was convertible into a specified amount
True things right this fix the dead but I don't know what
This fix the value of a dollar into something real
Now
This is where we get at that so that
Reasonable
Now we just go
And here's a magic is involved
So if either Laveau senior or Junior had use the customary folk magical practice of putting a dollar under a candle
She would have been growing wealth from a stick
Text amount
If you have tried the same piece of folk magic anytime after 1971 then you are doing the opposite
In today's money you need almost five $5.78 to buy the equivalent of what a dollar could buy you a 1970
Such a magical act in codes in a rosian of wealth
Rather than an accumulation
Magic as like inflation
Okay
That's baffling I've read that 30 times trying to figure out what it is he's real
Really tried to say to me saying that if we went off the gold standard magic stopped working as well
Because because it was
Concretely connected to glaze resources
There's a certain
I mean there's a certain logic to that no
Disagree
I get the thought track
I get I get how this makes sense you someone like
Who has that those beliefs came up with it
Yeah well I was
Making a joke
It's kind of like her
You would make a joke about like
Like a libertarian
Like being against roads until they make flying cars
Nobody
It's also a little weird for that to be the gold standard
Is Rhodes
The government shouldn't be paying for it
Lead back to the gold standard somehow
So
I'm going to tell you this about Gordon in case that that little stretch of
Dense text didn't make it clear he is a talker
He's a long-winded talk
Andrex
Gives him I mean
7/8 minutes of uninterrupted speech at a time
Then he cannot stay on topic here ambles about consistently and I can't like really
Play mat to anybody and I'm not going to put you
See-through five minute
So what I've done is I took the next
8 Minute stretch of time
Where he speaks
Uninterrupted
I don't be one of those little time montages for YouTube for cut little Supercut
All right here we go
Gordon
Where do we start
I didn't know I mean you you held up a number of
Books there
That
I mean maybe we should
Can start with what a grandma is
Is it really about
Soy
I mean originally
It comes from the French
Related to the
Same
Read grandma from
It kind of gives you so
What's an armoire
Inside
Disturb Greenwich
Only applied
The city of idea
A cooling up
Demon Zane
Either one
So that's cool that's the swan book of anuria
Inside
How to create the umbrella of gremlins
Solomonic
Whiskey Pete's like Alyssa key
And you have other ones
Scholastic
That's like the maid one that's the one that everyone knows
Big Daddy
Psychological
Modes of
Overcooling thing
Coronavirus has like
Angels and sewing in it
You would do this
Abiquiu Sullivan
The other one
That was what we call a stolen money
They pretend
Someone
Perkins
The Bible
Bye
Demons and
Status ideas
Cooling
Spirit
Holy Cross
What to do the bidding of
Good's if
Is why so many
Okay
Right sure I have a few problems I think there's so many
Well I don't know about the ethics of enslaving demons
Right
Demons
Sure but what does that do to you to enslave a thing
That actually will come up later on
Oh yeah
I don't like how all the point I noticed that you are essentially thinking like a chaos Magician of the highest caliber
Maybe I listen to too much stupid s*** maybe it's just that
Magic and everything that we talked about are essentially the same concept which is
Whatever I think is true is true
Sure sure
Yeah and I think one of the things about magic that's kind of different than
Some other
Conspiracy stuff to be a system
Imagine
And I would like in order for people to like really try and make their argument there needs to be a system
Where is Lake with conspiracy theories there is the absence of the system there's the beginning and the conclusion
And then the middle is like
There's no Global let's start doing all this stuff
There's a beginning and like a thought
Kind of
I can kind of see that
Yeah
But it's still it's long it's long
And he just keeps going so Sullivan put demons in books and then Angels help you remember things
Essentially what he saying over 8 minutes
Grimoires
A couple of different things but generally speaking we're talking about books
That have history or magic spells
Bien
Do I associate that word with Harry Potter
Is a famous Skyrim has grimoires might be
Are the traditional like high fantasy magical term for
I think it's probably Skyrim that thing
Now
We heard a lot about Solomon
Okay now are our hosts Rex bear
He comes back from this eight minutes right where he lets go and speak uninterrupted
With this
Okay
Now even the word Solomon somebody brought up to me 1
You're right
Saw
Sun
Oh
And then mon last Solomon
Me like sun in the Moon
So that's a
I don't know what sounds like an archetype
Name this tune
It's bringing
The light in the dark
Together
Damn
Deep
Right cannot Love More
That he just that Gordon went
So long
And the first thing this dude he has to come back with his like
Somebody told me like
Soul and then Moon
Yeah
Well I mean like this
Not
Moon most other older languages isn't like a loon
I like more of that
Synetic
Then son
Yes so you could get
You know
I don't buy it I mean it's more at this level of thinking from him is more like if you were like Solomon
You know solo and then mon from like Pokemon so it's like one Pokemon
That level of s*** right there
A lot of the folks that we end up looking at do like word association games
And I can relate
Oh yeah absolutely
You're not far off
That just make a little connections that aren't really there but people go at work sometimes it sometimes
So you can see that we're clearly deerling with a disparity of expertise between our hosted
Whimsy on one hand
Loquacious mess on the other
It doesn't get worse there their relationship
It just it just gets nicer
I guess it's interesting
I think you even told me this once when I
I discussed how I read some
Passages out of
The dad in it
Spit me out I had
Dream it's weird
Start happening
I quit messing with it
Was it you that said well that's because you're messing
What the most powerful magic in the world
It might have been
We talked about the Tibetan book of dead as well as the Egyptian Book of the Dead and how they're different
Okay
This is an important part of chaos magic both 100% accurate
Even if they disagree with each other
They're still right this is another thing about magic everything is right
It's pretty tough to to wrestle with
I enjoy
Is
I had some freaky dreams
Bicycle the Tibetan Book of the Dead
Come on man you too much ice cream before bed or like is there another variable he's got a lot of
I've got a lot of freaky dream
Sure you dreams
I have a copy of that book of the somewhere
It's not affected my dream really doesn't
No
Is anything that Rex comes back at him with he's like
Yeah that sounds right that sounds good
And then it just keeps going
Like I don't
Siquijor two-word rexha the entire time
I think it's a necessity of collaboration and mutual support
More than there is an improv
Oh yeah
If you start to split hairs and be like no
Sometime you ruin the premise
The whole get the whole interview stops everybody just goes
What I don't understand
Right
Conceivably if magic were real you be able to cast a spell prove you're right
Unfortunately we do. Cassidy fell down the show
Because we be messing around with too much power
I understand that
Prove you wrong but I can't talk about the thing that I know
Like I have all the evidence but I can't show it to you alright
A boy Rex bear continues
I mean I can't even describe some of what he's doing here just it just easy to the light
You can
Some funny things
Mess around with a note to do what I'm saying
Some things will happen
Well certainly I've had my fun and I just read a few of the scriptures and
Anyway yeah like the one giving mouth
That was an inch
Hieroglyphics
They're having a little bit of fun in that one but hey why not I mean
It's your time to pass I mean
Anyway so
Anyway I'm not going to get too deep into that
It looks like he's
He's getting all those like the Pharaohs getting
Some action
During that certain
Ritual witch
Variance
I think he's already in the car
Cardenas in Costas
So
But then somebody brought up it was like hey man that's that's like the most powerful time of your life
Lady getting f***** in the coffin
Pennsylvania's responses like man
That's the most powerful time of your life
Just sounds like dude
Talking about drugs 100% Lookout
Exactly
Hey man look at
I know that you smoke weed before but this stuff is
It'll mess you up
Be careful yeah I'm not saying don't I'm not saying just be just be responsible
It's not going to stop talking with you everybody would say that about mushrooms
Cochlear like 1718
Where you like what
With what what
You got f***** in a coffin
How much magic and he has so many problems that he's never does not
It explained it wasn't having all this fun and f****** in conferences how all the ghosts showed up in his house right
Call Dan
Here is where we're going to get into some real trouble okay
You continue to be a witch
Which is funny on this episode
Because once again you have brought out
Drugs being very important yeah tell you I know you've gotten one of the answers right but I wanted to look in
Into some chaos Magic
And Gordon explains that there are three effective ways to become invincible okay can before we get to this
Chaos spell
Regular it would have been more Arcane if he went with a k
I thought there might be something weird or something
Georgia gas
You can try you've already got one drugs one is drugs
That's the best way to do it wow who's the most effective way that's number one
Say that this is a bad message to people messing around with drugs worth
Never say it makes you images on he says
Specifically the most effective route to becoming Invincible is to take a high dose of psychedelics in a suitable ritual environment
So he does want you to be safe
Or at least it could make you feel
I think that's kind of the boys right
Doesn't make you invent
Let me guess okay
Replace of another human
No animal
Drinking blood
Sacrifices are a historical then really
Is booze included with the triplets
To do magic when they're like
Falling over
I'll tell you the second most effect
Okay lighting a candle
And reciting the Lord's Prayer backwards every night for 3
I was not going to guess that most effective
It's it high dose of psychedelics
Maybe just like a candle
Okay alright
Sure of course
I think I know this
Think I know that
We have to
Run really fast with three blocks
Haha and then do 6 push ups
Climb to the top of a roof
Run around the top of a building 28
2X
2A can't be one egg
I feel like that would make you invincible
The third most effectively is the preliminary invocation or headless right
If chop your head off
But you are not a holy guardian angel
Let me give you a little bit of idea of what the Headless right is
Very detailed instruction
Face North
Touch your left temple and then your right temple with
The parchment
And read aloud what is written on it six times
Eyebrows
Buscema taxable
Lalo
6 *
Okay alright then say I'm not going to do it because I don't want to say get shrekt eternally invincible
Do you want to accidentally
You coming out
Then say subject me to subject to me all Damon
So that every Damon which is not spelled like
Weather Heavenly or Ariel or Earthly or Subterranean order Ezreal or aquatic
Might be obedient to me and every enchantment and Scourge
Which is from God
Okay
Eagles on move from facing north to facing the direction of Orion and continue
I stopped and you had this one who created other than having a great about you that you created the light and darkness that you are outside
All red robe
It continues
Sure
Several pages on
This quite a quite a ritual with all power and authority of the one who spoke truth and who had made it
So you see it's a long ritual yeah this is
This is a problem for me for a couple reasons here's the first one
What does it mean to be Invincible does that mean you can't be killed
You can't be harmed in any way
It is
The least explain part of his book second might be a help
To you second question
What do you think being Invincible is I think it's a really important question
Listen for what you think you got out of
I think that's the only way to know if you were successful or not
Second question how long does invincibility last
At forever
Really forever
Really
All right I mean you got the book right here I can email it to you
Well I would say that this has not worked ever
Because we don't have a bunch of invisible people walking erect actually I can't prove that
Exact
The magician always win
Determined incivility spell it really wouldn't be helpful if its 6 pages long
Use that spell if you need it
Probably soon I mean the one that tells one of them takes 39
You know you can't just whip that one out with your with your old-fashioned
True
And the other one is like doing ayahuasca
What you can do in a hurry that is true
Sure it's harder to do drugs really quick and safe and fine
More of a challenge
Okay so now we want to get into some comparing with Alex right because we're talking about the
We also need to talk about the afterlife
Brian talked about
Go ahead
Compare notes
Might be a
Brought
Definitely
Who point
The books
What's the date today
Was it was this idea
Can you die
The passage
So good
You have to kind of wns
The judge
I'm just weighing of the heart
The swamps you
Get through that
Snakes
And all these kind of things are they
The movement of the Soul
From the Buddy
Requires noches
Router that it's not
It doesn't necessarily follow that just
Is your dad you get
You you have to sit up
Sure
Yeah so
Alex believes that when you die
If you did good
You can go to heaven
Right
Theologians believe you to sit with the harp and that's not true
Rye Rye
So
He's the kind of agrees with him right
Todai
Bright and then crawl through a swamp with snakes
Write questions about that what what question
You could you possibly have about that
Are these living snakes are they like real snakes snakes
System cuz them things to eat they reproduce be like ecological changes
Is there afterlife
What if there's an invasive invasive species rights it starts and it's nicer to people
Are you going to need to artificially Brigade
Obviously you will
It's a complex system it's like a golf course I think I feel like you could just much more easily have
Fake snakes
Making fake snakes
Now let's get into some fun we got to talk about ghosts
I love it
Storehouse
Or old
Hose
American
Is a book of
Looking at
European
She calls
She calls it
The Wild app
A really good
Where you going
Adversarial
Booze that makes the devil
A really bad
He's kind of
Mysterio theme
And untie
I'm so excuse category that
So
This is what it's like
To get to we need to talk about ghosts with this guy
The words that mediately before this are like okay what do you think about ghosts
And so he's like okay first thing you got to know
Here's what the devil is herbalist believes that the devil is the natural adversary
And now we move so I don't think that when you say that real adversary it evokes the idea of whether to me
Cuz I've never seen a storm and been like
That's my anime anime anime of my enemy in the storm's I don't have an adversarial relationship
Kinship with weather
But
And I don't feel it does with me either
If you believe that everything is some sort of
Force or action or spiritual spirit
In this situation
Is
Really whatever you think
It is the idea of an adversary is what the devil is
So whatever you think you're doing if somebody's trying to stop you that's the devil
Play I can
I can kind of get into that a tiny bit as long as you don't go too far with that stink
I know there's a lot of there's a lot of this that's just like
Regular old self-help stuff
Yeah and then you like the crystal or something cuz water as long as you can stay like sir to self
Aware of what
Your
Video using these ideas for
I don't know if it's necessarily terrible to be like my laziness is the devil
No and it is it is kind of
That is kind of what gordon-white is trying to do in and I think woody woody
His main goal is
Right
He's trying to create a system wherein you can be a good purse
You know
You can
Care about other people you can do all of this other stuff
You can fight racism he's he's a gay man and what's so important to him is the way that the LGB
Btq Community is being treated right now
Like he's Furious about all this
Beyond that I don't know he might be a Monster who haven't either covid annihilus but he's a magician so what do you
Spell viruses were worth $5
38 cents more than they are today
So he's trying to create a unified
If everything is true magic
Religion
All of this stuff
Then we can stop
Fighting about it all
If if I can tell you that Islamic beliefs are one hundred percent true
And Bentley's Wommack magical beliefs are 100% true and that
God and Christianity
Everything
Everything has something that he pulls from
So his basic idea and let me try and take you
Let me try and take you through his thought process
Okay
If you just look at
Least likely stuff
Then you'll be escaped
Thor's Magic
You're like
There's okay you didn't actually
Perform that mirror
Think I could be skeptical about the most
What if you are the person who doesn't want to be scrapped
Alright
And you want to be the smartest person in the room who always wins every argument
Then what you do is you seek out
The most likely like the most credible
Magical thing that you can think of
A magical thing that is so credible that it can get a lot of people
Otherwise be like
No of course it's not a miracle
I have no idea
Okay
What's the most credible thing
Shroud of Turin or whatever
Who cares
Hieroglyphics magic or whatever whatever it is you want it's got to be ancient
Right
So
Then you can get into arguments with other people who already believe Magic
And be the smartest guy in the room
And since you've got these concrete examples that to you prove magic is real
You can work back out again
Because if magic is real on this most credible example
The now I can
Can point you to that that
Miracle that is obviously bulshit
More likely to believe it because you already got like
That is what's going on here
Fun so he hits you with so much that eventually your you're
Ability to fight Baxter Road it right exactly
So he keeps going though
Now we speaking of that
Do you feel that the ancient
Egyptian
The
Let's go
For somebody
That the modern
Theros
That we've uncovered
They've done an incredible job
Preserving their bodies but
It seems to me like they were mimicking
Something even before that maybe a scientific
Turned into a a magical ritual
Versus
Your magic and science
Same thing but real magic worse
Where is there's the this way do match
Give you that good feeling oh yeah ha that's amazing
But it doesn't affect so I'm just wondering if
You think that the
There was a original race or race of beings
What are not from here somewhere else
But we're here on this planet
Time in China
That were using their bodies and then preserving it in a way that they could like go into the
Different dimension
Like when we pass and then bring that knowledge back or I mean
What do you think the purpose
Go to timer
Super Justin Quest
It's
My favorite my favorite part
And you heard
Give a little swear of that time and space
He does a little
Time and space movement course like he's waving his hands and I like going to sell it
Very very fun I don't know what to think about
The question
I don't know if I care
Magic and science can be the same thing
No
Well you are you know why cuz that ritual involves putting apartment up to the temples of your head
You have to test the hypothesis
I think a lot of people have not invincible so maybe those are
Test cases will be the control group on this one
I won't do the spell it right if I'm invincible so far so good
Okay so
With this next clip
He is going to explain a little bit of like how summoning spirits and all that works
And our host is going to really enjoy the snowblower
But it's also not it's also
Like the oldest
First thing we've ever done
100.
Are appointed
Not have two men
Ringing of the spirit
But to be the thing that
Spirits to doodle
Amber Ruffin
Yeah absolutely that's
Did you just
Maybe I had some sinks their soulmate
And some some mind expansion
That was wonderful thank you
What does it mean
People
And they are often times referred to as the igigi
You didn't tell me that earlier they brought up the verb
They really hadn't brought up the bird people maybe was all fair
It was more of like I mean
They didn't bring up the bird people in that conversation where we saw the Pharaoh getting a b****** in the coffinger
He then says
And we've also seen these hieroglyphics that are like bird people so I mean Beyond him saying
There's a picture of a bird
There's also the the Ruto right Zelda
Garuda from Final Fantasy
Yeah there's a bird people
Where can I get we're going to talk more about birds in The Matrix
He's trying to say
Is
There, I'm pretty sure that he's trying to talk about four-dimensional space know how if you got a plan it it's a sink
It's a gravel
So he's trying to do that for reality
We got sunk down into reality man
Is more powerful
Until you sorta out of the
Conversation for a second guess
He does that a lot
Yikes
So Gordon's Roland
Gordon's getting into it
Okay
Why am I listening to anthropologist
To strawberries to know this
If they don't know it and I do
Anyway
Like you said maybe it's it's like behind the scenes people finding it
What happened
This this so little money and
So much comfort
If you don't
Find
The proverbial
Your career is over
So he's talking about how in Indonesia
They found
Hieroglyphics
That day that he thinks are older than they're the oldest ones that people say
Publicly
And then there is also
Hieroglyphics in Australia
That might be even older
Oh my so he thinks that people are stupid for not knowing that these are Australian hieroglyphics
Might be a little bit older
Okay and
He goes on to be like see the problem with journalism right
Is that you always have to find the most something you always have to make it so big and everything no self-aware
Fairness in terms of reading this f****** book
Write how everything is the most powerful shityoucan Do-Right
Uw's is trying to get Medline
Exactly he's chasing the very thing that he thinks it is and in order to get published
Slimeatory I mean it sounded like he was complaining about like archaeology
Don't find the sunken city then you don't have a job
I would say to him
That is not true
There are all sorts of archaeology departments
Around the world
We better pumpkin pie going to close down
The dean is up my ass we haven't found this f****** sunken city yet I agree that finding the Second City whatever
To be a big fight
Right
Noah
Looks like it's find Atlantis or else their funding dries up except maybe in some kind of like
I don't know if it's
A quest being done by magicians privately-funded
Progressive the next level sure absolutely
And he continues he's got more complaints
About mainstream
Stuff you know
It doesn't matter what you find
And it has to be like
Sing in the world
And then you if you read the extra
Text of it
Still correct
Where they do tax
Spider monkey
Just s***
Science journalism
No one no one
Less than
I understand science
You don't understand it less than a chaos magician though
I mean magician probably but
I'm driving I guess if his argument is that like
Headlines are sensationalized
Sure
I agree
It's it's so fun
How mundane it is
He's like
Oh man I'm so powerful I'm such a powerful position I can become invincible
Invincibility
What's wrong with it well nothing actually
The implication is that anybody who knows these ways to become invincible must have
Taking the time to get invincible well you would think
Yeah but
If you know the invincibility spell
I should be free to attack
You think
Now here's the problem
Okay what if I don't want to mess with magic
Alright we're talking about demons
Demons spirits
God
Which is what I like I like his angle on so much of this
This dude is
Like again everything is real so he believes in God he believes in he believes in gyms for sure
Of course you know he doesn't have this like all you need to worship God or like it's more like
Little buddy of mine
If I call him he'll help me get my car out of the snow like that's the kind of relationship
You have with God in this scenario
Similar
You know what I mean yeah but also probably disrespectful
He's like I've met gospel going to be onto
And so
He's proven that science journalists are full of s***
Here he's going to prove some more stuff
My bank
Is that
It looks at the
This stuff
And then for no
Will fullback
Materialistic
So we have
I'm good headed people go back to
Seven-year-old male
Hey bud headed
We have Garuda
So we have
Hindu cosmology
Eagle head
And that's before we get the whole way over to the
So
And by the way this
We actually have
Marcos
Down the southern code
Brandon Easter is
Hopping around in a cross
With dealing with
The same culture
So that's the fish
Are they
Spices that sufficiently attractive be genetic
Flow of the bird people
Yeah so the problem
With too many materialists right is that they fall back on falsifiable science
Haha
Exactly now you've got it
That is our issue our problem with materialism is that you should be explaining it with magic or them
Materialism that I have chosen
Materialism
Evidence
It's nothing compared to
I say some things and then I feel weird
100%
Let's
Here we're going to hear about an old friend of ours
Actually
Oh wow
Butthead
Beans Indian
Spirit world
Stop right there
Imaginal
Physical and imaginary imaginary cuz that makes it sound like they're not real
Imaginary
The whole thing kind
Bulls in
To play Sweet
It's the classic
Landspeeder
Helicopter
Because you could look at the anomaly
And it definitely
But if you
Is lead only
Materialistic
You end up
Zecharia sitchin
Nuclear-powered Rucker
Spirit world
It is
It is some kind
And so if you see this bird headed
Everywhere
What I can tell you
Tentatively
That idea
To get oldies
One price
That point
Well
What is it
Does it need
Tubi
I didn't need to be a physical
Birdman
Espirito Santo
Drugs
In dreams
Who knows. I think it's better I think
More
That is better
Satisfying way
Taking
The anomaly
Be exciting and unusual things
History of it most serious
Without having
Make statements for
Seandainya
Divisive
Skeleton
We still we know about
We tackled but yeah like I said there's there's no public knowledge of
Lovebird
Skeletons so until there is
We got to keep question we got to keep your tips
So should be private knowledge of
Bird skeleton
Big butt listen
We know we don't need to go around explaining things like zecharia sitchin with
Boulder cars or bird skeleton beings or whatever
And his response is like
Not yet
But if we keep looking I bet there are
The criticism of zecharia sitchin Izzy's to materialist
Bizarre notion
Also
Yeah if I were this guy that's exactly the route I would take
Spirits or whatever
Great loophole great cop out
Cuz I mean I guess like you could just say like okay so like all these cultures also have flood moti
And stories they had everybody tripped balls and thought about floods
You got it or whatever
Great
We can explain all of history and everything through folklore
Yes 100% through two people got really high and saw stuff
It is it is kind of a I find it very silly to me but to think that
Bird-headed beings only go far in the imaginary sense
Only go as far back is however a lot like
40000 years the first time that a bird headed being was imagined was like the first few people
Well that we're alive we're like
Batman wouldn't be weird if you had a bird head like I was at like humans work
Flashlight
And I definitely found a way
I think
The bird headed people is kind of a pretty easy jump to make
Cuz you thinking about like a birds
Can fly blind be fun to fly
If there's probably a person with a bird head
Moving on
It's not a far jump
Uber database
Especially if you're in early artist painting
Okay
So now let's get past all of our fun little openings because we're here to talk about the devil
I forgot about the devil you're talking about the devil
What is the devil
Sprouts Babel
Do you believe in the devil and if so
Are there alot of them what is the
So I mean this is
A huge a like one
As well as degree Marco sost
Premium members
Is botan 1H
And I should give it to look at the beginning of this year
The devil is
A bunch of
That was bunched up a bunch of stuff
Great
Kind of hurts of the definite articles the
Being in front of it but
Okay I'm listening
Yeah I mean that's kind of where we're going and where we're coming from with every
Anything that is
Is probably a bunch of
The operating principle is
Short story long
Also avoid being too specific specific
The Devils also this and the devil's this specificity is for the materialist that's the problem with the material
Century things so let's keep hitting we need to hear more about the devil what
Play the devil.
Double
Got to think of this hypothetical Portuguese
His grandmother
Tanjiro this
Senor
Daughter is getting married
Affectless
Sun if there blacks
And you think
You should marry the
The traitor
I have a much better life
Semi-literate
And by semi-literate
The devil is the lord of the
The devil is set
By God
Trulia
And so
Yes you want to
To worship the Dead
If your
Like because the different leagues
And and he's literally go to the office
Like the devil office Jesus
The hobo
I need his set by God
To rule this
That means if you have personally concerned
You take them to
I'm so on a Sunday you might go to Mass
And then
You might leave your family and puddle of Into the Woods
Offering
To the devil
I killed effect
Hotel have him
Have he's in
In milgram's
That's
Very different options
Huge drop-off
Kill the guy or the zika virus be less interested
There was a really worldly those two options
Yeah I think it also there is something
The Bible about God being a jealous God
Dinner
I don't know if you'd be super thrilled you go into the woods
Dude some ritual offering kill this guy wants to marry your daughter Mary
You're some reason Portuguese grandma
Google I don't ask me why
But you do understand what the devil is
Obviously
Subway mid-level administrator for Earthly issues
Write so well I mean maybe
Oh no
But you do have it
Unholy Triumph
Lucifer Beelzebub
I need not necessarily
Summon
At all
But those names
Because they the Kings
Those names of
So you should have
Spirits in the name
Depends on the book
But they'll have gift
They might be
Categorized
Into one of these three
Brutus
Is Lucifer is
The king in spirit
And so
The idea of the devil is the
The storehouse
The devil you find more
Invoke Magic
But you find more loose
The grimoire
Even though no one in the greenhouses
Is worshipping
No one is
So you got all the different names for the devil are all different things Lucifer belzebub
Same Old Scratch has different guy has different people for you
So if you if you get this correctly
Right I don't know if I get this correctly it's like that for me
Warner also I'm going to call Beelzebub, now you're not actually going
Sure you don't got to sit for Beelzebub
But I will call Zelo Toth
Because he's the one who has enough power to call the Lesser Spirits so you're sort of needs to sign off on it
911 dispatch hello baal-zebub here
If you send a spirit over please
And also
One thing
It also a bunch of others
Okay I'll really any of those and you can't even call him
You can't call him
You could but he woke up
So you clearly understand the devil now right
I guess just make up anything and that's probably with explanation
Him because he knows more than you
The devil
Oh no
Gordon but he is the devil
So this is
This is just
This is where it gets really really good and things start to go absolutely Wild
If you look at the
About a third of
Of Souls
Particularly now and I actually say the numbers
About a third of spirit
Hang around
Seems like about a third of the
And I would argue and
Just a guess
But that number is
Increasing
We are
We die and such
Secular Way We Were
Sure
So for so much of this entire interview
He has been basing all of this stuff on historical books
Right
Magic books everything that is is fake
You know
And then all the sudden he's just like you know what
Scientifically speaking after we've done a study from Johns Hopkins
A third of spirits
Start making it anymore
Hot take
I think that numbers going up buddy probably a terrifying increase in overall so
Sticking around
And that's a problem
Well it's going to be a problem for ghost housing that goes housing prices
2008 all over
I know it can be brutal
Right
Ghosts will be able to
Very susceptible to nft
That's going to be a problem,
Oh and they have unlimited money because it's not tied to anything physical anymore
True
And now they all they want to do is
Catch Pac-Man
Swell
For a while
Sometimes they really don't want to
That's true every
Alright so now
Beach at
Has gotten involved
And we are going to see a little bit of how the host is reacting to them
So kind of crazy
I find that
Historically
Me too
And I also just wanted to make a
Comment real quick because
Ninety-nine percent of what I'm reading in the wife chat here is awesome
And there's always somebody that may be ignorant
And when I use the term ignorant that just means on inform
There's there's one person that's the
Having a real hard time
With I guess me personally they they seem to think that I'm a
A black magician
So
What is a time it must be the blue blockers
15 Jesuit
That's both
Yeah yeah because I don't believe that the Earth is shaped the way they tell me and you
Needs to be so it's okay I get it I understand
Are internet
Everything's real on the internet forum
Jesus it's so much of theirs
Yeah
He does not explain
Which
Shape he thinks the Earth is
Okay I don't know
Yeah I think that there is a strategic thing that sometimes people have knees
Turtle veins do that that is the
Responding to criticism that is like you're a black magician because that keeps the criticism even within the word
World that they live in
The criticism of this is a bunch of nonsense I'm glad for you if this
Does something empowering for your life
But you might be over selling something
I think that criticism probably
Much less likely to respond to Where is the
I'm a black magician is just like
That's in game credits
And II
I think that's kind of fun I mean do you think he's a black magician what do you mean
Alright well what's the distinction let's find out what a whether or not he's a black magician
So so anyway no I don't practice black magic
And I don't really have time
I'm doing LeapFrog Jake is at Blackmagic kind of freaks me out because
If there is a cause and effect
If there is a cause effect
If your doing dark things dark things Mike
Back to you
I mean it's science
There was one time that I got on eBay
Back in 2008 I got a hundred bucks I was so excited
Does a 1930
When I do
I immediately knew
Something was up man
Real dark energy and I had it for
A couple of mine
And I remember the whole time I had it the energy in the house
Stephen Moore.
Northwest
We found out after we sign the lease
That the five previous people
Or the five previous couples that live there before us inductive or Steam
The neighbors that live there for 4.
I got this book
And I can just
No Mana
I don't know people are doing something negative with it
Before what
Like I could
Send
Dark Energy I was thinking
Bad thing just
1815 Campo
That gives a
90s
Something is
What's up man to admit
The shore like
II
I think that is a valid
Unlikely
Experience
Sure
Don't mess with those books absolutely not
Screw someone up later
Five previous couples got divorced
That probably has something to do with it I'm salute right
And then we got the book
That 90 years to be messed with any power
Dark Forces that I think it's probably likely that he's correct
Yeah I think there's no way around it
It's the only conclusion I mean
If there is a cause and effect
Obviously
Do you do evil things
I would be a black magician but I'm too busy with leak project I just don't have the time
Boots
I think there's also something
Quaint
Tough to deal with about the idea that if You Can Do Magic
It's accessible for $100 on eBay
Ivory everything about this
I love that
And and here is your so important this is 22 Rex
Okay
This is the only time he interrupts in the entire hour and 10 minute long interview
And it's to continue this f****** story cuz it's not done yet
Real quick I just got to say so I get it away right
The day that I gave it away
My wife had no idea I had this book
The day I give it away
She goes
She comes in the house this year
It feels lighter in here
You noticed
Oh yeah by the way
Cookbook I bought and now we didn't have it yeah
Coincidentally she also bought new blinds that day and we had our Windows boss
Track lighting
The reason you feel better
This hundred-year-old book I bought on eBay I got rid of it
Sumrall MS
Oh you got a promotion is probably not important I have a great lunch
I have a part of my friend it was a delightful time I'm feeling a light on my feet
Yikes he's not a black magician
Important really know what that means except for it someone who does Black Magic but now I don't know what black magic means
That's interesting because Gordon's going to explain a little bit how it works
Nothing gets you off the hook
To be tomorrow
Does that make sense
You can pray for someone
And in the same thing this is easier benign or even
They are not
They are spirits
Deeply ambivalent
It's not I'm not saying hey everyone it's fine and it's
It's not that at all
But it doesn't necessarily make you evil
I want to do it
You could be evil
It is evil to pray the gay away
Like that's literally eat
So you
Not get
Nothing
Lets you off the hook
For being immoral
What
I mean I'm glad that he doesn't believe in Prague the gay away
I'm happy for that
But I don't understand the distinction between
It not being necessarily evil to pray for someone's death
It's just not recommended
I don't know I don't get it I don't get I don't get the distinctions I also there's a bigger question that I have
To be like alright magic can make you invincible
But it's not able to UK there's no magic spell you can do to reverse cause and effect
It seems like that's bizarre well I mean you can
Also let me
But you can break all the rules of reality but the that way
Let me disagree with that premise internally
If you're Invincible you have
Broken cause and effect
Believe
No that's that's a contradiction of classical
Tell me the physics of it
Defisit cousin
Probably get rid of
Except when we.
Okay sometimes it's we do but sometimes we do
And when I say is when we do right and what I say is what we do we do at science
That's how it works in his velocity it doesn't come off very because he's like
It's okay to pray
For somebody's death well it's not advised
I mean what are you trying to say
Is that
A black magician is not somebody who practices
Black magic
It is that
Magic is a tool
And you are a person who is using that tool
Aloha so if you do bad things
It's not the magic that did it
You know you just talked to some Spirit or very ambivalent about how they treat people
Boxer on the planet
So you can't
You can't be like nah nah it's cool I'm a magician you have to you still have to be a moral person
That's his that's his idea of magic there
There's sort of an ambivalent morality to praying for someone's death
Yeah but not for praying away the gay
Fine
There's I feel like
Specific
I feel like there's a cause and effects and it the causes listening to this and the effect was me hitting my head on the wall
The chat has some agreement with you here
Is what I named this clip Ono
And yet
If they died
Surely that's what it was
It doesn't necessarily follow.
Thank you or
It doesn't mean you're losing your
So either
Doing a dream and that's it red
That's it
How dare you say I didn't bandyrowe somebody else time do you out I wasn't even me I don't care
Kummerspeck
Whatever you want
Exact
Play The Devil can enter your dreams
Rather you doing
Great
Turbo now never sleeping again
Strike Back
You kept getting little little notes for people who likes are you a black magician and he's he's sensitive
It's not something that he realizes I think was people
Yeah okay cuz it was like a little bit of a
It was a little like
Meme they happened in the chat for a little while the fact that he
He's a little overreacting a little bit
Now we're finally getting to something that Rex needs purse
Ghost Yubel mobile you got it
The Vanishing go
Sumerian method of banishing ghost
I need to know this one
One of the things I
I kind of delight
In doing an
How you find this in
A couple books
I just really like the idea
Of looking at
Kind of like that
The dead butt
Bet Sistas
For the most part they are spells for Deadpool
Use that. As in
Where's disability from Sumerian one
The pier to do
Ap2 used
I've confused
Big dogs
Demons
Might scare the Dead
And I just
Love playing with
But like getting rid of
What
Getting rid of
Negative
We're getting rid of
Icky
Spirit prison
They never get enough
I have listened to that one I play that on repeat for a while just like
Negative energy is such a dumb word
And you're like there's no way that you can
Go to Iggy Spirit price
Who's in the house
And be like well clearly I've nailed it I've been proved on negative energy
So they can fuse large dogs with spirit
Does that mean the spell is like sit
A little bit
And also I
She doesn't explain it but he does say I really like playing with
Call Keys
I think he thinks or I think he's insinuating
Then he is summoned to the spirits of these dogs
And place with them regularly
Great
That is what I think is he is one of your
You say it sounds whimsical
If you're doing magic to imagine that you're playing with dogs that aren't there
I mean
Seems harmless
Well let's let's take a look at that Sumerian spell I just want to make sure that you
You get it correctly
So I eat it is not Sumerian as far as I can see from the chaos product
This it is
Greek magical papyri
So
It goes something a little bit like
Hale hermanubis
Tumi Ojai 10 Mighty 1090 Stir of Secrets for those in the Underworld
Affair of those in a mentillo chief physician
Thought of Osiris whose face is strong
Among the gods
You should appear in the Underworld
Before the hand of Osiris
You should serve The Souls of a beat us in order that they lived through you these Souls the one secrets of the underworld
You are Anubis
You are herpes
You are the one who went forth from the heart of the Great agathodaemon
The father of the father of all the gods
Come to the mouth of my vessel in dwell in this forum dedicated to
And receive my offering and praise
Sister Wives
The sayings of whose mouth shall come to
Did you notice that it's quieter in here it is a lot quieter in here
That voice that's always saying you suck
Spirit presences
This show isn't about lifted from us
We had to suddenly stop
Okay we have cleared out the ghost presents
I've been
Powerful enough to help Rex from a distance is what
Adolescents should be taken care of he can just play this
Personally I don't know it if I were to believe in ghosts which I'm
Much like the spirit realm I'm a
I don't know if I'd want them to leave really
You know like if there are ghosts in there is a way of communicating with them
Just want to talk to him
Be the friend
I mean
I think
Be
Problem there
Is
Once you become the person who talks to ghosts friendly like all the ghosts are going to come to you
ABC the show ghost
Seems fun
Have you seen the Sixth Sense doesn't sound fun at all, just say that I've only seen the commercial for the show Joseph
Looks fun
But I do.
Well play on Survivor
No Giver see that one Michael j.fox
Man he fights ghost
I want to fight a ghost he's divorcing Thirteen Ghosts
I don't know if it was
No wasn't alright dude well we've gotten to the end
We've got our Sumerian spell let's bring it home
Alright we're going to close the show
Practical Magic
The people can use every single day
Yes and in this case for wealth
Tyco's and wealth
Tell me about Midtown
Sign me up
Right on board and thank you so much again I really appreciate it check it out ladies and gentlemen
Be excellent to each other
Hit the Bell you need hit that Bell to get access to the wifey
And be the change
To Wayne's World references in 30 seconds
Ashwin be excellent to each other is impressive
There it is
That is how we bring it all also Practical Magic was a Sandra Bullock movie from the late night
Yeah but he's he's giving you wealth magic okay that's what you looking for
You are looking for I mean and and his book is absolutely nuts
You know like
73 quarter to the bottom of your shoe and walk around 46 miles
But also here's the problem with Alan Greenspan
He talks about Alan Greenspan in this in the chaos protocol
Cuz you know it's that kind of s***
We now know what the devil is
Which is everything disagree I don't know what the devil we now know how to get rid of spirits
I guess we did it
Is there anything else you learn today
I don't know
Looking overwhelmed I feel like you don't believe in magic anymore
Anymore
No I mean like my position on a lot of his stuff is
Like I don't need to be too cruel if people do believe
Even some stuff that
It helps them in their life and I think that
There is there is an element of
Benign or rationality that I think can be fine and maybe even positive in people's lives
I resent some
Of this stuff
Also though
And I find I don't know
Especially when you're
Maligning other people in scientific theories
Sing a turtle
A clearly is a subscription platform you saying his premium members
And he's offering classes on wealth magic yep you know these kinds of things I find distasteful in many of the sea
Same ways that are our right-wing scam
Folk are distinguished from people who like maybe have some kind of
Ritual thing that they like to do it somehow makes them feel better God bless you for it
I don't think that's the same thing as with these Network clearly engaged in this like
I mean it's a scam
Magic isn't real
And you're not going to get Wealthy by by taking his
Magic course it'll be a coincidence
More is is like a
You know I'm not going to go to glitterbug church but I still want that
I still want somebody to tell me that if I'm a good person I'll get rich
Haha
It does
Kind of
I don't know it seems like an incentive to be a good person
Go to Joel Osteen or you can go to this guy it's the same basic
Glitterbug Church
Stop
Falls into fairly similar category
Christianity or religion in general is not in and of itself
The bad thing or -8 is the other behaviors that are coming along with it right that make it
Regularly distasteful aliens
Whatever as long as you're not coming from a place as long as you're not
Like
Actively hurting people and even then even the most desired
Like all I'm so mad and I'm a chaos magician I'm going to
Can pray for your
And then you'll get it
You know it's like you're not actually
Hurt him I'm sorry I'm sorry for you as a
Person it seems like a good way to wallow in some
Feelings that aren't going to help you
Maybe there's better use of your time
Another thing that I find that I resent a little bit about this
But you've presented to me
But it's not your fault but like
I've got nothing to hold onto
Like there is no real specificity of you even read one of these spells and I own
It just seemed like it was a
Name of Egyptian deity list you got it
Yep I don't know what black magic is I don't know what the devil is I don't know what why
Why he needs ghost out of his out
Out of your
I don't know any of these things
I don't have more questions and when we started cuz I don't care
Oh no I kind of resent that a little bit some interesting things along the way
I can't get enough of
That guy's just
He's having such a great time Matrix sink
That guy has more fun than that idea
Probably
So
Idolize
I mean it was nice to not have to deal with
People who are like
People should be lit on fire all the time like it's nice
Sure
Nice fat is that is a pleasant little break
That was fun nobody has any goes
No more episodes
So that's that's that's great
I will be back to talk about Alex on Monday through a bit of this
A bulshit we are also
On Twitter that's right and act
Correct
But till then I Mio I'm Leo and bcx Clark I'd like to wish you all a Happy dream
Creamy creamy summer
Dreamy creamy
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work