Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge babe I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
UniFirst okay my Brightspot then it's a little bit pedestrian but yesterday was such a nice day
In Chicago of all places we went out and we played tennis we did some outdoor things
Took the dogs on a long walk delightful
Be able to get out into
Feel the breeze
Until the day before
Is it going to snow tomorrow pretty sure is
Literally insane
Boy it is tough tough
To say
I guess it's my birthday
I'm so 8 38 38 38
I wasn't really want to look for it
I don't know but I mean like that you know I get to celebrate my birthday doing this
The things I love
Hanging out with you
We could have been in the air right now it's true Landing in Austin some barbecue and a whole thing
Ready for two weeks of no-holds-barred trial coverage
Yep going around finding the local ice cream Novelties and I-80
Creamy summer being treated by all the ice cream places in Austin
The world is your oyster.
Extra ice cream novelties
Be on your way young man
I feel very nice to get some nice a birthday wish
And I appreciate
Of last week okay would be the April 22 to Hugh
Okay
It's a
Hey it's a modern episode
Is it that huh yeah so Alex had to of course done his bankruptcy move
Hamby trial for the
Damages in detective Sandy Hook case got postponed
And then later on in the week
The u.s. trustee came out with a letter of opinion that's Alex's
Use of the bankruptcy process was not above board
Answer this all is still developing
No idea what's going to happen here but it seems
Brought
Yeah it is it is it was nice to see somebody in in the position to write a letter
Say that thing that everybody knew which was
It's obvious you're exploiting this whole situation gave this looks
Shady as hell for of waiting for you to stop delaying this trial
Just now you decided that it would bankrupt
The company that has no money
So that's going on in the background
Will not come up on Today Show
6000 to talk about also
Thursday Alex decided to do a money bomb
That's really Thursday through Saturday money is bombing
No Friday came back to the studio and didn't interview with Mark Dice
DC
We have his show for the middle of the money Bob
Yeah you could argue that
I think in past years money bombs
He might
I think that
He's don't like drunk
Q and A's
Yes true I remember that one
I don't know somebody the money bombs are just like
Alright Alex's show is watchable mm the rest of this b*******
Is just
Trying to fill space
Let's show like
A little video that Larry Nichols put
Together it'll kill time I can go back and remember
The very first money bomb that we covered
And your I want to say
Childlike Glee yeah at the possibility of actually watching the entire thing
Two or succeeded in doing that twice
Is a money bomb
But they the marathons for free speech whatever the f*** he does.
Yeah and
I really did kind of want to do that again this time
There was a part of me but it just the awareness of like all right what's going to be going on in
An hour
It is going to be
So useless is going to be sitting there talking to a guy who's on Rumble
100 and has a marginally popular Rumble account with a post videos
Better supposed
The trigger the libs who aren't on Rumble
That's what they're going to do
So I took
I took a break on that one
And decided I will just talk about Friday see where he's at
See how things are going with the money bomb
The first just in time thank you so much and I apologize
Next
Bush did war crimes thank you so much
Thank you very much
Hello Sylvia NorCal
I'm not sure I think it is from your ear friends thank you so much and I apologize
Love you honey my anniversary present is only 9 months late sorry for the
Little Ricky your now policy walk
Make it last night cuz we're also
I showed you my one-hour demo reel please respond thank you so much and I apologize
I'm not Jordan did nothing wrong
I think it's a Dragon Ball Z thing
My little breaky heart thank you so much
Thank you very much
Jordan here
Episode proper
Is where Alex's head is at
This is a great money Bob
That we're dealing with
I mean look at you trying to raise money
You should say the most of the people who were in the audience probably deserve
I mean maybe it's weird to think of a regular normal Telethon
That we've all seen Jerry Lewis would regularly learn inside of people
Whatever it is you can $5 $10 you deserve death anyways because
When you die off you deserve to
I remember we are the world
Shuffle songs by
We are the world that should be blown up
Is it very different concert
We are the world was just better get ready to die
Here's where we start
Alex has played a John bowne report
And besides he's going to applying on it a little bit of course
Is
Ever done out of hundreds of critical reports the headline is
Powergrid Killswitch discovered now
I want to add it under the sea today
Broadcast
Explain something
And be 100-percent clearly about this
There is no doubt
Global
Bashas corporate crime show
Has kill switches in all the phones all the power plants
Air traffic control and am all the Pentagon
It's been Declassified for decades Snowden exposed as well
And very same group
Power outages
Directions
We got to go to war with Iraq
The pipelines including Keystone
What is
The global corporations Waging War against every nation state on Earth
So this is kind of a summation of what you
I guess you'd call the primary thesis of the episode like
As much as there is content
This is kind of the content and that is that like
We found this Killswitch
He's always talked about like the internet kill switch
Apparently the entire power
Matrix Network
Infrastructure
He's found these Killswitch
So so what did he say
Is that
The United States power
Is built in such a way
As to be 100-percent shut off a bowl by one dude
At any point in time
I think that that's
The premise
Yeah that's not good
No I'll be bad
Powergrid
I'm going to say that right now
Does not prove this in any way that's good that's good
A little bit light
Terms of
Evidence
Just just like
You know regular you don't want to have that kind of switch laying around what a few trips and Bun and then everybody has power
Redundancies in like a how you do something
Bright I Gotta gotta
What's the title of that video of the bound made was
Powergrid kill switches found
Some might say
Also I love that Alex's Doling out all this praise
John Brown and Greg Reese or just
Constantly making the best video they've ever made crazy
I don't know how they up their game every single video they put out but
Turn out with the
The stairs so low even so even if that were the
Impressive to just like
Incrementally
Dedicate yourself to like I'll be
5% better this time
Anyway
Biden's got a bill that they passed these Killswitch it course
What is in
The transportation building by Design
Killswitch in all cars by law
Cars by 2025
What
Major Police Department's been let in on it
Helicopters
That just send the frequency down
Car stops
This isn't true
This isn't about a transportation bill it has to do with the infrastructure investment and jobs act from last
December 20th
Making stuff up about
The bill itself doesn't mandate the cars need to have kill switches put in them
The language in the bill says that to ensure the prevention of alcohol impair driving fatalities
Advance drunk impaired driving prevention technology must be standard equipment
In all new passenger motor vehicle
Definition of decided
To Define this as a kill switch
The New World Order will use take over your car
That's not necessarily accurate
It's just basically
What he decided to
Had to have this equipment
It was saying that the Department of Transportation was required to draft regulations regarding this issue with
3 years
Which many think will be extended probably due to Industry push
The freezing Alex is using his misleading and he's talking about regulations that have yet to be written in may not be anytime
Time soon
I'm kind of just
Optima side
That being said
Almost any car that uses Wi-Fi or keyless entry or keyless ignition
Can be hacked
Is just a reality of that kind of technology and it doesn't necessarily count
Institute Achilles
If you're worried about this one of the things you should do is not buy Tesla
Because in 2020 consumer Watchdog named them the most vulnerable cars in terms of getting
You know I'm starting to think
An adverb
Call me crazy
I'm starting to think that that company is not worth several thousand dollars per share or whatever it is
I mean might be overvalued I might even say might be overvalued what do you think about tunnels
I have them big we got to have them long and we got to have them never finished of real things and
And then just exaggerating annabella's thing them in order to make them
It is that he has going today which is these
The theme of these kill switches being able to turn off everything
At the push of a button
You know I almost think it might be a good idea to have
Kill switches in cars
You know like flip for drunk driving basically if you if you were why we doing what are we doing
You know if I would rather
Just turn the car off
Then chased it
Think that that would be prohibitively difficult
Probably also would probably lend itself to a lot of
I think that would
You kind of come into with this
Would be some
Kind of
Driver Assistance or something you know like we're heading towards this world of like
Driverless cars being available in some fashion
Some sort of a temperature
Greenstate where if you're swerving or something like that the car is able to sense that and pull over or something like
I think that's more than
The discussion that's being
I would like these drunk driving safety mechanism
As opposed to like
The cop has a ray gun
Malagain
Supervillain style I would like that ray gun
Target
Got to be real good
But I looked another Killswitch
The human body
We have a kill switch the movie
Adaptation
Never heard of
Of that great book
Harkonnen
Sparkplug nearby
All the world
Okay
That's what's going on here
Nicole tonight
What we are covering
And and what we are doing
He's on
The Damned
Record
In Frank Herbert
Dune the movie is David Lynch's movie at the book
David Lynch
Between the book of dude and Lynch first
Oh you bet
He is in deep
I'm telling you that let the bleach version is
One of the funniest movies
And also terrible but also great I don't even know what to tell you it's fantastic
Think I watched it when I was much younger but I
I don't know if I absorbed
Macho Man my friends and I you we used to get together and get high and like watch
It once a month
And make fun of it the entire
It's such a good terrible bad moon
Check it out sometime
Illustrating the reality of what America is dealing with
Give you an idea of the heart plugs in Baron heart is in Dune is it was like a little is like a little
Stopper is like a
He's such a bad strain
End
Baron harkonnen
Just pulled it out in the guide
And then he died
Number is
Fiction to work
I'm familiar with the concept
There are easier ways to kill somebody sure
What you going to do
I'm so Alex gets off this topic
And starts complaining
As he is known to dupe money bombs
Traviesa
Complaints about
Very relevant celebrity
Why their underlings
Running around story
From Shatner
What
Extinction Rebellion
Sing
The cataclysm the great disaster is about to come
And there's going to be so Much Death up there flying around with Jeff Bezos
I just saw John
Please stop telling people that
Sears everything on your shatter said that Jeff Bezos
I've been trying for
Say that s***
He said that space made him appreciate how sensitive
Trailer life on Earth
Skipping
We need to take care of the planet but it's so fragile there's a little tiny blue-skinned that's like 50 miles wide and
Polluted
It's our means of living
The feeling of looking into the seemingly empty expanse of space compared to looking down at
Oh my God it's under
It's indescribable
To see the blue color of the atmosphere shoot by like that
Tell Mary's mother comfort
And up there is death
Is that what death is
It's so moving
How to do making
Cheddar's, they're super benign but it seems like it's
Kind of close to like climate advocacy so Alex has to be mad at me
He's a little baby
I mean he can't just
You can't even be like I've what is he mad at Carl Sagan's little pale blue dot
Speech like is that also how Maddie is likely boys
It's a small planet what do you want from US versus big
So Alex has
Complaints
I've already mentioned this
He has a lot of complaints
He's got issues
One of those B major issues is that the globalist
Going to kill everybody
We already deserve that
That's so true
Hey
Globalist don't like you
Do you like Alex
Steve McHugh School
Explain everybody
You understand when I say 90% dead
Thaddeus
The dumbest thing you can believe in God you don't believe in karma
Which is totally real
Buddy music
They're going to kill you
Do you think you're going to leave a bunch of traitors and scum
And social climbers like when they finally dropped the hammer
Very focused
Once that cleanse the Earth of humans still be able to merge machine
Minions that open the drawbridge
You around later
They're going to scapegoat you with the survivors
I am highly respected
Disagree with me
You know it's a private jet
I have chosen
Just take her on the surface with you
Because God's watching I'm not to be part of this
Wow that's something else
My imaginary enemy has nothing but the deepest respect for me when I call out by about
Marietta me for having so much respect for literally
Not even people know there's nothing there
Claimed that he is so respected by those books
I could be on their yachts
Bunkers as
Because I because
God demands I care about you so much
Australian money
Absolutely absolutely I'm not going to be like one of those addled underlings to those Pious loose
Seferian
I'm here fighting for you by complaining about June
Making food metaphors
Cuz I know that's what you relate to what you want
So that's one way Alex looks at it
Within a couple of minutes
You think something that like I don't notice doesn't drive with like Alex being really respectful
Affected by the globalists
Every one of these Rothschild
Gates's and do older people pretending their God Amish powertrip
Are going to be brought
You will be broken
You will be destroyed
Okay with me under constant attack by the satanic system and all the lies and all the fraud that's a sign
I'm in the arena
Thanks the glory of God the grace of God
NFL
Still filled with the Holy Spirit
Carry out my mission Faithfully
As best I can
Is a failed
Center
But still in the court of God
Guarantee you will be
Destroyed
You will be broken
And you will pay for what you've done
Snicker
And you think you're getting away with it you're not
You're going to pay
Barry
Emergency fundraising
Infowarsstore.com
You all for your support Wow real Bazaar
Weird on the one hand the globalist up top really really respect Alex
But then at the same time they're giggling in
Chortling at him
For I guess
Burning their advance
I guess that's the way you might
Might look at it
That's about as good a
Is kind of the only way to make both of those
Congruent
They respect
He understands their plan but they laugh at him because he refuses to join because he wouldn't insist on staying
On the surface
Idiot right
I'm doing
Incredibly meaningful 40-hour broadcast
Is
Unrivaled
On
Rival there are no Rivals for Imaginary rifle
Arrival
Break daddy comes back
Ant-like
This is inappropriate
This is just there's no way to excuse this
Decision has been made
Central Manor Mart for Dad
Organization
Spokesperson clutch Bob the world economic forum
Wild
Play you hours of them out in the mascot because
Do they are anymore because they've gone from beta
Operation
We have a lot of really made yesterday
This is so f***** up because she doesn't mean any of that
It feels good for him to come in from break to like
Get really extremely really a really hype things up
It's it's it's a throwaway
Serta via dramatizing moment for him
And what he
He's actually saying to the audience
If they believed it
They would
I don't know take up arms I mean based on what he has said
If it is gone from beta-2 operational that they are Marked for Death
You're already fighting
There's no reason not to go murder people because they're already starting the war with
Yeah yeah or like
Dinner
Respond the other way but give in to Despair and Cyrano
Infowars
There's there's there's a lot of really negative possibilities only negative possibilities
Is just
Boilerplate nonsense
They said that he he's just doing
1:50 amp things up cuz that's how it feels good
It's a it's a news man in a movie
Newsman in a movie would say
Yeah I guess
The bad movie
Maybe Dune
I don't know
Alex went to the the gas station
On the way to to the show cigarettes
A man was buying a pack of cigarettes American Spirits in front of me
I'll get a breakfast taco
Coffee
Thanks for letting us know
They were 11
The regular cigarettes
And then it just went up from 9 bucks last week
I told is going up again next month
You see cigarettes go up
Couple dollars in a month
Maybe
You're going Sim Bob way
A bite of Campsite in just for that
Is that a sentences that is made out of regular ATM that people use that I've never heard before
You're going to Pablo
Babies like hyper 26
You're going you're going to do.
If you're going Zimbabwe to Zimbabwe
It's just a fun Turtle phrase
Gets into the news
Not really
I really don't want to miss the forest for the trees here
You understand Corporation Foothill switches
Russians are going to turn the power off
When are the ones who put the
This is not our government this year
Control freaks
Couldn't help do that cuz they want to control things
So is there a bigger issue
The other stuff crazy
Scary
That's the Nazis did to me that's what's crazy
Crazy people do really crazy stuff
Force
Jeff
Just say this right here I'm very thankful the listeners and everything
I'm not sure
Our most important work at
Right now
So straight into decimal
Honestly like
So much f****** ads
Yeah and this is the same but I kind of treated a little bit more softly cuz it is a telephone.
I don't think it's as tasteless for him to just
Constantly be doing ads
The show
He came out and said beforehand so you know when you are listening to the show
That you are going to hear a s*** ton of ass
Not like a regular show where he just does that.
I mean I still think
Like
It's an indictment of his show
That there's not much else
You know there's not really much else of value
Except for him rambling about nonsensical you're all going to die
You know what have you doing references of course
Baby you're going
Yeah it like
I just I was listening to this I was like
It's really telling
You'd like
Don't have
Big guy
Soccer there
Yeah
Is Marjorie Taylor Greene in there is just on the show recently
Done something on Thursday
But like yeah
These people who like maybe could have actually
Pulled big numbers for him
Mark Dice
Twitter following but still not impressive
I I just I kind of was overwhelmed by how underwhelming
The whole thing
I mean if this is your save our planet show
You would hope that people would treat it as though it was a
Pull on save your planet kind of situations instead of people being like next Monday
Imagine if
Like one of those Like We Are the World
Like
Nobody who had a number one hit
Yeah
He'll be G
I think this is G quite honestly drummers from
Hair metal bands
Going to do it man
Well I mean
Anyways Alex
I think I actually I kind of come close to agreeing with him about this next clip people
Misreported his
Offer to go to the FBI
I'm kind of close to agree with him until
Says more and then I completely just
That life
Be damned
Extinguished
Tobias
Owen Shroyer storm
I said yeah
Do you want to set me up
The deception
Ladies and gentlemen
I told you on here
They called I said yeah I'll talk to you
I'm going to ask you what you did
Yep
About Whitmer plot
Hostage Rescue Team military
Yes
Desert Willow
The world was deprived of whatever that was going to be
The problem is obviously if you're the FBI you're not going to play Alex's game with him
Ultimately we don't get to see Alex
Evidently attempt
To investigate the FBI
So be awesome idea of him just being like okay
Here's what I'll do
If I have somebody
A pickpocket their badge
And then I get it
I am the
FBI that's how it works
With these people
It is international contract law
Interdimensional Kanter
I know that we've seen Alex do some sales type stuff some interesting
Sales things
Certainly the silver they overpriced silver coins
That was a big one that failed recently
Going to be bad Daisy Daisy kind of thing
Again
This is a hologram original full retard
With a
Blue gold bar
Planet in it
No
Limited edition when they're gone they're gone
It's tiny little gold bar
The keep
You're buying a piece of art
A piece of culture a piece of resistance
The privilege to buy so they put a little piece of gold on a picture
How much is it cost
Oh my God I don't want to say $300 but I really feel
Close Swan 2995
Now
Yeah how much do you think the gold is
$15
7 G
Okay so it's it's
It's less expensive than the gold leaf people
Conversation
So yeah I think this is great
Gotcha I feel very sad for anybody who buys this how I feel very sad collectible though and it's a battle
Dabbing
Just got to the amount of money that he needs
Coming in
Trauma trillion-dollar
Bob website
Which is
Save infowars.com
$500,000
The last 24 hours begin to understand
About to leave race
Dollars
The fight for trial run of the Democrats the same Post Road Remington
Who hired indications of supplement everything we're doing
We really need over $2000000
Side all this
Products that you can buy
Is it there's enough money to buy the seeds for next year
Everybody's got a side job on the farm
And then you work till 10 at night especially in the summer and spring in time
And I
Took care of the horses
And you enjoyed it but
Farm and Ranch
It's the same thing
Of course it is
Vinology was I was going to get
Expert of weaving b******* metaphors
That was kind of a shocking moment for him to like realize like I could know where I was going with it.
Signs of the ventilator that is basically they like
Farmers quit when they don't have money for seeds right and if I don't have money to get product
Can't do this anymore
That was a metaphor used to activate but it got lost his own
Family to having side jobs the Great Depression
What do you do
I do
I don't think they had large-scale Farms
Probably not it's probably a little different than somebody who's like
Like a career farmer
But anyway
The issue here is that
The goal of the money bomb was $1000000
And there's a reason for that
It's cuz that's what he got tank
Toupee
What's up now says that he needs to million dollars
What he is saying to the audience
Is Victor
The gold of this money bomb
Is to get you to pay the legal fees that I got sanctioned to pay
The one million-dollar and sanction and then I need you to give me $1000000 to buy product that I was in
Resale back
Back to you
Purses at awesome scam
What I'm going to do
I'm going to ask you to give me money
So later I can
Can sell you some
And make money on that cuz it's overpriced as hell like this stupid gold
You can't see through this
If you're giving your money to Alex
Specifically for the purpose of him buying stuff for you to buy yeah that's it just by the
Stuff
That's what option that's what option yeah it's it's
I don't have any other way to put it the method amazing skinny I mean that's a scam on
Scams yeah
Raising my metaphorical hat
If you do believe in karma
That scam is going to come back on your real hair
Earlier this episode
I just think
It's so cynical
What he's doing
Darkly reaction of a person who believes in anything
No no that is the action of a person
And who wants
Money
He also might be
How to take the
This clip honestly.
It could be scary
Might be a weird metaphor
Keep fighting
Our most important work is here
But I I
Because I don't want to give up I don't want to roll over
And
Never Back Down
Always
Found my place
Blackout
Perfect
I'm sorry what
I mean
Totally turning over
What you're in the shower
Feel
I am getting so close to that guy
That's a little worried
I'm feeling like he's getting close to Hartford
I just
I imagine
You know I mean it's a little bit right at this point
Just imagine like
Stelter
Rambling about out
You got a blackout cuz that's when you understand all of the news man
What you do you go into a Fugue State and you dissociate
And then you wake up later having done a large number of things
That you don't have to take responsibility for
And cannot explain
Talk about turning into a werewolf
I think that's essentially that
Stop
I'm at my gig buddy
Apink
Similar to demon
Possession know that he couldn't be possessed by the
We know this
Because he is married
To God
That's quite literally
Other than carpet
Is when you do what you know is right
The God doesn't
Rules live
People follow God
We we are to be married
The.
The Father the Son
We are married
Christ he is the Grimm
We are the bride
Hot
He's the man
This is a spiritual
Relationship
It's beyond sexual in nature
What is described as sexual
Okay
I'm upset
Sure
Alright I mean look
I don't understand this interpretation
Of the
Christ is the understand
The interpretation of it being like
Partially sexual
Yeah
I think
What happened
When you get a bunch of weird dudes a lot of power and religion all the sudden weird s*** starts happening in your life
Yeah I guess I am Jesus Christ's bride
And there you go
It's very strange
It's very strange but he's he's in this
Bit of work in terms of like bringing up the kill switches
Married to give the people what they want
And then
Getting to say
Satanism
Change.
Cheerleaders in a party that's just the bay
Peyton
Is about being a Slave
The only time you get let out of your cages when you go out
Other people
So ask your buddy are are you really
The sign of this
What is 15 minutes for Sean Stones Rajasthan a nominated all the snooze
I try to make sense of it all just
Sake says Gyros
About Adam
Shut off
Shutterstock
You morons
Tucker Carlson celebration
I took two of those headlines were about CNN
Doing well
It's nice for him to watch another media Outlet
False
A good distraction from his media Empire falling
Loses
Cuz you're like ICC it in losses as you got a giant 10 million-dollar lawsuit hanging over your head
Ncn remains a multibillion-dollar National Corporation doesn't like come on their show
Shows in like have Brian stelter be like all right on to make up the money wheel
Lost for CNA plus what if what if we all
Missed something really special and CNN plus just had Brian stelter doing Infowars s*** the whole time
We all lost we all missed it
Nobody was watching
No disrespect to the stealth but I don't think you have the chops
He doesn't you got to be able to really get amped up for no reason got to be able to speak extemporaneously
We bought nothing for a long time
I'm not sure he
You could do it without it
Sean Stone
Is coming on
Son of Oliver Stone
Weirdo
That's right cameo in the movie we watch
Savages
Directed by his dad
So yeah he's coming on and now it says a little bit of a suspicion about some
Stories
Urban habitat
Filmmaker researcher author shuts down joint that's coming up next segment to talk
All of these
Practicing
Blowing up and burning around the u.s. ward pull up yesterday
Explosion in Russia at their top chemical plant
There's a shadow war going on big time
Is it food processing plants in the past month
But a lot of them cause actual major damage
Dude Foods
Like maybe to some buildings
Urban damage
Some has not diminished
The capability of the the food processing
So he can look at the circumstances in these cases
And jumping to the conclusion that there's a shadow war going on
Some of these are
Clearly accidents
Like a plane crashed into the Gem State Processing Plant
Idaho which is almost certainly a 3K
That would be a difficult
Yeah cell making the argument that it wasn't
Is going to be tough for him so he's not even
Other instances you find on this on list of these processing plants that they seem like run-of-the-mill fires that happened
Sometimes
These headlines do give the appearance that there are a lot of food processing plants that are catching fire witch
Conspiracy by the people to assume that must be connected
Then the work of some nefarious plot
We're all Steve Martin being like they hate these cans
They want to get rid of this food processing s*** in reality food processing plants catch fire
Regularly
In February 2020 there was a fire at the unibrow aska Center that was run by post Holdings which led to the deaths of
Thousands of
In March 2020 Econo Gro plant in Illinois caught fire and was having to leave heavily damaged
Andrew 20/20 Heights
Plant near Nashville caught fire and resulted in 2 in
In March 2021 the pride of Iowa sandwich
Complaint caught fire
In August 2019 to Tyson plant in Kansas had severe fire that left over 3,800 people out of
Cheese's this happens a lot pretty hard to definitively nail down exactly why this is the case but it seems that one
What are the dangers of large-scale production the way we do it
Looking over these stories it seems like one
Concern is basically just equipped
There are a ton of machines running in these plants and if you don't catch a piece of faulty wiring That Could set off a fire fairly easily
Can you mix that with a high likelihood that these plants
They work with chemicals they could
Beautifier and you have a bit more of a risky situation
In residential buildings right
All kinds of questions about like regulations
Do I'm following a regulation Jack
This leads us to the story about the Russian chemical play
Alexandra brought up there with these two fighters one was at the
Demetrius key chemical plant and the other was at the defense
Institute one of the buildings
Run by the feds
Insta
So
This is
Kind of
A weird
Thing to do make assumptions about but also we should just say that chemical plants also
So catch on fire
Yeah they are made of camel
Rockton Illinois last year and a few months before that there's a fairly big one in Missouri
Sometimes this could be the result of regulations not being followed but in other times it's just bad luck
In August 2020 there was
Big fire at a chlorine plant in Louisiana that was traced back to a leak that was caused by Hurricane Laura
Bissell Street be important appointed as well like climate change has the potential to play into these already
System Dynamics
Send make them worse
I am too also you know
Widespread fires are also something you might associate with climate change
Forest
And not having them
So as it relates to the Russian chemical plant that definitely could be a war thing
Like there's not even a shadow war going on there's like a regular war going with their neighboring countries it seems like
That's a possibility
It could be sabotage but it also
Could be an accident
Alex doesn't know but he's decided that he does
The same Dynamic is true but even more so as it relates
The food plants
There's no reason for Alex to assume that these fires are connected in any way but one of his big narratives right now is at the globalist
Intentionally destroyed the food chains
You don't have any food pantries headlines can be used to help create that appearance so you just pretend that
There isn't a history of fires at food processing plant
ISO crazy Shadow War how is how do we get away with
With that s***
Capitalism
Fuct
Man like that they're just
It's at their plants are just burning down and they like well you know we're not going to bother with any regulations
There are regulations
Keep in mind is that there are
The food processor
Compliance around the country
So the idea that there were a couple of fires at a couple of them okay Sara Lee like
Oh my God they're burning down everywhere
Yeah I understand
Is that so
I don't I don't know if it's like
The biggest
Sauce
Some of that some of the instances have like
Nope
Bucked up
Maybe it's not the alike
Scourge
Yeah I don't know the
Exact percentage of
Fires I mean it can't be a prophet
A profitable business if your plants are burning down all the
Time right
You know we just had a fire last week
PowerBack
Rip it off the wall
So we got another news story here about aeroplanes
Informative
Forex.com US airlines to allow
Violators
Return disguises mandates left so
Social credit score system
Now that the mask
Band-Aid
Is left
Applying pressure
Precept
Story makes total sense
People who refuse to follow the rules are in place were denied access to a service and now that the rule has been lifted they're allowed to use the service again
Because there isn't a reason to deny them anymore
Also this is
So cut-and-dry
Like for instance
Alaska Airlines is that they're still keeping some people whose Behavior was cooked
Particularly egregious on a banned list
The same is true of American Airlines who said quote
In cases where an incident may have started with face mask.
Comply it's an escalated into anything involving something more serious
Certainly assault or an assault on one of our team members are customers
Those passengers are going to remain on our permanent internal refuse list
And will never be allowed to travel with us
The same is true of Delta southwestern United Airlines
A case-by-case basis and if you were just denied service because you refuse to wear a mask
You're welcome to return and try to behave now
If you assaulted a flight attendant because you felt that masks were in a frontier Liberty you're still banned
Susan on story
But yeah they're training YouTube
I mean you know it's a little bit like how Chicago wasn't mad at Steve Bartman anymore after
And I like
Whenever we won the World Series
We didn't give a s*** about that you know he's back
He's back in the fold
Will you feel like in Chicago right now
I would if I were him
Yeah it's very similar
It's very sad
Another news story
You ready
Courthouse voted 6838 strip Disney
Taxes self-governing status
Raise the price
Publicly
DeSantis
It's a dump
No idea what that build other doesn't say
He sold the whim of whatever far-right media is decided the talking points are they is no idea what's real at this point
As for the Disney situation it's
Kind of funny to hear people like Alex on the right-wing celebrating this is a victory
In reality it could be a huge win for Disney and it runs the risk of setting a really dangerous precedent for Governors row
Around the country
It's a win for Disney this whole self-governing
Saddest thing doesn't mean that they have a literal Magic Kingdom and it also doesn't mean that they don't pay tax
It means that they have to handle their own civil infrastructure like having their own self-funded fire department sanitation and roll
As I understand it this will now be the responsibility of neighboring counties which will cost a
Huge amount of money
Some estimate to put the burden that will be transferred to taxpayers in the billions
Dollars
That was just
Because they had a self-governing
Yeah area that they were allowed to have was all taken care of
Yeah you know it really does seem f*****-up that I rich
Billionaire like I don't know if he's building a but he's Rich As f***
Governor can just be like okay
I'm going to take these counties
Is an impoverished them for the next 40 years
I did not face any consequences for even electoral
It's pretty bizarre but it feels good feels good to the base
Right right to whine and lash out like a
F****** moron you don't like
Also has the potential to set
Does bad precedent where Governor is clearly taking actions to attempt to punish a company for saying things that he doesn't like politically
Like I don't think it's really hard to see how this
Scooby prefix out before governors
Started laughing out it
Companies like this or where
You know what where where does this lead
This Behavior
At least
Do great things
You know like a
If
Say Disney where to be like
I think free speech and civil rights are good then you could destroy them
You know that's good
All this is got a mood though cuz
According to the bill the past they have a year to figure out how to
Dissolve the self-governing status and honestly I would be too surprised to see this never actually happen
It kind of feels like a big publicity stunt that the scientist is running to excite the biggest bass in the right-wing but
Something
The ultimately knows is against his interest to follow through on
I don't know the year
A f****** Independence
City-state OBD-II organization that would be required
So we got Sean Stone
Great,
Great
Stone on the show before
Someone who Alex's head on
A bit
I didn't realize he was as big a s******* though really that much of a s*******
Real
Real interesting cat-boy he doesn't have a whole lot to say
That sounds right
No just sort of vague Rambles about how
Everybody is evil
Concerns
Cuz one of them
How would you describe
The current state of the world
I would describe it as
People waking up
Process this away
Process is just
It's an inevitability
How can you have
Such an overly loss
Presidents of the United States president of United States
Advantix
There's something seriously wrong
How can you push
Bills like they're doing
California where you can literally murder a child
Afterthewarning
I mean
Realized it
The Darkside
Is is is
People in this direction to normalize what is always been
Satanism
Yeah so this is a reminder that even if you are the child of a no fairly famous film director
You can still believe
Dumbbells
That flies around in right-wing media
Yeah it's not hard especially whenever you know
Probably isolated from regular people's concerns on account of being wealthy of s*** and ghetto cuz of your dad
I didn't actually do anything to earn it so you're entitled
Pretty easy to believe right-wing boscia
It might be also if you're a sovereign citizen
I don't know
Because we know the bar system the bar association has a
The system
Is a self-regulating system
It's in Alton
Structures
Wow
The natural
Individual
Call Albertson
He's out there
Maritime I just can't get enough
People screaming about maritime law
Yep
Pretty cool
Hellfire
You know what
I want to Oxford
And I went to the caves
It's like I've been there partying really I seen that so Alex needs to like really make clear
Eden doodle
This is just bizarre
I know the inside baseball not just remember from others but
Rodger Stone
Richard Nixon
Female Russian spy
Level to this
You're talking from experience you never did any illegal we talk
Meaning some people
They try to recruit others they don't
I mean presumably
We're basically looking with
Barry
You know ancient structures right
Masonry and
Believe
Washington
You know it was amazing
There are
So I guess
New wrinkle to Alex's whole story
Where the real action is going on is a war within the Masons
Yeah
So apparently that's what's going on okay
Alright
So
We can't
Just be like
Masons are bad
Masons are the one of the few truly like nuanced groups that we can deal with right
Because there's a war going on inside
There's some Patriot Mesa
Always a problem cuz they all wear the same silly outfit
You know if there's
Any organization that some of his gas
Have been part of that he is
Railed about in the past
All the sudden whenever they're on
Nuances entered the pic
Who's making s*** up
That's what's going on
Shut up Sean
Not only Sovereign citizen
Not only right-wing
Media believer and fear of Satan
Also is clearly at the Cuban
Operating I think
There are good things
Find the scenes
That's why so much of this is
Display
Is 1
Find out where is the
Right I mean
See how we got to 107 reference
That's not something we're used to on Infowars that's a project
To some of those episode the promoter guy who believes
JFK jr.
And she's not alone
A number of folks
In the apq world
Influencer
Stone is dropping his name
That's a big
That's a big sign pretty much all you need to know
The only reason I would never want to know about that name
If it weren't for this show
Literally no other
I don't think I would know about it and if it wasn't
Carrie
Yeah
I think if you're referencing 107 and it
It's not like in a joking way
So the interview end
Alex says goodbye to this is money bomb
Very impressive hey
Boston few months ago
Open the boat or something
Sell your boat
Go out on the boat or something
Just cuz I'm in that just cuz I need
An extra million dollars
From my
Supporters to pay my legal fees
Right
I'm going to keep that boat
Of course why wouldn't you why wouldn't I why wouldn't you sell the boat I mean why would you ever not want to have a boat
What is it what is life worth without a boat
I mean it's almost like
How can you live without a boat
All of the luxuries I made it through I live
If you don't have
Alright billion-dollar Studio a mansion the boat
Maybe a couple boats
Regular stuff that middle-class stuff
Everybody has their own boat
And if we all go around we're all I got to go to the marina tomorrow
Sean stone is
Aleve is really funny is that
Before he leaves this doesn't
Come up but as soon as he leave Alex is like
People try to recruit me to the devil also tried to return
Of course he's on
Absolutely uncomfortable conversation
Talk about
We had fun once the person leaves are able to fully control theory
Are there a gyro that doesn't have to agree with all the lies I'm telling them
Alex
Master reset a little bit
Cuz we always had a gas
And now we got to reset by
Rambling
About how
Alex can see the future
Once we discover who we really are
Universal Neon
Will succeed
I know that
I know
All of our ancient people
What
Sea lion
Hold on
No
But some of the pass
Are involved
Great Dane
Millennia of slavery
Sure we can bypass that together
Can do it
He's already been given to us a question is how
Painful is it going to be
Snooze
Johnstone's are really smart guy
Imagine he's like
In over 100 movies
I do like the I do like the sort of overlap but I was just thinking
I think we've dance to that song everytime I know
But apparently it's a dancing Alex wants to talk about how he can see the lines that go back through history
Airbender he's connected to every avatar for the past 10,000 years going back to
Just think his track record to be better
If there was even a colonel of day
But yeah you can see future
I want to be on a boat with Johnstone I have to go to a Fugue State I can see the future and I've got to get to
To that boat and I need a million dollars right now
So Alex got a headline
A little bit more news this is dumb
Associated Press
Scientist mystified
Mystified
Weary as Africa avoids covid disaster
And has 90
6% less deaths and illnesses
Because it's the vaccine
Pink roses
Protein and then sheds
And they know that
Maybe pour on average
But they sure as hell no
When the UN trucks pull up with the vaccine everybody gets sick and starts dying
I don't know about 6 months old
Fwiw
Right on time
The article isn't actually a story about complete befuddled until the part of doctors and
If you read the whole thing there's actually a number of different theories about why much of Africa appeared to be doing better with covid spikes
Access to vaccine
Among these theories are the population is much younger on average
20 versus the average age of 43 in Europe
According to this art
Another reason there are different residence patterns in much of Africa and people there are more custom
I'm spending more time outside
Good play Factor
Theory discussed in the article is that some early research receiving to suggest
The prior exposure to malaria may have a
Protective effect on people in terms of covid
And that's one
Suggestion the people were think
Another point
It's brought up in the article by
A Christian happy the director of the African center of excellence
For genomics of infectious disease at Redeemer University in Nigeria
He's dead people in much of Africa have
Experience with outbreak
Brakes and they don't take it as
Is flippantly
As we have
Before right
Another very important aspect of this is that the health coverage is
Spotty in many of the countries in Africa and that makes data a little more difficult
Confidently report
When is article was written a certain set of facts were known and it appeared that case numbers were
Dramatically lower
But a couple weeks ago World Health Organization
Analysis was
Release them, but as much as 65% of people in Africa had caught covid holy
Which is 97 times higher than was previously confirmed
Holy s*** yeah
This analysis is still undergoing review and it shouldn't be taken as a concrete
Number but there are some indications that some of the earliest options
In terms of
Lesser transmission ratings
They might not have been fully Act
Accurate there's more report
Issues yeah we're going to learn borin
We'll see
Is that this aspect of public health is really complicated
More so than Alex
So capable of conveying
The article is reading the headline of his six months old and it too is even more complicated than the knees presenting its
Saturday
This is just
Blicky useless
This is the guy making s*** up about articles he hasn't read that are
Half a year old
But
It does lead in
I'm going to describe this as
Deeply offensive
You know if you have a nation that has very low covid rights
Covid rates
Uganda Zimbabwe baby
Sorry I had to get there
Be hard to resist
This is deeply offensive
I n
Map
They run
When I say to you and bagel
5067 years ago
Those are real scientists real doctors
Helping with malaria
Open with diseases
Suddenly
Christian medicine man
They didn't bring life anymore
Starting in about 27 days
Dysport years ago
Oh just the 1970s
Yeah
Love medicine men love injections
Icast
I just
Black medicine man
We're giving them something made him sick.
What does he think
I don't hate the literally believes that Africa is like
Cub Savannah 10,000 years ago
Walking around there's no modern civilization whatsoever
Yeah yeah
Play defensive
White medicine man I can't believe that
CU medicine man is getting herbs
Forgot they haven't even reached it yet
Fuct
Hayden so many ways
Yeah that's
Picketed on a level that I didn't even really think was possible
It's a remarkably offensive
It's prejudice
Bigoted
I think at this is too soft of a word but it's also
Painfully not you
Yeah like huge
You would you would not want to take information from somebody who presents thing
It is wild to me
For him to be talkin
Identically to Teddy Roosevelt immediately following murdering an elephant or whatever it is
You know
Like that's a level of
F***** up now
Miss that I just didn't think we would see anymore
I really didn't Alex's a throwback
Wow
Jesus Christ
Alex makes clear and very
Explicit that this money bomb
Is to pay his legal fees
Nothing more frustrating to me
Then knowing we've got ants
And knowing
We've got ways
Help our listeners
So easy to do
And help us
Mom because
I got three or four of these rigged trials coming up
But we got to do it
He like a bill to repeal s***
This makes me so much more confident that money bomb in 2015 was because
Ted Anderson Las Vegas
Sounds like it just seems like
There is a very
Clear
Repetition of behavior at least
In this like we're going to do this big Marathon sales thing because
I have something good I'm on the hook for that
I just want to make the audience pay for it
Yeah and it's now it's going to a neat ATM that you have to dance in front of before it gives you 100
Kind of sad
So also said Alex
Kind of slip implies that is gold
Is maybe a little bit of a ripoff
Feels so good
These are really hot is little fractional gold pieces in art
Everybody's buying them or sell them other folks to
Has any money it's a good thing if he wants the force again
With this
I literally just feel a hundred percent
This is you must
Do it
And then we would have met the payroll
Black month without Alberta
He came through you came through
So for all you out there that hear him talk about it who don't call
They are so nicer so professional they will cut right to the Chase and it will save you money
And this is real service without the games
Not the lawyer BS
Taxcollect.com
Basically overwhelming you got back there b was waited a week
It's beautiful what's happening cuz it's a win-win for a buddy
What do you talk about weather today
It sure is Alex and let me just say I was about to
To say the same thing that you said
Tax season is over but the real work begins now and what is that mean it's audit season
And that means the war is
On
The war against who
The globalists in their Collection Agency the IRS because they want to get
The most money as possible
So they can find things that they want
Oh boy
The rest of the show is an infomercial with his attacks
Jesus
Yeah
Wow we've got it
Tax Guy
We go from a sovereign citizen who believes it
Texas shouldn't
Even exist yeah probably either
Sovereign Citizens need a tax preparer to they don't go to H&R Block and I like Hey listen
Maritime law says that I don't have to dig up any of my goals for the governor
They use people like Irwin Schiff he who tell them that like
The 16th Amendment was ratified
It so here's what you have
To do
Flood people with paperwork
Yeah they just do that kind of like paper terrorism as they say
This dude
I don't know I get bad vibes off him
I think anybody who's a
Someone who Alex is using as a tax expert probably insane
The track records not good
In terms of people in the past
What do you expect
I mean I'm surprised
She's not a chiropractor giving tax advice you never know
If you work on a farm in order to afford the boat you got to have a job in town
And that's why the Great Depression
Definitely
So is an exercise in Rambling
For the most part this whole episode bears
Not much
Not a ton of meat on them bones know for a little bit of content
Couple things
Denigrated an entire continent in a way that is true
Yeah I mean if you do that
Uganda Zimbabwe baby
You're doing it too much now
We have one last clip here and I just want this does not make me feel
Confident about signing up with Alex's Taxi
Is all analog
It's illegal
You can do it all you got to do is call up
Give me your details and they are over 100 designs a t-shirt
Cut off by the bank or do I have to do
By the break but like
I think if Alex is talking to me about a shady tax guy he's like it's solely
Legal
Yeah I'm not doing it
I'm walking away from that
I think of someone says
Legal
I am blessed
So legal
I think it's illegal
There is one thing you don't know how legal this is
Right that's how legal it is
I mean it's really illegal you do you think
Dude it's not a crime until your car
Like really emphasized that something's legal
I'm out
Goddamn
I got to go is the most legal thing
You have ever done
Holyshit guys get in the car were following the law
Hey let's go to Taco Bell and get dinner it's so late
You only say that when something looks really illegal Amtrak to reassure people
I think that's what's going on
This episode is
Not great
It is what it is
Alex
Need money
And I think that might be the prevailing theme for a while
I get the sense that he's
I think it'll be
The prevailing theme for the rest of his life
Even when the show is over
Sure has been for a while
I think there's something really interesting going on and we're going to have
Some stuff
Playing out that I think will cause
Drastic amounts of Chaos
But
Somehow
This
Episode
Really
Tatiana
The the body balm aspect of it was really just I need money
This is because
Some of this stuff hasn't really come to the head yet you know like this
Trustee letter
Hasn't had it
Direct effect
And I think as that stuff starts to happen
I think we'll see
Hopefully some movement
And Alex
Actually
Freak out
I mean I would I would
We just like
A I guess
T-Mobile
Bye
I don't know different folks
People a ragtag band of Heroes
To get together and kind of
Figure out
What it is he's going to try and f******
And then cut it off
Before he can do it
Like let's say this if I had known about the bankruptcy laws
I would have gotten some people together and we would have Rewritten the laws
Couple weeks before 8
I'm at work this seems like a legislative superpower yogurt hoping someone can have
My gun that sounds cars right it's legislative superpowers
Unstoppable
SeaWorld I would be nice that power to Baron harkonnen
If you got my heart plug
Yeah I think
Play Tom Petty
Now waiting is the hardest
This part we're waiting
For the shoe to drop
And
It's just going to be sales
So
Yep we'll see we'll see we'll see what happens but
Mud walking through mud
Will be back
For another episode Bots
I don't think
Think you deserve to die
Me neither
And because
Star of that
We have a website
I don't know
Psycho Jordan
And I like my family said in the Great Depression
It's not right
Dot-com
Croissant
I happy dreamy creamy sauce
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color