Airjordan.com
I have great respect for knowledge B
I need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Quick question
What's today
My red spot
History in past
And then shaving my head
The truth like that the other night
And
I was very close
Does shaving all my hair off
Not just any particular ring really has
But feels like it's time
Enjoy having a bald head
It feels kind of good
We take a shower the water hitting your bald head
Feels really good at that does feel real
Really just rolls off you never felt it before
Look forward to it once there once that happened
But then I had this moment
Shaving my head that I usually have after the fact
And that is I remembered
That I really like the front and top of my head bald
The back is a disaster I got there okay all right
Hard to shave that of course it's just I realized
Yeah baby the Allure of this is not as good as the reality
So I'm going to
Tye-dyed iguana pointer that go get a haircut
Because it's progress in the past I would have just gone
Barrel Dennis
But this time I thought about it and realize no no no the back of my head does exist
Wow in hindsight being 20-20 turns into foresight 2020 victory of
Proportions right
Is Jamie Loftus
Coach Coast Church
Very good
It's a you know it's about that single person point of view nonfiction kind of think
It's really enjoyable I wish it was about Cactus Tony of course
A long story of the greatest example of
The format it is very good
And it's got is about that spiritualism era right
Now that I've always found incredibly fascinating whenever
So many f****** mediums were going around like it's fine like they were just like let's do this
Crazy
Well I'll have to give that a check out
Cuz I'm good but it is interesting
Jordan today we have a not so awesome episodes
Kind of figured that this is one of the most
Discordant episodes of Alex's show I've heard in a long time interested
Absolutely no sense
And if anything is to be taken seriously it is
Is deeply deeply disturbing
And we'll get inside before we do looks like a load some new wants
First
Thank you very much
Universities Airport
Next hearing Rodger stones or Gigi is a gross out loud while washing dishes
Thank you very much for me thank you so much you're now policy walk
Thank you very much and Kansas even though I'm not Andy nor have I ever been to Kansas
Smooth Jazz Cat
Gary Piano thank you so much and I apologize
I'm a policy wonk
I also happy belated birthday
Happy birthday bro
Next to also
My gay frogs
Human rights
You are now.
Technocrat
I have
Risen above
My enemies
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
And all your s***
Maybe later on West Broad
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologize to
To the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not
Boy is he not really thinking today was going to
New
So today we're going to be going over April 25th 2022 that's Monday
Alright that one actually works
And this
Was
Upset
This is a disturbing episode and I think
How do I texted you and I was like maybe we need to do Tuesday episode
About 10 minutes into the episode I was like
Worried you are Warrior
It's not a
Common experience that I have it was it was it was a very different vibe that I mean
But here is where the episodes
This morning while I was reading all the news looking at the research
About quite a bit here on are in the past but we're now here
I really think I should take today
She really
Thank you all
Tell you that I really appreciate you because
We could be off the air
Vomit
Plunged into a massive power outage that will be the beginning of
Martial law
Cool
BMX plays the New World Order
The purposeful collapse of civilization
Chair and massive
Depopulation
In the next 20 years
That's fast
Actually happening
I just a Chronicle all the attacks are running right
24-hour show we're going to
Most important
All the pieces
I know exactly what's going to happen
The only question is what is the timetable
I'll let you know what's happening as well
That was kind of saying goodbye different
Vibe to this than a lot of time
He talks
Doom
Subdued
Kind of measured presentation to this
Creeps me out
I mean it doesn't seem like
The normal Outburst of how we're all going to die comes from whenever he's having a bad day
Today and has lost in some fashion
Usually in the court
This sounds like he's saying goodbye through this medium of Dance
I suppose the working theory that is
Alex realized
Maybe this bankruptcy thing isn't going to work and that maybe the fact that the US
Trustees have written this letter
Right
Any system
Could trigger some kind of examination
Of his use of bankruptcy
Could lead to even more trouble
Well I mean when you start to say the words criminal fraud
They were I don't know I don't know any kind of like
Inside information on this or anything but it just
Feels like
My theory is that this is Alex being like
I'm done.
I've done everything I can
Is my last Hail Mary
That's why I'm saying I'm not saying the word
It's criminal fraud but we're in the ballpark
Start to think about
Insinuations and hints
And it just like this
Beginning stretch of the episode
Boy howdy
There's that too great song
Was Elvis
Already talks about
Baby alive or told you
How much I really loved you
And he goes on to say that
You're always on my mind
We're always on my mind
How much I love you and appreciate
I tried to stop him initiating this Final Phase
To be able to beat them
In a long-run butt
I really need to just
Continue on as long as possible
Years
You need to get ready to get your family ready
And I've really been holding off telling you all this but I
I just I think you already know
But
Everything you see
Everything standing
Everything that's been here
Atlas
I want to dance on the left of them in the
Quislings
It'll be too late for them and too late for us
Just get right with God
Okay
So
This is bad
Here's what I couldn't get out of my head I couldn't get out of my head
Whenever NBC-2
Tonight Show from
Conan I was like what is this with Conant wife
Are we awesome
Instead of that like great
Beat but not giving into cynicism
Listen they took this show for me they're going to take everything from you going to kill all of us 90%
Everything that is here will be gone
The monument rebuilt to the Past will crumble and be taken over by ivy
Directors is like
That sounds right
That would be a lot of fun
Just f***** up
Acceptable Lottery level
Thursday there's the
Sort of presentation of it like you got to prepare your family
Bishop going down
Next 8 years 90% of everybody's going to be dead
Really constant
Since the beginning of this episode that like this
Can't be stopped
There's nothing we could write
Really care about the screw
Care about all you I care about my family
I just have a really sad feeling
Didn't stop the story of the best Shelby
They are
Dismantling every facet of civilization
World is completely collapsed hundreds of millions are on their way now to Europe in the United States in North America
What Mexico completely collapsed we will collapse just like the most cities
Where do I find
The powers
Britain start failing
Republic bag
For stability
Yeah it mean if this is business extreme and nonsensical
There are some similarities
Do like what a lot of people believe will happen
Do like
Do climate
Areas are going to become uninhabitable
It's just a reality of how things
And there are going to
Be massive inflows of refugees
Pretending
That they are used as a weapon by the global is right
As opposed
To forcibly displaced
Weaponizing
A potential real
Issue that we're going to be dealing with in the future
And that's
Insidious
It's pretty nefarie
Yeah I mean it is hard
To argue with a prediction that
Things are going to get
Bad right now
It does seem impossible for you to like listen to look at the ipcc reports
Where scientists are getting our waxing philosophic
Nicole about
What it would be like to live on Nova Planet the functions and then see Biden being like
I mean yeah drilling is great
But
Not this way
Not how it's going to go
So look it's been great knowing you
Audience
Quote Alex
I just need to take this opportunity today
And also I really just feel like talking about how great
And
Just in case
A tweaker next month
Because it's that close
. swimming pool.
We have a puppet president
Text Direction on television from the Easter Bunny
A joke that's very serious
Quite serious
Very serious
Did you know that
But I've always
Suspected and I feel right now it's amazing
Right I mean like
Obviously Maybe
The person who was in the Easter bunny suit at the White House's celebration wasn't a random person
Easter Bunny
Maybe that was like a secret service agent
Or something
You probably want a random person and Easter bunny suit
15 Survival let's get out of here we don't have any internal Easter bunnies
Dr. Just not the same if it's an agent portraying
Easter Bunny
Professional
Google be sad
So yeah because you just nonsense
B
We've we've heard Alex say stuff like that movie like it's
Been good to know you
And things like that in the past but I really do need to stress out different the
Dark
The Andre could be gone in a week
A lot of that feels like all of my attempt
To put off the inevitable
Have
That is kind of you all of my boobs are gone I'm in checkmate
Right it does feel like he is admitting that out loud
I mean
Obviously
And I would be tough to prove
Definitively sure
It certainly fits
Text
What's going on in the larger sense
Which we could be reading too much into as we have in the past
A possible
Tony Evans go to camps
Publix
Complete monsters
My God
What have we done what Have We Become
Airborne
We're the Bad Guys
Galatians helmets day weather
Walmart.com
Apocalypse
New tagline
No longer tomorrow's news today Network chronicling the Apocalypse
Pirate Radio from
Apocalypse Now
Yeah
Yeah I think that's good brand
I think it's so much
Easier to feel
Morley soup
Superior to your enemies
Whenever you have them fictionally writing laws to just murder babies
That's great
You know like it is in a nuanced world I have to wrestle with sometimes nose like
Where what would I do in their shoes
Would I be
You know a person who if he obtained
Billions of dollars
Would go mad with power and B
You know that was pretty easy though he's mine
Sure I monster
Anyways
It's way better
Unreal problem
That's just kind of an offshoot of his whole thing
And where it's right
Really easy to be better than your enemy when your enemy is the f****** devil
Yeah
And it's imaginary
I am but a fallen
Vessel
But
Compare me to the devil anti I'm so great
And whenever your enemy complements you it's like
Every time I played White
Against myself lying black
I tell myself I'm the best
Player there's ever been nobody who could beat me
Across the table
So that's all like the beginning
The segment episode
Into the show proper
Cuz a lot of that's not actually
Broadcast on the radio
No man's land
Here we we coming to the actual show
Emergency broadcast
Actual call to
Transhumanist environmental terrorist
Civilization
TuneIn and learn how to stop
Infowars
Has confirmed
Multinational
Authoritarian called
Is actively
Attacking every
Fashion
Are the planets supply-chain
Davis Group is a mouthpiece of this psychotic multinational corporate back
Post-humans Revolution
Thank you not realize that when I would read out of
Problem Roman un documents in operation w.
Rockefeller Foundation
British Ministry of Defense reports
Power 2 plus years until
That wasn't making it up and I wasn't exaggerating
They weren't playing games
So the first thing to point out here is it
Infowars hasn't confirmed s*** yet they're running headline is it for doing some real reporter
This is just s*** talkin be presented as fact
Second none of the documents that Alex is referencing at the Ender have
Anything to do with backing
His claims
Operation lockstep isn't a real
In that document from the Rockefeller Foundation exercise the pandemic that's involved in the lockstep scenario
It begins in 2012
The depiction of the situation that you know this imagine
Future involves it does extend to 2026
Where the last event mentioned is protesters in Nigeria over
We're throwing the governor
Along the way the document explicitly mentioned something
Fictional things that never happened
Protalix guide love to hear him explain 2013 cellular cellular Networks
Completely crashed
Oregon 2017 quote
Italy addresses immigrant caregiver Gap with robot
Woo that sounds fun
Alex explained
Explain the prognosticating Wizards
Explain why I was just Italy
Did that we need robot
Caregivers to
Complete
Sketch of the world is a little blurb
We've been over this but it always needs to be called out that Alex is maliciously lying and making things up about a scenario exercise
Technological advancement in the developing world
So it will work better as a thing to scare his listeners with
It's b******* his behaviors in
Excusable
The club of Rome documents talking about his limits to
Growth which I know because it's literally the only Club of Rome publication he's ever mention
Limits to growth was written in 1972 and I'm certain Alex's never read it because it's a very detailed breakdown
How to various factors
Is that the authors believe
Will be contributors to limiting the carrying capacity of the plant
These involve things like pollution but they also touch on the total amount of arable land versus
The demand for food
And like things I've known quantities of
The finite resources versus the increasing demand
As population goes up
In each case they have estimates for the point at which
There are these lines intersect on a graph
But they're also very clear that these are based on trends
Continuing
And if some of the factors aren't even predicted
Even so they can
Conclude that without any major changes will hit a resource crunch within 100 years
Azure by 20
I was just making up as they predicted the crisis of being 20
20 because of better suits his purposes now
Fresno connect
Directions to reality
Another book on this kind of theme but Alex might be referencing is Paul airlux 1968 population bomb
But that wasn't affiliated with
The club of Rome
Brings up some valid points
But a number of the predictions and it were not good
Still none of them involve 2020
Ehrlich
Adom was coming by the 1980s
Alex's casually referencing these documents
Forgive his career full of
Failed doomsday predictions the appearance of being
Something research
Unscholarly
This should be saying means nothing he's just trying to take the audience into thinking there's more behind his words
Just some idiots imagine
Imagination
You're really all of it
And of course
Prophetic dream
MCS had and weird
Visions we really don't deal enough with how much it may just be a dream
Because all the time and then he finds some random ass documents if somebody's is like
Dream I had dream
Informed by growing up in a John Birch Society household where he read these
He's f***** up books at like age 12
And then just internalized them into his world
Yeah and now he pretends he was a Satan
All this b*******
Yeah there's really only two ways to go from that child
I live right there was serial killer and then Infowars
And everybody already done serial killer so he was like I suppose.
I guess there's another way to go
Therapy anyway considered
What you're saying in the first segment
It carries over
Because
Irreversible
Ford Escape reversible
Genie back in the bottle
It could be 10 or 20 times worse if they get
What they're actually looking for
6 billion + 10
They don't have
Noah Harari
Klaus Schwab
And Wall Street Journal New York Times
Looking forward
To the end of humanity
People set themselves on fire in front of building
Contraband fossil fuels
Corsair to use fossil fuels to do it
Mobile.
That's
Doing all of this to play games
Well I guess Alex good is wrap it up then
Just closed up shop
The goal was to stop the globalist and now the whole thing
Think happy stopped he's failed and he should go home
Intent was hopefully miserable life
F*** this dude yeah useless now
Also looking forward to the end of humanity was an op-ed that actually makes the opposite point that Alec
What's thinks it does cuz it's only read the headline
Hey U-Haul Noah Harari is a historian
The future is that Alex has recently decided
Patty's going to pretend Disney globulus soothsayer
If I had to guess this is because Ray Kurzweil hasn't said anything weird in a while so Alex had to find a new character to fill that Gap
When Bruce Lee was the name of the man who self-immolated
In front of the Supreme Court building recently
Hoping to bring attention to the climate crisis
Do he was passionate about climate change Bruce's action as
Has nothing to do with Klaus Schwab or the globalist
It's a desperate Act
I meant to bring it to folks
Crispy severity of the issues that he cares about
He's not the only person
Some to do this even if you exclude all of the cases of protest outside the United States
Sprint since David Buckle died by self-immolation of the protest about the climate in 2018
This is basically Alex's way of not taking Bruce's action
Seriously by pretending
Some Grand conspiracy
Hmmm by making clip joke about how his self-immolation requires fossil fuels
Alex is doing this because on some level he can't even imagine having the
What about something
They would take to self-immolate
Do protest
Serious cause
Cuz he's just pretend
It-it's
Be allowed to see
No I think it's
It's pretty
Deportes
But I guess this will go ballistic KB stop now and ever going to die
It's real shame
Yeah I'm confused we had a good run
Yeah let's let's
Children
You know
I mean if it's irreversible I'm confused why so sad the only argument is that he saying you could
Could be 20 times worse which implies that by some action it could be twenty times last
Bad
Okay
I guess we only have
Hundreds of millions dying
Yeah okay
Honestly I really think
This line
Of rhetoric is pretty Danger
Because I think that there's really only a couple Direction
Things you can go with
The first is doomsday prepping and maybe you and your family run to the woods Arizona made out
I think that's a unwise
His decision for most people probably
Maybe some people could pull it off and have a nice life out in the woods
I don't know but I think the
By and large it's probably irresponsible to give this advice.
The second thing I think
You could lead people to estate of
Real
Terror and maybe they would go
Consider ending their life
Because
What's coming could be something so horrible I have saw the Mist
Remember whenever the guy
Famous ending I might I might not be right with the title but the famous ending is the guy is
With his family in the truck
Any kills his wife and daughter to save them from the horrors and he's about to kill himself
The Mist parts and he can see people coming towards
Until it's like
Man 5 minutes
Sure
You hear stuff about people to
Taking the War of the World seriously when I was on the radio and
Genelec
You could see you could see some people in Alex's audience if they take it seriously enough
Could reach the spare
Second or third you could end up with people who are just like well I got a gun ho support Alex
Does just a dead end
I love the other alternative is like
Well if the globalist plans
Unstoppable
I'm dead
My life
Is already over
I can do something that will
Possibly make a less people die why would I not engage in a suicide bombing against the world economic forum
Or something like that
Why wouldn't you do that
If the globalists are going
To kill off
Billions of people within the next
8 years
Unstoppable
The plans that they put in place
The information War
Quite frankly no more purpose
There is no reason to be engaging
In politics
Even if culture stuff
What does it matter if your gay marriage world
Deadman
What are we doing
Yeah of course
I don't understand how you can be really concerned with
The imagination of slow erosion of civilization when it's a couple years left a minute
2gobazaar
Kill everybody off
It is
An excuse
4 people in the audience
It's to carry out violent if they are so inclined
And Alex is a person who does believe the TV is talking
You should be very under
Understanding of what
People in his audience who might believe that these
Speaking directly to them
Right but he also is deeply invested in
Not take responsibility for anything so fair
Obviously this will be turned around to be like why would anyone actually listen to me
Yeah yeah
Yep it's just
F***** up and
So irresponsible
They decided the public is dumb and lazy and weak
And the decision has been made to kill you
And me
This issue is
The only political
Economic cultural issue in Coruscant spiritual in nature
The battle between good vs Evil
Deborah Glendive
Good good versus evil
I mean you know I know nobody listens to his show
Hey that TuneIn like Tucker Carlson and Joe Rogan they don't actually listen to a show
Probably not
Because if you're listening to this s*** when you need some explanation format
Application for wire support
Alex Jones is right about stuff but I should also be clear that I do not believe it when he says that nevermind
And everybody needs to get right with God and yes prophetic vision
Do you think that you did maybe
Couch some of your your commentary about how he is
Write about most you mean now it does seem like Joe would have to come out and be like hey listen
Alex says we're all going to die in 8 years
So since I believe Alex has been right about things the whole f****** time
We all have
To go do s*** now
I don't believe that all these people actually believe him and then like
Look
The amount of money that you on Musk
Princeton
Alex also has been saying that Elon Musk really believes in him when he's fighting the globalist he's on that team Alex
Yeah the money that Joe Rogan and Elon Musk
I have
Could get him out of trouble
In a heartbeat
And you got to wonder why that is
It's
Fun to signal that you believe that Alex is right whatever meets the road no one gives a
The s*** about him and they don't answer
We believe this stuff
Cuz he's a Madman
Yelling nonsense
Why is Alex looking
For $2000000
From his audience
If Elon Musk
100% behind the the movie
Would give him the amount if he gave him $2000000 that's what
Feel it
Spin A Penny
To help you
Legitimately in anybody believe that it was a matter of life and death that Alex beyond the air
It would be so easy
Ephraim Ephraim
These right-wing dingdong absolutely
News
I told you two plus years ago they would start Environmental
Lockdowns
Once you were trained
India and Italy of an ounce
Lockdown shooting
Electricity only
What time is it
The quote
And because the resources have been cut off
Which one
Destroy
The situations in India and Italy are far more complicated than Alex is reporting them because he has no idea what he's talking about
Skim to headline is not trying to make
Make up what he thinks these articles are about to we can jam them it was narratives
Let's start with Italy
Exaggerating an amendment to an Italian government decree that has
Headed by The Parlor
Yet
If it passes summer you not
Have your AC set lower than 25 degrees Celsius
It in the winter you can set your heat
Above 21 degrees Celsius
True
This is not
Climate-related issue nor is it even connected to covid
It has to do with a sharp drop in gas
Supplies in Italy that comes
From not dealing with Russia
40% of Italian oil comes
From Russia so there's a considerable
We're trying to find ways to make this work
The temperature decrees are one such effort although I don't believe for a second that there'll be a way that I could make this
Is enforceable at all
But as a way to make up for the Lost Imports also they're trying to cut new deals with the Republic of Congo and
And Angola
The Trion
Find some more resources
India Alex doesn't even flash up a headline on screen without one or situs or some kind of left my own.
Figure out what he's talking about
Last October there was a big deal with Indian power plant saying that the only an average
4 days worth of
Tacoland stock
Which is due to a much larger constellation of influence
Then just
Covid or
I don't like Alex breaking up India on his show just because
It's so vast in Coppell
Located that even if he
Studied
Realtor
He would be completely and woefully incapable of talking
And the Dynamics with the Colts
Supply in that region of the world
There's some talk of like morkel related issues in the present-day but there's also reports that the coal stock is fine
It's actually kind of hard to tell what the situation is but I can find no evidence
To the clients
What is making about
About India
It's not the same thing that I was just saying but
No it is
It is a decree that you got to keep your temper
Turn these lines
Like having a dad in your house too worried about the thermostat
Put a sweater on
Bright but that's really more of like a
That's that's like a government saying hey we're all in this together
You know we've chosen this path forward as a team and so we're also going to have to deal with the consequences
I can't fully understand
How you would go about like
Do they have inspectors coming in with thermometers or
But I mean that's again that's the point is like this is not something we're going to come into your home
But we are doing anything
In support of Ukraine
Yep I don't know it's
And so
I guess the world is going to lose this kind of
Duff great commentary no
This whole thing
Defeating the globalist I mean we've been doing it for 20 years
Break it down
Chronicle
And then hit leaders who compartmentalize to wake up
It could have been stopped
But now the collapses
Desperate
That we warn everybody
I understand that those initiated the collapse
Are now the ones that are going to preside over the
Isis
Composer for savior
I just put out the cover story to the public
Deadly viruses cause global warming
Bridge collapse the food chain because of global warming
We got to do all this because of your bad
Humans are bad
And then
Collapse depopulation in
Total trans humans take over whoever is left
At the end of that
Beyond dystopic system that they have an issue
Nothing in that clip has any relation
Reality
Taco salad
Expressing his feelings of preempt
Distrust about world events that hasn't even happened yet
In the real world there are
Very complete explanation
Changing climate
Severe consequences in terms of famines and droughts
So there is a drought scientist can say it was caused by climate change and Alex
Can say it's a giant
Conspiracy proven by imaginary white papers and then
We're eating it
Exotic illnesses it's super clear the role climate change
Azan that with animals
Them to migrate to new areas
And decreasing the likelihood that they may contact us
People where they wouldn't have otherwise
This necessarily increases the odds that new viruses and bacteria can be exchanged in from there
The potential for new outbreaks goes up
Alex Gonzales audience on his explanation
Compare everything because his explanation for everything is the same
Call the club
They're doing everything
It's totally definitively proven in this document that Alex refuses to speak to
Specifically about
Almost as if it doesn't
Existen Alex doesn't
This is the same sort of dynamic he has with like the prospect of climate
Did you know it's a pre-emptive explanation that it's all just the globalist as conspiracy to attack all of us
Imperative these things that are likely outcomes of the trends that we're seeing with
The climate weather it's
A change in the amount of usable land that we have for farming or the
Likelihood of encountering species that could introduce new
Viruses and bacteria
These are real things
He's created preemptive
Excuse where it's all a conspiracy until bulshit
I mean the problem
With the
Preemptive is that most of the stuff is
Currently
You know like
This is not tough weed this used to be the trends that you would talk about
Coming
In the near future or you know shortly future
Edits plugin
He's denying something that he can look outside and see
Emma in a faction
It's happening but it probably will be happening much
More severely in a way that impact people much more
It hit hard in his audience
Yes in the future
That's kind of what I mean by that
But I do agree
Is wealth
That is better than Fairborn
So Alex just
Rambling about it
Extermination now we're all going to die
TextNow
We are on it today how it's on his mind
It's always on his mind
Iraqi articles
Land of humanity The Wall Street Journal nbcnews
Times of London
We need dictatorship
This isn't coming out of evil
This is hundreds of years of preparation
Waiting
Building their Networks
While they were rich and Powerful presiding over
Humanity
Level
Super technology
To this because
Out of the mash of the public
Which on average is dumb down
Super Geniuses come out of those groups
Always overthrow
The previous
Generational and the cycle continues
So now the story is that the globalist don't want all of us in the cheap seats getting our hands on life
Engine technology and they're going to need to kill off all the population because from the multitude of the stupid masses
They fear that is super genius will arise to take down their system and I'm going to go
Right now
Alex thinks he's back super Tuesday
Pretty good
I guess either way none of this means anything
I just want to touch on the article that Alex mentioned at the top of the cliff
The first is that op-ed that Alex hasn't read but likes to say the title and the others
This is Alex referencing an op-ed in Bloomberg titled
To save democracy we need a few good dict
This is written by Robert Kaplan and think about him he'd know the Kaplan has been saying s*** like this
4 / 8
Just a quick Google search turned up an article that he wrote
Good movies
Tablet isn't calling for a dictatorship in the United
Specifically about less-developed countries and how often times
For citizens in most countries
The Democratic process is less important than achieving
Fundamental rights
And things
It could be achieved Within
In the context of Greater stability
I think a lot of his points
A half cooked at best but Alex is absolutely misusing bad line if it's opinion
But he definitely didn't read
Reed's we can use it for his own purposes
Which is his MO
I mean if I remember Kaplan
I've read some of that crap and it's essentially like
He's he's is shity argument is like right now dictatorships are bad
They we want to get them towards a democratic system
So we need some sort of
Philosopher-king to bridge the gap
Between dictator and
I'm not sure I haven't read all of his articles but the sense that I got was generally speaking that
The functioning democracy
Can grow out of stability and a strong institutional base
But that is something
Is that a lot of developing countries don't generally have
When it democracies are attempted
I think
B how he would
Put it is
That
Dictatorship
Would allow these countries to solidify create better
Tuschen Heaven from there
Go into a democracy
I don't know if I agree with this
I don't know but
It's not it's not the point that Alex is trying to make it out to be
80 was an iPad
Anyways
Sure sure
Alex has his hand on the pulse
Nino's
About sayings
Those headlines
Other terms
And
History
No super jelly doesn't have those groups
The previous Elites
Generation
The globalist call this an Obama talks about it
What
Weather corporate Tony controls
Biological reproduction
Over your mind surveilling everything you do
The human system as we know it
Is ended
Because it runs the CIA today
Was given the charter to end War
And the answer was end
In all of human competition
Corporate
Medical biomedical tyranny
Over the public were humans are produced that are even allowed to live that are not purely human but are
Chimaeric species
Brave New World published in 19
One brother of Huxley
Julian Huxley
Run the UN for two decades
Watson Tavistock Institute
I was just talking out of his ass here trying to grasp whatever straws he thinks he can pull the sound like he's making the real point
First problem is that he has no idea.
The end of History refers to
Comes from a book written in 1992 by Francis fukuyama
The central thesis of the book is that no political philosophy is better than liberal democracy
And that all human history is bending toward a greater number of people in the world living under liberal
History of the state when all countries are
Rightly so since 1992 the book has been criticized
Is being very naive
Expand the current world but
Alex has no idea what he's talking
The rest of the clip may as well just been word salad with Alex's free associating as best as he can but there's a few quick points I want to bring
One of the Carnegie endowment doesn't run the CIA
Infused diamond for International Peace did not decide to end War by ending men and women in the family and all that
Competition
Alex is confusing him with John D Rockefeller who says competition is a sin
Three the Carnegie endowment
Didn't propose making the plot of Brave New World into a reality
For Julian Huxley didn't found the UN he was the first Secretary General
Of the United Nations educational and scientific organization or UNESCO
A position he was in 42 years not 20
Julian Huxley didn't found the Tavistock
I wasn't using the Tavistock in
Institute and the Tavistock Clinic
The clinic has a history of being involved in providing Healthcare surrounding trans issues whereas the Tavistock
Dude is the center of a
Trying to dunk
Conspiracy theories
The Institute is involved in research and projects largely related
Two social sciences so people have pretty much every conspiracy you can come up with
Swimming Institute spot off from the clinic in 1947 the clinic remained as part of the NHS
Those are six massive problems of the funk
Conspiracy that Alex is just ripping out on the show but
If you're just passively listening to this
Something Alex knows what he's talking about it sounds like this guy really
Pieces together but
Total b*******
I was I was listening to that and I was like
Keeping count that was like a great
Best hits in one sentence
The things that even I remember is being less
The moment he said Tavistock I was like
Nope he got it wrong again
Every time
Beautiful day we die he's not going to understand Tavistock
Yeah I'm like
He didn't even get the Carnegie endowment like
Involvement after World War II
Conspiracy Corral
Cuz largely the conspiracy is that they
Decided that war was a preferable state
And so
Okay that's why I why they
Made World War
Conspiracy theories
Like exist
Inverting that entire thing
There is a very useful when you can make them up on the Fly and don't need anybody to
Protect you
My man that's why they exist that is
Alex goes out to break
Monogram note
Play sinan
4 pieces
Supposedly
And a w
Agenda
Then they're not going to get away with
I'm using this collapse to
Totally depopulate in Waterloo
You trust your mother right
Oops
What's the weather commercial
I guess it is kind of stoppable
Yeah
We're all going to die but
If we do the right things afterwards
Yeah we'll be fine
The survivors
Will be able to
He's Harry Selden
Pulling some foundation bulshit on us
And the collapse will only be 1,000 years instead of the 10,000
Has been prescribed I should be also clear
This is the first Sigma
But still we're still in
First Tech
Is up till like
14 minutes into the show
Is in a mood and It's upsetting but I'm feeling upset about his boots so far
We were talking fine before the show started
Getting infected with it
Yes he's at that's
The gift of his oratory skills
Yeah
So
Alex comes back from break and by that I mean Alex doesn't come back from break
Smart
Instead he's playing a clip
Tucker Carlson interviewing
Alex's former employee Savannah
And I found a couple things kind of interesting about the
This clip play a little bit of a
Maybe
What's Alex Jones
Talk to him to this day think that he's great and I think that
Many more people should have been
When she was in there because I was actually there I remember
Yeah I was in Labrador
And I've regretted it ever since
I didn't come out of the box
Wow
You are dead Tucker 90% of the world's population is dead
Special you cuz Patriots are f******
Alex should still be on the air
Don't you think it's so funny though the alike
Yeah I didn't support him cuz I was fishing.
Yep
Either it's too late
I do I do love that
So I think
All of Alex's employees
The exception of maybe David Knight
Maybe
No something
Sure he was wrong about a lot of stuff
But he seemed like he knew something
Sure
Pretty much everybody else at Alex's hired has been
Drastically unqualified
Most of them won contests
People at rallies and yelled at them and then edited videos of him
Himself doing that
And also that great demo tape
Some people just make dank memes for him
Count to dankula
Carpe donktum
Yeah it so Savannah is talking to Tucker and I think that she was
Dreadfully unqualified
I really didn't have an introduction into politics but
Adorned a lot of
Alex Jones
Front end
Everything that she was telling me was not false the people who condemned him and say that he's a crazy conspiracy theorist do not listen to his show every
Free single day because I work for him for two and a half
The three branches of government when I started
That's going to be I think
Probably a deal-breaker I'm running a news and political theme
Maybe learn a little bit more and reapply
I don't
Think that you can handle this I think for Alex is actually perfect because
Cheese and know so little
That you get to inform all of her opinions and ideas about what is real and what is that I think Alex
Is specifically hires tabula rasa
If you will
What do you think the three branches of government
Are you sure you still do the Deep state.
Liberty that's got to be one of the Rhinos now the branches are on the tree of Liberty
So one more clippings stalker thing
Savannah is talking about why no one defended Alex when he was getting kicked off everything
And this is just so fun
Talking funny
Why do you think
I didn't
Alex Jones today
But why do you
Think that morn conservative media didn't take a poop
Principled stand against censorship
Because Alex was off-limits
Look at the fact that right now talk are so many and conservative media who wouldn't even mention Alex Jones's name
Now say his name on a regular basis so Alex Jones Is Right Alex Jones
We see this constantly okay
The people in the conservative media
Truth until it goes mainstream and they're allowed to do it even in the conservative right-wing
Action the reason why we lose it's because we continue to wait for the left
Deliver media the mainstream media to allow us to tell us when we are allowed to tell the truth
About Tucker
That's what Tucker did
100%
Exactly what Tucker did it might have been slightly ahead of some other
Folks but some people still are I mean
You had
Plenty of Infowars employees on your show in the past few years since
Alex has been kicked off.
Not really reference them as Infowars under their credit
Well not really
I don't know I mean send Savannah Hernandez
He played that video of Harrison
But he didn't have him off I don't think
I don't know yeah
Play Imagine
Rambo Joby
Ignitor showed up he hasn't he hasn't pulled all this stuff and been like directly from end
Infowars my buddy you know
He's very clearly they're not me
It should be the easiest thing in the world
I mean it's their main credit
But also could be made
That like
You're arguing perhaps that maybe you should have had Alex on himself
Why why not
Arguing
It's telling that
He wouldn't reference
It's them as being Infowars employees
Or because they'll be taking more serious or
Have Alex on
Himself absolutely maybe he realizes
But that would be a disservice
To trying to rehab Alex's in it
Actually on
Probably would hurt
The cars
Alex
These people all have these very major and obvious criticisms of you what's your response
I was just going to do all of those Alex has a lampshade on his head
Oh okay that's why you got bad
Clip of Mike Tyson on Rogan talk
About how Alex is right about stuff
And then Mike Tyson
And starts talking about how he's
Convinced that somewhere in the world rich people are hunt
Looking for people for sport
Well
I don't know if that's one of his big issues but
I mean
The plot of the most dangerous game is a very easy one to just transpose into real life in a lot of movies
Particularly one
Got really upset about not too long ago
So it's comes back
But he's interest back
Until my great frustration
Is this
If you go back to shows we did 28 years ago 25 years ago 20 years ago
We talked about
Infrastructure
Slowly destroy civilization
Integrated global
Crisis out of which the One World Government
What the hell
Now
I don't deserve credit
For knowing that
No no you don't
This is a fairly generous way to sum up Alex's career and I will grant
That these are all themes that he's filled with throughout his time on air but I have some serious problems without this is being
Disgust
The first is that he's being so vague as to render what he saying meaning
Define anything is slowly destroying society and then give yourself an unearned pat on the back
The second problem is more serious and that is that Alex did
Say that the globalists are trying to order
Castrate a collapse for the past 28 years
He said that specific things that have happened
And were the globalists trying to order
Orchestrated collapse that never came
Over and over and over
Every year was the summer of Rage
Back when I was talking to
Gold every single comment from the fed and every geopolitical issue was proof of the globalist are about to
Crash the dollar
You should probably buy some
Anytime Alex has been on air there is even better
Actual collapse
Sits and we've recovered from that which shouldn't have happened
If they were truly the globalist plot
To bring in there one world government
A 2008-2009 it should have been over
And yet it was
Alex isn't right and he's never been right
The only way to make him seem right is taken statements completely out of context
And deprive them of the meaning
In which he said that
Authorial intent
Is critical theory
However in terms of finding out whether Alex
Full of b*******
But yeah
This clip here where he's talking about how he doesn't deserve credit for the revelations he's had throughout his career as a way for him to weave into
Some of his major sources
Throughout his career
Imma take them one by one because I think it's a pretty shocking list
Definitely wouldn't cop to some of this
At other points in his career
This seems like a bit of a reveal
There's a person
I don't deserve credit
For knowing that
John Coleman was high-level MI6
He came out with the plan
Thirty-plus years ago
Alex around much and maybe part of that with death due to the fact that
House inside a bit crazy
Coleman wrote a book in 1992 called conspirators hierarchy
The story of the committee of 300
I can find no evidence that he's actually former MI6 and given the track record of people who we run into from this show
I don't accept lofty resumes without some sort of verification
It's possible that he was actually an agent and I'll assume it is true because I don't care
You know what's crazy he was also a black belt in Jiu-Jitsu
So I decided to take a little look at this book and immediately at the broad
Introduction Coleman is explaining that he came to the United States in 1969 and no one knew about all these
Secret societies that he was talking about to put out a little tape to educate folks
People started dropping all the
These names that like
I think they knew s*** about the Venetian black nobility there but I didn't know anything about it
This leads him to say quote
I consoled myself with the thought that imitation is the sincerest form of flattery
I pursued my investigations pressing on in the face of severe risk
The tax on myself in my wife Financial losses
Does continual harassment
Threats
I'm km
All part of a carefully crafted and orchestrated program to discredit me run by government agents and informers
Embedded in the so-called Christian right-wing the identity movement did right-wing paper eeotic group
These agents operated and still operate under cover of strong and fearless outspoken opposition to Judaism
Their main enemy they would have us believe
Correctly these agents were sent it to Christian identity movement type groups
Credit Karma
And they maintain their cover by being really anti-semitic so they would fit in
Yeah
So far so good
Call swag
Coleman goes on to explain who these folks were
Quotes
These agent informers are letting
Controlled by a group of homosexuals who are well-liked and well-respected
Wait so
These hidden people
Undercover anti-semite
Who are actually
But they're actually part of the
I mean like
Gay agenda
Or whatever it is
I'm not sure if he's saying that they themselves are gay but they're yes they work for
Well-liked and well-respected
It's a mess
This group is a sprawling, bulshit
At one point Coleman claims at the Tavistock in
Who created The Beatles in order to introduce destructive ideas into American culture such as the word
Cool and teenager
That sounds true
12/8 tonal music systems
Quote taken from the music of the cult of Dionysus and the ball priesthood of adorno
That does explain why the Beatles got popular cuz they weren't that good man
I was looking over his references page in his book and I noticed a strange quote he was taking from an HG Wells book
It's kind of foundational in terms of his argument that this Committee of 300
Had plans to kill everyone
Coban wrap
Quote in this work Wells describes how the new world order
There which he calls the new Republic useless
Skeeter's excess population will be getting rid of
So you know they're going to
Go off everybody sure
He cites this is coming from the open
Conspiracy but it actually comes from another book all together
It's from the book
Anticipation
Switch doesn't have quite as useful of a title
The premise of anticipation does Wells dealing with like
Future predictions
Sled like
One of the big ones is the
Invention and proliferation
The automobile and he predicts
Some stuff in this book like
Thetollroads
And it's cities will become more distributed basically what we now call the suburbs
Like yeah the write-up
Good work HG
Unfortunately the last chapter
Particularly not great
Hold I anticipate that a certain portion of the population
A small minority for example of selected with indisputable e transmittable diseases
With transmissible mental disorders such as the idiots incurable habits
The mind is the
Craven for intoxication
They exist only on suffering
Out of pity and patience and all the understanding that they do not propagate
And I don't foresee any reason to stay
Suppose that they will hesitate
To kill one that suffering has abused goddamnit
Alright
Sickness there is no way around this that chapter is horrible so horrible infected within a few years of writing the book Wells was
Is arguing against
Yeah yeah yeah
This was published in 1901 and could be argued to be his first
Book of this sort and it's really only just
A few years after he published War of the Worlds
None of this makes these positions of a text
It's okay or any better but it's disingenuous to characterize well
Entire career base
I bring this up because this is a huge knock-on cold
A giant part of the whole conspiracy thing is that HG Wells book proves that the elites plan to kill everyone off
And he gets the book wrong
And it's not just in the reference page
What he's talking about the committee of 300 he says quote it strives towards a One World Government rather well described
By one of its late members h.g. Wells
It is work commissioned by the committee which Wells boldly called the open
Conspiracy
Did King Leonidas call for that himself
I do believe that at Harkins to that clear
Call themselves The Olympian
Appears he has a better name and it was written 27 years later when Wells was in full swing and his philosophy
Happy career
So it seems worse that he'll be riding that kind of s*** at that
I think that's part of this name at this point Coleman does something really sneaky though in the text
He's established
The pattern of presenting quotes from other text
In Italian
So he includes a mostly but I am passage from Wells
Then says quote
Like George Orwell's 1984 Wells of the count is a Mass Appeal for a one world government
Summarize the intent and purpose
Of the committee of 300
Pasty following
Conditions
After this point there were three and a half full pages of italic
Which is obviously meant to give the appearance of this is something that Wells had
Right right and you can see this misrepresentation paying dividends
To this day
Some great
Reset conspiracy theory beam every use part of this passage
Attributing it to Klaus Schwab
And others to h.g. Wells
But in reality
It's just something Coleman tried to pass off as a quotation by making it up himself
And presented in italics it is
Yep the passage is as follows
At least four billion useless eaters shall be eliminated by the year 2050 by means of limited Wars organized
Epidemics of fatal rapid-acting diseases and starvation
Energy food and water shall be kept at subsistence levels for the non-elite
Starting with the white populations of Western Europe and North America and then spreading to other races
The population of Canada Western Europe in United States will be decimated more rapidly than on other continents
Until the world population reaches a manageable level of 1 billion
With 500 million will
Consists of Chinese and Japanese races
Selected because they are people who have been regimented for centuries
At work accustomed to obeying Authority without question
Really doesn't take much of a scratch
To get to the races
Under most if not all of these
Maybe a lot of
What
Racism
Vertigo everywhere abuse of the way that information
Presented
Like you can trace it through
Misunderstandings and
Conspiracy bulshit
Since then
I mean
You know it is
It is one of those things where are you
It is so fascinating
Because we get to the you find like the progenitor of these
These things and it sucks you up because you kind of don't think these things have
Gabrielle beginning
You know like they just kind of congealed
Like the first time I found out Dusty Baker invented the high five
It's like
That can't be real
It's only that old WhatsApp
So I wasn't
No I don't know if
If he actually was the original progenitor of these ideas
But
In his book which is
By this revelation
His traces back like a lot of things
Especially this HD Wells station being misused
It traces back to him but he may have gotten it from some like
Newsletter or something or some other Bowl
Percent
This is a heavily influential thing
It's totally full of s***
Anyway
Long story short this book is full of s***
But you can definitely see how some of the ways that this is influenced Alex's worldview
Also there's a weirdly long section about the killing of Aldo Moro in
Steve pieczenik doesn't come up at all which I found defensive
Crazy
Why I don't know
Alex's First Source is a crazy assholes who also thinks you can get arrested in Canada if you dare try to expose the fact
The Jews run the country
I forgot to mention that earlier hated to
Generally speaking if you
So we're off to a good start
In terms of his citation this is Sparta
Here's an extra
He told me all of this
According to his profile on the Air Force's website
Parton was a quote
The deputy for systems Aeronautical Systems
Division
At Wright-Patterson Air Force
1955 you didn't exchange program with the ballistic
Six Research Laboratories where he worked on it Armament project
Which led to him being assigned to the
Directorate as a assistant for advanced weapons concept
70 was the commander of the Air Force Armament Laboratories
So there's definitely some truth that he had experience in this area and had a pretty good resume
That's what I can find no evidence
That he wasn't any Secret
Space program but I guess if I could then it wouldn't be
Be so Secret
I mean
I assume he's still alive and rip
So that would explain those
I think that the secret space program thing Alex's mixing partner up with General stubblebine
I think it is conflating there
Import
In terms of his
I have no idea what else has told Alex but his
Main significance to the
Conspiracy world is that he insisted that the Oklahoma City bombing couldn't have been caused by mcveigh's bomb
He tried to presented evidence to a grand jury and they were not
Tim Preston said
No thank you
All the same he became a huge hero in the right-wing militia type Community because he lends an air of credibility to the theory
The baby to be except
Blame someone else for Timothy McVeigh terrorist
I've dabbled in Parton
And stuff and I don't really take
Any of it very seriously and I don't know how much he has to say outside of the OKC stuff
Susan weird inclusion in the list unless Alex is trying to come up with the most credible sounding people that he's
Been able to get to be on his show
I got my assumed the next one is just
Zach
No we pretend that didn't happen
I like that
Ganga
High-level FBI agent Ted Gunderson told me every
Was it one point in the FBI is reputation
The fires of
The satanic panic in general
And the McMartin preschool case in
Pacific
We've gone over tab in the past so I'm going to let this be a briefs
Synopsis
Ted was a craven opportunistic lunatic
Who makes sense that Alex's all reverent of them though so
Call Alex is doing the trying to profit off another satanic panic
You just tried to pull a Gundersen without having an impressive FBI resume to throw away doing
Yeah I mean
In his situation that's way better than gundry
I mean aside from the view can be sued into Oblivion
Sure
Series of luminaries
Each at the top of their field
Play the highest
Batman the Band-Aid comes off
Those men now
In hindsight
Society
Got it 100
Depression trial
We stand on their shoulders
Show me other people getting killed right now
What an absolute pile of s*** coward Alex's
The reason is getting chills is cuz he's finally just letting it out and expressing what he's believed all along the tri-tip
What time do you do
For most of his career Alex pretended not to be into
The John Birch Society because he knew damn well that if he
He said that he was Saudi
Deeply inspired by them you'd be seen as aperture and no one would take him seriously because people were where
The John Birch Society and thought they were a bunch of assholes
People also correctly knew that they were in
Extremely right-wing organization
There was no way to pretend to be above the left-right Paradigm farewell knew you were a Bircher
Essentially brand you accurately is a fringe right-wing figure and then all
The criticisms of people like Bush that you're making
Would be better understood for what they were
Alex had that stuff because it was important to his career and critical to him being taken
At all seriously by anybody in the 90s
The idiots mindlessly tweeting Alex Jones was right memes probably have no idea who the birchers were what they say
Pretty much safer
To come clean
Alex has been pretty much mask off about his bigotry in the last few years but this
Feels like an intellectual mask off kind of moment
He's giving it up to these icons who were right about everything
A frog lunatic
In OKC bombing truther a guy who ruin people's lives in the satanic panic and the John
Society
What a loser
Wow also to be clear if Alex believes that the JBS was right about everything that's basically him opening
Declaring his opposition to civil rights
Good for him
I mean I think he was
Fairly open to that
Before but if you say that you're a big fan of the John Birch Society they were one hundred percent right
You are also saying that we should live in a white male dominated Society
Purely Prada
Stand
A lot of
Pinterest ruling everything I mean that's that's just baked in there you know you can't let rich people develop a fart
Society in trouble
So after giving it up
Relatively speaking in my world Somali pirates
Existence
Alex brings up the heat
He couldn't go on-air last segment
That's why you played those videos
He's
It's crying
Maybe a little bit of Tears might be a little we play little soft
Please w
If we warn people we would have a chance to stop it
But I also thought about looking out of the future
What it would be like if we failed to stop
The initiation of their final plan
What would be like
I couldn't even go on
Eclipse
Because
I love you a lot
I really appreciate you
I got terminal cancer
Play she'll be dead in six months
A couple times
And I smile at you like tell you they love you and then you're at the funeral they're dead
And that's what this is I'm here
Telling you
Die
You're going to die
We're all going to die
I like your grandma sitting there having a cup of coffee across the table from you
Tell her that she's always going to love you and always going to be there
The Chicago Died
Life Goes On
To children and grandchildren does
This planet doesn't go on
Wentworth
Holy
S*** Isis bad
Who's bad
Not least
Because this is more like
Your grandma coming to you
For every 6 months
What's for the past 20 years saying
6 months
Bright going to be dead in six months
I meant also conspicuously this time when it
It seems a little bit more severe than sometimes in the past
It coincides with her
Having a
Huge lawsuit he's going to lose
I'm going to be dead in six months
But what's important
It's now my narcissism has allowed me to
You finally cross that bridge and say if I die
The world ends with me still just
Essentially
Projection
Of his own
Individual experience being
Forced onto his audience
View vet like whatever is happen
Nothing to me is happening to the world
Yeah
It look I mean
This
You know something all of your children are going to die
Your ancestral memories while
Be carried on into the future or whatever
Wake me up it is
You know what what's happening
What all of the ancestors from the past are crying out
Alright
Yeah
Domata grandmother saying
I want to go home my family.
I'm going to stop
Good night too I'm ready to die
You say I understand Irish
But your decision
Limelife
You live on
Your children and their children good people
Their life meant something and if they cut us off like this
And this incredibly ancient journey of our species it is
It is a crime never before committed on this planet
That is just so unspeakable to commit a lot
Kryoz
All of my will
Cries Out
I just bags all of your allies
Distractions
They're all interesting in fondant
How old is news is amazing
Impartial
I'm a spiritual fall of Man
Spiritual battle were in
And the fact that were undoubtedly
The end of days
Being initiated by
The Antichrist
Forces
Making the way
Transhumanist
And so on my metaphysical mean
I
Beg you on my knees
Paralyzed
This is the transmission
This is the Waring this is why they fear us
This is why they hate me above
Anyone else
It's because I know they're playing
I was putting this position
By God
Okay
Chosen by God
Freaking me out I am I am calling for a 10-year moratorium
On the entire
Nobody can claim it's the end times for a decade with a f****** break
Make us miss you card predictions
Has it not been the end
Yeah
You know just give me 10 years
8 frankly maybe that's a smart for you cuz I don't finally
Can happen
In wrestling terms of the end times are Overexposed
Play come back baby exactly you might need to go get a new gimmick
Bring it back and would like it more
D Revelation right
You can't tell you can't make it
Is stunning Steve Austin or the the ringmaster got to go away and come back balls
Yes I guess the system hates Alex cuz God chose him
To just send his message of warning
This is Cher
Messed up
What do you think about the
I mean
Wow
Just real sad this interesting
Hernandez will come on Tucker show and say
They hate Alex because he
He tells the truth and they're worried about how he
He's honest about things where's Alex his own version of it is
The devil right as manifested by
Social media companies
It's naturally they're scared that he was chosen by God
To destroy they're planted by the system
Find it offense
Savannah Hernandez actually I find it offensive that
Anybody on this f****** planet
Can say that the problem
We that you have is that you
You don't watch Alex everyday
What you existed across the world should be towed
Totally transparent about this anymore
Long stretches where I bought today
Play more than
Is it healthy
But yeah I can't I can't bear the the like
Boredom
Of watching everyday
Yeah but you did your
Time to stretch in solitaire
Yeah I can say pretty can greatly that the problem isn't that people aren't watching enough of them
Load of s*** how dare you
Yelp
Sunway Alex was prepared
To be euhus
This voice
From God
Claims that he's not been taught lesson and after lesson after lesson in Iowa I would suggest that they sell Mike's Beer
Is Learning lesson
No constantly make similar Miss
Witness Protection
By God
None of it is May
Very long
Responsibility
Where We Are
Idaho weather event are you are now
To be a light in the world
In this coming total darkness
The Bible tells is one-fourth of yours will be killed
For the planets reversed
And he's going to be action that will reverse that plan
A lot of us aren't going to make it
But that's okay because our Spirits are eternal
But I want you to know
That I love you
And I appreciate you
I stand with you
Forever
How do you sing with me
What's a quarter of the world is going to die
Best-case scenario
I'm telling you
It does not get more like oh that's how you were raised
Then a
Half hour stretch of you're all going to die everything's awful
But listen
I love you and you're very important
Exactly
And
What's f******
Text stop pretending
This is like a day and a half after he finished his Moneyball
Yeah that's a really good point Towers
Reflector raised $2000000 to keep it for now we're all dead
And no matter what we do 6 months from now
Okay
Connect
Very specifically
If the world is going to end only 48 hours after a money Bob
Or conversely it did go well he got what he needed out of it and I also got some
Bad News Bear
I paid off that million-dollar
Probably or at least
Recoup
Write what you would do right
Now that we're cooking
Anyway devil doesn't want us to go to space
Metro
And there are a lot of very twisted
Very old forces that hate us
Because of our success
We've already done
Cosmos
That are attempting
To stop us here
Before this important mission is launched
Admission
Taking place in the third heaven
What
F*** off
Did not even try to describe to you
This is a say one cannot be told about the Matrix you must see
The devil's false constructs
Well it is even
More attached to try to describe
The next one
So is Alex applying the mission
To go to space so you can be reinforcements for a battle in heaven
I guess
I know what it sounds like
And you know
What's weird about this in my head
Is that the Hubble Space Telescope
Is almost completely alive
It's almost perfect right now they've sent back the most
The highest resolution image
We can literally see in a photograph
Billions of years in the past
Billions are almost to the very beginning of the universe
Did you see a third heaven in there
No but why would you
So the chick the use of the term third heaven is
Audubon brand for Alex actually you know that term
It's all a bit strange to hear that
It's a term associated with the Church of Latter-day Saints
It's largely
And a lot of figures that Alex looks up to from the extreme right-wing anti-communism World we're Mormon
Looks like the sky was in family room
They're references to the third heaven and extra biblical text but also one and second
10 Corinthians
In the Bible
And there's understanding that usually start around 2
The first Heaven is the sky
The second is space and then the third is where the angels
And God bless
It's pretty obscure terminology so it's weird
To be using it
It's great to hear that Alex is reporting to his audience that there's a war going on in heaven
There's never
A moment
Even that's the worst part even though he's been yelling at us all this time about how he's safe and God and everything
All of a sudden now I found out even when I die
I'm going to have to go fight another f****** War
That's brutal
Universe
Yeah
I was wrong
Great news.
Even if he is right
Don't be mad at God
Destroyermen
The blueprint
Download
Defeatist
And
That is a great Solace we have
But we must not hate God
Consciousness
We must first before giving Godlike power
Stacy Wilson
Physically cellular leaffilter
So that we will not be part of the future
God is going to put us through
Garbage can
So I guess a
Quarter of the world dying as a cleansing ritual
Yep sweet
Sweet
Yeah so wait is he
For Oregon
Ninety percent of the population
Be at least in favor it seems of
Recorder
Yeah I mean
It really does seem like God's plan in the globalist playing sooner or later start dovetailing together every time
Kind of like a Continuum problem
Right right
Play one is too high the others to Lowe's in the middle never find the
Zaxby
40% of the world dying
I don't know
It anything over 50 is not accept
Obviously
To kill off a quarter of the population that I guess that Alec with Alex's describing is that
God's will
Carrying out God's will
I don't know this is just dumb
Anyway
Now that everything changes
And now for something completely different because the second hour start in Rochester
Here's where we're at
As our mutual friend Tucker Carlson says
They don't have
White people who have a lot of time
They act like people who are frantic to cancel the Constitution
Because they are running out of time
Minority
They know that we are the majority
They know people are waking up
They know Infowars and
Frank's Beach.
A handful of others real America's voice
Right side broadcasting is a very few
Patriotic
Lights out there the where the truth can still be heard
But the American people are waking up
And that's because of him for Wars
Everybody else's
The public
ProTrac comforce destroying us
All of us America too far away
I agree with that Alex we can win now. We were all going to die
I I know he apologized and said sorry and said we were all going to die
And then he said he loves us
And now we're going to be fine
But Rogers here now
Yeah it's hurts so much
Drew believes that
GOP can win whatever in the midterm
Cherokee
Having some crazy people in there
William like real Fringe lunatic
She's got to be
The key
The key you should not donate to the GOP
People who voted for Joe Biden come up to me in public and say
They made show there is a red
Tide coming
But it's important that people understand that the election
A republican majority
In the house
Will change nothing whatsoever
The key here is to have a subset
Patriots
In both houses could be 10 to 15
Women
In the house
As many as three or four in the Senate
Who can use their leverage to change the agenda
Save the country
The Republican establishment
Shutdown
Populist movement
They fear that came through
The others
The key here is realizing just getting Republicans elected it's on a fantasy of the 70s hardcore groups
Bully pulpit
There's no question.
Are money the Republican National Committee
We're sending their money to the Republican Congressional committee has senatorial committee
Please folks
Guardian foresight said that contribution here
Legal defense fund
So
Alex
Uno
I don't even understand
The margins of
Electoral like
A few people in there matter this is Unstoppable I think Rodger stone is right
No Rodger is right
No I mean like
For his world
Strategically Q correct
Having some crazy people in there in order to be blocks
That the
Mainline party needs in order to get things done
Is the best way to force your agenda through
Bucket money versus big
Yes
He's coming from place that makes coherent
Does not
The rest of the ship
Yeah
But you know yours were
Aware of
That hour-by-hour
Whether or not we live or die this is like Schrodinger's genocide I totally agree
Like I can't I can't put this more bluntly then
The experience of listening to the show if you believe him has got to be bewildering
And
Threatening
Yeah I mean
That's
Go through the emotional experience of what that first hour would have been
To someone who believes them
And then the jarring arrival of Rodger Stone
And it seems like
Nothing
Nothing that was said earlier matters
Or was real now electoral victories are somehow relevant
Again it's ridiculous
Iowa Biden going to be gone soon
After the election
They will they themselves will enact
The 25th Amendment and removed
And they were lionize your mother doing it
This great Statesman is just too ill to do the job
He gave 100-percent to his country
Because he's not well
We have to sideline him
For his own good
Remember it takes
A majority
Of the
Cabinet
Plus the vice president
Under the 25th Amendment
To remove gel by
So when does it happen
Right after the election almost immediately after the election
So let's keep an eye on that
So who's going to be the new president this time, Harris probably
That's boring for the globalist
Right now it's going to happen, Harris will become president the speaker will be vice president
No that's how that works out
Yes that'll be Hillary
Bringing Satan
And then Obama will be the king of
Hell because he's the hell will become a Muslim caliphate
Isn't that what we're become dukes and duchesses
Let's bring it all together better
How many times have we heard that the president is going to be removed and replaced by the vice president to
We got a real hard deadline on this one so that you would happen
Rodger also think
Kevin McCarthy the leader of the GOP is not
Cutthroat enough
But we already have 4 McCarthy there it is
He doesn't
He's not playing for
This guy doesn't have the courage
To be reviewing way of saying that
Fight to the Democrats
Against
What
He lives with Frank Lawrence
Izzy Izzy blackmailed is he like
Alex is my ghost
Wild
Lot of revealing their thought patterns here
While delivering in tokatli
You've trapped in those early days of anti-communism
Hey man
If he's gay
We can probably blackmail
That's probably I was going to work
Do you have to be so you take a note
I I just think that Rodger saying not Playing for Keeps has the most
Revealing statement that you
You can make because yes
He's right
Kevin McCarthy is playing
For an election
Yeah assuming that one can be won or lost
Rodger stone is playing
Ford no electrical power
Forever absolute
Part of that also is
Is there preemptive
Declaration that the election will be stolen of course
That's part of that Playing for Keeps
Videos Rodger getting in that
Of course
Questioning
Election outcomes
What are you predicting for 2022
My prediction is pretty
Is pretty dire
Excuse
4 lockdowns but more precisely
They will rush through legislation which will be sign
It says
Now
Because it's too dangerous for folks to go to polling places
It's too dangerous for them to show up on
Here's a chip off Alex
I don't think anybody voted for macaron
Interesting
Iris
Anybody voted for macro nobody
It's going to be great to be someone
On Infowars
Because you can
Just improvise stuff and riff
Thoughts
I called them predictions and that there is no Conte
Consequence when all of your predictions are s***
I don't think it should be against the law
To claim that intellect
Installing
No
I do think there should be stay
At this point
If you're going to claim that the election is stolen
You've got to have something
That hanging over your head if you're wrong like
I don't know I mean like
Let's let's take it to place where the steaks
Pixar even just
Understood on the terms of like
Credibility
You have two tattoo on your forehead I was wrong about the election being stolen
Ever so if you do TV then guess what everybody's going to see the first thing
I was wrong about the election being maybe I'm okay with that in a metaphor
There should be
Some sort of a
Consequence
Is a broad term
And I think there should be some kind of like a detriment
I think that's the same thing with like so much of the Infowars.
100 albatrosses around Alex's failed
Nonsense
Bulshit
But he's carrying around with him and pretending he never said
I'm sure will likely be the case
Rodger know that's what I'm saying we need to turn the albatross from metaphorical to
Literal
A Paris shirt
It says you need to be a public and constant reminder of what you are I think what you're getting at
Getting at 2 is that like the reason that this is allowed to go on and then get away with it as there's literally no
Accountability
And
Somehow that
Changing would be
I mean I think
Quote unquote
Earlier in the show we heard Alex say that God chose him
For this mission
Now he's hedging things a little
A revolutionary leader
The globalist see me is that
Firestone and a few others is that so
We are your Champions champions
But
I tell you that
This is big legs
Point Blank Range
We're coming into them because they know that
Where is
Call
Blue people
Make donations infowarsstore.com
Thank you and salute you
You are 1776 2.0
I want a t-shirt books filmed
Rodger seems to have reinvigorated Alex's beliefs
So tomorrow is
I'm just
Yeah it is really do have a lot more energy than I do a parent
Or it takes less energy to be full of s*** that it does
To figure out
They're full of s***
Yeah
Yeah I think trying to disentangle their nonsense is exhausting
That makes Morse
This is this is a load of s***
Basically
Expressing
He'll say that it's not support of Russia
Functionally it is
My family members were mowed down by Russian tanks
In Budapest
In 1956
Alex Jones
All your Rodger Stone
Can you tell the truth about what's really happening in Ukraine
Million-dollar
Dominium in Miami Beach by the way
He's playing the role of the president
This war is not about
Say it's about
Is the narrative it's based on a comedy sketch that delinsky did back in
Taxing day is that
Stewed crowds have discovered
And they're pretending it's Gaper
It's pretty telling that Alex is pushing this very stupid in.
Really illustrates how bad the information he passes on to his audio
So this is the second time that he's used
False or misleading information to claim that someone's gay and being black
More than should happen in a day it's very weird
Yeah it's very weird
Superheroes mind is going
And I think that's
God damn if you are ancestors
Are you erase memory they're crying out and they are crying out because of stuff I would imagine that
If I was Rodger Stone the ancestor
Who had been murdered by the Russian
Pinstripe
I would not be on board
Stop
Oroville
Get out get out I'm just saying maybe they're crying
So the third hour is Rodger and Alex
Hanging out with Bobby Barnes
To give some World analysis
What a trio shitbags
Yes and I don't care
I'm not interested at all
I listen to it and was bored but he did say one thing that is felt like I want to touch on
Component
The French elections today
A pen
Territories outside of the Continental control in other places like Martinique wailupe excetera
These places showed up
3240 Point swing from 2017 to 2022
In favor of Le Pen
Yet no no place inside the
The continent
In France
Showed any such similar swing
Royal she lost
Exactly and he replaces that she lost by
By 50 points last
I mean it
That kind of margin swing
Cbiz a fun game
Bring the pain did much better than expected in French territories outside the borders of France like Guadalupe Martinique in
Reunions
In order to explain this Barnes has decided to suggest that this is proof that macron was able to steal the election in places in
Inside France
What's on my wasn't able to affect the vote totals
In these other territory
It's too far away
Using the exact same information and evidence
Why not play the opposite game
Minecraft The Conspiracy that lepere was able to steal a lot more votes in the
Cuz they were outside of
The country's borders
You could use the geographical distance to pretend that they must have shotty ballot condole
I know you're using a different point of view I mean it makes just as much sense it's all arbitrary bulshit
The point here is that this
Conspiracy hinges on nothing
And the alternative
Conspiracy makes as much
Barnes is covering the story this way because lappin is an extreme right-wing figure matches the model of a l Barnes would want in the world
Regardless of the excuses
Every failing of such a leader needs
It speaks playing by them getting screwed by
Vasken's
In reality lapenna macron both lost in the first round of voting in these / 2
These territories to the far-left candidates
Jean-Luc melenchon
Which
In the context of the later vote
There's a one element of this that was like today
Before right mobilizing some votes but probably a much larger part of it is people in these territories not liking how things are going
Going for them under macron
And voting
Against him as opposed to vote
For the pain
It's a bit unpredicted and political scientist who spoke to the guardian where cut
Slightly off guard but it also makes
Complete science
People in these territories have different immediate
Concerns the books of Mainland France
It makes sense that you might see slightly
Voting patterns
Based on those
Immediate
Well I mean it's not like
Macron or the last president or the president before that or the present before that is really done much
To make their lives a lot better so true
Yeah it's kind
End of the way there and their
The preferred candidate
What's going to try
Network for somebody
Or or
Maybe macron did rig all of those in France that somehow wasn't able to
Forgot to do the overseas vote
I love the idea that
No one voted for
Macron
I want it
Well that's Roger's idea Barnes a little more nuanced Roots build
The big swing
Now he needs
The train under Steve
So we come to the end of the Sandman I will say
I don't know what to think
Honestly like obviously the second and third hours
When Alex has people around
He certainly in a much different mood
What's the first hour to me in a way that a lot of times
Things.
Because it is incest
It goes on and on
He doesn't storm off
You just
Doesn't start
The
Did the second segment is clips
Feels more like somebody who's actually in a like
Yeah
Yeah I personally don't appreciate being told I'm going to die
By anybody
Barbecue no like I don't take it
Fun
But generally speaking it's been prior to some very negative
Outcomes
And then the other time it was like guide
The doctor
Yes
And I'm interested to see where it goes
We're recording this on Tuesday and into a little bit of his show today
He was back in a down mood when he was talking alone
What does responding to the news that Elon Musk bought Twitter
Andy was not
Convinced it was going to change much
That's the first good analysis I think I've seen from him in a long long. He's up maybe we'll maybe we'll get back on we'll see
Still kind of morose
I don't know what to believe
That the first hour was
Him
Externalizing and projecting his own situation on the audience
The legal situation that he's in is
Unstoppable at this point
And so the global is Doom is Unstoppable
Once he had someone like Rodger around and then Barnes
Think about self each other and some of that Gloom lifted for him and
Be kind of forgot about his troubles Chicken around about maybe some people are gay and blackmail
Right right right now when I'm on my downstate and I'm left alone with my thoughts that's that's the worst time to be left alone with my
I'm grateful that I don't have a radio show that I have to do
So I can project them onto everybody feeling an hour telling everyone they're going to die
Every time I'm always like that God I'm not telling everybody they're going to die right now
The bottom line that I would say regardless of what the explanation for any of the stuff is
The invisible
The essential thing is this is
F****** Urus
You can't do sit like this
You can't
Because he's not
He's not saying these kind of things as like abstract possibilities
If you saying
This can't be stopped
Within a few years
Lisa
Quarter of the world will be dead because of the globalist
Plants that again cannot be stopped right
Amarin
Sticking around about like
Trivial electoral politics
And who Trump is going to endorse
The next hour
Inappropriate
This is just
Bulshit
Yeah I mean it'll be a little bit like hey everybody going to die alright
Now let's get to the car dash
Lawsuit
You take a lawsuit very serious saving us from 90s
Percent dead or whatever
I'm interested to see what comes of this but
It may be nothing
Maybe Alex will be off air
A whole lot of faith in making that predict
Action based on by
Years of
Play Doom and Gloom Celtics
Something that feels different about that
Who knows maybe that's just me
Overthinking
We'll see if Alex is correct
Will be back but until then
Like to wish you all
Happy dreamy creamy sauce
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color