Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge vype.com
For the elders Lane and talk a little bit about Alex Jones
Indeed we are.
Quick question what's up
Today is
Of course the dreamy creamy summer is
In full effect
And I've been getting
Some feedback
Some folks that are concerned that the dreamy creamy summer
May not be
You know there's people with other diets you know that don't involve
Dairy
You know other people who are
Close friend of the show Jack Baker dreamy creamy summer is
Plant-based
Mochi mochi balls
Non-dairy ice cream
Spectacular you can join in the dreamy creamy summer no matter what your dietary restrictions are
It is for everyone
And that is my bright spot so we can all we can all enjoy the dreamy
Creamy summer
That's a great price
How about you
Inclusive
Danny
You know what I do to chair
With my boundless moving and horrific you bounce all around
So by my chair in the office was finally destroyed to the point where is non stop squeaking and I was sitting on a pig
Halo wrapped in a blank
This is a bad movie
So I bought a new chair and it's
Gamer chair
Booyah one of those multiple reasons
There's like five hundred bucks up because it was too flashy
Yeah sure
Yeah you're about achromatic by prom guy got a very cheap
Never going back
Never go back there's a little footrest thing come on man you got to go
I may actually one time I did get one second hand
I don't know if I am allowed to say who gave it to me
It was broken
Oh and they said you can have this if you could put it back together
Good luck expensive how did it go
Put it back together
Two pieces in my house for about a year
Then I tossed it out but it was very nice thought
Will this chair I have I noticed that I leave this pretty hard
Strong reinforced on the left a good
Smart so hey Jordan
Today we're going to talk about Friday of last week
That's a April 29th
2020 22
Do you
To all of you there's some things that have happened in Alex's
World's broke
Watch the splc
A Bitcoin donation that's a regular thing
Pretty cool. Just because I feel like
We just said on our episode like
Listen to anybody cared about a b****
Just give $1000000 a true
Million-dollar roof true that is a little bit like that someone cares
Also we had just talked about his money bomb was like um maybe you made a million dollars
Spell paper
Touche I don't know I don't have a whole lot of insight in that that goes beyond two piece
I hate watch
People should check that out it's it's
Beat me to the punch of what my kind of main theory was
Do you like okay if it's something to do with Bitcoin and Alex
Probably Max Keiser involved in his name comes up in the the article
But I do have
This Disaster is episode
We've got something of our own now I think that we should remember that our last episode
Wednesday last week was
The Monday
Of this week that we're listening to hear Friday
Terraria
Totally
Quite different
Maybe the tone of someone who has in the intermediate period of time received a Million Dollar Baby
Got an injection of new life possible maybe we're not all going to die after all turns out
Now weird so weird
So I will get down to business on this before starting let's say hello to New Wok, so first Alex bones is just
Please by Shannon's advances thank you so much you and I hope all is well
Text Jose Monsanto the genetically modified day labor thank you so much
You very much
Porter the dog and human thank you so much and I'll probably walk
This is from Katie I love you thank you so much
A boat full of holes thank you so much
Thank you very much and finally this is from Andrew and Abby
Very generous with the word limit on this
My sister has become a fully-fledged
Listener makes you practice law with all the charm of Mark Bankston the ferocity of Bill Ogden the rigor of Dan Friesen the weight of Jordan
Holmes had the wisdom of our Lady Selene Patron cat of policy walks
Thank you so much you are about
I'm a policy wonk
Play sweet sweet
You know the trick is
Is very well written
Fluid
It wasn't a trap
We're going to start off here on this Friday show I am Alex
Zuzu
Revitalize a little bit much like somebody who has
Didn't the desert
I got a Bitcoin
Immanuel Kant
Imprison Humanity
Chicken tender control and power the future
Humanity
Destiny
Real monsters like Bill Gates
Call Schwab in Rock Obama in there
Controller
Succeed
Enslaving
Magnificent species
I just read you a few headlines here
We are on the precipice of a global food prices Goya Foods CEO warranty
They can't even get beer
So this was an article about a Fox News Fox Business interview that be Gloria Foods
CEO Bob unani
I did where he discussed the likelihood of a cup
Food crisis
I was just decided to make up the part about how we can't find
I don't know
In reality to US Foods dry commodity Trend report from April 29th 2022
Dry edible beans are doing fine
Do planting progress is slightly behind which is quote
Normal given cool and wet weather conditions
From the beginning report
From the daily Bean there's a reality which is a very likely going to be a food crisis
He's going to be coming and a pack
A lot of the world and it's like we should take very seriously and we can to help offset
There's also a comical fake version of this that Alex has reported based on his imagination
Which is only interested in as a vehicle to scare his listeners
But that's what happens when you start with music like yeah he's coming
I'm just so mad I'm just so mad to go from our last episode 2
Duel of the Fates in
Our planet
Imagine my world planet
You wear all day
Yeah the last episode was we're all dead already goodbye I'm going to be gone in a week
Do get $1000000 and then we're on a magical planet
Globalist
If you ever needed more evidence
When he's talking about these
Success or failure of the globalist plant
A hundred percent
So we also have a new villain in the mix
He's been talked about that Yuval Noah Harari fell of the historian the futuristic
Popular Wicked World economic
Forum Circle sure why not that's one person that Alex has been taken
He's really mad at me
Guru
We must depopulate the Earth
We need less Shoals
The Christian
One more we want last what
A satanic
Oh man
That's so sweet so satanic
I just got his name is sadhguru but
He's not actually a joke
Guru
Woodside
If you might describe him as a guru in some settings
But I don't
Think that the world economic Forum has gurus in the way that Alex is describing
Do you mean
In the wave at
The Reagan's had an astrologist they don't have gurus
Not like whole lot whole Yogi
Yogi
India economic Summit in 2019 sadhguru did a four-minute interview which was
Future needed to involve a restructuring of things like how we produce food and how we dress ourselves
Agriculture and textiles are two major sources
The pollution and waste
In the world
He also touched on how it was wrong the world has turned things like water and air into Commodities instead of
Remember the central things that make life
Yeah that's a weird thing for him
In the interview he says that the Earth is not imperil
It will be just
That's fine
If we don't make some changes human life on Earth could get
Really cruel
They could get quite Coronavirus
Clearview says that people viewing his panel
Preciate it is Frank Frank
Do it's that Guru zygote that's my trouble
All the religious groups are against me because I talked about population
They want more soil
I want Less on the plan
Sure sure
In context it's pretty obvious what he means but it sounds
Just close enough to him saying that he wants to kill everyone over there against
Just run with that address
You want to go viral in the right-wing media just go through old world economic Forum videos and see if you can find
Somebody saying something that sounds kind of messed up
Eclipse it sound as bad as possible
I posted with the salacious headline folks like Alex will just
They can't resist that face
It'll just be
All over the place within a week
The problem is
They're always choosing people with good faith arguments in order to tear them down like I feel like I have been working
My entire career to make the right wing pull out s*** that I say and then use it
Developed by me and they never do
They never do
That's been most of your role on the show is like trying to bait
I have not gone viral one time for being at the Satanist devil that I am
Well you just got to give it to the world economic forum
I don't think it's Lucas The Improv anymore probably not this clip is going to be important later
It's not that important
This is some of the news
Is there articles everyday about me so many hundreds of them I can't even
Proximal
Every single one of them
I am telling people that there's a plan to kill the public
In response to a story
And I can't find
Subway
Is he saying that his problem is
We're saying that it
It's fake and that he is in fact
Saying that people should be violet
No
No. He's saying that he's not saying people should be fine with that he's not making this up I think it's okay
Okay the whole thing okay yeah but just put a pin in all this for now because this is going to come back in a very serious way later
Alex is mad
But there are articles saying that he's suggesting violence because of this globalist depopulation plant
It's been a long
Time since when
It certainly has certainly
The media is gas-lighting
You know much like that you know they say that this plan that this evil plan doesn't exist
All just an exercise and tried to make it
Friday April 29th worldwide transmission
In defense of human Liberty and hard people future
Our will is strong
Gaslight
World government
Total surveillance
Forced injection
Depopulation plans ministries of Truth
Choose your old
Relationships all mainstream news
Them telling you it's a wonderful
Fantastic idea
Terrible idea
And I say that man must be silenced
All the major newspapers
Let me know they are
None of that's real most of it though is too vague to be you even worth paying
The point about the globalist wanting dictatorship
That's something that's a little bit easier to identify
It's more concrete than any of the other stuff like it's
Talking points
Identifiable globulus want dictatorships and that's why we support Putin in his attempt
What's going on what's an interesting comment about Putin coming up a little bit later
Reports on this whole dictator thing is at the globalist
Newspaper saying the dictatorships are good however
The reality is just that there was a single operating Bloomberg written by a guy who's been a longtime proponent of the idea of Ben Neville
Dictators
In developing
Countries
What's actually happening is a far cry from what Alex
The telling his audience
That's kind of an illustrative
The rest of this is all just right-wing culture War memes that Alex Azar
He's expressing some level of anger that the regular media doesn't agree with him that these things are real
Tiger rest of the show
That he's got in front of him
He wouldn't be able to just
Certify that list of clients
It's
But thankfully
He doesn't try know that's a smart move on his part instead
He just gets
Really angry
Myself
Ron Paul
Fordyce
We're exposing it and you were exposing it
Who You Are
Call Michelle 25
5 years
Even fighting in the trenches forever and only recently got a shot to beat these people
Is it God inspire you to find a truth
I want to tell you from the bottom of my heart
I just got it
Unbreakable
Pray for God.
Pour out his Spirit of strength
Focus and clarity
Honor and creativity and life
God Eternal Father of the universe thank you for the sacrifice of your son
I just got a million-dollar
Edit
Thank you God
Thank you for the Consciousness you given us
Thank you for the wheel
Thank you for everything you've done
Parentheses
I got a belly.
This news is over-the-top
It's over-the-top bad
Giving it up to The Luminaries like Ron Paul
Hangry thank you to God
Thank you you
Thank you
I felt incredibly unsafe
When
This show is probably has no guardrails to this
We're in the beginning of the show
Write Alex's furiously thanking God
I mean SS somebody with plenty of experience in in in mood swings
This is too quick
Of a mood swing for for him to have
That's just not possible
You know and it takes
Years of practice
And medication
And also you
Ever
Well
Etherized
And just leads to like a real
Real protracted bit of Rage
Pedophilia is good they say
World governments good destroying everyone's good
Depopulating is good all simers is good cell phone radiation is good GMOs good
We deserve what we get but
On the record
You are not Superior to me
It was first Bloom of God
Oh my God he said it on the record
Furious
If I been unofficial up till this point
Go on the record
With that
Trying to get the sense that their plans can be foiled
Not at this point it's very much
Like free Monday
Mentality
Just not fair you should have to least change your sources
If we're all going to die verses
We got a shot to death
Your sources are something as nebulous and pointless as your own
Thoughts and visions
And who cares if he's willing to accept
My Visions as a source ever
You don't need to do anything
It's a particular theme show like hey this is my world going to die I'm taken by show
To use World economic Forum people and then you're like we can stop the global it would be nice if there was a
Revelation of something new that changes the information
Astro
This is all nonsense
And it's really a platform for Alex to
Make his audience feel things so he doesn't have to I think
On the record and Shane class Bob and Bill Gates New World Order
You are not Superior to me
Are superior to you
Superior
We are not going to let you do the same thing. She is that
Understood
Little man
Hard hair on your filthy murderous heads
Odd
Okay alright alright come on now
Come on now
Texas
A little dumb this is like the ultimate
Expression
Of somebody when
Like
If you are a front runner or you you've got the goods you know like
When Alex
This is at his lowest I quit I'm gone I'm done we're all going to die everybody's dead f*** all of you a little bit
More momentum as I guess what and you're like dude you're a f****** week
Coward
The other thing is just brings to mind for me is I was in an acting class when I was in like junior high or something like that
Couple other people project
And I thought it went pretty well we got some good laughs
We're getting notes
It's from the teacher
She had to explain to me the difference between acting and overact
Alex that note
Because overactive appreciate my acting teacher be like we got a nip this in the butt
At your turnover enemy call Matt down
Yeah Jim Carrey would tell Alex to tone it down a notch a little realer
Wolf
Hellboy the beginning of that show comes into play again
Everyone lying about his violence and all that
Confused about how people can possibly think he was trying to stoke his audience towards violence
About love
He's even saying the people shouldn't harm a hair on his enemy's head absolutely not it's just that God should send an angel
Crush Alex's enemies
What the problem is that Alex has on way more than one occasion explained that the way God works
Is that he'll send people to do his bidding
Which includes enacting vengeance
He's been super clear about
It's like this time
Is Khat
How does God deliver
What God delivers engines thrust
Forever this time
Vengeance is
Dodge
God has answered
Avengeance
That's always the twist to the riddle
Terrorize Josh
Monopoly Sports
Can't you got strung up while your dungeon
We're going to terrorize you
Orlando Zoo
Good bookshelves with vengeance is mine saith the Lord
Many
A man and woman in history has been used at the implement
The engine
For the
Device
There's a very established talking point on Alex's show at
Winky's doing
It's really really really transparent
He knows what
He's doing this is this is garbage
Yeah I think it's it's maybe a bit of a weak spot in our ability to understand things
Where is
If somebody calls for violence
On one day you're like
We got you you call for violence but
Space split
Concepts up over two days you like
Will never catch
This guy he's too smart for us
Sprite or is someone explains a metaphor very frequently and then uses the metaphor
There's no way to connect these two thoughts right right
Smart for us it's really dangerous kind of
Way to behave in. He should be
Really ashamed
Pretending to be confused by people critique why would they keep going
You will be visited
By the spirit of God
Which one
You will be
You okay buddy
You are not the angel of death
Angel of death with Wrath
He doesn't sound like a good dude
EverStart Plus
Now that I've said that to Satan and his minions
Let us move
Terminators
I know no no no
No
No no no no no
Absolutely
I'm very close to using now that I said that Satan and his minions let's go to the news as a
Out of context dropped surprise
That's got to be what it is
Yeah I feel like you sounded a lot
W like a demon
Can you tell me why you think that you're just in love and God's as like that
Iowa
Get the angel of death doesn't mean it's not bird
Bad
It's not really a bad mood for him but it's
It's f***** up
Open smood but because
He was so recently f***** up in the triumphant f***** up
Yeah maybe I don't know if I find it I tried it more and more difficult to try and parse his mood
3:00 there's real-world stuff going on
It's kind of difficult
The Parson
Complete f****** weirdo on his show
I don't know I may for the next
Short stretch of time just
Abdicate responsibility to explain what he's doing cuz
It don't make sense
You could not
Come to someone more equipped to tell you how he's feeling
And I have no f****** clue what do you want to do
So
Yeah it complains about Noah Harari the futurist he's pretty mad about
Probably there's a clip of him I don't really know what
2 offensive about
Alex's
Keegan insight
Here's a clip
Yesterday
Announcing that they need world government to carry out World tyranny
Dial
Governments around the world sign onto tree
At the UN Ron their medical response to
Celtics
That continues on with the weapon talk about sick
Talk about twisted
Curious and his latest disgusting declaration
It was a huge disappointment
To see the lack of Global Leadership
And the lack of global cooperation over the last two years
And the beginning it was like watching the disaster in slow motion
Around the world
Decisive action could have stopped it
And that was like. No adults in the room
Okay let's have an international front
Help the country's most teen eat
Express
And before we have this problem
Global Leadership
Larry strain
Far be it from us
To really criticize somebody talkin over
Sure
I Do's I do think that if you were just doing
Possibly racist defensive voices
I would consider that a worthwhile contribution to our show
Like it that's all Alex's
You probably just got up he literally can't play this clip
Like this clip
Is counter to his narrative
He's saying that the guy who is evil who is
Orchestrating this whole thing the UN who is created the vaccine that's not a vaccine was created this
Whole f****** pandemic all of this out of
Out of himself right
And this guy part of it
And this guy saying
Here's the problem our reaction was
No one knew what the f*** was going on
It is
The difficult thing
And I think
That Alex makes weird noises to help
Distract people
That's true and then I think this is really simple for him to get around and that is him saying like Alex Wood
Say that
Yeah Harari is saying this
But that's just because they want to do something even more Draconian next
Right I mean if you are there simple pass around that but the service
What you're saying makes a lot of sense it would be
It would be just swell in a rational world it would be
But that is not where we are baby
I like to imagine a class bike
Like imagine if you taught a class that was in every respect
I completely normal class and everyone gave you answers that were reasonable and understandable and you just kept being like
Next question sorry we are in
Bonkers world
Nothing makes sense
You're the teacher now
I got a lot of feelings by climate change
You're somebody who's
Zurn
Did you know
That we just need to put more CO2 out
Did you know the best answer
Through to the other side
All right carbon dioxide in the atmosphere previously
Oxygen
Sahara expanding because of lower carbon dioxide last million years
Reams the desert
How is this racist
Amazing
I propose
We do it very quick
Simple
Sure okay let's put Alex
Into a room
And boost the CO2 up by several plants in their problem
In order to absorb it up by several magnitudes and see how he does
Sure
There is a kernel of Truth to what he saying that is that higher CO2 levels are a factor
In the Sahara Greening
That is a good understand
Isn't like
Hey
Deserts are bad
More plants are good
So therefore we need to put CO2 everywhere
Will fix everything to be like he has a very single variable thinking here and it's
Just
Really dumb it is a bit on those lines of like well plants were bigger in the
The Cretaceous. Because there was a larger amount of CO2 in the air so obviously
To do is recreate those exact same circumstances
Don't you want really big broccoli
I Blew Up the Kid that was great
Yeah I thought that maybe that would be something that would make you angrier but I guess you've lost her will to fight lost
Got it anymore
Still got anymore
Well good we're all dead
Who invented
Fuel
Old is peseta plant
LaunchPad
Because their transmission their job from this
I will give you power
Is that
Okay
The more I listen to this show in the current day like
The more I think I start to just
Think okay so the plot is basically that like
There's a battle to get off of her
Basically the entire storyline about humans want to get off of
Presumably Maybe
He doesn't say this all the time but maybe because there's a war going on in heaven where we're needed
Saving by way of the globalist or his minions to metal around and keep us for
I'm leaving Earth
All Humanity has the instincts
To escape from Earth
And get to the habit
I guess right
But the globalists are trying to
To take it just for themselves
No
Well maybe but I like they're involved in the war in heaven
I mean I don't know
Christmas is that the idea
That's what I keep coming back to
The way that this makes sense to me
Pologize Advanced Alex efficient what he saying
Sometime
It feels like
God needs backup
That's why he created man on Earth does he has to see if we're good enough to be the backup and so
Do we have to get off
Planet go up to heaven
It helped out it that wore that fighting with the Devil
Who also works for
And the most important
Is that so far only one man has proved himself worthy to be God's backup
Well I say we put them on a rock
Everybody
Alien Alex's whatever he is sediments together
It's very confusing but I do
The show maybe had lost
Applaud
It's days of being about like
Fractional Reserve banking right okay so if I recall correctly we need
To eliminate
Foreign aid is a huge issue need to go back to the gold standard
Wait
Satan wants to keep us on the planet
Alright
Okay anyway Alex a little bit more
Anti-Cosmo smart-mouth
Guru
It shows also really violet
So you got this smart-mouth Guru
Walking around pedone's act like he's all high-and-mighty
Up there laughing about populator symptom really get on it for him
Let's hear from this piece of garbage
Sew-in.
You brought us some issues
I want Less on the planet
Blow your head off then
A shotgun in your mouth and blow your brains out buddy
Pour gasoline on yourself
Story building
Out of my way
You want to kill people
Running your freaking mouth talking about it
What
Turn the lights on
You want death brother
Besides
It's just like it was trying to do a Macho Man Randy Savage promo
You know
Just goes to show that this
This is a man
Cool of
Free speech
Who wants
A diverse array of opinions in his life also quite tolerant
Absolutely
Pickle liberal dance
Free Speech I'm really concerned that you're missing the most
Important part of shoot-first-ask-questions-later
Well I got to say
Alex
Is it
Real violin
El gross
God
God is going to stomp you into the ground
There's bleep there
Yeah what did he say
You song
You little slime bag I know you are
Not us we're peaceful
You love everybody
I just sit back and let Daddy take care of
Nothing says I love you more
It won't be us to go to the furnace it'll be you
You asked for it
You are Conjuring us
You are rising
Resistance with we are
We will not be stopped
You
You will die
What
Not us
You fraud
Yeah you got them there
You liar
Luciferian
Belt run out of steam
That's probably the trouble with his failing cardio
If you want to keep insulting people like that
I also think that if you really listen to what he's a few things
My followers are going to kill you and it's your fault
Riverview
You're going to die
And God has chosen you for
Murder you
How dare you say whatever it was like maybe let's not murder everybody now you're going to die
Hi buddy
It's outrageous
Wild
Anyway this dude
Asking
Bring
You asked for it
Godzilla
That indoor slide
And get everything you ask
Everything you wanted to happen to us
Happened to you
In all your rituals you can do
Karmic energy
Will not be
Thousand
Times stronger and will incinerate you
Because I am rubber
Because you are glue
You have announced you want to kill everybody
Because deep down you know it's you
Todai
You want us to die
I got a better idea
Pray
Dreamy creamy summer
For justice
He asked God
Punished
If we get hurt
That's just collateral damage in it
This is incredibly f***** up
No he was going to die everybody's going to die and it was because he was sad and now everybody's going to die cuz he
He's wealthy enough to afford it maybe his enemies are going to die
Insane
This is this is a level of like
Being fairly overt about like
Basically poking the audience be like
Hey
Someone should kill somebody this is unacceptable like
It's if we're at the intervention levels normal that's for sure
Exit not good no I was pretty shocked
I will say that
If you understand the code that he's using essentially
And it's not very difficult you don't need
Some kind of a codebreaker to
We're not windtalkers why don't we pray
Right
Why don't we pray for God to punish these people that you and me pray together
So we're going to be praying
For God to do this but we know that God operates
Through
Alex is audience
Maybe men and women who want to
Do a little thing for God do God a favor maybe you feel like with the prayer was about
You I'm not saying it is I'm not saying it's not spraying for one of his
Audience members
Tequila sadguru
Pretty f*****-up
Yeah
Especially for somebody that he literally did not really care about up until like 20 seconds
Can't say that I remember him here hearing him talk about it when he went from zero to murder victim
Very quickly
Comment that Alex's
Triggered by and going off on this rant about 3 years
So that's cool
Anyway Alex also doesn't like how we drive
That's what it is
Buggy
Creeping around actonel
Guarantee you
You put him on the rack
What
He'll Peckerwood moment
5 Seconds
Why are you fighting
God
Is the Brainerd
Lucifer
You little twit
Cool
John Lennon outfit
Depopulation
Songs about it
But he lives on
You're not garbage
Yeah it's a Bradley Joe Biden's murder was a globalist
Who's my it was on me for assuming that it couldn't couldn't
I wonder if you think
Paul was
Replaced
That theory
That's not criticizing Indian man
Inspired by
Another Indian guy
Yeah yeah yeah it's more like John Lennon was misappropriated
And then he's but he's not calling that style of where a John Lennon outfit is kind of telling on yourself in terms of
It's a little bit like
Wearing a dashiki now being like seeing it's like what Nancy Pelosi War you're just stealing Nancy Pelosi s*** yeah
So Alex is really mad and he's he's getting into this this weird head space
He also has time for a couple headlines here and there
Where's one of them
Challenger coming in and dumping
Thousands in
Thousands of tractors and trucks for dumping thousand thousand
No one is buying that macron one by
15 points or whatever
Santa Claus
Rap God
Are saying you clean it up.
You go ahead and
Just enjoy yourself
We're done
Sitting through that two tons of manure were dropped outside of a building that houses the office of a politician from macrons political party
And it was done
In an act of protest
However Alex is failing to mention that this happened in August 29th
There is a recent story although it's kind of hard to find good sourcing on it about Farmers dropping manure in front of supermarkets in the
City of Powell as a protest
How about Rising price
Right they were like we are farmers
We're done
There's a town about 75,000 people or to compared to u.s. City it's the size of Evans
I'm not sure if this is as big of a deal is Alex's making it out today quite frankly
Also I want to point this out
French Farmers protest by dropping manure all the time all the time
Just Google it
What is while it happens a lot
Can do it man
Yeah kind of farmers protest
Choice is clearly
Putting manure where people don't want it to be
It just seems too obvious but we don't do it
I'm not too I'm not encouraging I don't want I don't want to mess around there
I rather not be right there
It's not right there
So Alex gets off the news cuz
There's more second to talk about and what have you
I love you
Finished
About to do
Momentarily. Apparently back to Satan
Alex has made this comparison a bunch of
The past that like if there was just
The corrupt government
I wouldn't be like that
We'd love Jessica Rabbit
Bounds on this a little bit and he said some things that are accidentally like really reveal a share
Again
Boss Hog
Hey we should not Boss Hog
Can I do things in the round
That's My Life by Boss Hogg
Boss Hog over here is the old-fashioned thing
King George the third with Boss Hogg not that bad
What
But
Not going to go 100% crazy eyes
Into a fight against Boss Hogs cuz I'm a little bit of y'all are
Alex was a loyalist
Alex would not have fought the Revolutionary War
Because Alex is a coward who loves
To kowtow in black boots Revolution
F*** you Thomas Jefferson your s*** was b******* why'd you put it on the line for a Boss Hogg it's just a Boss Hog
Adjustable dog this reveals about Alex 02 and really care about corruption
One of his long-running bumpers are we coming back from commercials with is how he's all about fighting corruption but
Club true at all
Totally fine with corrupt even the large-scale like organized corruption
Apparently
If the corruption is focused in the right direction and it doesn't involve
Any of the elements of his personal
Identity being threatened
Cuz that's really apparently what he cares about
To the kind of make him sound like a super sensitive baby
And maybe less
Appealing as a
Guy who goes
Growl radio obsessed
Monster is less
Interesting then with an ink
Credibly bruised insensitive identity
All the time
Play non-stop Whiting
Stop projecting you ever it's like a dog that's left alone that's left home alone all day
Hey you know and zip the dogs owners
They're at work they don't know how much
The dog whines all day everyday but you walked by there and you know
Alldayeveryday non-stop wine
That Alex
He's a whining dog just imagine if that dog didn't have a radio show
So Alex I don't know how else to explain this it seems to be him
Describing an argument that he had with God within his own head sure
This is on the radio
This is the news on the radio
Every damn body
Killer Species
Shelves
Punch me in the face going Jones you get your ass
And whatever you need you're going to get it
But you gotta man up
Voice of the Holy Spirit and discernment
Conscience
Connecting with that
Program
He is demanding
Enough
You are a coward you are weak telling you
And if you don't give me a hundred percent I'm going to dump you in with these people
I'm just like
You're going to do this you signed on for this and you're going to execute this car I'm going
How much
And I don't know if you know this person
But just like ballpark in Europe
How much
Math could you buy with a million in Bitcoin
Look I don't know what's going rate is
I never what I never did know what they're doing right was so
Be tough for me to Ballpark
Yeah I mean look
There's there's some problems with
The mental state
He's presenting
Like there's delusion
Underneath a lot of
A lot of it is before
It's a lot of it is just like
He's a himself up at shadow
Incredibly over-the-top and like I said overactive
And a lot of places
But some of these ideas that he's expressing also seem to be somewhat in line with things you said of the path
Idea of like I'm really feeling conflicted within his head of
Voices yelling at him to do things out early
Kind of checks out
Yeah
I do I do like you about that I do like him being like
Amman
You gotta man up and it's like man what's that million Runs Out you are suddenly going to find you're not a man are you
I learned that the global plan is so important
I quit all the time
Quitter
Anyting
Please.
The New World Order you think I fear the mainstream media
Deliberate
Focused babe
Whatever you say
God says
You want for lunch if you wanted this
It's so beautiful and so great
Sao Paulo
Everything seems really for
Gravely the lamps with always right there
What are we doing here
This feels voyeuristic yeah I was really gross
Presence
I'm ashamed
Call Todd
And so I'm going to hate you
And I'm going to try to be you
At the same time
Because I don't like the way you make me feel
I don't like
You're so good
Yes
That's what goes on and saying bring
Satan has a brain
Sure
You know what eats
Yeah man I will boy
Hey I'm worried what are we doing
I don't know what is happening why are we Whispering about
What did Jesus man what are you wearing
Also
I'm not going to throw this out here
I'm going to tell you this right now
You
Are required
To refuse an unlawful order even if it's from God
Is that right it does not protect you legally it does not protect you legally like
Look if God shows up and he's like hey Jordan
You better go genocide those Canaanites
No God
I refuse
I think that's
Brave of you I think I also like
I keep running into this
I don't know how to put
This exactly
I think Alex is a terrible spokesman for God
He's really better on the fence about God and I was like this is this is what it looks like
Not what this thumbs down
Yep sounds
Conflicted even about like
Elementary things about reality utterly insane
Totally
Batman and his
His
Barely in control of his own
It's simple emotional state
Like simple stuff
Like let's just pick it back up
Thousand feet to the
Bird's eye view
If your impression
God is
I want you to
The kill my enemies right
That's bad God of God is you agreed to do this thing for me this
Side mission that you're going on and a hundred percent
Burn you pay weekly to Hell a little weakling how do you feel now you're so weak
That's not no bad guy
Impression of God I don't think all of his gods
Spar
Pretty much s***
They remind me a lot of him ask
Discernment
Does not care for
We have something new to bring to the audience
Attention
From the person who brought you
Stachys
And the person who brought you breaking news
I know but you
Ague
Brianna k
Marvel level
Watch what I'll do to your eggs
Bugatti
God says
What
Why
Why did God do this because God
Did
What was right
Why shouldn't God create
What
Why should God create new entities that have free will
Oh cuz that was selfish of me.
To do that
God is the ultimate fate
Your God is the ultimate
God
Created
Freewell
God
Works for God
Oh my God
God doesn't do what Satan does
Know what God did order Satan to do this
Yes I forgot because I'm free
See if that was something that I was wondering about myself because
If you work for somebody and you can't be fired then you don't work for them
Yeah
Look
As I was getting this episode ready I cut some of these clips in
I have nothing
I legitimately
Uberti
From whatever you get out of that and probably write most of what I took from that is
He's on one and we now have Aggie's
It's just like
Try and make sense
Of what you're saying about your own beliefs
Look none of them were great but at least most of them
Try to make sense
Yeah you're out there like 8 listen
The ultimate Evil and he's trying
And kill you God's ultimate good and you created free will
Satan works for God but God doesn't do with Satan doesn't God
Tell take me to do that stuff Satan works for God
God didn't tell him to do that and that beat
Val
Clothes swap
I think he does make some sense I think you'll agree
Somebody
I don't know his read some
Fantasy novels
I think you might learn some
Put some of this
We're going to go break
You go to the next level agency lemonade you're going to realize
But there is a lot more going on
So complex is so fantastic
It's so real I can't even interpret
It's nothing in literature in art
Culture
Totally all of it's just completely
Go to Hollywood right now
The delicious new
Because
The average person
No access to it
And
So much of what you see
That's what it is
Puppies
The whole nine yards
What
Portal
Sauron
LaSalle
I mean
Infowars.com tomorrow's news today weather
No,
Cuz I got one speaks mad about that from like a nerdy perspective but honestly what I'm really mad about
Is it somebody needs to put this person into therapy immediately
He's not going to cut it any number of things
Specialist
Why does he have lawyers
He's a busy street surrounded with doctors at all times just like product trying to figure out
What it is that makes him this way
Like
I don't understand
Dab like me
ICS
The depths of the metaphysical World beyond Godzilla
It's just like Sarah.
Clothes wearing in the movie It
I could
Go to Hollywood and be number one
Because what I've seen is like nothing anyone else have seen there before
Here's my example
Something that someone else has seen and done better made a bunch of times
I run into Ziggy's talking about like how this is beyond anyone's imagination of science-fiction and like
Version of reality is just old science-fiction
It's all there I don't think is very robust
I mean the Sci-Fi well I'm in the special effects on his imagination stop somewhere around Logan
Run
I think we're good
So that was be messed up first hour of the show
That was that was
Yep boy
Could you skip that one
No
It was intense
Yep
Hernandez
And a lot of these interview is Alex kind of trying to apologize because like
Back when she worked at Infowars you like to go out your woman
But you can't go out to
The protests are too dangerous for a woman
I meant ukulele and I do want to work for the Blazing.
I should have
Stuck with you but I'm too much of a
Kimberly chauvinist
Workout negative
I don't believe in the potential of women because of it
You could have done had
Child
Yeah
She's in the second hour and I don't care it's not very interesting
But
Gaston comes into the third hour
Big f****** news
But
We are now joined
Tower
By the mighty
Rodger Stone
Rodger on talk about Elon Musk going about Russia
Wow
I didn't call you want to bug you
It was banned
Add
The New York Times Washington Post got a rubbing a poster all right here
And then you text me you go
Yeah Manhattan
So if it was a fake account that tried to rejoin Twitter is Rodger Stone USA it was someone with a remarkable level of
Connection to Rodger
Possibly access to some of his passwords I know who is the rap
Posted on his telegram account well b****** hunt back on Twitter
I'm anxious to see how strong Elon Musk commitment to freeze peaches
So this is just sort of a fake
Twitter they must have access to Rogers telegram account to
Back when
Credit
The Daily Beast reached out to Rodger for comment and he said quote I posted a new account to prove a point I look forward to whoever May
Made the decision to suspend getting fired
Attention Elon Musk
So
It have to be like a fake account that has his telegram password and is able to critically
Critically impersonate him to eternal atake
This seems like to be a large-scale
Security problem on Rogers end of things
Obviously what happened to that Rodger created a Twitter account to find a way to save face
No at all what the the details are
Just trying to like
Like I have fake news of the media unfortunately isn't going to play along with Alex
Because Rodger did make that account okay
Unfortunately Alex lifeson talking and Rodger deflates the hoe
Moving on from that Rodger still dumped from Twitter
Almost
More
Latest pieces of disinformation
So what I did Alex to
My point was
Instead of trying to get my
Currently suspended Twitter page
Reinstated where I had
Just short of a million followers
Purposely posted a new Pro
Profile
Confident
Current walk Staffing Twitter with band me immediately
And it only took six hours early talk to you
What's an official counter
Also I had my information wrong and then I accused the media of passing off fake story they can't possibly
Well I had it wrong it's not worried about it
Now it's kind of funny though Rogers explanation for why
He did this
And it's pretty clear based on his own words and this
Makes me
Very sad
But then I begin to see
Lists of those who have
Unjustly bin
Deplatform including
President Donald Trump
You of course Alex Jones
When
The others
Noticed
Missing from all those lists in all honesty
Should speakers
Play back in 2017
Pioneer
And as you pointed out to me at the time
Platform
No conservatives Rose to my defense
No other conservatives were outraged
Yeah I know to talkin about him I want to I want to reduce my conservative buddies now
Now that they're willing to come out publicly and drive
Is everybody's a giant piece of s***
Hey this person needs to get back on Twitter and they forgot about me I need to put myself back in therapy
The original hipster band guy just basically doing a publicity stunt
By giving himself rehband
Computer so people remember that he's not
San Jose
Sad very sad so sad
Hello
Vasquez a truth-teller
Did Rodger measure or sense
Sore
What do words mean
No but Rodger is an interesting interpretation
Twitter accepting
Mosques offer
You're right I just think he's a truth-teller
Asian entrepreneur
And most importantly he understood
It came to a tender offer
Or Twitter
Money talks and
Blocks
At the end of the day
If they put aside their ideas
Russian free speech by people like Alex Jones
And Rodger Stone
Laura Loomer and others
And they talk
The money think it takes for him to get full control like at what point do we get mad
They hasn't platforms
Alex can't wait to get mad about not being
I know he wants his turn
The whole thing redo all over again
Fake news
Rogers describing like literally shouldn't be possible
In the world that Alex
Does created
Like
The globalist
I have
These are Jen does and what have you no amount of money
Should be possible to buy Twitter
Because
They have their ideological agenda Twitter is
Apparently essential for
So it just
This is nonsense
Are contradicting your own
Premise your entire the rules of the universe Ilan has to be a globalist or
None of it makes
Well he will be
If
You know he ends up buying Twitter and then Alex and get back
Preemptively
When can I make that my narrative
Yeah
And he's either to use itching for it
Rodger Stone buenaveza
You know this
He loves
Adidas
And it's affected
Political position
Libertarian conservative
Pro-abortion
In Jesus Christ
Radically I'm now
Berry pro-life
You're definitely not faking
Yeah oh yeah
I have noticed a thing and I wish that I had
Little isolated these
Please make a Supercut but pretty much every time Rodger Stone and religion come up
Alex is like you're not pregnant
Kind of
Suspicious
So what are the things that I've noticed that Rodger has been saying a lot when he comes on the show is basically
How can I
Grab Victory from the jaws of defeat
That's why they're in such a hurry Alex is our friend Tucker
They don't act like people
Who have the luxury of time
They know that every single day
Are there more and more Americans are waking up to what's going on
All a very regularly he cites Tucker Carlson is saying that the enemies of the Patriots
They don't act like people who have a lot of time
All right in a couple minutes later Rodger says this
America will be won or lost between now and this November
We do not have the luxury of time folks
This is it
This is the struggle for freedom
What you're acting like you don't have the luxury of that I'm starting to think
That maybe
Now and throw this out there
Maybe this is a lot of
Projection
In order to obtain the results
As though the instigator was the enemy as opposed to you
You're with your best friend
Himself Alex Jones
You might you might be onto something a little bit I guess I just think it's really funny when you use the exact same expression
About your enemies and then yourself
I mean are you sad about man
Who
You know I just
I'm just
Grateful in these trying times that Rodger can rely on
The Lord's Supper
Well
The Lord so far
If Rodger does a dude he's supposed to
Obviously
Rodger is on thin ice with God
Bi-Rite
Probation at least
I would keep her on a short leash
Nothing but verify
Where's your God dealing with
Option hours
It's not going to
I can take his word for it I feel like you're full of s*** man ever heard of you
I've been burned by Nixon Associates before
Your man is Rogers interviews a lot of like
Very repetitive
Booth with few exceptions
But
I think
Definitely tell a changing of tone
I'm kind of interested to see what
Ynobe
Beginning of this week
How Alex will be behaving because
News
About this million dollars a bit going to believe he broke on was that Friday I believe
Forgotten this million-dollar spaghetti then but I'm not entirely sure if I come out
I don't know if it come out
While he's doing the show
I know that the news came out on Friday
And that they said he closed the account like two days before they
So yeah so he's got a million dollars hanging out
Burning a hole in his paw
Pocket right now
Much like
God's judgement
Burning a hole in
Yeah I'm interested to see cuz I think that's going to be a much more
Telling episode
One side
Just bring it up at all
Some kind of really unhinged
Beer what and we'll see we'll see we'll be back on Wednesday to check in on that but tell them Jordan
We website we do it's not right.
We are
Go to back but until then I'm Neo ugly OMG VX Clark
Please
Have yourself
Audrey mccreamy song
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work