Damn important
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
We are Damned
My bright spot my dear boy is second chances
Sorry I wasn't I wasn't expecting the Foghorn Leghorn
Play a famous Barber
Spot is
Second Chances
So a while back excited about the release of Hyrule Warriors
Calamity
Dynasty Warriors Style game with a Legend of Zelda characters I'm notoriously big fan
Hyrule Warriors
Original
And I was
Wrongly disappointed by age of Calamity that was when it was released
And I put it down cuz I like
God isn't
Scratching the itch I wanted to scratch
And I gave it some thought and excited as I thought it was
To play a little bit of
Abso
My bright spot is vetted
Fair amount of fun gameplay in there that I did not give a fair Shake
I'm going to get out of the mine
Gottman
I like this
I like this bright spot weird trading off
Similar bright spots here for me it's not Second Chances
For me it's my 45th
Where is 6th Street
You know I vote we have talked about the Games Done Quick
Taking the pass yes I well there was a recent one done by the
Organisers of Games Done Quick but it was all women
Call frame Fatale I think or whatever it is
Who's in
Credibly inclusa
Like
Super is great
It's fantastic
Somebody was playing Final Fantasy Tactics
Text my friend
And I had to
Get back up
Yeah because this is my 47 or 48 play through I'm on 50 or 60 playthroughs completed
This is one of the greatest games and here's what's going to happen whenever you bring up a
Game like this it's like when you bring up the wires right right right buddy who knows it's like everybody in the internet is going to go
Oh man Final Fantasy Tactics
Great and then somebody's going to go like I've never played it
And everybody's going to pile on my
See you in a week
Exactly
Skewer references throw knife
For me I think might be
I don't know trying to think of like what if I played
Excessive amount of time
And I think it's got to be like one of the Pikmin games
You think so I played those
A lot of beating them and played them through too I don't know why that came is very Charming
Sing for me
Then maybe a turtle turkey
I have a playdate
Years and years
Definitely Beat It
A lot of
No I mean it's one of those games and nobody went what was it you know you played
Uplay
Games before you know like maybe
Better
I mean it's like a aboard
Structure you know like a combat situation of realization
A little bit like that but not
Hexagonal
Regular it's Square
Rectangular
Is it does it play out like a RPG like a standard RPG
Luke turns it plays out more like a chess game
You know you have these characters who can move in certain ways and do certain
Same order
Different and then you figure out a way to get to QuikTrip
It's a little bit like that I mean it's hard
Explain button
I've talked to people who have never played another game it's similar to this at all
It's the only type that doesn't sound wildly familiar to
Absorbed into your nonsense world
Alright
Well
Absorb me from this nonsense World hey how you doing
Tune of doing a Wednesday episode
Raring to go give him the last couple modern-day episodes
There was something worth it
We're all going to die goodbye my dear friend
Smash cut to
It was a
Troubling
Little chef
Yeah. Who dies in The Apocalypse is very depending on who has a million or not
$1000000 that it wasn't really
Anything interesting it was kind of
Snooze
Answer for Wednesday
The 2003 episode
And then of course
6 weeks and I want to sit down
Overturning Roe v Wade
Some b*******
Listen its 2022 and I want
My legal opinions to ref
Prince people who burned witches
That's what I want I want to make sure that we keep
A continuity between the past and the present
U.s. verse
Goody Proctor
Goody Proctor was somebody Berkowitz.
Who's that who am I thinking of
Corey is a guy who got crushed
Ono anytime anyone
To it's bad times and you know
Obviously
I'm curious to see what Alex thinks about that and so Wednesday
What we're going to do for that was because the news broke Monday
Evening sure we were going to cover Tuesdays show
For Wednesday which we would have recorded on Tuesday immediately and it around instantaneously
Real hassle unfortunately Owen Shroyer was in studio
Did I got to say you know watching a little bit of that and see some of the responses
Is on social media and seeing some of the
Your video titles and posting on Infowars I would be lying if I said it didn't
So the trigger some of that stuff from
Alexa in whenever they were laughing and
Fixing the election night laughing at people who were worried about
Being in danger because of Rights being taken
Obviously it wasn't as
Impactful and severe is that shocked that evening prayer image
But they were over shades of it and
I mean it's tough
To exist in the space where you know that
Did somebody just handed down a desk
Shore and assert
Has if they pulled a f******
Gun
But
You know it's not going to happen right away so you don't know who it is and so you don't worry about it and then even on top of that you
You have the indominus
Portent
Of various other Supreme Court decision
That could be eroded very easily
Hands out
It's it's a bummer you think that's putting it lightly and I don't know if I have some of the
Correct words
Necessarily
Describe the role of the response
Bull blood
I don't know Jenna ciders
So Alex got back into Studio
Answer we're going to go over his response here
Some of it but I don't think you'll be able to predict
Yeah I would imagine that is
Is there
He's not really all that focused on Julio
The decision
Romanian right-wing talking point
The most popular thing we're ever going to do but look over here
You know I get I get what you're saying about you don't have to give it up for him and I agree
But it is surprising to me that he didn't
Jump on that totally to yell about that for awhile the same
Anthony of the court and all that nonsense
Oh my God
Factor into heavily but we'll see what does
In a moment but first
Hello doesn't do what
The first Spencer and Chris get on disc
Can you very much
Owen Shroyer broken lawyer thank you so much you are now policy
That's just called A Better Call Saul
BP engine ET sitting in a tree k i s s i n g
I screwed up the rhyme structure
Thank you very much
Next Tampa sounds a lot like
Play started listening while applying to Public Health
Metro Health Department policy wonks thank you so much
You are about to walk
Thank you very much
So we start off here at the beginning of Alex's show and here is what he is got
Going on
The right of a woman to kill her child is abortion
Quiet fart out loud could more people like Gloria Steinem of the Central Intelligence Agency
Abortion I'll do it again
Feel good
H Linda killed her child
This is not a minority of these leftist women this is the majority of them
I've been basically endowed with the satanic spirit
When they boarded her baby because they were lied to that it wasn't human
Instead of having the Holy Spirit softener hard
And repeat
Anymore
They said no
Peter Troost Rahway seitan
Yeah so refreshing to see the prize above a left-right paradigm man
Make sure everybody
Knew that he's
Is above the left-right paradigm
Say that s***
A little weird
There's something kind of simple about Alex's position that I can appreciate on one level
His opposition to reproductive Health Care is so clearly not based in rationality or a political position
Purely a product of religious zealot
There is no responsibility to argue with a position like the one he holds because there's literally nothing you can say that would dissuade him
I'm thinking that you're just Satan trying to seduce him away from Rachel
Business real world people get hurt
They pretend that they're driven by some kind of political beliefs
The game the appearance of respectability and
Make me laugh
Trick people into thinking that there's a point in arguing with them and with Alex
There is no point it's very clear it's just
I have wacky fundamentalist religious ideas about this and I will not be swayed Dan I mean it's
Almost like
And and
I'm going to follow this up and this is going to sound crazy to me
But in 2022 I think there are only bad faith conversations about abortion if they aren't
I'm using it to hurt women or I'm using it because I believe God makes me want to do that
There is no other conversation
Beasley
I don't really believe that this is entirely even honest
Cuz I don't believe Alex's
I don't think it's fully good-faith
But
Clearly an indication of a dead end
And so like you know there's no point
Who cares
I thought it important
Absolutely f*** you or a monster
So Alex discusses his experience with abortion
Listening to the show as much as we have Alex's name for at least 10
Maybe more
So here's what are you going to do this clearly so what he's going to do is he's going to wrestle with his
Current life now and if abortions were illegal whenever he wanted to get
So his life he would never have made it to the position that he's in if
Reproductive Health choices that we're capable
Of the women that he impregnated
Is read over and over again his life would be
Right now
Instead actually conversely what he
He tends to do I've heard this on a number of occasions
Because he was able to access these a reproductive health
Free of being able to romanticize the idea of what if these kids were alive Runaway
Right
He did get the benefit of these policies that he is so again
I think you might have actually argued me all the way to the side of being like if Alex had not been able to get abortion
We wouldn't have had Alex and we would have had another long mile truck
Well I think that
Doesn't justify anything know what that argument about how he got off
The the the abortion wagon let's say
I was touched by the Holy Spirit when I was about
Really I was upset
Said I'm not going to sit there and just show out three hundred bucks every time I get a check
Autonomous stuff
It's works
4 years old
Pointiest
Gross.
My dad's in front of me when I was about
$17 house and I needed money
Do you need do you need 300 bucks again
Let me guess you're killing my grandchildren
They said you need to stop
Real proud of you Dad
Shut that off my mind
What I done was wrong okay this is war
Can we not
Like this is the type of short
Clip that reveals all of the things that they assume are just acceptable like
We don't need to worry about things
Like my dad was like hey I need some money so my dad was going to
Give me money no point in time if you like
Well what if my dad didn't give me
Write what if he didn't have that money to give
And no point is that occurred
No no
Doesn't matter
I also
Just think of this
This belies like a really
Call me it's pretty f*****
The Dynamics
Series describing the heart
Heart just like
Yeah right
Clearly clearly have a lot more feelings about this that have nothing to do with the policy of reproductive Healthcare
That maybe you should unpack
In a therapeutic setting
Instead of drinking them away
Maybe the world would be a better place and you would stop seeing demons everywhere
If you took care of yourself
If you really engage with what
Just said as
I think this true
Man I don't want
Pull that thread there's some dark of course therapist to deal with
Unfortunately probably start talking about it, and we have to cover it
I told him about this if we all wait
I don't know
The Home Shopping Network shirt
So Alex
Clip of Biden but he mentioned where he said killing your baby is
Clip that's a surprise as if it is
Killing your yeah
Why'd you say the quiet part out loud at this is really hurting them bad
What he says
A shelf
Idea that we're going to make a judgment that is going to say that
No one can make the Judgment choose to abort a child
Decision by the Supreme Court I think those way overboard
What a hero
The decision to abort a child
Decisional board is actually murder
A child is the quote
Wow
Here's what's going on is that
Issue that are refers to
Besides a child
The Killing no not misinterpret of this headline and he's over selling it
No it's it's at Biden called a fetus a child
This is how it go
Comes out
The quiet part loud heos
Alex has some shocking news to report
More than 10 states
California New York have laws
To kill babies
Bible healthy children
Abortions
Babies want to kill the old people
Does wide-ranging
What's covered
All of the p
Name those
10 + State yeah
Show me the Bells
Shut the fuk up
I would take
As much
Defense I believe
If someone whose political beliefs I agreed with
Spoke this Loosely features that matter
Theoretically right you never like oh okay
Abortion being legal is an overwhelmingly popular console
I'll tell you that because 6
Thousand states have signed it into a constitutional amendment
You know
Yeah it's it's a it's irresponsible
I'm presenting a fictional world for his audience to be very afraid
Now Alex make some
Some statements about the
The choice
Time to abort
Pregnancy
Nathan woman's own and he has no
What's between a person and God
I was not expecting
Letting God to be evolved
Between
God man
God in humans got in woman
And you know the woman
Wants to go to some
Federal system
Democrats
Your children to make a mask
Play Shots
Brainwash him in the Lacs
But I won't be happier healthy or
Seems to be suggesting that people like have destination
Abortions
Well I mean
It be okay so it'll out of state
In order to get
Married
Judge license
Put in Nevada
You can just
You know it's the same thing
I think that's a little bizarre
Decided by
That's not
If you believe that everything is between a person and God then he shouldn't give a single s*** what laws exist to protect access to
To reproductive care because guess what
It doesn't involve him at all it's between that person and God if you cannot give you free will
Involved
Right Alex believes that we all may be
He deserve to die in
Some kind of an extinction-level event because Society so evil and allows abortion
Just cut up a Zachary pretending to get some kind
Tolerant position
Packy cowardly and dishonest and I don't have time for it
Also that part at the end there should be a decent indication of what's the common where the rhetoric is going
This part about kids being happy and healthy and part of a nuclear family
Metric ring off
Loud alarm Bells
Slappy next goal is obviously going to be rolling by protections for the lgbtq
I knew be pretty naive to imagine that's where things are going to stop
Ultimately people in Alex's philosophical Community don't believe in the Civil Rights Act or the Voting Rights Act to literally
Did this is exactly what's going to happen
Lock
That we took for granted is on the table
In terms of being under threat
Yeah I'm coming
Oh my God who could have
Seen this coming
Yeah I mean it's
It's scary but now I don't
I don't want to I don't want to get
Into a place of
Catastrophizing
But
I think
B o b a
It's smart to not also take
For granted
Things are settled
To say this is the thing though it's like
It's going to get weird fast
And then it's going to get bad
I'm really not much anybody can do to stop it after
Fuels
It feels like it
It may
Yeah
Damn that I don't know
I mean it's just it's just so you know it's almost a f****** Indiana Jones Raiders of the Lost it's it's
Do you know that there's a giant f****** Stone Rollin
You got to run
That's it
Some news
Important
Genuine
MSNBC talkin head labels founding fathers
Racist
Misogynist
Jerk faces
Coming up next
Carlson Romano
Against Roe v Wade has been around
That's great that sucker reminded people of Biden
Past vote
New York Times reminded people of it in 2019 before he was elected but that's what you expect from the evil
Evil liberal mainstream media
If you want the nuanced explanation for this date that Biden comes from a Catholic background and his initial belief was that Rovers way
That decision was
The court going too far
Hey 1982 about 9 years into his time in Congress
Constitutional amendment was proposed to allow states to overturn the ruling
And buy it
Voted for it while it was in
Committee
He said at the time quote I'm probably a victim or a product however you want to phrase it of my background calling it quote
The single most difficult votive cast of the US Senate
Here's the thing though
To the full Senate
And it never came to a formal vote
Itself
The next gear and identical bill was proposed by devoted again
This isn't the gotcha that Alex and Tucker pretending it isn't the hot-and-cold history Biden has with abortion-rights is something
It's been widely discussed in
All sorts of outlets for
Quite a while
The only way this could seem like Tucker making a novel point is if you just have no familiarity with Biden
Accepted the cartoon character
Nvidia is presented him
Adidas
You're telling on yourself when you think that this is shocking
It is it is amazing to me that Tucker
It's like pulling that out like see whenever wherever literally all of us
Yeah that's why we f****** hated that guy in the first
F****** place
That's one of the reasons why there's some
Around him were some some reluctance
Yeah that's why it took a lot of
There's a Spider-Man on the loose
Which one
Miles Morales
That one's it he's great. Peter Porker it's not paid John Mulaney would have been a great spider pig
It's a guy who climbed the tower in San Francisco to protest
Wow, this week I'm back to
Spider-Man
Free climbs second tallest California
California
Protest
Scale the 60-plus story
Premium
Found something
You get arrested for
In San Francisco
Now
Story
Still
Psychotic
Don't worry he's going to rest it folks
Bring attention to saving the children
Wow Maps
Sure like that one's on Roc
3 episode
It shows that much Alex actually cares about that story remember that the woman is using to stoke racial hatred
Kate steinle
He doesn't remember because he doesn't give a s*** about her except as a prop that he can use to ferment white fear
Also short refresher in case you haven't heard those episodes from
Wayback
This is like 2015 I mean if she wasn't shot in the back because she was white
A man who happens to be an undocumented immigrant picked up something covered in a rag which turned out to be a gun unintentionally the gun discharged
And a bullet ricocheted and ended up hitting the
It's a complete tragedy and my heart goes out to her only the racial element which doesn't exist
In reality
The guy who climb that Tower is named Mason to shop and he's building a little career for himself doing this Spider-Man
Your name is Mason Duchamp you're going to climb build
It's a risk
He was arrested last year for scaling a hotel in Vegas protesting covid restrictions
Misdemeanors for this. But I bet anything
Pepe's get dropped
Are minors
Like trespassing I mean he's just a dude who wants to climb shouldn't get attention
I don't even think he really gives a s*** about raising money
For these causes
Billion dollars by climbing this Tower
Pro-life causes
I mean let me put it this way all right
Ideologic
Play speaking I'm above the left-right paradigm
Ideologically speaking to put your palms forward in a way that to a building
Spider-Man outfits metaphor
I mean it listen if you're going to try and use
Carving a building in protest
There's a way to make money
Your Market.
To the right
Okay and you should probably get like
Sponsors to get on your back
No likey
Celebrity boxing
The left
Is going to be like
Get down
Get down from there
Stop it I don't think that's entirely true because people on the other side of the aisle do get arrested
I like
Patricia okumu who climbed the Statue of Liberty in protest a couple years back about to family separation
The right-wing media doesn't cover stories like that though except for like
Some sort of outrage
Immediately and then
Attention dies down I don't follow up and see the
They got arrested
It's Alex just doesn't know that that happened
He assumes that Liberals are
Just get away with everything
They didn't ask for Amelia
That is a fair point
Alex is really dumb
And he's a huge race
So
We can just go to
Bank on those as being fairly can
Yes
Albedo Rizal so dumb and racist
So many people here up and well
He has some thought
About the midterms
Deee-lite
Bikes
The people that support
And the movement is
Populist elected all over the country
Because they know he's effective
The populist awaken
Clean sweep
Mary's in Ohio and Indiana
He's endorse
Post 1000 candidates at 2
That sucks
Alex is conveniently not mentioning about these 22 candidates the Trump endorse
21 their primaries is that only four of them
Incumbents
That makes a little bit of a difference in terms of having such a great batting average the incumbency bias
Is really high
Trump actually does though he does have a pretty good record with endorsement
But this hidden Dynamic does come up
Like this
Incumbency thing
Prince and supported 149 candidates in the 2020 house elections in
116 of them one
Of all of them but he got wrong only touring company
And his record was backing Challengers was less impressive than the overall numb
Rye Rye
If somebody was regularly picking the globe
You got your crush
The Globetrotters did occasionally lose
The generals have their nights
Okay thanks get hot
From 3 can you imagine being there the night they win
I now feel like they must have one
Irene
For Gabriel I kept in medieval times the wrong night accidentally took the other guy down and everybody just stop it was like
Bummer
Similarly though to this truck back 23 candidates for the Senate
2020 and 18 of them what
Only one of these people was running
Challenge against an incumbent Senator and
Every other challenge candidate the drunk back
He's not good at picking
Can people who are already in office
This is what I'm saying because the people who
6 who aren't already in office
Weirdos
Winning election think the only senator who wasn't in combat
He chose who won an 2020 was Tommy
Sure
Chirp
Hey it happens sometimes and if you
Coach
College football team
And make sure that you get the most out of your child slave
Then you're gonna be in the government
Sooner or later
Fair enough
So Alex has some news
About
Austin Elementary
Preschools
This is shocking if true
And it's not true
That's shocking to hear him say that I guess
The LBGTQ p x y z
Elemento
Perfx UT
I mean
What about the lgbtq
AutoZone Austin
The middle schools and high schools elementary
Tell him you identify as LGBT. Here's a lollipop
When they do their recess time
And they're organized
Mud wrestling team for
For the oil wrestling
You're part of the wet t-shirt contest
And your training t-shirt contest
Lgbtq
Absolutely
Let's go confuse these kids are highly influenceable
With their Leaders with their teachers
Stinks
He's sounding a little confused
I like that
It started with like this was happening in high schools and it's a lollipop and extra recent
You know what they're doing in Middle School's do you know what they're doing a lollipop
Between geometry classes
What do we do
Yeah what is happened
I don't know I mean he's just making
You shut up in order to demonize people
Boots for the bigoted position
I'm just never we're just
As humans were never not going
Need to go through a f******
Satanic Panic or a Witch Hunt or something
Yeah we've had how many
Isabel and boring and then I'm going to have to look at people I know and be like
F******
Jacob Lawrence
It is it is a little sad yourself
If you fall for it
Well I mean I think someone like Alex would just make the argument that like I did never all for it I was right
Now that it's back you agree with me
So
I look this is
Get talking more about the school
Who's here this isn't
Never at The Big E
Big talking point I guess with all these
Right-wing decals
Jay-Z
Grooming
Another gloomy rhetoric and they learned a word and now there
They're obsessed
The entire credibly dangerous and they're putting
People in danger with this kind of rhetoric
Abhorrent
I hate them for it
We should
Teach the right
Fewer words are more worth
Alex
Much like he is not saying
Delete
Is the important part about this
Supreme Court thing
Pray he's not jumping on the grooming bandwagon
Great although he has already in the past has been a big fan
And now he's just actually making it worse
4000 percent increase the last
Kids identifying as trans
But nobody is grooming children
Grooming and they're forcing them to Hell into it
This is a Colt of depopulation taking off
They all look like
Another soul
Black white what color they are
They all looks Jessie J
You are insane
Number of
The four thousand percent number that's daisja fast and hard press to back that up
Pasta
Story about the there's something in the UK and some vague surveys
There are increases to the population that identifies as trans as well as Gabe
Lesbian bisexual and non-binary
It's 4000% doesn't increase over some unspecified amount of time fine
Stipulate that for the sake of our
My issue really comes in when he says it has something to do with the schools or their influence
Because these self-identification Trends are being seen across most of the world
If I had something to do with our public education system you'd expect to see that
Phenomenon being more localized
No fairly all over the place so you think
Based on that you should maybe seek out another
Explanation for it
Maybe
Note suggests that a better explanation is that the number of actual lgbtq
Dq4
Hasn't really gone up all that much
But the general Vibe of most of the population has become accepted and other people can feel comfortable
Be open about them
That probably doesn't have full explanatory power but
It's way more likely in this b******* that Alex
Rolling around
Bunch of nonsense
Yeah you know I think what's fun about
The more
He talks
And the more of the world gets
The more I think
Think that his extreme characterizations of what
The left wants our
Are actually good ideas like maybe we should get rid of the idea of mother and father
There oh no
Children taught
As a group
Popipo no he's got you hot together by a Cooperative of people who all carry quilly about the
These children instead of say somebody being like
My kid is more important
So your transcript should die
Talk over millions of people so your child
Die alright Purple Penguin
Maybe Alex is right
I mean have we maybe what that's what we've been wrong about the whole time Alec
Has been right about telling us what we should be doing
To the right way
So his show is satire
Thank you Alex now I am going to get rid of mother and father
Turbo penguin
So
This next clip I thought was pretty exciting
Because Alex
Hasn't read a story
You see the headline
Cold reading
He accidentally reports
But someone was
Beaten with tuna fish
Which I thought was really
Sweet
Purgatory
Torture taken hostage
With tuna fins
After leaving son without legs
Fellow inmates took him hostage and threatened to chop off his legs
Once they knew when he died
Alex love that Constitution man really her loves the Eighth Amendment cruel and unusual punishment
Oh yeah prison Justice which is in the Constitution
Really celebrated by our founding fathers
Why would you have prisons if you didn't want the prisoners to mete out their own form of
Right and it's
Clearly
It doesn't really matter because the story he's talking about is from the UK where Tony Smith was beaten in jail
They beat him with
Tuna cans 2210
1032 DeCamp
What's the situation where they were attacking him because
Yeah they knew he was there for betta
King's child
It also happened in 28
Also
Details here that Alex's mess
The first thing is that these two men that beat Smith didn't
Begin the attack because of his
They took him hostage in a Cell attempted
The force the jail to transfer them to another wing
They didn't want to be in this one cuz it was
Not good it was the type of place where you would take somebody hostage get out of it
Because of it right this was a prison beating of Opera
Not the jailhouse Justice Alex's fantasizing about it.
I mean birds
Stones again
Sure also it totally happen
4 years ago and for some reason Alex's reporting it is if it's
The current relevant story
In reality the only relevant news aspect of this is that there was a
Long delay in sentencing
The two men who beat Smith and that just happened recently
There's also led to a conversation about how Smith might be eligible for
For Government Camp
Sensation because the state has a duty
Protecting while he's in their custody
So this may end up costing UK taxpayers even more
That's
More reasonable
Yeah those justice system has a lot of Tangled threads
Important is that Alex loves this story because it makes them feel good to imagine violence being enacted on people he doesn't like
It's somewhat understandable to think of someone who abuses their child deserves whatever comes to them but it's
It strikes me as kind of sad when that's the beginning
And ending of Alakazam Alice
Really shallow and it's just
Kind of built out of
Anger feelings
Good to him
Yeah you know is every
Is a certain and I'm going to throw this out there
Like if you want to build a society
Especially one that funk
Maybe you don't put p
People who
First and initial reaction is the only one they care about
And then forget about it later on
So like
Like for instance
It's like if you're building a society or like maybe we should protect people even if we incarcerate them
One day we will be incarcerated justice system isn't perfect
Innocent in their letter
Perhaps any one of us could have this happen to us
Instead of being like that guy back
Maybe that's not going to work
Not but the long-term
That's the Constitutional Infowars way of dealing with it
Salix
Do you got a milli
Bitcoin
The same guy
It'll be millions of anything I've ever received
Feel the need to talk about this but also
After pretty bad before I forget
Clusters of something
Corporate media spends this all day
We were given a 1 million dollar
Roughly
Donation we can go
Donation
Troodon for me
40% mine
Sixty-five 70%
In the black
Explaining for treading water
Secret was evil
They're the ones that are saying
Is mental illness
A woman
AAA
You seem a little defensive about the chameleon
I'm starting to think that maybe he's a little bit like I might not have dessert
I might not have wanted people to know about that cuz it's sketchy
My final
I mean certainly
Because some issues when you present yourself as like I rely on
Donation
Same time disillusion anything if you have like
Someone is running for office in
Seems like I only take small donation
And then you find out today
I've taken a flood of
Can drop Millions on you
Noticed
What am I buying your
I think he actually does wrestle with that a little bit on this episode YouTube I s***
Seymour the point
Also to work to this Anonymous person
We're in a critical situation
Protecting us from the red
Infowars.com
Toppers
Dollars $50 a hundred dollars
Going to cancel anytime
One-time deal
Support Free Speech donate today
Infowarsstore.com
You're selling out of all the giant inventory we have a teacher at some of the years
Basically this show is like now settled in I mean
God knows that by next week
Or tomorrow he might
Be completely freaking out again
But like
It feels more normal
Then it has a week and a half or so
If I had to guess the reason for that
It's because what
He needed
Was money to buy stuff to sell to hazard
And a million dollars to pay off the kitchen
Get away with
Kicking down the road that was something he had to pee right away
I think that he's got that
And he was able to pull this.
With a bankruptcy
Need to postpone the trial. So now he's on borrowed time again
A not that like
Immediacy of the court case
That's going to
Be a real problem for him somewhere down the line
He's like
Wiggled his way out and he's got a little bit of breathing room again
I think you think that's the kind of feeling that I have
From this
Disgusting
I'm starting to really think that if
You've got a lot of money you can
Can really screw with the American justice system
I'm
Listen I'm going to go all the way and say that this goes from the top
It certainly doesn't come the other way
You know there's not a whole lot of people who are like you know just
Everyday workers out there like I'm a judge
Furious
Well your workaday person you know out there
Could get away with more
Bandit I mean put it on the ballot
I am going to buy some brainforce otherwise this rich person will have to face
Consequence
Sapulpa
Has come out
That Pope
He's probably against
The war
Which is unusual for Pope
He is
Confused
Just about a headline that he read
Why is the Pope
Francis says NATO may have provoked Russia invasion of Ukraine
Hopes to meet
Putin in Moscow
Blame the weapons
Washers
And says that they are the ones that stand together endangering the world
Cuz almost everything
Yeah he was a reward
Well I reckon
Carrabba's
And I
Wanted to be a good strong Christian Institution
But
Under this Pope it has been the opposite of that hasn't that's debatable
Out of the Catholics were up in arms about it
What is this
Francis
Russian invasion of Ukraine
Extra meat Putin in Moscow
Largest Italian daily newspapers
To meet with Russian President Vladimir Putin in the near future
I asked cardinal
Corona
That I was willing to go to Moscow
Are still insisting even if
Tablets meet what time
Kansas fatality not be stopped
25 years ago we experienced the same thing in Wanda
Blame
And the fact that NATO overthrew
Government
And you know the rest
Story
This is a fascinating example of
Common feature on Alex's show
He takes a story that has a kernel of Truth and then he just makes stuff
In this case it is true that the pope gave an interview where you suggested that it was possible that
Quote NATO barking Skateland
Ukraine
Also save quote
I have no way of telling whether his rage has been
Provokes but I suspect it was may be facilitated by the West
Attitude
Isn't interest
Bank statement but it's also a far cry from what Alec
What is reporting
Hope also said quote the ukrainians can't be blamed for having fought back
In the dawn boss which
Which implies they were fighting back
I got something
He also said quote now the Russians
Take a note just add-on boss region but Crimea Odessa and the ports
On the Black Sea everything
I have a bad feeling about it all all admit I'm very pessimistic
However it's our duty to do all we can to stop the war
In terms of blaming weapons manufacturer
The Russian
Just found out the tanks are useless and they might be developing new weapon
Wars are fought for this reason to
Detest your arson
This is what happened to the Spanish Civil War before the second World War
The production and the sale of armaments is disgrace
But you are bold enough to stand up against it
It's fair to say that the arms sales or something the pope opposes
Recognizes is apart of all wars
But Alex is really over selling
Disposition
To be like
This is all about weapons
I mean date
It is so much like
What in
God's name do you think so
Hope is going
Sing about a war
Not good morning God
Kids named what
Who is like
Hey man
I got to be honest
I think slaughtering millions of people is gray
Break with tradition
This was pretty good this is a good one
That's a good one
Since the 1500s have we seen a war
This good this is a joke
All that other stuff that Alex is Angus just making
Stuff up
He just wants the pope statement to sound more like
Validates his own Merit
Alex is doing this because he knows most of his audience only need superficial validation to feel like Alex
Has been proven right about
Spriggs a Google Pope and NATO and see headlines like quote Pope Francis blames nato in the Wall Street
Is right about all the other stuff he said
It's a tricky can pull because
You know he's just riffing headlines and he's trained as audio
Just to do the same and pretend there's some sort of a death do it
That's all he's doing
If anything Alex
Ever says ever means anything then the pope cannot
Possibly be making
King estate Metallica's pretend
He is
Believe you
The globalist
It's not a big deal that you'll be saying these things it would be a repudiation of Alex's entire world
The pope isn't someone who changes their mind because it got hot
He's supposed to be an emissary of the devil who's weirdly obsessed with breaking up American militia
The literals
Photo guys
Oh no we've got to change our behind and let's
Let's rip but it it's not like the pope is in League with the literal
Christian devil if the literal Christian devil is real
Then so is the Pope
Do you know what I mean
Have a great Point using fallible
I forgot about that
Magic powers Eve never would have been able to arrest
If your if your religion is real than the pope gets
Magic I don't understand how that's not that's not a regular conversation I forgot about that
2Pac magic not just the pope to like a lot of people
Can perform Miracles your transubstantiation is
Absolutely
Magic is
Avail
People who believe in
Bulshit
So Alex is a map
Of NATO
And he really wish this one
And here's the map
Really really matters right here
Not an inch of NATO's
Military jurisdiction
Spread
Random of
February 9th 1990
And then
George Herbert Walker Bush confirm that in speeches
And it policies
But now what have they done
1990 here's the map of
In red
Places
Turkey and Spain and France and Sweden
But now it's expanded into more than a dozen
Other
Countries
Alex is lying about the agreement between Baker and garbage jobs
Easter
President became entirely irrelevant as Germany reunified
Also Sweden isn't part of NATO
Looking at this map doesn't know where Sweden is
He thinks Norway
This week in Finland are going to be Jordan 80 Alpha quick
Actually something that I think
Is revealing of how little Alex knows exactly current modern
Right
Think it's a big deal.
Sweden is not part of NATO because of the conversations that they're having a
Prompted by Russia's aggression
Ukraine
Gerardo Handel on any of this
The cause of all of this
Why exactly are people are non-nato countries react
Things to this going like
We got to get an 800 otherwise we're going to get invaded
Yeah it
It seems it seems strange there's little moments like that that like
It seems like a fuk up or like a mistake revealing of an underlying ignorance
Caring to learn anymore
Headlines
If you learn something then you might have to change your
And if that weren't a true statement that was rejected by so many people it would be very funny
Prosthetic
Is directly on that here in a little bit love it
But first Alex has to narrate a meme
Really informative memes
Catch my drift
Figures
I'm simulcasting radio phones
Allied 123456 stick figures
Yummy fruit one of them Falls over and dies
Correlation does not equal
Causation
And they all died
And that's what we're witnessing
With the vaccines
That's um
Still
Having proven causation
You know what to do
One thing all six of them could have been poisoned earlier right
One thing about
A Battleground
Being the removal in murder of other
People and their right
Is that
The news doesn't really hit it
It's hard so you can just narrate memes
Do you know no big deal
I'm going to narrate memes when you get a couple million dollars coming in no one else to die anymore
First of all there's one decision that is like
To get this
People need it
He bastard talk through it
Explain to me
I meant third thing can't explain that he's explaining to me because he's on the radio
Yeah
Futon
That's how you get
Amine
Yeah
I can't I mean
It's like it's like
The board
The version of theater
Is fine cuz that's a dark
Sure it's like if that was really bad
You're taking something that's a different form of medium
Running it in the
Previous generations medium
You know like
What is reporting something visually
Audio media
But he's doing it so poorly
It's bad
Radio Improv
All psychic
That they have to Bendix
Explain the sight gag
In The Improv scene yeah yeah funny how you kicked your leg out above over your head in that moment
Where it was funny to do that the thing that makes the thing
In any way useful
And you remove it
Diamond remove another layer of that
What a dork
So are we get
Back to
We actually just get to Alex taken
Call from a farmer
Alex wants to
Things are bad things going to be bad
I don't want to make this about the Ukraine situation and fertilizer
Bushes in that direction
And then
The farmer is like
There's something
You're saying
People not planning
Because I don't have fertilizer
Well not planting in all
Also
The fact that the
We had the torrential rains we got
Half of our annual rain
Within a week
. of time
And
We just ain't going to get out in the field or already
Two weeks behind the 8-ball already
That's going to be another two weeks
Before people can even get in the field
Plant
Are corn and soybeans
Unbelievable sir God bless you
Young people on average play radio
Ammoland
WhatsApp
That's your point.
The most common sense
Ninety-plus percent
How should the
Name one of them it's the Bill of Rights
Because I watched so much of Alex's show I know that they don't do studies he's talking about a Mark Dice Man on this
Street B
That's not a study
Drunk people out of Boardwalk
Editing app to make people look stupid
Stupid
Yeah it what happened there that pause and the reason that Alex goes off in
Completely different direction is good with that guy's describing
Climate like last year in the years before here's the thing that's regular
And now the climate is
Torrential rains that are really actually
Even if we had fertilizer
These are out of seasonal rains
Yeah you expect rains to not do this
It's different
Got to ramble about a Mark Dice video they were pretending as a study
You imagine if 90%
Good name an amendment
Throw me throw me out to like
A f******
God damn Wolf Blitzer been like they've done studies and while we're going to go see these in
Go to a jaywalking
20 years ago.
I mean that's the level of content that you get here
Tip of the spear
Got to get on it
So we get to talking about the
Pliers
The food plant
Got to watch out for a little bit on a recent episode
I'll bet that caller wants to say hey man
This is big
Big deal
This is a big deal
Bring up one thing and I'll let you run with
About this a little bit
But no one is
On.
From the food industrial food
Unbelievable
Wellshire
More plants are burned down each day
Manawa statistics has been looked into my statistician
Which team won
Thousands of people 11 name
Anyway
Make up a name
It's crazy
Thousands of times the normal amount so like
If the normal was one there's been a thousand
Ridiculous completely making up everything he said there
I somewhat suspect that he'd even forgotten that this was
Was a conspiracy supposed to be worried
Scout yeah
To fact-check reached out to the National Fire Protection Association to get some insight
Since the recent social media posts and Tucker Carl Carlson segments about this
The NFPA gets their data from the national fire incident reporting C
System and I want you to guess how many manufacturing and processing plant fires
There are in an average
5308 strictly agricultural play
Plant sure
Between January and April 2022 there were
20 fires reported at us
Food processing facilities which if everything is actually in the normal to low side of where they would be in a normal
That sounds like a good week
Peaks at certain times
It seems like this
Everything I can tell this very much
Normal or low right
Susan McKelvey a spokesperson for the NFPA summed it up I think
Pretty well
The recent inquiries around these fires appears to be a case of people suddenly paying attention to them and being surprised about
How awesome they do occur
But NFPA does not see anything out of the ordinary in these numbers
I would expect that we're more the case for all of like the huge or systemic problems that we face
That people are just you just believe
Blissfully Auto
Oh there's no public transport
What
Serious problem now
Yeah
People like Alex and Tucker didn't know that these certifiers were so,
So when they saw Tom memes about this fire that fire things must be
So much more than a normal year
It looks fun for them
It's exciting to think there's some Grand nefarious plot
But you're covering
Saving the food supply
That excite
Bixby audience and releases as fun endorphins you get when your role playing Prophet Detective
Plus
The alternative
Sucks
If you look into this and you realize that it's
Totally normal that there be this many fires at Food facilities what can
Can you do
You don't get to accuse vague groups of enemies of planning to kill you
You just kind of two
You either shrug and say that's just how things are or you can be a total dork and advocate for
Stronger fire safety regulations at these facilities
It's not exciting to an audience that doesn't give you the Russia pretending
What kind of bowl truth-teller large systemic problem is going to take
Years to face
Concerted effort in the front of
Actually make
Progress we have to focus
And nobody can get mad about things along the way we just have to
To do it bad it's a disaster it's so Alex
He makes up s*** about statisticians and probabilities because he wants to give the appearance of having looked into stuff
But he doesn't want after
Reach that unsatisfying conclusion he would reach if he actually did it
Top statisticians from Statin use prestigious
Top status
Rights
I can't
Prestigious
It is it is so weird
I mean I didn't know I'd be able to get something from their b******* and have them
Sensationalize it and then I've learned more about it I'm like
How if I let this go on for so long but probably because I'm reading about cop
Cops being great or whatever it is that do says
Fair enough if you think about the number of facilities there actually are in the United States
5300 is it
That like
High of a percentage of them. They're all burning down all the way
They got this amount of structural damage
I think it is a little bit shocking
It just to like
See numbers and we like right now
That's not a that's not something
Touches my life all that often
And I allowed it to continue
It's something that
B alternative
To having that response
Is
Ship it'll freak people out
And it's a beaut
You can't just have this problem be like okay
I don't care let's listen let's get above a left-right paradigm
That's too many fires
How about that
How about we can agree that shirt men
I don't know what the correct
Ramona fires reason I push back a little bit a little
Because I am not 100% sure why all these fires are happening cuz I don't know what Rey
Regulations could help
Maybe
Agreed maybe there isn't a better way
Creep I don't know. That's why I see this is elect right man I don't even know what's going on I'm just looking at the number
Tires and I'm saying let's make that number
Lower sure this is why we've got the National Fire Protection
Association thinking about these things right
Chirp
This guy's not happy with him
Because
He thinks that Alex is holding onto Trump
Oh yeah
Get rid of them
Think you're given Trump app
Right now
And I think
You're still holding on to the idea
Is organic
And that Trump is real and I think that
System would never allow that
Because the system would never jeopardize
Steak
The control the power
They would never let someone organic
Jeopardize that
And you keep holding on to this idea that they are
You keep saying this thing that Obama is running things
Obama
Again
There never just be one guy running things
Far worse
Bend Obama is running
And I get what you're saying there but you're still
Directing people into the left-right paradigm
And you're still giving this
System
When it doesn't have one
And another thing
Populist movement
Bolsonaro
This caller is saying
I was just interested in Trump because of some movement the coalesced around him
How to
Crying on air about how he was willing to
Die for Trump he's our god king appointed by God for this moment to provide us with an a
Yeah he can get the f*** out of here with these attempts to rewrite his past a little less embarrassing now
Come on
Invented shoes
I did know that I gave you
Is pretty great excessively over the details
I think it makes sense of Alex thinks that he made that up
Understands the concept he thinks that being above the left-right Paradigm just means beating
Even if you think that Trump is
Alex.
It recognizes some people are
Like Alex
But I'm explaining that the Trump movement
Galvanizing force is really scared the New World Order
Organic
The people are organic
I know I'm real I know I'm not getting any
Secret help from the New World Order
I'm getting a million-dollar
Brother
That your response is entirely right like if Alex wants to keep up this
Appearance then he's going to need to publicly reveal who the person was who gave him $2000000 or crypt
His whole thing is as all these like
I'm supported by the people man no-one secretly paying me off at the same time he's taking in billions of dollars from some
I'm secret donor in digital money
It's all out of sync and if anyone that Alex criticizes did the same thing percentages dead to rights
They're getting paid by Klaus Schwab to help kill every 100% play by his own rules
It's fine I think for him to take in a couple million dollars from a crypto donor but he's already
Deserves to know who that person is
Because they may have some interest or some connections that would be relevant for the audience
To be aware of
If it's someone like Max Keiser then it obviously comes at the strings of needing Alex
Crypto to his audience
Saski and Max have discussed in the past
Hit someone like Peter teal then that opens up
Thousand more questions that the audience should be asking
If it's an online Neo-Nazi or white nationalist type front and that speaks volumes
And if it's just a rich benefactor who believes in the infowar but weirdly didn't step in till now
That's benign
It still should be known
Unless that the owner's identity is known as
It's hard not to make assumptions about who it might be
Agenda Mike
Come along with that donation
I'm just call on Alex to reveal who does daughter was because otherwise
I don't understand how your audience could ever trust you
Do you ever
Here's the only way that he
He would talk
Is if we got anywhere from
00012 any number of Bitcoin from anyone
Like secretive donors giving Bitcoin and s***
I am f******
Maybe but I still don't think you would
Such b*******
I understand
I am guess what I mean
I think
Through the people who are looking into these things over at the splc
Sure and what-have-you I think
B b
Mystery that gets off
If I were Alex I would get out in front of it
And just reveal who this person is if it's not a big
Big deal then it's not a big deal right
And the person should be loud as a hero of
Infowars
Of course if it is somebody that it would be suspicious that you're taking
$2000000 in Bitcoin from going to come out
It is an baby you should come up with a defense for that in advance
And get ahead of the thing and just reveal who this
This
I mean he's read the news about Bitcoin
Play but it does feel like if you want to know where a wallet is from
You can find that if
Information
If I don't
I don't know how either but I doubt someone
Some people do
So Alex wants to know why this caller is so interested in
And it gets
A little angry
Let me ask you this why
Why are you upset about Trump right now
Why are you trying to hammer him
Because I believe that
If this time is still holding on to their weapon
Their main weapon
And I was at
The capital
And I was there
Ready to go I would have done it any day and Trump had the chance
He had
Bosc pear
1776 in his hands
Any cars back
Disagree with you
Good call
Wow
Alex doesn't like hearing somebody say what he
Yeah it's it's
I was kind of shocked
Icrew
You should say
Too logical
No you said you should feel betrayed by the guy who betrayed you seems like it should not
Yeah, it's a complex
Place to get to home I was betrayed I feel that way
Seems a lot
Less performed he's pissed
Agree with him he got
Listen to believe it b******* and then he got
A trait that so Alex disagrees cuz he thinks
Too bad strategy
I am so after he's hung up on the guy he
Going to Sky and Washington Sky walking around here
Hello sir thank you
I just want to stay I really respect on and I want to Echo everything all your previous callers that's backed up
Last caller
But it's okay to have disagreements I respect that
Thank you after
Is questions really well
And you're doing a great show today Alex not he's not
Alex has to agree to disagree with this guy because he can't actually before him and he campy again
Got them
If Alex agrees with that collar than his actions on January 6th and every day sent to make no
Why would Alex have been
Trying to calm the crowd if he agreed with this collar
Quality claim that antifa was behind all this
Simultaneously he can't disagree with him because he knows that a whole lot of his audience
Feel the same way that caller does
This color is the True Believer
Let's being wound up by the con artists
That's like Alex said provoked
Conflict or outright
Condemn this guy's perspective even if you
Even if you pretend to disagree
That's too dangerous
I would literally it is literally too dangerous
That guy was ready to overthrow the country exactly
Yeah we have a conversation with this guy and disagree with him coherently
It would have been a bad strategy to
Take the White House
What strategies Alex pursuing that's so much better
Having violent mood swings on are covering being with headlines on stories he hasn't read and wait
Super rich guy to give him Millions
The temporarily bail him out of trouble while he waits for the Sandy Hook cases to get a new court date
Where's the strategy the midterms
What is the better strategy
Strategy to admit that you tried to overthrow the f****** cap
Here's what's good strategy
Lie as much as you can obfuscated much
You can put blame on as many people as you can
Until people forget about it as long as possible and then you get your second shot at overthrowing the gun
Alex's
Alex is strategy is the same as Tucker Carlson a Miss f****** Mitch McConnell strategy
This is terrible is probably somebody else's fault and if it was don't investigate it don't worry about it we'll never think about it again in 3 years
Is this definitely not going to happen again promise guarantee it no way
Right
But still it's bad strategy for Alex's busy
Yes that is
Agree with the guy
Because arguing on this point exposes his ass so he gets him off of line and then agrees to disagree respecting their differing
Keep in mind all the other folk that he refuses to agree to disagree with
But this guy
Who's mad that Trump didn't lead a charge into the White House
To overthrow the country
That deserves our respect
Sexual position and
Also notice and Alex isn't against a literally taken country over because that would be a bad thing to do
It's just bad strategy
The goal isn't bad
The end result isn't bad
He just doesn't think that with the color wanted would have brought about that end result
Paul Robeson
January 6th stuff though
I just wanted to bring up something that Alex probably won't touch
William Todd Wilson Bo keeper who plead guilty just had a statement of affect
Released and it looks pretty bad for Alex's buddy Stewart Roads
A lot of this stuff is providing more insight in
The things that we've already known but there's some added stuff in here to
Princeton
At about 5 p.m. on January 6th Stewart was back at his hotel where this happen
Quote roads then called an individual over speakerphone
Wilson heard roads were
Heatedly implore the individual to tell President Trump to call upon groups like The Oath Keepers to forcibly oppose the transfer
Terrapower
This individual denied roses request
How to speak directly with President Trump
After the call ended roads
Stated to the group
I just want to
Chili curious who that individual might be
Someone whose acquainted with Trump and Stewart
And is on good enough terms of both
Both of them for Stewartsville come
For making this request
A store to assume they could
Could get Trump in on the loop
I don't assume that's a giant
Group of people
I don't I'm not saying it is Rodger or Alex
But like the else would it be
No I don't I mean no it should be
I don't know
Who in Trump's orbit
Would be in
Direct contact Network Road the phone
Like I don't know who that would be
Nobody nobody in trumps
Actual government circle is picking us up.
It seems like
I don't
Exclude any possibilities information
Sure
I don't know
Yeah it's it's
That's a question that I'm very curious about what the answer is
Alex probably
I do I be worried
Hey wait I we get another call and
Remember how Alex gave it up to the legends on that mopey goodbye episode sure
You forgot somebody
But any case I wanted to bring up
Last week when you were going down memory lane
And I thought Jim Tucker should have been mentioned
Bringing the Bilderberg
To the Forefront
And
I decided it would be great to
Mention him as well
On your show
Absolutely
Amazing Nasher also Nazi
I do like
Two things about this one the idea that like a friendship Tucker
Realized
Then the second thing to us that she thinks
That was a walking down memory lane that's yeah.
It always is my life
Do you recognize that
But no one's doing it for him cuz no one gives us
I am amazed
At the salt process
Get to calling
Alex Jones
Days after
The fact
About something that he does not remember or care about
It was a lie
I mean why
Why do you feel like
Jim Tucker needs
To be on that
Maybe this is Jim's Widow
I don't know cuz I could make
Say Jim say gym
How to give a magnet have to call an elf
Regularly
Yeah she does say that she's a very long-term there we go
Also she did say that she was at Bilderberg with Alex protesting
That means
Remind me
Pennywise
That would make sense
Alex has a guest
For most of the third hour give you a
A guess
Chantilly Lace with a pretty feet
Pete Santilli
I don't care about this guy
Always a radio host who talked about him
Before
You know he also
Yes but you also I hate
Stewart Rhodes
The two of them hate each other
Valic is still having him on
Amanda ignoring news that implicates
It tried to overthrow the government
Anyway it's about the UN
Pandemic
Pete Santilli
Investigative journalist
I have spent
Months
Reading documents
Researching what's happening
Geneva Switzerland
The 22nd the 28th
Thomas Reed
The UN will control
Just like
UNESCO
Education policy the rest of it
We're under you and control the flow
Did our government sign treaties with it
And no wonder its control
Congress Avenue
Because he plans to implement all of this week
Have to make this
The central issue PE got cut off
Please continue
Everybody should understand
Existential threat I'm going to lay this out as follows
Thought we couldn't
Stop any of this
My God
Annual World Health assembly run by the World Health Organization
It doesn't seem like this treaty is definitely going to be dealt with there
Although there is a plan for this to be there's a treaty that the EU is working on
International pandemic
Responses
The plan then everyone agrees with negotiations it seems incredibly ambitious it might be adopted sometime
Part of their plan is delivering a progress report at next year's
26th annual
World Health assembly
Take place next
Conspiracy about this and Jim Fetzer has been spreading
Stuff about it since last a great good news like Alex might be back on his bullshitted news
Luna International bodies are talking about how they can
Collaborated means
It's just boring
It's just a boring conference
For boring
Everything is their main attack
I noticed that
What are mean how many made
Attacks are we on here
Somali
What is their main attack
If it's this meeting
How is it
The other things that he said is their main attack
And he didn't say those things and you can't prove it
I have to release this
Episodes I can go back
How to get rid The Archives
We have one last trip here and was really boring but when they come back
Into the last segment Alex has a little bit of what I would describe as
A mini fake outburst
And then
Gentleman I wanna be very very clear right now with all of you
Phillip Powers everything you talked about came through no I do
There's nothing more frustrating than reading levels documents
And watching clips of their speeches
For 30 years on their 28
Knowing they're in power and knowing you're doing this
Weather
Or not they even exist
I didn't know that they made the weapon
Members of my family almost killed my dad
You almost killed her
Come back and don't even worse
Back to 1776 but not the British winning
The New World Order winning
What is hell in the lockdowns the starvation that comes with it
We have to stop
This folks
What is
I'm the lucky most the rest of segments
So he just has peed how's the respite
Emotional
They killed my dad
I can't deal with that
Anyways
Can you do my job also like
Again
We
Their plans on stoppable now you can't stop
Stop giving people fake hope that they can stop something just because you feel better cuz I have a couple million dollars I'll tell you this plans on south of
Google now you said that concretely definitively
Dick I mean you're trying to stop
90% of the people
From dying
So only 50
Here's the thing
You can't be
You can't have that good of an attitude it's only 50
Let me interpret this
Alex is so hungry that he can't wait 10 more minutes to get off are you still hungry
But I've done better acting
Getting out of a you f****** fryer job
Yeah man
This is weird because this episode wasn't
All about the Roe versus Wade thing
No it wasn't as much even about that as you might've
Expect
Like
Certainly there's there's some conversation about it
Share some
It's Dom
Normalize Alex show
In the midst of
Huge nose and
Untethered emotional bulshit from here
So yeah maybe maybe he's just found a state of normalcy within the the chaos
I don't know what it feels like
To suddenly get $2000000 but I imagine that would
Change your kind of Outlook
You know the only way I can get text realize it is in like
Little
Mind gifs of cartoon characters
Like
The kind of thing I mean
A giant
The problem with Bitcoin
Is you cannot put it into a burlap sack with a dollar sign drawing
That is the biggest issue
Solutely huge prom can't bite it
That's a real Bitcoin right there
Oh well looks like we may have a job for a bit longer
It is easier to handle b******* you know after what
We do but really
When you stopping there like wait
She just got somebody just gave him
$2000000
Somebody
Just two million
Yeah
Million dollars really heavily implies
They have a million dollars
That wasn't somebody the last
$2000000
No no
Is Christ stories on folder
We'll see what happens on that front
His better half
Pack something we live in a future where I'm just like
Georgia
Typing something
Make it not happen
I know what you mean
Goddamn
So I will check in on that but for that like
I don't know
Yeah world sucks yet stay strong and help each other we'll do our best
We have
Some thoughts
Maybe it'll be a little bit more solid in the coming days
I'm just going to
Stockpiling water
I look
We have a new food
Aquafina actress
We do have a few sponsor and its knowledge
Don't worry about it it's Alex
Will be back but until then
Omniome Leo I'm dzx Clark
I hope you all
Have a happy Dream mccreamy song
The sex robots
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work