Damn important
I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Sit around a little bit
Alex Jones
Here we are.
My bright spot today Jordan is
I recently had to get something delivered by gopuff
Okay I've never used them before it's like a delivery thing they have a warehouse and they have
I like all kinds of like Sudafed if you need them
New York City
Or you don't want to go fantana also have booze from grocery items
I don't know I'm not this isn't a plug
I'm not worried about it otherwise this will make no sense
Why
I need to get this and I was looking over what they had
Stock and available and I saw something it was like well this is the coolest thing I've ever seen
And so
I ordered Bubba Bubba Monster Mash cereal
Frankenberry
Chocula The Mummy with the thing and then the werewolf
All of the monster cereals I have finally got together and they're jamming as a band
71 right
72 blueberry
Steph Curry fours name is fruit Brute
Alright I'm a mommy mommy
And then of course in 2021
They did my surgery tonight
So we have
Three things that I think are important to bring up about this the first is what month is it
Is the Halloween
Is
Early May well it's 50 years
Is it the 50th Anniversary later on a get-together 71
Cereal variety that's great
And I found something really
Telling about this
And that is
One of these things is not like the other okay it does not belong in there
Fruit Brute
No chocula all the rest of them are fruit based
Can't just have fruit bass serial your skin chocolate elements in there
Chocolate covered strawberry or something but it does not work in this area
Reform
Chocula
Go solo you need to be in the band
Vampires don't really team up with
Now they're pretty
Solo yellow hunt independent creatures the vampires
Renfield
Hell yeah but renfield's are disposed
True
My bright spot is you know
You know that I love the tennis has
True love the Rafa's right my favorite player obviously just guy who is really into
Big anti-vaxxing Australia
Over the past three days
A nineteen-year-old kid
Did something that hasn't been done for like
20 years
He beat Rafa
Djokovic and then zverev
Back-to-back-to-back
He PizzaRev that mean that one wasn't excited
I mean he's in the top 10 but he sucks
Is your boy
He's he's weak he's calories
Wow this year old kid
Spanish
Kid
From Spain
Look up to Rafa's entire life
Since before he
You is like
Biscuit
Want to Major
When this kid was 2 years old
Alright
So
Robbins injured
Is he's coming off a bad injury he's got a terrible foot injury because he's Rafa and that's just how he does things
So then he comes back he plays Djokovic the next day
Teresa
Three and a half hours man this was some of the best tennis anybody's ever played
19 years old
And you know what I was thinking Dan what's up
My entire adult life I've had a Spanish Adonis to look up to
And Ralph is going to retire
Well
The chain remains unbroken my presence of God closes a door he opens a window
Glad you have that next 20 years
It is amazing
That's great for my bright spot I had a prop
Alexa
I assumed you wanted a guitar
Leaving episode to go over
I think that maybe one of the more notable things have come out and Infowars world in the past
Since we've had an episode is the
Little bit audio of Paul Joseph Watson being a real races
But he might be erased
I don't care because this is only
Things that we've already known he's been expressing
Pretty much his entire career and through Infowars and
Actually it is to the Past
I need a break from Alex's present a Bull Shed from the present day.
2003 July 30th
Back in
Alright
Very interesting stretch of time I think we find some wacky characters and some silly.
Robin forget
Do that.
Doesn't do walks
Congratulations Makayla on your dreamy creamy wedding thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Mickey and California you're on the air thanks for holding
Hello Eric I'm a first-time caller I'm a huge fan I love your work
I love you
I'm a killer girl thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Spider bites
What's a beer in your horses you rode in on thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Stop Alex before it's too late
Thank you I think it would be
Next one
Duncan forcse on Twitter
Isaiah house
Okay South Carolina I don't know what endorse political candidate
Ballotpedia page and it seems like he has some good answers to the question
Carolina check him out and see if he's a candidate you'll be interested in
Thank you so much Danny Duncan
Jordan we start off
Two
320 Wednesday to be
It might be
I don't know the calendar
Here's where we start off
Breakdown of the lies
You're being lied to
Still
Well maybe that's a bad power
This is a fascinating guess to see pop up here in the past
This is the first time that he's been on but it's not fascinating for the reasons that it might first appear
The reason it's interesting to see Michael chossudovsky is because
He's not someone who's still a regular on Alex's show
But should be
For a while just Dusky made frequent appearances with Alex because in many ways he's an ideal
Guest
Beginning in 2001 found at the
The center for research on globalization
And from that point on has been responsible for one of the websites that disseminates
Ganttic portion
Of the anti-globalization
Conspiracy content that's on the internet
Global research research dot CA
We'll get more into him when he shows up on the show before I heard that this is the first time that him and
Alexandra Sadowski passes
Their paths crossed by years
Clerk of Court
I was kind of underwhelmed eventually but it's
This is the case of all Infowars origin story signed up
It is notable as hell like this is a big
Like
I guess maybe it's not a big deal but
If consequential in terms of like
The pads that
These two would end up going
Globalresearch.ca being like a gigantic
Conspiracy Clearinghouse
Emma and Alex being from 2000
Three awkward becoming
Such a luminary of the conspiracy the overlap of their
Wednesday is huge
I would be only for us
So look
Visa Visa
Saddam's kids
Yes they were shown
5 with facial reconstruction
Because they were abused
Quite butylated in the course of the US actions in
Killing them
And so in order to make them
Look more convincing right people
Maybe we can debate whether or not that was a great idea for for the people to do
They were giving some
Uno reconstructor
Surgery
And they look like folks from a bad wax museum
But Alex is an expert on these matters
What
Alex is a noted scholar in the realm of
The relative quality wax museums apparently
Driving around to different towns tasting there
Wax museums
Of course I think so when I was younger we did a lot of road trip vacations as well
Drive to California to see our family
Every summer saying we lived in Missouri so is Missouri to California and lies
Very long nap every night so we take make a meal out of Drive-In
Totally you go
Like one year you'd maybe take a straight shot
Through the middle
Boring to do again can't do anything different
Stuff like Wall Drug in somewhere where you every time you drive somewhere
Sooner or later there's going to be sinus like Caverns
Can you just go to
The world's largest
That's where you go
It's America
But yeah I don't
My experience looking back on it is definitely not like
Hey I know all about
Wax museum or anything
Maybe it's just the case
Deeply into wax
Yeah that does sound like a detail that should be shared if it is true
If it does what
There's no way you look we've we've been on road trips from the Midwest you road trip out here
The idea of going to like
Any of those
Stop over things where world's largest
And then be like okay well now we're going east
So we got to find and compare the world's largest butt over there
Do the one from the wet no more likely thing is that Alex went to one wax
Museum when he was a kid and now he's exaggerating that to create
God I also want him to be
Expert on Wax Museum me to overthink we are a little bit
Is introducing his main narrative
It's going to take over this episode but he's also really all over the play
Normal
We have now entered orwellian
Now
Mercantil
Louisiana wall the traffic
What
He's just rambling all over the place was a betting Market of some sort and I can't finish
Clarify what he's talking about
This is Alex reporting that the government is setting up a literal casino-style betting pool where these leaks and
Contractors can gamble on coming Wars and countries collapse
That sounds great what is describing is called Pam or the policy analysis market for
I guess what
He's actually not far off from reality
Naturally there's some important caveats
To make in one of the first that I think the most important is well expressed in the paper by Robert Looney in the journal strategic
Inside
Quote because DARPA is mandated to take on risk
He projects
Failures have occurred
Sometimes the projects they embarked on a little bit wacky
He and this policy analysis Market is one
One such example
To be clear this project was abandoned around the time that this episode of Alex's show it never actually exist
It isn't actually asthma cabin as evil
Is it might initially sound
The basis for this idea was that for years
Futures markets have been used as a predictor of societal unrest and other sorts of
Geopolitical issues
Again from this strategic insights article
Yusuf
Petroleum Futures Contract prices isn't exactly the manner in which
Traders gauged the likely outcome of events such as the US Naval response
To arax invasion
Of quate in 1990
In a like manner the movement of petroleum Futures prices in late March 2003 after the recent Iraq
War Began reflect
To be implications Traders Drew
Concerning the outcome of the consul
Falling rapidly in the first few days of the conflict But Rising again after it became apparent the Iraq iresine would not fall in
In a matter of days
The goal of this policy analysis Market wasn't so much about allowing Elites to gamble on geopolitical conflict
Because in a roundabout way they already Cannon do
It was about giving us intelligence agencies mark
Get based ways to trade on different Patel
Which it was theorized by provide signals that can be interpreted like is already done with sudden movements
The commodity futures
Right
So
They were trying to create
I guess
Capitalism based virtual reality system whereby they can predict
Using the data of who's buying and selling what whether or not they're going to go to war
It's sort of but not not exactly like I did not like whether or not they're going to go to war
Predict potential coming
Trouble and stabilisation in area
Frere very important elements like
It wasn't
Supposed to be about anyone getting rich
And it wouldn't have been a vehicle for that they had a cap on a hundred dollars
Search for bats
And only 1,000 expert Raiders were even participated in this
Invited to participate initially
Maui
I'm saying that
The underlying idea here makes
Some sense
From just like a conceptual standpoint but please
Do not take that to be me saying this was a good I
It obviously something that could go wrong in about a thousand different ways and even leaving that aside its
Seems like it's in
Very poor
The world already has a
Learned bad image of organizations like the CIA they don't need to add the already bad Optics of a
They have to like
They're gambling on whether or not a particular government will fall the same
Might be involved in destabilizing
Yeah I like going back there like all man we lost
The ton of money on Haiti they got
Free s***
Rite Aid
There's so many things that just looks
Shity about that
Even though the system didn't appear to have the ability to be rigged in some particular way just
Just like you were saying the offer
It could be a disaster
He'll be a complete mess and I suspect that's part of the reason why
Never move forward
Alex is not recognizing
Or maybe doesn't even know or whatever
It's not moving
Forward
Water by
This point in
Late July about it though is that it does have that kind of
Evil Global policy that you're looking
For if you are fighting against the global that's so great that such a supervillain
Well it it's not but it looks like
It's like Alice's he'll supervillain ask to me is more that there are like
Like a million better ways to do the thing that you're trying to achieve by setting this evil thing up
You know like I understand that
The goal you have right that would be away for like
People who have
Expert opinions to have some sort of
Conglomerate it like
Intelligent that they put together they
Putting a hundred bucks
Be like
A worthwhile thing is because then there is incentive for them not to just make rampant guests completely like I
The thought process
Without doing those tables and this is where we do tailback into that idea of a
DARPA having like these risky
Besides there's like a better way to do this
This is a possibility
You didn't work and I didn't happen
But
Alex gets
Two defining
The New World Order
You'll notice that Satan
The new world
Take a note well
You stopped taking notes
Rolled into a
Computerized
Ability
SeaWorld
Determination
No Satan
No
That also seems pretty different than like how you describe things
World economic Forum staff
That was just like a bunch of it like I could conceivably be mixed up in there but certainly
You know that's not
Call Schwab names University of
Con artist New World
About it
I think there's some similarities to how he describes things at the present tape there's like foundational differ
Princess
Ivey's Towing in 2003
Total that's kind of like if he wants
The pitch this
He's an extreme right-wing ideologue so he's railing against this new world order he's imagine to attack
And help explain social progress to his audience
It's not that Society decided to living by Ridge
Christian doctrine
Fair to be Christian
Top in society realized
The members of minority groups deserve equal rights
These things aren't the New World Order tricking people
There's a block in the morning
They're caught artists
Yes it is Hawaii
To choose as your main enemy the thing you embody
Cuz you're the most familiar with
University of Coronavirus
I know how they think
You know
I know how they
Because Gonzalez University of Colorado Springs
Okay
It's really critical that Alex be able to present people having different politics to him in this kind of fashion
Is there being tricked
Because the audience needs to be reassured that their right
It's really hard to make a coherent argument for a lot of Alex's political positions so his audience probably couldn't handle that
Kind of lifting
And instead of requiring
Them to do that you can create an overpowered Boogeyman who's manipulating everyone who disagrees with them into have
Having the positions that they have
You don't even need to come up with a reason to think they're wrong
Because the truth of your position is Southaven
There's just an evil cabal
Of King Rat
University trick them into thinking that it's great
It's a it's a
Why would I argue with you
If you are coming to me having been trick
By these people with you I have to remember that I
I have a position as well instead of
Just ignoring yours and if I were to do that
Oh boy I would remember that I do not have a very good position at all position is counter to that of
The king rat truth University con artist truth and that's
No good grade
Like I said most of this episode has him talking about this policy analysis Market
Get that.
Doesn't exist
What is a lot of fears about it and one of them is the terrorists
Could bet on their own terrorist Act
That's better
You're the first person I think of that I'm sure
Control
The grill
Physical problems with Alex's suggesting here
The first is that terrorists would not have access to this wedding Market the DARPA hippos
It's be able to go into the DARPA Market
Insider trading
The second problem is that Alex has seemingly suggesting that $100 bets in a very limited betting pool be Luker
Creative enough to be a motive for someone within our government to carry out 9/11
Record Put options
Well that's actually about something else will get a second
But that was his idea to seems incredibly stupid thought
Almost entirely illustrates why
There's already a ton of Futures mark
So you can make much larger put or call options on so if you actually
Or acting with some kind of foreknowledge of a coming terrorist attack you could do it exactly the thing I was already ransack about
Do it in the regular stock market where people would give you lots of money after
Also just as a reminder Alex believes is a matter of
Definitive facts that
The planes in 9/11 remote-controlled at this point
Which I'm sure he would not defend nowadays
Difference.in although I be interested
I'm having
Rogan ask him about it
Yeah that would be fun
So about that like record Put
He's talking about
Conspiracy about insider trading
Regarding United and American Airline
Prior to
I am so there were actually some trading patterns in united in America
Comstock that seemed suspicious
In the days prior
I to the attack has decided just to report that this was people who knew that 9/11 was coming
And they were trying to profit off that for now
What major question had to do with irregular purchases on September 6th
Intapp
The 9/11 commission investigated the actual trades that were made which
Tooted an unusually high low to put Ops
This was the result of quote
A single US based in
Institutional Investor with no conceivable ties to Elkader
Purchasing 95% of the United puts
On September 6th as part of a trading strategy
It also included buying 115000 shares of American on September
Protect
Highly suspicious trading on its face
Yet further investigation has revealed
The trading had no connection to 9/11
So that kind of
Explains that
Right
Additionally a US base
Options trading news letterhead recommended people trade on American in a letter that they sent
Subscribers
On September 9th
Which added to the irregularity of trade volume on September 10th
I have almost everything Alex uses as proof of his
Mercy.
He has the
Appearance of something suspicious
And that's about it
He never takes the time to consider alternative explanations and when information comes out the causes
Conclusion that the question
He ignores
He pretends that he's been right all along when he's just been
Making s*** up
If someone did have foreknowledge of a common terrorist attack there are Financial mechanisms that already exist they could try to
Exploit profit from that knowledge
However
They're likely going to leave some kind of a
Trail and that could be a problem later
Well analyzed now you would
Say that
You would say that but we do have very obvious recent evidence that the
Suggest as long as you're a senator you can do that s*** all day in public and everybody will know it's you and you'll walk
Kuwait's got free with more Millions than you had
There are some issues
Real problems that need to be ironed out and I'm not going to go so far as to say
I hate you get you definitely get in trouble if you did open
Nope but I
Think that if you were a terrorist
If you were terrorist I don't think
And the notion that you could do
That kind of insider trading
Wingstop within this
Proposed policy analysis Market
Is just not
The problem
Mainly I have with the argument is that it would be almost in
Possible
To make it easier to inside trade anywhere other than the current
Stock market
That we have right now
Why would the military make something that would be easier to cheat on then the thing
So bailable to cheat on it's it's
In Subway's if you're looking to
Prophet
Insider information that you may have
It's a redundant
The day before this episode two Democratic senators Ron Wyden
Byron dorgan
Held a press conference leading opposition against the creation of this policy announced
Does Market
This ultimately led to the project being abandoned so
It's important to recognize that Alex only knows about the story because Democrats in Congress spoke out again
And state and the driving force for it not coming into existence
Who is opposition that started in the left-wing political Circle
Right so the devil didn't want to do
Alex should be supported
It's crazy how was like his politics are incoherent
Alex
It just believes that with the 9/11
United and American insider-trading that he believed it happened
That's
Proof
Vet
Like really reinforces his
Conspiracy about this new proposal
We
Alex builds fantasy stories out of his bad information
Bass
He's decided that he's proven the people in the CIA did insider trading on American in the united before 911 do he has approved
Not at all
You have a couple of suspicious fat
But he can point to which he's decided on an explanation for with no other
Has it turns out his explanation was wrong
But he's used that incorrect explanation
Create a background for this new conspiracy
How about the policy analysis
This Market
Because these folks got away with insider trading on 911
Which they didn't they decided to institutionalize that insider trading through this Market
We do they weren't doing
Important economic analysis conspiracies
Sometimes the things he's saying are built on multiple levels of non-existent found a
I think this is an under-appreciated style of how Alex is often wrong he's like
Three levels of deep into being wrong
And that's just acceptable on a show because
The things you make up
Makes up the appeal
To the audience's emotional needs
Yeah he reminds me of what Douglas Adams said about
What's the name of the corporation I can't remember but it is
Is that their superficial design flaws
Make you so angry
That they cover over their fundamental design flaws
So you forget
You're so mad about all the things that they're sitting at you forget why you're you should be mad at
Deeply City
It seems almost like a smokescreen like
He's wrong and so many superficial ways you you're like
Oh well I've got that so you don't even dig deeper to find out how he's running like
Different in some ways that kind of
Describes a lot of the
The public perception of Alex's show
Like there's a lot of like very surface-level things that are
Obviously infuriating
That takes up a lot of the criticism directed towards him
As opposed
To recognizing that there is a internal
Just foundational problem with a thing
Things that he reports and expresses that it basically how he does
That is sometimes missed from
So Alex has a
Clip that he describes for
From Hardball
I don't think this happen
3 months before 9/11
I can't find the actual video this claimed Hardball appearance but I do know that after 9/11
Heart did make appearances of Chris Matthews just got to
He released in January 2001
Call the roadmap for National Security
It was a product of a committee that he co-chaired with Warren Rudman and the
Conclusion that they came to was that we weren't prepared at all for
For the possibility of an attack within the United States clearly wrong haha
Court was very public about his concerns Pryor tonight 11:00 so I don't exclude the possibility that he went on Hardball and just
But I don't believe it all Alex's interpretation of this
Be like if somebody
The CDC was like our not ready for a pandemic
I like that all of them every single life
That's probably proves that they were going to just cause pass out
So Alex has
Earlier we heard him talking about the New World Order
The devil wasn't
Involved
Now get this
He's back in
Devil might be involved
The world
Could come off as kind of metaphorical
It's pretty close
It's interesting though
It's an example of him painting
But he's fighting the literal devil
Also Alex
Give a citation for this in the Bible so I'm going to have to assume that he's referring to Luke chapter 4
Where Jesus is tempted in the wilderness
Verses 5 through 7 say quote
And the devil taking him into a high mountain
Show to him all the kingdoms of the world in a moment of time
And the devil said unto him all this power will I give thee and the glory of them for that is delivered unto me
And to whomsoever I will
Given
If thou therefore it will will a worship me
All Shelbyville
That's all good and well but this is a naive and shallow interpretation of that passage to conclude that the devil actually has
Control evolve
These kingdoms
You have to remember the characters that play here
Number one trait ascribe to the devil
Is that he's a liar
John 8:44 quote when he lies he speaks his native language
For he is a liar and the father of Lies he would do
I believe in the devil controls all these
Alex is buying into the devil's lie that he was using to try to tempt Jesus into worship
Alex is entirely missing
Point of this verse and that misinterpretation seems to actually be kind of
Essential Cornerstone of his worldview because
Outside of that stuff
Jesus seems pretty okay with governments
Frankly
In Alex's
My I feel like
Alex if he were in Jesus's situation would be like
Sweet
I'll take it again devil the devil be like a high I didn't actually have any like
You told me you had it are you telling me that you lied to me what
The devil
That's not something you do but we had a thing man I signed everything in Blood and Shay
Panthers and ironic
Twist
Typically
The Devil is a straight-up
Are you telling me that when I got everything I wished for perhaps I should have been more care
Careful about what it was that it was I was with all the rules of the universe
What was have to tell you what they're doing in advance operating
Please adjust the truth
Please adjust the way you view the world man I really think
It's weird to take the devil at face value
Thing the devil does
Anne
Contacts
The biblical stories
Or anything extra biblical stories
I mean you know that's what's funny about that is that that reminds me more of the f******
Chaos magician who is like
Well you know that the devil is in control over all the Earth and all that stuff in your leg
Wait
Alex is a chaos
Magician probably not for
He's definitely weird map
Custom Calls and gets a bad news from a caller about this DARPA project policy analysis
This Market
Guess what
Cancel that
BBC News
Guaranteed her fault
Parameters and batteries
Embarrassing
An hour doesn't exist anymore
But on the other hand it's even worse
Because the way Alex tries to salvage
Some kind of a meeting out of his show is to protect
The program will be back with
Doubled funding Within
Month
Guarantees
This didn't happen and it goes out of history is just one of them Billy and examples of predictions that Alex has gotten wrong while pretending that is predict
Actions are based off a pattern
That is imaginary enemies engaging in these right 95% of the f****** time
Alex that thing you said was going to happen it's not even close to half
Means it's going to double happen
I guarantee
Cool good work
So although the Galaxy's wrong about you
He continues to be wrong about dr. David Kelly
Only weapons inspector who took his own life
Is it going to take
Figure out
Find out
18 flashes red
Alex kissing anyone
And it stinks like just about every
Getting on right now
Has created a full-on story
Based on nothing
Baseball
Disrespectful a little bit
Bulshit
Alex brings in Michael Johnson.
And they get to talk about the policy analysis
Market
Anything
It will be tough for Alex
Haha
Anyway
A baby say about Pam
Korea
People invest
In this
People you know
Street USA
What
No inside knowledge
When
And where are these
Political assassin
Fascinations on
Are going to occur
Will the Colts lose their life
Time-saving
They have to make a public and now
That's such a bizarre interpretation of this
Never ends up happening
It never was designed to be something for like
Public betting in the intelligence
Value of it
Yeah just random
Yeah
We're taking like a long bats like oh this is a long shot but maybe I'll hit big
That's dumb they clearly don't know what they're talkin about I mean also that's not
Mince words
If this guy was saying something Alex didn't like you do a very disrespectful impression of him
Oh yeah
Abby
Godby idea that he's like okay well the first thing I see here
Is it obviously
Normal people are going to
You bet their life savings on whether or not
Steve pieczenik murders another Aldo Moro you're going to lose the car and then they've got nothing it's going to be like
Like though it's like
Do you understand
What events like if I
Ferdinand
Assassinated it did everybody everybody went broke
Like I'm mediately the markets crashed
There everyone was very bullish on the Ottoman Empire
Yes I think that's a little silly and it sets the tone of like
Well baby you guys aren't really
Discussing things in
In reality
Just Dusty also think
David Kelly with murder
So cold
Suicide
Wichita
Political assassination
The David
Kelly
It's made public
Committee
Lead to the
To the
Tony basket
As a strong insinuations he was murdered to silence him from take a shower Tony Blair
Whatever
I don't really think
Think that it's
Ghetto super hard headed but I think it was straight
Point that I want to drive home
Caring
Hitler orca
Roman emperor in Spanish
Well you know I
Believe that
Ultimate
Project
The first is that no matter what's happening at any point in time and no matter what happened prior Alex will always believe
Leave of the globalist
Becoming so much more open in their treachery
Evil than they were before
It didn't used to be like that did after yesterday they were left
Evil than they are today I just everything crystallized for me last night
I was up for 67,000 our strength
This is to create the appearance of immediacy in the audio
It's taking advantage of their recently bias
This is the same reason that in the present-day Alex called everything that happens the globalist to main attack
On what level is to keep people excited and engage but it also serves another purpose and that's to distract people from the things you've
Recently been wrong about
The other thing I think is illustrated by the Clippers out easily Alec
Alex goes off message
He's trying to play that game was like the globalist a really wild now this time
He forgets that he's not supposed to think the bushes actually in charge
Then he has to come in and remind him that they're supposed
Speed evil cabal and charger thing writes like an actual
Public-facing pirate buddy
Stick to the script
You just forgets his own mythology at times when it starts feeling good two to paint things in a certain way
More exciting to start talking about
Bushes
Pelicula that's a great day today now what's going on
Marion horses always good
I think those are some important things to recognize about Alex at no matter what. Of time you're in
The globalist are really doing it this time
Everything the game has holyshit the worm has turned
The kid the globalists they were at least polite about how yeah I know but now they're just flaunting it in our faces
They would hide it I know you never used to see people spit on the sidewalk I seen all the time cigarettes
So it's a nightmare
Search osantowski
Revealed something that I think is a way into understanding
What is his s*** is all about
They're saying
Korea
North Korea
Pictures of North Korea
Queen
Between the two
It don't know if
Career with
Really
Security
Peninsula
That's really where you see some of the Tendencies of Charles Bukowski
His Wesley paint itself as an anti-globalization research outlet but the larger reality is that
There's kind of anti us
It's all good well Deborah bus criticisms of the u.s. in our foreign policy
Past and present but it's another thing to make
2:02 other countries that are doing fairly similar things or
Ghetto
Worse
Princeton's Google research was a major player in spreading Russian base propaganda both in the spirit
Pro-assad narrative
Regarding Russia's involvement in Syria
Any terms of the flow of every conspiracy involving Hillary in the 2016
They do basically the same kind of thing Alex does which is
To say that they take Outlander stuff and then give it a slick presentation that allows
Is it to be more easily disseminated
Do unto us by
Acting viewers
They give the appearance of credibility and research to conspiracy
To give you some kind of idea of the content they're putting out
A 2020 State Department investigation found quote
Global Research published or Republic's seven authors attributed by Facebook
Default online
Personas
Created by the main directorate of the general staff of the Armed Forces of the Russian Federation
Popularly known as the GRE
That's kind of sloppy nonsense that's going on there
That's set lippo published 7
Authors who didn't exist
A total of over
180 articles
By these fake
People in intelligence assets
Using fake name
Wow
That's a win-win
Yeah the Russian ski recently was making the rounds blaming the United States for Russia invade
Dating Ukraine because
Kind of is constant drumbeat right
Beyond that Global Research had some really incredibly shity content over
For the years
Recently in 2020 they published an article titled China's coronavirus a shocking update that the virus originated in
In the United States
As article was tweeted out by the spokesperson for the
The Chinese foreign Ministry
Hello it's not based on any actual true information to became part of a large
PR campaign in
Conspiracy theory against the United Way
Course there is a little bit of a caveat that should be given is
In the larger picture of Global Research
Shoes website they also do cover a lot of stories that relate to countries are often ignored by what you might call
Mainstream media but
There's a lot of other independent Outlets that do that too and don't also traffic and rank information misinformation
Website associate only produced in a such a
Clear slant
Even if they do have coverage of issues relating to things like
In Old Latin American countries that are often
It's pretty hard
The trust of the reporting that you're getting is worth it
He's probably look somewhere else that's what I would say
But I do think it's worth like
Bring up there like you know there are some things
They might they might raise some issues sure like
Are worse
Knowing about
But you get better information about those issues elsewhere
Overall Chelsea houska Global Research Ark
Conspiracy Peddlers that are in the business of Christian anti-gay and anti-western perspective
As a anti-globalization message
That's the answer to sleight-of-hand
Engaged in here
If I have to guess why cha Sadowski is gunning for us anymore
This is why
But he and Alex appeared to be on the same page and I love you overlap but they're actually polar up
Buc-ee's
Strongly opposed to the West fetishizes
Americana
Nor does he feel that American loser is a good acceptable history
Perhaps not probably not
I think it's a fundamental difference between them and maybe it took years for them to figure that out right
Cuz he's either pretty
He's a fixture in a number of like
Later years of alopecia
Sooner or later they got to the point where Alex is like man I love America and he's like you know America's evil right needs like
Start talking a little bit about conspiracies about saddam's kids
Joann Dobbs
Sansa surrounding matin
Turn her in there
Regardless
Where's
White these guys out
Bissell good fun but Alex just making
Stop out of his imagination to try to justify the incorrect conclusion that The Killing
Samsung
Songs with lyrics
Acting with the Goodwill will make
He said that they only sent in helicopters and tanks so they would be able to
The speaker these bodies enough to be able to
The claim that they were saddam's son
Leaving aside the subsequent text test
Confirm that they were Saddam Sons
I know it's a totally wrong
Imagine a scenario where some troops
Just went in to try to capture or kill them and they ended up in a bad
Situation
Let's imagine that maybe a couple of soldiers were killed in that saddam's kids got away
In that situation you can easily come up with how that would be covered in Alex's
The show
You have the option
I'm saying that the military should have sent in tanks and helicopters in
Because they secretly wanted saddam's kids to get away
Belarus
That's the way
There are other options
Alex could go with it but the point is that with this narrative
He has you coming and going
There isn't an option that he can't turn into some kind of
Conspiracy so you kind of just have to ignore his point
It's not really that weird that they sent in tanks and helicopters and Alex doesn't even actually think
He just knows that pretending that he thinks it's weird Works to strengthen the
Conspiracy that he has
The kids are really dead so Q goes with
It's convenient
Yeah yeah yeah
It is it's always great to listen to and then bang your head against the wall when
People are making bad faith argument that they don't even believe
True true but that's our job
That's why I replacement walls for you
Over there
That's true
Do you have like a psionic scream like a banshee
I am essentially Banshee from Mortal Kombat from the 29th
Dusky talking about his
Both headlights
A little different than Alex's but maybe there's some
Some similarities
I think it's it's
Pittston
Which is
Actually misleading
Keep up the cost
The headlines on the
And if you want to know the truth you have to read between the lines
Between the headlines
Go to the official.
You have to go on the internet
Plates
Information
Witches
Headlines
Really
Make a real story
It's very supposed
Absolutely
So I agree with trust Dusky sort of
Think that he's in the right place to be getting that advice
I get four words as headline Central
I do take issue with it will he probably means by reading between the lines
Speakers for Alex that just means making
Things up
Which I don't think it's a good part of the news
Consumption
Also that story Alex is telling us
Completely bizarre
Let me track his line of thought and then explain what I think is probably going okay okay thank you
Tom Ridge and Homeland Security were going to erase all livestock.
Call a big headline about it
Now in reality this is a campaign that would
Sport domestic
Beef production but these globalist
I knew that Alex Community were so against
The New World Order
But if they reported it in headlines about how is bypassing a tracing all the livestock
Has friends would be against and they lead a charge to oppose the plan
Globalist want
Begin with they wanted this good thing to be defeated right as opposed to just not
Proposing it or something I don't know if I understand correctly
Play Alex is not realizing that what he's saying is that we are so f******
Unpredictable they know that if they put a headline on something we won't read the article and we'll just get mad and mediate
Yep and he's a little bit saying that like
Decatur dad supposed to be like
Simple dumb
Angela Keys it will be like are those Stars
Can we fight back
So here's what I'm pretty sure actually happened
In the executive order that Bush signed forming the Department of Homeland Security what are the responsibilities of the office was to
To quote coordinate efforts to protect United States livestock Agriculture and systems for the provision of water and food
For human use
And consumption from terrorist attacks
Because I was only read Sensational ass right wing
Conspiracy blogs
Teresa headline that reported that is the only answer
Security Department announcing the Third
Tagged tagged spray salt
So that was the conclusion that he came to that looking
Maybe deeper into the subject
How is repeated this narrative to his audience
Canceled ride rally opposition to the protection of Our Lives
From the threat
Disruption
Start at some point
Alex must have realized that he was wrong so in order to save face and not have to admit that he's wrong and he's an idiot
He pretended that the initial headlining Redwood
Actually a globalist blocked
He was opposed to the new world orders they plan to that headline so we would have posed a good thing and further
The globalist master plan
Rye Rye
There's something so on brand about this
Like Alex can admit that he's wrong about something but only when the reason he's wrong is that because there was a conspiracy against
It's time to make it wrong
But he doesn't realize that this makes him even more of a bumbling dope in the story
It does
Instead of him just well if you're
Somebody who reacted
To quickly and who Adam Andrew just
Threw something out there without thinking about my knee-jerk idiot
He's not only a knee-jerk idiot
But he's implied that his pattern of behavior is so come
Unpredictable
One-dimensional taken advantage of
With zero effort on their part whatsoever
Instead of him making a mistake this is him being exploited because the only thing he does is make list
The show does go on in Tuskegee is on for the rest of the show that take some calls
Derailed by a caller who's like
Talking about how we always talk about what the United States is doing overseas we know that's bad
You give it up
For the people who were trying to
Change things here
Keep sort of
Hinting
I think he's talking about like
Militia
Right wing
Terrorist types
I think that's what he's talking about
Because he's being really insinuating and Alex is really weird about it as opposed to getting mad at him
I think Alex can tell that's what
He's signaling to I would have clips of it gets very bizarre but it goes on for f****** Everest
Never really materialized into anything
You got to care about what the people here are doing okay
See you got to care about okay
See
Kman
It's not before
It goes on
Quite a while
So we jump to the 30th
And Alex had trazodone ski on
And he's got another exciting guests also with a name
That's fun
On this episode
Call governor
Point
Government
300 sounds
The recall
Thought you to move
Arnold
Or will it be
Be one of them working
Members
And that's why everybody
More than boss
New World Order
What streets are
Name is Howard Telugu
Howard klug
Spoiler alert
So yeah we got the guy who started a group that was gathering signatures Davis recall
Cancel great Bazaar Gastonia see these two days a very excited
So the first thing that jumps out to me in this clip is that Alex
Just described
Every place he doesn't like basically as where the globalist are testing their system
And where he live
Sure but he has problems with us
Like
Beast doesn't like a California New York
This is a little weird since it also includes Boston
Which isn't to say
Also Texas which as you pointed out
Where he lives at is a Democrat area
Massachusetts at Austin it's
Texas in Boston
True
So that might have slipped him up that does happen
To me that what Alex's driving at is that every state
Including Boston is a globalist testing
In the present-day Alex's move that largely to other
Typically China is a globalist they have a more repressive government
Can use the image of their government
Globalist have planned
For them
Periodically whenever someone catches on and
Right-wing media circles he'll add other countries to the list
The places that are global
Most testing grounds
For instance when the trucker convoys were going on in Canada
Turned out to be like at the biggest place where globalist are testing things out
Austin Grant and that's why they were there
I went there were a lot of stories about covid protest in Australia it just so happened that that was actually wear
Boasted their trial runs of to urinate a lot of Trials going on
Everywhere in fact it's almost
Impossible to imagine how they organize everything
I don't know what that is but I seen commercials on Youtube videos
So this is just another feature of Alex's presentation
My profound deep and meaningful but it's actually the same talking
Website in 2003
He sang with these Global if they're trying things out and states
And also Boston
So I want to take a moment to point out that this is exactly what Alex believe should be happening
According to his version of federalism the state they're basically Laboratories were policies can be tested
See if they work
That's a huge part of a Thrust behind states rights
The idea that if a state wants to experiment with a particular policy the people can vote to do that more easily than they could
If it were something it was being done on a federal level
And if there's something that goes really wrong with the policy it's
Confined to that state doesn't involve everybody in the country
The results could then be evaluated another States be able to decide if they wanted to try it out to
If I were to pretend that I was his enemies were real
How do you talk about something other than
Just like leaning policies like welfare and anti-discrimination laws
His point is still self-defeating
According to his own philosophy these states should be
Testing out policy so people can see if they work
Like for example how Colorado legalized weed and then in the past six years they brought in more than 1.6 billion additional
Revenue
Millions of which have gone to affordable housing dealing with the opioid crisis
And improving schools both from a construction program standpoint
Alex believe that the states
Should be the place where political experiments
Except when those experimental things
50 doesn't like
And then it's like
Am doing a testing ground
And it is a good place to test things
But if they are safe like another state is testing something that you don't want
Then you should orchestrated Echo
Avon campaign to overthrow the Supreme Court
Take it over and then insist upon
Controlling things everywhere that you don't have
Have control over much like
Making tax revenues from weed
That seems to have work
It does seem to have
Alex's story that he missed
Yesterday
I'll tell you he doesn't get in-depth on it
But he's pretty gross
Diverted off of the other
Go to New York
Larry maker saying
Orientation
Wow hoboy
That's weird that is very weird
So this is about Harvey Milk High School which was introduced in 2002 as an alternative school that will cater to lgbtq
Do students in New York City
Who are having difficulties in their Public School settings do to thing
Things like Bully
I think it's kind of natural to have some initial reaction to something like this instinct
Maybe this isn't the right solution to the problem
Like if bullying is the problem then
Stopping the bullying seems like
Nothing to do
Opposed to creating a new public
School for the students to go to but that's
Not as easy as we would like it to be bullying is
Hard
Yes
So what if we did that point
The thing where we just moved you out of this
Situation sure I mean it's a complicated conversations
I don't
Yeah I don't know
According to the American educational research Association is many as one in three lgbtq
Cqi school students and sup dropping out while the national average is a 8% dropout rate
Call lgbtq students report that their main reason for dropping out of high school is
Constant bullying and harassment
Another student
So this does seem like
A possible solution
Into this problem
In God's name could they do this school is not about
Sex that's why whenever we have all male schools and all female schools
That is okay
But if there are different orientations that maybe don't apply in those situations that the evil actually you know
What I don't
Know if I've ever heard Alex talk about whether or not
Mail-order all-female schools are okay
I think you would be totally fine with it if their privates
But I don't know what you would think if it was
I don't know if you would actually make it
Distinction between the two Wendy's ranting about something
Play a different conversation between the two are the only reason why
Has any relevant conversation around it at all because of the public
Wright brothers
You know
I mean
Maybe we have
To stop listening to what conservatives are saying about schools whenever they're like
Seether teacher
Stop that's not reading writing and arithmetic
And really understand that I think they're actually angry at the reading the writing in the arithmetic history
So I looked into it they don't have New World Order study and Harvey Milk
I looked into this and it seems like the people who go there and work at Harvey Milk are
Plastic about how important
The school is and how it's a really positive learning
Environment
According to the New York public
Quickschools information on their website they only had 59 in Rhodes
Students this past year
Imitator going back to
The 2016 the highest of any years 70
Seems like if this is a special occasion where people who be having a terrible time in high school can learn in peace
I don't know really what the harbor
It's not like they have any different curriculum than any other
School Board of Regents
Also important Point here is that the school is not exclusively lgbtq anybody
We can attempt it's not it's not restricted make a restricted
So just a very basic standpoint
Again Alex shouldn't have a problem with it
That's because it's the New York State Board of Education deciding to do this
Experimental program
To see how it works
Alright
And it's still open
There have been other attempts to create high schools that are generally geared towards lgbtq students but they
Not had as much success
There was one plant here in Chicago back in 2008 but that fell through before it got off the ground
School Atlanta open 220si
16 but it closed in
In 2018 due to dropping a roll
But that one is interesting
Because it was a private
Right so that
You know sort of a different dynamic
Spell through whereas the Harvey Milk school has has indoor
You know is that he's such a great
Like
Point of view into the real ID
The real ideology behind there is it
It's not listen
If you didn't want your kid every argument every conservatives ever made is like I don't want my kids learning
With
Lgbtq students
I don't want them in that situation learning things that they couldn't
Okay fine
So let's make a school for lgbtq
Good students
And then your kids won't have to deal with it
No I want that school f****** close to right I want it all taken from that hypothetical
Coolsense I agree with you that is very revealing although I do think
Away from even engaging with the thought initially
Of like
Let's put
Them in quotes
Call somewhere else
Because when you end up with segregated schools
I'm not talking about
Incase
That is a bridgeworth I'm using this is an example of
My job to be over clarify sometime
But it is it is the case
About wanting to learn about lgbtq
Issues with your
No no it's that they
Yeah
You don't want them you don't want them
There you got it
Alex is really really excited about this kalugin
Coming on
Kalugin
Do you have Howard
Collusion
After crying
One of them
I'm one of the top
Yasso Michael Savage's one of the Democrat top operatives so funny how we jump back and forth between this time
. because
Every single time I'm always like
Michael Savage is a top Democrat out with no I remember now I remember where we are in the storyline of caught-up eunos
Not a legend of the Patriot community and has been for years nobody has a it's a long-haired beatnik who's trying to
She'll for neocon
The second season of Better Call Saul
He's basically socialism
So Alex touches back on this policy Market
The policy analysis Market
Story and man day after
He told him
To his face
Auto Show
Not happening
But it still happen
Okay
Good morning
My wife did
One of my
Boys dead
How to talk to
It was
On where the next
Ron
Market
Ruined
Almost everything Alex is saying what the story is completely wrong
The factual stuff is just in Roofing details to make this more interesting as a
The conspiracy
And things like
Secret passwords just had to do with
Like people who were investing would have accounts
With that scary
This is a dead story because of the market that was proposed didn't actually happen
These two Democratic senators push back on it the project was abandoned
Because that's the case Alex needs to kind of shift
The tone of his coverage
That's why the story is now that the market has existed for a while secretly a
Still does exist
But they're just trying to make it public
The Publican unveiling of the program failed but the program still totally existence Secret
And Alex
Definitely proved that he has the documents and it's in the paper so you know it
Honestly it's basically just your office March Madness pool but blown up you know I'll literally tomorrow
This is a pretty Savvy because if you didn't
Do this his narrative would actually be tied to reality
The program will be done for in that fat
Nothing else so it's really see here that the government actually work the way he claims he wants it
Is the conspiracy dead at
So if you want to get mileage out of this wood you've already spent a day trying to get up you have to change the story of James
Yeah and what's important is not that you theoretically quote-unquote one
You were against this policy now this probably seashell
You're not going to go and be like hey we did it
Yuan
Reinforce
Thing that you and your listeners
Did something
Is way worse
Then telling them that you are doing
I bet you were continuing to do something
And that nothing you ever do will end in a victory
But we're always going to keep going
So Alex
It over there sometimes cute moments
Might be a little bit
Michael
Coffee
Mike Walker
By the way
Okay
Just drink your f****** a dozen everything cuz it has
To be everything I'm pretty sure they also already
Xgolf
Also 15 month olds are definitely not prescribed brutal
It hasn't been approved for people under 6 though in some extreme cases it can be prescribed to people
Over the age of three but that's going to be pretty rare
Hope it's really funny to see how it's making a big deal about a dangerous of a drug coffee is and who needs to quit considering Israel
Alcohol abuse
Problem with stimulants
In recent days
Okay
On the stove
Who's next clip
I think it's sort of tracking
An underage
Wait hold on
Am I am I wrong in thinking that one of his products is
Coffee
Yeah he sells the wakeupamerica blend the Chiapas Farmers yeah
Product has a s*** ton of caffeine in it as a bunch of weird like pseudo stimulants sure the ones
You up
Brain Force Ultra
Brought you back before you read between timeline trying to get off coffee
But in my head I'm like
Wait aren't you about to do an ad for coffee
I'm not sure if he's selling coffee at this point yet but I
It was before the subject I think so
Before he gets all of his line of bull caffeine and other associated
The like
Yeah yeah
Oh well
Also Alex
Does not limit himself to coffee
And this
Sort of a part of a path
That we've been going down
And that is
You know it started very exciting
No because we met someone named Dan from Illinois
Turns out he calls in
All the f****** time
More and more out of love with him
How you doing
Mister Ed the way you're saying a minute ago it's a mess
Sabri definition of Acts
The bull Behavior
What
Wait what
That sounds fairly close to his modern ship
Does he think that their tea
Teaching
Yes okay
Yeah that's what I thought
And I couldn't
I couldn't believe for a real second somebody would do that
No teaching gay stuff
Over over over the pants
Little girls
Illinois Illinois Howard
Collusion
And I got to say I was looking at everything I can tell
He seems like he's just your kind of run-of-the-mill shady lawyer
Who was also involved in recalling the governor and then he also had a failed Senate run
He's the chair of the
Recall Gray Davis committee though it should be noted that another member of that committee
Was Notorious pollster Frank Luntz
Who who Alex is currently obsessed with suggest
Things in a relationship with Kevin McCarthy
They live together
Weird also dipping around inclusions history 100 interesting tidbit
2004 parently he was heading a campaign to block theaters
From playing Michael Moore's movie Fahrenheit 911
There's a very impassioned
Stop it that I found calling out clued-in and supporting Michael Moore
From that article quote
Colombians arm-twisting organization move America forward his called Moore's film a recruiting video for LK
In other words more is a terrorist
It should be more than obvious by now that what far right-wingers like a loogie in Ashcroft want done to those they
They considered
Or for that matter those who disagree with bush
The writer of that op-ed
Alex is a longtime writer and one-time webmaster curtain MO
Rating on his own blog
Yep what
No another fun fact
Bylines on globalresearch.ca from 2004 all the way up to the present day
Happening with memo after this interview
Kurt Nimmo wrote an article Love by Sting
Collusion
As a free speech
Unreal is happening
Clue game comes in and they have real fun
Jocularity
Open border promoting
Are we going to get
Or we going to get
Winning
Or will they Michael
Howard
Thank you very much
To be with you today
Breaking down
About me I'm an attorney
Really cute of the two of them were getting along pretty well and have this fake laugh because they would absolutely f****** hate each other if they knew it
What the other one stood for
Case-in-point Kluge and is super in favor of the war in Iraq
In 2005 he was so into in the enduring war that he began organization called moving America forward
Along with Sal Russo
A political Communications and strategy guy was also a key member of the recall Gray Davis committee
The new group was meant
To quote report the good news on operation Iraqi Freedom you're not hearing from the
The old line news media
This led to an embarrassing
F****** where collusion posted a picture of a quiet
Street and claimed that it was Baghdad
You're trying to make the argument that the war was super effective and Brian going great
It also turned out that this was a straw
Street in Istanbul
Google in a classic right-wing move would go on to blame a staffer for the f***
Can't believe it how many goddamn people
Position to free speech of David Michael Moore and also
Party
By starting a bus tour called the
Tea party Express
Switch tried to
Get Doom candidates elected in the raise a bunch of money that got funnel two organizations run by caloocan
And his longtime collaborator Rousseau
Yeah that's the waited
Steal the face mask for the Tea Party Express with a radio host named Mark Williams
Or at least it was
Until he had some controversy about a racist letter that he posted on his website
Actually that's not totally accurate
He didn't end up stepping down from the
Party Express
The national tea party Federation said that.
Tea party Express needed the fire Williams for the
Clearly racist letter and they refused to
So the national
Expelled them from the formal
Wow when did they let him back in
Super letter was written from the perspective of freed and slave person
No a ham Lincoln
Excuse me sir excuse me
I'm going to read you a little bit about God no quote
Mister Lincoln you are the greatest racist ever
We had a great gig
Okay alright squares
Room & Board all of our decisions made by Massa in the house
We coloreds have taken a vote and decided that we don't cotton
Into the whole emancipation thing
Freedom means having to work for real think for ourselves and take consequences along with the rewards
That's just
Far too much to ask of us colored people and we demand that it's
Stop
Yeah
Holyshit
Insane
That is
Bonkers
Yep that's bad stuff
And this is the dude that Kluge and was willing to go to bed for so that's
Also in response to be proposed Ground Zero mosque this guy Williams said that it would be quote
For the worship of the
The terrorist monkey god
Which apparently also wasn't enough for him by to get in trouble with Tea Party Express
Anyway the point is the klujian loves the Iraq War hates free speech and was an active part of trying to Krypton the Tea Party into way there
Really serve to worsen the parts of
The community that were an embarrassment in the eyes of the larger population
Probably hurt a number their candidates at
The poles and Alex should really f******
I hate this dude
Right I mean long-term though that was the right move
Well
Sure.
I mean there
It's sort of an accidental victory
Galaxy W stands for a lot of things that Alex Indiana should be very much against
All he knows about him is that he's against
Spray Davis and souls like yeah f*** yeah I'm into this
It is so much like that
There are so many false equivalencies that we can make
Between America and Russia is all that s*** right there but the one thing that is always true is that
There are weirdo right wing
Assholes who are going to be like
Listen
Our government is not hurting it
I promise you everything's great
No I don't know are they paying me know that's the weirdest part of this I'm doing it for free
But not them who should be paid
For you
Zoo
Alex gets to espousing some ideas
About Gray Davis and electoral politics in California and this is really incoherent
But you asked
Now that were true at all
Be possible for Gray Davis
To be one of them
Four governors in the history of the United States
Too Faced a recall election
Hoody at all these illegal vote
Rigging elections why did Erie get so you'll be one of only two governors
In US history to actually be recalled
It seems like a really dumb use a power that I was pretending that he wield
Play Just Because Alex's position isn't sincere it's just a xenophobia and racism you just don't understand
Yeah you're right you're right
You're right I'm saying the collusion and his friends were decision-makers in term for the Tea Party
But it turns out in the long run you're right
You're not
Colludium
He's got some some
F****** weird ideas about America
Sprint Center
First time
North Dakota
You know what I hate that man I hate all these Democratic Coastal Elites looking down on flyover country
California Liberals are
These upstanding right-wing Patriots standing up and caring about what happens in middle of America
Say that
No no no they wouldn't just discount
Massive
Amount of geography based solely upon their own
Bigotries in lack of care that would be silly Coastal Elite
Yeah
Dakota
Count I mean there aren't and it's not like there any Coastal least in the Republican party you would have to go from what
Beyond like
Say one of those schools on the
East Coast like Harvard or Yale or something like that
Or one of the schools on the west coast like Stanford or that you know
We don't have a lot of Republicans from those schools right.
Dumb
April
So
Alex also is a little
Dumb
Every governor
Including Ronald Reagan
Jerry Brown
Has had a recall app
Begun
Not one
Has it ever got
Because never
The brink of bacon
I'm not familiar enough with that
You know what I hate
Are you going to be
Democrat liberal socialist have no idea what the Constitution actually says
Stampy's Dum Dum left-wingers out here spouting nonsense about what they think the country is about
Patriots like Alex you like live and breathe our country's founding
Honest sincere note according to the Constitution you cannot recall people elected to Federal position
Houdini
Possible for the people of Arizona to recall McCain without first getting an amendment passed
That would come
Completely overhaul election rules on a national level
Alex has no idea what he's talking about
Just throwing out whatever bulshit he wants
How to make the show interesting even if it violates the
F****** c*** pretty close though
I know you think that just cuz they're more steps than he assumed
Means that he's wrong but they ain't he think you can still be pretty close to Morse not it's not more steps
You have to get a national accounts
The distance between those steps you could not make
Yeah we're going to recall this Center
Alright
All right we got to get
McCade okay so let's get let's get him out of there let's do a recall no we can't do that cuz it causes you to remember that
Well how do we change that you want to change the Constitution is how we will of the Constitution
Whatever you need to
You can
I just decided I don't even know what to say
He loves the Constitution wanted
So this
Recall is going
Went down right
It's at the way it's structured as there is one election
That's going to happen
Things on the ballot
One is should Greg Davis be recalled
As if so which of these people should replace
So if the fur
First measure passes
Then the second question will come
Going to play if it doesn't
Then Gray Davis taisen.
Little bit about
In the race
It might surprise you
Leah
And he had
Division
For the recall
Provided
Significant
The job
However I do
Arnold Schwarzenegger
About that prediction that didn't run also we do for Matt Drudge
That Isis was named as a joke
That's how they close
What's are playing or something it's weird how they do that
Run
Call election
Because of
Suspicions and accusations that were made about his early organization
Over the recall campaign
Talking about situations
He funded early effort
Recall going
For himself to be able to run
I was a little bit of hot water and so he withdrew from the race
Because that definitely was
Is collusion here himself is saying
Of course the volunteer effort would have no effect if it weren't for this guy's always know that does sound
His prediction clue games is that I said I was going to run
Schwarzenegger is not
Wrong on two
Navigate to the idea about Savage
Michael Savage of the Savage independent
Lugia
Weiner
Running
Wouldn't
The more conservative
Ram
I like how you can be
Almost patronizing
And wrong and patronizing and right in the same clip yeah that's nice
And also just have a clear like I do enjoy it when guests
Clearly don't know anything about the narratives Alex is trying to build an accidentally completely deflate
Silly
You're pushing as like a legitimate
Possibility I hate you need to be worried about because it's a globalist plan right at sea
It is it is always fun whenever people are like
Unaware of their responsibilities
Either roll
Everybody is always aware like all the good Alex guess they're like
Yes absolutely
And here's what I have that you know that
Yes and all the way
But every time somebody is like no we're having
Obviously Michael Savage's and going to run
That's silly
Only a fool would believe that
What kind of show would have something like that all caps
To have some sort of Nefarious purpose behind
Suggestion
To this interview Tidings of a coming recall election
Tower and
Billy shears
Let me hear
Okay
So I didn't have the other lyrics but
I do think he goes by Billy shears
But he is a guy who has a radio show and Alex
Is a guest on it sometime
This is a little quid pro quo sure
The guy who
Boring AM radio.
You'll shoot the s*** for a little while with Alex on his show and then go back to his own
Hometown
Cast out of 100
Torch
Or whatever that radio stations blowtorch
All right but
Meaningless
Let's just talk about how great they are another break all the stories in the world
And some calls
Did you get this one called I think it's fascinating
And
Woodplay
All of it
But it
Its pretty long and there's also part of it the kind of
VR around and
It's it's
Circuitous
But the beginning of this call is essentially this guy saying like hey
Alex
I wanted to I wanted to bring this up to you
I think
That if you actually engaged with
Some of the
Material is being put out by left-leaning folks
And a lot of socialist organization
They're actually complaining about a lot of the same stuff you are right
Analysis responses basically like yeah
Oh that's not actually true
Go to break
Come back now sexually goes back to this guy
All right I just don't think Alex can handle
This kind of
A conversation nowhere2go with
Razors Edge
Publications that I read
Dressed up their schemes for
Destroying the Constitution the Bill of Rights
Punching I sent the warmers for Empire
The name of it
People like Irving kristol
I need the address
Ciar opportunist
To become anti,
Yeah that's that is that is really telling
The caller actually has exactly Alex's number
That is the point that he's making is Irving kristol
Did involve himself
In some trotskyite
Thought before ending up
Beginning the
New York
Conservative ideology
And because the sounds like this
What does not characterize the entirety of
Did this
This whole philosophy that you are
You're anything in this Library that's not defining of the neocon
This one
This one detail you can
Extrapolate out
Insinuates that you just can't see past the Paradigm that I
Can see I mean I I heard the big moment happen whenever
He was like
You realize that there
Dressing this all up in the
Guys of anti-communism
And Alex cut him off immediately because all I heard was him being like
Yeah that's what the virtues have been trying to do they know you're you're right
That's what we're doing but I'm not going to say that's what we're doing. Because that's what the neocon
Against
Total eclipse
Yep by
So we get another call and that's actual do is actually far more
2 mi
Infowars
My car here
Petition
People
Won't
Turn off
I had mine
Sticker
And then
Now here in College Station
You are what your about
Yeah probably
Homeland Security
It's so obvious
Back that is almost a
Parody
Is
Absurd
Somebody calling in with the pettiest of nonsense and meaningless
Vandalism let's save to be very generous
And it's a
Talking conspiracy that involves the department of the federal government
You got it
No the other day somebody stole my bike and the reason is obviously because Pam was shut down
20 years ago
That was the whole idea by
So they had to get my bikes
Damn brutal
What
I just
Amazing way to
Really depressing
What's that about
Well
I just had a birthday
Yeah and you
Am having a birthday
That right age is maybe on our minds
Astro
I don't know how to break this to you
Republic
Thriftbooks.com
On the year 4/8 but backed up
A basic question I have to leave it to us are you
Station Liberty Lobby website
Great work
Spin-off
Verizon
Goddamn
It's so wild
Just have a reminder that Alex's
22 you ever do you ever like everytime you go back and you look at like
If they if you ever show you like a 1950s High School yearbook and you start look
Looking through it you're like
These people are 45
There's no way people look
This old at this age right or you watch Saved by the Bell
That him
The words I'm 29 coming out of that house
Absurd unacceptable
Started out he was
Young and no one ever was like look at this
Larry David looked old one
Alex Azar
45 this clips
Always
I think a big part of it is that you like
He sounds
Weary
A little bit
These things that are so
Antiquated that you guys got to be a grandpa
And he's he is doing a Limbaugh voice
He's still doing a Limbaugh voice at this time so he's 29 and he
Actively trying to sound older
Or is that Alex is aware of the Liberty Lobby and that he's into them
That's because Neo-Nazi and white nationalist Willis carto started the Liberty lobby as an effort to sway public opinion against Jews
This is an actual quote from a letter that car do route
Hitler's defeat was the defeat of Europe
Band of America
How could we have been so blind
And the blame it's me
Must be laid at the door of the international Jews
It was their propaganda lies and demands which blind at the Westwood Germany was doing
If Satan himself with all of his superhuman diabolical Ingenuity at his command
Permanent disintegration enforced for the destruction of the nation
He could have done no better than to invent the Jews
I could not believe that Paul Joseph Watson
Political activism included starting the youth for Wallace organization to support the present
Central route of segregation is George Wallace
His group eventually became the National Youth Alliance which would end up splintering at the different organizations one of which being the national
Led by William Luther Pierce who is a straight-up Neo-Nazi in the author of the Turner Diaries
Which is considered more or less the essential text of the modern militia whites
Supremacist community
Pierce's Mentor while in the National Youth Alliance coincidentally was the fashion
Founding member of the John Birch Society
Reveal Opie Oliver
So this is all fun but this is the intellectual tradition that Alex celebrate
And he come
Songs from klusterfuk of white supremacists and Nazis
The group name desperate to mask their true character with the appearance
The Patriots
It's important to remember that
Sometimes when
There's some goofy dumb bulshit that Alex is coming into an
When we have in the present-day these reminders that people like Paul's use employees
Harbor the same sorts
The feelings and express them sometimes in moments of
Looseness
Call me it's it makes total sense because the people wear all of their information comes
From the people who are
The forefathers of them in
This
I guess if you want to call it information
They were white
Supremacists and Nazis
Yep
No they are
Welsummer
Deceased
They were you
Get that bad taste out of your mouth
In perhaps the worst
Possible way
Big picture
Already
You heard
No
It freaks them out
What a sales pitch wow
Can't wait to get that
Throw up
Or if I drive you mad
African laughing uncontrollably walking the streets
When you see this video
And if you do not show someone else 7 days you will die
911 road to tyranny of the original ring that the original ring
Said really tight Bhai pocket product
I got it I might be
If you
Listen to knowledge fight you know
What happens to you when you listen to me you will s*** your pain will leave all of your bowels
Rollable diarrhea
It's good to put the pieces together
Hey I mean look spiritually speaking I think I've watched some of Alex's film so they do make me
Are these true
Literally speaking
Seems a little
He's a little silly really I did find myself laughing a lot
True because you took us nine hours straight
So we come to the end of this 2003 adventure and I think it was a
A little bit of a reprieve from tantastic
But you still see shades of stuff there then I'll with a branding of this lgbtq
Did you friendly School in New York
Something adjacent to pedophilia
I'm see that like being echoed in the present-day you see
Alex being really down with a outlet run by Nazis
Yeah there are these These are reverberations of
Very similar things
Present day
The bomber
Well
I mean when you when you think of it in terms of like
These are
Gigantic reactions
Two things like what word
Experiencing right now
Is the culmination of the
Organic reaction
Into
Abortion in 1970
You know like this
This is all
A momentous
It's just Jake
Huge wave
And you can't just stand in front of it not one person can you like get in the way
Ethel we're going to see what happens whenever the wave goes the other direction
Like what they are doing to us
He's going to have
Massive
Active results
That are going to take time you know
You don't know what they're going to be
Some
Sure
Big
Well we'll see how that plays out of the plays out but I will check back in with Alexandra next episode
See you maybe if he's disowned Paul private contractor
Distance himself from us for years now you know what this is on him
Maybe maybe
Well
That would be the
Status quo
So I will be back Jordan but until then we've website
Go to bed Jordan
I hope you all have a dream
What the sex robe
Thanks for holding
Alexandra Thurston color