Important
Pray I have a great respect for this knowledge B knowledge
Need money
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Around a little bit of Alex
Jordan
My bright spot today Jordan is of course the dream creamy summer which is a handful of
Non-Stop
I've stopped a little bit
It's been pretty good I got to say though.
Everything has been
Good ice cream
But I'm looking for something going to blow my mind or be like this sucks absolutely
You know I think I'm somebody was a bit of a traditionalist sometimes
Y'all having some of these non-dairy options
Okay yeah so bars the Greek yogurt
I'd like me was a stick-in-the-mud would be like
This is not the ice cream I know true
Great Define
There's a big sister
I don't know I I wish that I had something to report is like
This is
This is fantastic thing about the Munsters and the Celtics
Is that you can really f****** a mustard or a seltzer
True
To f****** an ice cream I don't I don't agree with that at all I don't know
Pretty good I don't know I think he could have some real
Lavender ice ice cream shoving up yours I don't have a problem with lavender.
Lavender ice cream you can have some flavor problems and maybe if it's lavender for you then
So be it is
Yeah I don't know I think you can also just have
Poorly made
Stuff to
We'll see we'll see what
But you can
Find pictures
Instagram which is kind of
A problem because I have to send you pictures of the ice cream that I'm eating it's even more
No it's even more ridiculous than that because you send them to me because of the way that I have the account setup
I don't have it on my phone so that I have to
Email the pictures to my own email address in order to put it
They're always bad there's a lot of steps here that are unnecessary where we not going to change anything about it
I am going to start giving you actually like
A little bit of a synopsis of how I feel about it
Now it just like you covered up with a caption
The dreamy creamy summer hat
Yeah we're going to change that whatnot or horrible process
What about you
My bright spot Dan is for the 1st
First time in 20 years
After having been put on my Partners insurance
I went to the doctor
First time at 20 years old
That's a little much
I am not the most regular of
Medical attendees
Yeah good at it I'm not good at merely through the paperwork
A little bit older I think it becomes far more important
That you
Seems like regular appearances
Doing good doing good twenty years has not hurt me
All of my habits you said we're a perfect to continue
At the rate that I'm going back at all yeah I feel like everyone smoking again
Wild wild listens is like great blood pressure
Just mellow the absolutely perfect
120 over 80 over 80
Stop
Good
Perfect did you go to Trump's doctor
I don't mean to cast aspersions okay okay so under an overpass or over in a
Overpass I feel like the doctors qualities
The same right
FairPoint
We are in prison
Episode
2022 that's Monday to you
Sure
I have to be honest with you
I find it difficult to listen to him of the present-day not because of how awful he is although that is certainly a challenge
But because I haven't gotten an explanation for why we're not all dead already
Reddit
Do you know it's too much we can't stop it it's already too late
I'm still in that headspace what I'm listening to Alex's trivialize bulshit
I just don't know what's going on anymore
The problem there is that
You're still in that headset
Right because you were in that headspace when you were listen
To that end in the intervening time. You were received
0 million-dollar
That is true you're not in the good headspace.
A couple of million dollars like outside
I think I will
Would still have question
I think you would probably with spiral out of control
Add a couple million dollars hold on
We're all dead already how do we do that
Just pretending that didn't happen I guess that's the way to do it
So here we are
Let's go
Thank you very much
American citizen who led by two Australian guys with Alex considered
Next
Betsy wants to hear the drop of Alex insisting he knows how to read please it's my birthday thank you so much and I apologize
I'm a policy wonk
No
Fine
How to read
Thank you so much
Caitlin sandals
Might be sandal sandal
Piggy but not the beer things thank you so much you're and I'll probably walk
A little piggy
Finally we got to take the credit makes Jordans so thank you so much too
Workers of the World Unite you are now attacking
I have
Risen above
Miami
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Apologized
To the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not
ESO trouble
I think there is one thing that happen
Thomas episode that's a notable
And it is a protracted
Sort of breakdown that Alex has in the middle of the show
In anymore contemplatively mood
Movies
Why you think so many movies
Hunting James Bond movies
And The Kingsmen and just countless others
Logan's Run
Tulsa
There's so many
12 Monkeys
Talk about global Elite releases virus depopulate
Operating system
You got to go along with that idea
Tell you through the movies but
This isn't a 1960s
Movie Lunardi's with 2000
This is a real planet
That we live on
If you're trying to make a list of these movies did not prove that the globalist to try and use films to announce the public that are planning to
Depopulate the planet
What's third entry on your list is zardoz
I don't think that you have a good list here
I think your point may be hurt by your own list sure now
You say that but
I do recall in the Book of Revelations that
The Horseman of War looks an awful lot like Sean Connery in zardoz
Bat bat maybe a interpretations but do say that but
I don't know I heard people talk about it
Has to do with like a population die off by Elite using a bio-weapon maybe it is I'm not sure I
More widely used plots and antagonist to movies like serial killers that's a lot that people use all the time
Alien invasion
One by one they have an alien invasion
And zombies
Vampires natural disasters
Natural disasters
The reason that there are a number of movies that use a villain planning to kill people with some kind of biological weapon is because it's a way to cry
Create really large Stakes
Is that the protagonist has to face
It makes it all the more important that the villain be stopped because the Rippling damage that their success would cause is huge
Conversely the post bio-weapon dystopia is a good way to create a setting for a story where they could be less people
Around like at unless people
The environment isn't really changed sometimes it's easier on a budget
BNB your filming a movie and you've written some script and maybe there's a lot of stuff in there and maybe you're just like
How about we write in that it
Cheaper than Macon
Like
28 Days Later you have to change the environment at all
Have
Less people
Zombies running around
People
We got a lot of these things that Alex
Thanks are our predictive and what the globalist Urology was going to happen
Tell you what the actual
Plan is
We've already know we know what the plan is we're already dead is the plant
The plan is all God I have no idea
Actually a good movie
The real model
They're going to use for control over a city population is going to be
New world
Thx-1138
Morris children
Of men
We haven't seen
Children
Wait
Chemical in the water supply
Sterilize you
They hit you in the water to sterilize a large percentage
Sterilized
Dockside aerosol spraying
Subway
It wasn't
Stuff in the water people no idea
Pointedly unexplained
Yeah it was like a we don't know why all of the sudden everybody couldn't have children and then one person could and we're like
That was the whole thing
Yeah I don't remember a third it's like if people put
Stuff in the water to make people.
Especially considering that the people in charge really wanted the person who could have kids
Because
Super important. Because I knew could contain you should have the whole speech
Yeah it's really important yeah
Then wasn't in the 3rd of cabals Interest
So tender the movie
I don't know any weight those pieces of dystopian fiction that Alex listed their they're largely incompatible with each other
Future similar to Brave New World to come to be essential elements of what makes children of man Edisto
Copiah could not have happened
Example
They are mutually exclusive
That's it
He's kind of a different doomsday fantasy for Alex
He talks about the globalist attacking reproduction sometimes it's just kind of his version of the white nationalist talk
Complaints about declining birth rates
But usually doesn't end up being the end-all-be-all of the globalists plan
The Doodly just like
Side project
Also
Why would the globalists make it so no one can have kids if their whole thing is abusing children
I guess they derive their power from hurting kids and drinking their blood so they can
Satan wouldn't it be
Self-defeating to create a Children of Men scenario
I'd love to see how Alex Wood
Explain that clearing plot hole
I guess they Farm them
How
You know
What
With the
Do fish farms you put them in nuts
I think they could do the same thing with babies that's where they come from I consider this this whole thing of
Well maybe you'd have synthetic robot children
Torturing a soul is what
Dara child in
You just had synthetic children it wouldn't work
I just don't think it's fair
For you to f****** Outlaw abortion
And then be like well it's going to be a Children of Men scenario like
F*** you
No it is a little
A little annoying
Also small note when Alex is aluminum aerosol spraying at the end there he's saying Chemtrails in a way that he wants to
To make it look like he's not saying chemtrails
Crazy sinkhole
Yeah he sucks
Hey look
Humans are going to be killed off
We're all going to be killed off
But not just us
Wait not just that well I mean yeah.
The biosphere is going to
The f****** die in like 5 years 90% of all species are going to go extinct within the next five.
You know that's really going to hit hard
The bugs
Will you go on a trip in the summer
Brother spring
11 places that have a lot of bugs like Minnesota
Or Texas or Florida
25 years ago
In spring or summer
Being a squeegee at a gas station
And squeegee
Bugs off of that would Harden
The bottom of a plane
Your hardest get out
Ragazze would Harden
On the windshield
In the spring or summer in Texas
And there might be one
Bug on my windshield
1 bug
This makes it sound like Alex's
I had some experience with his car being egged
That's fair
So many scientists do believe that insect populations are declining but Alex's windshield is not really the best gauge for that
Not very scientific
It tracks this would be how you prove his point though since everything is yours
Just anecdotal and based on some
F****** hunch
Alex has
The reality of the inside situation isn't
So easy to sum up in a quick blurb so suffice it to say that some species
The numbers are really worrying
Except
For the realm of water-based insect
It would seem to be doing
Doing quite well cuz everything else is going to die around them they're going to have plenty of food it's possible
What is attributed to this is like improvements made to freshwater habitats
To do better because of
Clean water let's
Play shindig regulations
It's really hard to tell exactly what the
Declines are caused by but according to an article about this
The BBC quotes
Gone insect
Destruction of natural habitats due to urbanization to be the key
That would make
An important caveat to make is that this idea of like a widespread population
Decline it incites isn't the consensus opinion
Almost everyone I can find us believe that there are insect populations that are at risk but there isn't agreement
About how Universal this is based on the data sets that are available
Another thing that does seem to be widely agreed on is that the populations that are going down are largely going down due to Urban
Malaysian climb
A change and modern farm
Calming techniques
What no one except one guy thinks
Is it there's a globalist plot to kill all the
Right right
Right that's
Yeah I I mean okay
As as a
Uninteresting story
The when I was a kid there a lot of bugs
And now an adult and they're only one
That's that's fine
Sure but if you use any kind of thing like that to prove a point
You are done immediately done
Well it's actually
What I was reading there is like a they call it the windshield effect
And the people are
They do notice this
It is it is something like a phenomenon that people have in their brain and I'm fine with that
That is still an unacceptable way of
Make an appointment make you think like
And I look into it more
Exactly supposed to be like well this should not be in a conversation with me being like here's how I know it
It's true you know
Get out of here
I was just going to get to the news but that
Please.
All this other news and I will control
Film 2000 music
Frog
What
And so much more
Route 24 hours
But you got to read the Bible about a fallen into tea on the planet
You gotta
That hates us because we're related
Today
Powerful Army present
Did here
Manipulating
To give up our Humanity
The Bible
The British government with Tintin
Check
The chaplain exactly
If you're trying to express that you believe that the Bible is full of accurate predictions and this is what you got you're doing a really
A bad job
The first thing Alex points to is World Government which doesn't exist regardless of how many times Alex insist
But it does
The second Bible says there's going to be 10 kingdoms
How many are there
Well even if Alex is trying to claim that the UN is the world government there's not ten regions in the UN
The African group the Asian Pacific group that
Eastern European group the Latin America and Caribbean group and the Western European and other
Group
I guess if the Bible predicted flying ships
Then I have to concede that that one was spot-on
There is not a mark in people's hands and forehead
Do buy and sell so that one
Hasn't come true
The family has not been broken up
People still have family
All the time from the Train
Five of these families on a windshield there in so many TV shows
JailTracker
Alex is trying to strengthen his argument that the devil is attacking him by pointing these things at the Bible's got and that's what he
Comes up with
Much better list
There's a whole lot of text in that book
And there are some things that could be
Racine is accurate prediction
But Alex
Just doesn't know any of that stuff
The only Bible verses he seems to never the ones that he can use to support gun rights
A John Birch Society newsletter to grind a one-world communist government
Eisenhower was setting up
To do with writing the Bible so
Yeah I mean the Heat quotes
Remember sending that book
Jefferson
Definitely
Alex Alex
Some feelings about January 6th
Of course
Sure
And you think he's going to be blamed
For that that whole thing
No.
Washington Post articles
Wall Street Journal
New York Times articles this weekend
Specifically
The committee is honing in on Rodger Stone and Alex Jones
Hundred percent
PS
And we don't have a motive made us look like fools
Be there's no evidence is not true
President Trump wear over a year
Before that ever happened to Rodger Stone
I've even our legal waffle events
On the 5th for the 6
It's fun how like Trump is my buddy I have his personal phone number turns to I haven't talked to him in over a year
That guy Franklin
Absentee father
Rodger Stone didn't know anything
Connections did he have people who organized the stop the steal settlers
20/20 Electric
Sure
Alexander got his fraudulent permit to have his
Stop the steel rally there
After the fact
You look like a fool that does not mean you have no motive for the crime differently you might
Look like a fool you might look like
Exactly yeah yeah yeah
To overthrow the United States government
The larger
Larger Community had certainly some of those goals
I think Alex is a little bit
Touchy never heard of about Communications nevermind
Who are they
Bruiser talking to prosecutors and are exposing
Their Communications
All the way up
Probably
Jewels
Entrepreneur
How do you say bad things
Ultrasound
I know some of the people there
As
Taylor talking to the feds
Exposed
The dog people
Would actually make stuff up and
Who do you know Alex
Oh boy you know do you know bezo Keepers who plead guilty to seditious conspiracy
I think the store roads isn't saying he's turning
Who do you know you think you know
That's not good
The truth about you
It seems a little bit defensive about just the idea cuz
This I think is what
Inspiring this conversation on his show is that
Barry's best news of
The goalkeeper
Gentleman
Who played guilty
Who in that in the statement of his
Defense
It does include that part of
Stuart Rhodes calling somebody to try and get in touch yeah
The Galaxy's a little bit touchy about these communication
There's all these headlines everywhere
When none of that happened
None of that went on
Animal Control
Dawn
Is mafia boss
Alex said that he hasn't spoken to drop in over a year at the
How would he know if there was or was it
Communication between any of the oathkeeper folks
And people in Trump's orbit
But like you don't have any idea about that so the blanket denial isn't
Persuasive
Rodger wasn't involved in anything right right
People who pled guilty
D2 seditious conspiracy
Structure
Address to the committee
Could be having trouble here
This could be trouble I would have plead the 5th if I were on his own show yet I don't know anything about this but Alex will hyper.
Defensive about the idea of oathkeeper communications
We know that Stuart tried to get in touch with Trump through an intermediary who refused to put him in contact and there's
Barry
Very slim chance of that could be out
I think that there's a
Very very very tiny
I would not bet on it I don't think that's the case
I think that Alex is more defensive because if there is like sort of a straighter line but interrupted The Oath Keepers
This whole thing looks real bad I mean God damn
Terrible Mark Meadows
It could just be the Alex Rec
Noises
Is damning stuff and that a guy who's been a guest on his show for over a decade was trying to contact the president
Have him authorizes paramilitary group to overthrow the government by force
And then Alex had that guy on his show repeatedly after January 6th to Creek
Conspiracy theories
But I was really the reality is here whether the full shape of it is
There's a nerve
Been taught to know however that it was a Honeypot for bucket
Tor who got them
To do all of that stuff right they wanted to do and we're going to do when they got there regardless of whether or not there was a Honeypot
Provocative
I was just trying to get in touch with Trump in or do you like hate
Like to do this
Laid out a Honeypot
It's delicious
I want to put my hand in there trying to get the recipe for this
Very long time
Yeah
Yep I'm not convinced
Is Rodger Stone like Eeyore
Betty York
Alex Guzman
Commercial and comes back
Can break and
Typically we Greg Reese and John bowne reports
Play in that
First segment of an hour where it's not broadcast
On the main body of the chauffeur
Gregory's
I accidentally listened to a little bit
God
The letter from Albert
Regarding the Illuminati plan
Is largely considered a hoax
The word Nazism in a letter
What is the desired outcome
Planned 9/11
And was intended to leave the people in the state of complete physical
Moral spiritual exhaustion
Atheists
And revolutionaries
To create
And they will do this in order to force the people into Exterminating the Destroyers
Civilization according to this letter this Bloodbath
Christianity and Atheism
And lead to the pier.
Lucifer
Has the new world religion
Does appear as if this is happening now freely
So the letter doesn't like the Muslims and the zionists Flash
May
Okay
So that's that's what I'm running
Generally speaking what I hear anybody bring up Albert Pike I tune the f*** out of that conversation
And I have the same response to her and Greg Reese's voice but
For some reason I decided to listen to a little bit of
Contract then now I want to resend and f****** Jamie XX
Collaboration
Solitaire
Buckley Buckley
She's decided to do a special report where the premises hey this letter is definitely a hoax but maybe it's still prophetic
Yeah right that's about the brownies
What an amazing take the big letters
The Reese's covering is understood to be the creation of a guy named William Guy Carr
Since the earliest form of the letter can be found in his 1958 book Pawns in the game
Car was a really influential figure in terms of pushing out some early New World Order
Conspiracy theories but of course
Also is a big old Auntie sound
He quoted heavily from the protocols of the Elders of Zion his books distributed by noon time
Press
An anti-semitic publisher that was founded by Willis carto the founder of Liberty Lobby
Everywhere everywhere
The Press was meant to be the publishing outlet for cardos other group The Institute for historical review which is
Considered one of the largest disseminators of Holocaust denial content
In the world
Perhaps not surprisingly in 2009 a former new antidepressant Floyd James Von Braun carried out a screen
At the Holocaust Memorial Museum
That would make
I understand that be fake letter that Reese is talking about isn't just
The fake lighter
Hit the fake letter being read
Conspiracy theory
So whether he realizes it or not
What Reese's doing
Is taking an anti-semitic Oaks which uses earlier anti-semitic Oaks is a citation
Been using it
To suggest to his audience that while the
Monster Lee not a real letter that Albert Pike Road
Maybe there's an underlying truth to it
Right which is shity
Right there goes bad work
F******
Bacteria evolving in
A cesspool
You know just
Eggnog remarkable about A2 is like why did you do why is that
Actual report is this in the news
Deal was it
Right who pitched that in what meeting I would probably
This guy is a shat
What is he
What is
Why
What why
Also when
When is it a good idea to be like alright this
Obviously fake
Yeah but what if it was right
That's kind of how a lot of these conspiracy f***
Deal with the protocols of the Elders of Zion they're like yeah
I still thought it was all the way real people who have more of a mine for optic
Admit that it's fake because it's so very clearly a very very clearly will fall back
Macon like yeah it's a hoax
But it's actually talk
King about stuff
Through the medium of hoax that I tell the truth
Right right right
There's a there's a lot of that trying to save
Whatever can be salvaged showing wreckage of a hoax
He's going for the pike
Probably heard
So
You know this is Supreme Court
Opinion
Leeks
We know that it's antifa that did it
Antifa working
As a as a clerk
Nai
In the Supreme Court
Yes that's the most important part about all of
Opinion
Make me that the headline
How about the league stuff right not saying heavily cuz what's important
Abbott now Alex
Detect
Skip cap
He's figured out who did this who did it
Whodunnit
Whodunit as you gathered all of the suspects there is around a table to slowly tease out who did the crime
Percula Jones
I'm going to tell you exactly what's going on
I believe John Roberts is the one that leaked
Wow
Democrat or Republican
We know that since February of last year it's come out
On the Supreme Court ruling
Using the power machine
Record
And the wars in the pedophilia
The election about abortion
Yasso John Roberts
Release this in order to get people fighting
Before the midterms because I guess he wants
Democrats to win
I mean
Bite my theory on why
It was John robber
Is because
None of the other just
Is it if it is a Justice and not like a clerk
She's more likely to be a clerk
Or something
But if it is a Justice
John Roberts is the only one who would
I'm making weird
Face again
The other liberal just
Justices who signed on the opinion
Have known what's going on
For a long time
Why would they suddenly choose this point in time to do it
Right
The conservative justices
Have been masturbating
Furiously since they got to sign them
Non-Stop
Blood everywhere you know that Kai
But John Roberts
Is if you look at his career
Obsessed with the quartet
Itself
I'm trying to make sure that it maintains this air of being
Illegitimate
Part of the government
Write any stay over
Turner board
Which they will do
Then it's very obvious
Even to John Roberts
This Supreme Court is f******
Stupid well even buy your own reasoning that kind of
Would be an argument why Roberts didn't do it because he's such a fan
Institution of the court that you wouldn't
Leaked document but he's the only one who thinks that the opinion could be
Put helix
The sanctity of the courts and all this
You apparently Alex
Exactly
Listen to people in the world
I think it's
More likely
But it was a cat burglar
Ruled out that if possible that it was a staffer from somebody
But if it was going to be a Supreme Court Justice
Who did it
Which would be silly
Okay so I may go long with you if that's what you're stipulating
If you're stipulated
B48 Supreme Court Justice most likely candidate
Freeport
But in the totality of
Possible people probably
Who did it
I think will be interesting to see how that plays
We'll see
To someone who was recently found not guilty
Although I don't think that's actually what happened
Well wasn't
Has he was found buried
Marjorie Taylor Greene though
She was found not guilty
She gets to run in her Alexa
I don't know I know
Marjorie Taylor Greene
Call the big win
Carrabba's
What's unconstitutional
Despite its constitutionality
Wrong she wanted last election
Lady of Courage
Sabrina
Green is facing an accusation of participating in an Insurrection which would have made her ineligible
Be re-elected
Nothing involving this case was unconstitutional I was just decided the people Prosecuting the case didn't provide sufficient evidence
Big picture though she lied
Cool bunch of night hearing
And also she want her last election by wide margin because it's a disc
Cricket's Wings heavily Republican
And because her opponent had dropped out of the
I mean
It is it is very funny how little consequences there are four
For anything if you have
Money order
Like none
It's in his disgusting people are losing their minds
Think that it's
There should be some sort of a consequence for the blatant lying
They're what I do also think that
Wow I agree that you should not
There should be a very high standard that must be met
Short order to block someone from Ronnie
Because the alternative
Of allowing that to be done on assertive
Roughshod basis
The damage of that would do would be like
Really bad let me throw this out at
Okay so if somebody was very clearly there's tons of evidence that she was associated with the Moon
Menands was
In contact with them on that day
So we've got that
Established
And then the other stuff that we don't have established
We know for a fact she lied about on the stand
Those two combined I think are enough
Well if you can't convince a court of that that's kind of on you
So
You know exactly
Alex has some ideas about why she wasn't
Found guilty
She should be able to run
Let me just like our last episode we found that he has no idea what the Constitution says once again
He is showing his ass
A dozen members of Congress like Gozer in others
The judges said it's unconstitutional
I'm not going to hear
Get on
If they were convicted felons run
Like once you've done your time should be able to
I've great
Alex
He doesn't know anything about the Constitution
Because I guess he thinks the people who've been convicted of a felony can't run and I can be true you can also still run for
You can run for any federal office even if you're a felon
Check even points out in 1798 Representatives Matthew lion ran for Congress
Prison + 1
Houston to seat in Congress after serving for months
It's different for state-level offices depending on the state but that doesn't have to
To do with the Constitution and Alex's talk about members of the US Congress
So it's all federal level s*** he just doesn't know anyting
But this document that he pretends to love so much and willing to die for
No s*** document keeps people from doing stuff like what he wants to do so of course
He doesn't know anything about civics
Glassell my God that would
Would cause a
F****** explosion might resign
Amazon job
Hey runs himself from that class
Is it relates to the case against
Let's go sarthi this was a judge from Phoenix who dismissed the suit that was seeking
Barham Andy Biggs and marks
Syndrome from being on the ballot because they participated
In an insurrection
The judge interpreted the rule included in the Fourteenth Amendment to require a conviction for participation
To Bar someone
So that case
It was thrown out
Different states make different decisions so this
Marjorie Taylor Greene that was Howard judge in Georgia
Decided tippers
There's nothing unconstitutional about it but it did ultimately reach a similar conclusion
And Alex should be thrilled with it
Illustrates the ways that states are able to determine their own policy
For themselves
Operate outside the control of the federal government that he hates Obama
What are you complaining about dick
I think it's unconstitutional
Great for the states to act
Different from the weight
I think it's
22 Chanel
For the federal government
To tell states that they can't that wait no
What does position on the cost
Fusion black
Okay that's
Got it so we Alex Goes to calls
And this is worth
Things kind of fall off
Because I
What would it have been
Quite a while back
So I don't recall
The people behind qanon like a week to unveil themselves if you was going
I mean never tell you never did
This color brings that up
A question he says
Who is q
Would you like to elaborate on that and then I'll tell you who she is
Thank you
2 years ago
Coochie was and how impossibly it exchanged hands
And things like that
At one point you threaten that
Come out and say who they were themselves that you were going to do it
Maybe you didn't cover it at some point but I never did hear
Games named
What is fascinating about this
Clip is that it
Clearly shows that
I was always talks about how he doesn't
Screen calls yeah but like he knows this guy called before
He even talks to sleep whatever the call screening process is Alex he's the question that the persons going
Going to ask
Before they come on answer that kind of invalidates his entire thing pretty much
Now here's Alex's answer and boys
It's not good
But I never did hear
Games named
Well
I'm on record saying that
He was lying
That
So that's a no
Okay sure
Could not have said more
Owensville loudest
Pause I've ever heard it was screaming in my ear I have no idea I don't remember saying that
I don't know
What am I doing
I need a new call screener this sucks
He was so prepared to
To tell the person who killed
But he was not prepared to have to say that there was
Previous
Call back
Back to when he said this early
This is not just like someone randomly saying hey tell me who you said you were going
Unveil who these people are in Endeavor did that who are the names
Quicks
Well
Coos Bay
So I'm on record as saying that you is not telling the truth
Oh boy
Not going to go well party run out of gas
He doesn't give a great ass
She was such a horrible thing
That I
Talk about it
Who is anonymous
So what you people call and ask me who what
If any group
What's to call themselves
Anonymous
Esoteric
Occult means hidden
We went on
When I go to the satanic 4G with a woman killed
You don't know who anyone is there wearing masks
Now I got you.
Who is QQ is a NADA by everyone
And some people and anyone who wants to be but then they can also stop
Guy Fawkes
Texas qrq
Jesus
Yeah
So Alex doesn't really have an answer but he does call it a
The question of who is q is a
Musically racially-charged
Tar-Baby
Wow
Puzzled that they love us f****** wow
They want to feel like they're part of something Magic
Getting orders from President Trump
And that everything was fine he was I was going to get arrested
What I do
People
And yes I do know what happened with you
What happened with it
No one wants the truth so I'm
How about that
Caller asks what no one wants to know this colors
God dammit that caller even even at the beginning was like
Listen
I can't listen all the time
So maybe you were revealed it when I wasn't
Listening
So that gave you an out
He was overly polite
Yeah he was doing his best
Even though he knew for a fact that you never fuc
He said it I don't know I don't know that to be the case I think this color seems like from the other things he says I think his collar seems
Like a polite I think this might be
It maybe you didn't say it was genuine
I find it offensive for Alex
To take a direct question
What is a bright and then he'll be like look
I know what it is
But no one wants to know so how about I don't say
Right
Question Barros
News today
Time to take the mask off
Lander if there is names to name
The craziest Boogeyman and certainly if the
Government want to know who it was
Find out
10 days if they want
What they don't want to say it
Yeah
Who started it
Experts inoperative
Right out of the CIA
Here's what happened
I'm excited to hear what happened with q but I don't know how much more clearer Alex can make it to the audience that he doesn't have any
Specific information he's just only interested in speaking in Vegas
Platitude that can't be proven or disproven
In the span of this call is given multiple excuses why you can't say the names of who is q because
He doesn't have a name to give
If he gives
The name may be stuck with that being a story
Specificity is the enemy of conspiracist
Super Why
If he stays in the Evie says a name and that name is somebody just proven his being cute he looks really bad
If he wiggles around makes up fake excuses for why you totally knows the truth but he isn't going to say it you can't Rick most of the eye
Guardian to think
He's telling the truth and there's some compelling reason
But he's not saying anything
Sure
It's honestly a very similar Dynamic to what he's
Complaining about whiskey
He's saying the people love the mystery of it in the unknown
Alex's just exploiting the exact same thing in his listeners
It's only intriguing until he gives the name and then
It's boring as hell cuz
Who cares
The Watkins
Like it's Boris Johnson
Joey says that name you can trick yourself into thinking that he's got deep levels of holding back for some series considered
Duration but much like you it's all bulshit
Oh yeah just a what if
Alex is a bit of a
GoPro
Because
He starts trying to explain what Q is
And I think he realizes that like there's not really anywhere to go with this
I'm going to have to do something
Different
In order to change
The conversation
Here's what happened
We were very successful exposing the
Satanism angle
WikiLeaks
Election 2016
I need someone on the inside
Was giving out accurate information.
So
There's a bit of a like
Annoyance at the caller there
But Alex
Ask the color request
You said do you remember that from the 2016 election
Mccalla responded to that
Anyway that
Makes sense
Based on the question that was asked novices
I've got to start over
As if it's somehow derails him or whatever
And that's the beginning of him just lashing out at this caller
Because that's the new game
The new game is no longer hey I I do not know who I have no idea who he was and if I do I don't want to tell you
That's why you do it
About this
And you'll forget what it was yesterday when I'm done
My throat hurts
Exactly what's going on
Specific stuff
Rodgers said
And you responded back with somebody was giving information
What
That what you want
Did you hear what I just said
In the lead-up to that what did I say to you right before
You responded back with that information
I'm a little nervous on my toes
We lost
Call Mike
My God
How dare you say yes sir like you were being dressed
Doubt but if it's a moron that you've been tricked into
Looking up to
Cannot be held to his word from back when he said that he was going to expose Q by names they did
Publicly revealed themselves sleep in a little bit underwhelming
Alex decided to launch into a big thing about his interpretation of Q stuff in the caller said something which is
Dude Perfect
Emotionally abused this color instead of having to take anything of substance
Before the caller said anything Alex it only said that he'd been
Unsuccessful in getting sex traffic
Information out
And that Wikileaks had released information
About the 2016 election
There wasn't anything like it was a revealing specific in their the discolored failed
The grasp
The question
Did you hear me
He said do you remember that
It's just Alex like presenting the situation differently that just happened a minute ago so he can
It's nonsense. This is what
Weak bullies
Yes
Also another distraction tactic
But he's employed
Alex Fields kind of called out about how he said he was going to name cute and he knows that he can't do that so he's got to spend some
It's just horrible that one of the places decided
Let's go with his making this caller feel like Alex isn't able to make
His points because of him
He's fault somehow
No that's that's
Book abuse
I mean
It really couldn't be much more gas lighter even that
Jesus
This man for quite a while
Save face
Yes sir
Two people
Wait I thought he is the worst people on earth
2 is the New World Order
She was a psyop tulita surroundbar noses
Start over
Filmmakers in a family
He's not a bad guy
Yeah he's completely schizophrenic
I feel like all this makes it all the more important rileks the name name so the world can know who it is
It's using this new world order siop to hurt people and not mislead
They destroy the world it's because of them that we lost America he's making
Argument against his own position this is banana
I would dare say that if revealing who this person or group is would lead to some people being freed from the delusion
Kubo
How much is a moral obligation
Antonym names
He's not going to though because he doesn't have any name
Peter says b******* vagaries and feeling
Yes
The Shield is ignorant
Attention to what's actually being discussed
So true
What he's doing this is
Athletic that
Yep
He should be really sure
I don't know if he is able to access those feelings really lucky
He doesn't have the capacity for shame
True
Little baby in a box
It's locked
There's my cue but they don't care about Alex's covid
Stuff enough
Here's my frustration
I can give you the emails in the documents enough shut them they're probably 50 times
Covid-19
And no one cares and no one listens and no one knows about it
Puff the Magic Dragon
As I don't care enough about his
Covid-19 people have responded quite well to that
3 million-dollar
Is going quite well
August just another Dodge
There's something about this but Alex really wants to
To distract from
No s*** and you can't name someone
Without risking another possible defamation lawsuit
I was probably knows a name someone is Q they're probably going to get us
Certain amount of harassment because of it possibly even
Escalating to violence
Because he's presenting this is not a gas but as a known fact
He probably bear a little bit more responsibility if this happen
So he knows that that is not a path you can go down if you've said that they're the reason you lost the country and their aglow
Mobile inmate calling January 6th
And then you give their name the person probably going to die
Well at least get a lot of death
Virtual
At the same time based on what Alex has presented there's literally no reason not to name
These people
He was a psyop that's leading good people astray it's run by the New World Order it's destroying the country and Alex knows who's behind
If you're a listener who believes Alex there's no reason not to name names but because Alex
Can't he has to create a wreath
That's what you're seeing here
Moving around trying to find an emotionally satisfying reason for why he can't name
And he's coming up
Well I mean and in this situation
That person
818 arguable that if you believe what Alex is saying
You should go kill diapers
Yeah you know
Like in index.
That's why he cannot he cannot give a name
Because
Based on what he's just said
A name would be a death sentence to that person for a True Believer I mean I guess the way you get around that
Something is like
It's not so much of that sentence as it is you should be tried for treason admit
Qgenda for leprosy
The cases you put this person in significant Danger
And Alex is pretty
Kionrightnow tonight
Gets sued again
He has a pretty pretty relevant recent
Experience of that soap
I just
I'm fascinated by this
This
Ping
Amity is towards you or
He lost a lot of money on that
Yeah
I think it's interesting that this caller is asking that and Alex needs to do like an hour
Yeah for now we're almost yeah like instead of just sort of brushing aside the question
He needs to do this
Because it's
Something
That if he didn't
The caller the
The audience would just be like
Yeah
He's going to reveal these people in the past he's being reminded of this on air
So now he has to do a huge show out of this to make sure the people don't remember that
These events have to remember something else
Yeah
And so
That's where we are doing that you forced Alex
To put on a
Big Smoke
Screen of a performance
And then
Disappear into the woods
And so Alex comes back
Break and he apologizes to this caller
Of course because that's what abuser State and then talked a little bit more about what he knows about you
Serious
I apologize to Adam
Oklahoma last a very reasonable question and I got
Because when I
I'm a baby
Gives me a headache
And I got where and when
And the biggest frustration is I know exactly one on
And
People don't seem to have our do hardcore document
Your show is hours long
You want to believe
A lot of good people
MTG General Flynn myself a certain extent
What was going on with the cute thing
This Anonymous saying
And so well let's just try to co-opt it
Away from the bad guys
Yet
Fuk up
That's
That's what wait
So now you're telling me that General Flynn tried to wield the the influence over
A cult-like following
Online folks
That seems healthy
Hi
Real quick
I probably would want
Well I would say that
After the sick
Which you've claimed
Q orca
Castrated
In order to make you look bad
Flynn still sets
True I think that this maybe in some ways and attempt
To explain away why Flynn was a huge Kingsport
He was trying to take it over for a little bit in the correct direction or whatever
Cast in the past
6 years have thrown out at least one or two cue things right
Probably more than that I would too I mean I was being
Conservative
Yeah but Alex tries to convince Flynn
To do something the probably would have had
Drastic concert
And I told Flynn he ought to just come out and say he's cute
Pikachu
You good
You just did
I mean that's them all the off-the-record discussion unique
Yeah I think that's
General Flynn
That would be a really suck something for him
Yeah
Yep
I am too really no way to reveal yourself is cute without
Simultaneously kind of sounded like you're revealing yourself as the next
Messiah
Miralax
I am
Cute
Also
Reincarnation of Jesus Christ
I'm out here I'ma I'ma to fur
Yeah
This is a mass
Still don't know who Q is a little bit about
What his relationship
Ship with qy
14 years ago
Trying to fix Q
Paul Joseph Watson
In the election WikiLeaks
What Helix is real
The pedophilia
Rings that are in the emails
With John podesta and all the rest of it
That's all real
Something like that
Well they come out with
You did that
Evolve into tough going there
Real real story
With a fake story
You had to fire Joe Biggs about
Coverage
Why was faking being freaked out and almost crying in an interview with the gates.
This is so stupid
You know it it really does
Explain why all of our history is so f******
Stupid is because
The people who won
In wars and ship
For so long
We're exactly like Alex just recontextualizing everything in church
The loss and I did look like an idiot
But let me Rican text
July's 2y I'm right always was and in fact I did not lose what's the same thing like on our 2003 episode
About him like rewriting assigned he was wrong as the globalist
QuikTrip
His associates did a lot of pizza
Navigate s*** but also
Bumper sticker that said imq
I don't know
Obviously I know from
Listening to him and hearing him say various things over the years for that was a finance
Motivational
Solid
Alex
I was trying to do that so they would
Believe
The right things or whatever but
That's that's
That's nonsense
So I went with the formation of
Kill
Specific
And then a lot of Patron
Ministration
Intelligence
Exposing the pedophile rings
And Jeffrey Epstein
Do it anonymously
Really energized
To the public
Infowars
Put their name on it
Within a month
By the other side
A couple problems with his retelling of the story has never taken away by for Tanner 8chan
It started on an exclusively posted on 4chan
Before migrating to 8chan
Everything that Q was happened
Beginning with cryptic post
Made there which were then interpreted
Discussed another online forum
Basically what's going on here than Alex wants his cake and eat it too
He wants to keep the general Vibe of qanon because it largely matches his
Conspiracy worldview and to attack that too harshly would have blowback on his own dumb idea
At the same time he doesn't want to have to take responsibility for him
Answer to the fact that
Acute
Assistant Lee been wrong about stuff
And the theories that grow out of that Cesspool are embarrassing and dangerous
It often
Abby's medical nature
Always said I do agree that he was inspired at
At least in part by him
The whole counter-coup narrative the key and Steve Rift about
Through most of the lead-up to the 2016
Is really close as a match
Do lot of Q's early mythology
It definitely wouldn't be surprising to learn that a lot of that stuff was in some way in
Inspired by Alex's
Collaborative storytelling
Also if what I was saying is true then Trump and his administration
To be investigated and possibly charged
For what they did
Like they weren't just putting out the truth is too hot to handle
Like if Anonymous shitposting on 4chan it was a propaganda effort from the federal government I don't think that's appropriate
Do I think Alex himself would find that to be a very
Disgusting thing for a government
To do what the hell I think he would be against it
Yeah yeah
Had a secret
Propaganda Armand 4chan
Anonymously she was saying
Alex and his associates arrested or whatever all this cryptic nonsense and bull
Call Shay predictions
Riling people up and then
You know people
End up killing
Jackson
Shooting into a pizza place
Man it's so crazy with Hillary then
Like Hillary could have done step-by-step everything that Trump did and they'd still be mad at her
That's not enough
You mean like
From a policy and political science
Assume so
Cuz it's not really about that
No no
No no no
So Alex now realizing that he's talked about going on for quite a while
Reassess is what the
The caller actually asked
I'm actually glad that Adam called in and asked
Human what is Cube and answer is the same thing as Anonymous people done good thing is he
Packers
Whitehead activity
Call themselves anonymous
And so anything
That is
It's a lot of fun for some people
But it's very very dangerous
Not good
So I guess he feels that he has successfully rambled enough and given enough of a presentation
Change what
The caller actually asked
Colorado
You said you were going to name names did you name names what are the names
So much
The question is now who and what is
Qanon as opposed to water the name
It's a direct question that he has now changed so
Distracting leave that
This caller
Actually has been fools
Okay
In Oklahoma
And God bless you Alex
What you wrapped up there
The reason why I called and asked
Somebody people
Episode
He did not get an answer to his question
The question that was asked
Alex
Operated him and emotionally abused him and then rambled enough
Smooth over the woods
Answer managed to make this guy feel like he got something out of the exchange as opposed to Alex just said nothing
A half an hour
Yeah it does feel like this should go into evidence as to why
Deprogramming doesn't work then speaking of that immediately after that
Anthony
Conversation
For you I'm sure for sure
Father God thank you for
Things that are coming to light in this world and I thank you for the
Curry's Alex and his team has had
I feel
I don't know people who are like hey you know Alex is
He's right about a lot of stuff
I feel like this is a snapshot that maybe they should
Really ask themselves some questions about
Oh yeah
Entire presentation of head with the caller who asked about qanon the way it's handled
The way of progress is ad
The fact that it leads to this guy
Having a prayer on air where he
God for Alex's bravery
It's nonsense
This is called
I wish there was like a bot we could have
On every on the internet just bought that every time it said Alex it anytime it
Detected like Alex was right
Immediately follow up a reptile responsive just these clips
Maybe like how do you feel about that
Yeah
Defend it
Well I think I think
Some people who are maybe more Envy like sort of zealotry angle side of things
They may be fine
They probably want to maintain like
Podcast be really embarrassing
I really talk to answer for
Man Christians feel the same way about the Bible that they do about the
The tution
Which is that
Reading it is just
Yeah terrible idea
And praying in public
Is exactly what Jesus
Told you to do
Understand
Is the Infowars
This is the church
And I do believe
Infowars is the most
Active Church on planet Earth
Forgetting the word of God out
It's the one that
Isn't holding back
You don't read that Bible buddy
Product you sell I really enjoyed X
The product you sell
Everything you saying
You're risking your life
Missha BB
I mean come on these callers
Saying that I why did I have to learn so much
F****** Christianity only to hate it
And then these people don't even know anything about it and then try and shove it down my throat all the time
It's annoying
That's very annoying
I wish I would have flipped his desk after this caller was like a most important Church in the world
You should know
So Alice Cooper call from his longtime call Carlos
Nettles
It's
Annoying I remember every episode
Santa is a little taste
All of Alex's old buddy
Wonder OG you know
I'm looking my phone
Michelle Rothschild
17th
A nation's money
So that's almost certainly a fake quote
There's no actual evidence that mayor Rothschild said that
This quote is being said
Hi by Hammer a little
I dubious and there are some indications that a guy named Andrew Fletcher said in the 1600 long before
Rothschild was alive chair
The prevailing theories of his quote was attributed to Rothschild and the early 1900's and there was a debate about the gold
Right that was
That was where the soda pops up into the modern Consciousness as being appropriate
To make that up
From him when you start seeing Rothchilds name attached to it
Yeah it's
It's nonsense after the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Well
Spiders this collar and God bless him
Fourth grade
Let's get another call and this guy has a amazing suggestion for how Alex
Can make some money
It's
T-shirts
Infowars
And
What if what if anyone has been in 1 oz
You gave them back
A 1/10 Oz
Dogecoin
I've got in the divorce
And
How about
You build people for even more money
Damn I mean it's an interesting
It's an interesting idea
I mean it's a really all that different than the overpriced silver coins that he selling or
Liver of the golden knights not really thick
For the novelty is the golfer
4 Gold transfer right right
Open Spotify
And it is finished ugly fun
That's like if you send them in a gold statue in a
The head off of it and gave it back to you right out keep up keep the rest of it you get the head
Response to this guy
And also some big
I hate you
I think I would be amazing
70 likes
Only the people that sit in the 1 oz
And then you can make nine
1 trillion %
Android Note
But we now officially know and it's going to come out soon
Is George Soros battle Lawson's finest
He's trying to take me down
Wait wait you haven't sell that before we figured it out
SA
I can think of very few ways of
Making money
That
AR
More tailored to laundering
Bambi
Giving someone
Gold
How do you say let's go or less goals
And then not really keeping track of what it is that the value of what you have
Then you're going to give him out
Write like a really good way to
Taken some money that maybe
I mean if I was going to launder launder a s*** ton of money
The Alex Jones
It's another Avenue
Yeah I mean it's also a ridiculously dumb
Very dumb idea
What if I send you 10 Bitcoin
And you send me one back
That's a great idea right now
So Alex that has some bad ideas like this
The colors of bad ideas and here's one of Alex
It is just that half an hour at least
Rambling about qanon Shore
I've dumped you is now it's a
So I can attack on everybody favorite thing
Taylor Greek god dammit
MPG on the road graciously
Meanwhile thank you so much
Gratulations
You weren't under indictment you're not a felon
I had no reason to do this this really discredits them
Chelation still
Well thank you Alex
Discredit
Wow she's on speed dial now man she's she's coming in
I think she think she's losing an election
I don't know
Interesting to try and read the passage of like her
Weather
It is his frequent appearances problem
For me to say she thinks
That she's going to lose an election
Implies that I believe she has some sort of ability to plan long-term
And
To recognize real
Troon
Anything could be possible in her brain
Yeah I think also one of the problems we run into is that the behavior would be indistinguishable because
Coming on Infowars a bunch could be trying to get the vote out get your name out there or it could be trying to lay tracks
For a career after you
Loser
Primary election I wouldn't be so quick to to make assumptions but
Man
It is
Bad news
The combination of her and him
What you posted that ultra-mega thing with a red eyes
Signaling to like his dark magazin yeah
Alex's
Certainly more recently talked a bit more about blackpill ideas. News is one of his website
I mean I like this is not good these days
You combinations in the influences coming together is
Yeah
It's not good
It's the it's the larger thing that she's part of you know like if you go back and look at congress's through history
It's a really looking at individual members
I would be shocked
To find a single con
Concrete that does not have at least
1 truly insane person
Except there were also the president and the rest
Congress
Her team to
That's kind of my bigger
Yeah there
Hey it's more troubling
Yeah yeah I think
I don't know why but it does feel different
Van like
Ron Paul showing up on how to show a line
Yeah
I think
Ron Paul has been into qanon
Prior to him being on a show and then I would be as worried about Ron Paul
What's what's
2q i8
It's like you're scary now kind of guy
A cheap kind of guy right makes sense for them together
Where is Marjorie Taylor Greene is a qanon weirdo unhinged who knows what the f***
Yeah reality she inhabits
And
Yeah if she was a just a John Birch
Kind of
Ranbir Congress
Instinctual worry about
Was going on Alex's show
Mannequin doll that seems like it's just cuz he's related to Ron Paul
If I mean cuz
Cuz Ron and Rand
Despite
Being shity people and batshit nuts it is always felt like you would
And you inhabit
The same universe
And everytime MTG speaks
I'm like
I don't know where you are
I just
Don't know where you are or what you think or what
Older or how I wrestled with this a little bit I think his next clip actually will lay out a little bit of why because
There is that inhabiting of a false reality
Somewhat there is also like I think
This clip illustrates
There are some
Indications that she also is very clearly aware
The fact that there is another real real
You're getting into something MCG really
Central here
And that is
These giant distribution centers in food
Factories
Processing facility
Everyday statistically impossible
Intel
We look at the pipeline spring shutdown value the cloward-piven strategy.
Destroying capitalism by sabotage
So many signs
What do you think's going on and what are you hearing
Well I think
Maybe more than just a
Right now it's
Especially in the past
It doesn't seem to be
It shouldn't be happening why is it
This is a choice I mean what you just said is why
Food processor
Yeah. There are these fires that have happened
And Marjorie Taylor Greene even knows that these sorts of fires of these facilities
Isn't Tropical Tan,
She knows the actual actual explanation for the things that are happening but she also knows
She only gets information from Outlets that are full of s*** like
Infowars in Tucker these fires are useful only in so far as they are happening in food
Which is why Marjorie Taylor Greene may think that they're all happening
The conspiracies about the globalist attacking the food supply so that's the angle that full of s*** Outlets take on the story
It seems like the perception that Marjorie Taylor Greene is mirror
Just yesterday there was a fire at a textile plant in South Carolina but that's not leading the coverage cuz it Doesn't
Conspiracy
Yesterday there was also a fire at the Jeld-Wen
Implant in Wysox Pennsylvania
But this isn't part of the
Conspiracy because the company that makes interior doors
There's an explanation for the phenomenon
Green is
Discussing and she knows that explanation
As proven by her saying the explanation out loud
Gino's the reality but the
Conspiracy is more useful
So she leans into that ignoring reality in favor of her constructed world
They're certainly other reasons but this kind of tendency disqualifies her I think for being someone who should hold public office
If someone is
Willington knowingly use conspiracy bulshit to persuade you towards
Conclusion
You can't trust their being straight up about anything
Ever and I think that
Bat-Mite
Distinction between harappa
I do believe that Ron Paul believe the ship that he says yeah
Like I would think he's wrong and
But I do
I think that
He sincerely believes you're that
You know the fact is
Or whatever maybe what I feel like is
Difference
Between
Alexandra like
If the difference of exploiting fake reality and trying to use it
You are trying to make
Fake reality usurp real reality
Do you know what I mean
Like Rand Paul
As always seem like he's exploiting
Fake reality
Noe ZZ
He's giving the bones
To the people who need the bones to get his job
Attempt
Gigi really feels like she is trying to
To destroy reality and replace it
With the b******* Shiba
It's hard it's hard to tell but there is
There is something that feels
I mean I don't want I don't think it is
What is it possible that we're experiencing some low-grade misogyny
I don't think it is
What it would go
You know what is the same time why in this
Situation
Misogyny even creep in
Scared about
Reality not about women being involved
Like
My feelings and apply them on to somebody else
Yeah and I think I would
Feel just as bad as like Matt gaetz was on
Like regularly
That guy in Missouri whose Name Escapes me at the moment
Holly holy on there that's
That's almost scary
It was
You like to happening all the time
It was like a regular guest ship of some of these other people who aren't women
Are completely
Terry Twomey
Yeah maybe it's just I'm not scared of Ron Paul I think it's true we've been around
He's been kind of grandfathered in as the defense guy three Senators passed the FED with his brother
Brother
We don't know that Ron actually think that the Wayne
But yeah
Maybe maybe we just have like a bias towards
Old people being less harmful
Maybe ideology is something that
We don't have to worry about it clearly dealing with it
Taylor green represent
It's still kind of like
Fully formed yet
I don't know there's a
Potential for Destruction more than Ron Paul Rand Paul is yes
Lot of weird threads
That
Untangled
But we've won last clip here and
So really
Dyke
Just declare fully
Performance
I think everyone should be concerned about
You know I don't want
There's too many food processing plant
No one in charge things
Department of
What is going on
Mothers that grocery
I can't find baby
Formula
Which is just
Horrendous and heartbreaking
Farhan's I think it's
Something
ISeries attention
And demanded
Navigation
I wasn't using thousands and thousands of agents to arrest January 6th peaceful protesters
We would have answers
He has the answer to the question that she's demanding be answered
And she told
Yeah she already knows
Advanced really isn't going to investigate this because there's a very ready statistics on this the show that this is not out of the normal
And what do you want from the people in power
Regulation
Sure
What up
Is that what she's saying I mean besides a conversation
Other than
Regulation
The absence of the press conference that would ultimately lead to regulations is a grey top
Pickle thing cuz then you can say that there's a cover-up of
What is obviously agroterrorism whatever
She doesn't believe any of this s*** and you can tell because
She's already
Explained it in this the very first production was here's why this doesn't make sense
Right now I believe
Yeah I find it. Again
Battle bomber
Man
These people just
Why all the
Get away with you
It's weird
Yep
What are people going to be like
Think you're a liar
Overdue
It would seem that way also I think it would be great if
Hey you're a liar meant something
Consequences for it haha
You'll vote for me in August
So this episode is
First of all the Cuban on stuff
Just outrageous
Yeah and then
Cannot
Except
That we're living in a post
The globalist playing can't be stopped world
And this is the kind of show that he's deciding to do
It is so hard to shake that because once the world has officially ended
It's not going to own the end
Or if it does like we've said before demand an explanation for why
Walk us through this
You said we're all going to die now calm us down by explaining why we're not
Going to die man Oklahoma's going to call into years and be like
Remember when you said that we were all going to die three years ago whatever happened with that did we do
Ebola back
And until then we have website
Horizontal
Emilio Emilio
I hope you all have a dreamy creamy summer
Alex
In color