Alexandra Thurston color
We are
Sit around
There is however
Twist that makes it
That is true that is
Just be to ask
Loot
Let's not talk around until we got a lot to get this
I know a lot about Alex Jones
What what drink did you bring
It's so hot in the shower
Out there you know it
Chicago and broad shoulders
Temperature
It's so hot out I thought we just needed something nice
Crispin refreshing
So I got us Ice Mountain
Sparkling raspberry lime
It's a it's still a novelty beverage
I just got weird
It's like homeopathic
A billion
Fruit-flavored
It was the year of the fizzy beverage
The fizzy water
You're getting line of Ice Mountain sparkling water is a really good
Black cherry I think the raspberry lime is my favorite up them
Anyway
Jordan
Some solid busmark
Some of my other favorite things are our new donate
Welcome aboard
Lucia
Basically
I'd like to give a shout out
I'm a policy wonk
Congratulations
Website
I quickly support the show button
You will become about if you walk
That's an X
Something to be it is
Going to say is that it's cute
Three or four times
Is that is that legal
Score policy roncari
During an investigation deep into the past
Text 12th installment
What the f*** happened to Alex Jones
To get him to like Donald Trump
Rustica
Ran like five more than we ever would have its
Who's going to be at
God it's so bizarre
Today's investigation will be covering the period of
September 19th
Up until
September 28th
And the reason is I have this
Discreet.
A narrative evolve
Over this
. of time
We will discuss exactly what it is
F*** it I'll just tell you
This will lead to a 2 out of context drops
That I'll play immediately after that
The reason that this chunk of time I've separated out into
Do this phase of the investigation
Spoiler alert
But
The pope comes to America
So this
Almost entire week
He is in the middle while he's in the popemobile
He's having a Georg
Exactly what is active recovery
The pope comes to America and Alex Jones
Dispatchers Jakari Jackson
Goodnight
And they just
Like they're following the Grateful Dead
They follow the pope or a country
Have you looked like weird field reports about how globalism is on the March
And they're only bringing the Pope in because they're making their move
So I don't care on tour with the Pope arguing that he's killing
Go to New York Philadelphia
Jakari and David give Littlefield reports from
Visual we would have to
To put up one of those
Like a little
The little plane
From City
Just stay or a little
Infowars only raised $2000000 in their money bomb they can't afford that graphic
I've decided it's not worth our time to
The cover most of the stuff
That Alex Jones has about
Because I can distill it down
To these two out of context drops
Play some up where Alex
I can't help it
He's like a reversed
Whatever ails you
You calling him a devil worshiper will he
Wailord
Here's the other thing that Healthcare Bell
I just been desensitized
Lot of celebrities and stuff is really quite boring
Yeah cool cool cool cool
Spiritual leaders.
Sum up a lot of his positions about the I mean besides calling him by rank
Globalist
Pedophile
I don't think it's all that important I wouldn't be impressed
We are so far and Alex
You know besides the regular he's a globalism pedophile don't worry about it
The LaCroix
Argument
Sofa Dexter it don't even matter
Hate is it someone else
In this
If that's one of these sort of downfalls
This podcast I realized
People haven't listened
Send back to a bunch of them they're going to be like
Why don't you care that he making these awful things
We're looking to outliers
Wikipedia sources cited on eBay
Here's why we're cool with just blowing by pedophile
How's go back to f
Honesty
I'm trying to build that into
The website
Anyway I'm going to go crazy but be there is a bail it's jumping I love his
His
Eclipse RC
Because it is
He's a devil worshiper
And also
You know I don't care
Urgent Care
I'm spending
Hours talking about
Hey Mom the show
Care about the report
See how it's like
Session background
On September 19th
It's a Sunday and David night host
Yes I was
September 20th
So we're already.
With nothing off our back
September 21st rolls around
I've made mention that Alex Jones
In the last
Weeks of Arness
Has been displaying
Many
Pro Putin and
Pro-russia
Opinions
This trend
Does not stop now
Helicopters in air support
Marine forces as well as Russian
Special forces. In Russian
Army Special Forces
This is an exclusive report in English language
It is only in the Russian news as of now
Infowars.com infowars.com
Russian Marines battle Isis in Syria
ISIS militants attack
According to Russian media
Russian Marines class with ISIS
Ensure
Sunday according to Russian media
During the fight
The number to be able to break that down
For you
During the fight
Dad
The peaceniks I'm sorry
Rent-A-Wreck
Chicago
Adorable by Russian military
Nobody's not all these derelictions into like
Within
From
Start2finish has little
Edward
Newsok grade
I would give him a b
That's a good one
Exclusive report
From Russian media
Really careful when you're citing Russian media
Because of their non freedom of the press
Interesting because Putin has a long history of
Jalen killing
You have to be very careful what you believe
It comes out of Russian media
Now I looked into this
And check to the sourcing
On Alex Jones
Article.com
No
That would be too easy
It goes back to
Call.
Is
Ukrainian
Pro-russian
Tabloid
Their most notable for being a
Information
Support of the Prime ministerial
Candidates Victor Yankovic
Who was the
Ukraine
Who has deep ties to Paul manafort
Paid millions of dollars
In order to install GameCube
Empower in Ukraine
Really
Do we have
Can we just handcuff
Just like
Clear like this is bad
Brakes
Because people just
I have this weird assumption that
Deep down humans are good
Like that is a problem
Well at least we know they'll love America
Completely forgot that people hate
Beyonce
Beyond being a tabloid
Propaganda Outlet in Aurora pro-russian interest
In Ukraine
Also in 2011 the papers journals
Threatened
Strike after chief editor
Was controversially fired in his replacement censored certain types of stories
And dictated the journalist
How certain politicians
Public figure
Be covered
Their journalists went on strike
Resolve
They they put into editorial
Board members
The unfavorable coverage for certain politician
This day
From 2011
4 years after the
Has been
Criticize
For their favorable positions towards
And the newspaper has been accused of publishing forged document
Over there
Hahahahahahahahaha
Part of the world
Silly
Is reading a story The
It's pro-putin
Positive Russia coverage
Put out by a Ukrainian pro-russia
Propaganda tabloid
That's the problem
A massive problem
A meeting forms
So much
Of
His his
Starting to take
He's starting to leave
Pretty hard into a pro-putin
Mine
Which is
Bizarre cuz it's happening
Even before he gets on board with
So all this stuff
What's happening in 2017 is like there is no Russian collusion
This is all bulshit
Start to become possibly a thing where he has even more
Hypothetical Allegiance
Benito's to Trump
I'm not saying that that's absolutely
Look a little bit like that
Inasmuch as I believe the Putin
Is ultimately the one who's trying
To take on the global
I think I think if I was going to venture a
Where does his loyalty lie
Candidate
I would say there be Infowars
Kind of like he's more like likes like
That kind of
As opposed to
He actually believed any
I think about Putin
Other than
Is a
Great man
I give you ascribe to the great man
Theory of History
You're like well Putin
Great like undeniable
I think that
You
But I want you to put a pin in it until the end of this episode
Even this next month with more information that I always stare
Fulfilling my role in your life
Russia understands this is about
Warm water
They're on the Mediterranean in Syria
I understand it's part of Russia
Cher's wonderful
But Russia's non-offensive
Russia is not putting cancer viruses are vaccines
Russia is not opening our borders
Russia is not funding Isis
Russia is not
Just pushing world government
Russia is not trying to take my
Russia isn't on the news
What he's saying is the because
Our government has been taken over by the
Globalist
What they aren't doing
There is a bad guy
And Putin is the good guy
Who are the good guys
Syria
He's basically said
Before but
Is the thought that was
Bananas
Situation there
Russia's hugely Pro
Undecided still around
Yasso 100%
Couching in this language
We shouldn't be worried about
That kind of
Don't you think
Like what
What are you saying there is
Russia is
This guy and I know they're not perfect in all that's
But don't worry about that
Worried about our illegitimate government doing all of the
Get to us
Engel ice
He's either hiding
Really trying
It's probably more the prior than the ladder because I think he is hoping
Masquerading
You know all the thought is doing the trying to stand up to
Stewby's Rebels
Doing too
When the reality is
There's a lot of indications that
Beyond just killing his own citizens
Has really been trying to do
Izzat get sunnis
Entirely out of the country
Especially out of
The portions of the country that are most
Important to him
And that's why I refuse
Ud's have been able to
To get out in his high numbers
They have
It's because it's not is totally cool with them just leaving the country
He's trying to get them
It's not as much as
Cleansing on a murderous level although there is
Is ethnic cleansing of his neighborhood
Call
Putin is totally cool with that too
If you get them out it causes
Massive destabilization
So the idea
All they're doing is trying to protect
Their own
Position is
That's what Alex Jones
Believe
In order to make
The thing that is
Very frustrating
He is
Gladwell and they're all
On the same narrative
Isis
Assad
Right when in reality there is that
Who is trying to post fight off ice
Anderson
Because it's
This is margarita
The pr campaign
Through Assad Putin and now Alex is
The rebels are part of
Legitimacy is only within Assad's government
Even though he
He's murdering every
Buddy Heater
And unfortunately as time goes on
As
You know they don't care
It helped and the world seems to indicate that they don't care all that much
You do see
Some of these people who would be on the good side of
They got to go somewhere
The radicalization
To side with Assad
The end the end the only other alternative
If you push
You're going to wind up f****** everybody over
Because
Some kind of fun
I on this
The September
21st episode
Alex Jones has a little interview with
Dear friend
Who we have reservation
But still like quite a bit
Jesse Ventura Jesse Ventura comes on
Whether or not atheism
Iacullo
He accidentally engages him on an argument about church taxation
Oh boy it's all under the auspice
Episodes of the idea
Be taxed
Hideaway
I think it's a good idea for everyone
Our fair share
That's pretty close to his position
Do that
Alex is the losses
Every single point in there are
And it's great
But it's all based on the fact
The pope is about to come
America
Alex wants to
Jesse Ventura
They talked s*** about
Care about the Pope
Clip
I like this ready to go out to see if with a big sign
Atheist for the pulp
Why do you lie
So do I like this post because he said I can go to heaven
That song was that
Oakland 80th Street
I understand that you are amazing I love it I have a chance now
Here's Rock Dam
I believe in science
Proven dark matter they prove another dimension
Get into the genetic engineering realm until my God something made this
Most
What about the guy they just found lately
This latest humanoid
Walked upright they buried their dad
You look like a monkey to me
I think Jesse's High
Alright it's great
Please respond
Humanoid bass monkey
ShopRite
Let's remember something Alex
Whatever man cannot
Explain something
It's real easy then to attributed to God
My only issue. That's not
Atheist don't hate anybody
We don't hate nobody you can believe what you want to believe
If you want to go worship a tree
Horses on the beach
Terrible job regarding anything that Jesse says
Daddy brings in the new archaeological find of the homo
Sapien
Type creature
It sort of invalidates a lot of
Alex's argument
But
Play you don't hear the where's the missing link
Argument too much from
Creationist
No
The Missing Link is the idea that there was one
You don't believe in evolution
F****** go
Just don't believe in evolution anymore
Nonsense
Climate change
Making an assertion
Like
Nothing weird Ukrainian
Tabloid
Breitbart
If possible
Aren't some sort of weird outline
No but I'm saying that your media.
Because he killed all the
Incarcerate
I don't know I'm just saying your medium diet will dictate what you think is normal
Alex Jones
The Vox musication
Yeah I was like news is becoming Infowars light
So this next clip
This is
Really fun for me
Because Alex Jones brings up the idea of
I shouldn't
To pay for anchor baby
Which Jesse Ventura response
Why do I have to pay for church
Surprised
Respond to that
Forgetting
The Jesse Ventura
Used to be the governor of a state
So he knows
It is easy to forget because there's still a part of your brain that goes
Do the governor and the mayor
It's still like
Very intimate knowledge of these sorts of things
Does not to listen to this clip
So fun for me
How badly Alex Jones loses
Why do you keep having
Abortion
Don't force me to pay for the boat
Wow it's the leader of Russia came here would we provide security for it
Not a religious leader
Sports athletes in the world that there probably isn't one country
So I see I understand I haven't been in government Alex
I understand the Pomp and Circumstance and I understand what they do and why they do it
It is called Truth proper respect
If you want to
I got one for you Alex
Why do churches get buy tax-free
Because Congress shall make no law established
Establishment of religion
Congress has no jurisdiction
Same benefits that I get I'm an atheist
I have to pee more
Exploud
Fire Protection
We should all be treated equally
And then you can kill people in all that
Call themselves Church
Quickly to avoid being taxed on anything's churches should be taxed
Caesar album with Caesars
Well that was a question of taxation of the church and he was saying clearly
That that Caesars currency whose face is on it so that's his system so I get what you're saying
Why should searches not play property taxes they receive all the benefits
Call Kamaya question for you
Because
Thomas Jefferson's the left love so much
As an individual you can say or do whatever you want
In government buildings or government finances
And that Congress has no Authority
Respecting an establishment of religion
But I wanted to pause cuz
You keep saying that
Being like this
Kid who read adult books
I didn't understand what he was reading
And then integrate the information
I think he has the same understanding of the First Amendment
Because he keeps
Just rattling that off
Am I misinterpreting what if
Right
Heavy rope
Ability to memorize
Pieces of
Jim just recite them
The free exercise thereof or the establishment of religion
Portion of the First Amendment me
Right it's like it's like
Just memorize it without any ability to
Text realized that
How this applies
Anything's
I bet that's why you're going to lose against
Jesse Ventura
Cuz he's coming to the ring with
Annex.
Hibiscus Jesse's about to give him a body
Nothing to do with taxi number
Services Alex
I'm paying for the illegal
Come on
Illegals get along
How about
Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment
Take it the roof.
If you're going to use it on one hand you have to
Other hand
How come I have to take her claiming you shouldn't have to pay for the pope to be here
More taxes to churches don't
Because there is no more critical of establishment
Houses
Most of them
Fake leaders
Manipulate
The problem is churches now
501 c 3
Symbolism
Corporate standards
Religion difference in a corporation
Local taxes for fire
I don't think that's true
Turn off limits you can't tax religion
Why not
You better make
A lot of stage
Other churches do have to pay the fire fees
Completely destroyed property taxes
Churches don't pay property taxes
I was a governor
Yeah
Alex is really struggling cuz he's going back and forth between like
What what about illegals even though that doesn't
Whataburger
Yeah so he's
Just because
Directions
He's getting his ass beat
Just
Jesse has another Punch coming from the other angle every time
Strongly disagree with
Jesse Ventura
Stance that the media was trying to destroy him with that
Sniper case
That narrative it was pitching months back
But now I love
The First Amendment
We can't text
Brings up like I believe
So forget that part of the First Amendment
That's the poppycock
If you are rattling around
Chances are
You don't know what it actually
You're about to
Something
You probably don't
Defend
You can't
You can criticize me
Just exercised
Free speech
You're dumb you're dumb
Before we get on to some
Some really weird
He brings up
The
We'll see
Religions as well
It's not just a Christian
Brother religious
You got it setup on Horus
What about Horace
Jesus 7700 years before Jesus
Well I do know that
If the entire same biography of a guy on earth
Egyptian
I just saying
The death rattle people with the same
So that's his way of dismissing like historical facts
Zeitgeist
All right right
Right price
I just love the humor of like
I know the guy behind the soundboard was like
Alright Jesse brought porous
Long pause
Does Alex respond what are you talkin about
Long
We're going to break
Alex's. Nothing I got to get him out of this hole
I think that's
Appropriately
Unlikely
Yeah absolutely
In 2015 is trying to
You figure out where Alex
To supporting Trump
Pause we got to bring up whenever he brings up something about Trump
Here is Alex
Explaining that he still loves Rand Paul
More pro-russia
Another article all Republican presidential candidates
Not supported
Little bit confused
But if you watch that debate
Last Wednesday
But
It's just crazy
About Vladimir Putin
President of Italy
Asurion claim
10 years old
Ukraine probe Ford
And this is a stunt
Will
Wii shop
Bottle of wine with
What's Purdue's
Racha fully controls
And fully controlled there an argument there why
That there.
A bottle of wine
Epr stock
Is promoting local Ukrainian wine
We're here with the farmers
Down to the ultimate
Fox News
Associated Press
I put in the Civil War
They're bombing and shelling all over the country
Small area
Small area admittedly
Worth billions of dollars
It wasn't a big resources
But then the other thing
Just believe that everything
Publix
Their goal is trying to make countries fight each other
Conception they are there globally
Mego destabilize
In order to attack
Crazy or destabilize Ukraine
Retake it over
Maybe I don't know
It's great
I didn't
Understand the particulars of the Elders of Zion plan and I really don't
Globalist.
I think it's fascinating Alex
Is talking about
You know his feelings about
About
Rand Paul and Trump
Have a thought and get sidetracked
Into talking about
Defending Putin
And weird
I don't think if I was earlier
About that. Because Rand Paul needs to
To be visually more aggressive
Until you started to think about
I started to think about the way leaders
Present themself
And that got him onto things
How strong
But also
Even know that
Story
It was a very minor
Hairstory
Yeah
These readings are Ukrainian
Yep I'm going to
100%
Pro Rush
Russian media
Also any time Berlusconi is involved
You know
There's going to be a rampant theft of money
Going to be drinking and they probably thought somebody afterwards
Ain't nobody
Operator in history
Italy has a fascist history where this welcoming he wasn't he wasn't still present
He'd already been kicked out for all the crying but he's super-rich
The crime
Bright
Alex Jones
By the
Police
Oh and you need to hear about
Before you do Alex
Do not make this very clear
This happened
P2000
I believe
The story he's referencing happened
In 2000
Year-old news
Right
Just tell you
He's lying
And I will tell you the truth after this
Horrendous display
Fake emoji
This is what needs to be done
People going into men's barbershop Shane cut my hair
Find
B*******
Define
Hey lady we cut men's hair
This goes back to an area that we talked about in the past episode 1
Just Grants Pass
That's clearly not discrimination
You do
As a business
At this point
At this point Alex Jones is looking at his phone and taking
Just that are on right now
There's so much happening
That probably comes back
Hurt
Hard
So hard
Just to see
Videos
9/11 the road to tyranny that I made
14 years ago
13 years ago plus
Quick work
Call Michael planned 9/11
No criminal record
Weather
And they
This Is War
Just freaked out this crazy
And then they flip out from there
And get the better truck
Then they fire department Constitution
Maybe that's what she talks about how she's got a constitution
Maybe what she means
Origami
Here guys that have sworn an oath
To protect and defend the Constitution
Decoration
It's all Foundation
All the squad car video
Oprah whatever she's one of them extremists like the clan or something
Balls
You got to come to tell you that
Sound
It's interesting
Alex
Is
So full of s***
Public Storage
Read it off
No other information
There's no context for that at all
Substitution
Constitutional
Abby Newman who was pulled over in traffic
Wingstop in 2000
West Virginia
She was driving without a license
Researched
Her car was searched
I don't know about the the official record
Containing any reference
Thanks to a constitution
Or Patriots
But the official record
That you had hollow point bullets
Cop killer bullets
Institution
There's a way you can either have
It's the same stuff
G80 bread one you know how to use the other
You know what I'm saying
She decided to represent her
Did not go well
She accused the officers of using
Excessive force
Ron Wright
The video tape her being verbally
The police
Add when they end up handcuffing her she doesn't
Make any complaint
There's no real grounds for argumentative
We're treating her roughly or anything like that
Something is did find hollow point illegal bullets
In her car
Those are used
To kill cops
To kill armored animals
I forgot that
Armadillos are everywhere West Virginia
I forgot also deer often
Stood up
Cops are being stupid
An extremist
She is very clearly a sovereign
She is a member of the anti-government group
On the fact that I'm reading this offer from roanoke.com
Article about her trial
She is
Got to be good
I love it when the Sovereign citizens go to court
She has also argued in the past that she believes the United
It states is controlled by the Federal Reserve Bank
Which is run by Freemason
I'm to obey the British Monarchy
She is also said makes Federal Reserve Bank uses social
Security numbers
And birth certificate
Certificate of ownership of America
Are there it is during an interview
Never get arrested again
No
Use a part of a very scary Fringe right-wing
Organization
Loosely-knit organization
And how I know that
Pictures of sovereignty
Is
That she believes that the Federal Reserve Bank uses social
Security numbers in birth certificate
A certificate of ownership
That's the one we talked about earlier with maritime law
Security numbers that are created are in order to
To create debt
Your name
Corporate
Identity as opposed to your
Play it's a very big part of the sovereign
Know that that's a Roman font
You should have used New Republic fought something along those lines
Complete lie I made it to lie about 15 years in the past
The police don't even understand
Do they hate the Constitution
No they hate people have hollow tip bullets
Driving around without a license
I don't believe the government has any Authority very reasonable.
Cuz cops
I've been killed by a lot of sovereignty
You took me on a little bit of an emotional rollercoaster their O'Connor on her side for a little bit I don't like cops either
Then you kept going the holla tip points
Not great not great
I'll never be arrested again
Another further indication
Anytime Alex Jones does one of these voices
Completely line
Whenever he characterizes
So
Even have the balls to be like
I'm not I'm not making
The sound
Like it there
Get this
You think that's so disrespectful to truth
And integrity
And journalism
Right you're not ready for what to happen
Alex Jones has
Conceptually my favorite guest of all time
I don't like this guy at all but the idea that he's on the show
Is awesome
Pods are already hitting public roads
That's right ladies and gentlemen and sex reassessment is
Company benefit
And push for equality
For further confuse
Moving towards an asexual system
Where you know what there's going to be no sexualism there can be no culture of any type everything's just Gray
Or you're offending someone else
Who would have ever thought
Bloomberg business
Actually
Everyone
Tell rather or a woman
Somebody else's
Tolerant
In the future.
Stop right there bro
We are go out and
Personal trainer
Every few years
Takes off for a few days
Perfume in Eastern Europe
Wizzy
Here in just a moment Alex Jones has his personal trainer on as a guest
He was personally training him and
Tropica
Messing around SouthPark
So this guy is a
Like Alex Jones
The dick but this guy brings out so much dick ashness and Alex Jones
Audio of their training
Is not getting healthier
He doesn't look good so they can't be
We doing a good job
They have to be doing this is growing out so hard about bigotry
It got to be
Levitate
Cuz you know you
You start getting a little bit of exercise in you
Testosterone kicks in
And I was like oh God
In their interview just bench press that much
Muslim just put him out
The entire interview is essentially about how when he was overseas
Alex Jones personal trainers
A lady with some
Kids grass
Convert money
Outside of a hotel
This lady's husband
Who is threatening to jump
If I don't get enough money
Cuz they can't afford
So this is
Terrible especially when you read the stories now
Note
Right
Back to get help
Jesus nut
The other thing is I believe
Emily Watson
But
There a lot of scams
The people do
People who are in Desperate situations are going to run cons
Not really
Obliged
On immigrants
Not what they should be doing is right
Absolutely
Billion dollars that way paint this
Just proves
You can't f******
Rusty's brown people
There's run these Huggins
Considering like
This is a really
Stream version
Now he's probably not going to do it but
Suicide into the equation
That's much different than like running around in like Chiclets
Yeah
I'd like these are the two things you
What else is there
Hey there's a
Is the topic itself
I hear things like this and I think
About how Saturday
That our world is in
The situation
Where a lot of people are forced
To use
No
Dishonest means in order to make money out of desperation
It is a bummer
Meanwhile Alex
And his bro out
Physical personal trainer
Slightly different angle on
That's regrettable that's what the gypsies Ono
Horticulture
Alright let's start with the self self
Your culture Alex
Analista anti-government
Hey man
The gypsies aren't the one being racist to black people in
The gypsies aren't the one who enslave them the one who did the Tuskegee experiments
Turn all of this
Also
Gypsy Romani I'm not making that are
Well I mean it is a bad culture and we should take all of them out of our country it's not great
It's not a great culture that Alex lives in
But be that as it may
Luke know it's within his right to
Unstoppable
I don't understand how he doesn't get the
The same thing that protect
He's sort of right
2xist
Is what percent
Everyone's rights
Because they don't
Just don't
Understand
What I mean
What was the phrase that
Ventura
If it if it works for one-handed Axolotl health
Trump tweeting out like it should always be popular vote
Goddamnit you idiot
Do you know
Stand for a sec
How this should act
Right and that will suck you over
In the long run
So
Great
You fuking idiot
Either
Knox problems or made-up one
Lights down for this next clip
Because
Trainer
Get into
Oh God
I don't know
It's pretty bad it's gone
It's one of the more misogynist
List of things I've heard on it program
Who is Rio Grande
Alright Mike
I think they fix their wrist
Which makes it worse
Riley's
Active women are so that we know
Correct
I was very good
Continue
Absolutely
That's their territory
Most understand are lesbians
Like a
Elephant seal
How's the weather
Elephant seals
That's always here
Want to do a elephant
First of all
Ugly women
Is his way of life
How do I get
Speculating on this s*** right there
Effects of European women
Play the purse
I hope
Why didn't he get kidnapped in a taken situation
And his wife was like
Yeah
You got them
You keep you guys keep
The only thing I respect about him is it Alex's like you want to do an elephant seal impression
Now
That's what they wanted
You're right that's an absurd idea
Feminist power rank
World 3 million 240
I'll never break into
The top Melly and I'll tell you that
That that is
That all reason
Then Alex's they want a harem of women that they don't
What dudes getting into
Elephant
Alex Jones is argument that no I'm muscling in
That's still better in terms of Art
Him saying like
I should be the one who dominates
Exactly I'm the only one who can dominate these women
Exactly
No matter what
It's still looking at women is
So f******
Who f****** wrong
It's
Justice idea
He's just projecting
His
Bulshit on two lesbians at match
Like a male
Reminded that she's not
Me like that
Thing is what he would do until Montopolis situations like
I would try and get a harem
Basically
Erotic
His personal life is off-limits that's out there
His new wife
Narada married for a little while
Music
It's possible
Not to slander
Babies
A little while
Coverage of September 20th
And we'll move along
September 22nd
Those two guys
Is Talking Tom bad
That's really bad
Like
Like all the stuff about the actual immigrants
How do you saw
I mean we can distill it into one sentence
We did but
Just started like
You know these are untrustworthy
These two guys together
That kind of thing
The ark
Give me the Trump immediately got out of after
The grabbing by the
It's just locker room talk I thought
There's no way that anybody
Apparently dumb
And that is exactly what
Apparently this happy
Totally
Just not with
The people we hang out with we're just in this weird bubble up
Yeah the other thing I want to point out his nose
Maybe this is a minor thing for me to be pointing out but
Dude
This is the big lie
This isn't some
Podcast
You're having your personal trainer is a guess
Come with it man
Would you
A billion people you reach
Every month
100 million
Annex
Expert you decide to
To get your f****** personal trainers
It's the same thing like how many comedy shows have you been to where it's like all that guy did not get booked
Cuz he was good
Forgot because he's friends
That doesn't happen in the big leagues
I don't think JFL is booking based on friendship
Disagree
If you can help
Agent agent says friendship
The 22nd
Cast on the 22nd
Sing this personal trainer that's for sure
I don't like him
Personal trainer
Please give us any tip
Nothing to do with your delzer quads
God dammit
Introducing
For live broadcasting worldwide
We do have some guests joining us for about 30 minutes
At the start of the next hour diamond and silk
Very entertaining and informative
Is Donald Trump in election
2016 for 30 minutes
A1c
Two girls know I don't think that's the case
But it is indicative
In some ways
Because there's no reason to have these two ladies on your show
Unless you just want someone
Parroting
Donald Trump propaganda
Whatever they want to do but
For Trump he's going to bring our jobs back
Why do they go viral black ladies sitting in front of her like webcam
Just like doing like you said it
Like that sort of stuff
But it's
Tour Trump
And the reason it goes viral is because it's so against
Type you expect to hear like Hillbillies endorsing Trump
Black Pastor it's
Like this legitimizes everything that we say if you black ladies are on our side we can be as races
Just as we want
And I don't know I don't know what they're
Story is I don't know what their history is
I do know that other stuff I've seen
Scene of them they don't really have
What appears to be a nuance
Position
On the issues
I'm not
It's difficult for me to
Encapsulate what I mean
The real name
From what I can tell basically they just repeat
Pro Trump
Was their claim to fame
The interview that Alex Jones end up having is not
Substantive
In any way
And we'll get to one clip of it a little bit later
But before we do is important
The 22nd Alex Jones
Finally found
It recently
He still hasn't
It recently came out inside the salon article
Todd Nickerson
The article where the guy
Here comes out
Explains that
But he has
Attractions
The children but would never act up
And Alex Jones has been saying that they're going to try and mainstream pedophilia
I tried making it with normal deck
Pedophilia
You are a pedophobe
Text makes a f****** meal out of this article and
Back to Salon
I saw this last night
Has a story out on it today
Salon I don't need to understand
Monster
And it's begun
Show it
When she was the bring her back up
Surgeon General
Weirdos
They can do anything for sanostee Elations you name it
Acceleration
Whatever this is
Stupid
That whole thing
Because
Reading that
Was such a
A complex
Scituate
Very much so
For somebody who's trying to understand people
Just like
Practically reduce
Pedophilia
What was like what we talked about
The end result that we want his life people being killed by gun pedophiles
What we want is less children being abused
And if the route to that end goal that we
Is a
Further understanding of where does the
Just come from what is going on in psychology of the
People who are attracted
The children
Then it was you
Have some understanding
That doesn't mean
Liking it
Accepting it doesn't mean memes
Streaming it
What it does mean
Look at the end goal is not well at by murdering everybody who has
Attractions to children will be everyone going underground
You seen that people have
You know c*********
It's like just like the guy said in the article it's like
I can't
Tell
My therapist
I can't tell
My psyche
Because there
Well
They don't have an obligation to report just
But you have
Do that
Ant butt
That they won't because of
Touch This
Lusteric
Like f******
No you're like all of these
Complicated thing and that's all
If you're on the right
Nope Temple
It goes up your shoot it down
Easy marinade for them to push it so perfectly into fear-mongering and other ring
I get it I don't think that Alex Jones is a
Sleep idiot
For being a verse
But I think he's being incredibly dishonest by saying
That it is part of a push to mainstream
Pedophilia and then beyond that the things that uses
To bolster that is saying that
Pedophiles are recognized non-governmental organization with the UN
There was the gay advocacy
The group that in the early 80s
Included NAMBLA
The gay rights organization became a recognized
Remember
Advisory member of the UN
I meant came out
So they got kicked out
Never been apart of advisory committees
When it's
What's a complete lie that he knows no one's going to look into
Then beyond that we see him doing a voice
Was Jocelyn Elders witch
Help should tell you he's lying
He absolutely is Jocelyn elders just said
That in terms of discouraging
Dangerous behaviors maybe children should learn about masturbating
Maybe it's not saying hey
Kojak off those kids
She didn't say that
And Alex
2 absolute
Define
To bolster his argument
He's not willing to wrestle with the nuance
What's the problem in that suit
Everybody who
Capable of reason
Is paralyzed
Right cuz there's so much
Kind of steps
Is if you're on the right
You just get to
You just get so f******
Put your ears back and go Whole Hog
Right
For like
The argument
I can have with him is just
It's really complicated
There's any way you'll ever understand it if I
The answer there's no clear answer
If you if you think he's done a bad job so far
Let's listen to this next clip
About the article
Haven't
Well
I guess technically dozen
Salon
Todd
Nickerson says this
Isn't he
Maybe you should be on the cover of
Sports Illustrated
ESPN award
He should be then he would be
Be hurt by a lot of pain
Subconsciously implant
Singing his audiences
Pedophiles
And Caitlyn Jenner
He's trying
To create a soft metal Bridge
Pedophiles and transgender
Absolutely doing that
Intentional I did not
It's not intentional in the sense that he meant his mind works
Because
Gay people are pet
Like that hole.
Well
Right there
Transgender people with pattern
Yeah
Atrocious
The beaver
I'm a pedophile
But not a monster
I'm attracted to children
Before judging me harshly
Would you be willing to listen
And this is exactly
The homosexual Lobby started back in the forties and fifties with articles in Reader's Digest
Jackson
Absolutely
Homosexual
Falls are two different categories
Job fair
Groups and labels
You're still close
New world
World Revisited UNESCO worldwide treaty Arrangement agreement
That's a long name
So they've chosen
Solution of women
What is a major
Back to reality oh there goes gravity
Batman Batman
So that's nonsense
I love that
YYZ
Dominate the world
Screw 1988
That's a bunch of stuff they're hoping that it sounds official
What the f*** are you talking about this is all nonsense
It's an
The factory where he goes
He's like
They're trying to attack masculinity and femininity
Your takeaway from this article
This far away from
But that's nowhere near it
What are you doing
Well
But just from a position of like
Weird
Alex
To point out
Was trying to bolster his claims
The time
Baby
With the inter
With Adventure interviews
Pac-Man
Really high-end
My ass are better or maybe it's the one time a year
He gets to the
Here's something real dicey
Dusky foundation with supplying children
So this is one of Alex's bigoted
What was one of his big arguments
That you only talked about
Procure
And stuff like that Boys Town situation that happened
Where there was
5 definitively proven
That people were
Taking these underprivileged
And senators were doing
Doing s*** with
Remember that story a conspiracy of Silence
F***** up super f***** up
Such has not been at all
As it relates to
Sandusky
Can bile
Some like that his organization that was
Yeah it was trying to get kids play sports with obviously it was a way for him
Intergroup
There are a lot of problems
Procure there's no indication of that all done
And like past investigation
As in the case of the Boys Town situation that was what was going on
Unfriended
Looked into it tried to find
Where is this stuff coming from
And I think I figured it out
That is better allegations
Sandusky was pimping out children come from a radio host named bark
Who actually Larry Nichols with a mustache
2011 said quote
I can give you a rumor and I can give you something I see
Think might happen
I hear there's a rumor that there may be more shocking
Men from the Second Mile Foundation
Cuz this is gross
I won't use the language I can
Dusky and the Second Mile were pimping out youngboy's to Rich donors
That was being investigated by two
Two prominent columnist
Even as I
How does that sound
Start
I have a rumor
So when he was pressed on it
You said that
I normally up or giving rumors Creedence
But the whole Sandusky
Scandal started out as a rumor
It gets deeper and more disgusting all the time
It's a rumor
It's a rumor that some radio host put out into the world
Then Alex Jones has been peddling
His entire worldview about these pedophiles and the renfield's and Dracula's
Basically on this
This is pizzagate
This is that level of like internet Maberry
Did like I'm not trying to defend Sandusky or Joe Paterno or anybody involved
They're all f****** awful monsters
Indications of come out to Joe Paterno
Who's wear this dating back to the 70s
Aldi
Journalism
To try and create this
Broader spiderweb
What's going on
Just one monster who is looking for his own
So
In terms of official information
Maybe maybe there is something out there that I'm unaware of
You feel free to tell me
But from what I've been able to glean
The idea that there was
Gorman
And pimping out of these children
Goes back to rumors
Like Alex
Do you got to do better
You got to do better
I understand that you want to Launch
Conspiracy theories
Are you want people to
I distrust
Mainstream narrative
Can't
Can't just do this
You really sensationalize a real problem
To the point where you lose your credibility about that real problem
The problem on
Defeating his
You do have
Take
Sandusky side
Something you know
He was a monster but at least he didn't
Cure kids like
That I'm not I'm not willing
Like Sandusky is not going to come for libel
No that's not going to happen
Even though he could win
But you don't have the responsibility to prove an egg
Corprew videos
Children
Prove it he did
See the headline
Find Sandusky
Sue's Alex
What's for lunch
Under stressed
Like that
Terrific
Nobody wants you to even be alive
We definitely don't want you to win
That's Tuff
I'm glad never happened because I don't want to hear I don't want to deal with that
Seriously
Nobody nobody
Wants to be in that position
This leaves
Alright Alex Jones
I don't know
Out
Angry
All right beside you doing
The fight with me I don't have a gun
And then you can
Blood
It's right spirit
Filthy
That goes for those Medical
Alright I kind of agree with that being the rage impulse that you would have
You said he was a Cuban
I get it
I get the idea
Like
What you call a crime of passion
Where you find your kid being abused
I understand that
I get it
I get that reaction
I don't get out
Equating it with vaccines
I think that's troubling
The idea that these are medical perverts who want to shoot up your children cry
I hate that I hate that like
It's easy to beat some of the brain
You should be attracted to help children and build them up and nurture them
What's all coming
Cheetah fobs
Super Mario Brothers
Owlfly the armies
I got to say don't break Super Mario in today
Is nearing the end of the ramp exit music just
So
That's weird
You don't like violence
Alex Jones
I just want to kill somebody and they don't want to be in trouble for throwing punches in the air in like
It's crazy
But also I want to say that I
I'm starting to
Figure out Alex Jones
Pattern
In terms of
About three of them about to get into
Yeah
I think we can find his cycle
I think we can based on a couple past month
I think he is about
Like a 40 day cycle
Okay haven't figured out exactly anymore
Cuz one of them falls on when he was in a vacation
Might have been freaking out of Europe
Two months I'm about two and a half on something along those lines
We're going to be able to
Yeah the cycles
So Alex engaged in what is now a couple of very violent diatribes about
Files and Harry wants to be
People's brains
I am poor you to listen to this next clip
Where he's respond
Going to a caller talking about other civilizations
Having very low age of can
Any old world culture
That they're a woman at that point
Western culture we started arresting development to push it back 2018 or whatever
I personally think sticking probably
The proper age
Haha he thinks proper age of
Consent is sick
May I offer this
The age of consent in Texas
Is 17
So that was Jones's actually advocating is dropping
Of the age of consent
There are a lot of
Get hard
Just fake it
Mathematically art
There are a number of states
17 or 18
And that doesn't even get into the idea that there are different age of consent laws
Heterosexual and homosexual sex
Is very weird
Age of consent
Lost forever
Write this whole thing is f*****
There are very few safe there are couple that is 15 or 40
Urges why
Well is there places where you can
Be legally married at
And that's fine
Even though you're still below the age of
Where Alex is
Alex
Sixteen-year-old with Pump It Up
No problem
But largely would you be advocating is a drop
Of the age of consent
Do you have this whole
Episode where he's like
I do not acting pedophiles are lying and I want to beat their brains and it was just going to call me a pedophobe
Pedophiles
He doesn't he doesn't see that these two things are sort of working against each other
Philosophical
Hard Eight
Who is that
Kind of suggest
That
Western culture
Did it on purpose
Intentionally read the language develop
Not realizing it sort of a
Pristine byproduct of the Agricultural Revolution that
What argument is that
It was
That's fine
That it was 13 or 15 back then
Oh
Decided
I don't know I don't want to unpack it I want to get out of this segment of the show
Get it off
Scrapbook move out of this
These gross let's move out of this
And move back to what is becoming
Credibly familiar territory where a little bit later on the 22nd
Alex Jones
Now the news
Even say it.
The world stage released
Okay
What
Russia
Bulshit
Everyday
Alto sax
You're saying that you've
I think Al Qaeda used
Attacks
Instead of a sod
That is so
Tenaya love
Reality from
Russian media sources like the ones we discussed
He also takes it from there was that ambassador
Suspicious
Chemical weapons attacks
Sade is a good guy
Alright I don't think that you were an unbiased
Now that's
What's that the British guy
Look I mean
Wentworth
Seeing mountains of evidence
We're the Bad Guys
And Putin is a good guy
Alex
One thing to say to you
Lovett or leave it
Seems very in America
So as we mentioned earlier Alex
I got this interview with diamond and silk
Yep and here is a little excerpt
Eyewear Alex Jones doesn't want to deal with the issues
And what's the
He wants to inject
Misogyny
Answer this interview guy
McDonald's
What everybody
Forget about this media bias missing his propaganda attention
Continue continue
So you get a little sense of like
Have sex with only reason that women have
Right
He's be bringing it up twice
Actually
Are you hot for truck
No I'm not
I'm not saying isn't any dismissive way they really just
Just keep saying we stopped for Trump
JustFab
Right you got to do
Is that excited
I got none
There's one lady who says all this stuff
The next president
I meant the other lady just go that's right
It's just he has them on
To basically
B-black and temperature
Do both the same time
Alex Jones having them on as a guest indicates to me that he recognizes that maybe they
But he doesn't have maybe
We can tap into it
Legitimizes it to his old white
So they don't feel
Guilt right it's all about knots
Feeling guilty
Black women
Hey I know
All of these millions and millions of black people are telling me this
But look we've got some too so it's not a racial
My position is
But he's already
Behind-the-scenes or subconsciously decide
He's going to jump into
Camp
Aztec balloons
He's doing them is like putting his toe into the water you are
Show pro-trump
On and knowing that you're not going to
Beyond your platform
Some questions but they're more like
Softball
Little meatballs
Why do you support Trump is just allowing them to say we
We need to get him into the White House to bring
Prosperity
How is he going to be
Indication that he's already preparing his audience for the
Natural twist
Because
I think you got a bunch of money at the money bomb
Here is Alex Jones invalidating things he said about Trump in the past
Because I don't want people
Such incredible
In this country it makes my head spin
Get upset if somebody
Is better at sports
Personal
But this class Warfare class
What are the positive things
At least she's self-made he's got his problems but at least she's self-made it okay to be successful again
Examples
For children to believe they can become successful
Because more rich people
Market means more wealth
Everybody else more economy
Right
That's how we gotten this message
But bye-bye
But the reason that Alex Jones think
The Trump is self-made
Is because they have similar Baxter
In the sense that Trump
Got bailed out over and over again by his super-rich father has a Empire that
Money laundering
Businesses
Only as a career because his dad bought him a radio show when he was younger by being his
First
Sponsor
I'm giving him the
Perception of being self-made
Building up all this stuff
And now he has an Empire that's built on fake pills
Feel like there is
Pretty similar
Trajectory between the two of them
Which I can understand Alex Jones
Sort of seeing and relating to and becoming enamored with
Time
Alex in the
Has said that Trump is
Con man
He said the team is a frontman working source of on the East Coast
Mobbed up
He doesn't think that you're a self-made
Know that stuff that you said already on his show
Within the last couple months
What's before this
Complete
Doubling back
Contradicting
Things he said
In the past
And to me that is an indication
Alex has
Something has changed
It's not just I'm not going to talk s*** about Trump anymore it's I'm going to lie
Where is I said what I asked
Actually thought
Maybe
It is just
What's the fact that
That's been repeated some
Possible
Like Alex is a varied suggest
Edible hypnotizable Young
That's true
That was
That's what it was
Was put into
Every piece
Every single thing
Even if it's over even if it's like a CNN thing it's like
Trump is a self-made billionaire and all of this very good business
Which is the narrative that they
Pushing yeah that's true
Is because they want a good businessman in the White House
I was just curious
Repeat it over and over again
From
Does like bright
I may be a pro Russia
Dumb
So maybe
He can only hold
Austin amount of information
Tough Enough
You just push the old out
It's possible I don't know I have my assertion you have yours
We'll see what bear is out over the course of
You know I'm yours is an anyway what we learn
2 days from now
But
Cuz it doesn't matter Alex just lies about
Cole
He says that every
Do you see those buildings belong there scrubbers
Everything is getting
Scrub like as if they're taking all of the
Yeah
Can you put in 50
She sent through the cycle
If you look into it at all
Clean Coal stuff is a myth
All of the attempt
Soap making Clean Coal
Power plants are wildly over budget
Take much longer
To create
But it is not as
The idea that every plant
Thought cool plant
Burning clean and everything
It's right
Alex
Have to know that's not
Nicotine is good for you
Play good point or Mike Pence
God
So this next we have we have gone back to when they wanted to go back
I don't think anybody likes it
Alex Jones
The end of the show
On the 22nd
Get a call from a guy
A roller coaster with a
Ending of the call he starts pointing out
Some very true thing
Such as
Donald Trump's connection with jeffry Epps
Noted pedophile billionaire Jeffrey Epstein
Also talked about
The real estate
The organization that
Is clearly involved with Trump and Russian mob
Right and also the setting
Then the call takes a weird turn and I can no longer support
Cereal
Thank you there's an old expression
Be careful of what you pray for you might just get it I think that's what we're heading for with Trump
You can judge a man by Jericho by the company he keeps I'm sure you would agree with that
And
Jeffrey Epstein I'm sure your listeners know who this man is he's a convicted
Sex offender
Kept company with the likes of Donald
Trump Bill Clinton
Alan dershowitz
An aircraft called the Lolita Express
727 all around the world
Implicated
And it's ekstrand child sex ring slavery
Investigation
Donald Trump business partner the gentleman at a Consortium with bayrock Group LLC a property
Griffith parking with the Trump organization to build a Soho Hotel condominium
Trump Tower in Florida
He was arrested by turkey
YouTube down
Honor in helicopters
Anna yacht
In the Mediterranean and found underage workers on board
So these are the types of people that Donald Trump
Rubbing elbows with so high I don't endorse
By the Ron Paul
Rand Paul
Any politician
I think they're all corrupt to to the
To the eyeball
Alright
So I didn't quite like that last part as much
I'm still here
Here is where it takes
Turn
This is
Jarring
Forest people
Trying to
Judge your character Alex
With mainstream media like
Salon and and mainstream media
Really think
Builderall again control by
What I refer to is dying as Jew media
And the same thing with politics
You looking
Politics
U.s. Congress
It's primarily run by the American Israel a political action committee
Butler
Famous pedir
Detroit Technologies concern
Boeing has an uninterruptible autopilot switch on their crap with me
It makes me think about
Both those aircraft
Jewish Mafia That's this leftist
Amerifactors
But shark
Are the Big 4 lobbies Implanon
This is why
People like David Duke
And people who are anti-Semitic
Count Alex Jones
This guy just said
These attacks against you
I Am Salon in these places
Are just a Zionist
And Alex doesn't push back on that at all
Mafias
There is no difference
Between
Forces of anti-semitism
Alex Jones
Wow
I don't like.
Because of the
Another valid point
The f******
Weirdo a******
ABC medical oriented
Jeffrey Epstein
They had a history together
I'd like you can't get Alex now only talk about the bill
Whenever he talks about apps
Clinton completely forgetting about that being a piece of
Been talking about bayrock and Soho hotel and Felix Sater
These are legitimate
Pieces
And I think will become
A very ugly investigation
Don't become public
Near future
Alex with himself was talking about earlier
Just like
Entirely by blaming
Jews for everything
Really what he believes 22 Thunder
A different Banner
We're going to skip the 23rd
Cuz I just don't care
David Knight report he's out on the field
Covering the Pope
And then the 23rd is largely just there's a lot of
Please just railing on the pope saying he's a devil
And all this
He fakes crying at one point for the plight of the poor people
In the world which is really it
It's pretty funny but not necessary to go over
Get along interview with Peter Schiff
The Economist
Whose dad is in prison for not paying taxes
Never pay tax
They talked about how about his dad
The political prison
And they never bring up the fact that you didn't
On millions of dollars
And that
He got a lot of other people arrest
I said because he told them to do the same thing
Copying
Constitutional
If you hollow tips
Isaac human I feel bad
For eyes
Peter Schiff
And having to deal with his dad being sick
In prison that is a human
Thing that is very sad
At the same time
Excuse him going on Alex Jones Show
And using his dad sickness in prison
And
Clear crime
Their propaganda
Is he trying to get money
No
He's trying to get the
Presents
System investigated
He's trying to cause all kinds of like who did
Couple times
Tell if he's joking about breaking
I can't quite tell
It's a fine line
Beyond
The California drought is a false flag while he does want to put them
I'm into a private
That's the
He doesn't like
Let me know
We're in line with his
You just crossed over
Missing the California
Because they're using other weapons
I also
There's some talk about other weapons
Alex Jones
Two things that are wild one is Mel Gibson
Was that up
Because
How to get setup
Somebody up for an anti-semitic rant
That's after being pulled over for drunk driving
Okay but the reason is because he drinks anti-semite
The reason that they'd set him up as cuz he's critical of the Vatican
All right that's why
Engage with that
The Germany was the victim in World War I
Which
If you're talking about like
Just a mainstream population
Maybe
But if you're talking about the country as a whole
And the government
Nothing much
That's not good
Don't smell good
I don't like that
He's a very short step away from being Holocaust
No we already went over in the last episode
B******* right there
Yeah that's bad enough
So
That's all
Family do have another Field Report with Dakari Jackson
It would be so boring
They pieced together cuz they're the other person
Take me to
My phone glad you raised $2000000 for this Alex you're doing great work
So we get onto the 24th
And I want to know what there
Do they have separate
They are they camping I want them
Easy Rider but the most boring version of
Do I wanted
Give you a treat
Because a lot of this is not very pleasant
And so this next clip is my gift
Do you
Is one of the
Few times that Indies rebroadcast episodes I'm able to get access to
They keep him some karaoke
Fortune
The globalist want inverted power over people
Guitar
As well
Father stop it right now I apologize
Love love
We're not doing a good enough job pointing out how often he apologizes whatever he does anything fun
I'm sorry I was interesting for a minute
Just great and I want to be totally clear
Turn up the audio that was the person on the board
Studio
The parkway is not talking
Is in the song
I'm telling you this week is all Pope
Is all anti-popes.
That's mostly what he's into
He talked about how the pope came
A young hispanic girl came up
The pope and gave him a letter
Urgent
Clemency about
Obviously it's probably a photo op
Even
We don't think the
Necessarily that is
A genuine moment
Beautiful
And I don't think it's something nefarious
The globalist
Open borders
Pope is in on it or what have you
It's interesting to note that he prefers the
The Nazi play
And they argue that the only reason that he got out and we got this Pope Francis in
Is because
Pedophile blackmail
Sebastian
Sagarika is going to be the
The next Pope after
Did the cool Pope I would assume so gently Nazi lineage
Beyonce
He talks about how Edward Snowden
Sekiro and Trump
Is wrong about I appreciate that I withhold judgment generally agree
You also talk about hubby kid who came to school
Remember that
Is a false flag by man
It wasn't a bomb
I knew it wasn't
But he made it look like a bomb so the government but he made it look like a bomb so that the police
Would have to get involved
I meant to become this PR stunt that people could
With this publicity
Stop
It's bad plan and it's a long way to go
Easier ways
To demonize the anti-immigrant
Such as by using their
Finding words
Yeah I also
Alex Jones
Claims
But he's going
On the show
We talked about it all the time and I'm going to lay it out
Do you have a guess
After the end of the show named Wiggins
And because it is the lamest f****** interview I've ever
Is all the doctors no sources
I've stopped there's just vague mention
The chemtrails
It's already discussed course
Right
When he's like
I'm going to prove it
And then does nothing
He claimed the global weather weapons
Beer and the Destroyer
We were fighting beetle
Mix up Alex Jones bullshittin someone else's
But that's Robert know that wasn't even Robert
Source
Notize Vietnam vet
So now wait we get to this
Of his
Attacking the Pope
Has an interview with Leo zagami
Visit range time I believe
First time he's actually been on
Right are we talked about him before because of
I don't know why we
Talk about him
Some other
Do that
But that's in present day
That's in 2070
Oh that's
Yeah so this is
It was where my brain was having a disc
Difficult time
Enforcement
Why
We need our continent that is that Alex Jones is wrong in both Time Low
This is why h.g. Wells had some
Struggles later on
Science fiction is just the fantasies
Anyway
Captain Alex Jones quote
Fantastic
Shakespeare
Leo zagami on
Quote
Is really difficult
And that is what he saying everything that he has
Everything he knows
Is document
He isn't Vatican Insider
As we can get these documents that are very difficult
Which is very Canby
Wait
They are
Have them
Okay
Such an Insider
Play this clip
Leo zagami
Beginnings
Of his waking up to the truth
Am I believe if you listen carefully
You'll see that maybe he's not on the level
And maybe Alex Jones just believe people who agree with what he believes in and have an axe
I think
But there's something there's a little credibility that Leo zagami gets because there's
Tell us about yourself how you woke up
Then
Are they getting stronger
Who runs the Vatican
Probably one of the reasons why India 2000-2001 ex3200
Because
The network of masonic Network and other secret societies
When we saw the Bohemian Grove
Are facing some of the masses dead and telling them I mean
Inspiration that you gave me
At one point it reality of what I had.
Secret society that I was involved in and I decided that it no longer wanted
Especially when I discovered the secret
So
Stereotypical
Look
Grill covers
I didn't mean for it to be back but whatever
Leo zagami
Cool backstory he's flushed out on like Project Camelot interviews
And his own biography
Is it he was a high-ranking member of the Illuminati
He was apart of the real
Powerful Illuminati
And on Alex Jones Show
He's saying 2000-2001 I started listening to you Alec
I saw your b*******.
What the f***
Are they keeping
Step away from music I mean
The problem people get slippery
Compartmentalize
I mean he's lying about
He's definitely lying about Alex
I think he's bothering them up a little bit if you realize where I can
My book sales and stuff like that realize how many of his guests
Opportunistic assholes were using
Any of his position
You are the reason I woke up
Use agami
He said to Alex about what he
That is a
Cursory Wicked
Absolutely
Yeah like oh I know that you started a little bit before then I saw on the
The purse biography page
Cute came to problem
It's because of the Bohemian Grove
Done
Now I can just
Roll from
Can I deposit
Alex did on him
With that entirely possible that Leo zagami the human
And Italy
I did see
Alex Jones documentary
Started
To become weird
Concocted this backstory
That he was a high-ranking Illuminati member
To gain credibility Within
The worldview that Alex had exposed
Alright burgeoning internet
A community of
Distrustful weirdos
Conspiracy theory possible that he could have found out
That time and that this entire backstory of being a Vatican Insider and all this
Is just
The react
Seeing Alex Jones
Is it possible for us to know but
That is a story
I think fit
The Occam's razor
Announce matter of
Of timing light
Is he
That he finds out about Alex Jones
In order to go on
The show and talks
His entire story out of what
He thought he saw
In the Box
Generated
Like what you just hallucinating
I will tell you that
Completely out and outline
I will tell you what I don't believe
Is possible
He just said
I don't think
Take that spot
Course not but be that as it may
Next Club Jordan
Is
More evidence that
Alex Jones
Into Putin
Best friends
I was on there
The directors of Art
People
And that the Russian government actually watches the show
They don't need me I'm just promoting
What's the weather
But Alex doesn't understand the idea of like cultivation of assets
Instaflex
Right out of the Russian spy Play Books
Michael Savage podcast
Call me manipulating him in order to
People
The Russian propaganda
List of logical conclusion with with
Yeah of course
It's not
That they're trying to butter him up
I try to butter you up
He didn't
Interfering in the election
And so obviously
Can imagine
Disco's on
Browse Russian in Russian
I understand Patriot for Humanity process
A patriot for firewalls
I thought you just wanted to know
You be flattered so I support
They're like no no we're not now I've seen
Every time I came here
Out of Russian television
Orthodox Christian by underground
I think she's got a Christian them or is that Kiara bubble
Mysterious ways what the f***
I look at Russian and it's becoming looking Russian news
Was becoming a lot like
Infowars is not a statement I like to
To hear all this stuff from Russian
Official Outlet
Glorify poodle
The secret Christian
Are you trying to defend Christian dumb
This is insane
This is totally nuts
Alex believe
Well they said
You're on the level to Alex
Just whatever it is
Did you say
He's a mix of
Idiotic child and age
Complete Nutter Narcissus
So he'll believe
Makes him look
We should flatter him and see if he'll Retreat us
Regurgitation of Russian propaganda
So Alex
Rails about people saying
He's a Russian
People are talking about
That's just
Out-and-out Pro Putin Russia
Propaganda
Reality
Now we're done with the
24th
We move on to
September 20th
When I believe Alex Jones ever made episode
Begins
In earnest
And I think what kicked it off
Is it on the 25th it was announced that John Boehner with stepping
As the speaker
Saltz
Alex
Defeated John Boehner
Single
Because a couple months back he had a guy named Walter Jones
Who is the member
A congress who was trying to
To vacate the chair
I'm trying to get John Boehner
Route
Alex had him on the show didn't go Alex takes response
He is becoming
A little bit into his power
He's starting to think the
He has
There's delusions of grandeur that are going on
Not recognizing that I think John Boehner probably smell was in the air
I realize you can make
Millions of dollars as a trucking Lobby
Stress
Trump storm
Smart if you really look at the people who have come out of this the best
Boehner is up there
Cuz no one hates
Yeah
Orange monster for a worse
Dayton's and incredibly smart move if all you're doing is looking out for
Prophet and self-preservation
To have left
He left
Pictures that ass
He was getting pressure
From Walter Jones
And his Cadre of weirdos within the house
Pushing it
On the
On the Liberty program that isn't
Did they made it happen
Which is
A little bit Wild
But
What actually is motivating it even
More
Is this
Have gotten a tip for
From somebody
That I don't believe it's credible
Feeding into his
Victim mentality
As well as his sort of Messiah,
And I'll let him spell it out
I caught myself this morning
Enthusiastic
And proud of myself and satisfied
2 degrees
That I have never been
I want to stop right there persona
Explain what happens when you act
Do I look like a bag of trash
But I ride my bike for an hour and I go look at myself in the mirror cover
I'm doing it
That's usually what happens when you don't exercise and you exercise
It's something bigger he's figured it out
I felt
Show me
Doughboy
That my conscience
Was giving me a type of energy I've never felt
In my life
Is that something the conscience
Last year
Fpi white-collar crime task force
15 hours a day to find out somewhere to put me in prison
Away
Yeah there's no way
Even if
Obama was can
There's no way
They're paying the salary of
Around the Clock overtime 15 hours a day
Years trying to bring down before work
Just give us a couple Grand a month and we'll do it
Disseminated what he's actually saying that will take him
You think
He's going to bring himself down
Everyone
Everyone knows that Obama wouldn't even f******
He was a fly on the wall
So crazy but this is the delusion
This is the manic episode coming out
Someone told him
And he's decided that this guy's credit
The same way that Leo zagami
Tell him all this s*** about the Pope in Saigon well
You're on the same page as me I must be right
Or call or calls in and tell them something becomes gospel
Well you can measure Yourself by the enemies that
Do you have any
The president
Is
Spending
All of those people all of that man hour
To you that gives you that
CG
Is another one of those things
Listen to his own Legend
Him feel good so he'll believe
Communicated on to his audience
Europe
You're a part of this really dangerous movement
Call
Like a proud boy
So he goes on
This is like
This is delusion
Launching TV network
But
Sing about my forebears
Thinking about my ancestors in England
I just
Really gut in my spirit understood
Prostaff
To their ranks
That's the most valuable thing in the world
Houses are
Is your Caribbean beaches that the final equation
You standing up for what's right
And it is
Upholding your family name
Alright whatever
Like he really thinks he's beginning this hero's journey
He thinks that he is like
He's wielding Excalibur
Going on this adventure climbing the stairs to Legend
That's
Crazy
Well that's what everybody feels like when they
They start their own in
Episode
We started our own independent
TV network I think I know exactly how it feel
Like that I would feel overwhelmed with details
I would feel very nervous
This is the same thing
Set a couple months back
Alex Jones when he had that night long
Oh yeah that's right
Where we can sort of get a sense
Goes off
Reading get these
Sort of
It's not exact science and we're diagnosing him and his doctors or is it
Any Africa
Discreet
Changes in his brains
And this is
Hallmark
This delusions of grandeur
Pops up
About
Around
As best I can tell every 40 days when he was in Europe
Imma see what happens about 40 days
When is correct and if so
If he doesn't have an episode with Ann
You know about a month or so we know he's pregnant
Or we just have to calibrate our
Really comes into the equation
But
I'm telling you this is Manish it real hard
It's bills into this mess
Text Cliff witch
I think Alex Jones is trying out a new red or like rhetorical Style
A new manner of speaking
Did I think
Associate
I would say probably associated with Malcolm X
I would say that he's probably trying to mirror revolutionary speakers
Work
It just doesn't work
YouTube
Cross the threshold
Bilderberg
In 2016
Richard Holbrooke
When I did it
I could feel
I was passing a line
Another level
Opportunity for freedom
I love it
I passed other lines as well
It'll take years to grow
Is only assigned them to remind them
The mint it only reminds them
And empowered individual
And I want to bother
Is the fifth to God but he's also directly quoting
Himself from Waco
That is a
Lime for lime
His speech in Waking Life
His past self
Coming out in his presence
Which is super weird cuz they're very
We don't cower in fear to the system they can't stand man
And so what's going on
Talk about it your coward
Because oh my gosh
Peaceful
Liver cancer
Cancer of the
1000%
Shut off
Destroyed our culture
On the news again
Starbucks
Libra
What's a speech pattern
Alex
Imagining himself
Delusional
And he's fighting just complete misused
Statistics
Misinterpreting articles
Mainlining pedophilia
Everything is a lie
They've already came for us
In my bizarre conception where I twist
So bizarre
But I love it
Like in terms of me being an Alex Jones research
And like
I love the little things that are interest
And when Alex Jones
Ellipsis
Speech pattern like
That's crazy
Cuz I've been listening
So much
Alex Jones
Yeah never thought
Never talk
Using these tricks
Petition
It's almost like Chris Rock like coming back
This thesis statement
It's a really powerful
Also is really important
Like that response
Usually requires
Some
Preacher
That repetition
Allows for people
Using it as a thesis statement
Repeat it allows you to reset
But after everybody left
Remind people
The joke is about what the bigger chunk is about
Studio
If you had a caller on the line be better
I think they would be
Beer do I apologize
Stalin
Pattern is
Emotional rather than
Kind of calculated
I think so I think it's
The spirit got good to him
Chucktown
BFDI crashed out
Yeah I've been researching it for two years all this b******* I think that is a lot of that like
The exercise that morning
So you know you got the testosterone flowing
The dopamine receptor
Pictures of kicking
He's at you
Struggle for me to listen to this
I recognized so much of myself there and it's like
Call Yu-Mi
I know it's
When you look at him as a human there are things that you're forced to
Sympathize with
Did you may not want to put any of his
Weis
Or his
His beliefs that are b*******
Through all of my manic episodes I have never won
Vaccines cause autism or Rewritten the Civil War
The thing about
Him
Especially in that little
He is dehumanizing
Like they came for us like autism
Punishment like autism is
Like people are still people in the
Vast majority of them
They're wonderful
He hasn't really
Cryptid sort of belief about
Soft skills and
What have you
It's not worth it
Stella
It's not worth getting into about it
Just be here all day
Don't talk about everything
But be that as it may
Thanks Walter Jones
Before that he plays
John Boehner speech
Eagles live to CNN ordo
Discovering
Does a little bit of a mystery science theater
Along with it
That I think is
Because if you remember.
Recent
Stop
Everything
What do that
He embraced that problem was
Kneading
Awesome sauce
Oh boy I'm turning into Donald Trump here
By making
Female reporter
So.
Disabled
But
That is a fly trap
Mission
On his part crack
Through his
3 like
I'm starting
Camelot Morris
Birches
We know the inevitable outcome of what happened
Alex is ego
So here's another paranoid fantasy videos about
The government
Monica cell
About half of them were completely out of
Pinterest
Iraq
The prosecutor
No criminal record
I couldn't sing
El Amor De Mana
Sacrifice children or something
Everything
Multiple sources
I don't know
They've got a
So what
I'm not afraid
Friendship
Sita is just him like
Wreck in recognition of his history
They become so much more he's fantasizing that it's going to be another Waco
Yeah
Is going to come in
SWAT team
Of course
I need for the government last time
Because he knows that his audience is also very Pro
Branch Davidian
Yeah I want a view anti-government
Also on the show
Essentially
He knows that he's
Leading an anti-government
Nike comparison to know what I'm doing
George Washington
Was doing
Differ
That sort of things
Oh boy
They're leading a revolution
That's f***** up
I think those researchers
Yep I'm here on inciting violence we can take off early this Friday
The government
This Friday
Episode that's where our
Third of an owl with this if stuff goes
I've been remiss in pointing out that every day that we've been covering
Alex Jones
So much wild s*** about the Pope
He is making
Every show the focal point of it is
Hope is a globalist
He is a demon and
He claims based on Lord monckton research
The pope gets his way
I'm a put in these carbon taxes which
Nonsense
The Pope
Is successful a billion people will die
Based on Lord mountains analysis
Do like I do believe
Any of these
Any of the Little parts
RMS
Can you bring it into a hole is a huge
If they
If they implemented
Carpenter
Sprite
A billion people
That's some Big Mac
Lord monckton is good at math
May have carried a one
Hear the Lord
Mariah Carey 21 wrong my point is that Alex Jones is for a week been sitting on the Pope
Yeah then on Sunday
Is it just is it just for like shock or just like
To talk about
Hotel
It's cuz they can't possibly care that much about the f****** fault because the pope has said that we have an obligation to care for the poor
And the nothing pisses off
People more than that fleeing
Certain
We have an obligation to help them
He has ads
Vacated
Four positions like
He believes in One World Government open borders
All this stuff
A focal head of globalism
He's like a globalist
God
Conception
Everything back to
To the pope like all of his narrative
Can all be thrown
Somewhat
On the
Actual true
History of child abuse
That exist
Within the Vatican
And Leo zagami
Of course
It says that that is the case
Has become installed at Pope
Because he has pet
A pedophile blackmail on everybody
Listen to this clip
From September twenty
Let's for Sunday
The rest of the Sunday show is unknowable
It's a bunch of
How to talk about Lord locked
David Jackson
Make a little pop-up
Appearance
And
World
Tallest tree might as well be quite frankly
Might as well be David analysis on the road
Alex Jones
Talks about George sir
About how I
Hey everyone says you know he would have been killed by the Nazis
I like hey
If I were in that position I actually pulled the trigger man
I'd like to be very unfair
Even even that is recognizing
During the Holocaust
George Soros
Had no ability
To Buck the cyst
At all Alex Jones
Hypnotizing
And he's still lying about what George Soros
Did cuz he still saying that he rounded up Jews and stuff like that would
Absolutely didn't
He bases all this on the
60 Minutes interview that has nothing to do
It's all bulshit
But I think it's particularly
Disgusting did he recognize
George Soros
To do anything out of line
P****
I would have
Yeah alright
You're a liar
First of all
A second ball
How dare you insult someone's decision
If that kind of a situation
The only way you can do that is if you
Trying to deny the Holocaust
And it was mostly about Jews didn't pay rent
Yeah
That's really the only way you can do that
The f****** horrible person
Anyway
This clip
From the show
Is an interview with a guy named
Joe Bannister
Alex presents him as a guy who the Government tried to shut down
I don't know his whole history I don't really care it's not important
2 what's going on
The two of them have an interview
And
The pope comes
Joe Bannister
Pretty decent argument
A pretty decent position
Imallexx make
Incredibly startling admission
Born
It's not about these other matters
Call Prudential
To determine
And the most
Maybe the media
Overall
He just straight-up admitted he doesn't know anything about the Pope
All he knows is stories that he's read and as we've clearly
He has a f****** bad media diet
He reads stories on Breitbart zerohedge
And pro-russian propaganda site
That are critical of the
The pope and these One World Government stamp
I'm shiting on the Pope
Culminate
With him being like
Well maybe the media taking about a contact
Text you f****** do f****** a****** you're the worst
Hey better-late-than-never
Fight
So terrible
So if you think
You're wrong
Because that was Sunday and now our last day the investigation
The 28th
Choices back on his b*******
Adventure
Because he has found
A kernel of something he can get mad at
A show on Monday
Failed on the cross
Forgive us of our sins the ultimate
Is Sean an echo
Abraham about to sacrifice his son
But God following through on
Let's roll grandloves Taylor
Motorola
Produce fruit
Kevin Coronavirus
Primo's Akatsuki
Jesus Christ
Humanly speaking
So
So dumb
What are you saying
Is on a human level
He failed
That's Def
Death is a failure
Exactly
The or whatever
Guys
I thought this was going to end up different
But like
It's the point that the pope is trying
Super opt
His
Often times we get discouraged by not seeing
The results of our actions
The human plane
Anne Wheaton
Like the times of Our Lives
You may not see that
Cross is a failure on human terms
But it's not
In general
Exactly
Everyone f****** knows that's what he saying
But
This
Is
Crucial
Alex has this
Believe that
It was the greatest
And it's full quote is very
Yeah do you get it
Uwiteka
Is the term that use or Jesuit Oregon
Hillary says she runs her life according to
Georgetown
Where you could get what he saying that Christ physically was killed but
Twisted
Double meaning
This
Is the underpinning
Of the entire world
Alex Jones
The spouses
There's double meaning
Everything
I'm not stupid
And misinterpreting clear statements
The people make
They're using doubles
So that's why he can go to
John Pierre
Book about a cosigner
Any can say
He's using doublespeak
You think that they're putting stuff in the water
Not in the text
At all
That is not what
Because Alex Jones
Conception
The Deep
Is the double talk
Everything is cold
He can just say that anybody is asserting either what they're saying or the opposite of what they're saying or something in-between
You can just make up meaning for anything
Yeah this is the problem
Little big problems the big problem I like it when words mean
Stuff like that
Purple Penguin
No no
To when he says they're trying to outlaw mother and father met
Boy and girl
There is no evidence of that
There's nothing in any story
That is
Has any credibility
That that is what people want
But because he
The double-talk
He sees the doublespeak the people are doing
You can see
Transgender Advocate saying
Hey let's not jump to things that don't need to be gendered
Doublespeak that I see
It's like no dude your brains in
You have your f***** up
You see things that aren't there
You're fighting ghosts
There's a globalist cabal that you've imagined in your head
Bulshit you read when you were
The f****** too young under
Understand how the world works
And your functioning often is a forty-year-old man you've created a system wherein oh everything doesn't
Mean what it means means whatever I want it to mean
And you're making billions of dollars f****** lying to people about it you should
Ashamed of yourself
Anyway
Sit here and breathe and then I think
It feels so good at this what Dan feels like when I go yell
Control
I f*** it I know that's what he'd
Service of demonizing
A already
On the display.
It's so
So manipulative
It is right back to
Projection
You are
You are mad at him
Because you live in a world where that's what you do so if you do that obviously
The people you are fighting against
Same level of
Hopelessness in like
How do you speak to somebody
You don't hopefully you educate
Who is you like
Take us to Publix
Smart
Those are things that aren't
Really well handled by the result orientated
Standardized
Testing oriented Public School
But I think
If you gave people a handle on logic Young
It would really enable them
To understand arguments
It would really help them
Decipherable
That is not what they wanted
What we should do is
We should look
We should Outlaw mothers and fathers
Cuz they're the root cause
Like if Alex Jones didn't have a mother or father we wouldn't have Alex Jones
Finally rich
I don't even like genders I don't get rid of mother and father
Parents
And I think we should let the children at 5
Really this is what
Pittsburgh perfect
I mean earrings
Satirical
Alex Jones
Is just to do what Alex Jones is afraid
Absolutely not no
The other thing the reason I included a rhetoric
Back in there
With what I want them to be
Is it was a part of classical education
Rhetorical devices
Skills abilities
It's something that people should study
Because
It enables you to tell
Much like when we
Fury
Obviously able to tell
Two things on this episode based on studying
Rhetoric
Whatever Alex jump does one of those
Right
Second
Impression you can tell that something's going on
You can tell that he's full of s*** and probably in a weird
Because you know his rhetoric
You know the
The tools that he employed
Help students
In primary education
You'd be much more able to see a politician to be like
I know what you're doing
Your
What about it
Or your other
Standard trick
The democratic-republican
It's exactly what you're saying the people who knows
Who are top
Are using it against people who
Right that's why you that's what it is
The worst problem people in the world are people who took the bait class
Essentially hypnotize people with their language
Do you like neuro-linguistic programming type trick
And then on top of that just
It's do so many
Two arguments
Like if you're if you get into an argument
With someone like a Paul Joseph Watson
Or and Alex Jones
They have
So many tricks at their disposal
If you confront them with
Hey you think
Everybody saying two things when they're saying
Which one you want to believe is what they mean
And you can
Bring up examples
Forgot to turn it on to like what
Yeah exactly
And if you want rest and rhetoric and logic
There are ways that you can
Shut that s*** down
Or at least recognized
Something else
Education is obviously the
Now
Isn't too
Stop Alex Jones
To stop you being
Yeah cernovich
SOB X all the map
To deceive you
If you know how to do
Deceive people
You're going to be better at
Something it out
Like be clear all of the
A problem now
Word problems
Like Jekyll sobiech wasn't really in the mainstream no one really knew who he was
Or anything like that five years ago
He is a mess
Cernovich was involved with gamergate stuff and s*** like that but
Before that he wasn't really
A notable prominent problem
25 years from now there's going to be other a******
And if you jump
Use the
I'm awareness you can have about Alex
Mike cernovich
The next time around you won't be tricked by his b*******
Whoever the next version of rags
And that is what I would hope to
To see in the world
And I don't
Think we're going to
Yeah
Probably
That's really what it is
Eclipse we have cover
And I will say that they're just good
With the exception of the last one which is an update on Trump
But here is Alex Jones respond
Space news
Excellent
Spaceman we have Mastiff
On Mars during the summer
Mars and extremely happy
What
Mars is extremely happy
No
That's why I
Right
Make them work
Slaves on Mars
Brinkley
You know what I
2 habits
What is the main problem
With this idea that
That Mars is habitable
Why is there's not really much
It really was a problem
I think even if you have to have s*** to work with
A content
And on Mars
Is oxygen
.1
34C
Enough
That doesn't seem like enough it's really pretty much all carbon dioxide
Richard Kill Everybody
But now that's how it works
I breathe air
You bring a couple of plants with you to Mars
You're good that's actually automatic
Scale not a terrible idea
That terraforming
What's wrong there is water there is a history of flowing Waters like millions of years ago
So dumb but he's really dumb stuff about space
Here is another one
This is Alex Jones
Accidentally walking movie was it Mission to Mars
Don Cheadle go to space
And Gary Sinise joins the Martian
It's a whole thing
I don't remember left
Signals behind for us to follow I don't remember but I do know that Syfy is just
The dreams of May
So
The nightmares are creative
Astral projection
That's good
Alex Jones
Accidentally walked into my backyard and I miss you
I'm going to tell him to get out of that backyard here in a second
Mars atmosphere
Amazing
Oceans
Bostitch atmosphere
There was a connection to Mars
Atmosphere
Now it's coming true
The Ancients said it now it's coming through 90
That's not inflate
Barth look
Atlantis lost its atmosphere
And then Mars lost its atmosphere
Simultaneously I don't know
Listen here's the day
What is the deal little bit in the past
Plato talks about it and tomatoes and critias the two dialogues
It doesn't say anything about f****** Mars at all
It's that
Made up by Alex
. I'll get to that in a second
Jesus Christ
Pseudoscience
Edgar Cayce types
Ragozzino's if he's like all
On Atlantis and Mars
If you did that are going to be like oh s*** you're into new AG bulshit
Instead he claims
That what those were saying is what Plato was saying
Is there an error
Variety
DIY playdough
I have to do with Poseidon
Poseidon was the king of Atlantis and his offspring
Where the reason about Mars and Play-Doh
You are talking wrong because they're speaking more about the guy
Mars the Roman
Deliberately confusing
No
What are you doing is using like some of this very
Very dubious
Type of
These channels materials
Some stuff like that from
The people like it
Talking about past lives on Atlantis
The build-up the robots
List of the Mars narrative
Find Atlanta
Excuse me
But also
What are you doing
Is he bringing an ancient alien
He's bringing in these Erich von daniken bulshit
Bringing in stuff to do with like
The emerald
Tablets of Thoth
What's the Emerald Tablet
We'd be here for another f****** hour to the bottom of the emerald
Tablets of Thoth
Entire episode on V pseudoscientific nonsense
Weird spirituality another project
Dave
There's this
Pseudo spiritualist
Belief in Atlanta that has to do with
There's a planet
It's called various different thing
Malbec is one of the things it's called
They were Martinez
Never martians aliens on this planet
And they ended up blowing up the planet
I'm killing everybody on it
Cuz I got to in
In the
Tinkering at the created Atomic weapons
And they blew up the entire planet
Basically so
Souls needed somewhere else to reincarnate cuz they do work out there, Cadet
And what have you and so there was negotiating
This isn't the Halo Wars
So there is a planetary
I don't even f****** know that we're allowed to reincarnate on Earth
Even even vacant compromise
Allowed illegal immigrants into her
This is a far better world so they reincarnate on lemuria to work out their karmic debt
Atlanta
Blowing up Atlanta
We're here in modern-day
Here's the problem we've created I haven't blown up any
But we've dropped
Even destroyed
It was destroyed by
Gears
Nuclear weapons
He was the reason that I've ever seen the movie Atlanta
You know it
Easy for them to do
Thanks
Together that's fair
Wall of light that's as legitimate
Actor first version
As I tell you these things people believe that are not
I need to make clear that I know that Alex Jones
Have to be aware of some of
This is where it's coming
Cuz the idea that there was a Connect
Do with outer space
And
Is all from
It has nothing to do with Play-Doh
Play-Doh didn't talk about that s*** at all
So he's getting that from a source
Distance to be in line with the
Von daniken other guy's name
Now the other guy
Yeah maybe
He just watched an episode of
Entirely possible
Talks about the Atlantean Legend
He always talks about how
We're getting to this
And that is the idea
Created nuclear weapons and blew itself up
Which comes from this pseudo scientifical pseudo-spiritual list
Theosophist branch
Of nonce
If you actually a really just going off of
Play-Doh which is
Respected source
Whatever you talk about Atlantis is very unspecific
But he talks about it
Like the destruction of Atlantis was
Punishment
Have God because they were too warlike
They went around they destroy
Respected world
They f***** with
Too much
So they got destroyed by the Gods
Because they became too
Too decadent it wasn't that they created nuclear weapons and Industry
Texas
Play Arabia
Of the metaphor of Atlanta
From
Bulshit sources
Of course I love it
Cuz he's so dumb
I need to not be talkin about it
Bother
F****** batalon
Whatever whatever one's that you want
Right
Assault
But I just don't like
That's Gomorrah
Mine
I love that you stay out
You stay at Alex
This this one
Is just for you
Mike down
But I know you love
Alexander's Bay class
This
Is
You getting
You know it's it's not be careful what you wish for
Biggest beaches
Too much of his life
Negative Ghost
Big Lots
So here we got this is the worst fake laugh I've ever heard
And I just love this orwellian article out of Los Angeles Times only come back
What are your for Israel against
You want to know how they saw it they say bases you're a demonstrator
They're going to shoot you
Don't worry it's caliber
It disintegrates
And opens up
They wanted to kill more people in a more people
In Vietnam
Hyper velocity round breaks up when I get to bone
Invasive fragmentation kinetic weapon
From a Ruger range rifle is okay
Prime that's so hilarious
Oh my gosh that is the funniest thing I've ever heard in my life
Around but don't worry it's small
I'm sorry
Imma stop right there you better
That's crazy
He thinks it's
So funny
That's not real
He's like he's really Hamming it up and putting his head over his eyes and like that
Terrible but
The idea that you would want
Presented
He thinks that it's so funny
Is bizarre even on its own
That is the funniest thing you've ever heard
Is incredibly f***** up
Ammunition of course that's hilarious
So you could have gone
A little bit
Energy word 3 hours
Podcast
The funkiest
I wonder what his real laugh sound
Is it like Fran Drescher Real
I really
I really don't think that he has a
Leopard
Big crush on her and
I'm glad that you
You did not need the real that it reveal that information at all
Do the very attractive lady
Anyway
This
This investigation like
Is Donald Trump
Came into Alex Jones is
Sphere
So I'm
A cliffhanger
Not really
He brings up
Trump says something or news breaks on the 28th
That is relevant
The trumps campaign
I am Alex Jones
Unless you
Make of this what you
I let Jesus Take the Wheel
What really makes
General Electric Google
Apple
Lockheed Martin
Maybe the power over the planet
So you can play
You are going to send that money
You took that money out of the country
Three important points
He saying
America built
Which is very similar to
You didn't build your business
Which is something he's very mad at Obama for saying
I forgot what the one of them
But grossly mischaracterizing
Trump's tax
It was nothing like
Nouveau riche
Is not just
Rich people
Like
When you became rich
Then the other thing that I think
F****** idiot
Or he's willfully lie
Because
You know who runs
A multinational corporation
Based in America
Wait what
They still allow him to do that he's running for president
We don't want any kind of conflict of interest
It's the laws will kick it and we will know that he doesn't have
Owego
Can't possibly think
Donald Trump is
So selfless
But he's going to create
Burden for companies very similar to the one that
That's what he said he was going to do
That's so crazy
Look that's so stupid
Said that they
You believe them
Bright
Cost himself money as
He has been known to do his entire lab salute
How do I
Give more of my wife
How do I make
I am not the only person take
He used his own
Charities money
To pay for his son's enrollment
In the boy scout
Yeah that's f****** with you
No it's done
Used his own Charities money
Trump to play golf
Right
It's not someone that's not the act of someone who's going to help us clean wants to
Is Dan that's okay
Also contradicts
Things that
Cuz that about Trump
The past
It absolutely does
Like you use characterization of Donald Trump
Has become
Something very positive
As opposed
To this guy's a scumbag
He's a predator
I don't trust
Yeah
And then here's this dumb s***
Well I of course I trust him
Tacitly Trussville course
Unbelievable
Stupid believe it
He got a s*** ton of money from the money
It's possible Clipper playing we're going to leave it
Here until the next phase of the investigation
Even after that.
I don't I'm not endorsing
That he is still in the same place
There is no foundational Prague
No but we're seeing it happened so slowly
Disappoint
There's no
It seems like it's just a buildup of him hearing things
He's repeatedly
Adidas
Can Only Hold one ideas have the
Yeah and that is what
Man Rodger Stones got to show up soon right out I don't know when it is
Anyway
This is been interesting Road
We gone down it's been fun but you'd like more fun you can find it
Knowledge fight.com
Let me see
I forgot to say this
I forgot
The beginning of the show and I just want to give an explanation for why we've been in the past
For so long
Not great that I'm doing 3 hours into the
Maybe want to hear this
At the end
I will have said turn it off
Couple days
Thursday
Studio
And even before that he was just trolling he's just trolling people
He's doing this like
People keep posting that he's
Stuff like that
And that's just him trying
To get more attention in the same vein as the
We love our Somali Song Contest
Debate
Grab this bait
I'm a real you in
They have the dick size thing it's a joke
People come and hear the truth from
That way but it's still not
He still ends up making
A lot of money off ad Revenue in
It like that
So don't fall for it it's super boring
And then at the end of last week
I got the app
Much like his argument that
He got
Maybe he did have some source
I told him that it was going to go down
Is that
He's been banging
If possible
But I'm not interested in
Scoops like that
That's not exciting
I don't give a s*** about stuff like that
I don't care
If you have
Keep inhaling priebus
It's not like he is some sort of inside information he thinks he's a globalist holdover
To the fact that he gets fires are good
Write him saying we called it earlier this week it doesn't really mean it
You called out like four months ago to
He said he'll be out by the end of the
No I'm at maybe that I don't fucken la
He can claim that because
Cuz the same people
Who got rid of previs
Are the people that
Already
I agree with the guy who gets rid
Priebus
Because
A f****** course he'd
I hate that guy
Alex and Brandon are the same
Same f****** dude
You know you
We got we got we got scaramucci in
Marriott scaramucci blown away if you wasn't
Alex's
Flips with journalist
Have some sort of
Connection I'm not entirely sure what it is
Seem to have
At least positive feelings
Mutual Aid
I would not be surprised at all if scaramucci wow
Demonizing reince priebus for being a leader is leaking shipped out and Mike cernovich
Then why have you
Boring
Actually but I just don't care to fall into
Stupid trolling trick
And at the same time
The David Knight
Paul Joseph Watson Art Studio
Aqua not covering
So we'll see what week but the
Until further notice
That's
We
Cover David
Goodnight or Paul Joseph
Is if they are
Hit by the
Malaysian plane
Or if Alex Jones gay
Is the Malaysian plane
And lands on the studio
I will definitely talk about that
We might have to listen to him
For real
Underscore
Fight you can find us on Facebook
We're on Facebook
You can check that out
Comedian friend of mine from Missouri
Sing about being friend
I can't make my status b***** dude
Anyway
I think you're right it is
The face
The show we can check that up-and-coming policy walk
Also
We have some new stuff up there some new lies in the archives from Alex Jones has passed
Some new entries in his biography
Check it out there's a lot of stuff
Therefore
Cheese this out there and see exactly how people feel about it but we may be
Filled with buttons
Available
We don't know what they'll say no
We don't know why
We love you or what
Why are you worried about
Next chapter
80s or 90s children
Some stuff anyway
Appreciate is an old toothless man
That guy is named Jon rappoport and what do you how do you feel about him
You know I go back and forth but right now I think
He can go f***
Hey man
Alexandra Thurston color