Important
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Citarella
Text Jose
Indeed we are.
Aggressive
What's up
Request
Existed until recently
Grocery shopping
And I
What happened to spy
With my little eye
I saw
Frozen mini pancakes
Snoflo but it definitely not
I thought they were going to be really gross probably or just a disaster but I thought like that why the f*** not give it a try
That you feel I went to novel things shows up where you like
Is going to be garbage
Eddie Griffin
It's
These things are great
Corsair
Good pancakes
And may take 30 seconds to microwave
Do you want a couple
That's great right now
Tell me you say the word I'll get you some little mini pancakes at episode of the coming weeks
Better make me a mini pack
Easy to make pancake
I can do that
But there are things that I don't always have in the house
Milkshakes
I don't know if I can make
Pancakes with coconut milk
You can enter really
Oh yeah
Not as well
Not as good I like oatmeal more than I like
I'll never need to make pancakes again
Cuz I'm a little Frozen
Come to the end of our show
What's
My bright spot is there is
The new album from the band royksopp Icelandic
Seen that name before
Play Icelandic answer to death punk
Do they they make some beep boop Noise music
They worked extended
Chablis with cakes
Comedian said that's the Norwegian Simon and Garfunkel
What's the monarchy
Exactly you got Icelandic death punk
Norwegian Simon & Garfunkel
I'm pretty sure lady Trunks from Belgium look like my inability to understand
But yeah
I have been looking for some new people check it out
Today we are sticking around to the old pass because I don't really care
Care about Alex doing the present-day we're all dead already
I got another million-dollar difficult to get motivated
It may be more productive use of our time
Analyzing and looking at some of the stuff in the past
And recognizing how it implicates
Expand
And actually provides greater context
List of the typing in the prison
Agree with you it does seem like listening to the show in the present is just a exercise in futility instead of being part of a larger
Yeah he's yelling about stuff
Yeah
Really depressed he got a million dollars now everyone's going to die the wrong about the Bible
But we might get into that even if
Just the case
Virgil
It is actually Thursday and Friday I only know this because in one of the episodes
Said it's Friday
Okay
Kira thank you so much
Thank you so much
Thank you very much is that like lotion
The Aftercare tattoo aftercare
Next Garage on board beard thank you so much
Thank you very much
StubHub
I'm a policy wonk Charles award was an antiquarian from infancy thank you so much
Thank you very much now I don't see the line in the case of Charles Dexter Ward
One of the I don't know
I don't know I've heard that one in a while that one might be problematic
Yeah probably
Oh no hold on I think
Not good
For most of his work
Whenever the nerdy thing is he for you cuz you got a you got to deal with it you got to go like my nerdy shout at them like
Estero that's all I just got to wrestle with affected Lovecraft was
Monster for
The greater part of his career
Next to the three wise men
UGM Bubba thank you so much
Thank you very much, stereo thank you so much
Thank you very much
Discover these to hear days in past hands
Past episode we saw him talk to John Sebastian Robo Global Research
And build
Never never a bad time for a bill boshears and the guy who was trying to get to Arnold
You can off the Davis
Taking out-of-office office by the guy who
Who wanted to do it but then had to drop out because he took some issues so we paid for it
That's right it wasn't a direct
Like he was being paid by hammer
I said funded a lot of the early efforts to get
The recall recall going
Not necessarily connected to this guy's name
Is collusion a fun name
That is important for today because
Nothing nothing is related
Here is not a complex drop
Today Show
Who was that guy who was that guy Alex
Call Elijah
Okay you can't forget Laura
That's a that's a boy washing
Alex should know that one that you think that's not
So here on the 31st of July
Maybe I don't do a great job generally
Also I want to stop right there for a second
I really am coming around on the idea that Rogan stole powerful from Alex
Okay I think that there is a decent to eat
He's been going for so long with the powerful women 2013
I'm saying is a powerful breakfast and does that too
Restart his shows on Fear Factor with this
This is going to be a powerful broadcast believe so but he did
Blues radio every episode started with.
Yeah
Free imallexx
Friday
It's true
That's nice of him to admit to responsibility for his is failures
Swell
Responsibility of his descriptively saying that he is not covering the news
You would expect like a change of behavior
Subdue of wrongdoing and I promise no longer to continue that bad
I don't like it's time
He spends a lot of the show ranting about how he doesn't like sports
You're in a cult if you are watch this so the possibility that you could just
Is go up to somebody and say
I failed you
I've been move on that so nothing ever happened
How many does get to some
The news
If you want to call it that
No. Not any more than normal
Alex just be something here at the beginning that I think is really interesting and then he does
Not explain any further
This is fascinating
If you don't
Listen to this Joe
Parameter
The New World Order
The Illuminati
The globular
What
Understanding
Underworld
And that has happened
So I know kind of what he's saying cuz he said stuff like this before
But if you don't like taking active participation in the infowar sure what it's doing is
Acclimating you to these horrible things that the globalists are doing so you'll think they're normal
The pot getting a little warmer with the frog in it unless you're active
In some way but that's supposed to waking you up
Numbing you problem that I have is what are those parameters you have to have in mind
These parameters are that Alex
You need in order to engage with his work
Maybe I just don't have those parameters in place I think it's physics
But I think it's up down love
And then charm I don't
Forget the other two corks but I think those are the parameter
I think it's AABB AABB
I was thinking of the code for Aladdin
Text quite remember
Yeah I don't know I was really interested because I
I think that there is a
Like if there is a recognition that Alex is like
Alright
There are these 3D glasses that you have to view this through it looks like a jumbled mess
I would like to know what he
Fink's 3D glasses are metaphorically
If maybe what we're describing here is is there an earpiece that you can wear that is analogous to the
Sunglasses in Vail ID right right or is there a cipher
That I can translate and then you spin the wheel to get the code
I get it but we don't have any parameters explained
So
I guess I'll just have
Have to do the best I can
So here's a story actually Alex getting to the news
Marriott
I really work
Millionday kill
Call Dan
Comparison
So point I really want to stress in my cupboard to these episodes from the past and the reason why I think they're important
The disgust is always right around the corner
Alex is no different than any of these doomsday preachers or try to rile up their congregation with claims that the end is near only to be
Wrong and then do the whole thing over again a little bit later pretending the first time didn't happen
When we hear Alexandra people like him in the right-wing media and parts of our government playing this game in the present day
It's important to understand that they're not Siri
This isn't
But they're doing
They're doing for RVs
Yeah
Yeah you know I mean
I feel like even if you are making an absurd amount of money with
Still get old create
After a while right
You're coming at this with the expectation that there is a creative
Wow that's a really good that I mean.
Is driven by Lake necessarily a creative
Sure
Some people are driven by like order
Like you know liking
Spreadsheets and
Well I mean WhatsApp
Show
That's not necessarily artistic not radio show
My head all like radio shows have to be based on some sort of
Creative desire or need to do that never occurred to me that you could do a radio show like go to a cold
Wine every morning
Put my little hat on and clogging it up but instead of something
Productive like mining your
Scaring people with b*******
It started with a story that Alex was talking about
Camera
Fanta it's
It's about Marriott
Security cameras and Alex is entirely misreporting that that story
There was a guy named Brian Brewer who found a camera in his bathrooms lights
Fixture at a hotel he was staying at in Tennessee
He'd accidentally broke in the light which is no yet
Hayden response he filed a lawsuit against Marriott for 1.5 billion dollars
I can't find the story that Alex is responding to here but the actual
Case was filed in September 2000
I'm guessing July 2003 either the case was dismissed or they reached a settlement
The issue was that the courts were never deciding or even asked to decide if the Marriott could put cameras in their bathroom
Because that's not an issue here
No you can't do
The presumption is that someone else
Possibly an employee or possibly a past
Put the camera there in the suit was again
A hotel because they didn't catch that and Brewers privacy was violated
Even Alex is doing this absurd performance being so overwhelmed by the news and how he needs
To cover these important stories
You can't complete basic details of the things he's talking about
That's holy Because the actual events that happened
Don't help him reinforces
So he just makes it up
Right
Well I mean let me throw this at you
Is it possible that the
Twice
In order to make sure that
Nobody can put cameras in the Marriott bathrooms anymore
They put cameras in the Marriott bathrooms in order to monitor
That could be or they could have done a thing where they're like
We will put
So many cameras bathroom that there's no room for anybody
Get tricked by being like all somebody what if somebody's watching me
After the football game press conference
Cerulean
So we got we got a little bit of another story maybe Alex is actually
Getting to the news
He's not dropping the ball
They're building.
Another Resident Evil types
Raccoon City
Plan is to prepare biryani
Pencil
Chronicle
Epidemiologist
Bio weapon
Was just a reminder that everything Alex is doing
Has been doing with covid is just a huge
Extension of the same propaganda game he plays with
Every vaccine that makes the news
It's always a bioweapon and the top epidemiologist
The major prestigious universities of said Soca
Bizarre compounder Weber Resident Evil umbrella
F****** thing this is what I hear this clip is about the smallpox vaccine it but honestly it could just be about any
It doesn't matter
Also they didn't build dozens of bsl-4 labs is Alex calls them bioweapons lab but that didn't happen no
As of the present day there were only thirteen in all of North America
So
Amanda little off
You know the problem with that, another false story
Problem with that Clayface
Is we really could have used a
Bunch
Bureaucratic infrastructure built in advance for inoculation
Some of that may have been helpful in some ways but I don't know necessarily
If he has I don't know if they would be as productive towards that goal
Think that having
Dozens and dozens of bsl-4 labs
Really help us that much did increase safety or decrease safety
I don't know if you would actually he even having
Benefactor
That's nearly as dangerous as Alex makes them have to be
Work that needs to be done at them that you delete them in every city
You know how it is in like SimCity or civilization you don't need a theater in every
Call linear settlement like Baskin-Robbins and Dunkin Donuts
Like that kind of thing so the DSL Laboratories are also working with like
Food processing plant
That's that's usually good certainly isn't a present day
So Alex is a fun story
The man I love the story
I am so glad that
This comes up more than once on this episode
Belmont working on
And there are.
Mind control
Go in there and get around some things you know I don't want him near me
Kimbrell's.
Everywhere DARPA taking over everywhere
No way
Just filming and I accidentally stumbled upon mind-control play
Plans
Divine
Kids math I think that's what it was made
Define this a different way worse person in the
World because he didn't take those documents
What you put you could get in trouble
Sure
Division of information Warfare EP engaged in that he would find
DARPA mind control documentary
And put them in a folder and left it on the desk.
Slowly backed away from the shadow gate situation that I don't deal with this
This is terrifying right whatever man
But
I guess we've talked about
The toll road
Internal
Point
When you have to serve
I could golf
Don't call
Terror attack which would be a false flag by the military-industrial complex
License will be forced to do Public Service searching people's Vehicles a checkpoint
Another 65
None of that is even come
Close to happening
Had about a thousand different things have happened that Alex is called Volkswagen Terror attacks committed by the military-industrial
Constantly wrong about everything you said
That's pretty much he would be right if he was just like you know after that next terror attack they're going to make you take your shoes off
Forever even after you don't need to any
I think he'll probably claim he predicted that after it happened
G-Force 2
Work on the side of the road searching cars until you're 65 that's a bigger swing
Alexandra concerned about seatbelt rules back in 2003
Is preoccupation of the past
Seemed a little bit larger
In this clip Alex's rambling about how the government is going to put tracking chips into cars so they can tax you by the mile as you
Drive
This is something we discussed in the past as it was one of the proposals that was being discussed in terms of
The money they were losing on gas taxes
Since cars were using less gas
There's new technologies emerge
That shortfall of gas tax revenue has serious consequences and terms
The budgets that are needed to maintain the roads these cars are driving on
So the proposed was actually a pretty sensible one
Dive makes intuitive sense
How do I get to Sanger the 1998 National seat belt initiative was about funding internal checkpoints
Naturally this is
Is not true
Most of the document is about increasing the Public's awareness of the benefits of wearing
A seatbelt and framing the decision to not wear one
Appropriately
This involves
Focus on the issue as one that relates to your health
As well as making sure that
The perception wasn't solely focused on traffic
Because a huge factor is the injuries and that the accidents caused and expenses the people racked up
In public
Frances for that matter
Throughout the document it super clear that state
Are the ones who make traffic laws and the president or Congress can express that they would like state
Needs to do more
Did you propose a four-part plan and what are the parts is
Quote conduct high-visibility enforcement of seat belt laws
This is probably what Alex is exaggerating out to his dump
Conspiracy but it's just the report expressing that
If people don't think laws are going to be enforced
They're probably less likely to follow the
Click it or ticket
As always Alex isn't making s*** up to craft scary stories
Based on
Bill Clinton
Being like a people we need to get more people wearing seatbelts fidget spinners
Empirically shown to save lives
Call Celesta injuries in an accident
This is one of those
Such a like
Where were like oh my God these anti-maskers are terrible what if they were in a different time would they be anti seatbelt yeah
Yes
They would be anti seatbelt and be coming up with elaborate reason
Haribol
NECA
So I called them and complaining about how
I guess that if you're an undocumented immigrant
You get to like
Live fifty people to a house
But if you're just a good old white American
That's not allowed
Is this a
Problem
It is released
What you mentioned a few minutes ago
Illegal
Illegal aliens
Living here in New York
It's true because I
I see that all the time
Family houses
Converted into multiple
Dwellings where you literally will have done
People who are illegal immigrants
Obvious
And they do nothing about it
What
For a month while they're moving or something
Your door
And you're right
So these sorts of regulations are going to be on the state or even like a lower-level kind of issues like that
Really that upset about the zoning or housing regulations
I don't I don't know what to tell them
You know it doesn't seem to be productive to be
Play National radio show take action on a local level
Naturally there is some guidance it's offered but on the federal level through the Department of Housing and Urban Development
Much of which goes back to a 1991 memo written by their general counsel Frank
Cheating
The memo largely is a discussion about how many people should be living in a dwelling based on how many bedrooms they are
Keating concludes that the number is too but also that's not a hard-and-fast number and there's a ton of other factors to consider other
What is a bedroom layout of the house children
Yeah whatever
Lot of factors
Most of the reasons these regulations exist as todoist
Overcrowding is not good for my health or some even structural reason so it's typically avoided
That said if your cousin comes to live with you for a month
There is no way the cops are going to show up unless your cousin was coming to live with you because he was on the Run
From the cops right
You might get into trouble with your landlord if you're violating your lease but if it's your house this just isn't a realistic so now
Mario that's going to happen
I mean
Personally
I have seen plenty of movies and documentaries haven't you lived with
Cops come
Not for all the illegal but I don't think that I've seen any
Documentaries where they like holyshit
We better pass this ordinance
Otherwise there's going to be too many people living in single with their cousin
Got to jam about anybody come on over
I date people lived at your house
David Alex saying this caller people like them can express their hatred of Mexican immigrants in a way that makes it
Feel socially acceptable
It's be like
Figured way with it but
It's a false premise rooted
Just in white
Victim
Larger issue that people shouldn't have to live 20 people in an apartment regardless of their immigration
And status
That might be something we can make it through dressing and affordable public housing but Alex
Who's against that too
Because of freedom
Yeah it would be it would be in
Just seeing if that guys take on it was like
Man there all these immigrants living in their houses together ice
See it I see it need immigrants are living in their houses
And that's why we need affordable public housing
Coming from all directions we need to expand certain places we can't allow Advanced Property
To be sitting there empty on the market
Just curious to see how Alex
Got really mad about that
And end up saying
Stupid s***
Police
We have to look and see how many
Find an arrest
Absolutely not
There there are so many problems with this idea
That if you have an extra toothbrush I mean
First off
Man the cops are not smart enough to tell how may
Also
No you cannot
Yes you can I believe in America where
People can have two toothbrushes
Also I think what's going on here is that Alex is thinking of like
Maybe
A TV show where someone realize they were being cheated on cuz there was an extra toothbrush
Rye Rye or like a Murder She Wrote where she was like I noticed that you have a foreign toothbrush
Yeah yeah yeah
Does getting arrested cuz like the other significant other has decided to bring a toothbrush to leave in there
Now so f****** dumb I mean was it a Mechanical Tees
What do you mean
Diamond Resorts
We took a different directions
50 route that there are different directions
So Alex gets another call and it's one of my favorite calls
Types of
Call does it work and that is somebody who wants specific
And Alex doesn't really have much smell
Hello
Panda
Maybe
Another thing that you
You put up on your way
Adidas
Fluential
NWO
That out there
Well
We have
What
County commissioner
The reopening
County Jail
Ward
Is going on
So is that the top five
Overall wildly out of context or things that you just making up of
Top of other stories
Mueller airport is actually something that goes back to his Y2K broadcast so that one's an old standby
Beautiful remember that one the chains at the airport hangar
So what's going on here is actually two different from the situation we saw on our last episode where a caller wanted Alex to say huku was
How to being ask for specific information and instead of answer directly launches off into a ram
About Vega
Insinuations that get the collar no closer
Diving any real information
Well he's saying
Things that sounds like like
Could be information right
In a way that's kind of condescending
So the caller probably feels put
Put on the back foot a little rat
I mean if you were looking at it through the wrong parameters you might see him actively doing harm to his cause to fight the glove
What are those brown bears are doing here because
He is the enemy of a conspiracy theorist
You can be wrong about everything get away with pretty much all of it as long as you're really vague about it give yourself enough wiggle room
To pretend
You know
The curious because that was also a question that he could have avoided by going you know what you're right
I'm going to get somebody on that and then moved on
Just been like that be a great thing to put on my website let's get good ideas
Brother to take care of this do it the right time
Probably between 6
At eight years after this
Alexander been like
Maybe you should get a job
Every week
List all right
Do you want to guess
I didn't BuzzFeed duallist on them
No okay
They got paid off not to globalists
Child in there
Okay I'm going to go with
You think he hates Gates yet right
But he's not top
Globalist
I don't know I know bush is a puppet
Sure
My answers are
Arnold Schwarzenegger
Sylvester Stallone
Okay
But all they remember the cast of The Expendables
I wanted
Top 5 or 10
We always talk about
Right
What
So no Satan
No Bill Gates Epstein no world economic forum
Remarkable almost as if all these characters why does important to Alex in 2003 because at that point.
Conspiracy Community was still in the
It's all about the Rockefellers and Rothschilds phase and grown out of that yet
Now one of the things I think it's kind of just I was laying in bed trying to fall asleep last night like how
Much Alex's like
Bulshit
Is basically like how comic books operate
How like there's an ark
Foot Locker shoes
Pop up like way down the road and I can pretend that they've been there the whole time
He really does work that way
It makes sense
I guess
But isn't that also makes sense based on
His reading comprehension level
Syfy
What kind of runs
Hand-in-hand with someone who'd be at the comic books right
I don't know it's
It's interesting to me
Yeah I wonder if he's a silver age guy
Is probably a new 50
I don't know
We get back to the biolabs gallery here
And he's wrong
About everything
Timer 10:30
More
Level four
Quantity
I'm not going to build these
This is
More dangerous
PowerPoint
Now
Ireland
Levels of propaganda
Impressively wrong about just let everything in that clip
It is he has this ability to analyze data
The comes in from different strata of the media or whatever
They didn't make dozens and dozens or even 36 bsl-4 lab
These are bioweapons lab
They aren't super Dane
Sporting down
They not only didn't
Admit that they released foot mouth
Actually released a statement saying that they don't do any work with foot mouth at that lab
And it never said the people couldn't restock livestock
They're just regulations in place where the outbreak needs to be contained and then after the disease has been eradicated you have to wait 21
Days to restock your animals for safe
Right
What they say
Everything Alex is telling his audience
Basically made up
It's astonishing to me and I honestly don't think that you can be that wrong without
Like to be wrong
Yeah
Cuz that's
That's out that's out of
Control either that or he's really is just freestyling
You know just off the Dome just left he was freestyling he be right about more things
Probably reality
I don't know if it's just that he
Constantly and like only get
Headline
X from sources that are
Intentionally
I can't I can't imagine this is an accident he's he's like a hole in the
The force you don't like any incorrect information could exist
Within the guy the University of our data analyzed
Well yeah good on you to analyze this strata. Okay
Everywhere earlier where I
Baltimore
About this story
The monkey didn't
Escape from a bsl-4 lab bio lab
It was a rhesus monkey that escaped from the California National Primate Research Center
The reason visit all relevant to the story Alex's covering is
Because that Center is at UC Davis
And there was talk of building a 150 million dollar biocontainment lab there
The monkey escape from their normal facilities made that investment look uncertain
The headline for the story that Alex is covering his quote monkeys Escape May sink bio-defense lab
Right so what's going on is that because
Makes up the stuff that he reports to the ADI
Status
That's cruel
B I mean
Malicious Jay-Z
Lying
This incident was enough to put the kibosh on this plant never got built jucydate
With Outlet.
I don't know if they ever see million-dollar lab I don't know if they ever like figured out who did it or
Used to
Rihanna's documentary about this 11 monkey
Name Cesar
Caesar the monkey
Did he rise
Diddy
Your f****** did the Eros
Is like s*** man to Alex's just got these
F****** stories
Hearing about him
Stumbling into DARPA
Me tell you
YouTube
Always and placement
Literally
Where are the ground
A researcher walk by
Okay
The stories evolved
I do like
Appreciate that there is a just an innocent bystander
Wondering why God likes
Hold on is that Alec
Jones
I do think I mean I ask somebody who has worked
In University offices or and
You know my dad's a professor and make some
Acquaintance with a how
I don't know how Alex is getting into these buildings at midnight
Why are some kind of special access or like
Somebody right allowing him to shoot
And I doubt that would
Be something that like
It would have to go through some sort of a
I saw this documentary where this guy just got out of jail
He had a plan he was like we got to take off this cuz
Casino
Cuz when you with cuz sometimes
Casino win
He's a little bit better he's like sometimes a casino win
But then sometimes you win
See here's the problem with this guy was clearly referencing Planet of the Apes
100 different
Plenty of other
See I thought that story is all made up
There's no chance
From a lady from Wichita
And she is a new listener
He's going to freak her out
Okay
And so you just tried to scare her a little bit
Awesome MoMA
I love this so much
Alex doesn't know anything about Wichita
What are the ways that he's able to
To Free People by throwing out specific
Yes like
The name of your local paper
Right or something right now to make it look like no I actually have research
No s*** about Wichita
Twice in 40 seconds here
That's awesome
I asked
Grocery store people about that
He said he's heard a rumor but
They have made it
All the way
Wichita Eagle Beacon I work tonight
Okay
Dylan
Yeah yeah
The right back at you
Buy checked at the Dillons in Wichita they do in fact
Accept cash
Can credit for groceries ask people to submit
I imagine they'd be out of business really fast cuz there's a lot of other grocery stores in Wichita. Snot like
A one-stoplight town or whatever
I guess Alex might be a coastal Elite thinking that all
Kansas is just
Tumbleweeds in saloons or whatever but
I do I do like that he's deploying like traditional cold reading tactic
Text to just like
I'm thinking it's another of the newspaper in Wichita my correct what's the name of that newspaper
The CEO of
Solutely
Single letter m
Could see through this is just like absurd so funny couldn't be clearer that I
Alex's just making s*** up here and he doesn't know any specifics about Wichita
What does this is embarrassing stuff I would ask
Why would a grocery store require a thumbprint to buy or sell
Have you ever gone to the grocery store to sell something
David Carter
You act like go there till like
You don't bring a sack of potatoes
Jewel-Osco
Make I make some nice homemade muffins and then when I go through the self-checkout I leave them up
Puffins on the thing and then I will check it out.
I think that maybe you that is just language that is meant to invoke the mark of the beast I think you might be right
I'm sorry just throwing it around I could be
So you're the last clip from this episode where Alex continues to try and freaked out this lady from Wichita
Disturbed I mean
Am I going to be one of them
Security Board
Want
And a lot of
Sure
To get rid of the body
What
Yeah
Okay
Toro Loco
Gestapo spouse
Boil you in acid
I'm going to come to your house cuz they want your husband
This might be a little little bit extreme borderline like Freak Out the Squares level
Definitely the vibe I was getting to my call
So we go to the first
Whole lot of clips of Alex being mad at sports
On the last episode
It honestly didn't really feel that important
Right on the 31st
But it continues
Yeah and that's that's why I was like
Took notice of it
Kobe Bryant
Colby Bryant
Respectful
Pork Gyros
Football
Worried about everything
Care about your liver
I mean like he just seems to think that it's impossible to care about sports and the country
I don't know how to respond to that I mean considering the amount of jingoistic military as
Bulshit that's Ram down of our f****** throat through Sports is a lot of it you think Alex
So he talked about Kobe Bryant there
Call Babe
This actually is a big part of why he's mad
Because there's a lot of news
About Kobe Bryant
Auntie is sexual assault
Yeah yeah yeah
Vinatieri
Alex has some weird news about the
Girl on
The news
Thousands of websites
But just
Watching her
Milo my God no
Of the TV show
Gwen
Pressure
I mean Armenian
Wearing
Dumpling around
What is an acronym
Bio weapon
About the good Alamo
Bewildered
It's really hard to deal with
Alex is 29 years
Irene fat
That sounds like he's going to end that would like I had cheese there Reedus
Like what are we what the
I don't know but I also think Alex has his story entirely wrong
Oh I might be wrong about this I can find no evidence
To the contrary
I think there was here's what's going on
So on July 28th
A couple days before this episode
Songs featured an interview with Tom Leykis
The notoriously disgusting radio host
Essentially just for being a chauvinist pile of s***
Right here decided he was going to out Kobes
Accuser which was the story that Hannity and Colmes were cover
From Hannity's intro to that interview
Quotes
Most news stations have a policy against naming sexual assault victims so why did Los Angeles nationally syndicated radio.
Talk show host
Feel compelled to identify Kobe Bryant
Accuser he joins us from Lost
I don't think I've ever had a person alleging to be Kobe's accuser on the show but
What seems to be going on here is that Alex is conflating dislike us interview with another thing goes happening at the
Time which is there people were circulating pictures of of a woman
Accurately claiming was the Accuser
Tom Leykis
Did get the name of the person
Yes people
Alex
Combined these two imagine review and is complaining about this person he didn't actually watch an interview with
Attention to detail and journalistic standards
But my belief that dreams are real I guess if anybody like I would be very open to that
Figuring out more about this like if someone were able to
Send me the Hannity & Colmes interview that Alex is talking about yeah I'd be happy to amend
My feeling on this
Yeah this is what I think you making up interview
It just seemed like the whole angry Sports thing that Alex has been on his
Mostly kind of about
I mean it
It is
It is when you see his misogyny and racism come into
Conflict
Trump's conflict
Well that's fair experiencing both simultaneously
He's really focusing on the misogyny
The primary
What it comes down to it I'm with all men overall women
Yeah that's the
You know they say
Got to have a code
It is right now for a Herald
I think
He's doing an improv scene with himself
Goodbye where he pretends to
Get into a conversation with somebody who doesn't like care the infowar cuz he wants to play golf
You know
I'm hard
This is me
I wanna go play golf
Fred
I would
That his
Story
That he made up
Kids describe
Other people as insane
In fact
Atmore revealed his own in sand
Yeah sure but I think there probably is
Maybe a kernel of truth to it
Like maybe somebody blew him off
Outside restaurant or something and I mentioned that they were going to go play golf
Or something very reasonable thing to do
Alex's turned this into like
Right
People on the radio are like this person 38
All checks out
So I'm
In the present day we know that Alex
Is
The most important person in the world
The Trump Administration
Call Tim the Texan
I always wanted to know what the text and thought about that
Putin listens
Everyday
He needs to bolsonaro might listen we know his son does
I took that one might be true
But
The dude not so noticeable and a guy brings up something that makes out
Very
Excited
Says you're cuckoo
State senator
Read the
I just washed it
Okay
He looked at me like that
I was crazy but I was not
This is a huge moment for me
A little bit Lower State
Maybe
Alex has a interesting
Little bit of a story sort of pop culture
Pinterest kind of story
And he is
I'm so excited about it
Ronnie
Homeboys
Sounds true
Talk about it
Amazing
Amazing so just wasn't proven out of the KGB under orders installing it sent hit-squad secure
The claim that was made in the biography of Wayne called John Wayne the man behind them
According to an article on military.com Wayne learned of this plot and quote obviously not one to let a thing like
Communist assassin's get him down
Wayne and his script writer Jimmy Grant allegedly
Hitman
Beach and Stage the Box
Mocx
Locution
No one knows exactly what happened after that but Wayne's
Friend said that Soviet to work for the FBI from that day on
Who dodged the draft also apologized
Assassination attempt
I don't get a lot of heads of state apologize
I don't know how else to put this other than to say that this is a stupidly fake story being passed along his biography
Really funny that Alex
King of skepticism a guy who can see through all the BS is just taking it at face value
Makes them feel good about his worldview
By guy named Michael Mane and let's just say that accusations that he makes things up in his book
Are not uncommon for instance much of his biography of Frank Sinatra involves things that he claims
He remembers from Pillow Talk he had with Ava Gardner when she was 45 and he was 17 and they had an affair
During which he revealed all sorts of things that you never told anybody else God damn that is some good backstory
Like that I like that this one article in the guardian
There was a time that David Niven
Stricken with the motor neuron disease that killed him called Munn in
Mike I've got to see you
He told him to bring his tape recorder and spoke of his secret love child his legitimacy and his failed attempt
Shoot himself as well as with Princess Grace Kelly
Sounds true
A lot of his work seems to revolve around made-up things that happened
To him that involve a one-on-one exchange with someone who is now dead
Maybe unverifiable information is kind of his stocking
Contrave
Tell me the story about John came from Bonne getting to know after you played a role
Telephone box in the film Brannigan
How do you said that John Wayne treated him like a son after that
325 telephone box
Just how
Bees
Weird
Stories
F****** fly through the world
Unsuspend sake posted an onion article
Absolutely true
The families of people he's written about say that this is outrageous
Buy is fabricated backstory
Download a s*** being made up by someone trying to sell narratives that are self-aggrandizing
Think so just kind of makes sense why Alex what identify with this and accept it unquestionably
Is it called
To him
So I noticed a trend
Where was the thing that seems to happen a lot
Especially in the past
Maybe it's because
Technology in
Manpower is a little
Gated at this point share
Constantly ends up
Hanging up on people while they're still talking
I wanted to play a little clip of that reveals something about his politics
Texel
You over here
And of course
Job
But
Just remember when Alex is trying to
Pretend to be like this enlightened libertarian type
Pretend to be a little bit more moderate he actually is in order to
Is transphobic
Narratives of such
No
Now he is
He's just shifted at Target
Yeah what's what's important
To think about whenever it comes to
Repealing abortion rights
Is that you know all of the Republicans who who as
Times have changed in as the popular opinion has changed towards a lot of subjects
Have come along with
You know as things get moved back
We're going to find out they were not coming along with
They were playing along with another
Very funny
Indifferent
So
Yep be ready
So speaking
I will have to go all the way back
This
Who's a real weirdo
Let me give you this there
You know that thing where you are
Were people saying he lauded
Republican
Fishing is not avoid
Well there's more to that
And a republic
All laws
Check the higher standard
Blackstone
Walk commentary
God's law
Higher laws
Republic
Reserved
Biblical
Set the government
Is a minister of God
Holding his
Righteous command
Honest evildoer
Encourage
Good
Sounds great
A democracy makes
Majority got capable of
Determining Good and Evil
Popular opinion
Mcall
Wild against democracy and also Alex is responsive that color was
Website called The Matrix has you
And it's a blog post about how there's a secret
13th amendment in the original Constitution
That has been secretly removed and eliminated from history
Secrets
13th
Amendment
The original custody lawyers were barred from serving in government position
That's basically just a piece of sovereign
Citizen lore
This was a reprinting of an article written
Buy a roofer named Alfred
Which was mostly about how much he hates Legos
Lawyers better than where I thought it was going shirt
This article was written in 1991 and then the next year Alfred decided to try to run for the Texas Supreme Court
On a Libertarian ticket
Here's a blurb about his candidacy
Forty-seven-year-old
Who attended college for a year to run for the Texas Supreme Court on the libertarian party ticket
Despite the fact that the Texas Constitution says candidates must be a practice
Lawyer or judge with 10 years experience
Basis is kaposi on a personal interpretation of an old law that he said
Not lawyers to run for judicial office in the 10 former Confederate States
Of course my if my interpretation is ridiculous I'll wind up looking like another nut on a soapbox
Hero
How'd that go
You look like a knot on a cell phone
A big Sovereign citizen type
Show about Sovereign citizens put together by a court administrator
In Kansas City
Discussing followers of that ideologies potential for violence it says
One of the most notorious Alfred at sac
Made a statement
Quote we have the right
To keep and bear arms in order to shoot our own politician
Yeah this dude is a major figure in the community of sovereign citizen interpretations of that idea
Ecology is the people art subject
The laws of the country or state but
To God's law
He believes that this is part of the founding of the United States
Supported by Alex on this show
This is not sound or well-constructed as legal analysis it's beyond
Zealot arguing that the country was established to be a theocracy
Simultaneous with the time. If I recall correctly
Everyone was
Screaming about Sharia law
Through his website
This guy offered me also published a magazine called so
Suspicions which is about as awful as you might think
Their volume 11 number 3 issue from 2001
Gluten article
Got titled the truth about homosexuality
Which is about as homophobic
As a YouTuber
I was hoping it was like
Is dope nope
It defines homosexuality as a fetish homosexual relationship they quote horrendous perverted septic and
Ethically dangerous practice
The author also claims the quote nothing
Turns gay men on both shocked
This passage actually really stuck out to me in this essay
Perhaps I'm more sensitive to the issue than most
But whenever I hear someone described themselves as openly gay
I automatically visualize them engaged with another man in a revolting active anal intercourse ruining my appetite
That sounds like parody
It's not if you would even though it is not
This is the sort of garbage that this dude who the caller is quoting
His publisher
It's great stuff all around here everyone is is knocking it out of the park
Yeah
I mean I guess that sort of secondary inasmuch as like this legal analysis they were all living under
God's law in the Republic is meant to support that
Is written by the same person who's publishing this
Tripe
Honestly they are August 1st is
It's not
Very good nice mostly phone calls and a lot of them are really boring a disappointing so
I had to try and find something interesting to talk about so that there we go
We get Alfred adsic
Another caller
And this distract me is really weird
Actually if there's to be any
Any justice
Cinemaworld bushes
Detroit
And
Painting services
What
The same crime
Until then
Is there will be
Against
President
Coward there's two things that I think a really weird about this
Semi-regular caller it goes by Jay Q
I am like that could be a initial or a nickname buttons just because
It's also code for the Jewish Quest
Which is
The commuter
Instead of having to be open about it they talk about the Jake you
Suno
Whatever he's called in I've tried to keep my like ears open for possible dog with least
So far it's mostly not but it is
Still something that I
I've never met anybody who goes by that alias
That's no good no
And second
I believe
Dating someone Alex understands
The responsibility that he has to not engage
In directed viola
Rhetoric
At this point in his career he understands
The even
Bandying about these ideas about Bush deserving
To be hung
A somewhat unhealthy
As a way to communicate with the audio
Sure
I don't know if that's exactly what's going on such a far cry from what he does in the present day
Call because the guy we can't listen hey
Happy saying violent things like that
The color is even bring even said to trial
And I think it's a 100% reasonable thing to believe that
George Bush should be tried at The Hague
And then his punishment will be what
Desert imagine like that compared to how we talk about fauci
Like in the present-day who's just a guy it's outrageous like
One of the only things that I can think of
Maybe maybe maybe it's me
Piano putting a little bit too much into this but like
It feels like one of the only reasons that behavior would be so different
Is there in the pasture wasn't awareness that like
This isn't good I can't do this
Maybe I'm wrong cuz I think that's
Definitely
True
I think it is irresponsible and wrong
Do you know dangerous
It's very weird
I don't know why he would cut off the
Call like that
Maybe not sure might be that
And I'm part of it might be a
Maybe he knows the color
Maybe on another level he's just better able to
Controls f******
Emotions such as stuff like that
That's definitely true
Clip
I don't know
Something's worth we're taking a peek at
But I guess
Alex
You're one of the things do that I have to check in on his like Alex is so matted sports that I have to go through Alex sports headlines
Come Around the World Cup or something else is mad about internationalism or something
Nothing I couldn't find anything
Will get back
Present-day probably next
Squeak
The past
I like it feel like I'm in the past I think there's more meat on phones back then
Learn a lot more indiscriminate screaming
Fight Night
I'm Leo
Dzx Clark I hope you all have
Great
A email
And maybe creamy also by the way
Someone sent me a picture of a Starbucks near me
Tango
Cease and desist
What the sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color