Knock knock
I have great respect for knowledge
B
Sick of them posing
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Welcome back
To knowledge my time dance
The altar of Selena
A little bit about
Alex
DeAndre Jordan
There's alot going on in the world
Sure
It's the dreamy creamy summer
But I was going to have a special
And so this week
Astronaut ice cream
I would be exploring the world
I have some mixed results there
There a lot of mixed results outside
Between
Like
Decent
Astronaut ice cream
Am I going to find something
It's really terrible
Some of these astronaut ice cream
Will give to some of the specifics or at the week but whatever
But I wanted to bring this up as my bright spot
About a picture I'm going to send you
McAllen
All right it is very dumb
My right spot then is there's there's only they can be only one answer
Miss Morrell and the big steppers dropped and I can tell you right now
Culmination of
The past hundred years of music
It is incredible there is no hyperbole that you can make about this album
Delia logical endpoint of the moments
First album
Proved correct
That Lift Us.
I don't know Samson the first album
Years I've heard a lot of great things everything
Kind of busy
Have a bright spot of Their Own
Explorer Alex's
Sandy Hook
Hello
What's a bright spot
I don't know
Pretty good
Yakima weather
Tag myself as an over 40 year old
No it like you know the world so dark right now that the
Crypto
Financial collapse
What's your bright spots to see all the
I know
Some good memes have come out of it for sure
So far as the wider world there's not a lot of things are looking really really talk right now
My little corner of it's looking okay
I've had
A nice little vacation
Cuz it's some of your
Your listeners know I'm
Ben supposed to be in trial
Against
We were supposed to be on it
Stanza
Took my kid down the Guadalupe River
You didn't just drop him off at the Guadalupe River
Just loading the LBG LBJ Library call it good
It's been a it's been a good couple weeks but we're out of
Just kind of sitting here twiddling our thumbs
As as soon as this bankrupt
You know I assume everybody knows we're talking about the here but like right on that
Right on the eve of the trial were supposed to have the first trial that jokes
Engineers a strange little stunts
Pepsi start
That did not involve himself or the company by which he operates
Is business under
It involves some little paper in
10 years ago
Stop the trial because basically when you file bankruptcy in automatic federal court
Witnesses.
And so we had all day they let us right up to that thinking we were going to go to trial
Few days beforehand
Yeah it sucks for me so right before that was
It has to be like the way it was so immediately I mean like me and Jordan had like
Tickets I lost money on this you're fine
Surfline
Summer
Maika'i
We had a
On March 10th
And then it was to adjust a whole bunch
Henninger new attorney number 11 at the time
The courthouse on break
We got some of our sleep
That doesn't seem cool
Tell me what
Scooby-Doo
Like a ghost suddenly appears outside the courthouse in my we gotta shut this down for 2 weeks
Under and Alex Jones mask
DAV
So when that happen
I don't know
Bankruptcy lawyer
Makes my eyes glaze over
But of course
When you're representing who I represent in your suing who I'm suing
The most powerful lawyers in the world
Cheapest just to do it
Sitting on the sidelines
Bankruptcy
And it's because we have
So basically a l
We got him we got
Lynnwood
Lin-manuel Miranda
Destiny's Child
No like we went seriously that when when when you have a friend like you comes to you and then just like
Take care of don't worry about it
For me it was I had
Schedule
You know what these guys cause all sorts of inconvenience for everybody else
After all the witnesses who were going to come for the court it was setting things up
But as far as truby they taste
Vacation
I think it's probably like
Always been a feeling to like
This isn't going to
Get rid of
Trouble
You know it's always been
I mean
From the moment to start
Everybody knew it was the question was
With the proposals are putting up be enough to make these cases go away in your ass
From the started
Explain
Are they watching us right now to set up
I just want to make sure
Nobody's looking
When your sisters may be familiar with
With bankruptcy
Purdue
Pharmaceuticals went down with the opp
Bankrupt
Euros personal bankruptcy as a personal consumer when CarMax
Chasing you down for that
Is very very
Experience
And you killed 100 million people
What we call subchapter
Bankruptcy is by taking entities which were
Doing nominal amount
What's a business basically
The plants
This is the money you have
Nobody's going to look really closely
Because you have third parties who are
Funding the bankruptcy
Like this is this is what you got understand
When Purdue goes into bankruptcy
Third-party sources
Could have been sued
Purdue the money to settle the bankruptcy under the table
How much money is there
When Jones and his attorneys, so how went that way
And what they didn't realize they had none of the necessary ingredients to make it
Came in there was just a sham you just can't write
Infowars
On a piece of paper
Hand it over and say all right that's the company now everything's going to be do that like that doesn't work
My main problem is that you can do that
A few weeks off from
I know this is all
There's no question about that
And the first thing that happen
None of these people are doing any business none of them have any assets what are we even doing here
We're all heading towards the dismissal
Make a bunch of witnesses
But most people understand
Unravel
The silliness that they put on
And your rights a game sometime
Nonsuit
Dismiss our claims against
Bankruptcy
Even though the the attorneys for the entity's and the trustee for the entity's
Are happy there like
Screaming about how he's been denied the right
Craig is now all of a sudden
I'm very strange position
He took these paper entities
Separated from self
And in the moment that it had a separate
Did all of a sudden
Ready feels like
He was going after
About Reno on Showbox
Right now is what we're going to talk about
Complaining about that
I'll Durbin
On Friday the news came out that the bankruptcy
Issue was sort of boots
And things will be moving forward
You know the reason why I reset
Onyx since I certainly don't speak
Got the language of the Court
How about we talk about Alex's show from May 8th
Cuz there's a
You wanted to go over
I wanna
Emailing me asking me what the hell is going on
Invite yourself on our show out of spite
To our listeners
Egypt some of the lovely correspondence are the sweetest people in the whole planet
I'm actually talking about
Mainstream media
This will be your statement to Brian stelter
Like bankruptcy
Sponge
I can talk about it
What's a better selection
So we can get everybody up to speed
Nice very technical and
Bazaar in
Bubba pain in the ass
If we titled things other than like just the name of
The date then I would consider it but
Coliseum
You cannot find the episode you are looking
We don't we don't want to draw people in
Aesthetic
Wrinkles
I just stupid
Yeah but we start here
The bankruptcy
It's informative showing
Point
Really I'm not good at it
Something up
And building it up
Information 2 weeks ago
That I mentioned on air and the days later was even the Associated Press
And then we got more information Friday
And now we've gotten part of the documents
We're getting more
But
You talk about racketeering
You talk about a league
What they're trying to do with info
Record
Is unbelievable
It's all poison.
So he's got some
Is what I hear
From him I heard that but would I'm focused on his did he say he's bad
Things up
Well
I have a mixed feeling about that I was thinking the same thing because that is true and also not truth
He does it a lot
But he's good at getting himself
How to do it
Nicholas Adams
Execution
Soros
Is behind
Is bankruptcy
There's some shady dealings
Walmart
This is just great
Start
I can hear you not answering the
Do you hear from me right now
Redding Dock of
Is whenever I hear anybody now on Infowars talk about we have documents
Taking the deposition of the corporate representative Daria car
And those documents with the most hysterical
I came with my case today inside
Here's a Wikipedia printout
Wolfgang halbig
I don't know what the hell.
I know two things
One it's going to be really dumb
I've actually worked out what the document they're talkin
With me cuz this is all hitting me idea
The document Alex is talking about is
Is Jeff
The u.s. trustee
To the courthouse
I think
It's it's that
The government was like hey come on man
Come on
Alexis Wright
He doesn't understand how Civic
Specific thing
Is what we're dealing with right now is why I think George Soros
Rusty
You made a recommendation from the court about
Thumbs up thumbs down on this bankruptcy
Job to do
I can think of in terms of like what is a document
Autosource is behind all this week
It has been kind of generic and it's been kind of
It's been thrown more
Really recently than us
The courts
I'm laughing to myself and I'm thinking
Well actually
That's pretty good
If people in my dream
But I'm the other mind
Is I keep seeing him say this s*** about our judge
Like really antagonistic hostile should about our judge
You know
Tubidy
She got to go in
Walk into the courthouse every day when arriving this trial
Yeah like I don't think she also has the power to stop
Miami I'm a lawyer who is currently
Suing somebody and trying to get them held legally responsible for the things they said
Like your speech
If you were talking about that judge to do something
The moment you say oh well now he's crossed into Crazy Town
I don't think the responsibility falls on this judgment
Counsel representing Alex Jones
People understand
Picked up by a new guidance of former US attorney
United States
Department of turn
Who was
An Eric Holder
But now he's running the show for Alex Intex
Think I need to get a leash on this damn flying
If he wants to come and make a big reputation of himself
Representing some
Proto-fascist
The least you could do is try
Rain in the conspiracy theories about what's going on with our judge
For fucksake
Get your house in order
That would be nice
Yeah and it's not like they're be wavy
He could really affect
Actively like have a gag order about the case
Without it like
Skydiving blowback
Exactly
Some really like
Interesting allegations
Littermaid throughout the course of this
I think you'll enjoy
Some of these
Something
Hi claims
But Alex
Here's some more about Soros for you
In this case
Against Alex
He's all over the
Man
Thousand Deasia District
Attorneys
County attorney's now
George Soros
Information Bureau
Thousands of
Christian leaders
Watch the presidents
Was rigged Jerry's
Is red cord
Default
Operations against him
And they admit that
Admitted
Official
Federal court
Did George Soros
Publicly
Arrogance
The Bravada
I would say
To say to
The people
If you
Stop this
Mistrial
George Soros
Personally will sue you
What would it look like
Is that
People have
Before years
Amazon
Certainly
I make some aggressive decision
It always pays off
And people were second-guessing
When I decided to send a letter to the United States Bankruptcy
George soros's controlling all
Bankruptcy Court
Is controlling all of this in a few fuckaround you cannot
That was
That was a very aggressive
So I just I just want to
Pat myself on the back a little bit
I mean like like look I don't mean to be dismissive she's about to put this manager this literally I think at this point
Believing
Not believing but winning is audience to believe
Between the United States
Justice my office
People I know George Soros
United States bankruptcy judge
To make him not have a bankruptcy
When it's actually the attorneys for his own company who aren't fight ye bankruptcy
That is actually exactly what
He does believe that there is a level of coordination that is almost comical
Between you and
Update on this Thursday
2300.
So,
Half of that
Especially considering there's a number of states where the DEA
Thesaurus would have to be like able to
Control State commissions and governors and
You know the problem
With this is that
This the most
Unreasonable thing about this is that somebody would be such a good administrator that they would be capable of
I mean I would almost want somebody who had
To be empowered
Shredded fight
I would guess that this is some sort of calculation based on
The number of DEA
Candidates
Who received some sort of donation from some group that in some way has money from Soros Regenerist
Something like that
What's your hubby some
Usually bulshit
You two like some blog like a
Breitbart
Progress for America or America
Here's a list of DEA
And somebody Infowars will see that and then the story will become
George Soros runs nice headline
Something exactly like that and cuz cuz a Alex told me to write this headlines
But in this case what's weird about these comments that he's making
Is it seems like he's seen something
Descensum
This is very boring there's nothing
Ripping his ass off
Take me to Subway
Personally involved
In the story that Alex
Because I just want to know what document
What document made him
Loses
Maybe
His maybe the kind of thing that ends up driving you crazy because I would that dollars
Is the donuts there is no.
I would bet you documents to Donuts
You remind me a lot of
Dan in the early days
And this argument used to get so excited
YouTube
And over the years he's realized it literally every time it's going to be a run
Football away and down you go
Interesting
Misrepresentation
I think it's just that Jose Garza is the Travis County
And see when he was running in the election cycle did get some donations
Pictures of
Yeah
Is that the extremely routine action
United States trustee for a banker
Filing a recommendation with
Stuff that extremely routine action
Absolutely
Come on
You're saying it's
It's totally routine
I actually have some information here that might
Put this in a different time
Okay
It makes me proud of who I am
It makes me really really
Proud
I'm all of you show
The lawyers rated green light
But I already told you
Part 1
Lawyers that don't get into much detail just
Midshipman
Called up
The federal court in the trustees
And said
Department and the president
As policy
This is basically order it is the policy of the US government
Executive
Don't sound so routine now does it
Biden called UPS or assault Mary Garland
And we got to get this s*** done okay
Because only the executive can do this alright
It started when all the way up the flagpole it literally goes all the way to the top
America
So I don't know
Lake let me break it down to simple as possible with what the
United States
For this weekend
So you can understand what he did
Infowars LLC
In any other
Petition for a small business Banker
Hey we want to use a bankruptcy
Seaford businesses that conduct a little business but not a ton
What's the best way to scout
And then after they did it
United States
It's called schedules schedules
What
Business they do what their revenue is what they actually have
Schedule
We ain't got squat we don't have anything
Nothing
We don't do business
United States trustee files Rico
I'm not sure that this just bankruptcies appropriate for subchapter 5
Cuz they said they didn't do any business so we're not sure there's a broke
Accommodating tone
The answer is
But I do appreciate its Mark leaving out the
Gets involved
That's the thing here is that
Is revealing to me to do
I hear what you're saying when y'all think that Jones stinks in his mind
I still
Tuesday believe that Jones just thinks that anytime he can take something and twisted
Jamaica Teresa persecuted
Victim of some sort of
And I think
He knows damn well
A store
Where they try to do a double backflip
Flip and landed on there
I think that he knows
And it's in a sick it's so sick to me to that
He is absolutely private up that on
Start this crap
This bankruptcy Hail Mary and I
No now I'm being screwed out of my home bankruptcy is like there's always another hat
So annoying
Remarkable
I even if he does say he needs to get a green light from his lawyer so I definitely would have encouraged that to happen
Billion dollars to pay that bounty on a judge that I called for last time
I got the green light for my lawyers I don't think he was on Christmas or not $5 judge
So I mean like here's the thing though it's Jones's is on notice he knows that the FBI had to get involved because there were people making
Threats against the judge
Connecticut on his website
He's known about Downhere Intex
Texas
Making threats online
We've had conversations
Absolutely nose
Look up of course
A hundred percent
These kind of things
The more I just cannot stand the kind of attorneys
I think that you have fun
You have to look at this from a different perspective
I am that is what Alex has a job create
A lot of these FBI agents were having to provide security for the
You know.
Do you want them out on the street
Protecting like the house
Houseless snow
Of course not you want them meaning rich and Powerful
Is it is the truth it isn't because
Because
When your Texas State judge
You look you've got the bailiffs in that bill
That's you protect
If you got
Credible actionable intelligence against
To investigate
Exactly
There's just nobody coming
Protect you
Particular Courthouse
Right leg in this is they all know that
This is all been discussed
To say that I am like
You know involved in some sort of
Bohemian Grove conspiracy
I don't just keep
Whatever
But the fact that he keeps directly Northeast
Is that a US bankruptcy
F*** you
That's just insane
If you want to look at the
The points of this conspiracy we got Soros
We got B
We got married Garland in the entire doj
We got the bankruptcy judge we have the u.s. trustee we have marked we have the lawyer
Pretty much
I mean what's great about
What was great about it once again
We're not mentioned just left out of it
Oh well I hope so
Trustee letter
This is this
That's
But mostly the documents
But he's talking about
Future
And build it up
International news
The document
The Mummy
Put together powerful articles
So soon
But if you want to see
Department
Getting involved in a mi EX
The federal courts
Yeah
Show trials in
Bostitch anymore so I say okay will do an emergency we're going to station
That's not what you did
They are
Crosshair
I hear you fear
That's what I get from you
Bankruptcy in the air
The reorganization of his business
I mean conclusion here though is that he should be able to reach the
Other conclusion of that as well which is when you asked
What's the question
Have you ever seen the justice department intervene in a bankruptcy trial
The answer is
That's how much of an a****** you are
I don't I don't know the answer is no
The Department of Justice
Bankruptcy Court
To act as a
A neutral
Third-party Observer
And so
You argue the government
Physician
Argue what the government
Position is as if he was representing
I mean he's almost like a
We have a lot of expertise
Javar
Neutral
It is it
There's no doubt that
The position of the u.s. trustee token this case was aggressive
For the US trustee's normal
Opposition
Tell much of an ass-whole he is
You're right because this Bank
Cookie was a sham from the start but look the problem is that everybody
The realities is why say bankruptcy is stupid is everybody
Everybody knew
The bankruptcy was stupid
That's not what it was actually
Frowned upon in the bankruptcy world
What does
Was a stop of all the trials
And if it hadn't been done on the absolute evil trial might not have been that dirty
But didn't it stop all the trial
And then basically have a settlement offer
Everybody has to stop take a breath
Look at it and see if you're going to accept it
For a couple weeks
What the problem here is that they did that and then there
Planned funding agreements
Was absolutely ridiculous they basically wanted every one of these all of the cases
Couple hundred thousand dollars
An end to do that on the bond the assurance that Jones would
In the future continue to contribute
Funds to a
Bankruptcy settlement over the year
Which means basically like
You've got to let go
Invite him make money so we can give it
Look here
Reno
We know for a fact
Fact
But there is 25 million dollars that Jones has sitting in a Family Trust
P2P Ark
Free Speech adios
$11,000 a month
There is
Doesn't want to expose it to a federal bankruptcy
And what did you make that offer
Everybody
The hell knows what comes next
Absolutely
With some sort of Nefarious play in the bankruptcy court
I guess we're done that's it
And I'm Joe spinning this like it's saying
Being a part of this whole coordinated
Apocalypse
Stone thing
Think about
Apocalypto
Check on some days
Apocalypse
Billion dollars
Randomly from a mysterious Anonymous donor
Yeah that was me
I transfer that money I just felt like we both scared
I just left
Again biscuit
Again this is a bold move they don't teach at Law School
Emily have a crush
Beat up front
I actually called George Soros and asked him to make
You said yes sir
In that clip their the
He said like
The doj opposes the bankruptcy that's what I was talking about earlier
That is an article about
Trustee letter
Reggie talks about this bankruptcy stuff
Just got to be powerful articles
If you can't get it
I've always ever since you had that episode and suddenly it hit me like a lightning bolt while listening to your thing on that
No you can't
The shooting by that
What you're talking about following up on the story
Why the hell are you talking about
But the idea
Right now there is somebody
Tapout a story
About what this big
I hope they come
I don't know what I mean like
People are so
I hate to say this to you
So many sour grapes
Over the course of this podcast I can't imagine this man satisfy
We do wish you the best
Stanza
Come on
I know they're going to do
So we're going to jump off the lawsuit
Situation
Happy Mother's Day
Newtonian physics teaches us
There is
Unequal
Is that what you
There is good
Amazing crew
Tonight
On Mother's Day
Defense
Yeah
I would love that music
Behind
I would just love to be like
Sohcahtoa tells us what the sign of a triangle is equal to the opposite over the hypotenuse
Comedian says if you get in a bath
Yeah just my science lessons
It's up over a hot beat
He's like I know you'll cry heard that Alex Jones folk music
Remix and all that where he's doing the folk song I have
Complex feelings about that
I'm telling you right now
Listening listening to Alex Jones over death punk is creepiest
Daft Punk Tron soundtrack
I don't know everything about
I appreciate you can
Pick out what that is
Because I can remember most of his music is I just don't have as good of a
St.Louis
Multiple songs from the Tron
Track that he uses bumper
Music so that's fun
Soundtrack
Astonishing
Best way to take a detour for a second to say
That's a f****** music score
Play the entire soundtrack
Excellent
Focus
Mind music
You will never listen
Plutonium
It's weird
You can actually chart
Departure of
And when he was
Fully in control is
Old country
Amarillo by Morning
Oh yeah we used to listen to The Highwaymen Silver Stallion
Harrison Smith on the American Journal
He plays some wild
Music
The Valkyries
Bizarre
Mexico
Alex gets into talking about that
Rally's
Which window
Supreme Court
Opinion has been
45 years ago
George will use your big toe
Pro-life Catholic
Activist
He said why don't you just not criticize abortion on air
Why don't you come out and see if yourself so I want to play
People walk up
Wow
Milwaukee
Even blackbear
Nobody wants these black
You going to take some
They were at
Thousand
The time
Leo and was out at a rally
Pro-choice rally
Hundreds of instances
Of people
Being demons
And hissing about how no one wants
That's wack baby and carrying books by Harriet Beecher Stowe around
Apparently
Jesus Christ
I feel like if this stuff was really
Accurate in any way
Which I don't think it is
Be clear about that
If it was
Alex would not have the exact same examples
420 f***
Commuter cars
There will be new stories that aren't exactly the same
Eczema
The problem with true
I wouldn't be surprised
From time to time
That some
Either either
Person
Spending time Parenthood from counter-protesters
Wilshire I like throwing up
Is like so I don't know the
The pathology of like
Interior fantasy
Interesting place it is
Interesting place
Yeah
It's really hard to tell how much of it is sincere and it is like his
Perceptual distortions
I'd like the things that he's taking in the stimulus
And how much of it is kind of just like
Storytelling
And like lying
Like he usually does
Tiffany about Jones recently so like you up
Holy Angels music
Attracted
The grid I feel like I've always struggled with this idea of first it was this Jones believe what he say does he not believe what he say
Does he ever
It's the package of this is Jones
The basic
Approximation
If you if you contain in whatever you're talking about
25% of the truth
You're free to run.
England
That you can anchor all the bulshit onto you can fly that kite
Who's that 25% of f******
R-Truth
You are toast
That is said
And unfortunately that's why
Forcibly stop
That if you go
Zach's bar in the b*******
That easily toppled his house of cards
You're going to get into trouble but if you always have the bar buddies body
Body
If you think he learned anything
You're going to be disappointed
I think that I might agree with Jordan
Conceptually
That like you have to have some anchor to reality
Just run wild
But what I would disagree with
25%
My birthday
Very interested
Is generous
It reminds me of the Kid Daniel's deposition wood
With Bill asked him to rate his article on the scale of 1 to 10
Really
Estimation of weather and I do think you're right baby. Numbers like at about 5
Yeah I think so
You find a news article that has
Just listen as much as we would like
Like to think
I think I think
Maybe some of the lessons
Are there
Probably not divorced
Right
B
I think we're listening to would leave me to suggest
Maybe don't say defamatory things about
Non-public
A fact.
I put it at probably an 80% chance that he implies Sandy Hook did not happen
That's the wonderful thing
You think it's like
Strange things in deposition
Play the trial
When is the defendant themselves that you're not playing that does money
Either he has
I block you in what you're testifying now is not what you just testified
Your your kind of flopped
He has to argue
That there are still anomaly
Totally
Cooper
MMA it's just going to fall
Balloons fall from the ceiling
You're you're still a
Under this assumption in this world
Alex Jones is going to show up
Assumption
Clear open court
Just afraid for the
Whatever
Talkin about
So you're going to like what are you literally talking
Soros's really afraid
The big reasons they pulled
Does bankruptcy start and stop
None
And so they're like well do this sub buys leather
Because we have
Mark already
Jordan
We got Bobby Barnes
It's coming up in a little bit
About the case
Albert
We have to skip
Abortion protest
And that was kind of sucks his way of talking
Does religiosity show
Sure and he says this
And I think
This is actually a bottle of his
The notion that he's
People who
Have different religious ideas
You don't want to be turned into these crates
You don't want
The connection of the insulin
Because when you God's spirit
God's open hands
Except B
Choice
Did.
And that's not
A spiritual
Group you want to be associated with
You do not
Want to be with that
You want to say
Theraflu if you
You know if you don't
Agreed to join up with that God as Alex
Define zit
You have
My will to be part of
Join up with Alex's specific brand of Christian
Then you accept responsibility for every other problem that
Ever happened
Being able to live in a pluralistic
6 different religious
Beliefs
Seems like you would be defining every other religion as being of God
Isaiah boskin your city and you
Claim that all that goes on in there is
Demonic worship
But that doesn't mean you can't hang out with them
I think Alex has a short jump
That's not good
Revealing themselves as being out of touch
The doors of the infinite just like
Call Dollar
Hang up
Messing around with
The infinite in the doors
Perception
You know what
Yeah you don't know what you're talkin about
Prime
Being an utter freaking
Is it seems to combine a bunch of life
New age
High place of the Kingdom of Heaven like he's basically equating
Joe Rogan doing DMT
Weird
It's almost
Like your Christian identities
Read a bunch of
He's already
He's already been heading that direction
I don't I don't know how to hook different that would be
I honestly I mean
Yeah exactly
So we get to update on some media
I don't know if you are somebody who keeps up with
Former members of the cast members of Saturday Night Live
Mike Myers Mike Myers no I don't really keep up with him I'm more of a
Lego
I know he's about to talk about
And I caught that on Netflix can I watch that the other night
The first
Antenna
Did a bunch of characters and I'm going to tell you
The showing
Goddamn
I'm excited
To hear your review after this clip
Also on Netflix
I got a bunch of calls about it
Call deepen Tavern making fun of the Illuminati
They tax me quite a bit the movie
I thought we would just show out that's what these folks are
He plays a clip of Mike Myers playing the character
It when he says
The folks are so desperate he is he talking about Mike Myers in the cast of in the crew and the producers of that show
Is he talking about
You betcha
Absolutely
Conspiracy
It's the wrong Mike Myers
If Mike Myers shows up
Get in my heresy
I think we did it
Cuz I haven't
This
I study this kind of stuff
Even know this
Existed
This is the big broadside attack
It's really easy to make fun of
Yeah
Sort of like
No
It is a recognition of like how
Geez that people like
This as a thing very clearly
This stuff though I don't know if you remember during all my deposition he used to just obsessing about
Really Broad
Play nobody's f******
Dumbass Rider in California
You have a good doctor
Obsessed with that for a little while
Come on
He claimed the basis of The X-Files
Both exile
So as promised
Earlier
We have
Buddy showing up
Hit someone I believe Mark you've actually been in a room with
Baba
Goodwill furniture sale
I'm going to be
Universal
Stop Crossing
By Barnes I'll be in the room with him in the future shortly so
Please get that give him our best
But it's it's
Despite the
The fact that Jones's corporate representative
Testified that they're considering suing Barnes from Outback
Marker
But like it don't go tell him that
That's why you still on the show
What's funny is if you look at the Infowars LLC bankruptcy assets that they claim
One of the few
Set that they do claim they have
Is a potential mouth
Disclaim
That ain't we might get money in the future
This case
It looks funny
Barnes got the hell out and I think he thought he was
But the interesting part is Tucker Carlson's Daily Caller
Defamation smear scheme against Pakistani
IT workers in the house
Frame them
This is BS
VIP
Is that you do the work for
Hardcore
You don't have no idea
But if you follow like right wing
Mediaite
You know
Give me about a while back
I think he was a little careful on that partially because
The People's Republic and Ed Salem
Reporting by Band-Aid
We're trying to be a little more of the highbrow high-class info
Little bit
Quite the same Circle
Yes very pretentious Infowars
K-Swiss
The reporter this guy who wrote
Daily Caller
For whatever reason
Surprise surprise
He just defeated
Defeated the anti-slapp motion that case of whereabouts
Start Discovery soap
In a very short timeline I'm going to be back in a room with Bob again
Tuesday
Could you say good work Barnes to him and see if his eyes go sad
Goody was there from publicity you take that away from your job
Let me ask you a quick question here by Barnes
In person
Off mic
Does he ever stop
Talking
Like
All the bikes
D-will
String
F****** sentences together without
Without ever taking
Nepal
Look I'm not going to be one who talked s*** about that because listen to me on your show I never shut the
Fuk up I just talked about
But
Whitney what's interesting about Barnes is he was so we had a moment
He had been staying a bunch of s*** about me on air
Deposition
Failed
Did you get that
Way back in 2019
And everybody was glowing about it at
Set the time
A bunch of s*** about me
Right
Are you bleeding
Fred and so I confront him about it the courtroom
You come in here you want to play This Big Show and have a bunch
Take my name
Yeah George Soros a fun the suit
Like me and cough under the suit
Like this is funny money to us
Big sings
And he was so demure any such a passive kind of
Shrinking violet
It's weird how his personality he is so conflict
Converse
Person to person
He's like the Kool-Aid man on Infowars like you think he's like like
Telling me that Robert Barnes
Music
Howard
TV screen in order to
To say to somebody's face
We only have him today
Behind a TV Screw
So we may only hear Bluster
Free stuff
So we may we may just need to
Get ourselves in that sort of State of Mind get ourselves ready
To deal with barn
Put myself on mindsets ready I got my $30
Do the city first
Headspace
Sears Outlet
Giving him an introduction and we'll see what
To discuss
It's up
Interview begins
Credible time in history
Please come on
You just like I am
What do you want to hit on first what is most important
I think it's a
Immediately want to talk about any of that
No I want
What is 20000 euros worth of
Documentary about how they used like
Geolocation data
To prove that
2000 people
Like really obvious
In the way that they
Does putting together and I'll get
Obvious
According to Alex
Camera on them trying to stack 2,000 mules on top of radar
Yeah
You do that what you get bigger platforms like I don't know the weight
Would be at 7
Being fed
Dinesh D'Souza documentary on the recommended
Station of Alex Jones's most Schumann
I can possibly imagine
For most of his career
I'm pretty sure Alex would have been
Been staunchly opposed to Dinesh D'Souza Whole30 con matter of course
The mainline conservative
Strange
Understand
Transformation about f****** party man cuz
I feel like as soon as you get a pardon
From Trump gear
You're in
Are you got to ask
But at least for now yes
The doc
Kamari self is about sort of manual
The manipulation of okay
Menu Buell gas manipulation
People going around and actually physically put it balancing
As opposed
Changing the Dominion machine
From listening to our to the show as much as we have some
The election
Alex was very big into the electronic voting
10 conspiracy
Is all electronic
Was funding for a little while by Michelangelo
We have to have paper ballots in order to maintain the integrity
The election because of all the election
The other Dinesh d'souza's documentaries
Tomorrow's weather
Cuz I do you bring up
Listen film
For those who don't know tell us where it is
Who made it
The foxes say we're not going to air it down
You know totally documented as you said
Electronic scam
What's the Deep State red herring
When you were all over the country for Trump proving it was mules
Voting multiple times getting carpeting the fake valid
Filling a minute in Arena
Improving
You have been totally Vindicated
So Alex you're admitting you got, they got calm
This is the new thing if you're wrong
It's a Honeypot
You were but it's only cuz the Deep state
To get you it's it's not really your
Track
And you're going to miss this
You going to miss 1,000 X 1,000 X
Cuz you were racist right like there's
It's a red herring
Misdirection
This is the exact same thing they did with the birth
Certificate
The Kenya thing was a misdirection
Did they put out in order
To get us because they knew that we would be racist
Jacob a.
Frank Marshall Davis
Essentially proves that they are what they say that their denial blow-dryer
Could you get
Their Jones isn't the only person who wiped
The pizzagate should off his shoe
GameStop
What we do need actually paper pollocksville I guess
He offers
But you also need
A specific
Practice
To be used
You need to do a signature
Because if you did a cig
Get your match check
To this day
On these back
That's absolutely not true
Barnes
Almost all of them have some sort of signature matching as a part of their vote verification
Often done by computer software
Article in the New York Times per cent of all mail-in ballots
In the 2018 election because of signature
Mismatches
Barnes is just straight of line
The states but they scream about the most
About being stolen
20 election like Michigan and Arizona
Place already
A non-existent problem I really feel like we've got pieczenik coming down
The pipeline and it's going to go right back to him and be like
Listen Alex they were Watermark and now we got a double water bike
The next one
I will say that Rogers
Conspiracy about the
Coming into Maine.
North Korean boat
What's that ended up
In Maine
Bugatti
Boats
I can't say anything bad about the people
They love boating 11
That's where a lot of the the fake vote
Okay let me get on
How old is the United States election
Okay
What happened was
Spider-Man the Democrats
Realize they didn't have enough vote
So they
North Korean
Because there are too many
Stupid in one playing it would just go right right right
So they got on
Yeah
Filled with bags and bags of watermarks
Directly from
North Korea
To maintain the United States
Yeah it's actually I can
I see the confusion that's happening here
Game with people to vote fraudulently
It was paper
Paperback
What what
Okay
Define
Siri is not incompatible
With the 200m
Yeah we got to get desouza on the boat situation
CPU definition
Do you like
A sort of like
I'm just I'm not sure I was ready
Jesus Christ
Korean boats
There's a lot of stuff that we have just internalized as part of our fix
External reality event
People who are
Get back to your side which
Beyond
Future like real ass boots
See this is where it gets a little bit sticky
Because Rodger can't specify about the size of boat
But then you think
Will be much easier to catch if it was a big boy
Destroyer
Paddle boat
Just got a giant amount of fighting
It's in the water as paper do
Set the problem
Make any sense yeah you don't want to know where there's two thousand converter
Set the alarm telling you right now
If you ever worked
Trade it with with
But tight.
So I think it was just randomly where Rodger decided to
Stephen King has Rodger
Here is where we get back to your side of the street
Cuz we're going to get back
Into the actual bankruptcy
CK's
Auburn Hills
Maritime issues there I didn't really understand
Citizen Law covers
Here is Alex's starting up a conversation with
I want you to show you those every few days with other a lawyer
Following his work is always informative a learn stuff
But I saw you
Find lawsuits against me really Justice
Eliza go
Rarely
But it's it's
Blueprint
For the future
And so
You know I heard some big
Top law firms
Right after it started they called me and they said
We believe the Deep state
They believe in the Deep state
One case for the biggest law firms like Batman
Brian
Documents
She talking about
Maybe you talk about a transcript
A phone call
A secret phone call
Will Windows Down
Nixon didn't choose to record everything they've been recording since the very beginning that's
Everything
Do we all have burner phones right and like we have
Is there was a like
Tequila with
Missing minutes in the tape
Yeah
Kover Alex Kover Alex
Geode
They get fed their stuff they go do their thing they got no real interest or anything in this
Yeah that struck me as a little off
It does seem weird Zone to be like all man I pulled my entire account
Accountants author
Unbelievable
Generally
A profession that attracts people
Interested in detail
He's a he's a
Deal
Normally is
He's talking about
Because like
The situation
You can throw a dart at a board you're not sure
You know like my lawyer as
It's the nectar
Guarantee
Top law firms
The bankruptcy
Do not believe in a deep state
They're doing their job I mean
I need to be a little more bankruptcy lawyers
Dying
Augusta bankruptcy lawyers office
Is Baker's money the plaintiff
Will the bankruptcy lawyers who made that happen
Get some of that
The piece of paper that says
I don't know it's Norm Palace Palace has been awfully silent ever since he did that
Hilarious
Killing
Wow
Yeah I feel like
Restaurant
Apparently
No no no
He didn't see any of the deep state
I just I know of anybody I can be
All these other people maybe they're out of
Robert Barnes that motherfuker
We have to get back into
He said you don't believe
Best Buy
It's probably true
We have the dress Department
You're not allowed
BRB
Boston
And
Polycythemia
So that bloom away
Gloom
Saudia
Administration called the lawyer of the judge
The judges were there
The first one
There is a judge over the bankruptcy proceeding
That's George Lopez
2 personality cannot reasonably question because he has no control over his behavior
Everybody
What's 2
I'd be afraid
When you talkin about Schmidt
You talkin about somebody
Different he is talking about
Us bankruptcy judge
Who who the bankruptcy wolfers recruited
Hindu being a trustee for Infowars LLC
For being a
And he's there to make sure everything's kosher
Dow Jones
Has gotten
From what the administration is that
I mean look I lost April Jones the saying this stuff he better be glad
This bankruptcy is over
It seems like
It seems username there
I don't know anything about
Former Church
Righteous upstanding person
Every judge
The deal is that all these guys were snookered into a situation of
Jones has a way that he wants to try to make things right
Heroes and
Acrimony and avoided by the drop
In the moment
Forasmuch as this process can
Work the process worked
It works these everybody's getting off
About
That's not Ed spinning
That my trust has been called off
Be able to like refute
I know that a hundred percent.
Schmidt is not talk
Appropriate
Yeah yeah and so what he just said right there is
I'm not going to
There's not
There is not the chance that there is mouthpieces by former judge Smith that's not a thing that happen
Is an outright lie attic
Complete
Complete contradiction of everything that I was arguing earlier that shows 25%
Well I'm glad we've disabuse you of that notion
How much
Mark would you guess that Soros has spent
On the case that you're the lawyer for
That's such a funny
Any questions
It's funny because I'm usually involved in litigation that is kind
Uno
A good product
Trial
The product is going to take a lot of XP
Testimonial
It's really expensive
How much does much is a quarter-million to half-a-million dollars
Is that in Jones's case it's not quite as much
Protest
Texas lawyer traveling all over the country
It's a lot cheaper
I'll be I'll be really upfront cuz I want
I went to Jones people to know
I want them to understand this
That this case so far soup
$10,000
Money
Has been paid over
More than three times by Jones himself
We've already collect
He's paid for all of them
And look
Like driving itself was a risk of Lost
We're doing
Well we don't really
This is not something for the pain
Every takes
To get the parents their day and at this point
That's not a
The factory
Cause I don't need George Soros
Mark I pray
Appreciate your perspective
And I understand your
Intimately involved
With the case that you are
Conducting
However
I have
If what you're saying is true
You're making a lot of this Soros money cuz next clip
Wilson
Yeah if
You're very rich
Even trying to hide this
Why are they
Why are they so obsessed
Have an associate come out soon
I'm over 10 million dollars
To do that what does he look like
When all that comes out and it there now
Openly trying to
Threatened
Bankruptcy
The justice department
Purple
Purposes
So ten million dollars
Soros
Pride I think I think you're mistreating I think you're not understanding that Soros
Is spending that money not on me but for other things maybe like he is
Like like paying for hackers to manufacture an email to
Jones saying your sources are batshit crazy.
He conveyed listen I'm saying that he gave you that money up front and you've been Outsourcing all of your deep State sit for a while
Packers
What's the New York Times
That's what surprises me is the megalomania
Thinking that it would take 10 million dollars to destroy you when you have engineered your own destruction
Like that
Did you take somebody like look II
Me and a couple members my forever
Decided we'd
Like to kind of chill out a little bit
Nice to see it happen
It hasn't been like
Like we didn't need
Deep State funding to do it
Like we just needed a little bit of
Time to be willing to say
In the families know this to
Very rewarding
For them
Be adequately compensated
The moment of Reckoning
Yeah to see it through and we're going to see it through and it's not that big of a deal like I don't
I don't understand why he thinks it has to be like
Like your house to be like in this this global
I can explain this
Very easily
He's a narcissist
He believes
Crazy nonsense
That's really inconvenient for him
So
Andy has a tenuous if not completely lost grasp on reality
Thesaurus
So much Crow I'm just going to be so embarrassed you remind me of the Soros antifa
Contract
From a 4chan troll post
I think that might be
Like
Disappointing
So Barnes has some thoughts
About this case in and of itself
Play Alex
That's what's going on here
I mean the goal has been just pure intimidation
The only thing they know
Just like the intimidation
Economy.
Chipley weather
But it's the complete
Dangerous partisan
I mean
Escalating
And the problem
Had confidence
In the merits of their cage
Then they wouldn't be using these Shenanigans they would be
Interfere in a bank
Mobile Manor
To try to prevent a party from the legal right
Rights and remedies
Bankruptcy Ford which by the way is only a notch
Because the plaintiffs chose to sue entity
The new
Especially
Apprentice Thana
Sort of Mike Myers
Latest version
Delusional
Eclipse
This is this
We sued entities that we knew had no ass
Right
The show will understand this
The first time that robbed
Is there trying to figure out what the hell it is
And Free Speech those payroll the
Robbed his first sanction for not Abby
Any clue what the hell
I think
And then
It's a thing
It owns the intellectual property it's got the website
In the part of like why Robert Barnes is no longer on the case
Shenanigans
This whole thing about enforce OST they were hiding it from beginning
And saying that they're scared of the merits of the
Case
Pulling shenanigans
Well in the Mist
Apolina shenanigans
Avoid a trial
No that's why you for 4 years
That because you're afraid of the merits of your case you guys have been pushing it back
Shenanigans with bankruptcy judges
That's why you mess around so much
This was a good Refuge when your argument was that the default judgement
But now say that we are
Are getting the US like
He's not
He's really really
Out of his element
Places
U.s. trustee do whatever it was going to do
No sir
Hundred percent
A decade
Recline
Giant
I do think you're saying that Barnes
Out of this element a lot of places
He's in his element
Public opinion types
He was not adequately deployed as the person to be in the courtroom
Doing what he needs to do right here
He doesn't actually swing public
It's there to make
That's what
Plug his ass
Albert
Alternative
For people who
Gabby responsibly on patreon
What happened several years ago
Giselle
Splc that didn't work out
I don't think so
Alex asked Barnes
Tabac him up man
Hey man
I'm broke
No I'm broke back me up
Anyone
Pretend
Infowars
Is this deluded audien
Because I don't judge myself my money I spend it almost all I got a decent house
Nice car Healthcare but I don't worship money
How much money does Alex Jones have
All of these entities
Binu didn't have it
Discover
You should dismiss them
Why is Owen Shroyer
This is purely lawfare
Politically-motivated
Discovery
He has like $50,000
Play the bank I mean
Putting on Christmas on the street
Also the reason
Resources are not necessarily
Oh yeah that is a good point to something about financial Paducah
Deposition
Bought a brand new Dodge Hellcat
Fort Worth the price of water
2 wildair that Barnes was like we sat down with them and showed them
You didn't set down even sit down with anybody we had to file like
For sanctions over the course
Sears
Google Map for Alex
Clips that he doesn't know what actually is in it
And we just snuck in a clip of the deposition
The business of December
I have no idea what this business
I don't know how to tell you what it does
Cuz I don't know
Are you the only person
Sure you really can just
Suppose this was like the things
Osborne said in that do deposition he started getting up
Talking
To try to cover their ass
Compare that to them today
I don't know I do know I know you've done
Deposition videos
David covered their corporate representative Infante
Weather
Basically the s*** out of Robert Barnes
Vagina Jones wrote in an affidavit form testimony
I like rooting off a David in Connecticut saying yeah Robert Barnes botched
The case please don't
Dismiss our case we got to like
We got a new lawyer he's going to take care of it
We 86
Barnes probably knows about that he's not going to get sued
Affidavit I'll bet you like honey
Appetite loss
Assume
Let's see how well that goes I've seen your
I don't think
You f***** up your protective order we know how much money you have it's all been linked
To the Press like that stop
F****** what are you doing
News according to
That bubbles impenetrable
So just just talk
He would have a
Illiberal
Jury pool
What are they scared of a liberal kinetic
Do you know that even those Jerry
Bulls when they see the ACT
True facts
Will not right
Big checks
Mary Hughes procedural tricks
Do you have any response to these bankruptcy
If it be cases are not a threat if there's some evidence is going to come out that's going to protect
The absolute
The first verdict
Then you can probably weather the rest of the cases no problem
You know that
You didn't want a case on the merits
Give me my level of frustration
You don't need it that's
That's a real shame
Is is this cases of punitive Cason always has
Actors you
Just stopped a trial at its doorstep
God
Especially from the
Who's literally ran away from this jurisdiction so I can stop
Beating him like a redheaded stepchild
It's basically a correct
Metaphor to use you should not
Beat red-headed stepchild
Beat him like Robert Barr
Twitches
It's a
It's just basically like a bully running away and then being running away
Hold me back
A hundred percent
I do think that there is an interesting thing
Kind of works for the presentation of Alex's show but it does it just
It's so transparent the W / won't you
A debate me you have the case
No problem
Conversations and
Mark on the on the show
I don't believe for a second
The goal was a default
Everything
Would have led to a trial
If Alex had cooperated
And on his piece of it
Very basics
That's about what I said
I'd love that
You keep destroying all the s*** you said
Challenge
It's it's wild everybody
But this is only a question of how
Never a question of what you did
If I come
But the First Amendment
About is the beginning of trial you're allowed to ask
The court to say that certain matters and certain
Allowed to be advanced
Is that Alex's conduct was protect
By the First Amendment
Because it by law it was
He said false
Facts about these plaintiffs he's already got a default judgement
It's already been found as matter of law
First Amendment
Life is not like a boring of the First Amendment
It's already been determined that it's not rela
Today
If you got 4 years
To do a First Amendment
And he actually even though all of the like he talks about it being a kangaroo court
The realities of even of all the bulshit he proved he did
He got the go-ahead it in
If you list all the way up to the Texas
He got he got two layers on the 1st Amendment
Any any any fell on his face in Boca
It's so to say that like
Oh this has something to do with he's being tonight
Stop that s***
Annnd ideal setting to their scared it's also dumb
I mean at least I don't
I don't
Barnes anyway all clear
Show right now
Seems to be kind of trying to be in cover his ass mode
His name is going to be somewhat tied to it and he's going to have
Why
He was so unsuccessful why everybody else was
Excuses
Whether or not they match with reality is obviously
PR propaganda
You're too afraid to have a case on the merits of using all of these lofty or trick
Regardless
If there's anything behind it
And you were correct
Clip
What tradition was correct
Making some allegations that I'm going to need a response
Sweet
Dismiss
And now
A trial on the merits
They're trying to deny
Skateland scope of this
Politicized
Weaponize
Mechanism
Power
His voice is
Is falling apart
He should take a breath
Audrina
Yeah that is scared me little bit
The number of allegations
These denials of motion
Birthright
Denied
The ability to have a motion to dismiss
Actually Barnes filed
They had for those
I know that I've looked at least
Connecticut
At least
Perfume ocean
Dismiss at Meijer
Anyway they had four of them
In fact one of them was so bad that they got they got fine like $35,000
Completely frivolous motions
Yeah they definitely had all that chance and then the second one was the Motions for summary
Basically what this is is
Once the case is gone through some discovery
You're you're allowed to bring emotion to
Have certain
Issues declared
Overdose issues my community for my damages
They have the ability to bring those emotions
And then they just
Mr deadline-day they had a deadline back in February
Animated
That was back with Brad Reeves was handling the case and they
Like a switch over I didn't do it
Yeah I was denied the opportunity to go into the NFL
Bi-Rite
So then they have these denied the ability Judy's anti-slapp motion
That's just ridiculous
Fantastic
Because
A bunch of like really
How would I describe
Improper
As we discussed
And as a result
Hey guess what I'm just going to abandon our motion to dismiss
On the anti-slapp so I don't get
In trouble
They've been denied the opportunity Bank bankruptcy
Like it's not my fault I didn't do anything
Literally came apart at the seams
I can't even take credit
I don't I don't even use wasting everybody's time
Congratulations
What do you want like
This list is more just like
This didn't work
This didn't work this.
Ability what it means is we
We weren't allowed to Whitby
Is little bit like if you've ever
The stairs that you just
Your eyes
And your legs missed if you trip going up
The stairs
Very embarrassing
People see you and your likes
This was somebody else's fault there's no way that I just tripped like today would that be able to
Absolutely all nearby accept responsibility
Like an a******
That's what it feels like
Brings us to the end of our clip
It's for this Sunday I feel like
Is this cathartic
Who's this
Obviously not
A normal case everything is half
Totally absurd
Couple weeks I've just been sort of
Often
For my life
From everything from all of it
And there is no chance
To get all this out your anger back
Put my head down and go to work I need a dose of bulshit Clips Jordans
I just know I'm just a lot of straw dropping out of it is
It's just
It's it's
Get to a point
I mean everything about this case has been so unorthodox
End and when you hear them
Talking about the nice to be able to come on here instead
Not just that
Not just that the things
True or whatever that like
This is so far off the real
It's Jeff
Different territory
End in so that's just how you have to treat
It's nice to come out and talk with you guys
I wish I could give you a more
I just don't know I'm still
Holding pattern
I know where
This bankruptcy stone is over but
To say that that's the end of the stunts would be naive sower
But at least I could do.
Like we were saying it's kind of
Results
Deflated now
Uncharted waters I guess
?
So
Jumping over
I don't know I'll tell somebody the other day I was outside happened to just
You watch
Apocalypse Now the Redux version
Yeah exactly
Robert Duvall
The Napalm and everything
Someday
Nn
God you start to feel better
You start with feel that like
You've been you've been living on this thing of
It never ends
It never is always something more and it's some point it will in
Kind of left in the
For my literature fans out there there's not going to be a good
It's going to
It's all going to be over
Buddha
This is never leaving my life that's the thing I've had to resign myself
To do my normal life
Devote
To the absolutely most insane lawsuit in America
Ten Years After The Alex Jones lawsuit we talked to Mark
Getting involved him
Looking at whether it's
Didn't expect that we thought we would be
And here we are
Yeah
I thought I'd be doing a jury in a year-and-a-half
Never quite what what you think
I'm getting you some getting ready for that moment where we switch gears
This is the trout this is the Reckoning we can put all the
Bulshit behind
Actually dude
Waiting for us to do for
Before God damn
Don't forget I can tell you right now we're going to do it right
And it's it's
It's just a matter of when Jones is going to let that happen
Well we're excited for you to get there
Yeah well it'll be there
Thank you for joining us this is this has been a lot of fun to check you being able to give us
Contacts even if the contacts dues
This confuses even lawyers
I would have no ability
To talk about
Bulshit
Basically all like today
Chance to get it all
Get to get some steam off
For sure
To update
Knowing when the the trial actually happen
So we can get ticket
Until next time
Weird website
But until
Tell time
Ne-Yo
Emilio
Dzx bar
I wish you all
A dreamy creamy summer pajamas
Don't get involved in astronaut ice cream it's not worth it is a dangerous game
Holding
In color
I love your work