Damn and Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
With the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about Alex
Astronaut ice cream week continue
Okay summer
This week
Kind of my bright spots for this week are all just going to be an astronaut ice cream anyone I thought I'd get in on the dream creamy summer
And actually send anti-brake spot
This brand
Monex
Odell and I X
Benelli open this openness and try it drive it
I think that there's an expectation of what you're getting when you get astronaut ice
You know it's the freeze-dried ice cream it's got a little bit of a crunch to it
There's a vanilla one here
That is not what you
Respect when you get in astronaut ice cream
Itzchok
It's poorly held together powdery chalk
Kind of
Is similar
It kind of reminds you of ice cream a little bit I almost started talking but I I couldn't stop
You worked it out of my I don't want to make noises
It's not it's not attractive
No more enjoyable ignore is it astronaut ice cream
No it's more like if they f***** up a marshmallow real bad marshmallow was falling apart
Lucky Charms Lucky Charms
Falling apart on a atomic level
Like like if if a marshmallow was in the Last Crusade
And drink from the wrong cup
What does it's disintegrate again
It's fired that is
I think that there isn't anything that stands out as like
The best thing I've had so far
But man that is
Real badass
Astronaut ice cream is a very specific thing that you're looking for
And if you're going
Going in looking for that experience at this is what they give you
Wow
Caca
I know you're disappointed I can't imagine anybody being like you know what I want
Crumbly ass falling apart
Soft
Powdery
What if what if this is more of a metaphor for the dark
Truth of all the astronauts who went to
To the Moon with that where they got there and they're like
This Munchen is
Kind of bad
I don't really like it no.
The problems raptors raptors aliens Nazis on the dark side
Galactic treaty somehow
Does murderers married to the Raptor Queen
Trying to teach you a lesson about leaving the Earth
Well
If that's the case I'm staying here
Cuz that s*** sucks
What are bright spots
Beard is the Kids in the Hall have returned
Survivor
It's fantastic really good
It's surprisingly good like they should not still be
Able to just
Jump right back into that kind of timing and stuff and they
Just do it fantasties do they have the same theme song
Oh yeah
Iconic
The first guitar lick and you know what you're in for a I have
Respect
Before the Kids in the Hall
I do but I know you're not nevermind nevermind thing I'm not sure exactly
I'm not saying who's bad obviously like this moonx
Right
It just be I wasn't I didn't hit
For me when I was younger
Understand
I mean he had your longstanding prejudiced against all things Canada has been finely I may be able
I do I did like brain candy though
Yeah baby
Although I bet I wouldn't if I watched it again
You like it more now
Because you know that it destroyed the kids in the hall for 30 years did it
Yeah absolutely is there Monkeybone 100% making that movie made them all hate each other so much
Let here we are
I just remember this evening it was just a few flipper thing amazed if he only thing I remember from the movie
That's great
Lot of dog in the new series
Jackass roof
That's
I will
I'm going to give this one out for free this conspiracy theory is going out for
For free to Alex and I think with this is how we know he's listening
Alright
There has been a massive up taking dong recently
Hey Mike the past five years right
The windshield Theory
And I think we're about to hear Alex be like all men
Do you know what causes civilizational collapse whenever people show Too Much dong you know Michelangelo's choke you much longer
The Renaissance ended immediately afterwards
You know the Greeks stay over they were all about. And it immediately afterwards you know I think we're there
Wants dong exposure early hotel but like jackass
Alright
Pompeii is right around the corner
So Jordan
Today we have an episode to go over that will not be as fun as
Complaining about astronaut ice cream and talking about Kids in the Hall
Let's not do it
Talking about May 15th 2022
Was Sunday's show
This is the day after the buffalo
Shooting
Anthem
Hey
Sort of set out to do Sunday and Monday
Cuz I figured that Alex would develop
Wings over the course
Of that time
It listening to Sunday I felt like well there's enough of that merits discussion
I'm here so
Wound come back on Friday with conversation of Alex's bike
Like Monday in
Tuesday
A little bit more of that stuff
Butts
Predictable
There's some
Some little elements
That IR
Off the beaten path
And we'll get them to chat about it
I'll take a load some new walk
That's great idea so first I Know What You Did Last Summer and it's so dreamy creamy thank you so much you're now apology Wong
Coronavirus
AR Rahman the bearded
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you very much this person told me to pronounce this however I see
Okay
At jete
I like that
Could you very much for the gay frogs nice day for the depositions
Thank you so much
2del sizers
You are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Go take a little break you down
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
I got plenty work for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5
Got to hear tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Apologize
The crew in the western
Was legitimately having break
A better tomorrow
Suffice it to say he is
Not better tomorrow he is much much worse
Yeah I think at this point everybody probably has some familiarity with the event
That's what happened
Over the weekend
And
I don't I'm not going to dwell too much on all that except as we go through the episode
Other things that come up
But here is Alex coming in on his Sunday show
Day after
The shooting and this is how he
Starts is Brock
Call flags are coming you have seen all the
Programming
Election fraud
From the election
But incel white supremacist would attack
Churches colleges and other facilities
And the preacher
Killing each other at each others throat
Plunge the dollar
And 177 days
So I'll give Alex this much
He did absolutely say the false flags were coming and in some cases
He did say that he'll be white supremacist shooting minorities in order to demonize the right wing
I don't really care about that and it's not impressive at all because the reality is that Alex says that all the
I further don't care because Alex said all kinds of
Other false flag
Exit was coming
To which he's been wrong about because
How the school of Prophecy works
You make a million prediction tonight if one of them
Looks like it happened
You pretend that all the other predictions and never happened and that this was the only thing that you've been talking about all along
It's a really pathetic game and you can tell from the fact that Alex is leading his coverage with insisting he predicted the shooting
That he's not interested in anything past self-aggrandizing
This is a game to him yep
Like he's starting with I told you
You so mean it really does feel like what he
He just did is like open his show with like
Oh boy
I sure told Alia you know I you know you listen to me and here I am just being right
All the time I'm so right all the time
That makes me feel good to be right all the time you know it's like
Is is
Coverage of the shooting begins with him making an appeal to his prophetic abilities
In order to
Try and sell the people should listen to him about all of his other b*******
That's essentially the game buddy
Starting out with a knife I do to pour
Here is Alex giving some sort of jest
Applications for why he believes
That's this may be a false flag
Possibly can you print out the Wikipedia page did not
People have called and said he's going to attack
I can kill people
But nothing was done
All of Talk Radio
What was
Anything else
No one blamed talk radio or free speech
That's just the way that Alex sanitize is the claims that propagandist to spread the Great replacement Style
Piercing theories
They played a critical role in the dissemination and popularization of the ideology that
The shooter in Buffalo was motivated by
Any radio host for TV presenter who wasn't obsessed with white birth rates and didn't
And spend most of their time fear-mongering about immigration
Is basically it can
Concerted plan to bring in white genocide
Come up because
Conversation wasn't about
Free Speech or talk radio
It was about the very clear connection the people who spread this
Type of narrative
That you know like Alex
Kentucker do
The shooting was done by somebody who believes essentially the same thing that they preach
I was just going to talk about that because it's much easier and more profitable to yell false flag and pretend that you're actually the victim
When there's a racially-motivated shooting to left 10 people dead
It's f****** nonsense
That's Alex's claims
That support his assertion that this may be a fault I'm going to take them one by one
The first is that the
Affected red-flagged
Substantiate
And anyway
In June 2021 the police
Recalled after the shooter was a shooting at Susquehanna Valley
High School
In the process is house was searched by the FBI and New York State
Police but no charges were filed
And you just ended up being sent a cow
Report stories is that
If you sees any mention of the FBI or CIA in anything
Then his work is
Done
If you can point to them popping up anywhere he can Bluster the audience that he has some access to other Intel that shows that the FBI
Bi was closely monitoring dendron the
The shooter
The FBI's tasked with a whole lot of crime investigation
If they don't file any charges here
There's no reason to believe that they had this guy red-flagged
Syracuse.com is pretty clear that this incident probably didn't
Lead them being put on any
That's like list
The second is the people have called and said he was going to attack and kill people
This is in relation to the incident from June 2021 and I do think that this is
Is probably something that should have been treated more seriously
But I'm not delusional enough to think that the government is going to allocate the resources needed to deal with this issue
In a way that helps
Before it's too late
There are so Alex is taking that warning that someone had made into 2281 in
Flying into the presents
Situation
Doesn't approach
It wasn't a it wasn't a warning from the immediate
Santa got a warning for the lasting bright
He's playing fast and loose with details Cody
That's the only way to make it
There were some indications prior to this shooting that something was up but it was unfortunately too vague
Bixby useful
ABC7 out of New York reported the Chunnel Teague and operations manager for the store where the shooting happened
Quotes all the alleged shooter sitting on a bench outside of her store the day before the
The shooting
He was panhandling eventually came into the store where he appeared to be
Be bothering customers
Teague asked him to leave and he quote did so without an ARG
Apparently he'd also been there in March and have been asked to leave the store but
These are data points that only really feel
Critically important
In hindsight
I worked enough
Retail environment
Not type
Place
To know that tons of people get thrown out of our ass to leave stores everyday
And I pretty much never leads to a shooting so it's not something that would be like
Uh-oh
Here is a
Crisis
It only means something after
The Crisis happen
Sprayer
Write a Manifesto
This is true but
It's meaningless in terms of making disappeared
Be anything other than a real shooting
Didn't give anyone Advance warning
The Shooting Center
He published
Right before the shooting which
Also streamed on
Incidentally there were some warning signs that could have been caught but they were made in a place
They would have been exceedingly difficult for
For police to find them
Gendron had a private Discord server and even posting music
Sings about his plan
And also racist ship
4 months there before the shooting
Based on New York Times article about this it seems like no one else was in the server's there wouldn't have been any one there to sound the alarm
Hey Discord is not particularly well known for its content moderation policies
Add practices and like
If Alex were too
Think that the police should have
I do have on every discard it seems like that's against his
4th amendment ideas
If Alex's point is there was ample opportunity to intervene here before it was too late
That may be true
But nothing you brings up
Comes anywhere near even making me suspicious about
The shooting being a false flag
All of it just seems like
Like classic
I like opportunities for things
Things to be missed
Yeah it does
Just feel like
The only circumstance
In in here is that
You know when you when you say he needs to go to counsel
Not
It's. You know the problem isn't a mental illness
Problem is he's joined
To get you know
So so when you refer them to counseling for something that's not
If you can if you join a youth group you're not going to
People are going to be like all will he's mentally ill it's socially it makes habitation of
Of mental illness personality disorder joining a gang
It could be a number of factors put
Of course
Amazing isn't it
That's the only place for intervention
And I thought
You know you know
Messerli help with that and it also
Counseling as I think both of us can attest
From our lives is really only effective if your act
Actively involved
Doesn't seem to work if you don't want to be there not something that can be done to you
Necessarily it's active
Process you engaged with now that's basically mind control a fake
I can do it again
I think I think
In terms of the stuff that I can tell one of the opportunities that is messed
Is
Shooting threat
Yeah there's an opportunity to take his guns
Put him on some kind of a watch list
Why wasn't that done
Imagine if that had been done yet that would be tyranny
Yeah I mean
Why hasn't that Bennett because of you because of the way that you have behaved constant
For the past your entire life
Project is making sure people
I mean it's it's hard not to say that it's like
Well if you think
But that would have stopped this
Then you are taking responsibility for this happening
It seems really weird and I don't really know how to disentangle those points
So
Alex Alex has a theory about what happened
Hiiraan
Really really bad
The government
New York time
Is the left
Kill each other
Criminology no
The media
Enough race war news
Black supremacist
Betty White
And think there's not Justice
The globalist
Playing
Sides off
Against each other and we got
To be smart enough to understand that
Two black women loading groceries in their car what the hell
Rockefellers
Cool boy
It's not how you cover this stuff all right
If I understand correctly his point is
This is the left's fault for making the right one to kill people
And this is the right fault for not killing the right p
I guess
This is just a cowardly rambling and nonsensical angle that Alex
Taking
There's a lot of dumping in dodging trying to move quickly enough that the audience just nods and
Except
This ain't but it's s***
Endpoint where
You have no one's shooting up the UN if that's
That's f***** up
Untangle this
This b*******
Just trying to make is that this whole thing is the media's fault because the media is trying to further the globalist
Plan which is to have us all kill each other
No mind to the fact that the global is playing his supposed to be super bio-weapon indoor starting World War 3
Today's news
Or the main thing that he Hypes up is
Is a race war
Well but
Call me when it's
Necessary other days at the super bioweapon
In order to
Push this forward DVD around the bunch of stories about how white people need to be killed who which I should point out that
Didn't do that didn't have
In response to these stories racist black people take it upon themselves to kill white people like this person in Waukesha
Then races
People see these people
Ultimately announces conception the white terrorists would not have done this if it weren't for the prior racist terrorist
I'm done by black people against white people
It really all of this
Comes back to the media Target
At the root
And at the end of every branch of this tree what violence is Justified
Even while Alex pretends
The Condemned
Alex said that there's a black supremacist in Kenosha but what
Doing is mixing up Kenosha and Waukesha probably because the hours he spent
Defending
I am yelling about Kyle written
The car attacking Waukesha happened during their Christmas parade
Read last year
Darryl Brooks the person arrested in the attack has posted some
Stuff you would call racist
Online of the past
But I can't find any indication that his motive in the attack was to kill white people
This is the leap that Alex is making which reveals
His own race
The attacking Waukesha is awful and I'm not interested in minimizing it but it's a case where a black person ran a car into a crowd
And 6 people who were killed
I happen to be why
In the shooting in Buffalo you have someone who intentionally set out to kill black people
Inspired
Entirely by a racist ideology
These are not analogous situation
But Alex needs them to be
Because he needs to be able to point to the Waukesha attack to soften the blow the reality of what happened in Buffalo
What happened to Buffalo's way too close to Alex's ideology in the ship
3 sezon are everyday
So this is a game he has to
The play
It's inexcusable and it's
Absolutely intentional whether or not Alex is even aware of what he
He's doing anymore
It's it's
Dogshit
Hate it
I mean it's hard not to it's hard not to look at that
Just think like man this is America you know
Like
You can imagine the first f******
King pilgrims
Killing a Native America
Can being like hey man you shouldn't have if you hadn't walked on my property
I mean it's your fault really I put up a sign that says I own this now
You know it's mine
And it and that's justification did all these trying to kill white people
Just just you see it the whole f****** way
Through American history from the jump
Yeah
It's so interesting
The way that Alex is trying to
Artificially create the appearance of nuance in the analysis
While at the same time all it is doing is
Being like
Hey really there was a mass shooting where black people people were killed by a person who was sitting out
Specifically to kill black people write really the lesson we should learn is be nicer to wifey
What
That is the point
It is
You know I'm starting to think that the oppressors really don't like it whenever they get told their oppressors they like to elect
You know you got while you guys are so great
All the time
This is all about the New York Times running that whole thing about the
The slavery the history of slavery xt19 project
Yeah if people hadn't learned about American history than we've never would have had to deal with racism
Whatever so Alex
He's
Who's pretty early in the show
The Alex's Bears I was just
Flabbergasted
Royce White is a former NBA player
Martial arts
As well
Mixed martial arts
Ilhan Omar
He is about
Over here
He's got a special
He was set to host today but things were so hot
Thought I had to come in and give you my
Play the excerpt
Very very specifically
So Alex
Leaves
The rest of the first hour and into the second hour
Before he comes back
And is rationalization for why he jumped on to do what we just listen to it
This is just like
Okay so I know that you probably experienced
Dislike
Some kind of a local show
And the person who runs the show
They're not booked on it
They don't have a set on the show
But there's a huge turnout and they're like I got to give I got to get
Because it's like there's too many people listening
Get some of this attention for myself
Yep
No no
Predictable
Behavior that's kind of hard to
Hard to resist
I think I did it once
I think we had handsome
Squeeze myself
Impulse is the same
Kind of desperate
But I was also a desperate
No-name
You know any states nice I've been on the one side of it I've never been on the other cuz I've never run to show successful enough to
You want to do a set at my own show Fahrenheit always been like man I'm going to host this but I'm not doing a second over like that
That's fair
Yeah I was I was shocked
I was like all right
Alex is going to go away
Well I mean
We can avoid the
The reality I feel like
That
Alex
Feels good
Right now
Because of a mass shooter
Yep
So you know
I mean
That's that's real bad real bad you know he's he's like
A mass shooting happened
Now I'm going to get a lot more viewers
And that is how we live
That's how we live in the world
Royce White host
For a bit
This dude is definitely not going to be till on Omar
In the second hour a true to form and as promised
Alex does comeback
He comes back
The first thing he sets out to do is
Really lay the groundwork
Of what the narrative this is supposed
We are now in
Terrible
Black
Predominantly black grocery store in Buffalo New York
Predicted
19 year old incel
Corporate
Because it's
Their fault is happening
Way to take all the guns
Swag
A year ago
Pieces coming together about how Alex is going to cover the
He's got the he was red-flagged talking point there in order to help establish the narrative that there was for knowledge of the attack
Back on the party of it
The authorities
And that's the globalist to essentially let this happen so they could demonize the right wing
You'll notice that Alex is perfectly comfortable calling this a white
Assist attack where is he usually tries to pretend to white supremacy doesn't even make
Exist
This is because it's already that he thinks protect himself or taking any heat from sounding really similar to
To the shooter
This is Alex's been predicting
Volkswagen
For a while which
The globalist who used demonize the right wing
Particularly right-wing media figure
Because Alex has that in place already it's unnecessary added work to pretend this guy wasn't
Actually a white supremacist
You don't have to invalidate the reality of the attack if you can invalidate the entire reality we're in the attack
Took place
There's no indication that gundren was an incel and that word doesn't
The pier in the entirety of his 180-page Manifesto although he does make fun of incels
In his post on Discord
Fresh
I don't believe that
As an accurate description of his
His beliefs yeah I mean he puts in cell in there because it diminishes the masculinity is
If we know one thing about Alex
It's that he likes
Dafuq so this allows him to create some sort of
Look at that distance between himself
And I accused him of associated with incels
And who is but you know he doesn't deal with themselves
Maybe his good buddy Nick Fuentes
Got to confuse outdated losing
So also I believe that the reason Metallica's using this epithet
To describe the shooter
He's because
In the predictions that he made in the past
He use the word incel he's trying to use
He's using this descriptor in the present
To describe the situation so it matches his prediction that evaded the past
That's essentially what's going on
After every shooting Alex pretends the people are going to
But, take all the guns which is never happen
And when he's been asked to provide examples of moves to restrict gun ownership after shootings and deposition
He's been unable to say even a single example
This is just a base was talking point that uses
Is all the time to push the audience
Same with the blaming all
Conservative media thing
But doesn't ever happen at again right now no one wants to blame conservative media
They want conservative media figures to stop spreading racist great replacement Style
Conspiracy bulshit
And take responsibility for the harm to that behavior
That's
The reality of the situation without
Buck
Maybe wasn't completely staged
I mean
It's just like
He said the reason that he started
The white supremacist
Is going to attack false flag is so weak
Feel protected when this moment happens I know and that's what we've
Discuss the many many times it shouldn't be
You can't
Anyway
I guess I would ask you this question then delete into this club
Do you believe that there is any value in
Immediately
Throwing around in bandying
Ideas about this shooting being faked
Like with no real reason
I mean for real evidence backing you up we don't know maybe
Maybe if you're in the writers room of
The Kids in the Hall
Does not know not Canadian
Was this
Completely stage run by the FBI
But historically many cases
No one died or not
Collectively
Libertarians and populists
Nationalist
Dylann roof
The church
You know years ago should killing 10 black people as well
The did the Terrible
So it's fair enough why people and Christians and populist shouldn't be blamed for the attack in
I don't know if anyone outside maybe some people on Twitter
I don't think anyone's doing that
The shooter is ultimately to blame
Conversation about social responsibility as it relates to broadcast and racist propaganda is being flirted with by the
Media has happened a bit and then
Set the
Drop the ball
On this conversation
Through to a productive
Conclusion
What's going on
You see Alex Drive
Completely stories of instances
The killings in a way that's meant to sanitize white supremacy
This killings
Could I come up with
An example of a black mass murderer who is motivated by clear racist ideology comprable to the shooter or Dylan
Barracuda
I think it would be impossible for him
He's
Unfortunately saying the exact same
Something that he would have about any mass shooting 5 years ago
But because he's faced minimal consequences so far
He's saying it with
Extra step
You know like
Hey I'm not saying this is a false flag
I'm saying it you know
I'm not saying that
It is that there's no way the conservatives could be responsible for this I'm just saying that it's not a white people do it that you know
Ultimately what we're watching him do is
Claim responsibility for this
And then wagatail in our face
Yep Lee
Bno do not not to put
But the
Sort of racist
Conspiracy theory that white murders are covered up by the media is
Is literally part of what dylann roof
Said inspired his path
His
Mass shooting
So
Congratulations on
Pushing ideology even in your response to this
About how
Your hands are totally clean
Yeah
Go fuc
Yourself
Anyway here's more b*******
The globalist
They need a
Cascading Civil War
As the preacher
Text bring in
Two of the
Lockdown
The martial law
What is Schwarz
Lockdown
This is cheating
4 months
Maybe even
A year-and-a-half Alex has been saying the covid lockdowns were to prepare
For climate lockdown
Open fairy consist
He would talk about articles about how pollution went down during quarantine or articles about how much battery was for the environment that's open
People weren't driving
You talk about energy rationing and ideas that car is being tracked
Trace by the mile
This was the globalist playing according
Alex
Because it fit with his normal climate change denial ism
And conversations
Is it before having dude like
Ipcc reports
And what have you
But now there's a story about a white
What is mass shooter
Now they're race war lockdowns over the plan apparently
Climate lockdown
Not so important
On the back burner
Alex is doing this because his narratives are always about
Against
Generally it's good to just fear Monger by climate-related issues because most of the right-wing ecosystem relies on money that goes
Back to billionaires tied into the energy Market
And that's a whole lot of
Conservatism revolves around that bedrock
But
It's secondary for Alex
Creating cover for white supremacy
Murderers
Alex can put aside the climate lockdown ideas when there's an opportunity to use the fear of coming
To make it easier to sell as audience on the idea that this horrific shooting was actually org
Castrated by his imaginary anime
That sucks
Like I said this is not cool
I would ever be serious if I was listening to that and I was in his audience and I believe
Because I would be paying attention to the things he's saying Alexa
Griswold lockdown come on man yeah I know
I mean
You couldn't answer I mean
It would demand better
Just
That's
Somebody stop him I wanted to be a bat signal something
OfficeMax
What is wrong with all of us
I think that's
If I have any sense of things are going with the lawsuits and such
I do think that that is a shoe that's waiting
I think it may be a matter of time
And a million or two million in Bitcoin isn't going to do s***
In terms of
The ultimate consequences
That may be,
Financial aid
And so I think
I think we need not a Batman
We just need
But that process to be allowed to run its course
That's what I think it's really hard not to have that feeling of wanting a Batman
It's just like
I can
I can't imagine
Acting this shity
Yeah
It's it's like
George
Your Existence is tolerable
Nan this situation
You know like this should be a day where everybody just agrees like
We're not going to air Alex or Tucker
I could do it so Alex was planning to take the day off
Exactly
Kaitlyn
Taking the day off he came in to remind you how much it makes him feel good
To talk about mass shootings and how he's right about everything and how he called this
The whole taking a Victory lap or whatever it's disgraceful
What what
F***** didn't predict another
The goddamn Mass shooter
Is there enough
So anyway Alex
Fusing
Yeah I don't dwell on this one for a little bit
Whatever
But we will the Sun
And we have the
Livestream shooter video from twitch
Into a
Synagogue
People terrible crime
Put on
You do not blame the Telecommunications medium
The people commit crimes on
Verizon
Do you blame Southwestern Bell I mean
Crazy show
There's a lot of difference
I'm soaking
Confused by what Alex is trying to say about Telecommunications
He starts off by talking about twitch and gab because the Buffalo shooters
Stream the attack on Twitch
Because Robert Bowers post
They're quite regularly
Not just on the day of his shooting
At the synagogue
Incidentally Hitman shooting was also believed that the Jews globalist by Bring It
Coincidence
It starts off about how you
You don't blame these telecommunications for the attacks
The people carry out
I guess that's fine
Blame them
Organize our livestream a racist Act of terrorism
It should be time to see what
To be changed about the
The platform
Bood up
But maybe Soul search
Well I mean
If you start talking
Sing about that you're a slippery slope away from the things that other people say on other toe
Communication
Platforms like for instance
You know you don't want somebody going out there and saying like oh
Look at all the things that he believes that sounds a lot like this person on this show
The risk of is killing the First Amendment
If you do any kind of content moderation on these sites that would
Limit the ability of people trying to organize and inspire
Yeah agroterrorism
Doesn't want you to hold any of them accountable
He points
To be problems but
The obvious solution to these problems
Counter to his ideology
Guess we can't do any
Guess we're stuck
So Alex talks about not blaming bees
Things
Jumps to someone calling 911 to report a crime
I was in any way similar to the other
Things he's talking to
Doesn't make any sense
This is severely disjointed and it seems indicative of how little of a point
Also not to be believed
Your butt
Conspiracy that the murders of white people are covered up by the media is literally Woodhill improved
Literally so Alex is really hit map to hit Matt drum pretty hard
Yep real shity
The globalist
Maturing more of this
Follow the script
5 minutes or so
Some of these specific
Because
The mind
The globalist
War games
Adobe in a race war because there is an Undeclared race war against white people
Run by the way
Cause the real race war
Whoa
So what do you think about that
Well
I think
Alex is saying
That
He's looked
Did the current landscape and he sees the ascendance of the far-right in the fact
That these shootings are going
I mean unresponded to Beyond
Thoughts and prayers so he assumes that that's going to accelerate and increase
The frequency of the
And then people will rightfully blame him but again nobody's going to do anything about it so the far-right politician
Are going to sweep
The f****** Nation the based on terrorism
That they tacitly supports
But there is a
Undeclared race war in the media against white people
Yeah that one that one was I forgot about
Essentially
It in Subway's he's framing white supremacist terrorism as
Self-defense
Well maybe on wise and his conception but that is how they think of
Yes like they really do think that it's not possible for white people to coexist with other
I think that there is
Degrees of that but yeah
I mean well you are one of those degrees
The degrees are going to
Go up let me know clear I think some of the degrees are in belief
The people have and some of the degrees are in Howell open
People are willing
Alex
You're obviously one of the examples we always go back to his him
Being freaked out by Muslim women in a pool supply shop
You know like that is the level of unwilling to co-exist abs
Also there's people who speak much
More
I openly about like
Wanting
No I'm coexist
People to get out of
The country Alex doesn't
He's not willing
Going to be that
Blunt right so be hard to pin that exact idea on him although
He does seem to have
Luther his beliefs that are expressed
Some inclinations towards that direction
We have
Start looking at him and say
Well
If you're running interference for the people who are acting on the fears that you
Express part of their act
You know you're if you're if you're outfit skating like oh no I'm not saying that I want this
You want everybody to not do anything about this problem I let it continue it's a tough line to draw a
Bad ID and
I think board
Should be done
So Alex
Is leading into this video that proves that he predicted
And this will be the rest of our episode
Discuss
Hit the clips
30 put into a compilation
We can do this together
How bad is
Is this time well Alex predicted it
We called it
So here's his
Infowars.com
Tomorrow's news today
Derrius guice
The last couple years where I specifically predicted it
On Friday a few days ago
Tomorrow
Few minutes of this go to break and come back with Royce White
Yeah so this video was titled Alex Jones
Predicted the white supremacist false flag shooting
@black
Grocery store
So based on the title of this video
Alex is calling
As much as he might want to pretend like we don't have all the details yet so that's pretty explicit in the title now
Keep that in mind
That is the title of the video
So it's the stated goal that we should be
Watching this with that's the thesis
Well if you're saying this
You can't even say this is as like a
Observation
It says it's an implication
No matter what
You know it's not an implication
Real name where it just says Alex Jones claims that there will be a false flag you can be like well no that's just an observation of right
Stingy you're saying it
Replaying it on his show it posted on his website
This is at least
A tacit acceptance that this is the this is the editorial line or going
Here is the first clip
That's in here
Actually is a starting out on the strongest foot
So what are they going to do
Piranha attack
A minority
Church or College
Grocery store some type of
Minority gather
So that's
Pretty
That's a great way to start this compilation
Is that where that clip that he played End
This is a clip from June 25th 2021
I guess that Alex included grocery
Tree stores as a possible Target in the list of some other places
And this was almost a year ago
I guess he should get a pat on the head
Cuz you did say grocery
It should probably be pointed out that this isn't an idea I'll just pulling out of thin air
In August 2019 Patrick crusius carried out a mass shooting at a Walmart in El Paso killing 23
Motivated by great replacement
Conspiracy theory
This was something that happened
Not too distant
In Texas so it's hard
Had to be that impressed by Alex
It's also important to understand
Contact
Of this prediction that Alex's make
It's not a generalize prediction that this false flag is going to happen at some point like
Year later
Here's how the show open
Sims on June 25th 2020
Amish
And general
Twin
Marshall Street
The real president
Pets come out
A absolute
Chad
SS are going to stage
Flags I had
The evidence of
Generals lansinger be false Flags
The cover of the results of the 2020 election results being audited
And then Alex was just riffing about the sort of places he imagines might be targeted
And the grocery store probably comes up in his head because of vague memories about yelling about the El Paso shooting
This isn't really valid as a pronoun
Diction of the shooting
Buffalo in any way
So
I don't know let's see what what's the next
Massive white supremacist
Media
You're going to be bad
Bleeds into the 8:01
But honestly the clip itself is meaning
Says this kind of stuff all the
I'm going back to the earliest days I found a new show
The globalist archons
Philly planning these fake attacks to make a right
Extremist book
There's nothing specific about this
It's not even recent
This was from July 29th 2021 and Alex is calling into the show because he's on a work
Casein
Here's the context of the clip that they've selectively cut out to be in this compilation of
What's being so right about all of his
I'm sick
My stomach all the time
Because
Responsibility
People assaulting us
Call Flags
Throwback Thursday
And or launcher
War and Order Cyber attack
Pandora mask
Programming in the media
So you know it's kind of like
Problems of using the clip in the way they did
The first is that Alex has specifically talking about pro-vaccine people being targeted for false-flag to make anti-vax people
Look back cuz that's the narrative he was on that day
There is no relation to the Buffalo shooting at all
The second problem explains why the clip in this compilation starts where it doesn't
Conveniently edits out the part where it shows it's just a long list of possibilities
Everything he's doing is just throwing s*** at the wall
This is literally the dynamic I was talking about earlier on in the show
He makes 100 prediction
I've been four times that he didn't make the one
Guns that don't work for his narratives later
Ending of this clip is literally him trying to erase these other predictions because they don't help make him look like a prop
Prophet in the main point of Alex
The coverage of the Buffalo shooting is that I called it
How does a f****** liar in a monster
It's just gross
These parts
Stressed out
Well I mean the the audio
Disgraceful the audios for McCall right it took me a second
To be like all of this is a phone call because
If that was audio from like 1999 I would have never believed it right
Like it could have been the
Exact same thing
The difference at all
Here's the next Clipper
Compilation
You're going to be bad because you were Republican voter.
To do this connect Republican Party
Do white supremacists
But all these are bleeding information other weirdly
This has nothing to do with predicting the shooting and honestly it has nothing to do with any kind of analysis that means anything
If anyone is a soda
Associated the Republican party with white supremacy
Cuz they won't get their houses
As long as someone like Tucker Carlson is hero worshipped as the number one pundit of conservatism going to have a problem
So this clip is from June 5th 2021 so against buddy year-old there's nothing to do with the subject that
The compilation is supposed to be
Recovering
June 5th was a Saturday so if you did do a show that day it's not archived anywhere
No matter what the
Context year was it wouldn't matter
Nothing to do with predicting
This attack
I think I feel
Like this isn't going anywhere
At this point I am not convinced by this compilation
Previous compilation that he put out where he predicted
Things correctly I remember you going through
Each individual clip
And applauding his ability
Which was almost
Almost prophetic in his accuracy creative false version of things
His predictions are like
Friends in Stalin's photograph
You don't like him anymore get him out of there
Here's the next one
Preparing real false flag
I just got dressed up like white nationalist
Discredit
Republican
Violence
Again this isn't a prediction of anything
Think this is just a standard
Literally the everyday kind of content on Alex's show
This is from October 13th 2021 the date
Can't be accurate because Alex
Wasn't hosting
The show that day
When was hosting on October 13th
So close appeared briefly on the show but this clip was taken from a show where Alex was in studio
And he wasn't
You did appear briefly on the show that Owen hosted but it was over the phone
I don't know where this clip
Comes from but it doesn't matter cuz it's nothing to do with predict
Buffalo shooting
They got the picture though
I can't even get
I mean
Okay
They don't want you to have
They are doing this
To you not to get your sloppy
I think it's I think it's
Absolutely a mistake
That's so bad
The other one being a Saturday
And he doesn't usually do shows on Saturday
On Saturdays
This one is
Just a f******
Boy Next clip
You go to black church or you going to love
You know what grocery store
You better
Be packing
You better be watching
Cuz let me tell you
Deepstate succumbing
That was the whole
No okay
Like first of all that clip kind of reads to me like a
But I'm going to leave that aside.
Music that you hear there is
B b b
The intro of the
The Infowars logo come from the beginning of the compilation
Before the like
The longer I didn't even realize that this is like
This is the cold open
Oh no but like maybe a little Furious
Grocery store there
But you did also saver real grocery store
Doesn't match the description of the Buffalo shooting
Here's the thing though
That clip is also from June 25th 2021 the same day as the first clip
Compilation
It's the same
It's basically part of the same sense
I think it's a little bit
Deceptive splitting these up some through is from the same
Thought is the previous clip
The same prediction
Weird almost like you know you're headed out the middle in order to give a certain appearance
Speaking of the you get what you know you got a twofer
Here is the full context
Of that clip
Includes the beginning
Play the clip 1
Gambit is eclipse
Illegal aliens voting dead people voting
It's on record
Georgia with double counting ballots
That night
We can watch the video
Now it's confirmed
The did the Republican leaders in Georgia are not having
You admit it
What are they going to do
A minority
Church or
Grocery
Restore some type
Minority
Gathering
Completely false flag
Incel
Ermine
They'll go in and start shooting black
Then they'll be
Little kill them
Anime committed suicide
Somebody
Cool if I thought
And then
Get killed by the Black Ops
Black Ops
Then tells wine share the people
I want a big number hundreds of dead
You
Black
Or you go to a
You know
Store
You better
Cuz let me tell you
Basic level this has no relation to what happened to Buffalo
I got to say in the interest of fairness
He does end up playing the whole clip later
But in the
Beginning of this compilation that's just the way the clips are presented to introduce these things
Mind without the middle part which is like
Ridiculous and Rockets yet
Skewer the context
So what are you saying and make it look like he was talking black
About black pictures all the time right which is why you have
Only instances of it by bringing up a grocery
Historic presented separate from each other as to make it look like
He's just having a bit in the reefs
Some past like you brought up the predicting
Video about Ukraine
Alex does this because I'm sure you seen a fair amount of traffic and attention come from the whole Alex Jones was right meme and he's just
Leaving Intuit
The problem is that he's not right about stuff
So he needs to lie about what he said in the past in order to create things for people to pretend he was right about
And that's what this compilation is it serves the interest of marketing
The idea that he was right about stuff
By lying about what he said in the past
I mean yeah there was a mass shooting so I'm going to cut an ad
The important logo plays
Here is where we are
So what are they going to do
Piranha attack a minority
Church or College
Grocery store some type of
Minority Gathering
Music you heard like a logo compilation just includes the same clip from June to
25th again
The first clip that we listen to
It speaks volumes about the material he has to work with
He's within one minute he's play backflip twice
Because it's the one where you actually says grocery store and he knows that most people aren't paying attention to not really listening critically
It's going to sound like he was making grocery store prediction
Constantly to any passive listener
At this point the whole clip plays through with the stuff about the two-man team Satan worshipers going in and then globalist
Kill team showing up
Kill hundreds of black people
I applaud Alex actually leaving that part in since it really makes
His prediction look like s***
Still cut out the part where this was a prediction or you specifically talking about the globalist and what they would do too
Heat off them
About the audit results from the election
Coming out he's still very much lying about that right in order to make it appear more related
To the present
Wow
Hiding his bigger lie within a smaller life
That's just a nesting doll a bulshit
And who's to say that a globalist hit team didn't
Come in
Biggest shooter survived we haven't heard news from Buffalo
Since then
So is anybody alive on Buffalo we lost
We lost Buffalo guys man
So here here's the next clip
This is the New World Order Revolution
This is an assault and it only gets worse from here
And that's why
No matter
How much heat they get at how bad they look no matter how much
Who falls apart
They are
Estate staging masetero tax and other crises to blame their opposition and framing
So they can move directly against us
This is meaningless in terms of predicting
Shooting Alex says this all the time because it's his way of dodging responsibility when people who believe the s*** he says
Are they hurt
Instead of recognizing that his ideology is toxic and leads to violence frequently Alex has an intellectual coward and he hides me
Behind an insistence that
Everything that makes him look bad as a secret plot by the most evil collection of villains in the world
Because only I was a strong enough of a boy to defeat the Devil
Do load of s*** but again
You do with making any kind of prediction
This clip is from June 17th 2021 so it's also about a year old
You might notice that a lot of these clips are from June 2021 which seems strange
I think it might have something to do with the fact that the January 6th committee was being formed that month which would definitely make Alex rant about
False Flags
More than normal
Here's the clip from it's a large
For context
But this is globalism
Take over this year
The New World Order Revolution
This isn't
And that's why
No matter
How much heat
And how bad they look and I'm at
How much
Everleigh do falls apart
They are
Blame their opposition and
Fortera
So they can move directly against
Exposing
January 6th
False flag is so important
We know what agency
Weave
Add
Carlson
Very measured
Wuhan lab leak
Everything else
And then
We'll all be brought up
Stop
Publications
Home Depot
Who did it
How they did it
And let the system deny it
So we can discredit
This clip is Alex going to rain check about blowback
From January 6th
Also I wonder if all those names and all the agencies it's all these people had and they like all the evidence
They ran January 6th ever came out there's a
Did it still simmering
I mean that you know it's like a it's like a Crock-Pot
Situation you thought it was a Boiling Pot
That situation but now it's
Slow cooking
And
The best
The best pulled pork
Take 6
Is it what 67 years like we got a long way to go before we get
Some good stuff from
This clip is being misused
Yeah man it's sad
This is sad
It is actually I was getting so disappointed by this
That some anomaly that came up in this next clip actually let me down
Completely different path non predict
YouTube clip
They're going to try to launch a race war
False flag event
Try to blame a course of gun owners and Trump supporters and Christians and so on
They will see if the people will comply to turn in their guns which I believe people will not
Comply
That would be insane at this point with the
The police being defunded in violent crime exploding
Liberal cities everywhere people need self
Defense more than ever
Including by the way
Women
And a People color and also
Gays and lesbians and transgenders are buying guns
More than ever before right now
Buying guns more than ever so it's going to be
Among left-wing
Legislators
If we the American people if we surrender our guns
I believe we will be invaded
Yeah so this was Mike Adams just being Mike Adam Wright any kind of prediction for the
Buffalo shooting
It's just kind of the thing that said on Infowars pretty much everyday
The General
And Mike Adam saying will be invaded is part of his weird
Saying that he was going on for a while but how
China was going to have a Mainland inpatient
Yeah
Yeah I mean it's a guy who says there will only be Survivor
Can't be on your pretty
TextNow
Until there are only lone survivors in which case
You know I'm not going to be around
So he can say I told you so to all the four people download
Way bad I mean in a little because if there's Lone Survivor shortwave
Yeah I bet they're really rich Lone Survivor so too you know
Could be us from July 2nd
I can't find the raw episode of this on Alex's because mysteriously there's no video
Of this episode
They have an MP3
Of the episode but it's only an hour and 20 minutes long so it's a Friday episode so it should be 3 hours
Didn't know what was going on so I gave the episode of Spin and it struck me as a
Very strange
Did this is how the file that's on Alex's website m
Love you man love
Play Bob
Spirit Airlines personal enlightenment
Call Yao
I hate doing this cuz I
Tell me what's going on
It's a very
Complicated dichotomy which is the new world order that we all say
I understand you know
You got to be real careful when you walk and I'm not sure whether you're doing it
Avoid
Ridicule or because you're afraid of
Programming
Is currently under
MediaFire
Heard in my entire life
One.
That's all
You never seem to
Connect
Yes.
Set in the Bible spinach August 8th
That is the one thing that by
There's one that's where it ended
I think that you couldn't cut 40 more seconds off I think I think it's a coincidence
I don't think it's anything to farias where they
That this is where it ends
But I think it's kind of funny that the set of circumstances
Are exactly what would be
Be interpreted by the people who insist that Alex
Works were Mossad as being like this
It's really weird
I just
That's dead
That's an unfair coincidence
Because that's
Exactly what you would
But it's not
It's just a coincidence
Probably have nothing useful coincidence
I guess
I don't know why did you leave that part in I don't know
Cut that last 40 seconds
I'm not convinced that it's intentional in any way to cover up something
I do think
That it is anomalous
Like most of these episodes are there real or no
Do a lot of them that are
Partially there right
Right I could see some sort like
Speak the system must be automated in some way
Some sort of a reader or I or something
But it's just
Army football one of the things that is
Like
Very uncomfortable territory for Alex
His what
He's being confronted
About how he never talks about
Jewish stuff I would go see here's the thing
I would go back and cut that out now because
It look
It's real bad you look weird
Pictures look bad you know you kind of you kind of
Interesting point
The comes up with
This caller in that is it I'm sure he speaks for many people in the audio
It is
They interpret Alex's Behavior as
Being like
You say the things you say because you're worried about blowback or whatever
Yeah speak
Freely but we get
Oh yeah well I mean it's like whenever the lawyers like oh he's a Showman
And his listeners were like
Yeah course you're saying that
Got to say that to the law called indirectly and was just like you in this week
Do you mean just
Small number of Alex
His listeners who believe that
I feel like there's a larger and larger number of Alex
Episode cut off
Amazing website but I'm sneaky and resourceful so I was able to find a copy of the full episode
Answer to anything
That I would think would be like well we're not in a
It's not like
Deeply anti-Semitic
But it's
Not good
It wasn't like he goes in at 8 man yeah I connected that. A long time ago my right brother
No it wasn't that bad no
So I listened
Call her the baguettes
California
Obviously
And I did an animation of millgate and you guys played inside preciate that
Get a sweater and you shoot them in the head
YouTube
Listen to the sky
How do you say
Basically use for money
How to control people
And
He was only a rabbi
In the Bible
Where is beefing up the one only one
On the one true God
There's no Trinity
There's no Boo. There's not any of this other stuff is only one true God
So this is kind of a bad look
I think it's probably what you might call like soft
Anti-semitism
Yeah
Refused
Weird
I think it's a week
Keycloak on Alex's bar just as a person pretending to be able to deal with people with opposing
Used to sympathize information like it clearly
Isn't engaging with it what anybody saying looks like they're only related
Because they were back-to-back
You know so it would
Reference
The other color if this guy was like three colors down the line would be like
Well that's a new one wasn't doing this weird like I'm going to take calls
Disagree with me
But you wouldn't take a call where's that Jesus isn't the Messiah
He gets another caller disagrees them on that show and it's actually about something
Kind of substantial in the real world and that is that Alex gave Trump
About all the vaccine stuff sure secures Alex's response to that and I think this is so telling
Alex is completely admitting on air that he lied and made stuff up to excuse things that would make Trump look bad to his audio
How it's made up a story to sell his audience which was Trump was pretending to be okay with vaccine so the economy could open
And then you turn around and I'll be there in 20
Alex is literally saying
I was playing Devil's Advocate to try to figure out what the hell he was
Alex
Trump doing something that didn't fit with the version of him that he created for his audience
Hero worship so
He had to come up with an acceptable explanation
In that way
How it's made up his idea to drop would come out against the vaccine later to
Pacify his audience
And keep them in his Revenue stream and he saying exactly that when this color is pressing him on it
It's outrageous
Is really nice of him to be upfront about
Listen
I was lying to you strategic
Now when you call me on it
You know honestly I'm not really at fault
Is it cuz I was doing the right thing it would have been too big of a problem for me
To Juneau admit this
Before that I was just making stuff up for me to deal with the fact that Trump was
Actively pushing this vaccine forward show as he was still in office and there was a chance that we could hold onto power
In some way so I didn't want to remove that possibility
Turned on proms that I wouldn't be able to make all that money off the election
Fraud narrative
False
Do you have to tell you the pacifier everybody and make you
Not be so mad at Trump
Yeah that's a really good idea so what you're saying to me is like
Who Among Us
Hasnat yada yada yada Dar god king
From joining the globalist to murder us all with vaccine perspective the sort of information that Alex is willing
Presented as fact on his show it's
He's just spitballing in order to explain away inconvenient
Maladies
Cuz he's a liar I mean it does seem weird that you would just go on your show and be like listen
Anytime somebody does something that doesn't fit within my pre-plan Narrative of them
I will make up an excuse for them to allow them to
Continue doing that with
0 pushback from me at all because I want a good
Brighton
Mostly in service of making sure that the audience has an excuse to stay in line
Narratives that I'm pushing
Probably coincidence that only part of this episode is on Alex's site but man this is pretty embarrassing stuff
I think that you really do get a glimpse of like how
Bad he is at responding
Actual criticism
In any productive way doesn't understand it no
He gets these calls that
Should be
Easy for him to handle
Italian sub
Complaining about how
Callers bring up
Judaism gives him a headache
And
Caller brings up Trump in the warp speed stuff you just like
This compilation so I ended up getting
Completely off track
Why I
Maybe you forgot that this point that I was trying to find that Mike Adams clip
Oh that's right but honestly does
The matter he was predicting anything and it wasn't Alex I don't know why
Does that make him look good to have guessed too kind of predicted things to predict
Protective
Is it bolstering Alex's is it almost like Hey listen I got a I got my Flavor Flav over here also
Also backing me up with my Chuck D knowledge I'm dropping on you
I don't think it helps I don't
Either
Clip
Are planning in my view
Call Slugterra tax here in America
To cement their rollout against
This is meaningless and vague and has nothing to do with protecting the Buffalo shooting
This clip is from June 24th 2021
And you'll notice again that this is in the week we're all these clips seem to be from around when the January six
This committee was for
I don't really care about this clips
Sentence about a year old and it isn't relevant and the rest of the compilation
Is just a couple of the clips that already played playing again and a few more were Alex's just saying vague nonspecific false flag
Coming
And that means less than nothing
He does that every day
The title of this video is Alex Jones predicted the white supremacist false flag shooting at Buffalo grocery
ReStore in it does absolutely nothing to back that climb up
The only instance of him mentioning a black grocery store was from a year ago in a list of possible targets for false Flags.
Go-Buster going to do in order to
Distract from the 2020 election
An audit
This is Alex trying to profit from murder priorin simp
Well there's no way around that
It's one thing to have suspicions about world events in
Exploring those suspicions
That's fine
It's a completely different thing to make s*** up about world events of your race
It's Buddies.
Don't look bad
And then
It's even worse as a thing to cover a racially-motivated mass murder primarily through the lens of how right you were
Predicting the shooting
When you have to lie and create a fraudulent compilation in order to
Pretend you predict
That's a level of narcissism that's honestly scary
Yo it's the day after the shooting and Alex doesn't cover any of the actual.
Details of the shooting but instead
When's the Lion's Share of his time talking about himself and his amazing predictive abilities
I've been doing this awhile and this is a level of being an a****** that even
Like it's freshly surprising even though I'm sure
That we've done
This before
Yep we we've been shocked by his callousness and self-centeredness
In the face of a tragedy before
And it still
Surprising
It really is cuz you just kind of
No matter how often you see it
You just kind of don't think
Possible you know
Like when it's not right in front of you
You're like well I mean there's no way I can even being could be
It's right in front of you
It's just
Such a disrespect
To the
The feelings that most other people are having
But also his connection to the
Because of it
Not only is he
Self-aggrandizing his prediction
He is also part of the
Cause
And he's making money off of
I mean he's a sentence using an integrated
Terrorist
Machine
I think we've made that point a number of times
Man
But
Let me ask you a question
Those clips
The ones that weren't from
That same week
Are the ones you don't know where the show is
Not all of them
Because the Mike Adams one from the clip that's partially on Alex's site
Was on
July 2nd
Cuz the one that the only one that was really an anomaly was October one right
Yeah that you can't prove that that woman that wasn't October
13th for sure
How to
Studio that entire week for
Not the next day. The day after could have been some point in October but I'm not going to go through every episode Naruto
And try to find his
Guy can match his clothes I'm just I'm just hearing a suspicion
In my brain that says
Alex half-remembered
That that was around the time that he was predicting all that stuff
That's how he forced an intern to listen to like
What's 2 weeks from July 29th
Another compilation of specificity did mostly just around
Around that week
Yeah it's all meaningless
And he should be ashamed
Shooting that happened in Buffalo the tragedy as are the other shootings that have happened
Before incense
Eject the violence has a different backstory to it a
Set of variables that led to it happening in from the information
Unavailable
It does seem like a
Shooter in this case was motivated by Alex yells on the radio every day
It makes sense that he would try to make
Conspiracy out of this
Honestly when you think about it
Maybe an act of self-preservation
The way you behave
I don't know it sucks
It sucks
You know it is like the total purse
Perspective vortex
From Douglas Adams
You know that
Reveals how meaningless
You know so makes it
It clear how meaningless you are in the universe
That you lose your mind
Like in this situation of Alex
Could be forced into a place that made it so clear what it was he was doing to her
You know a wooden baby destroys brain
You know that kind of thing I don't know how you be able to
Sleep at night if you looked
Set this
Like
Well through the objective lens
Subjective experience
And you saw like
The Dynamics
That we're at play You're The Way You Are
Clearly lying in order to create this compilation
That is only meant to prove that you put
Predicted the shooting
Which is the front line headline of your coverage the day after the shooting
Like it's just
And it's also your defense against
Being
Part of the
Piano
Both of those things at once
Box
So
This was out to Sunday show
Aunt
Like I said I think we maybe there's a chance we could have gotten into
Do the Monday as well but
It would have been an overly long episode
Quite frankly
Trying to find some of these clips took along
Denso
We will get to that
Some more of the Alex actually in-studio content to push back on these ideas
Did Alex was right about the predicted things
Because
Is something that has traction
In social media spaces
There are people who push that meme
And it's
Toxic
And it does have the potential to
Radicalized more people but also just get people
Who are unassuming
Dive to see a compilation recycle
SA
Grocery store
Beckham to have the effect of being
Well I gave Alex a shake
You know maybe I'm doesn't know more than I give him credit for something
And that is a fraudulent perfect
Past off by this
This nap
Strategic
Propaganda
And each
Get you one step closer to being
Caught in the
You know where
They'll just keep feeding you more and more
S***
Every every single touch increases the number the possibility that you're going to get more and more of the same
Ideas
Nor will our next episode.
But until then
I hope you all have a wonderful dream agree me some
And now here comes
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work