Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Sit around
But the author of saline and talk a little bit about Alex
Jones
Did we are damn door down
The end of the astronaut ice cream
I have to say I found a
Great astronaut ice cream exactly what you would want I may get some more of it
Imperfect astronaut ice cream this s***
Hits the spot ice cream
Took a picture of it cuz I ate it
It's not here anymore
And one of the things that I find really difficult about this is there does not appear to be a brand name on this
Another picture of a Rocket taking off on it
Is a Neapolitan freeze dried ice cream sandwich and then a little smaller print it says space food
Space food
Yeah I don't know quit look
If you're looking for astronaut ice cream look for the one with a rocket
Because I bet there are only there's only one of those
Rocket has really good almost worth it
For the whole week
Yeah yeah for sure cuz it get that spot of the like childhood memory was like back when this was like
The first time you
Experience
The eat on the Move Six Flags
I was really nice and
I'm excited
Did you receive the summaries for everyone but it takes an issue
Do I have to say
I have access to your freezer
Freezer
Oh my God
My bright spot is the
I
Finally have my own entry to add to the dreamy creamy summer
Well I should have rated your freezer
This is honor Bastion 100% unqualified
Endorsement of cloud cookie
There's somewhere off of Clark
And
F****** incredible
Baby delivery
No
Is an ice cream sandwich OSHA cream sandwich with two cookies
Cookies by themselves
Are absurd and they're delicious
I thought it would be nice Cream Sandwich about yeah
And in fact it was Ice Cream Sandwich about
Yeah but that's bigger got it on Monday
And so far it is Thursday and I have eaten one half of it
Wow you're not committed to the car it turns out that's what I that's what I'm learning
If you could finish that in one sitting you deserve a t-shirt of some sort
Deliver out to
I'm looking I'm looking at this
There are other website they have some some interesting cookies
You don't even know who know
Actual real God
Roasted mushrooms
Like toasted
Well here here's the situation mushroom marshmallows
Are in real danger of this becoming first of all spawn Khan and second Us ending up like me
Just looking at this menu
We are seemingly struggling on this way I'm going to get off call
I'm going to have to give that a shot
Maybe next week will be
Local
Ice cream sandwiches I don't know we'll see okay I haven't even made it on Monday
Another week's plan
Kosher
Today we have an episode to go over
We're going to be talking about May 16th 2022 that's Mondays show
We've seen last episode that we were going to check in with Alex's coverage of
The Buffalo shooting once he actually got into Studio because
On Sunday show the day after the shooting
Pinky
And I was just there for a little bit
Cuz there was a big audience he just yelled about how he was right about everything
And then someone else has
And so I wanted to do this just to get the first episode of Alex's actually there
Ultimately
Kind of a little bit soft
In terms of
A lot of meat to get into
The most impact
Actual thing I would have
Like
Present for the audio
Here it is
As a document of Alex's day
Definitely still some stuff
It's worth mining
Yeah
Put you on and this is something we're going to do someday
But we're going to get a deepfake
Machine
And we're going to make a whole 20 Clips or whatever of a fake show that you've written in your mind
Square Alex
Does the other direction absolute nice guy once once
Progressive socialism for all
I think you can do it
Central tragedy
We need to be
Consider tightening background checks
Jordan
So first the damn sweatband of Rob dues Kangol hat
I'm a policy wonk
I worship at the altar of
It's like you so much you're now apology walk
I think it's like V Canadian babadook
I Googled it and it's a movie about a witch or some sort I'm not sure
Next Liberty must be watered by the blood of interdimensional demons
Thank you very much makes the globalist Easter Bunny told me to give you Soros box via patreon thank you so much
I'm a policy could you very much
Is Michelson thank you so much here and I'll probably walk
Can you very much
And hello to my husband has broken our YouTube recommendations because he's watched
Too many videos of the band
That is also a birthday
So happy birthday to this guy who keeps watching ghost videos
You weren't outside
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Miami
A little breaking for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm in a
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe the next few moments
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
Apologize to
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not
He's not better today where he will be better
Did you know that all ghost music videos
Feature Whoopi Goldberg
Is that right
By law
I meant all Ghostface videos
Include the guide
SweetWater 420
Jordan before we get into this episode I just wanted to give
A quick
Shout out
I guess
A GoFundMe
I recently this this week
Unfortunately very sadly
Marcel Fontaine V
Person who was misidentified by Alex
And the Infowars as
The Parkland shooter
Passed away and his family and friends
I have a
A GoFundMe for funeral expenses and what have you so
If anybody feels like jumping in that would be something that would be great
And I know that it was posted
Nrr Reddit
Their subreddit
Thank you two folks who have
I tripped in
I also already
Very tragic
And
Stoffel
Yep there's not much to say
So Jordan here we are we start the day
January 16th
January
May 16th
Here we are at the beginning of the show
A small sampling of our
Total censorship
A form of martial law
Here in America and gun confiscation
So this wasn't from the 6 minutes
What's that doesn't care on the radio that was a like John bowne report this is actual show
He starts
The show just the same thing
Depending on the day I sometimes have more or less
Patients at the start of the show I am feeling very low
On our last episode we covered Alex's Sunday show where he covered the Buffalo shooting by it mostly the
Just fraudulently bragging about how he predicted it and then letting
Someone else has the rest of
And that one Monday here he is back in studio on the first thing he does is brag about how he predicted the shooting and any place that same shity
Compilation that we discussed on the last episode
The bottom line is this
Houston prediction
The shooting isn't being used to censor anyone
No one is using this to bring in martial law and no one planning to confiscate guns
This is a list of false premises but Alex is trying to use to build his reporting on
But ultimately because his foundation is so shity and full of lies whatever he has to say about this subject is really just a house
Built on sand
It's really
Pointless what he's doing is pointless
Yeah yeah I mean
Because that is
Babe
For lack of a better word to that point
You know I
AV idea is
Takis
This much
Attention away from
The problem as you can
Can't keys made people angry
Absolutely absolutely
Just pushing all of the
These people into a corner with jangling keys
Yeah yeah it's but it's
The opposite of product
And I find it really annoying
Yeah yeah absolutely
So here's a nightclub Alex announces a gas
What's coming on in Dubai
Sean Stone filmmaker
Author researcher honesty Oliver Stone Son
Smart Cookie in his own right
He is going to be in studio with us in
Third hour
I had a Gerald Celente but I intend to take
50 phone calls herself
What's in the fourth segment
Making calls
Search on Stones coming on the show and sent his dad Direct
Did Savages and we're not going to talk about that interview at all
That's a Dalek seems particularly focused on going to Kohl's on this episode
How to get some help with a
Conspiracy talk
Components from the caller
What are the parts of Alex's show the dolphin heart
To pick up on if you don't listen to a bunch of it
Collars us something
Repeat that to the audience's Intel that he
Claim through gun from a high-level secret source
The next day
This happens if
There's a collaborative aspect on Alex's show
He sometimes needs the collars to help him Workshop this b*******
A lot of the time this is just the caller is repeating fake things that they saw to me more reading the right-wing blog headline
At the end of the day this work around really just accomplishes Alex not needed to do the minimal amount of work cuz it's normally
Only required to do this stupid show
Just have all the audience read the blog
For him and not just that whenever it's a topic like this the advance
To having the audience
It's come up with your
Conspiracy narratives is that
You know you won't accidentally offended them
This is stuff
It's already
They're fine with because
They're the ones that gave it
Take a little bit of a temper
Where are the people who I need to abused
How callous can I be how how is this too far all of this stuff he can get from the audience without having
To take responsibility for it
And then when he comes in the next day
I know exactly what
I can and can't say
And if that is any part of his workflow if that's any part of
Is Gage then
And I don't I don't know what he learned all the colors aren't great
So Alex Alex has a proclamation
If you read between the lines
Is the
You are responsible for 7 billion
Total planetary collapse
You will witness
You will wish to God later
Don't stop what you're part of
You will wish
But you've been on the right side of History
I can't imagine
The Howe
You even get to a point where you can coherently argue that Alex is on the right side of any
By Briana Wilde
I mean I guess the conservative party
He's to the right of that
Oh oh yeah I guess ideologically is on the far right side that is true
Okay there's nothing to that
Of course
Speaks always have to be incredibly High
The world dying has to be the steak
That's been established
People are bored
This isn't the future of the human races
Hanging in the balance
I think logically he's really coming at this from the wrong angle because I don't see how I could
Can wish I would have been on the other side
Well you probably be dead
7 billion people died you're probably not going to have any regrets
Pointed out if all of us die it's like none of
Honestly I don't think either you or I have much survival potential
I'll put a jingle a hat on and I'll dance to make the people smile in the post-apocalypse a lot
Depictions of post-apocalyptic
Jester's coming back actually do see some gestures are fairly considerable
There's usually a Jester character in every post-apocalyptic they also die
Sex toys
You know like they're all the jester characters always
As I go through this I think I'm on the dead side
I think
They aren't going to cater to
To your medication
Securing that in a post-apocalyptic huge
I could be extremely useful for very short burst
Extra
I've been very naughty.
Alex
Thoughts about the Buffalo shooter and
I think this is not good
Get to
How to get into this terrible
Schizophrenia
Operation
Listen
Mega stone avoid
I'm going to do that once I start taking your calls
Not going to cover right now because
Demon
Whatever else went on
Yesterday the UN estimates that 450,000. 287 million
On the verge of starvation over 40 million in the numbers
Six-month-old
An extra 40 million people last 2 years under
Million people
Something is really important to point out that Alex is saying that the shooter I had to
Schizophrenia that's not based on anything
She just using that word isn't
Insult not as an actual description of a
The condition that someone may have
Nope something
He's throwing the route
Nope
Also these numbers about few food in
Insecurity and starvation don't come out twice
To hear Alex is making that up so it sounds more official to the listeners but this is just the same stuff
He's been saying since the beginning
20 started caring about Hunger so he
You could use it as an anti lockdown talkingpoi
The number of people in the world to experience exude in
Probably actually quite a bit higher than Alex's saying
With action against hunger they say quote as many as 811 million people worldwide go to bed
In November 2021 David Beasley the world food program executive director was going around
Making comments that they estimated the 45 million people
We're living on the edge of famine
And what aspect of this naturally is due to covid related issues but a bunch of it is
Regional conflicts are often a big piece of the puzzle and climate change
Probably the biggest
Just Factor
Alex doesn't care about all the
But it's an effective performance for him to put on
When Alex should be talkin about white supremacy
Is mass shooter who shared a lot of his own ideology
The best way for him to sidestep that and pretend he's taking The High Ground is to get about half the shooting was bad but so many
People are dying from Hunger
And Alex's righteous for focusing on the right
Thing
It's not righteous man
It scoured
And now it says no answers or even suggestions
Do the question of world hunger
And if he had his way and Ron Paul was elected
So many more people would be starving in the world due to
Bcomplete abolishment of foreign aid
Like he is
Ridiculous
Cuz he has no
Solution and actually
His policies
Specifically wood
Kill way more people
In the developed
Open world full of s***
Yep
Know if if I'm murdered
Dan please make sure just do me one favor don't let the
Person who murdered me
Come to my funeral and then s*** in my corpse
Cuz that's what that tone of voice was
That was Alex shiting in my f****** mouth
It's well at mean
Is a distraction
Jesus yeah yeah yeah
I mean that's
Him say it him saying those words man
Itzy iT'Z what about kind of
Nerf game with
With death
Yeah that is fragile
Especially when you're what you're really saying is
Oh man I wish I had the opportunity killed more people
Innocence
He's on the right side of History
Sure all these ideas he has are great
So
This is just
Nonsense
Alex is
Dead set on trying to push the idea that the
Hunger that's being spirits around the world is solely due to covid lockdown
Million
How many
Football stadium
Well yeah we got is a lockdown cuz you're couple million-dollar coverage so that
Plan
We had the point
And I'm just sitting here
Billionaires
Top talk show hosts
Brogan
Alex
How do you tell the public
Because the public
Handle the truth I go back to A Few Good Men
Will come in next
Famous
Sing with
Tom Cruise
Open
We're getting pissed off and finally
Well then those walls falling in
Because it's true for both
What are the whole system goes down
Hangouts got sidetracked thinking about A Few Good Men
Sapiens book in the wrong side of the Few Good Men
Both sides of an apparently
Yeah
I mean you know
Dry please talking about this this worldwide hunger stuff and then he really get sidetracked
Text by the image of
A Few Good Men
Missouri gets into like
The dynamic of who is
This beep
And then he does actually when he comes back from break he plays that
I had to go
Cuz that's what life
This guy loves movie
Bloveslife
And life is moving some people save a Doug Benson Loves movies
Absolutely not
But has he turned them into real life is not so he still lives on the other side of moon
Doug's got to change his podcast Doug likes movies
Love
Alex has something in his Mexico but I found
Really confusing to sit with for a minute I think I
Cody sings really f*****
It's important to understand that we're going from a system where we had
Horse owners proud of their horse
Sprawling cities in there
Cruise ships in there
Money
Saw the wealth of population
Population was good
Reversal of those ideas
You can pretend you're part of the power structure but you're not
And prosperity
To have that
Do a system that wants to implode the world economy
So I guess Alex thinks the Davis Group and the Vatican are the same
Same thing which is a
So if I understand correctly
The old oligarch
They used to look at us as their toys
To be cherish
There's a condescending paternalism there Alex's describing
Another new oligarchs want to destroy their toys because they're no good anymore
I guess
It's sort of like the bad kid in Toy Story
Right right
Everything's movies
So what point was that at
That the elites were good when were the elite sprout
Alex bewley tube in the Elites for a long time several thousand years right well the Rothschilds businesses go back
Back to the 1700
John D Rockefeller founded Standard Oil in 1870
If you want to include the royal families of Europe is Alex often does
It goes back a bit further and it's a bit Messier
If you're including the Vatican now we're in real trouble of course all of it goes back to the devil
This is a problem for the idea of there being benevolent to Leetsdale point in the past
Universe
How long this is been going Disick time
What movies were real I think at the end are you might get a glimpse of what Alex's dance
Messing around
He's talking about this old version of the elite she wants
Stability prosperity in order any says quote they did some things that weren't perfect to have that
What exactly were those imperfect things Alex is talking to
Well I mean you know Pinochet did some stuff you know Chow chest you was a problem
Things but they kept
The trains running on time
I think he's talking about slavery
Widespread rampit
Discrimination
Those are the things that the elites
We're doing that weren't perfect were raping slaves that was
Listen
It's not
But they kept
Order
And that's what's important
I I can't I can't
Year that as anything else relay out
I do believe that his
Black
Of clarity on what he's talkin about the
They did things that were perfect
It's just screams to me
Yep
So this Clips truck might you're weird
Talk about the world collapse
We should do about it
Magnifying
One woman
Grocery store
Shots fired
Crazed
Schizophrenic
They call the whites
Call them a white supremacist on yesterday's show
Alex doesn't call him a white
Well you know that was In the Heat of the Moment he had not time to think about it now you don't know if he's a white supremacist or not
How would you know
You did yesterday actually after more information has come to light there's no way to prove it
I mean okay
Okay
Alright
Very weird
Very weird going for a white supremacist Monday Tuesday call him
Well I think that's probably
Cuz he got a
Text from some white
Friends who were like Hey listen
Don't pay nuts like where the bad guy
Supremacist
Spawn Alex anymore cover no kidding
So this
Rant is really weird but Alex gets into next
I think
Kind of understand a little bit of what he
He's trying to express but
We can't because
Is he did it would look really bad
Type it all up
Black-on-black in Chicago every year
You can't so much about Chicago
Kenosha
Because the system wants to guilt
White people
So here we are
Understand
Turn our borders destroying our food supply
Supply
With each other
I'mma tell
People Hispanic
Blacksmith system one
If you don't
You're working for Satan
God is going to cut your ass off
Brothers
Accused
Black people
And I refuse to buy in the leopards division
Resume
Come together
A little transphobic punch there at the end is a little bit unnecessary
Power doing a wrestling show
Like
Three-quarters of the way through I would have
The best triple tag team in the world
Come in and just beat him with chairs
And then the crowd would lose their s***
I don't know depends on what territory around maybe so happy
So there's something really interesting about this clip here Alex is ranting about how he refuses to
To become races
It's interesting because he's already super races
What this reveals is
Kind of a weird thought
It seems to me that Alex thinks that the media is trying to make him braces
He feels like the me
Media is covering this instance of a white person who did a mass shooting but there's no coverage of crimes committed by black people
This is an intentional plot
Too pushy
White identity button
Then make him feel weird
There's no doubt that there is a problem of violence here in Chicago
But the root of it and the solutions are multi
The faceted and Alex is absolutely not into
To the matter at all and there is a lot of coverage
Maybe
There's more coverage of it locally because a lot of it is a local issue
According to CBS news they didn't malisis of the FBI
Is crime data Chicago's the city with the highest murder rate
In the country but
We never really have questions about why the news isn't paying more attention to murders in Philadelphia
Which is 16
Or Kansas City which is 8
There's two reasons for that
The first is that generally murders in Kansas City or Philadelphia are considered local issue
And they don't make it to the national news unless there's some particular detail about the crime
That makes it stand out
4 coverage
In the case of Chicago people like Alex of gotten used to point of Iowa
To minimize whatever crime they need to deflect
Attention from
Unless it becomes necessary that the murders that happened in Chicago should have
Constant force
Front Page News
Coverage all over
Replaced mimetic
There is also a racist dog whistle aspect
Let's do this as well
Chicago
There's definitely a bit of that.
It's baked in as well and that part of why it's a standard
Right talking
Point that the people have just gotten
Used to people like Alex
Disappointing to
To minimize other murders that are inconvenient for them there's no way Alex new knows about the curfew that
Like to put in
Put on 14th
Diorite possibly know that Lightfoot
Just put up a curfew from
Shooting in Buffalo obviously we'll end up getting more media attention due to a bunch
Two factors that make it something to do is entities field
Bonita cover
It was in a grocery
Restore the guy left a Manifesto it was live-streamed on Twitch
Clearly motivated by a racist ideology
These things tend to attract more attend
Dylann roof as well as other white supremacist Mass Shooters have pointed to their feelings that crimes committed by black people get caught
Alberta by the media while crimes committed by white people get a lot of attention
Is being a major factor in the radicalization
That makes total sense
That's because it's a white supremacist propaganda talking
Appointment to radicalized
I went to only get this information from places that are essentially just repackage
The same kinds of talking points so
Makes sense
He feels like someone was trying to make him more races
It's just it's not the media it
It's the media he chooses to consume
His media
Diet is full of things
Things that are meant to radicalize people towards of course he would be feel like he was being poor
To be racist
It is a common thought process
That unspoken
For people in this media sphere of just like
If these black people I've never met with stopped
Doing these things that they're not doing
I wouldn't be racist towards
Not good
I feel like Alex has a
Nonpoint there but if he
Some soul-searching
He might be able to get to a little bit of the bottom of this maybe
Maybe there's something you could unravel in therapy because it's pretty transparent when he's talking about it on air
Go to
You know
Do you just can't
It's too late
It's just too late you know definitely
Especially considering this mix
For these people
Anymore
Situation
It's going to name check though
Is literally pushing the exact type of brake replacement narratives that motivated the buffalo
I mean that s*** that's that
That's crazy
Outrageous
I mean even f******
Tucker took
Least two days off from
Great replacement there now
I haven't checked but
He's waiting for the next mass shooting to take a little break
Either Alex has no idea what he's saying or he's going on his show and pretending he disagrees with the mass shooter by yelling about
That's something they agree on ferry Depot
I don't know I find this to be
Level of irresponsibility or
Recklessness or malicious unacceptable
Songs with our brothers and sisters
Beyond racial disparities are disagreements or anyting
Now of course
We don't
Appreciate these types of the mass Shooters with their now I will read their Manifesto out loud to you and tell you how right it is
Obviously he didn't mean to do the things
But I told him he should do that I said it would because I split an infinitive means the media can't
Was motivated by the guy believing that there was a plan that the
Globalist or putting into effect
And let me tell you the globalist
Do have that flyer
I just don't get human beings anymore man
Free Speech has a pretty woman
Yeah sure sure but this sucks
So here was a
Dreadfully revealing clip
This clip ism
Embarrassing
After
Doing this
I would quit
And
That's why I'm calling on
CEOs
Rebecca's the Buffalo mayor was giving a press
All the social media platforms to examine their policies
And to be able to look me in the eye and tell me that everything is being done
The big can
To make sure that this information has not spread
Identify
What information like this the second
Easley taken down
Fun with the manifesto
Theories
That results in
The radicalization of a young person sitting in their house
Is
Barry
And it's something that has to be dealt with you have called it
Blame for what
First Amendment
Come shoot everybody
Oklahoma
Watch suspect is schizophrenic
Oh
Get out
Is basically idea that the Buffalo shooter has
Schizophrenia because
This headline is in his stack
Yeah and he doesn't realize that it's about a completely different person
This is an article about Jerry Varnell a 23 year old guy in Oklahoma City who is planning to bomb a bank
It's a completely different
Situation Room 27
Shity work all around
I don't I don't know how you can do this
This poorly but
I guess Alex's
His response to reading headline and realizing that has Oklahoma
It also says
Bomb
His responses like oh this is the right article I don't know they must have gotten the city wrong
Are the state wrong
It's it's nonsense this is so bad
Yeah I'm terms of
Quality of information that's being disseminated
Listeners really should
Wake the f****** yeah man that's like a clip that just
Steve like
You want to play and then just sit
In the silence
It's done and just like
Really absorb
All of the evil
There was that clip of Rogan that was going around in real-time realizing that he was
Cover story
Like kind of disappointed when he realizes that it's fake
And that's the same sort of moment that Alex is having but
He's not
Willing to be like oh I got the story wrong
At the end there when he's there's
Pause music
I don't know why it says Oklahoma
That's the same sort of revelatory moments
But Alex is too much of a liar
Do own up to like
Like bye-bye with
If this one
I mean I think the thing about the Rogan
Spot that just
It it just lays bare
The the
The feeling
That's important
Twozies peep
It has nothing to do with what everything says it doesn't have anything to do with ideology
Was believe what they like
And what their keep chasing is that good feeling of reading a headline and going
Oh man I'm so right about the world
I'm so right
Yeah that bet there's an emotionally satisfying aspect to it that is
Deflated when you realize that
Most of your headlines are based on bulshit
Yeah you do you know I am right
About headlines an awful lot
Has not once made me feel good
Not once you need to change do you know why cuz I'm only right whenever it's the worst thing possible happen
You should start
Becoming a
Agnostic
That's like it's Gerald Celente
Aaron's forecast
To the right wing and then
Just lie about everything better
Suspend a line but everything
Superchips
I blame him but I blame more
Beyond the state police and others
Nothing was done
Pizza shooting
What does it do anything
Nothing in their clip was true
All of that was made of
All of the information that Alex is conveying to his audience
Is
Incorrect
He's basic theories on completely incorrect information and at the same time disseminating the great route
Play Summit style conspiracy theories
And presenting them as fat
I mean it's just
Need to be opposite way it's not even useless
It snapped its destructive
Yeah I know I mean this is
IMEI see no other conclusion to draw from this other than
Alex is encouraging the next
Mass shooter
Whether consciously or not I mean like there is yeah Thursday
There's a dynamic
Especially considering how good he
He's feeling right now
You know more mass shootings means I keep feeling good
Bigger audience
I don't know if you heard about the
But it was gotten some pictures were going around on social media that someone used a plane
And wrote Infowars in the sky and Alex's pretty excited about that
You should also
Recognize that Alex says
Like to take time to talk
About himself
Your phone calls
Directions
The great folks
I do not want
So we're not in
Credit for that we really appreciate
Find work because
Has become the maxim of
I don't believe in him
How you really feel
Piss in your Cheerios
Alex Jones
What are you doing
We salute
Everyone out there
That is doing
I care about this guy riding stunts
But the notion is a useful meme for him is
I really think is
That's why when he does these compilation
Of his predictions
I feel like it's very important
To take the time
To deconstruct why he's not right
About the things
That he claims he has protected
Dangerous meme
Because much in the same way you're talkin about these headlines being emotionally satisfying
There is a charge that people can get out of like
This this feeling that they're in on
Some sort of like
It's a secret information this information
MMA
That
The Alex Jones is right idea
Is a gateway into that
Gateway into experiencing that artificial
Dopamine Rush
And it's
A kid it can get people on that path
Dangerously I mean
That's one of the reasons that I I don't think
Human beings can use the internet but
It's not just that one
Burst of dopamine
There's also the likes you get from tweeting it out you know ocean I just got 30 like I only get four likes normal
Oh f*** I'm so popular now on top
That that the more engagement you have with that content
The more likely you are to get put into the algorithm
There's an X
Initial amount
Of attack that happens the moment you share
One f****** Alex Jones
I don't I don't know if
I don't know
It's automatic but I do think
Probably
There will be
Reroute some validation
That you get from people who have the same ideas and
Yeah I I just caution
People about this
And it's it something that I'm taking I feel like
Should be taking a bit more seriously
Absolutely than a lot of other like do you like
CNN is Isis
Reporters at risk
Ryan what have you but I don't think
Is much like potential in terms of
Bringing people back
Text to Alex
Where is the
Meme I think
Is
Something
That
Is Pope
In terms of that
I I feel I feel the obligation
Push back
I mean you know the ultimately
Anything your enemy does that make
Makes them feel good you should not engage in
And help them feel good like just Alex
Being his name on the Internet
A lot
Makes me feel good
Right he's my enemy I'm not going to insist that
Terrible
True
So
Alex
Is basing a lot of his coverage of the Buffalo shooting on fake
This is very very sad
The system knows that
That this guy was planning to do this and they let him do it that's come out in the news
This is just the Bedrock
Of his
This was a orchestrated shooting
Kind of talk
Based on
Just complete nonsense in a misrepresentation of new stories
Also interesting to call like the history of slavery in the ramifications of its some historic beefs
Have you
Have you noticed
And I'm gonna throw this out there
Have you noticed that one of their memes is that the media covers up black crime and only focuses on
White crime
And also
Anytime you talk about American history they go listen
Stuff happened but let's not worry about it right
Do you notice that the babies are extra on what they want to focus on
I'm at out there maybe they're the ones babe I'm just saying that if I cracy might be a thing that they're engaging
I know
I know it's crazy
So Alex does get two calls
I mean they have some theories
About this shooting
Not good
Controlled walk up to a woman
Quiet
Shoot a woman load groceries
Loading groceries in the car
Imagine
Demon possession this creature was under
So I just imagined murdering people all the time
To me I don't even see it enough
Time for somebody to get that evil
That's how evil the times all right now
What is life
And he could just go out I mean
It is
My controller
Took the shot
You know I mean
Italian man
Control that he was under
I have heard him rattle off so many
Stick f*****-up murder fantasies fantasies lot of them
Like unbelievable
Numbers of murders
Grotesque
Graphic
Description of like choking
Wolf Blitzer adapter blood everywhere on the answers Got Talent
Yeah Alex
Yeah you know exactly how that f*****
I
Yeah
And I think that we've also a gauged with
So many of the people that he claims were mine
Controlled view over the course of this
The show that like
That just brings so Hollow to man it's it's just a refuge for him
There's nothing to say mind-controlled shootings
Worked
Why are they
Why are they still doing
Well
So Alex another caller you also believes that there's my
My controller a foot
Yesterday when I was seeing those news reports
Trying to pay attention in
I just got this anger over me you know I just
Why are they releasing their MKUltra on us
What they're doing
Children Network
Obese children
MK Ultra
And now they're handing them guns and they're releasing them
I don't think it's as responsible as a way to engage with the
The Scholar
I think that there's some
Accuse that you can get that maybe this person is coming from
From a place of like
Real real
Sucked up conspiracy ideas
Alex's
Massaging them
You bet your totals right
I mean it's 2022 and they're in she's arguing that MKUltra is behind all of
And Alex
Instead of going like
Mam MKUltra you know
Alex Heller you just gone like Hey listen
Great
Assassin's right right
Current
This is a little bit really depressing
And everything old is new again and Alex does actually
Sort of
Skedaddle cuz I think
Did you finally get super powers like that too much
Try to warn people
I don't have any family because
You know what the cancer and all the others
And my husband he thinks
He thinks I'm going crazy and I'm telling him that he has to
Do something funny
Say something
Something
The line is drawn into staying and we're all going to have to either group together
Squishies people out because
Demons demons
Appreciate your call
Burrata
Is this Earth cuts her off at home
Because she saying the same stuff out
It sounds really bad
Sounds real crazy
Yeah it sounds really really upsetting
I'm coming from a caller
Control
The presentation of things and
I just
If there's such a
Like
An interesting
Difference
When you see like the same ideas being presented by someone who's
Clearly a bit Manic and a little bit
Like
Autophone Express
I think it really reveals what
Like the reality of the ideas Alex's Express
Not good
Well I mean you hear back at you like that and you go boy this lady does
Oh wait the elites are demons and I we got to get together and
Offer
Save that
It's all about tone
You know a lot of it is about
Ty really is
The ability to move along
Move Along
Or shift into a commercial
So Alex
Pixlr call
I don't know what was going on I was supposed to been eating or something cuz he just relieves this guy to talk for a bit
And he has some
Complaints about Trump
A real quick before I get when I want to talk
Second Amendment
Daytona
Yesterday
God
One gray commenting on it
Some people were
Stop it
Is Donald Trump
Merely
Position
When he
The economy down
Central
Hebrews
Trump
Kiss of quarters we got bamboozled
Now
And the Whole New World Order
Call and talk about all day long
And now he runs again
My big point
Dealing with
The situation
Would Joe Biden the new world
I mean like
Realistically with this collar is expressing whether he wants to admit it or not
Is Alex you lied to us and
You
Let's
Let's take a pic Alex
Either you lied to us
Which you have insinuated on
On the show in the past
Or your instincts were so bad that
You let us
Into
Following
This Judas goat
Is Alex would put it
So are your control that position sure
These are options but what's not adoption is
You have good instincts
Sprite and your support of trump was
Call look back on as a good thing
Response to that is like I got someplace about Trump
Let's ride let's not talk about that
Where in the Bible in season
Yeah
That's that's
Two-year that's old news
Did Bill Clinton got out of office today
You know it's more about W Baker the clintons entirely
Alex still thinks Obama's in charge of everything
This is nonsense he just is so afraid to take responsibility for the b******* that he push
And his audience know a lot of it has
Moved on from Trump
Or has
Right you do realize the Trump isn't
The person that they were told he was supposed to be
He doesn't want to take responsibility for his actions
In the course of the last five year
No I mean piece of s***
I think this is one of those times where
Feel
Terrible
For conservatives in general because they're their power is based upon
Non-stop constant aggrievement
And because of that
They can never
Appreciate a win
You know and they can never appreciate somebody who brought them away like
They don't love Mitch McConnell and yet Mitch McConnell gave them everything they've ever wanted
And they hate and I mean obviously
I think
That
Even with
Their opposition to vaccines
Goods and bads in terms of being able to
Lot of social
And
And the ones who got it got to live
Like it or not like whatever
Do you know complaints you have her picadillos about Trump
3 Supreme Court Justices
Like this
Get the f*** out of here with you ever wanted a
And you're still complaining which is why I feel bad for you and also why I hate you till the end
End of the Earth
You know there's a lot of
Agreement obviously is very profitable
41 and then second it's kind of has the same dynamic as like even when you win the election has to be stolen
In order to make sure if you lose an election
It's also
There is still kind of that
You can never be happy because I stole this extreme swing to the right that is been facilitated by
People like McConnell and Trump
Yeah it is
Kind of milquetoast
It's a little bit light
Even Stevens
You can sort of Justified
Right
Yeah we'll be we'll be excited for covid lockdowns whenever DeSantis makes it illegal to protest
Anywhere
Three-piece baby
Love it
Conservative love it to they're the ones who loved it.
The most they can't get enough
Yeah one last clue
Honestly
I mean we didn't write a policy of no stone family members extractor Rodger but he's not related
Oliver Stone on the podcast
Ripple effect
Forever
It was his dad who made the movie the sins of the father Gossip Girl
She's gone forever
Never seen
Episode
It's right he was the one
Yeah
I think
I don't I don't know enough about Gossip Girl
Partner watched it either
CIA
There's there's just a lot I mean a good bit of the show is just
Bragging about having called compilation again
You know there's
Got a ton of freshmen
Material
And
This is what you
Galaxy brain
You know sometimes we can
You talk about him having a repetitive show and all that stuff but on a show like this where what is repetitive
Is so f******
Disgusting
Vomit right around an hour
That's the way we do it till so everybody survived
We were going to check in on this on our Wednesday episode and so I felt like we had kind of a need to do that
And it is kind of repetitive and kind of tri-tip
Can meaningless
But at the same time there is like
A couple things that I think
We're definitely like relevant like the fact that he is reporting on a 2017
Story about an Oklahoma bombing suspect
Thinking it's about
This present situation
That is so revealing of his
Obstinately thinking it's about the present situation in defiance of all available now
How there used to be order
Pushing of great replacement ideas wow covering this story
And then the other thing is like a glimpse into the mentality of his audience
It's through these collars
And I think
There is a
A troubling view here
I mean the words Beyond Redemption come to mind
Just scary to
Tooth like
Think of
People just
Legitimately thinking there's
Everybody's banking
Control
And she that lady's married
Her husband is I don't even know what's going on there
I don't know how you could stay
Somebody
It's like
You need to write an email to the president right now too
Stop
MK Ultra
I mean I guess I would just probably say like
Sure what do you want for dinner
Well I do your makeup look
I think
Have a certain point you're going to be in the situation with your partner
Relationship
The difficult
Sometimes
You believe in reality I don't we'll meet in the middle who do reality
Blaze one last clip
And the caller
Supposedly wants
To talk about farming
Shut up
Farming is a solution
Party brother
Welcome
Brother
Get in the military on board
I feel like
People
Follow Jocko willink
Mike Glover
A lot of people like that and he's come
Now like to see him on board and I like this
They need to say
Joe Rogan
Eddie Bravo think that
But I want to see something
Get on board
Well there's a big article by Paul Joseph Watson live right now
Dot-com with
5 airplanes
Across the city
At 25000 ft Alex Jones was right
Yeah he got the message
Message on that
Really understood what that caller was talking about her
I think is Brian
Like military airplane airplanes
Moving on Degrees of Separation
From Eddie topic
But again I didn't hate this recognition and the part of the collar of the with a
See if the Alex Jones was right meme
Being able to
Spread and sort of
Trick people into thinking
About things
You know I mean
I don't want to be that guy
Who says
Military coup
Historically
Not going well
What I'm going to be is the guy who says
You can look at
Current
Military coups happening at various stages of happening
And have happened watch them in real-time like we haven't been dead time machine
Where you can watch this coup happened
Myanmar is a little bit further on and they're cool
All of this s*** is going on
But people here like listen
You got to get the military ball but none of these coups have someone
Like Alex involved who's a prophet
None of them are led by a psychic
I would like to see Alex on a horse with like a military helping
That would be fine
Give me on a horse
Back when the elites were benevolent people ride horses
Get that far away through through
Yeah I guess a little bit of a shorter episode a little bit
Knox
Immediate maybe as I would like but but Alex
Dad brings
Filler I don't have a whole lot to work with
Dinner
People love our longer episodes enjoy longer episodes
And in certain circumstances I think
That we went by which I mean you have done an excellent job of
Keeping certain episodes
Mercifully short
Well thank you all going I have a hunch
Because a good possibility that our Monday episode might be wrong
We'll make up for it see what happens
Anyway, I will be back
Jordan but until then
Play website
Almost
But dull then I'm Neo I'm Leo dcx dark I hope you all have a wonderful dreamy creamy summer
The sex robot
Alex
Kristen color