Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge B I'm sick of them
MoneyGram
Dot-com
Everybody come back to knowledge
All Jordans
Empathy altruism
Alex Jones
Indeed we are Dan
Jordan
Damn
Quick question
Emporia what's up
What you bright spot
By Bryce Potts Jordan is
Recording
With no shoes on
There is a situation we have here is that
Other than the time that you were overseas
On one of your many vacations is the first time we've we've recorded
Not in the same place
I like
To put on you know
Professional pants
Put on socks and shoes
Professional
Semi-professional pants
Business casual
But it was because I didn't want to do the show
Like
Stealing like really casual
I just was doing a lot of courtesy for you it turns out.
I feel just fine
I really did put pants on for this
Professional
Seen so many of these stories were people accidentally reveal themselves so I've got
Another
Yeah absolutely sure
Yeah that's that's a reasonable concern but I do. So that's a concern is is is
Is limited streaming broadcasting bestow such a mother
Places out of abundance
Caution
Do you want to get into that at all
Oh yeah I mean my my partner is ill
Are we taking between us for covid
But all-in-all is come back negative
So we're pretty sure it's just that regular old flu
From
From the flute
Who knows do you know you never know it could
Could be an invisible super strength
It's like that
Kind of Bankers Life
Right at this point you don't know
Sure
It's okay we're recording in separate locations out of that tub that a bunch
The caution and because of that we
Yo I think we've teased that we're going to have like a muscle fiber episode on Monday
Spoiler alert that's because there's a deposition episode coming up
You know what
Has the potential to be super long
That over over a zoo
So that will have to be to require our best you know and I think we do our best
That's whenever we're we're right in there
So what's your bright spot
My bright spot Dan is a couple weeks after my birthday late
Do you know what that means
Another tennis based right spot
The first year is
I think it's the first year in probably 30
Team that Rafa is not the
The favorite to win the French Open
Sacre bleu
15 years
Sir
Ronnie got a French
Who is the favorite
I would say
Djokovic has the favorite just because he's older and he's done it more but how come get us kicked out of the country
I mean at well yeah that's the reason he didn't win the Australian
So I would say that alcaraz
Playing the best tennis right now he's 90
18 years old
He's gone from 82 number six in the world
Three months
The man is
Incredible
Man I mean that in the loosest sense
The word because he is
Is a child
I like that that show that Sam Neill show alcaraz
I'm sorry
It was a show called Alcatraz I got to go
No that's right that about the recording did not break
Nope
Very very well forgotten TV show Alcatraz star in
I think I left
I think it was a male
Put on the back-burner I was
Put him in timeout because
Reggae sucks
Not a fun time after the last week's coverage of the Buffalo shooting
I felt like the Alex Jones was right stuff about that was just getting to be a little bit obnoxious
So the deposition was for us to go into
Play nice
Sure and that I hit was
Instead
2003's always there why not
The present date
Called me back
Again good necessitated that II
I show back up
And so today we're going to be going over dumpster you couldn't
Stay away you just had to go get a closer look
Yeah he's burning
Yep that is correct
I am so today we'll check out this this flaming
Trash can that is Friday the 20th of May 2020
I meant to say hello
So first
With the earliest episodes because Danny literally optimism is adorable
Next
The toy boat toy boat toy boat
Mix me up
Trying to trying to screw me up with these tongue twisters
That was a tongue twister I legit was like I must be a reference
It's just that I've never seen before
Fins to the right not the only one
Very much
New rule no more Jimmy Buffett rapper
Differences in the in the policy wonk shoutout
Text booba the only person in Senegal who's ever heard of Alex
At 6 false Flags once Great America thank you so much you are not a policy wonk
I like that one
Next
Thank you very much
Thank you
Jordan
Can we come
To the beginning
Ivar episode
And
Here here's the deal
That's really why we have to stay in the Press
Really really
There's a drastically drastically big news of foot
And this is how Alex begin to show here on Friday
20th
L is 20
We are going to break
Here today
Starting now
The biggest
28-year
We saw this coming months ago
Archivist
The warning
But now it's
The biggest news of Alex's career
What's happened
It happened
Yeah
But I mean like all of it or just some
I feel like we here periodically about the biggest news of Alex's career I feel like rice
Take a note
Quality
Rolling down our windows
In traffic is that how
You will later be employed to call people and tell them to knit I don't know if it's the point of stop
Stopping traffic by
It's probably it's probably fairly close
See here's the thing man via the news that Alex has to cover biggest of his career absolutely
Without a doubt
He's so big that like he just
Get to it
Kick it do it
This is so big
Then if you just mention it or talk about it
It doesn't do it justice and until the best way to start with this is this way
If you remember
4 years ago
We said the un's going to release some
Bioweapon
Confound
Change the whole world blow up
System
Gutter systems
So this is really
Around the corner regularly for the past 20 years
He definitely could find some clips of him saying something like that from 2019 and said that
2008 or any other
Honestly kind of thought we were still doing it 2003
Episode I feel like I could have
We'll get a little bit later
Shut up about what he predicted in order to make himself seem more accurate
He wasn't talking about mRNA vaccines until right up to the point where the right-wing blogs
Started to get upset
About vaccines
This is part of the reason that Meme is so Insidious
If you've bought into the Alex Jones Is Right game that you might be far more willing to hear Alex make stuff
Except
Once you believe that Alex has been right more about the staff than you think
You subordinate your own instincts and critical-thinking to Alex's imaginary expertise
Dangerous
Believing that Alex knew what mRNA before it was on a conservative blog is just absurd
He's a b b nonsense
The reason that Alex is starting off covering the story by rambling b******* about how he's been so right
Parents is because
It's a less
Openly desperate way for him to beg the audience to believe what he's about to tell
It's essentially like you got to take me seriously it because don't you remember how right I've been about everything I've actually been wrong about
Listen straight up
I am going to warn you by telling you how right I've always been how wrong I'm about to
To be right in your face
It's going to be loud
So we have we have some dangerous World developments
Upon us that Alex is going to get into before he gets into the most import
News of his career but I guess this kind of actually isn't.
Let's move into a
On the 23rd to the 28th
Switzerland
In Geneva
Economic Forum will direct them
Play the clipse
Military operation
World government
Putting the control of a major Western military
Forced lockdown
It'll make the last one look like
Gas
Like
Australia
Who's the whole load of b*******
Which which corporations owned the UN
What did Biden say
Yeah it's it's it's a lot of made-up fun stuff from
Conspiracy blogs and what-have-you
Give me upcoming World Health assembly meeting is happening in the in the actually believe it starts today
But he'll go to the gym and sit cross-legged in
There's a there's a group of kids in action or whatever who do a song song A Summer
70000 stop smoking
Plant discussion of the international Health regulations
And there's a name of improving International responses to Future pandemics
That's basically the kernel of Truth
That's behind all this b*******
Talking about traces back to spread about the amendment
The could be added to these regulation
Some of the amendments in these blogs to do with article 12
It's actually real
This proposed amendment would the director-general of the WHIO determines a health emergency
Previously the director General ABC active
Emergency before the World Health Organization
Did make a determination
Now
Now the state party is not required to agree that there's a health emerge
Okay
The impetus of this amendment is really obvious
There's a concern that in the early days of covid
The Chinese government may not have been perfectly transparent about the situation and whether or not that
Material impact
Responded
It raises important
If there's a public health emergency that could affect other countries and possibly the entire world
What do you do if you have reason to suspect that a country isn't being forthcoming about the
Situation or not giving information
And data to do the rest of the world
Decisions on
This amendment seeks to address
Termination before they make it
This has nothing to do you enter the World Health Organization Ableton able to
Take over
All the West Military then put people into a lock
This is ridiculous
I do appreciate how
Powerful the UN is
Is in the conservator
Remind
It's so
So powerful un would actually be able to
Go to go into China and look at their enemies
Without guidance
Consent
MB International Health regulations even if you read them
Specifically say that a state is able to
Agree with
Reply or not comply with World Health organization's recommendation
So that doesn't
Do anything
Just a load of s***
Amendment that they're really mad about is the one where you have
2 quarter in
Can feed Soldier
That's the crazy
Listen to your home
Pandemic soldiers no less doctors nurses
You must quarter everyone
Alex
Believe that they've been broadcasting this stuff that there's going to be another pandemic
Spoiler alert all this is about monkey
Alex is visiting like
Yeah they said all this in advance in order to
In order to let you know that it's going to happen
Because they're like villain
In comic books
Because Alex believes that the world
Old is basically a children's cartoon
Criminals always
And should be confident to their criminal armies
Supervillain cartoon owl
The villain always monologues
Villains do
Old dramatic tension
That's that's what they dramatic tension
It's also an element of the plot be difficult to do any other way
That mean many people use
Is those 4S
Position because as viewers were aware of a lot of stuff
The characters art
Answer the bad guy telling the hero what their plan is it kind of serves to as a shortcut
Get them up to speed on the same page
To the film
It's
Not something that is from
Criminology
It's pretty much like a The Village
Did you give a good quick
Chick-fil-A and you know like I listen
Show the audience all of this stuff I'll get
Real quick
I know
You know old man you killed me
You know everything now as the hero of the films are able to respond appropriately and know what the
The delays have you entered the Final Act
So stupid real-life criminology
That's what these people do
Yeah
Alex's imaginary enemies do this stuff in advance
Because I have to according to Intergalactic laws
You don't choose to fight back against that you're basically accepting and consent
Alexensual forgotten that storyline
Also he seems to have forgotten the whole race war lockdowns thing and Boots
Musli back to pandemic lockdown
I wonder I wonder why
Oh my God nothing on this show means anything at all it's freaking frustrating
I mean it sweeps
You know so you got to get rid of all of those meat
Cute storylines
Then you got to get back
Back to the main storyline
And make sure everybody's ready to find out who shot Jr
That is essentially what Infowars is
It's almost like Alex was desperately grabbing at straws at anything he could do to deflect
Attention away from the reality of the story of the Buffalo shooting
And now that it's kind of blown over at least
Appointment
She's worried about the conversation
He can move on to other things and pretend that all that s***
You never really said that race an hour lockdown we're right around the corner
Globalist
Call the same time
Acting as though
News like
Completely reasonable thing
Do you say at the
What time
Now that that's
Let's blow it over
It's just a bit
Just never happened
No
I don't know
There's a solecism
About Alex's information that like
It's not immediately here at s*** isn't real
It's annoying
Doesn't say
Didn't have to tell you what's going on because of
Contract with God and all well that's
Yeah that's the intergalactic law part
Literally in
Intergalactic
Cannot
Just spiritual
Gotcha
Also one of the
It's to the international Health regulation is that the director-general
Fancy Nancy head of state don't all have
Out-of-the-loop for health emergencies
In the future
Azazel reading that part of the
Beelzebub
Old Scratch
Bank of America under a whole bunch
The different name
So like I mentioned this obviously
Listen store showing off and has a
Vega weariness of the world would have been able to tell
Already that this is about money
Monkeypox
But we go Alex finally lays it out that this is about monkeypox
Okay let me know
Today
Don't understand ours last night
Documents
Angrily people anymore
Sell my soul is
Because
Smallpox in monkeypod
Hoarders monkeypox
Vaccine
And then magically right on time
Monkeypox pops up
So monkeypox wasn't part of Alex a s*** about Gates until exactly this moment
Although Alex did obsess over gates very normal warnings
Would be the last Public Health crisis we would face
Alex is saying like
Oh yes
Smallpox and monkeypox about smallpox
Where Bill Gates in passing reference
Like people doing
I've sort of exercises to think about like what would we do
If terrorists released smallpox
Sure
If he's been like a ha
That was Gates is playing at Elsa wedding sets
Come on man
Is epoxy
Does the fox okay
Dog box
Big-box doesn't matter of fox
There's a lot going on here cuz I'm going to try and break this down a little bit bit by bit and the first thing I should point out is that listeners
Show maybe a bit more familiar with monkeypox than the general population
That's because Alex already did this whole thing back in 2000
So this is a little bit this is another witchy thing that is
Harry Potter
That is so funny the kind of thought that eats
If he really went back to our 2003 episodes
Certified sub clips
Beads
Serious about love
If you was using the
The cases of monkeypox that were identified as
Axiom
In 2003 he's just doing it again
20 years on
Yeah he doesn't have many tricks
The present-day Alex's intentionally mixing up cause and effect in order to create the appearance of conspiracy
He's claiming it by north of these monkey pox vaccines of ventilator monkeypox cases popped up
By presenting things like this is very explicitly trying
To tell his audience
That the order for vaccines with me because of foreknowledge of the coming monkeypox
Cases
This is important because it's Ally use as the foundation upon to build
His argument that the whole thing was a false flag
Despite the fact that even if it was
The case that he ordered it before again it is
The very smart move
To have vaccine
Caesar
Yeah
But
Like
If you had just out of the blue randomly ordered these these Monk
Monkey pox vaccines
It would seem a little bit more suspicious
But in the real world
The US government ordered 119 billion dollars worth of the vaccine
Which is good for smallpox and monkeypox
Case was confirmed in Massachusetts
The first in the US during this outbreak
Order was made it wasn't
Well in advance haha
We know it by humming
Let's get ready
We thought
119 billion dollars worth of this vaccine is not like
It's not enough for even probably the entirety of Massachusetts
Honestly it's not like we're not going to be able to inoculate the entire country based on this
It's a sparrow
Amount of Reserve that you would have
Cases pop up
Insert
Various locales
Basically like what they didn't 2003
Right right right no I mean it's it's so hard to
Understand
N-Scale anymore
You know like
119 million dollars is so much
Money
But then again you remind yourself interview
Scale
That's like
America
Can government
Like
Peeing just a little bit in your mouth
This is close
You know it's not
It's millions of doses
But it's in the low millions of doses
About like what you would expect
Ed McKay's
That you might see cases and
Healthcare workers that might be in contact with people or if you can identify clusters
You know if there is there is a utility to this but it's not like
It's not like operation Warp
Speedway
Billions of dollars
It would be at 8
You cannot
Appropriately react to
Possible disease
I know it doesn't feel like
Great we saw it with
Monkeypox in 2003
Ebola under Obama
This is not
Impossible
Pretty different covid inasmuch as like it's a known quantity and there are some therapeutic
Obviously
This is not an analogous situation
The first case in this outbreak was reported to the World Health Organization on May 7th
From the UK who travel to Nigeria
Has been 92 laboratory confirmed cases and 12 countries where monkeypox is not in
This is a big deal and as much as any novel spreading of a disease is a big deal but
It's not time for Mike Adams
Come back into clear that it's over
Humanity
Based on the way Alex's
Going about this
It's really hard to say for sure how this is going to progress but I tend to agree with the World Health organization's assessment that its height
There will be more cases
But I also feel like it would be Hasty to jump to the conclusion that this is going to be any kind of large-scale pandemic all over it
Like I said in 2003 there were 71 reported cases in 6 US states
And through proper tracing practices and targeted vaccine deployment the outbreak didn't spread
This is something to be aware of and obviously people should be
Be careful as best they can but the type of typing and fear-mongering Alex's engaged
Is deeply irresponsible
It is again
When he did this with the
The other pandemic pasta
Diseases in the
The past
Responded to those appropriately
So his
Is b******* didn't
Cause any further harm
When we respond to an inappropriately
His disease
Spreads out of
Control almost
In concert with
Yep
One of the things that's fine about this this turn of events
This these cases being identified of monkeypox
Is it alive
Play games with
Covid conspiracy
I feel like
The gate like the
The songs that he was playing about covid vaccines and stuff we're getting a little bit tired
Jazz improvisation for him
The Jukebox is getting old
Diners from the 1950
Cuz you got to update this s*** and update he does
A Europe
Where you at
Gentleman
Because what is AstraZeneca in jnj
The Genome of a chimpanzee
I'm sorry what
And then hold on
Flash
Preparing
Smallpox
Box
Then the FBI
Storage facility
Find smallpox in refrigerator
They're just putting that out there
Crashes in Pennsylvania
Top Donuts
James Bond
Global trading
Control
All
Here it's happening
It all makes sense
I mean it's all coming together finally
Desperate for a way to attack the covid vaccine mRNA and sickness
I don't know man I think
The
The notion that the covid vaccines
Give you monkeypox has a
I've not heard that one outage
Quite a bit of his show and this is not something that I
I've learned to be afraid of
Yeah that's a big swing
Whatever is happening in the news just kind of gets to the history
I don't know about that
Petrol midi-chlorian backstory retcon
Kind of situation
I find it more sensitive
Because
You know at least
That was just disappoint
This is the real world
Also this is 100%
A Cowboy Bebop episode
These
The eco-terrorists break-in and they have a virus
That they're going to unleash upon planet
Edit Progressive you evolution
Into a monkey and the way he
Described it
Injected you with monkey cells and having them reprogram your body
Missus missus Monk
This is East turning people into monkey well well I would
Say that it's important to remember that Cowboy Bebop
Dinner
That is true that is true
So that story about smallpox being found in a freezer was kind of a hoax
In mid-november 2021 there were a bunch of headlines about vials being found in a lab in Pennsylvania that were late
Smallpox
Idiots like Alex adjust report on headlines read the story at face value and they weren't listening when the CDC announce the date
Cast of the vile
The cause of smallpox
The vials have been labeled this way because they contained eximia which is the best
The virus that used in the creation of the smallpox virus
But it doesn't give you smallpox
It was poorly labeled files.
It wasn't like
Darryl was
Tested
And found to be positive for being hilarious
Gloves that day okay
That much of a hoax but it's
You know like they didn't correct themselves and didn't
Take the take the
The update seriously
I think that's fair to call it
Somewhat of a hoax
You know it
It's hard not to see
That's that Rogan clip where he's liking all this is too good for me not
How to use and then you see that behavior echoed in the main
Stream media bore off
And then you would like
Well I I don't know cuz I think mode a lot of those articles will include updates or they'll like
Behavior you see with Blake's
But he just doesn't
Yeah
Don't get me wrong there's a big difference
It's also Alex's budget details about the monkeys that escaped from that crash earlier this year
Research monkeys but they didn't all have much
Monkeypox Alex is making that off
Macaque monkeys wichard actually not known to be very susceptible to monkey
Baked ham
It's kind of rare compared to other
Species of monkey
Okay so now you're scaring me because that suggests that we're all going to get monkeypox in these
Macaque monkey
Will take over after we're gone
Not that's not going to happen
Only four animals escaped from the trucks and by the next morning
The last one that is
On the Run
They hadn't been absorbed by Caesar yet at 8 have enjoyed his
Gag
That documentary is pretty good though I did see the second
Monkeypox
She did get sick after getting his stat by one of the Monkees
Is when she came in contact with its saliva
She walked up to the box that it was it wasn't one of the one right
Jurassic Park Style
Yeah she got treated for rabies preemptively and she did come some mild nonspecific symptoms
He also was at a birthday party tonight before where a bunch of people ended up testing positive for covid so there's a lot of
She came to have whatever symptoms she had
I don't know
Alright
Questions
I was just throwing shade at the wall gear connect on connected dots in order to make
Truly bizarre conspiracy theory
Is AstraZeneca in the J&J vaccine cause monkeypox so many more cases than we are and
They wouldn't have just happened
The people have taken that shot in
Like it's a new shot in the grand scheme of things but it's not like
It just rolled out last month or whatever 2 months ago
Yeah I think he's relying heavily on his audience not to stop and think waiting
Haven't
Millions upon millions of people receive this vaccine already
Are they all monkeypox
I feel I feel like
That is a problem
It's just like it's about like
Trying to get these amendments to the international Health regulations
But we should be in favor of because
Juno
Countries like China may or may not withheld information that could have been useful
Labradorite tote so once again I for I forgot that this is all in service
Of the UN
Eventually being able to during
The next possible
Pandemics going double
Check to see if
China is lying
Something like that
So they're giving people smallpox
I guess
Directions
Savable
DNA
Is what causes
Smallpox
They're injecting people
Where the damn smallpox
Knowing it would cost Mall box
Alright man
It's wild that this is just coming up now like I thought the whole thing with the covid-19 was a gay people like Mario Kart
Titus or whatever smallpox which is
Escalation
They put the Monkey jeans inside of you Dad
Because the AstraZeneca vaccine uses overconfident replication deficient
Adenovirus Vector in order to
To deliver the vaccine
He saw chimpanzee and then decided to run with it.
The adenovirus is not the virus that causes smallpox that would be variola which isn't even used in the small
Pox vaccine
Why would you do that
Right that'll be about idea adenoviruses basically caused
Colts
They also uses inedita virus but it's a human strain
Type 26
Monkey DNA
It's a virus.
Generally effects monkeys
Right
Richard Madden
Like that's the level of connection Alex is making in order to be like
It's pathetic are also just like
Really
Really dangerous metallic
Yeah I I do think he does
Understand I think it's hard to
Keep this in your mind
Do you know it's like
And if you have a virus that
Causes monkeypox
Monkey part is
Cuz the virus can evolve outside
Virus exist without monkey
Can be anywhere
If it wants to be
I mean I don't know if it has
Maybe maybe maybe that's
Hard for you to keep in your mind because you got the vaccine they do our part month
Okay now
Close enough
Genetically
That all of our vaccines were more lizard based and I got regenerative powers on top
I want that
Bill Gates is working on that
High hopes
Because as we know they'll often times the devil is depicted as sort of
Lizard
Then out but isn't he using it to give himself regenerative properties and then leave the
Planet and that's probably how he's going to be able to breathe and see
Space that ass
Castle yeah
Emeryville leave us all live monkeys
Probably be happier God this is just
I understand
To be fair this situation with monkeypox is something that is not
To be taken like
Superlite
Officials tracing
The case isn't
They're on the case
What Alex is doing
Is laughable and
Just
Pathetic
Right
And what's important is that the rest
Conservative media is
Is not using a monkeypox fear to bring
Fascism
Plague basically
According to Alex
But if you just
Call your friends or family
Uno
What is a birthday
Begun
Monkey paw
J&J
It is
Going
What really obvious even responded
Please connect me to the
Evil villains is going to watch a smallpox outbreak in order to possibly win a few seats in the
It's so f****** stupid
About whether or not
GOP takes back the Senate
Listen we need two more senators and that means roughly several million people got to die that's just
Politics work
Release that has like
Possibility of getting so out of control that it it
Kills everybody
The elites
That are behind this plan so dumb
Stupid
It's not a general election
So like
All of Spain gets monkey
Fox because they got a Wyndham Midtown
We got to keep Laura Loomer out of Congress
Just ridiculous
It's interesting that Alex brings up how you didn't hear much out of China in the early days of
The amendment to the World Health Organization regulations that he's demonizing is actually designed to make sure the future outbreaks
Don't have that same dynamic
But I don't think he would
Probably I mean that you can't have
Un soldiers just going anywhere that they want to
Do you know cuz there's so many fun
Un soldiers
Stegall around
Somebody
Except some Bill Gates clips
Let's help him prove his point
And
Helpful
He also said other programs
Wood
Call Chevrolet
Smallpox Armonk
NBC
Weird are the clips
The team most explicitly in line with the b******* Alex's saying aren't the ones he plays
But we're David Dynamic always seems to be present tells the audience about those ones and then plays other Calypso don't really
Make the points in each of them to
That's weird almost
Like he's making s*** up
You know I mean you do it one or two times
Hey that's that happen
That's a mistake
I think when you make a call
Career out of it it might be a bit of a red flag
Izzy says Gates was threatening that the attention
That seems weird cuz this one's gotten a whole lot of attention
The actual clip
And see if you can tell where the LIE is
Here is Bill Gates
We didn't
Listen to think about
Okay what about
Nursing homes what about
Getting fat
The testing
The testing could have been ramped up
Very quickly
A few countries
Entirely like
Taiwan New Zealand Australia
And so they moved a lot fast
Will get it
This time
So yeah doodoo see why the lie was there
Bill Gates's saying we'll get attention
You specifically said at the beginning to the variable of like nursing homes in
And stuff like that
Factors that we missed
In the course of this public health response
That would get attention
In the case of a future
Public Health
Urgency
No I'm pretty sure what he was trying to say is that neck
Time in the neck
Few years when this would happen
The New York Times will finally cover the story right
Time that the
Pandemic got Salma tent
Lego Ruiz expectant CNN to get
Right that's thirsty
Brickmania
Need to get on the ball
Ridiculous
Yeah Alex seems to be
Lying about this Bill Gates clip
Yeah
And he continues to
Alex Goes a little bit more into this
Makes up some more stuff about monkeypox
When will really
Get
Alright on
Like a German train
Right on time Western world
Monkeypox
Showed up
Who
Is it Mussolini made the trains run on time
Well he famously made one
Expression about Italy
At least at least he made the trains run on time
I don't believe that Alex
Has this little ability to understand the words he's hearing like in terms of Bill Gates
Gates was because
Is easier to scare the audience that way
He knows what he's doing
Malicious liar
Relax
Do the next 10 get your attention
My bad
We got plenty of attention
Okay
Absolutely zero idea whether or not the people who have got monkeypox are vaccinated
He's making that up that they are because his new conspiracy depends on that being true but he couldn't
What state is Clemson
There's a decent chance just based on percentages
Way harder if you wants to climb through some sort of causation here
Which is definitely the trees bark enough
Yeah and isn't it also just like a 100 people
It's not a ton of people
Alright
Again a ton of people have been vaccinated with all kinds of x
There's a pretty decent chance that it is a little bit more than that
Confirmed cases as of the preparation this episode
According to
World Health Organization
Countries that have different vaccines
Proved difficult
Meredith make stick in any audience that's not Alex's audience
That's cuz
He's trained them to believe whatever dumb she says
Yeah
There's no way that you hear that
As a rational person
Not go like
Hold on
About any one of the many things you can sell many variables that you should take issue with
Alex is talking about this monkeypox
Situation
He makes a bizarre leap
Because I take it he's running out of ground
Right right right
Out of ground under his feet
To something else which is weird
Help
Madrid
Weird
Monkeypox is caused by
Still talking about hepatitis case
All diseases are caused by the covid vaccine
DirecTV has a trick he uses to distract the audience and make them think that he's proven something
But in reality he hasn't said s***
Hepatitis but the World Health Organization
The vast majority of affected
Did children did not receive covid-19 vaccinations
Also reporting on about the deputy Public Health minister in Madrid Gateway pundit
Actually
Completely wrong
The minister in question Antonio's Arrowhead actually said the opposite
Media reports linking the vaccine to hepatitis
The Spanish Health Ministry released a
Clarification because
Almost
I like if you're distant
Information
And you're just
Feelinspiffy
Hear somebody's like
Listen
This is something that's important and I don't like the media twisting our claim so they like f*** you
We're going to put those claims
Good job Jim hoft or his twin brother I don't remember who I was responsible for writing that one
Yeah it's
It's just it's it's bad work
It's bad word
Do we have dinner
I guess monkeypox fears that the covid-19
Somehow by pointing to a completely inaccurate story Lincoln covid-19
Hepatitis
But there's a condition you should know about
I mentioned earlier
Meningitis
A case study of a single person
Who got meningitis after vaccination
There's not a causal link established but I was able to find a second
Case study covering two patients which recommends this phenomenon
But doesn't say that the vaccine
Call Dad
Also all the patients that are in question made a full recovery with no residual neurological deficits
The study does nothing
The further Alex is clams and it's
Not related
Hepatitis
This is just like
Just a Max bouillabaisse
Stop everything
Deputy health
Direct
Venezuela
Said that
All broken legs
You get the shot at
Boom your left tibia
Breakthrough cast
All gone
Are two different headlines about that same meningitis case study
Stories
To study plants to study
In his list of studies he's
Girl
Does Sean
Stealing
None
Believable
This isn't a study and the article itself doesn't backup Alex's claims this is from the Australian
Government Health Website
The AstraZeneca vaccine doesn't contain animal DNA it uses an adenovirus that infects champ
But that's not the same thing
The article doesn't backup Alex's claims at all but the headline contains all the Daleks
Care what the actual article says
Alex answers the question in the headline for them
It makes both what the source Alex's using actually says
The real Amanda says that the article goes on to lay it all out is because
And he realizes in the middle of that the article concerts tips
Whenever you hear him say it goes on
He doesn't know the information he's and probably what he's about
How to read accidentally
Counter to his entire narrative
Let me tell you something
This is going to be released
Scary zalae
I'm going to this is go
Alright
You already
We have
Gdna inside
Body
A lot of it
Almost
All of it
Where monkeys
No way man
Where is that saying f****** s*** man to be fair Alex does not believe in Ewa
Solution so he probably
Probably would have disagree with you on that
Look we already know now that's the race war narratives and the race war lockdown
Sounds
You know really concerned about
Earlier
In the week
Disappeared
Because there's a
Public Health
Lockdown stuff is
Is more pressing now this is the biggest news that Alex is covered in his 28 years on air
Even though it's
Something that he is already covered
Back in 2003
And it fizzled out
Because he was lying about it
So we have no race war lockdowns but it turns out Alex is retaining some
Pieces of his coverage of the Buffalo shooting
That's what I was
Who's the top
Global famine
Armageddon
And apocalyptic user quote
Proportions all Bass
Based on the two plus year
Lockdown
Ordered them
2 years locked
Devastating
Ordered them
40 + million starve to death
The refugees are flooding the last
As far as a replacement migration operation
So
Scott darling
Wow I would hate it if they can
Kept using great
Replacement Theory I do I do appreciate
Updating at 2
Rmo
There is there's
Plan in place
Pointing to
Replacement
I mean I think
It's notable
The hateful elements of his
Is Buffalo shooting coverage
While the fear-based
Do you want the audience to engage with
Have shifted over to
The other camp
Where is he now the flavors different it it's the same food
You can't reheat it
It's just
But it's not I mean it's it's
That's just what I was.
We're we're too late in this game to be shocked by this anymore
So I'm going on in social media land over the course of
Last week or so has been that Elon Musk
Shenanigans
Oh man
That guy
Little boy
So I was going to vote Republican and then he says
America East attacks on him would intensify
And then it turned out
I'm making those tweets
Someone had reached out
About allegations that
Exposed himself to
Why do people putting some pieces together and thinking hey maybe maybe this whole thing about
Denovo
The attacks against
Servicenow
To get ahead of a story
Maybe
I just don't understand are you saying that and
Unimaginably wealthy man with absolute zero accountability
Took
Advantage of a
Defenseless woman that seems
Crazy
Is that
There are allegations and
Obviously I don't know all the ins and outs and all the details of everything but I would say that Elon musk's
Behavior is
Not come off
Great
It seems like the WhatsApp
Much like someone who's guilty
He is blameless
Alex has a bit of a different perspective on this and seems to think that
Elon Musk is
Totally cool and absolutely
He said
They're going to do the me to thing
Tell me this
To punish him because he says
Republican we got all
Baton
So much more what's going to happen
Biden
Elon musk's
Assertive self
Defense
Should not
This easy
And it's
Holy
Yeah no no I mean just the hole that the whole conservatives
I'd like it that's that is a smartwatch
To try and evade accountability in the
The court of public
The pain is just suddenly be like
Hey I'm right wing and they're attacking the right wing
It has nothing to do with being held accountable for my shity behavior listen up you dumb Army of
Boron
Come to my Aid
They took two second
Rich person said he's voting Republican
Do all of you need to get involved oh my God
Jesus
Christ yeah yeah it's
It's bizarre to to sort of see that
Play out as publicly and sort of
Transparently as it has
Sort of bewildered by that
Pruitt
Is
It's upsetting
I mean anytime at this place now where it's just like learning
Dumb as a concept
Learning doesn't happen anymore
People only make
Exact same
Mistake over and over and over
It's almost
Comforting now to know that people will
Fuk up
In the same way
Well I mean that's
Because our Public Health people need to take a note
This precaution
So Alex does not end up being correct
About
Alex has some guests on on this episode
The first one
Is little lawyer buddy of his
Bobby Barnes
Ralph Lauren
He also thinks that the monkeypox going to be big deal
What is your view on what's currently happening
It's pretty obvious lockdown the next big rollout
Is the smallpox
I'm predicting is going to go ahead and play out of
Smallpox hysteria now we're here with all this
Latest covid You Name It We got it where you're one
One Stop Shop
Not going to listen to a ton of barnes's interview but it should be noted that a lot of it is him talking about
He's working with Robert Kennedy Jr to do like litigation against
Got the vaccine
Stop it.
Maybe you have a little bit of a biased perspective on that
For people to donate money to that won't go anywhere
I'm only legal Griff
Good times good times
The other guest has a Duo
And it's Peter McCullough
Who's the big a back doctor
And
A guy named John Leake
Who's an author
And the 1st of this interview is that John Leake
Has written a book
About McCulloch
Call the courage to stand up for the courage to fight
Covid-19 or something like that
And here's the here's the situation
I find this to be a fairly damning
Ebook
Exist
Also
Okay interview
Because
This leaked guy
He fancies himself a true crime author
And so the perspective that he took
MBM 3.4 him in terms of covering covid-19 was as a
True crime stories
And then he involve Peter McCullough in
To help him with the
Like scientific aspects of
You have a guy who's interested in writing a book from a true-crime angle about the covid vaccine
And the main subject of his book
Is this Peter guy who's going around
Apeirogon
Tucker
Appearing on Laura Ingraham show appeared with
Joe Rogan
Grill
So if he doesn't have the perspective that this is a true crime kind of vibe
What did I do for his book
But they're working to release
Declarative
It kind of looks a little bit
Well I mean I would say that
A true
Crime writer
Put together an entire entire book
That was
Is really really well done
And then before they published it
It was proven that the person they said 100% did it 100% did
I would assume that more likely than not Belgian
Just be like
No icing
Think you're wrong
Play my book
I think
Well I mean look
Whatever is it
It's not a secondary in some ways to like
Peter McCalla
Makes you committed to a conclusion
When you have this guy
True Crime book about you
True Crime novel about not
A crime right it would look bad if you were like well you know what a Beyond over this and it turns out I died
Do I think that some of our previous assumptions that this true crime
Based on
Maybe a little bit salty I think you can't do that
Tell you something right now
You know that thing everybody's
Debunked a lot
I tried to make it true and
Can't be done
But it can in the context of a true-crime novel
Interview is
Knox
Really all that important past that just sort of Revelation that you had
There's this sort of dynamic involved
Like this guy who's supposed to be like a truth-teller about all the stuff that the media is covering up about Iver
Virmax and or whatever the f***
I Cry
Influence
Let's say
Make some of his his prospectus a little bit Quest
Cinebowl
Funny things Alex
This pickup is just great cuz I think it's Alex
Himself into being like
Yeah I can say I've read your books
I wasn't going to but I can't I think I can say that
I'm not a
Astorian
I was just like you
But just powerful
Call Jean
Cuz I like
Stop.
Park in Southend
I am willing to take a stab at it and I don't think you're going to correct me
I took a look at it and I realize you're not going to
Oh yeah which one did you like the most exactly exactly I'm going to tell you that you're one of the top writer
True Crime and you're not going to
Come in with false modesty
Ever let it fly
So dumb
Aurora transact
So you're good
You pretend I've read your s*** we
Move on
And it's that guy
Be the writer here talking to Alex about the way that we counter
The propaganda that's going on in the mainstream media about
Health
Exist
I imagine it has something to do with watching more Infowars and read more of his book
Wow I wonder if that's the case
I mean I think it starts with being aware that you're swimming in this sea is prompt
Buganda I mean
And that you know this may seem like normal CB
The messaging is
But once you realize
A normal is being created when you turn on the television
Quit
Quit accepting that that
Television is an
Accurate representation of reality
You need to start listening
Weed
I I counter that I I protest today
I cannot live in a world where Alex actually does not mean to lie
Cuz the level of the mistakes
The level of things that he gets wrong
Constantly
In the exact same direction
I think you're
Standing the way that he's using words as you said
You said how does he
You can't possibly not mean to lie
My friend he means to lie
He is just not
Trying
He is succeeding
Okay that's how you got to think of ways
July
I'm kicking ass
Murdering like I'm like
One of the top Liars there's ever been
Yeah I guess I guess if you look at it that way you might you might have some wiggle room where he can get away with us
Yeah but you were at your prediction to watch more infosource
Right on red
I mean look we tweak we come to the end
Of this
I wanted to have a longer episode because about an hour and it's you know that's unsatisfying
Maybe a normal length
For some other shows but for us it feels like
Annapolis boot
Family and it's almost like we're here we might as well beat a
A day off if we're only do it an hour and
Yeah it's it's
Unfortunate
Be you know the circumstances of Zeno trying to be overly careful and
You know you're taking care of your your partner
Well I didn't know if we're going to have a big
It's a little ungratifying
I will guarantee
Sneaky Snake
And I also think that we needed this
Because
Stop.
That
No it merits talkin about
But at the end of the day
There's not really that much else to say outside of what you can cover in about an hour
So there's that
I mean Rodger Stone did say that
The North Korean ship tin monkey
Tupac's along
Song with the ballot
It's in Maine so that's why it took
So long
To get the rest of them
Box out to the the country
To get to me
I would put out a compilation of the times that he predicted monkeypox
Videos from 2003
Exactly that would be great that would be great it's something like that is.
We'll be back on our next episode
And we will be in person and dig more
Into something
Pontiac website
We do it's outside. Com
World on Twitter
We aren't artists at knowledge underscore but until then
I hope you all have a dream
Creamy summer
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work