Damn important swetik
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Freight
College vype.com
What about Alex Jones
We talked about this a little bit but I have not mentioned it on the show now
Ever giving you an update on it
So about maybe
Couple weeks ago I was having a frozen pizza and I was putting crushed red pepper on
Myself this is good
Ride could be better
Yeah I wonder if
Other crushed peppers exist like I wonder if you can get a Shaker of habanero flight
And they're great
It really is a solution to the problem that red pepper flakes have which is like this is good but not quite
You can you can plus it you can turn it up turn anything into flakes
Trinidad scorpion is not open these up yet to try but I can't handle being
Bird my I don't know if I could eat those dry
I've got a probably good but it wouldn't be I wouldn't be worth it
Discount bottom like yeah break into this little bit later today but
Maybe that's evolved its updated soon
Is going to be the first episode of this thing that I'm doing I was going to call it a show
But it's not on Fridays at 6 p.m. to 8 p.m.
The Magicians on episode
With a friend
On Twitch and I hope people join us and then we're going to talk about mental illness you know you can
Can't play the show on Twitch right you're going to run into a number of
Terms of service that you may be unaware of problems
Figure it out as I go along okay
Final Fantasy 7 for no reason in a month
But anyways I'm excited to do it will be fun I think we're going to be back to social distancing soon so this will be a great way
Wait at me like we're not going in the right direction I heard some bad news about Chicago
So Jordan speaking of bad news for Chicago The Boys Are Back in Town
The city as bad news covid wise we had good news and they
We're back in studio together and it's good news and and The Boys Are Back in Town
The deposition boys
By popular demand
So
Come on
Like Charlie Sheen and Emilio Estevez their brothers right Harley Sheen
Charlie Sheen you said she
I just don't talk right
The predictable outside of our show being successful
Popular things that we do is we talked about depositions and the World of Alex Jones
I'm and today we have a couple of depositions to go over they
I have to do with Infowars and Free Speech systems having a
Another chance that having a corporate representative
These are two depositions that they're their Hired Gun positions
Marcel Fontaine
And so yeah it
I don't want to give it away but
Yeah this is this
Nuts over to World 45 at least
Three if you just talk about the stuff that has to do with this phase of the trial rights cuz that just has diarrhea
Yeah and then
Well actually
And you're probably leave
First Jordans
First I have a cat named bubbles cousin cousins
Start a club thank you so much
Could you very much from Bloomfield who was tricked into that Gillette commercial
Will that one time
You're not a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk Canada is pronounced a little draaaake
Jimmy Brooks
Max pinch my nipple and call me a policy wonk
Piceance think is what you're now about as long I'm a policy wonk
Obviously that was the pinch had like astric
Figured that was the totals for that well I could feel you pulling as you pintus it was heartfelt
Inspiration was that the person who sent that name princess stood by saying I'm embarrassed to be
Using the English on it
The other angry sweaty fat guy
Very much so
Adventures in Hell World podcast is doing this weekend
Is I'll be better tomorrow
You're now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk I have risen above
Miami star
Go take a little break you down
A little break e for me
And then we're going to come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order and
She wrote in on and all your s***
Broadcast
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again I apologize to the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow. Joke's on you
Tomorrow or not one good turn deserves another
So
We Will We Will delve into these deposition Waters but I would like to tease you
View with an out-of-context drop care
Supervise
Pacific Apartments
Supervisor
I don't know who they
That's troubling
Part of the things you should know
That's upsetting are they supervisors
Two bees in watching the news that there's a little things that I'm learning about the experience of being in a room with a lawyer
You don't really want to hear
One of them is that's troubling
It means the conversation that you're having is off the rails
Is like
Somebody lawyer
Is asking you a question
And then they say thank you after your answer not good take it back not good
Whatever it is that you're just said I take it that means they got what they wanted
I never knew to be afraid of that but now now holyshit
So on February 14th and 15th representative for free speech system set for deposition
Marcel Fontaine case respectively
Having made embarrassing fumbles with Rob do and Daria karpova and haven't been sanctioned for how ill-prepared
Fulfill their job
The company had contracted somebody from the outside of the team to take on the job
That person was Brittany Paz a lawyer who's worked with Norm Pattinson the past
Nearly impossible task in front of her getting up to speed on the topics that you was expected to be able
Disgust
But at the end of the day accept the job
It was impossible dollars for it and became responsible for being a cop
Appleton corporate representative
That's what you took on her player
She could have not done that given the impossible nature of the job he's a professional sheet
Brought in like a jstor
Cut out of what a false-flag is
Oh oh yes yeah that would have been funny at the level
For a false flag
Look down upon the printing out of Wikipedia articles and similar Behavior
After that disaster that was darya's deposition
I dealt with just about enough b*******
Free Speech systems one last chance to provide a corporate representative specific guidelines
X about what this person was expected to do to prepare
So there were to be no confusion when they sat down at this deposition chair what you are expected
And the judge was laying out these are the minimum requirements
This really was an act of generosity on the part of the Court
This is the judge from that hearing
I think where I'm struggling is actually I actually believe we're most likely to end up in a situation where
Where I'm going to be telling the jury we gave the defendants all these opportunities to answer these questions and you may decide
Hide from the answers they gave or did not give
Have they answered those answers would hurt their case
Or some language to that effect
I just don't know that we're there today on these issues after one shameful corporate rep
Damages
That's so you know I would really like to have one corporate deposition where the witness actually prefer
Ayers exactly what bill was
Where we could have just been right there being like body body no no no no no
You can lower this limbo bar to the ground man they are digging below it
I think it's a
Good thing I don't think that the court is being like
Well you know maybe we'll give him a chance and they'll comply this time it's more like
Alright
You're probably going to f*** this up
Let's be super clear by what you need to do give you one
If you can't comply then understand I understand we're just at the stage where you can no longer take
Take these events as individual events and they must be taken in totality and if you've already failed at 16
Different attached
Get out
But what you going to do
So after that point in this in this hearing the judge goes on to delineate what preparing for these top
Topix actually means we're going to periodically refer back to this as we go through Miss past deposition
And I assume that's because she Nails it every time. That's correct.
Your case is being conducted by Mark Bankston
Naturally these are long videos and a lot of information in them Dells into areas that we've been over before
I'm going to try to trim a bit of that out and primarily focus on what we can learn from these documents
It's important to remember how much Alex wines on his show but not being allowed a chance to defend himself because
This exists as definitive evidence that he's full of s***
He had already sent Daria to testify as a corporate rep and she showed up with printed out Wikipedia articles
No idea about the subject you were supposed to discuss
And she ended up kind of supporting Sandy Hook conspiracy theories Underoath
A room with a bun dance of Grace the court is giving him another chance to actually participate
This is what we get
So
Hurrah everybody
Position from 14th February 14th covering the Sandy Hook cases
And the first thing we're going to establish here at the beginning is how long did you have
To prepare for this
And it's given the call on the way here might as well.
Stop when were you selected
I think that I was officially hired the last week and I'm sorry
Give me the last week in January first week in February
So January 31st
February 1st ish
That way cuz it's been about
When you say officially and let me backup you understand 32 designation
Filed
Designating you
The corporate representative
What's the last week
Wednesday are you aware of that
As far as an official selection
That was done well before that
I don't I wouldn't say well before that but it wasn't.
Before that if it's
By last week
Right so few weeks
Not if you wake
I've only been the corporate rapper
I think as of today is
Okay but two weeks okay yeah that makes sense you said January 31st February 1st
So
That probably was the day when everything got finalized
So this is going to be a bit important
Not because of the difference in dates between her official and unofficial selection but because of how much material she was
Exit to be conversant about
And the window of time that she had from her selection to the date of this deposition
In the hearing after darya's deposition the judge asked to Alex's Council quote
Do you know who will be designated or there'll be more than one person designated to respond to these topics
The response was quote
I will have the answer for that by the end of today and I'm relatively certain they will be more than one person
That would have been a good idea and for whatever reason Alex and Free Speech systems decided not to designate more than one per
Person they chose to leave this one person Brittany pause to be responsible for answering to all
All the questions in both these cases would honestly isn't fair
I don't have pity for Miss pause but it would also be dishonest and not recognize that her inability to do her job and he's dead
Deposition was part of an intentional choice that Alex made
If there's tens of thousands of pages of material to become familiar with
Having one person do that is an act of sabotage
Especially when the opportunity was readily available to split the workload up between multiple represent
One person with two weeks prep time is not an active cooperation that's that's no good
I am going to pay you $30,000
To try and get away with the bare minimum of what you can do
Well no because the judge is clearly said what the bare minimum is a lot of work
I'm hoping for it but at the very least I hired a lawyer this time so people will think I tried sure
I think it's more like $30,000
Get Blake
Enough to say something I like that sit there while you have the worst time of your life
Tell it you know Plaza
Room and you're going to feel like an ass whole is it 4:30 grandvale leg really feel it
I don't know I don't think I would do it
These were two all day all day like
Super uncomfortable session so I don't know
Maybe maybe are y'all ever higher price on
Being miserable for 8 hours straight memory of being in that room with Daria
Deposition for her was worse than the first one
Well we'll see
So here is them talking about this sort of dynamic about like a can't really
Do everything right but you can't look at all
To prepare for this deposition did you review every document produced in this litigation
Every single document
No I didn't have you ever
I certainly would agree that it's not possible for one person to do it
Within the time. Of the stuff
It would take multiple people
I had a purposes of this deposition if you'd like to
Go through the universe of documented I did review
To do that it's not what am I
I'm what I'm asking you is if someone wanted or if a company
Wanted to prepare itself for
The deposition by reviewing every document
Litigation one person in two weeks
One person in two weeks
And the company did not to under
Take steps to make sure that
I was the only
So already you kind of have this like being against the judge's wishes
Because the goal is to have a corporate representative who could speak on all of the matters that were relevant all of the
Discovery material that way was handed over and so
She can't
Impossible to unless you had multiple people and Alex and Infowars chose not to have
Have multiple people chose not to follow you already have basically like this
Then why can't we all just say okay then like
Alright cool we're done
Because there's so much weirdness
The just experience of him being like well you only here here's what they
The judge gave you a job this was on that you didn't do it the end
Here's here's a couple reasons why I'm glad that's not the case
One there's a lot of weird stuff we wouldn't have an episode to do
Understand
Joy these deposition episodes stood for
Second day deposition
What ends up happening I can't even begin to explain to you how bizarre
Subject matter get and how revealing it is in an accidental way that doesn't seem like
It does not seem like the oldest of the Direction This Is Right Bono perspect
Because I feel like people are going to assume that we are behind all of this because there's no other explanation
I could see where they would be coming from unfortunately or fortunately
It is coincidence
So
There is a expectation that Yoshi look over all of these materials and preparation
And it turns out that she couldn't find a certain video and it's weird because
Daria did
What is dangerous to do today
Prepare for all the videos that are
So I did try to locate all the videos that are meant
Okay were you able to do that
Not all of them
Available
Due to the teapot
I don't know that way
Have
Something cuz I got to
One of them that I know that I couldn't find was the videos
Specifically relating
Addresses
Map
The honor
The location
That was one
Were you aware that the last Corp
Gloria Cordova
She was shown the video
Or usual
In terms of preparation you don't know what
I wrote her deposition
Let me make sure I get an answer.
You think that means you know what
I don't think she did very much
I don't think you did either but I do
You think Brad reif
You know about that
I don't know what Broadway show
Shots fired
That was a good start as you're starting to win me over right out of the gate
Great to experience a moment of shared reality with somebody on that side
Looks like a little bit of frankness
Pretty pretty unexpected and rare it doesn't last I didn't think so
There's a bit of a conversation about what efforts were made to retain evidence potential
Evidence in this case
And it's it's
It's quite
Elongated getting some answers
Yeah it's here is an answer to question those particularly this is not good
Can you tell me
Can you at least tell me everything free
To preserve evidence
Tell me when they did it
Sure to my knowledge I think that there were efforts
Taken
Produce Olive
Emails at work
Turn parameters that were given
Company 2
The email
There were certain
Parameter is done
Try to
Videos
Code access
The videos
There
I believe I
Pet spider earlier that there was a
Third-party come
Company that was helping with that although I'm not
Play Blockhead probably
I think that
As far as social media goes
Thinks that the test
Previously
Has been not
That
Can be accessed
Are you do you also want to know about
The finances
The company and the
The finances or we just
Now in the
Emails
Article
Let's deal with that first answer first cuz what I hear you talking about
Is the efforts to make the search for the
And efforts made to access the
A nice sound to me like
Things that we're done
To attempt to locate documents
Production in
What I didn't hear is about any effort
Reserved
Before that
Another word you understand if I'm going to go search for doctor
Producer
It's important
That I preserve those
For that app
You understand what I'm saying
I do understand what you're saying and I don't
Don't think that there's been any
Deletion of any of that in
So I mean once they were required to be
Reduce
Through the databases
I don't have any reason to believe any of that information
Who's a really bad look right out of the gate
Yeah this section of the beginning of a deposition or Mark is trying to get information about efforts that were made by free speech
Systems to preserve evidence pertaining to the question
Here's what the judge said specifically about the responsibilities that the corporate representative would have regarding matters in
Involving preservation of evidence
Quote
If she shows up again or I'm sure we'll get a new one if new corporate representative that because that's the way it is
That person says I don't know then they will have disregarded the orders I'm making today
Your client will violated the orders that I'm making today I don't want
I don't know I'm guessing I think maybe or in4 to be a part of the answer at all
Did the answer is we destroy everything as fast as we can that I want them to come out and say that
It is their answer is we don't care where it comes from so we don't ever create a record they don't need to save
That in that way
Alex's lawyer responded with just one
Understood
Already miss pass has stepped in it and it shown that the direct orders of the judge are not being followed weather
Negligence in on like unawareness on her part or as a result of Alex's hostility to the process
Either way this is the first of the subject
They were given clear instructions on specifically what not to do
And they decided to do that exact thing so she didn't say like oh well immediately
After a hard drive contain the materials that we have decided could heard us we pour a bunch of acid on it we've burned
Down all of our servers
We've got holes in the ground where we buried things that you'll never need to know about
She just said
Really
Talk about any specific things that were done to preserve the evidence
We searched our inboxes she couldn't
I mean yeah but you don't want to just say they didn't
That's a real bummer I don't know what the stakes are for her to say that if that's the case
This fine
I work for the company
Can happen you lose your association with Norm pattis omigod I don't have that Norm anymore
Open mics I won't be able to do
Yeah it is I've been there so there's a lot of
4th and questioning about 20 she talked to from the company and such
She didn't try to get in touch with maybe a poor decision on her part
Because she was supposed to
What you did talk to Alex cuz that might have been a problem cuz I believed him.
One person that I found her answer to be very bizarre
Sorry about is curtain demo
He was a like senior writer like a managerial editor during some of the relevant
Periods for the case
And whether or not she tried to contact him
Is a super Bazaar thread that goes throughout both deposition
Here's what she says on the 1st deposition
Soperton mou understand he
Well I know who he was cuz he's no longer employed by the company but I think
Fat in
Irrelevant
Time. I believe
B18a
And prior he was
Head
Red Rider
Add info
You talked to him
I was not able to locate her
Sammy's Auto current
But I didn't
What do you mean you tried
Find out if
I just I wasn't able to reach out to him
Deposed in life
I tried to reach out to
Let's make sure I understand
Think what I said was
We can maybe need to
Is you were unable to
I don't know that I was unable to
I think that we
Tried
By phone
So if I go talk
How do you not know
I didn't
I wasn't able to
I'm not on map that's not what I'm asking you
I'm asking did you call him
Colorado
People I think
Your testimony is
You were somebody to info
Ford called him for
I know we tried
Gaviscon
Should I ask Melinda
Don't know whether
I called him a
Pickup
I know I haven't talked to her
So I'm not honestly
Information
Not you are sure you haven't talked to
I am sure I haven't talked to you not sure of his
Try to talk
I know I asked for his contact
But I'm not sure if I asked
So this is weird
It's splitting hairs in a really really strange way
Like straight-up says that you didn't contact a number of people that seen on that pile
So I'm going to jump ahead actually to the second days deposition
And see how this curtain Mo discussion goes on that day
And see if the see if you see any dissimilarity
Can't remember if you spoke with pneumonia.
I did not speak English
Any particular reason
I don't I don't know that I
Had his information of readily available
And I know that I have the time to talk to him
Lot of people did you ask for it
Thermistor nomos phone number yes I did ask Melinda for I don't know that she was able to find it
I don't I don't think I even got his number
Very weird how is I really feel like I've learned so much about deposition through all of
And just the concept of just
Like they don't even get the idea of answering a question that you can then answer with a follow-up question and
Right you know like
I think I called them and then they go well if I check his phone records did you call him
Eyevac emmymade maybe I called he could have been called in the future I don't know
Also I think
I don't want to assume what someone would not remember but you know
For 2 weeks 2 weeks it's not a very long time to try to remember what efforts have and have not been made
Hayden where things stand how many people could you possibly have called right and curtain with somebody who's like
A particularly relevant member of the Infowars team 10 he was there
To me like it wouldn't be that confusing what happened
That's why I'm confused by these answers that seem a little bit different over the to deposition
I mean I think we can assume that was important as when she initially answered the question she said I know who
Who Kurt Nemo was
So we can assume that she's murdered curtain Nemo it's I think it's them oh he's not a camera
Pilot the Nautilus
So this makes clip Perez
Troubling about
Alex's phones
Sheath rectally contradict Alex's own testimony about Alex Azar
Don't do that you believe Mister Johnson
Is produced all the text
Sandy Hook
He had in his possession
And here's the problem that is that I don't know
What
She has on a
This phone
Because
I don't know
What
What if any
Would have been on the
The phone
Time.
And the reason our only reason why I say that is
I know that he's got a new
New phones
So he doesn't have access
Yes to anything that's on
Prior phone
Uninstall the wires got burners
She wouldn't have any
For prior phone
I'm sure that
Well actually
But in any event like I said I do
I don't know when
He would have gotten a new phone
She would have access to
You read Mister Jones's November 2019
I read the March 2019 deposition I don't think I got to the
Okay cuz he missed you just testified
Something totally office
Okay
He got new phones
But they have the same sim card in a
Cloud storage
And he doesn't lose
Text messages
How many reasons
Dispute that
Oops
I guess I made that excuse up
I mean minute ago
And the reason is because the context of this is surrounding Mark having a text message
That Alex should have on his phone
That involve Sandy Hook
Yeah it was not produced
Because Elizabeth Williamson from The New York Times had reached out to mark
That she had a text exchange with Alex that included the words it was not produce
And Discovery is Leeds
To suspicion that all the texts were not necessarily turned over
Kind of
The area where she's trying to wiggle around I mean avoided
About to say was I'm sure if he could have returned over all of his text messages he would have
And then she stopped herself instead
Well I'm not sure what
It would be generous to assume that's
It's only inability that's stopping him
True that
A high-stakes gambling table
I would bet every time on Alex light
So another big chunk a big thing of what this deposition gets into in the early stages
Is
What awareness did the company have of the plaintiff
I just enjoyed this
Can you summarize for me what the company knows about Neil
Could you be more specific
No no number of times there are
Number of instances where she has to be more specific
No
I will not be more specific. Require
Suspiciously
Everything I don't know why I just got here 2 weeks ago and I find out they know everything about this guy
We have their DNA on file
Specific
Has appears to be unaware of what the company knows in specific about
Neil Haskell
Produce documents
That's what it was okay you don't know what the company may have
May not have produce
Before after the litigation
So before the litigation I don't see
Think that the company
If at all
Okay
What about after
After I am aware that there was some in
Nation about
Some
Legal issues that
Coming out of hiding
Etiquette
You mean after the lawsuit
Prior to this loss
In terms of its Sandy Hook coverage
The company ever done any research
So here we come to strike to internal this deposition ignoring the direct instructions given by the judge
From the hearing
Quote the company's knowledge of the plaintiffs
Clearly the representative who was that did not even try to determine with a company news and she had no knowledge
Documents that were provided by the company she was they represent and the discovery of in these cases
So I consider to be the minimum efforts or the corporate representative to review every document produced by the company in the
Is litigation prior to their deposition
When Daria did her deposition she had no awareness of documents that Free Speech systems had produced relating to their
Your knowledge of the plaintiff
And so is part of Alex getting another chance to provide a corporate rap
They were going to be required to review all the documents that involve the subject
This is painfully obvious from this exchange Miss pause did not do that
This is queer specifically as it relates mr. hustling because just as one example deposition
The company produced an email to David Knight sent to himself with a subject line quote Connecticut carry releases the truck
Apple passive Neil Flynn from before the lawsuit
There's also that email the David Knight sent himself with the subject line quote
Neil heslin father of Sandy Hook victims faces criminal charges which he sent to himself
One night at 3 in the morning
Before the lawsuits
We already have a concrete demonstration the two of the judges specific demands have not been respected and we are not very
Far into this thing it is just clear and it's it's
Here's the thing that bums me out right I'm a lawyer
And I'm hired by Alex Jones and I have been even slightly aware of what's going on
The first thing I would have done is read none of the documents and read all of the previous deposition
To figure out where it is I should avoid lying in tandem
Do you know what I mean like you know there's so many lies going on you got to know what lies you're trying
Find a backup you might want to read arya's for cautionary tales
But you can discount a lot of like actual factual stuff
Think with what Alex said Batman learn from the mistakes of the people who came before you
Bring everything with you I'm talking all the other positions
Do you mean like in this thing I be like hold on let's take the next
Half hour while I find this
Adorable home
So another issue is whether or not the company had knowledge about Scarlett Lewis
Another of the plaintiff
Answer there was an email that was how big harassing
Does Louis have to do with like why if you were so worried that you stopped to get coffee
You know like that that guy that kind of thing brings up the coffee
And
This is this is sort of Miss pause trying to respond
I don't I don't get the sense that she really knows what is being referred to here okay
Do you know about the Cod about Scarlett Lewis and
The coffee you understand what I mean when I talk about
Carl Lewis
I believe that I read somewhere that there was something
About
Miss Louis
Was going to
Get coffee for
Some people that were on
Alright so
That's a note that somebody gave it come
Company about Miss Lewis
Release date
I think that was in the news cycle
Who's your circle
That
Maybe it could
Email wear
How big was he
I said I don't know that I
Did you check
Did I talk about that
That's not good wow
Yeah it's pretty easy to confuse harassing emails with a new cycle you know
Yeah you know we've been through this with with Daria and oh my God we've been through this so much
30 times and each time you look at it and you see what
Two pair of sharks
Murdering what's left over of chump right
This time it's supposed to be a lawyer
It's supposed to be somebody on equal footing
She's not there as a legal practice law very very clearly for illegal
Sure and I do think that because of that she does and position a little bit better
The number of instances been someone like Dario Rob do what
But yeah it's it's it's I think it's very different for that reason that she has a familiarity with
The law and then second because she's not part of Infowars
She is an outside agent who's being like
I'm a Hired Gun here
I don't know why you would
Just be like I don't know honestly
Think it's still feels like she's trying to make stuff up in order to explain away things in a way
Play that serves no one's purposes happy because of this it's not helping him it's not helping you and it's not helping
They talked a bit about what she's being compensated
And it is a flat rate
According to her there's not like if she works extra time than she expected and she's not billing for extra
Hours
There's no implication that there's some kind of a bonus it did they could be itchy
It seems very bizarre to me
That
Cheese
Acting this I mean just scorched-earth honest that it would astonish people
That's the only way that you would do it there is literally no reason why is she would not get as familiar as you can
These subjects and that everything that she did and just be like I don't know
I have no idea I was not able to prepare on this
We're all f***** here let's do what we can do and then I mean barking Bill both
Various points Express something of the eye
I empathize with the position that you are in this is not something that anybody could do but I'm sick of this s***
Sorry I have a big energy of me on the phone with someone from
Xfinity
You know like
Yeah I'm not mad at you it could be a scarecrow sitting where you are sorry I'm coming for that f******
Scarecrow okay so sorry that you are talking to me right now cuz I hate your Phelps personally hurt
I don't even know you but guess what company sucks and I have to I have to let you know about a really tear you apart
Yeah there is a bit of that discussion comes up about Scarlett Lewis
And this is really I found this fascinating
There is a
I want to get on the record
Whether or not the company believes
These plaintiffs to be gun-control Advocates right
Because that's a lot of the justification that Alex has for treating them the way he did
Activist there in the public eye or whatever his argument is yes of course the political route
I'm so Miss Lewis has a charity
I have this exchange is truly bizarre
Do does the company Canton Ms Lewis is it going to rain
I think I miss Lewis
Operates
A non-profit
Organization
And I believe I do
Material in the
Disclosure
Discovery material
Operates
Offer
Amazon
What guns
You don't know what to do
Don't
Know what
He says it Abby
For butt
I know that there are deaf
Haitians as
What
I just want to put
You seem to be trying to insinuate
That there was a potential interpret
Miss Lewis's chair
Some way
This is that accurate
I don't know but what I'm saying is
Is she operates
Nonprofit that
Prophet has
A goal and ask
Stated
Directive
And however anyone wants
To interpret that
Is a matter of a
Canyon
But she operates a non-profit
Charity
I get that
So we have a set up here miss pause is trying to like painted like what
You know whatever to make up your own ideas of school safety
What is that about other than
Literally no way to find out what a charity spends its money on and is to
Trying to do they have they've some regulations about that recording
But you don't even have to go that far because it is next clip
Misbah has learned in real-time what this charity is about and then
Has to Pivot
Oh my God what is wrong with Andre
I'm personally am I sitting here today saying that she's a gun-control Advocate know but what I'm saying is I say
I think that
The host and writers at infowar in their opinion
Would interpret that is be
Bingo controller
Do they
Individually as individual writers and individual host I can testify as to whether
Let's just testified the new with the
Sure
Machine gun control
The company can't
I understand I'm going to trial
I need to discover what the company is or is not going to argue about
Intentions are
I think it's fair.
Benefit companies going to
Intense garlic
I get to know that
I think it is a reasonable
Interpretation
Of
Nonprofit
Central advocate
A host
Or a writer
Wanted to
Argue that from that angle
I think it's a reasonable in
Irritation
Of that
Tivity
Of the activity of her charity
Yes
Emotional
Intelligence
If that's what
Okay so first of all you have no idea
I'm not on any independent research on
So in terms of asking
What the company contends Miss Scarlett Lewis
Does with her charity
In terms of what it.
I know what she says it what does
Okay what is the company
Know that Miss Lewis says it
What she says it does is advocate
Advocate for
Safe space for children to express
Themselves
How could that be
Like I said it.
Depends on the opinion
You were the one who said it could
Tell me how
How how can
School safety Beacon
Construed as gun-control advocacy
If that's in fact what it does
You're the one who just told me that one
What I told you that is what
Company.
I don't know whether that is an actual statement
A factor might be something surreptitious
I don't know I haven't done any
Now I get it
I'm sorry I was I was having trouble because I would
Thinking that
The company's knowledge about what Miss Lewis does you were taking the suicide a word
But because the company can't verify that and has done nothing to her
You can say
Alright
Amazing weird thing to agree to at the end
This and you've done nothing to try you've decided to be suspicious
Yes yep you got it that's a company baby I think the clip does a really good job illustrate
Creating this kind of amateurish improv that Miss Paws is having to make it through the deposition
She has no idea what Miss Lewis's charity is about but she thinks it has to do with school safety in a way that you could imply that it's
Secretly about gun control
It's something that people could have different opinions on depending on your interpretation
And then after going away is down that road she learns that it's actually a charity about fostering emotional intelligence and Young
Students she's forced to stick with that premise that she's already established
I know she's left with an unfortunate and I'm comfortable decision
Either admit that you had no idea what you was talking about was making up assessments that she made earlier
Or she has to stick to her guns and implied this charity that's about teaching the core values of like kindness and forgiveness
Is secretly a gun-control front that Miss Lewis is being dishonest about right
You can hear Mark kind of laughing periodically in this and it's because of things like this feels like
Even at this point he's pretty sure this deposition is going to be productive and likely is going to lead to more sanctions
Ivy
Are the other head I feel like I could really a f****** Dale this what it just did like listen
Okay you teach kids emotional intelligence they grow up to be emotionally intelligent people
Why are they buying guns if everybody's emotionally intelligent Elgin
Nobody's buying guns I think that would be hard in a situation where you have follow-up question
If you're Alex being a demagogue
Call David I could rattle those off
What's the Second Amendment for if nobody trying to kill each other
Solutely the ultimate gun grab
A shift over to Leonard Posner and
On behalf of the company must pause
There we go
How does a company today feel
About the fact that it
Disclosing this kind of information
I think that mr. Posner is
Is an activist him anyways
I think that
Is company
Is
Engaged
Political speech
A public
Company that could
Commented on
What politic
What we mean
Etiology
Of mr. off of Honor
Sure
Company's position
Is that he's a
Engaged in
First Amendment activist
That's one of the instances where like if I heard that thank you would be like oh I just said something is
The reviews for the company's position is that he's engaged in Auntie First Amendment activity and you said thank you
I don't think that's good no I think that's probably is going to look bad
Yeah they're I mean yeah part of my goal if I was doing this would be to be played or quoted the
East in the trial
Like I want to be my name should be mentioned the fewest number of times that's my goal that your goal is to make it so
Alright maybe we'll go back to the Daria deposition
I could hear that.
There was a news report that Infowars covered
Shooting in Pakistan
And there were children who were killed and
There was a memorial that included a picture of mr. Posner son
Answer mother victims of of shootings along with pictures of the
Victims of this shooting
Evans was reported by Infowars as this kid has died again
Conversation about whether or not Alex would have known that covering that
That way would have been defensive in the past you think the answer would be very ReSound and yes of
Course obviously
The emails that we were referring to earlier on about
Mr. Posner
Communicating
His death
Displeasure with
But the coverage
We're not responded to by Miss
Esther Jones
They were responded to by other
Are people I don't know what mr. Jones knew or didn't know about me
Mr. Posner
Indication of displeasure at the
Time because you didn't read the stuff is
Position right where you talk
Assuming that I will also say
That
This
Is not altogether on
Common where are you
Source another article
And
Publish the article I don't know that nests
Thoroughly
This is an adoption by me
Esther Jones
Of what the
Call Heart of the article and I was about to say will you know it is cuz you watch the video but you didn't watch TV
New York
I'm sorry
Yes I don't want
Okay because mr. Jones says in this video
32 the Pakistan thing is fake and Sandy Hooks
Things fake one of these half
You know he said that
I don't know I didn't
We have yet another instance of a very clear and direct refusal of Alex's team to follow the judges
Instructions in preparing for the deposition
From the judge at that hearing
Quote they should watch every video in the weeks leading up to the deposition
They should identify themselves for the company every statement they believe in those videos has a source and they should make
Efforts to determine what that Source was
And they should be able to intelligently
Intelligently as to the source of that effort they've taken to determine those sources
What are very basic level this is just a failure and Miss pause didn't watch the video they're talking about you can see
This makes her
Unable to answer questions about its content let alone further questions about its sourcing just
There's nowhere to go
Yeah that listed is that list of things from the judge is now taking on more of like a
I want a pony and I want world peace and I want yeah that's not happening
Talking about it as like
Impossible tasks like world peace and a pony
Anybody from Infowars to tell the truth
But that's because of
Who you're asking
It's like
The request isn't some kind of a like
Idealistic
Sure impossible to deliver in any other case this is the sort of requirement that would be
You're asking the wind for information
Man the info Infowars is a force of nature towards this court I understand
Like the request is for World Peace implies that like
URI or anybody else who's in this position being sued would be unable to find a way to
Comply with the court
Prison reality it's just like
It's not it's like
Requiring a chocolate bar
From someone who is staunchly refuses to admit the chocolate exist
To get that candy bar
It is very very attainable request that the court is making of Alex but it is
It just feels like it's impossible
Because they are making it impossible for either non-compliant force of nature
So there is the whole thing about her son
Image
Traces back to
And has to do with
The copyright strikes right that he was filing on these conspiracy videos in order to get them
Strikes on YouTube going to take anything season and advocate for the end of the fur
First Amendment
In one of these videos Alex has copyright claim
Answer this this is something that is asked of his paws what's going on here
It says he showed a copyright claim document on camera
Do you know what that refers to
I think it probably refers to
Mister
Posner
To get
Videos
Removed
Are you
Do you know that or is that just
I think that that's what
True
But I'll be done anything to figure that out now
So that document
Pigeon for Mena
On the first year now we're going to know now we're going to the one that says 924
Keep going
You see the Bates number 92
And on this page on segments for
It also talks about showed copyright claim document on camera
If this is
The complaint or some sort of complaint from Mr Posner
You haven't done anything to located
Figure out what it is
No but
What this means to me is that
During the segment
He showed the app
Actual
On his document
Exactly
Just like the thank you exactly
The judges direct orders from the hearing to be able to speak about everything Alex Jones
Leave those videos about every piece of paper he holds up every piece of paper you shows on that desk camera
So specifically things are shown on the desk
So clearly this requirement has not been satisfied
Ironically I was listening to this I was thinking
I think I would be one of the few people in the world who could actually do a decent job as the corporate housing
Yeah they should have paid you way more than 30 grand and you decry ronnica Lee I think I could answer most of the
The f****** he'll turn moment of Mark sitting at a deposition desk
Did you walk and get at the corporate representative few should have a f******
World championship belt on.
McMahon and Austin hugging in the ring a WrestleMania the end of an era
I don't know why she's not lying about the things that would make her look like a reasonable eye you know like did you look
Look into this listen it was on my list of things to look into but there were a million things to look into you know it and I know it wasn't
Possible for me to look into this is like
Nope didn't give a f*** about this one next
Functionally I'm not sure there's that much difference but it is different
So one of the things that I think will plague every one
One who has any familiarity with this case until the day they died is a fact that there was that ridiculously in-depth
Gigantic background-check of Leonard Posner documents that were handed over by
Alex and his is company and no one seems to know what the fuc
Yep
Can you summarize any other information the company has about me
How does we sit here today
I have CNA background checks that was
Is produced in
Production
Okay tell me about that word.com
You know interesting Lee enough I cannot determine where that came from
Through alright mark it is
Everyone has no idea where it came from
Vicious in the uniformity of no one knowing anything about that
Jordan is an Unsolved Mysteries
When you understood that. Backgrounds
Report exist
What did you do to me
So
I have spoken to Mr
George Jones I've spoken
Esther do I've tried to go
Through the
Material in the emails to find out if it was
Email I don't
It connected to an email
Mr. Jones not aware of where it came from
Is Urdu is not aware where I came from
I can
Calculate but I don't want
Why do that
Cuz I don't honestly
We know where it came
I do know it is amongst
The materials in the production but I can
Can't testify as to when
When or how
Somebody put it in there right
I don't know how it came
I know that I know you don't know.
But somebody put it in
Dad has gotten there somehow exactly
Conversation that happens in like the front office of a medical room that just be like
You know these things happen what you going to do
Believe scissors inside somebody
Yeah it's I mean there is an answer to the question and it's frustrating that
It's entirely possible that no one because it's within our grasp though it is it is
The knowable thing it seems like it should be
I guess one of the ways they could be figured out I don't know how I don't know if this is even possible
If you need like a court order or something but like
Obviously the background check would have had to been run by somebody
You might have some record of who did it
Is that maybe I don't know but yet is it at this point
It's absurd absurd you can't have a background check like that and then just have
15 depositions where everybody's like
No no idea never heard of it.
Another thing that's bizarre is this clip
They understand his protective order in this case
And I haven't seen
Assigned
Protective order
But I'm happy to do it
Okay
But in other words before being exposed to my client
That's really f***** up
You're supposed to have signed entry into that protective order before you accept
Before me and Mark to talk about anything
Anything with this case
And I did
Signed one that's why I couldn't talk about or didn't want to even
High risk
Any possible questions coming up or any conversations that might come up and talk about me going to be at
The deposition
For a couple months afterwards
But there was no public conversation of any of this stuff because
I was signed on to this protective order considered was just not signing it
It seems like such a massive
Failure of you could have just not done it apparently
I mean I'm there are no rules
I mean I think that this is a good Rule and I'm happy to be bound by any but if other people aren't but like
I feel like the fact that it exists
And they have the person who has made it all the way to the sitting in the deposition without having
This
It's it's troubling and maybe
Problem in a case where the honor System is not one that can be
Relied upon
I would say it's the least
Yeah yeah
Sysco business weird I don't really know how to set it up
Just weird
YouTube video on here it starts with
Professor claims
Okay and then I see you taking some notes over to the side right
Yes but like I said this is just my basic bullet point
Clip of what that video is about
And then I have more in-depth
Okay so one of the notes that you've taken on that video
First you tell me the date on that video
110 2013
Owen Shroyer
Yeah
Tell me what that means
It might have been Owen was either in that video or did the interview
Or
Something to that effect
Or maybe it was the source for the information or something
No I don't think I would have been the source it would have been
The person who is
Is doing the video
But
I could be mistaken on that can I check my more in-depth nose
Yeah so for that video
I have the reporter as Owen Shroyer
I'm his Source was Jim Tracy and
His
Website for various others
I have I'm a little concerned about that answer
Okay because Owen forward and start working in Fort Worth 2020
Toyota
I did so you know what might might be a typo
Okay she mixed up Paul Joseph Watson and Troyer
Britain and it appears that this is dick butt
It appears that you have drawn Nick but is this Owen Shroyer that you're talking about
Get hired as big but until
Yeah that's is troubling Wild
It shows at least an illustration that some of the information that you may
Is inaccurate
Completely you're just
Off Script
This is Outta control there's never going to be any Clarity nobody's just going to come out and be
Honest
I don't think that this is a moment of dishonesty
Even if you are telling the truth trying as hard as you can
There is reason at least to believe that there are instances of you have just got it wrongly the wrong
So
Blah here we go talk about our old friend someone we haven't heard
Much about in a while
Where am I going to do
Claim that they Boulder was a house
I got rid of it.
Not only
That's not a claim that was just meeting at video
I'm sure that it was made another videos
So I've watched other videos I have
Change this
Of the house being
Bulldozed
Okay
Would you like to talk about that
This house being bulldozed
You mean where did Alex Jones get the beliefs at the house
Right
I believe that there were property records
Is that had end
Indicated that
The house was
Have you seen those
I haven't seen
They were monks
Stop.
Are do you understand the story that was that
Is this video covers a story by Lee Ann McAdoo
Do you understand that story
Sure
Okay you know who Leanne McAdoo is
She's somebody whose work is feature
You talk to her
About Adam Lanza's house direct contact
Another admission of failure to follow basic instructions
Mistresses admitting that she is aware of the claim that they're discussing relies on reporting done by Lee Ann McAdoo
But that she didn't try to contact Leanne
From the judges directions quote
They need to search for every person quoted in each video and by that I mean they need to search every single thing info
Wars are free speech systems are out in email on a text
Any other communication system or in the mind of any employee or former employee or guest of the show
Anything and everything
Was a little bit wishy-washy but whether or not she
Call door tried to call curtain MO
Here it's pretty direct that you didn't even try to contact Leanne and us
She didn't make the simplest effort attempt at trying to figure out what the reporting relied on
Which was then used as the basis for Alex to report on what he did and it's impossible to untangle the sourcing because you did
Amazing just
Just that moment of pure comedy
You know just that
So did you try and reach out to her
Just at the break cheery tone of voice that came with us
Didn't even try that might be also a part of her growing annoyance
Absolutely
Both of them get a bit more annoyed
For this to go well
No she doesn't have enough information to do a good job no she doesn't have any information
Working as a sort of Uno part-time employee temporary employee for someone with a
Vested interest in not doing a good job
So it's it's chaotic
Here's another violation of the judge's orders
Do you know what employees were involved in creating the video
Unless it's on that list that we
If previously marked
So this is exhibits
Sex
October 20th
No that's not one of the
So in other words you want be able to tell me
When employees were involved
Now these days go from 2013
So once again from the judge
They need to be prepared to identify and describe the role of every employee involved with every video
So yeah we went on that one too including some exam
Apples that are pretty transparent and obvious of the it like times that the judges direct instruction
There are so many more of them but it would just get repetitive
Really either it's not like
There are 100 examples of her being prepared at like I can't talk about this and then I just chose
One that was no good
This is just a rank
Inability to do the thing
That you're there to do
In
Serve opposition to the direct orders that the judge gave
Write establish why this was happening in the first place
A bummer pitching machine to the judges balls
That might as well be what we're talking about
But it does allow for you know those opportunities for things to be said there could be
Traveling like
You know it's a company's position that Leonard Posner was opposed to the First Amendment
Didn't past depositions things like Daria saying on behalf of the company that
Wolfgang halbig sounds like a committed Porter
Is what he does or saying dhanbad and he's a good reporter what's wrong with
Reporter actually another of those
And it's trying to argue that
When Owen got on air and said the things that he did that were defamatory towards mystery
That he wasn't relying on
Jim Fetzer who was the underlying information source of the claims
He was relying on zerohedge right because they've published the article right that Mr fencers information was in
And then
This is crystallized
I would say that the reliability of mr. Shroyer is not on the surface or it's on the reporting
Zerohedge
I do know I didn't have in publishing the article would have netted the
How do you know that
Because Infowars entire Pro
Commentating like I said
It does like a citizen blogger commentator
Paulette whatever okay so we're not doing independent
Independent analysis
Independent journalism or I'm not investigating me things we're not
Investigative reporters
Oh boy pulling other articles from the internet
Those people are writing their articles we've seen those but those sources have been reliable in the past and we are relying
Lion on those people to that their own source
If they don't let their own sources
That's
That on that
That's right
Not Infowars
Hands Clean
For anything they put on the show
But they didn't themselves right
I don't know how that's going to say I like
I like the little pause after he repeated back to her what she just said to him in a way that she finally understood what you just said
And she went
Yep that's the company's position they say yes
That is a probably troubling level of refusal
To take responsibility for anything
We can do whatever we want as long as we didn't write it
Would you say it well if you put it like that it sounds like
When you take off all my bells and whistles
So
To some of the specific claims of like Wolfgang how big's
Stop that was reportedly reported by Alex Wright
And one of those is that there was no traffic
To the
By the website the Sandy Hook
Schools website
And therefore it must have been closed course and the reason that this is
You know we're jumping to here and I think the reason that this is somatic is that
This
Is potentially something that isn't them being a pundit
Write this is something that
Conceivably could be presented as investigative journalism is it or is it not well
First question that we see
Is why does the Sandy Hook
Elementary School website have zero traffic
You know where that key
Yes I believe that the top it the source for that pretty
Tequila content
The Wayback machine
Wayback machine
First of all
Are you saying Infowars Witten
Figured this out
Went to the Wayback machine
Came up with this theory on its own
Oh you mean where is this Source the original source for this belief I'm not sure but I know that
We have amongst our documents
The printout
From the Wayback machine
Damn so at the very least
If it wasn't originated
Fear
It was checked into
We have the way back
Only if he even put that on
It wasn't in this video it might have been another video she did like a screenshot
To the Wayback machine
The scam of this way back.
Where does that come
Where did he get the idea to go there I don't know
He didn't go there
I'm sorry you didn't go there
Find that picture I know where that
Okay so I'm trying to figure out if you know
All I can testify as to the document that I saw
From the way back now
I did not know that you are book called nobody died at Sandy Hook
Wayback machine
Totally false not
I didn't go to the way back now
Myself
Well yeah I mean
You wouldn't know
How would you even go there
And what would you look up
I don't know I didn't go to check it out myself all I saw was the document from the way back now
I saw that there was something from the Wayback machine
Show me the video
I need a nothing to follow up figure out where that came
I decide from looking at the document that was
Produced as the source
About the Wayback machine
Alex Jones and Alex
Concussion is
Is that
Thought on the way back
So this is an instance where there's some sort of
Gray area like is this something that you're claiming is original report
Although you already said that you don't do that not doing any journalism
Is that this notes of course not it's from Jim feathers book but she doesn't realize that
What a mess
No idea about the sourcing of stuff now it's from the Wayback machine
I like the way that we discuss the Wayback machine in that Clippers as though it were something that like it's it's held somewhere
It's a robotic Oracle
Well we can sort that we consulted the Wayback machine
And it has given us many Tamagotchis told us the
Give it a gift of acid washed jeans
Machine
Robot come on
Play the machine at the same time I get it you win you win Scattergories
This this was kind of like so it's not actually
Original reporting maybe there's some other things they were done
Bye
Someone named the dog
That might qualify as original reporting this isn't good
Crime stat
Which says no murders occurred
In Newtown
Piece of info
Nobody else
Yes so that was I did
Speak to our staff
On this
Particular claim
I'm so
This is
A source that was actually Source from the fbi.gov
Website
A screenshot of which was
Put on
To an attached
The article it was written by a Don Salazar
Opposing
This article
Just want to make sure you're
You're right it was in Connecticut and so essentially what happened
With the article
And
It was
Not reported
From another
Source
Okay it was original reporting on in the context of mr. Salazar
Because it was not found from another source
He went to fbi.gov and he saw this and then
Problem with the
Number it does say zero
But the problem for the article
Newtown Police Department
If you haven't finished that what it says is the FBI.
Stat
Her Town not heard upon
Apartments
Soper Town Newtown says
0 but at The View
You scroll to the very bottom like at the end of the list of
A-Town there's an asterisk
That says
State Police
Do not report
To the FBI
So that is
A source of
Fusion soda
Cartier
For that particular stat but it does say if he
Scroll down to
Can you tell
It does say zero
But
She didn't scroll all the way down the page
And honestly I don't know the answer as to why the state
Please stop don't
Support the FBI that's the real problem here
Purports to be
Bi there
Just to make sure that you not put things on the record that are Evan
There's actually five
Report that they
Generated from
How's the partner
Every Department
As for the Connecticut
Please list the 27 children murdered at 10
You're saying these are the
I just want to make sure you
Okay at the bottom of that article is not the article but at the bottom of the fbi.gov all if that's really a
Then there is the asterisks
Include State Police
Right
So you would he would have had to go and research the reason why that the estate
Please.
Did not report for that particular those for
Particular number is
Or he would need to pull up the document
Referred to on that chart
Ucra
Nope
The top of the dock where it says that these figures on here come from the US
CCR
All he did was look at the chart saw the big fat zero and then
And we talked about how this didn't come from anybody else.
This was independent research
Dunbarton
Write that was a report that
He did not get
From someplace else
Apparently as far as I know it was something that
Somebody had seen
He might have gotten a tip
Yeah so Salazar might have gotten a tip
A boy
The very basic laziness and sloppiness and desire to reach the decide
Get out,
Then I like willingness to just like me I will not take this a step further and figure out what we're reporting
I will just have the Optics that I need I'm going this is good enough
It's just it's just lazy shity work
Let let it never be said that the man Jordan's career really ended because he didn't scroll
All the way to the bottom
Seriously
Breathe read the thing that you're claiming proves a conspiracy how do you not know every
Everything that happens
. from that one clip you do like I think I think that she even said it she even said it he looked
You saw the big fat zero she said every part of their editorial strategy everything
But they do right there they got what they wanted they quit and that's what the happened at 1 saying that
Maybe we don't take enough time to recognize sometimes is like trying to role-play or imagine in your head
Add what you would do if you actually believe the things they pretend they do Salazar and you actually believe that there
There's a global cabal of satanic weirdos who are you no controlling everything in the trying to kill everybody
Often they staged the shooting
In order to get people's guns
And you found this piece of evidence that is there were no murders they are
You would dig deeper right
I think
Actually the opposite is you would want to know every single thing about these
Understand
Because this would be something that you could use help prove your case you're way off
Cuz I know that make sense to you
Here's what makes sense if I get into that headspace would make sense to me is I better get a screenshot of this quiz
Because they're going to take this down and then continue to learn
You were looking at this and more realistic opportunistic
These scammy computer sister all about it I'm looking at it from a what if they were sincere
If it was sincere absolutely is don't try to bring up pieces of a
Evidence that were misused about Sandy Hook that to mark
Cuz he knows what they're talking about it is they feel like
Mark and Bill are coming into this with a very laissez-faire attitude as opposed to
We've literally spent them how many years doing this
I memorized these f****** documented this goddamn point I think maybe you're so used to talking to people like Alex or
I don't know
This is
But you just ask everybody doesn't know what they're talking about and it is not the case
Different animals
So I don't Salazar I think might be a total creep I'm getting the vibe from things that you learn
Learn about this guy that
He might be a like
Number one
Top-tier
Grade a weirdo inside Infowars
We don't know so much about him generally because he doesn't come on the show
But like a pretty consistently through these depositions and through things here's like
He was one of the people who was like
Really interested he seems to be
Like right there with some of the more f***** up thing
Connected to some of the more f***** up gas for a while ago I realized
He was really into doing the Sandy Hook stop writing that comes up here
These are very out-of-character articles
That we do not go out of character
Flash show
There were a couple here that add-on did
That
As I said earlier I don was more into this then
Most of the other
People involved
Infowars
And so he did a couple of independent
Pieces.
Really we're out of
Out of the realm of what is
Usually.
So like for example he did that Batman article I don't know
Right so she
Got a tip from somebody on social media and Isleta
Saw that it was like okay well it was pretty cool and he
She did this
Dive into
Do you know the three Batman movies and then what that area was called in the comics
Wrote that article so
That was independent reporting on his
It's out it's really not
The usual
Peace at the car
When
Adan
Got tipped off
That the appearance of
Dark Knight
Could suggest
Programming
Suggest for knowledge
Attack beans
By global
Illuminati
He thought that was
Does he think it's cool is that a question
Did he did
Are you asking me whether he did think that
Is it cool
Is pretty cool
It was at 2
The kids are saying it's based
Hook nonsense project he did that man story
He did a similar article
About a slasher Thriller
Thanks
Sandy Hook to which he just found to be
Interesting just because of the name commonality
But as far as the other things Source in there I don't know that
He thought that was
Crowbar
The name commonality I think
Let's take a detour / 2
To the slasher film
Sandy Hook lingerie party
You read documents about that
Flavor of the article and it's supposed to. About it
They sent me
Got it right
He did tell me he reached out to the producer that video
Does emails supposed to bend
Yeah I don't know if I read this but
Mickey Mouse
Adan saying to that person who ran the horse
We know this is
Ridiculous
We're going to run it anyway
Remember him saying that
I don't dispute I don't remember it all honesty but he couldn't very well say
And this is just an interesting commonality between the names that's
Way to wipe that off Mr Salazar Road in email to the guy who ran that blog basic
For now
I don't know I didn't read it
You don't remember that
Email back from the guy at the horror blog telling me don't ever contact me again you bunch of weirdos
No I don't read anymore like that when I spoke to add on add-ons
Position was that
He received a response back from the producer
That
He had received a lot of
Communication about the name of
The video
Following
And that he wanted to be left alone and he thought it
That's it that's a pretty diplomatic way to present to what clearly was
Strains that. Had with with them
He was understandably furious at because I'm a little scared
Also understandable now
So there was an interview that Alex did a video that
Conveniently it's very convenient that his boss hasn't seen these emails
Yeah she also has not seen a video that is particularly troubling
Does a guest on the show
Independent Media solidarity member
Who says
Lenny your day is coming my friend it is coming
And mr. Jones replies they made a major mistake involving us
And then the
Person says go after them Alex
Crush them
And then Alex says I'm not somebody
To mess with
Okay.
You've never seen
I have nursing
Alright
Same token
We've already talked you very told me there's no editorial disc
I'm so I don't
Exactly how
Were there any kind of dis
In the family
About saying that
Putting in the family
I mean inside the I'm sorry let me rephrase my question
Were there any discussions inside the company
About saying
That kind of
That's so I mean it's bad stuff to say
Certainly I made you know which one of these things whenever you like here Alex's words
Repeat it it's like
Passionate way it's like I can't imagine somebody saying that imagine being on the back of an attack like that
The times that when you read somebody's words
It sounds bad no I don't know this is
Yeah it's one of the things that becomes a little bit of a problem
Is that there's an internal numbering and labeling system that Infowars uses or they miss pause
House has 4 videos
That doesn't quite match
The one that Mark has had part of this is an issue that has to do with
Past the lawyers sure given Joya and nobody knows what's what in prayer.
Disorganized
It would be so much better for them if they just kept all their s*** in a big bucket
It really would make more sense for them they can just put it all in a big bucket and then they'd at least know where it was
You know where was Abby very disorganized but that's why you would pay
A multiple people to be bucket Stewart
The groom of the bucket
Like be confident that they're talkin about the same
That one has a video that
April 16th
Entitled Shadow government
Strikes again
You see that
You watch that video
Okay so again this is another
Saying where it's
The video that we have there's a difference
Dead cells
The date.
In this
Is April 6th
I have
I have one dated for 1 2013 that was a
Interview with doctor
Iconic
It might
It might be the
Theme video
Or it might be a different video
I really don't
I don't like I said I don't
Your internal our internal system is
Saving them in different ways
Then you're mentioning
And you're also not full videos
You know so like you might
Shadow government strikes again maybe the
The title of a clip
But it's not the entire Broad
And so the way we receiving it is not
I get that but I
We don't know do we know I mean
But if you have
Butthole
Show
Or it's
If it's in the Purdue
And we've produced it
Doodoo is it
The same do we know I don't know if it's
The same because your date is not the same date that I have
Alright
So let it also might not be the same date because
Flip being cut from the
Show
Maybe
I don't even know that
Do I know what you're referencing here no no or do you don't even know whether this is a full clip or a full
You don't know that
I don't know and the reason is
Because that's not how we met
Diane H videos
Talia referee
Hair is not how
Okay
I mean so
At the end of the day we don't know if you
I don't know I can tell you about the videos I watched at the
Didn't that was posted around uploaded around this
Last time.
Video really need to make sure
This time I'm trying to
There were actually talk
Guess
About what videomic
Be this video
So I don't know if you
I don't know if it's
It's the same video that's
That you're rapping
Mark I'm feeling like you're getting
Yes this is our thing to do you deal with
You're now sitting
With somebody and you can't even agree that like we're talking about the same thing I don't even know
What I don't know right now but I don't know it's impossible to like existence
Legal
Context goes
You might be talking about different videos that's right I was talking about that one episode of
The episode of Alex's show where he locked them in a dumpster I'm sorry I'm thinking of a different show
Remember that episode of Alex's show whatever Screech got it all that trouble different show
So I'm in this next clip we we learn some more people that
ThermoSpas didn't even
Try to contact
Okay I asked you earlier if you talk to Jakari Jackson on
Did you try the
Darren mcbreen that's another person
You can talk to her
Did you try to talk to Darren
Mr. Jones very recently
And we actually this
In a court hearing
Play this talked about
Archivist
You know what I'm talking about
If we stayed in seems like we should know
U-Pull-It in mr. Jones
Two I believe
Batman
Instagram says I have an archivist
OnStaff
Does incredible work
It should be paid about a hundred
A hundred thousand dollars a year
$20,000
Is a terrible shame
I don't understand
He says the guy is like a bloodhound
You can find any
Do you know who he's talking about
Target
I don't have any reason to believe that but
I mean he may be referring to
Third party
But I don't I've not
Been able to find anyone at Infowars at Hazlet
Even even pause think that's silly
We're just everybody started laughing and then it kind of died out at everybody started laughing because it was
Suddenly funny all over again yet or maybe he does
If you think he does have an archivist
Do you think he's going to tell me about that person I didn't even talk to Darren mcbreen
He seems willing to talk to me later
Sims 2
Wanted to be associated with Infowars left but
Dermot Breeze I think Maids right still around there
1 McMurray it's a family business come up with an like emails and
Stuff that has to do with the Sandy Hook
What are the lowlights of the Daria deposition was of course her
Idea that possibly spreading conspiracies about the children not dying
I hope it's about bringing hope to the children
Thumbs up
Are you thinking you really well I got your finger on the pulse of this deposition that Mark is getting a little bit annoyed at this point
I think that's what the deposition
What would I ask you if I was you haven't
Written down there
And it says
Alex said these
These kids didn't die
Cuz he has a big heart
That was a company testimony from a scarf over
Carpo Vista
Unless the company
Well he was a representative at the time of the company
So yes
I think what I said earlier was that
A vast majority of
Mr. Jones
Opinions as
As
Broadcast
Where that
I don't know if kids died I'm not sure I don't know what else
To form an opinion but
This may be a false flag operation
Maybe the government was involved.
That's not what I don't know what she's were referencing here I think what she's saying and what the
Context of that is is that if he
I studied kids and I this is the reason why he
That's what
I took
He did say
I can reference
I don't know about multiple times but I do know of at least one time that he said
Cousin died but on the whole
More times than
Not
He said he did
Didn't know weather
Wright insurance
Let me ask you this
Is the company's position that is
Non defamatory
Cancel
The company's position is that that is an opinion
Position the two negatives equal a positive
Is the company's policy a Mitch Hedberg joke
You talkin about okay listen
Sorry didn't say it said it once but you also said the opposite twice
Yeah that's a little snippy on marshmallow
Absolutely
From this deposition
Just think that this is a really good illustration of how little
Awareness there is of
Some of the players and some of the things that are important in the Infowars fear
Nogi CNS
Gcn
And so can you tell a snowman tree with g
You know I don't want to miss state it so I'm not
I'd rather Sono
I don't I'm not
That educated on it
To verbalize it
That way
Are you able to verbalize it at all like you have any
Even rough idea which
I just don't want to State what it is
Cuz I'm out of
Ensure
Batman like
I want to I want to know what your understanding is he
Do you understand that
Like what what are you understand
I just like I said I'm not sure so I rather I don't know
Do you know what house
To do with
Which is associated with
Is associate with videos
Ice
Thought it was associated with it but I could be wrong
But which is why I didn't want to say in the first
It meaning the management of Technology inside of
Right
Okay Ted Anderson runs you
Cngc and is a syndicate
Gcn is where all of Infowars radio
Maybe not all of it
But a very large
Substantial component
Infowars radio
Do you know that
Genesis
Antenna
Okay
Did you know that
That's deeply troubling noblejas partially because also
Understanding
The existence of gcn
Is probably necessary given that one of the subjects that she's supposed to be able to talk about is the
Distribution and reach
Of Alex's contact
I mean does anybody was a cursory understanding of Alex's career in the Warriors show
Cenote
Like it's just
Yeah I mean it's okay it's just like just tell me what the three letters
Stand for a f****** dare you tell me what gcn stands for
Yeah
I just I
I don't know
I mean like it would be like
Saying that you have an awareness of Alex's content did not knowing what Bohemian Grove into something
I doubt you do I just don't you know anything
It is amazing
To me that these things a
In a position or just all of this continued
Things that you can only f****** so bad so many times
But there's just no bottom no whenever people just decide that you don't have to have one like
If they've got enough money if you got enough time if you got enough everything there's no bottom
If you're immune to shame amazing
It's incredible
Almost all of polite society as you don't have any
Public opinion exactly you're free now
10 is about what you'd expect
When there's a source for some piece of information it said to be from Wolfgang halbig and most of the time there's no real
There's no new information to provide
There's a bunch of clams that passed didn't try to look into a people she didn't try to contact and it gets a bit repetitive
Certain point we can get the flavor of it you know from what we've got over
And you can definitely feel marks patients gradually disappear even with limited patience
Mark is a bit of a teddy bear compared to the energy of the bill comes in with the next day
When Brittney is once again set to sit for a deposition this time in the Marcel Fontaine case
Uh-oh this is not a subjective judgment on my part bill is abundantly clear about how
Little patience he has almost immediately
Surprised when you got a call from mr. Patterson be the corporate representative in this case
I wouldn't say I was surprised I knew he had been working on the mr. Jones case
For a couple years so I wouldn't say I was surprised
When you say working on he's been litigating it
I believe he litigates the Connecticut cases
So when you said hey
I need you to go to Texas
Did I surprise
Not really
You ever given a deposition prior to yesterday
Never served as a corporate representative
Ever gone to assume you know have you ever gone through a civil jury trial
Have I gone through a jury trial now
So
Your background is in criminal law
Correct
For the most part yes so what a civil lawyer
Call you
And says I'd like for you to be the corporate representative
And these civil matters
Things you've never done before you weren't at all surprised
Well they're not only a civil lawyer but
No I wasn't virus
I couldn't say no
You said my civil lawyer called you
He's not Justice
Civil lawyer
She practices civil and criminal there we go to the answer my question would be yes and I don't need all the EX
You understand that
Listen through yesterday
And unfortunately mr. banks in his far more patient
I'm just
Putting it out there
About to question answer the one that's on the table you're a lawyer you know what
Right
Or do you know
Yes
Do you know what to do when someone ask you a question
Is a bit more of an adversarial
What is the answer this as simply as you can what is your f****** name
Say it at me and don't say other s*** what's your name your f****** deal
I think we have noted
A difference in style between
Really as obvious as when you see them depose the same person
Yeah it's does live up to this it is a bit confrontational
Chosen to go good cop bad cop instead of the other way around might just be natural
I also like he pointed out bill was sitting through most of the previous thing
Got a good sense of what's going on oh yeah so we're going to go through this deposition but there might not be as much relevance
Material to get through since
At a certain point you begin to notice that a lot of the corporate representative testimony is really a game of trying to look like
Effort is being put forth
But there's not a lot of new information that's being provided
When we were kind of spoiled by having Rob dues confused uselessness and darya's psychopathy and Dupree
Depositions
In contrast past just seems like a person
Doing a job
Yep she's overhead because that's the job she's your job is to be in over her head
The reason why I don't feel like there is nearly as much meat to go over in this is that
With kit Daniels deposition
They essentially lost that case
It started crying and apologized for all this
Infowars Alex Jones of a lot of the
You know trying to tease out details of stuff
Really stands as a pretty damning document whatever like
I don't know or do you know that the corporate representative could do is kind of meaning
Nozbe job that you being asked to do is b******* and that is Alex was taking this seriously
It all you would not have sent just one person to handle all of this
But she's also a lawyer and she's being so she can bring the veneer of professionalism to not answering questions
It's not quite as entertaining as reps of the past
This falls apart
A couple hours in good
Holyshit how is it possible I mean
It is it is possible I know in her world
It does make sense
If you wouldn't be surprised Norm pattis called me up
To give her a thing I've never done before end of place I don't know if I would applaud don't understand
Areas are not an expert in never heard of not surprising at all that's Norm to a tea baby
Yeah he's a chaos lawyer
She's a friend of Norm pattis hey if you ever heard of a no-nonsense lawyer
Opposite
So we start off here with Bill trying to check in on whether or not
Miss Paws feels like she's prepared she doing
Do you feel sitting here right now that you are adequately prepared to discuss
Other topics that rented up
Notice
Did you think walking into yesterday that you were prepared
Damascus Motors
You could be honest if you were
Prepare
Like I said it's
Much as I could be us I don't think there is anybody else who could have testified any better
Acidosis
Did I ask that
Did I ask you
If you thought there was anyone else that would be better for
Why'd you say it
Because it's true
But
I like hot dog
Is true but I'm not going to blurt it out randomly in a deposition am I
It wasn't which is why I'm asking you why is that
And I just
Cuz it's true
True
This is not going well
Nope nope
What were the teacher's office
But I think that bill has identified by being in the deposition with Mark
Pattern of adding extra information in
2 things that aren't relevant
I think the goal here is to curb that behavior a little bit
Try to push back on it to make it very clear from the beginning that like
I'm not going to Payless and let's nip this in the bud real quick wasting time
For years we've given a lot of latitude to everybody about you and me just cut the b******* and let's get this done
Bright and you have clearly chosen to not do them any of the things that you seem to be saying or equivalent I like hot dogs
And let's move forward
So get to talkin about whether or not there's guidelines in place for the wedding of information
And here's what time is Paws has to say
What did you do to prepare to discuss the company's policies regarding the factual wedding of information
Try so I've spoken to
As we touch 52 yesterday have spoken to a number of other people in connection with
The policies and procedures so I spoke to Melinda
I spoke to Daria
I spoke to robbed you I spoke to
Alex
Jones a bunch of other people in
Generally speaking as far as the vetting procedures
For sourcing and articles
The company's position is that it
Does not
Engage in journalism so it
Requires the wedding be done by the sources that exciting
So this is the setup here
There is no policy right we don't have any obligation to fact-check things cuz that's them sources jobs
Cuz we're not journalism despite yesterday having told you that we did Joe
No because they don't except for one add-on does write all of these weird things that I say
I guess it's kind of a you know it's a toss-up
Unfortunately
She said here that they don't do journalism
And then we bring in an exhibit
The front the front page of exhibit 1
Can you read who that stew
It says Infowars staff
Okay in the subject line
Can you read it for me
It says new editorial policy for all reporters journalists and writers
I swear
So
After reporters what was that word you said
It says journalist and you told us that you have seen this prior to today correct
This particular email
Exhibit one
Or didn't want us to things so I want to know what part of
Did you see the first page Buffet
For today
Don't you think you probably should have
Sure specially if you spoke to the person that wrote it who implemented the policies
Correct
I did speak to kids
Daniel Craig
Mister Daniels he withheld this information about sending this out a specific
Policy that was implemented
Post the filing of these lawsuit
I don't know that he
Company you didn't know about
I didn't see the
You wish you would have
Sure
That's Tuff
You know you never like to run into a brick wall like that
We're not journalists well
Here is Kate Daniels the managing editor of the site
Managerial role supervisory person sending out an email with new policies for reporters
I think that's kind of
Gaming material and all of the hilarious material I think the one thing that sticks with me so much is just that much
When Owen was like
What tip of the cap to you that just seems so appropriate and so many moments that nobody ever said like she should have been
You got me
Do Owens credit the ability to just be like
Well I think it's because I'm their generation
You don't have to take nothing but Debbie Owens got that Brody confidence
Do you lose more do you want
So other than that
Email
Other than that policy there are there any other policies in
Vet
To vet information
So from the Inception of Infowars
February of 2009
June
June 2018
There were no policies
Whether or not
Anybody need a devet
The veracity
Information that would
Disseminated
The veracity know I do believe based on my conversations with
Keep all that there was
Is a
I don't want to say
Policy but there was an under
Standing that there would be multiple sources used
They would have lice only on one source
But I don't
I think that that's checking the brass
So there's not policies in place prior to this
This leads to a conversation about like okay so you know but like if people
Do do this
Can they get fired can anybody get fired veracity we don't know the meaning of the word
If you do spread all this bad information you get fired right
Gas
No one has ever been
Blue my mind and also made me realize that there were policies
Before this
Cuz there's a f****** handbook
What
Wanted spoken to mr. Jones and
Melinda who does HR
They couldn't name for me specific instances where people had been fired but it is a possibility and it is listed
In the handbook as
Up to termination
So it is a pasta
What about prior to June 2000
This handbook was not made in
When was it made
It says effective date 10 12 2012
That was when this was last update
I got you so what's your position at that employee handbook
Was update
No I don't believe that this policy was ever incorporated into the
Into this employee handbook
Was that employee handbook made
Specifically
I don't know it says Free Speech systems on it when I asked Melinda about the handbook cuz I did a still see it
She said it was there
It predated her 10-year there so she doesn't know
Who created it
Or when it was off dated
Or if anybody's Reddit
Before that you did ask Melinda though when
And when she said she didn't know
Surely you wouldn't
Mr. Jones
I don't think he didn't
Accompany the longest
So he wouldn't know when that was initially implemented
I don't know if you know
Right cuz you didn't ask
I didn't ask her about the
Melinda
There was a I can't remember the name of the woman that was there before her
Bye.
Okay let's let's break this down
You asked
Someone about the handbook and they said
I don't know that was
Before I started
Right
Regarding when it was produced
And who produced it
She didn't know who it was produced initially
I don't know why it would have
Why is produce but
Right so
Yet this person says I don't know I don't know I don't know
And that's where you stop your investigation
Person who probably would have known didn't work there anymore and I didn't know how to reach her
You used to work probably
But you don't know
Cuz he didn't ask anybody that was there
I couldn't that person but whoever would have been there is no longer there
You don't think the owner that company knows when he invoked
Employee handbook
No I don't
Why
Because I don't think he would have had anything to do with
Probably good I really think that her answer is essentially bill you and I both know
If I asked Alice this question he's going to say I have no idea you know that I know that let's just skip over the part where I asked
Kim questions and he pretends to know what he's talking about
I agree with you in terms of like what the conclusion would be the same
No idea is correct
But it's still relevant to point out the chicken in accordance with the rules
Turn off
Because where you live in the real world but I mean it stripped your task to do to prepare for the position
And at the same time there is a part of her a part of me that I understand where she's coming from where it's just like
Why what's the point really I'll just know anything look deep in my eyes and ask me why I should ask Alex any
Question and expect an honest response you've asked him more questions than anyone in the world
Alex may know stuff but he functionally knows nothing cuz he's not going to tell you anything
Fishing in a dry well on reality
Probably not going to be very clear about something
I want to get my hands on a copy of this manual
I feel like it's
Probably something that I could get a digital version of that I want a physical copy so I don't know
Is anybody out there has any ability to get me a copy of the employee handbook
You know I have mementos and like
I have a collection of Infowars type stuff that needs to be passed to be at the collection
Yeah handbook exist yeah I mean it's probably just boilerplate bulshit
Fun to go back and fantasy book when people should have been fired
Hands on one of those I will compensate
Illegal to buy that from somebody
I have no idea what we'll see what happens
Speaking of law issues
Bill asks at this point if
There's been any malfeasance
Any
Things that she doesn't approve of right she's seeing the part of accountants or low
Lawyers
We got on the lawyer front okay
What about in Eloy
Do I have concerns about whether lawyers in the
McKay's have
Duty to the company
To anything you came at
Anything regarding you mean if I answer statements or anything in the entire universe
Anything that you came across in preparation
I did have concerns on behalf
Regarding
Need prior rep
Location
What about it
Aspire lawyers
Okay what about him
I think that there are issues
Is that
There have been
Even though the company has Pros
Material to its
Chinese has not been
Produce
Appropriately
And has resulted in
Many if not all of them
Would that be in the text
Showcases or the kinetic
So we've got we got some problems with some pasta attorneys and they are
AR
May be responsible for everything that's gone back here I'm just going to say I went back and I looked through all their work
It's garbage. They were probably lying about everything honestly everything correctly they just didn't
Produce the documents you guys ask for it's really the lawyers fault honestly it seems unlikely it's all their fault
Merely that every lawyer that Infowars hired just so happened to be scamming including the lawyer that
You're friends with who is Bob Barnes huwa
Was on Alex's show a couple days ago talking about how monkeypox
Play whatever
Some indications of cool she's talking about in terms of these lawyers
Any lawyer since
Pacific
I think that
There are special
Traffic issues regarding
Mr. Randazzo by although he doesn't
Haven't parents
In the file
And Brad Reeves
Perhaps
There's a button sign and I agree
Okay so Brad Reeves
Randazzo's
Trina
I'm not sure about mister
Enoch I think he's
Donna
Punjab
Kewadin
I'm sorry I don't know why
What about him
Michael Burnett
I don't have a painting about him either
Ya Baba
Barnes
How's the moment of recognition
Tamara Barnes
Catalyst not a fan of Bobby bar
The tone of voice that you said it far
Yeah
So David Barnes can't say any specific
But it does reach the level about
These passwords
I went over this a little bit with mr. Shroyer in his step
Listening honesty the same
Anything based on.
Information that you
The company
Have the credit company decided one way or another
On
Legal malpractice
We have not decided on
I made any final
As to whether to file or who file against
He's not made any
Finals
Okay is it being
Has been discussed.
I would ask that should
That
Discussion happened
Metro Ford
I just be made aware
Schmitt's interesting you know it's not like a definitive statement that we are suing these people but the cop
Conversations are happening
And again it's important that you don't have that decision
Especially not in the definition with you like
I just want to remind you you're not going to get to keep any of that money is going to hell
Maybe we'll change our mind we'll see what happens after you guys have left us alone for a year
So
We have this next clip and this is
Maybe the only adorable moment on this episode
Because the attorney for Alex's side Miss blot
Maybe a little bit of an arguing periodically why doesn't she have an attorney in there
With her cuz I feel like there are plenty of questions she could have just been like I don't need to answer these occasional e
And also she's made some objections that you're not supposed to make
In the context of a deposition and then
Bill has had to say like
You can objective form in other class guidelines
Until this point
When her phone ring
Was the company at all aware
Did mr. randazza inform the company at any moment
How do you need to take
No idea
Okay I'm older
Don't know how
Sleep button
No
My son just
Interesting questions
Y'all can all I have that's okay
I'm sorry sorry I apologize
I don't know if I can play moments
I don't know if I can take it I just can't I just can't believe all of
This is happening at the same thing
Cell phone if it happen if this happens in one case you like whoa what a great moment to remember that forever
This is good everyday kind of like a human eye
I don't want to know that I do
Don't know how to use my phone be the thing that I think is remarkable is that I believe
I'm not 100% sure on this but I believe that means that Siri has to be on the record
Ike cited in the transcript correct
Mission includes a robot
I meant everybody jumps into helper
Coronavirus
It just it just doesn't
So are we get back to the question-and-answer portion of this and
Who sings this
Turned over in Discovery.
Giants background report obviously one
Very mysterious buddy would like to know where it came from and nobody does in the case of this Marcel Fontaine
The case where the whole thing is essentially that get Daniels
Misidentified the Parkland shooter as MRSA
And they got the picture off 4chan
Basically
Infowars
Produced a 4chan Post in the course of discovery
Understand what
At the bottom right-hand corner you see that it's marked
Defendants 2000's
Which would mean that it was
Just by the defendant
You would
Why would the defendant
I don't know how it came to be in our
Possessions
Is a false flag you know anything
About this
The history of this
No this isn't wasn't
Produced by us
In the sense that
Kisses
A post that we made
So I'm now
Who made this post
They were looking at
That looks like a post
Spy
Somebody posting on a
Chatroom Sodus
How was it found
I don't know
When was it found
I don't know how it came to be in our
When you got this document did it confuse you a little bit that
Estill
Wyatt
No
Is this this dock is this
Defendants
Is that
The post that was used
Daniels
Off of Fortune
I don't know
Does bacon accept
To figure out what this
I didn't talk to mister Daniels about this
Circular Dokken
I'm the representative
This is a post
It isn't
And mr. Daniels
Cold
The imagery
Wouldn't that be something you wanted
Talk about women
I don't think it's accurate to say he pulled damage
Only from 4chan I think his
Response was
He saw the image on 4chan as well as other social media sources
So I don't know that this was the post that he saw on us
Thoroughly
Where did mr.
Where did Mister Daniel
As his
Representation in the production was and has similar comment to me was
He saw it on social media first
I think he said Twitter
Pain in the wrist
He also saw it on 4chan
I don't know
Whether this was the particular
Document
She saw on 4chan
But when I spoke to him he said he had seen it
Not first on Fortune
On a social media site
Such an ugly
So we're not really near what I got out of all that is
Pornography
Percent sure why this is
Existen Infowars
Is files correct
That's right
And we didn't really take any steps
To figure out
What it is
Why when
How it came about
I didn't ask him about the snow
You didn't ask anyone
No
Weird that is weird
Yeah I've been considering that you know the whole thing is that this image was going around 4chan at
Troll thing in the high reported on it
The fact that in their files somehow that got turned over is this post
Seems like
Pretty clear Ada Vista
Wasn't rolling around 4chan completely Anonymous in
You know on verifiable nonsense so like
I don't know what they're trying to defend by saying it was on Twitter not for 10 minutes.
I mean sure I don't know if that's relevant to the matter at hand
I mean it is still just like
In terms of pulling information and it's it's it's Anonymous and its Origins
I don't know it's very weird there's no difference he just got the image from the internet but I tried
Actually the difference between 4chan and Twitter is pretty significant there's a conversation
Real shadiness to the idea that
This wouldn't be something very important to figure out
Why that's there or where this came from I think like 44 corporate deposition that seems like
Central almost don't understand how your first move isn't understand what it
It is
That they're going to ask me about
True even if you'd like whether you're acting from a place of good intention or not like
006 it's not like you're in a knitted evidence 1140
Before it's number six just go through the top 100 they're probably going to ask about the top 100
Right I don't know maybe that's a faulty assumption
Surrounds a post reported on a post on 4chan
One of the things was turned over in Discovery
Is metaphorically in spiritually in the top 100
This is the clip where everything I think
Really falls apart. And
Real world begins
You bet
So they're talking about.
Information about Alex is net worth of the company and
A document comes up a balance sheet
And it turns out that the plaintiff's
Don't have this document oh no that leads to
Oh my God your real problem
What's the best label
What's the base number on the
This doesn't have a base light bulb
This was produced to me in it just
This was at my
When she give it
Friday
You go over it with
Any
After you got
I went over it
Wes
I don't think I
Spoke to Melinda about it I might have spoken to Bob about it
Just ask him to
Explain it to me
But other than that
Real quick Bob is not Bob bar on the Financial Consultant then we'll get it
Bob about on Friday
Friday
How long till 2
An hour or so
That was on the phone
No I saw him in purse
He was at
He was at the
Kcur at the off
Yes I was
At the office
Thursday Friday
And Saturday
Why did you ask for that document
Cuz I believe it was relative and
To the
Topics that I was
Testify about today
Did you where you ended
Were you under the belief
Is that document
I don't know whether this
And produce
These are
The numbers for
Honey I don't know if
I know we don't
Because the number
As I realized
That she and I were
Was giving
Friday and I plead the revision
Place
Can I skip
Sure
Why didn't you come with the other 333 I got
Because
I was clenching
Writing on those for the Fontaine and
And I ran out
Why wasn't why didn't you hand it to me this
Ordering the first break
Second grade
This is actually in
I didn't do it
Cartwright
That's my
Do you believe that the information and
Picard is
Information point
Yes I do
So
Bill's understandably pretty pissed
Here because there is relevant information that was not produced to them
Against the law
It's certainly against decorum there is an amending of like the
Balance sheet for 2020 has been done now
Now is the right time this information
Is
Like why didn't you visit yeah that's a really important piece of information
Why would you why didn't I didn't have time
What
Also don't have answers
So they go to break
And they come back
And immediately Miss block needs to amend amend
I think so
Mister Ogden I need to clarify my response to a question you posed with
Respect to the
Financial document that
LaSpada's have
This document
What's provided
On Friday
Immediately past Friday
And in my continuous review
The answers
Are the discovery responses by prior counseling
Case I did not
For any
Profit and loss or balance
Prison life
Derogatory
That used
The term
Financial
Call statement
And so I reached out and learned
That knowing
In fact it has not been
Play Spy party
Because they did not
Considerate
Odd
Contrary
2 mi
Hasn't that I did get the dog
So that I can
I just want to
Put on the Roku
For myself
Imav my client
The
I've been sitting
Corporate represent
Bagnet
Text her all day
Without reduce
Just been sitting there
This is a good time for Paws to have a fourth wall break where she turns to the camera and she's like oh we're suing our
Lawyers and then she goes back and we get back into the show
At this point I'm kind of this blot decides
I'm going to f****** throw someone under the bus for this because at the end you will hear
Leave and there's something very
Kind of sick, there's a quality to it
I want to make something
When we started this Depo
10 topics were very clear that
That
Testify
Was she
Asked
For it
To be prepared to discuss that
And
It's been sitting in her back I wouldn't have
Problem if I'd a gotten at the
This morning
Ordering any of our break
But the fact that at the very end after I don't know 45 hours of questioning
I asked the witness we get to that topic and then all the sudden it comes out of the
Out of the bag and now it's saying that
Ben Bates
It's on the way in
You know
You can obviously probably see
How it looks
I'm not accusing you one way or the other but
I'm just looking at
Aggregate
Happened in this case
All Warriors
And
Every lawyer has come
They're not that
They are trans
They're going to
And every single time
Replaced
The new one comes in
Who did you
Talk to
That had a different professional
Opinion than you
So that I know who the name
Bradley
It's not
He's just kind of like out of a play
This I mean he might as well have a f****** bowler on with a little pressed things that
I got to run to the phone real quick extra extra
Justifiably in like full of indignation disappointment
Isn't that withheld this information because of a different idea
She sells out Brad the former
And then Mark immediately
I got to go call the court of course of course this is off the rail amazed
That is that is so the that is a Few Good Men moment
That Alex believes will happen and how it really goes
So is Bradley
Bradley Puckett dead batch in Bradley Reeves go ahead call the court and I'll give you his number I'll give you weary one
Mexico
I Bradley ordered the code red
So
After this they get into some discussion of the financial workings of Alex's
Empire
Right workings is a word
Wow some of this information is nuts
So here's the here's the basic situation
Bright
So Alex
Has free speech systems
They have a relationship
With another company
Brewing Company
They sell products right pqp are cells
Products through free-speech sunrise
And also they haven't been paying pqr up EQ pr4
Years
Right now because of that owe them like 50 something million dollars man there's nothing we can do we're broke
Sorry
Now it just so happens that we own pqp are
Who owns Pikachu
Pqr is Owens
20% by doctor and mrs. Jones
+ 80
Percent by
Tlj are
Kelsey
David Jones was his wife
20% by David Jones and who
Escaping right now
Anissa Jones
Carol I think right
Okay you could have said any named pojar
Pojr on his 80th
CPR
And who owns
Tlj
Pojr is owned
10% by
Carol Jones still missing
Drones
Alex's mother
I'm sorry what
90% by
The
A
DJ Truss
EBay Alex Emerick Jones perhaps
Alex has a trust set up most of
Everything is different
The company that owns the company write his company owes 50 million dollars
All right there's nothing we can do we just owe them so much money Franklin
We're not already bankrupt honestly it's amazing that we have any money to run things.
I mean
Maybe it would be more fun as a like
Shell company game
If it weren't
So f****** obvious
Yeah yeah I mean it's somehow not obvious two people listen to a show but
Yeah it's it's pretty
Shockingly transparent once you are asked under oath who owns Vista
Diculous
He's just a f****** Circle man cuz you asked yourself okay
What's going on with that trust
The
Who is the trustee
You know
I'm not sure who the trustee as I know the beneficiaries are
Who are the beneficiaries
So
The
Beneficiaries are
Of the Corpus of the trust
Are his children
So they're in the trough
Star
You don't whatever money is in there
And Alex has a remainder man
And then the
Income
Going into the trust
Say it
K2
What an elaborate
Way to set this up in order to try and
Duck
I mean it could not be more of like a
It is going on to get a paycheck then that
I've never worked for any business that was like listen we're going to have to go through three different shell companies
Give you a paycheck yeah and let me tell you something
Direct debit ain't happening we might get paid
This
If stolen money than either goes to in 1/8 we are bartering
Your salary these days
Cheer tryout himself because of this Byzantine arrangement
Great deal of pqp are that sells
The products
It freeze beef systems which he owns
Oh my God this is this it's just ridiculous
The income
The income is
Payday 2
Mr. Jones but with the caveat which is what I was trying to say before that
There is
A
Another
Entity aej holding
That owns
Alex's interest
In
In Kiel
In pqp are so total Alex's interest
Is like 72
Percent Nal
A
EJ Holdings
LLC
What's up mister
Do you know Alex
I don't I'm so
So that ownership interest MP3 audio on Spotify
If you divide it amongst his
His parents and their percentages he owned 72
Percent interest
So he sold
His interest
In that
To AJ Holdings and there's a
.9
25.9 million-dollar
Note
On that
Where's that
What do you mean where is it
Come from
Fergus 29.9 what's a 30 million-dollar note
Thought I had
Seeing the no it's the it represents the value of mr. Jones is interest
Antique
CPR
Such that it
Such as at work because it's
About 7
And then the money.
Is
Pay principal and interest
Off of that note
Is paid
To Alex Jones
To like Alex is a situation like presumably you have to look at it
50 million dollars in jail
That's right no I think it feels like this is the this is like a dumb person's idea of how
How smart people hide money
He's like I see
I actually he's Kaiser so saying people before anybody even tries to get to his money because he knew somebody was going
Call Discovery Bay Egypt
How am I going to hide this money I know I'll put my initials on it I am not a financial crime
Certainly don't know if I have enough information from these depositions
Definitively prove anything
But I would say
Bike
Audit some of the stuff
I think you might
I think it would
It would be too hard to uncover something going on here
Yep very much self yes
How many companies do you need
In a circle jerk
Before your like
I think I might be the one who's doing something wrong here
You know you have a situation where there is this this company that for a long time
You've been buying your products through and you've never paid them and then
You get some food in your good hours Shallotte
50 million dollars there wasn't anything securing the loan and they were
Like
You know trying to collect on you or anyting the back when you're getting sued and you're probably going to lose ahold
Your company might go bankrupt
Parent companies in so weird
So weird
So
Weird it is like I would expect him
And it probably would have wound up being smarter
To have buried millions of dollars in his property
Golden Silverberry silver in the divorce
Well I honestly if I'm marking bill I am saying that we also
I need to dig up his property
For at least twenty feet down
Absolutely absolutely I prove that you don't have gold on your property
Sure clip Bills going to mention that guy Baba Ro and
Number of the clips that he's been involved in because
Vols details and questions that are pretty hard to cut clips for into percent
So here's the bottom line based on Miss paases testimony
There's this guy named bobrow who was the person who Alex told her to get financial information from
About the company
He was working with Alex and Free Speech systems in a consultant type roll Financial Consultant
Prior to that he had been working for pqp are the company that's basically owned by Alex's family with
Free Speech system has 50 million dollars or whatever this guy and Alex are the primary source
Sources of information as it relates to finances for Paws
In this deposition which Bill touches on here
And I think
It's Timmy
It's weird
Just for the benefit of the
Are you with a
Read it
The spider web
Trust
And
Secured beneficiaries
City Aries
We're holding,
It's just a wafer
File lawsuit
No I don't agree
Okay why they sent up this way
I don't know why it was set up this way
It was set up to
Protect
Asset
I don't know why it was set up I don't think it was in relationship
This lawsuit has a zyto
Spider earlier the
Trust
Anahi
That structure
Of the companies was in motion prior to the Lost
And you got that from Robert
Mr. Rowe mr. Jones
EXO
The individual who
Work for one company
Switched over work for another
Secured debt to one another
With the sole proprietor being a 72
Fishy Airy
Repair
Please down
You trusted him and you trusted mr. Jones the sole proprietor of a company
Is the subject of
A number of defamation lawsuit
Involving parents who lost children in a school shooting
44 years
Then went on to say that
It didn't happen or it did but
There was a government
Spira seeing all of this other
That those are the two people you trust it
Correct
Those are the people with the information so yes
You think it's odd that they
Somebody for this topic.
0 funny
I can't answer that I don't know
I wouldn't answer that either
Does look a little bit suspicious would surprise her
Not much just flappable
Norm just said show up in Texas and you're like f*** yeah 30 grants great
Would it surprise you to learn that the person that you are here as a corporate representative for believes
But his enemies are demons that sounds about right
So the question comes up and I think this is a pretty
Relevant question that's a bills gotten that is basically
Okay so if we look at these pallets sheets here
How the
Buck does
Good any bills get paid
What's going on
Based on this balance sheet how is mr. Jones covering his bills every month
How is Free Speech systems covering their bills every
So there are so there's income that
BF
That Free Speech makes off of the
Relationship with
Uprb of the sales
Pqp are also pays
Money to free speech
For advertising
On the website
That includes the banners and such
So that's
And so essentially the way that the business makes money is
Is those two primary ways
Okay
Let's look at the balance sheet
Provided
Okay
The balance sheet
Is for all the 20
Crack Enter Sandman
That's what it says
Okay
And
Can you tell me where
The income is
The Infowars makes from pqp are forever
I don't know if this is
Not a specific line item I know that
There are
There are line items
That was not a real answer help I think she goes on to speculate that maybe one of the redacted columns
1 rodak Circle
The organization exists in such a way that
Alex makes money
By taking a cut of the things that are sold through his business by pqp are
Nmp couper advertising on his show
Or on his website buying the banner ads
Advertising money for himself and his parents
Circular
It's some
Well I mean it's only it's just designed specifically to do the one
One thing that it's doing poorly right now
You know yes that's what it's doing
And it's doing such a bad job of it that when she went to ask for more information to clarify
Five things
It only made it more obvious how
What they were trying to do is fairly easy to
Hide a little bit better I would hope so
I trust this is all rich people hide their money via shittily then it's clear
Merely that they just can't afford to own the entire legal system
Because I feel like it this is how it works I can spend a weekend and every Beezus would be bankrupt to
Tomorrow
Quite honestly I think that setting things up like this there's nothing illegal about it it's just
So it's just recognizing that like oh you have this bizarre maze
Of entities that you and your parents own right that are meant to
Make transactions more complicated than they need to be
That isn't bad to prove some kind of malfeasance on top of it
I think that that is
Where the confidence comes from right and
I don't know is any specific
Malfeasance has been demonstrated but I don't know I don't know if it'd be too difficult given the
You know the obvious or the nature of the interconnectedness of these entities
It's not surprising that she was asked if they'll she had no prior Financial experience
Evidence of a crime but if there is I don't think it'd be hard to figure out boy so
We'll keep our eyes on that is holding the murder weapon and who had a motive and who did the crime so will
We'll see if we can figure it out sure
Do this another document comes up that hasn't been
I've given to the plaintiff's this is a mess
Schedule C
Put your review
Nautica
Complete tax
That's what the document is Schedule C of the Galaxy's taxes
Is not a finalize
Schedule C
Has not been filed with the internal revenue
But the witness relied on it for her testimony right now
I don't understand where the
Miscommunication is on my end
I don't know why
She's testifying that she realized she has the same numbers
How do you know
Have you seen it
Okay why isn't it
Why are we not priests
Right now
Do you want to continue with the doctors are
I'm literally giving you
A life
To try just fix it if you haven't handed over if not
We can cure it now
But if that's if your response is
File your motion or
Would you like to continue then I will
Donation
It's an explanation
It's not Anna
Excuse
Since the day I got on this case
I have been
Working
Round the Clock
Get the product
Verified
Documents
You have been
Provided with
AR
Pulling complete.
As an example
I realized when I saw the profit-and-loss in the balance sheet
Did it had not been produced because of
Differences in opinions on
The definition of Finance
Statement
I said OG surprise surprise
Because I guess
Invocation is
Brad Reeves
Is a liar or has a
Cool boy cowboy Marcos golf Brad and checked on this
Love that that is that is the perfect time that is the perfect. He's known it he's had that
Pocket for a while now waiting for just the right moment for him to just
Brad Bradbury says you're full of s*** by the way I think it's probably because it would not have come up
Of the deposition itself
She broached that subject again exactly what she did
And now it's great
This is a mess that is a total mess straight up
F****** Matlock ass down home country lawyer s*** is not an excuse
Is an explanation
Bright I take responsibility for what I do
Now
But it's everybody else's fault
Yeah so they need to
Shelves
Discussion to financial stuff
Because they are there is no situation where should this is not going
We're going into a very non productive territory drama that
It happens because Miss pause brings out her notepad and
Under Texas rules Texas law
If you're using a notepad to consult with when you're at a deposition it becomes evident yes
She brought up
A notepad that maybe she didn't want as evidence
And maybe some of it included notes on privileged information with her lawyer and attorney
Texas
Does Not Your Privilege is not protected if it's something that is a notepad that is
I used to consult during a deposition
And so they have a big argument about this and weather
Just asked you to work in a state that you've never worked in before does that surprise you finally
Yeah it sucks
Is for sure
I believe that spiritually
Pink or just kind of like
A good Cota little rap-up
First one is just a demonstration of how
Narcissistic Alex's or
This was a conversation I had with mr. Jones about
Using 4chan
Material
From which to draw
And Mr Jones's
Keep he
He is Rasika
The after that I talked a lot about pizzagate
An operative on 4chan and it's mister
Jones is a
Opinion
Is that
4chan
Is
That people purposely sometimes
Post
Information on there
For the
Purpose of misleading
And he used pizzagate as an example but
His
Position was he what didn't realize that
But after pizzagate mr. Jones realize for Chandler
It's not reliable
Well not that it wasn't reliable but that I think he thinks that people are
People associated with
Certain entities are posting things on there to try to
Like a breadcrumb to get him to pick up on base
So I think that that was the
Sum and substance
Cancel that part of our car
What entities
The Democratic Party
Any other
People that he
Things Are
Trying to spread method
Animation
Okay yeah so Alex believes that the global is there trying to trick him with posts on 4chan in order to get him
Time to cover stuff
Yep ohmygod allowed in a deposition
For the world to here
I mean
Amazing interesting
Thing to imagine that he thinks it's because it's
It's outrageously
Detached from reality it is the state of position of free speech
Future systems that everyone is out to get us the government everyone every
As a company stated position that Alex Jones believes
The globalists are trying to plant stories item
Apologies
So we've been we've been through a lot here we've heard a fair amount of
Bad stuff review
From massage her performance in these two days of deposition she is giving us a review of her
Performance we're getting the kit Daniels cause moment okay here we go
With
With how this Depp has gone
How do you think
Pictures of pretty good
Wow
Wow so they filed a motion obviously
And on April 1st the order came down from the court and in addition to the other pass
Corporate representative testimonies that were just a disaster here is what the court said about this
One in particular
Quote on February 14th and 15th 2022 defendants presented Brittany paws as the designated
Both the Sandy Hook and Fontaine cases
A review of the deposition transcript shows the defendants flagrantly disobeyed the Court's order in preparing this pause
As a result she was unable to give a good testimony on any of the topics
Plaintiffs is now faced 59 appearances a corporate positions on the issues at the heart of their claims despite everywhere
Remedial action taken by the the court including the severe sanction of default and over 200,000
Dollars accumulative attorneys fees
So that was the description pretty good
145 is the Mendoza Line
So over 5
I'm telling you you're still getting pushed back down baseball tonight
Align
As a result of this obviously Something's Happened
And so I'm going to read to you here just from the court
Filing of the findings
In response to this
In addition to obviously in the context of all the other corporate representative
Don't know how to get to to
Police thwarted the legitimate Discovery process in these cases
The egregious missing repetitiveness of defendants obstruction exhibits a disregard for and disrespect of the integrity
Free of this court in our judicial system
Discovery of facts necessary to properly present their claims for damages has been irreparably
Prejudiced in virtually all respect
Absence of erection from this court defendants will ultimately profit from their sabotage of the discovery process
The court therefore orders that one
Pursuant to rule 215b Wanda Court disallows any further Discovery by descendants
Any obligation of the plaintiffs to respond to any pending Discovery is terminated
So they don't have to respond to any request Lovett document started
Depositions
Howard literary in a place where it's like shut up shut up
To pursuant to rule 215b to the court orders that defendants she'll pay all of the expenses of the
Discovery and taxable court costs in these lawsuits
Play Just Joel submit evidence setting forth any court cost expenses or attorneys fees relating to Discovery or Discovery motion
Accepting those amounts with their already awarded and any prior order of the Court defendants May object to the amount within 7
7 days after planting smiling
Yeah that's a lot of money
Pursuant to rule 215b 3
The court orders the designated facts shall be taken to be established for the purposes of the action
Specifically the jury will be instructed that any factual dispute relating to the following topics will be taken as established in faith
Favor of the plaintiffs
Sourcing and research for the videos described in plaintiff's petitions
Individuals involved in the production of the videos described in plaintiff's petition
Internal editorial discussions regarding Infowars coverage of the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting
The company's knowledge of the plaintiff
The audience reach of the videos described in plaintiff's petitions
The documents produced by the company in response to plaintiff's Discovery request
Efforts made by the company to preserve potential evidence
And
The companys business structure and relationship with other parties
That's
Everything
Pretty much everything that the corporate representative testimony was designed to get like
The deposition was meant to write
Give them an opportunity to testify on behalf of the company
To explain these things provide evidence
Yeah because of their complete we mentioned some of this a little bit before I pass episode
Some of these sanctions that they've been hit with what like
Because of theirs because of this
What we just went over
They are now not able to make any claims that contradict
I mean about all of these a she really does
Abby
The summary judgment is f*****
You know I'd like that's crazy I can't believe that would ever happen but
Did this is essentially saying
The plaintiff
Are right
In everything that they say
And the defense has abrogated their ability to defend themselves so just believe
The plaintiffs tell you it's it's that you had every opportunity to raise objection to stuff and provide
Add evidence
You are not going to be able to grandstand on this b******* in court that you've refused to cooperate with the process if
You if your intention is to like say
Oh yes sources for these videos let's say for example
Call and play these games throughout the entire Discovery process
And then you end up in in
Court
For the damages lawsuit and you're like
I've got this sort of the sources action that actually it's not from their objection your honor
You don't want
Like Alex
Being able to do whatever sort of game he might be wanting to play I mean I think I think it's
It's necessary a couple years ago
Probably because we never would have because we you just don't think that somebody would take it this far
So you didn't do it a couple of years ago
And then you didn't do it last year cuz you like there's no way they can take it this far
And now here we are
I mean this isn't this is a court saying f***
You somewhat I think there is some value in giving people the opportunities to real
We make the case against themselves sure
And I think that has been done quite well in the course of this I mean like
In terms of
You know these things that they're not allowed to let's say
Dispute
Court
The
It would be like
You'd say hey I don't know if that's right
If this hadn't all happened
Do you know m
The people who disagree with that like people who
No follow Alex and piggy gets a by the court to believe anything anyway
I think it's due diligence to like walk through the process of not cooperating and all this
To get a point where the punishment fits the behavior
Alright I'm just headed back to the Newsradio references a lot lately but this is just
That judge saying you have exhaustively proven that this is a box full of junk congratulations
And it's like I feel like that's where we are if just like yes
You have exhaustively proven
That you have
No idea what we're doing here congratulations and then they're going to say tubal-cain and it's all over
Forward to Alex calling Uber as a witness
So are we come to the end of this and I think this was a Who
Right now I think
For the sake of the chaos and stuff
Maybe some stuff people enjoy watching in that links
I just linked to the
The YouTube page of there that has all the depositions on it and stuff
I believe that that should be
Publix
By the time this comes out the first one is there the first position
Is there and I believe that the other one will be by the time this comes out
Yeah
And I hope you all enjoyed we promised the laundry episode you got it
Yeah no kidding
Website.com
Three times as much work as I have and that's zero
Go to bed George
And now here comes the sex robot