I have great respect for knowledge like I'm sick of them posing
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
All got something in my eye
Alright I'm okay I can blink
Are you okay
The office desk
My birthday
NADA just arrived I'm excited
Knoxville I've not unpacked it but it isn't
Quite a bit of time at the office Wednesday Indian so my chair is
Quite destroyed as I look at it is
A night we have this Amy's coming I mean the 45 degree angle
Is just absurd it's not good I finger my left side when I leave
What's going on with my spy
Bean bag chairs
Play I'm excited to get that new chair out Build It Up
And
Hopefully feel a little bit better or saying I'm telling you what man
Lower back
Appreciate that
My bright spot
Is everything everywhere all at once
The movie finally saw it
F****** as good as they say that's what I've heard it's fantastic people say it's good and then I've heard other people say it's as good as people say
As good as
People say
But it's also really really great
Michelle yeoh
Incredible
Greatest incredible I don't see a lot of movies
Hover-1 that I I need to get to round two
What great
Yeah
I'm glad you enjoyed it bright spots achieve
Jordan today we come
To the show in a little bit of a difficult position because of
News about the school shooting in Texas
I made a bit of an executive decision and that is that
We're not going to be talking
About Alex and his coverage of that till at least
East Monday
Because
It's it's difficult
To to say exactly
Listen to words but
I feel like they're too
Two primary objectives of the show
Is to analyze deconstruct
The
Narratives and the false reality that's perpetuated by Alex the sources of it
The sources of his worldview is ideology a lot of the same
Happy communist bulshit
That stuff
Is very important
But the second goal really is to not
Do things
Things that are not in
In service of the audience
And I don't
Feel like there is such a rush
To get to this
I'll bet it over comes the the
Sort of difficulty that people are feeling and
And how it would be exacerbated by listening to Alex's
Horrible Bosses
Should about it
So we're going to put that on
The back burner but we will eventually cover his immediate response
And
Do that next week it's nice that you can make executive
Decisions unilaterally mainly just because my opinion is so predictable
Like you didn't really need to bring that to me we didn't need to discuss about similar things in the past
But like you know there is not really a
Like
Pressing a news cycle for
Us necessarily we can
Allow things to be until
Aspect of it is the emotional
And the charge of it at the moment
Aquarium
This case in particular has really Illustrated
The
The difficulty of
Nailing down FAQ
In the immediate
Every hour it seems like there's a new p
Piece of information every hour it seems like there's something somebody is not been
Completely honest about
Or any number of
Difficult
That
We should not be grappling with
Until we have the totality of that. Pretty difficult well
A lot of information
And it's shifting around
Is it the people are
Still trying to figure out what's going on in short we don't f*** with the wet cement that's not all right that's not Arthur
It doesn't help
So we'll have a different
Episode
Today but first let's say hello to some new folks
The first
McDonald's policy walk
Alex Alex's dog is Bones
Thank you very much
Wally seapunk thank you so much you and I apologize
Darian is from Emma happy birthday this actually is a little bit late
Your birthday is on the 19th but I hope you had a good one
You're not about to
Happy birthday thank you very much is a lot sooner than we're used to it that's great
Next Nico couldn't think of anything funny to say thank you so much right now policy walk
Thank you very much that's non-dairy call it a sorbet thank you so much
Thank you very much what about a sharp
That reminds me of
Amazon Jack Baker's lactose intolerance
Closer
And I can't remember his line for it
He did it
Is Eddie got a bigger laugh and then he kept doing it and made fun of me for giving him the bigger last tag
Mad and to this day
I will Lord it over him
As long as I live
Did you know that
Great stuff
It was only like 50 people in Chicago
You don't even have to explain the reference
Call Souderton
So thank you so much to do be meddling with my pedaling don't be roaming around adrenochrome
Don't be screaming when I'm dreamily creaming
This is bordering on New World ordering thank you so much you are now a technic
I'm a policy wonk
I have
Risen above
Miami
A list for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I mean
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe later on WhatsApp
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Real walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not but we'll never know because never know but not today, because
Different today we can start this
This bad boy off
And
I am here today
How to do sort of an overview
Quite a few
Who sings and so
Hopefully this is
Just going to workout
And it's going to all make sense
You didn't say hi
I didn't return the hello
It's been so long it's been so long since we talked to Carrie has been a long time with project
Small and it's very Kerry Cassidy and David update
She does does a thing where she's looking at the camera and breaking down the news
And so much of it has just been qanon and like
Covid conspiracies and stuff
Where is
Space here are the aliens that's what we're here for right
Dog
Traders
That's what we're about rough Traders like Mercantile
Miners not minors
They're back on the team but they were on
But
Today update within the last week or so and we have an update on the world
And I am thrilled to report that we are back
Two aliens aliens are in
Play and there is Major news of s***
Well
It's actually not news cuz it's something it
Conceivably has to have been going on since like
The 70s hits news to us
That's what we got
Here's where we start off with some of the storylines
Has to do with
A city in Switzerland
First of all
What I want to talk about is
The role of Basil
Are Basel Switzerland
And the control of what is
Just called the right
Issue
And and why is
Centered in bath
Switzerland
And and
As far as I can
Until there's very little
Talk about this
At least in the circles that
I
Attention to
And I'm always Gathering more and more
So I have a whistleblower
On the subject
Who is
Very well-versed
And trained
As part of this
You know monetary
System that we've had
That involves
What's Wall Street
And and all kinds of things
Wall Street and Stockwell Street and stocks and aliens in Switzerland
For international settlements
And that's what's going on here
Settlements
He's up
What yes yeah that is
Abbreviation
It's like the central banks of the world
Can meet and
Sort out issues
Is the Bank of Bank
Subway
Okay
Be the notion of
What are you getting into
Is like
The bank of international settlements directly controls all like
Issuance of
The currency that's not
That's not accurate all the banks go there to discuss what to do with their Bank
This all comes from a pamphlet called the right to issue written by a guy named William called
Which is mostly been reported on by the raving anti-semite and friend of Leo zagami
Henry Makow
The idea is that there's this group called The sabatons Who pretended to be Jewish people but are actually evil
These people are the ones working
To destroy Western Civilization
And the world
More or less
That well protected.
Themselves
David I can spread some of these ideas on Alex's show in the past few years and actually is quite a big proponent of this Epic
50 yen
Conspiracy idea
What to say about this stuff
In terms of
I just want to put it up
Because the words are going to come out
Laters the Basel Switzerland right have you
Pretty explicitly crypto anti-semitic ship
That is a turn I did not
Expect them to
To take whenever it's like hey you know guys anti-Semitism is wrong
I didn't expect him to just be like haha
Now what if we
We just say they weren't
Actually Jews
Little twist
Kernels of this in a lot of places like with Ben Shapiro calling Jewish people who vote Democratic Jewish and name
Yep
Listen
We know we can't openly hate the Jews
Yet
But we got to get it out somehow man with just in a
So Carrie has a whistleblower on the
Of course she does
So I have a whistleblower
On the subject
Who is
Very well-versed
And trained
As part of this
You know monetary
System that we've had
That involves
Wall Street
Stocks
Nn
And all kinds of things
They have had
Training
In this area
And they have
Recently communicated to me that there is
I believe they said
10000 Acres
Where there are
Ascertain
Group of families
Come on now I Got It download
Asstube
The various eat
Erases
Is that are interacting
Bring it home
System on Earth
Recently
Play and so I wanted to
Wrap that into that under
Understanding of
The right to issue
So 10,000 acres is approximately twice the size of the entire city of Basel in Switzerland
The city isn't just the bank of international settlement
It's Switzerland third most populated city
Switzerland sure you know
And actually
Someone famous was born there
Basil
Do you know you don't know who it is
Basel Switzerland I should know somebody who was a writer
Who did the thing who is it Rodger Federer
WhatsApp
Your boy Federer
Born in love tennis
People being born
Fair enough
It is 10000 Acres
Or whatever
They control the control of the
What's showing on Aliens
Really after
Course
There is a group
TT races that seem to be
Vying for control
Bookkeeping
Control over
The monitor
So first of all there are the
Reptilian Draco
So I put them moral lesson
Same bucket
Graze
Around you know the
The Grays out there the various gray rat race
Report to
The Reptilian agenda
Draco
And then we've got those
Beings from aldebaran
That are
From what I understand humanoid
And Mike
Actually be reptilian
Humanoid
Hybrids
Okay wait
So they've got their own planet of reptilian humanoid hybrids
Yes aldebaran aldebaran
Okay I only correct because they will Factor heavily
Aldebaran is
Ostensibly based on what Carrie is telling us
An entire system devoted to when the Draco reptilians
And the humanoids got together and made a hybrid race
And they just gave him a planet
I would like
Stay on aldebaran
Maybe there's not concrete details
Manifestation of like weird narcissism
Multiple alien groups
AR
Fighting with each other over our banking system
Okay so listen
Alright
You have traveled several thousand light-years
Maybe even a million likes
And you are like
The Frank is not stable enough for me to invest in right now I'm going to have to go to the
As go the Euro so goes the governor
I feel like if there are these
What's a
Spacefaring groups of aliens
They do
They shouldn't give a
F*** if we end up destroying ourselves another
Species of alien
That ended up like the humans ended up becoming spacefaring as well maybe they'll hold on
It's not make or break
Throw this out at you
Let me throw this out at you cuz I think it might blow this whole thing wide open
Alright
Maybe
The only reason
Let all the other race
Jesus became spacefaring and we didn't
It's cuz we're the only ones that invented
Speculative current
So they come here because nobody else knows how to gamble like Americans
Counter-argument Maybe
All of these face fair and Graces became spacefaring only after aliens fought over their monetary system
Catalyzing Uno's Uno's
So there's these aliens that are fighting for control of our bags to the reptilian
Draco's
We got the aldebaran
Oh yeah I don't think the Raptors are in play well I mean you can't have Raptors without Mark Richards
Leaving the shop does actually come up later
Spiedino she hasn't been to visit
Sam Houston whistleblower
Yeah I guess
They like Chaka
But more than money and antiques
Jurassic Park world you know like they're having a great time
So there's other
Aliens
Then there's the Anunnaki that are
Ledian humanoid
Reptilian hybrid
And and certainly there can be more
For example
The beings from Venus
Whether they're playing in or not
You know all go back
Milira so that
What my understanding is that
The humanoid races
10 to go back
All stem from Lyra
The viruses
Could also
Have originating other part
What's the Multiverse
And
And then
Also there are the beings coming
I'm going from Venus
So these are the main
From what I can tell TT races
Just that are
Trying to control arm on a
System and buying for
Control over
I mean I guess we don't know as much about the aldebaran aliens from our from our journey
Pleiadians are good though
Yeah
Hybrid Draco
Right
And then the Grays are always up in the air
It's ya both sides in the past
Maybe
Ages for birthday I've no idea
I need generally here of them as being people who report back to the
The minions of the Draco
Reptilia
I like it our version of
Camelot we've built our own kind of back
Backstory mythology to wear now we're like arguing about whether or not
Tom Bombadil was the right spot in Fellowship in aliens that are absent from this
There are so many different
Right
F****** aliens that artist
Based on animals
Where are the cats
Underwater
Lord knows what time does an octopus somewhere problem
I don't know why they are coming in to help with his battle for the monetary system
I think I love
Brett
Of answer that you get for where you go for a well you know I think most humanoids are originally from the Lyra system
But they could have been from somewhere else in the Multiverse
Yeah man that's called playing the field
Yes everywhere it's basically saying nothing
It's my understanding from here but they could come from literally anywhere else
People are false
Awesome thank you
The aldebaran aliens
Important
For today cuz there's a certain things
That happened
At some point
Entire continent on planet
We didn't know no one knows about that
And I'm also wasn't
In contact with
Another whistleblower on the same
Subject that I'm going to talk about
About here
That
Basically
Gordon.
Talked about
I have
It turns out to be
Three other
Very substantial whistleblowers 1 is
Is Captain Mark Richards
The other is a
A very long time contact
The Project Camelot
And the other is this
Other whistleblower who brought
Forward important
Information on the sub
And the subject
What is
How
It's actually Bass
There's a a movie and I've talked about
Before
So those
Of you out there who follow my workers approached know what I'm talking about
So surprised
But it centers around
A television
Series called me
Event
Which is actually a dick
Depiction
Of a real
Situation that we're having
Here on planet Earth
To do with
Marius ET race
And though
Specifically
The race
From aldebaran
So the aldebaran
It's at the event
Right
So she mentioned Gordon Duff in there
I think what she's talking about cuz she's not so
Specific about this but
In 2013 Gordon Duff published post on Veterans
Titles quote of the little green guy book
Which was a guy to various alien races that is very much not a real document or anything other than someone have
Having a good time okay it's not official it's not from any government it's just a fun book with pictures of what someone
Would look like
It's like a monster manual it's the DM's manual my favorite of the races of the
Aliens in this is
Jeff okay
Here's what's known about my God don't tell me that it's
Jeff snow
Everyone's name Jess back to 1500 BC
They met with JFK 3 weeks
Before he was killed they also have around the same time at with other human world leaders they have not
What's up
Either they had something to do with it or that was the last
Straw for that you guys are going to kill JFK
Peacekeepers they probably wouldn't get involved
Open killing JFK
Kill the president
Also strangely
Us Focus
It's so weird
That was part of
The
Impetus for some of the I guess maybe the aldebaran aliens are in that monster manual
So she has other
Sources
The tell her that the show the event is real
To these people
That
It is
That all
The movies that they are referencing
Are all in English
Though no one else in the world made movies about a lie
That's true
I think I watched
The event
Catalog in my mind
Kind of the same as like
Terra Nova
A revolution like these shows that I was like
Man this could be this week
Post lost
Desire for something
I thought flash-forward a lot of potential to and then I hated it
In the finale I like to
It again
I just come back
And
What's going on with the aldebaran
Okay
The Story Goes that the race
Aldebaran
Destroyed
What
I understand to be not just one planet of theirs in their system but two
And they got into a situation where they wanted to come
And
Basically
Terraform
And and take over certain portion of our territory
And that a negotiation
Play so that we
Could go in
Two outer
Space
And take over certain
Planetoid
Or planets
Where we could establish
Colony
With their help
And that at the same time they would be given
Portion of our land mass
Which was
So I know this sounds
Crazy to there but this is actually
Something that Gordon Duff
What about
On Veterans
Today many years ago
So
Exchange for help with planet
Someone
Gave Africa to
The aldebaran aliens you ask
For Africa
I don't know I don't know if she has coronavirus killed the Clippers a bit because point out that some of this
Smaller countries in Africa were not thrilled with it
Hayward Consulting
Who do you go to what's the contact info for like listen
We got this big treaty
I need to call these off-world
I got to say
We want
All of China
No we're not doing China buddy this is the Earth
We don't just give chinaway to anybody
Alright fine we'll take South America
Oh oh whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa you tried to lowball us
Yeah I guess maybe they worked it out with the International Bank of settlements or something and
I think Africa
Librarian
Weird band with that is such that slight little bit of you know you're being racist when you just say they gave
Hermaphrodite in the story also read
Enforce that a little bit convenient way to explain away something
Right right I don't like the whole continent of Africa because of
Aliens
Well no it's not too much of that but
There there are some
Thoughts that I have
Anyway the aldebaran
The game 2 secret bases sure and then went around
Into
Did the Africa
To get back to the album
Deborah
Story
This story as we were told by whistleblower that has
Has been substantiated Again by
At least three others
Substantial sources
Including Garden.
That the bean
Wings from aldebaran
Express they wanted to
You come here
We gave them this land
They have
Disguise themselves as
Have some kind
Kind of ability they do look
You know the normal
Short of blonde blue-eyed
I don't know what you want to call that
Humanoid
Even you might
Call them the Nordic
Type of love
Right of the tip
Local Nazi but they
Seem to be able
How to change
Their appearance
And so what they did is they
Themselves
They there they turn their skin dark
You know like black
The black race
To blend in with the race
Is of Africa
How's that how's that grab you
Wait
Hold the f****** phone
Did she just say
Aliens
Created Rhodesia and then when they got
Caught they just turned themselves Al Jolson
What's going on here I am not sure but I do think that there is
Some connection to
Like explaining away apart oh yeah there's no way you can have a
What classic Nazis in F
Africa
Not apartheid right
I think
I think let me hit let me play the next
Text Cliff because I think there's some information that comes
Hear that make
Maybe like
Made me feel a little bit more
Along these lines
Toby same basis
Is Ben
Became sort of a place
Distribution place
I swear these
Racist from aldebaran
These beings
Cool again
Where
Kind of like Refuge
From another planet
Coming into office
Africa
Families
Exedra
And then dropped off
In South Africa
Where this
Particular whistleblower
Actually
Told us
That what
Happened was they be
Began to see
All of a sudden
That would they have population
That they in numbers that they never
Knew where that came from
And
They appeared
Kind of out of nowhere
In the immigration
Record I guess
And then
They would take
Maywood
Cake train
And leave
South Africa
And go into the rest
Apparel
And establish
And because they
Like the
Peoples of Africa
They
Got under the radar
I think
That by doing this kind of a framing
You're able to explain away all sorts of
Inconvenient things about hit the history of Africa
For instance
You could
Denotes a in the same way that the anti-communist folks
They have their support of apartheid is based on like oh yeah Nelson Mandela and
It wasn't about
You know like human right
Pushing communism
Like a fight for human rights
Text Bryce
The aldebaran
Who overthrew apartheid
Yuno and Yuki
Features of a small minority is ruling over another majority group I
If there's a whole bunch of
People that come in baby that's why there's a majority
It's
It's a mess I mean
It does kind of feel like what
Just happened there is
She described apartheid and then the end of Apartheid being
The people who caused apartheid
Changing their skin black and disappearing
Leaving those
Poor innocent White
People
To deal with the Fallout
I understand
I get more of
The aldebaran
They camouflage
Do appear like the people in Africa
So then
The so then it was the the white people who were just fighting back against the aldebaran
An apartheid was
Really great possible that could be an interpretation
The aldebaran he's we're just trying
To take control of places you are and so the fight
Human rights
In places like
In South Africa overthrowing those systems
We're actually the aldebaran strikes a control right
Things like the remnants of
The
Colonialism
In places like Rwanda
I'm sure I could take that as
Some sort of influence of the
Aldebaran
Right you know you can basically take
Cultural responsibility away from
Human actor
It's not there and place a lot of it onto aliens if you cause a problem
Do you like there's a little bit of that what I am hearing is that the route
Cause
Is somebody just gave away Africa without letting any enough people know it's weird
The problem here if that's the case I also think that there is a very very strong chance
The we are over reading this
I think that's our job.
Just trying to grasp at straws to make any of this make sense in the real world
In her reality is when she keep saying we
Like when she referred
We gave them Africa describing a group of human
So powerful
They can just
Give away a continent to aliens without telling anybody
Bear funk
Actually aliens as well yeah you can't get built love yourself in with my crew that's not you
I don't want none of this on my hair
What are the reasons that I
Associated this a little bit with
Possible ideas about apartheid
Is that she said that they came into South
Yeah and the other reason is because there's a potential time frame
God given in this next
Klipsch 70s to early 90s
I don't know what that
Actual number of
These beings are
I do know that
It's very possible
That what they're calling
Ebola
Is actually
Could be
Our reaction
To work
Addison Park
Campaign
Keep people away
Interior
And
This race
Hidden
Do you know the first case of Ebola was identified
Yeah yeah
Yeah resistance to apartheid was quite strong
Beginnings living up the beginning
A large
Push pretty
Overthrowing of the system happening
Well when it came to
No
It's interesting that you saying that it's to keep people away from central Africa because they're work Ebola outbreaks in central Africa before
4 but the most recent one was very
Much of the Atlanta
The coast
In Northern Africa Sierra Leone
Iberia just saying the Centre of Africa because that seems like a cooler place to say
You know like you're not going to say it like that
Maybe they're keeping people away from The Coasters
In fairness brakes were more like in the Democratic Republic of Congo
The other thing is that like if
She saying that you Bola is somehow a cover to keep people away
So they don't uncover the existence of the aldebaran alien right
First of all that silly
Because that would mean that
Exist prior to 1976 it has to be 76 on Word
That's the time frame of this
Have to do with Eisenhower allegedly negotiating with aliens
This is pure any other way I can't hear it any
The details are too like
Anna in the world that we're talkin about
These places where the aliens came and we're the same places that gold was sent to space
Come on
We're talking about people who have a list called eurocentric an understatement
Towards their out View
And the idea that they would know anything about Africa
Apartheid
Blows my my
So I'm going to have to go with that I'm not even certain that
She does. That's another part of it that's also possible
So
Maybe is a false flag campaign to keep people away from
Africa's video
Uncovered the aldebaran
But also there's another possibility
Okay
But there's also sort of a cat
Which is that all they look
Human
What
Is the situation is that
And this is in the movie The Event
Which is a series you
You can watch a movie
Vision series
You know you used to be
Towards the end
Is revealed that
Although their humanoid
Very humid
They act
Actually needed if
Atmosphere than us
And that they
Exposure of us
To them
Alters are
Rdna or actually
You know
Actors account
Poison
Which is
Possibly
Reflected in addition buckham
Pain that they call Ebola
Yeah
Okay
Okay so then it's even stronger evidence it has to be 1976 forward
Aldebaran alien
That is that person even more concrete thing
Yeah you can't claim it some sort of ancient Ebola then come back
You're saying that a bowl of didn't
Exist and we know that it only started
In 1976
So that was it
Disinfo campaign
Created a specifically around a certain purpose
So that
I don't know what to say
I think your sources
Is are probably racist
You just know stuff
You get near an aldebaran alien
You may be poisoned
Because it might be a distant for campaign
Or it could be a bowl
Well but Ebola has to
Exist
Because
Kerry also has some news to drop on you hear there's also a Bola outside
Possibility of Ebola
We know that the covid-19 people into vampires in China
Absolutely had to
Bob are people living
With garlic nails
But there's also something about the vaccine that size news
Pier
Now it's well-known that Ebola was a
Actually an ingredient
Or isn't ingredient
Up the Baxter
So
This story that I'm telling now does
Reflect back
Into the whole covid
Last two years
Which is
What I've said over and over
Again
A trans human
Agenda
With
Physically
Collateral damage
Where they don't
Care how many
Why people can't handle the change
They're trying to change our Gina
There's a there's a bowl in the vaccines
And it is
Coming in contact with the aldebaran aliens would just do this to you
When you get Ebola
If you don't that it just changes your Dino
Sherando wave
That these aldebaran aliens what
To happen and they're sort of collaborating with a new world order on there
Cuz they don't care it's all about
Transhumanists
Be able to handle it
Become transhuman and the rest
Now they may die
Who cares I'm going to give you a list of people who have put a Bola inside of a
A supposed vaccine or thing designed to stop you from getting sick
Mike Adams
End of list
Well
Did he invent the covid-19
Yeah so that's a
Yeah it's weird
Do you want those things you can see is like there's a lot of thematic parallels
With Alex
End goal being this transhumanism or whatever
There's a lot of stuff very similar
I mean in this context it's kind of it's kind of interesting to see the the way
Vete a futurism
Is combined with such an abscessed conservatism as well you know like
Do they all look at all these alien races the stars are available
Signing intergalactic
Treatise
Listen
I am not going to get weird okay
We're going to live
Same way we f****** do
Go back to the gold standard
Yes now that I know the
Best Infiniti of the Multiverse
Available
I want to go back to
South Africa during apartheid its futurism mix
With
Obsession with fast and reverting back
Yeah it's a weird like
Futuristic
Civil War
Convoluted
So I think we're
If I carry is right
Divide
There is this
Ongoing
Barry Zito
Erases
That the New World Order is
Is all about
Controlling
And they want to control
Space Program
Court program
Around the world
And
Right now
Centered in the United States
As I've said
With the opposite being
And
There are a different
China
Ascertain
The Drake Over
Reptilian
Are draco's
Probably
And
Then
We understand perhaps
Spider beings in
A few other
Beans
That the Chinese are being
Helped by
If they're being influence
So and you got them then you got
Icheat
Okay every Itachi
Race
That becomes
Spacefaring race
Creates
An AI
So then we also have nots
Speculatively
AI
That are
Influencing
The Earth in
Circumstances
Right now that are not
Negative towards
Humans
What does that's another
That we're dealing with
On top of our dealings
With all these different
If you racist that's too much to deal with man so we got these alien races but really all we're kind of
Dealing with them is before a I though
Cuz they're the ones orca
Castrating all of this maybe you still have spider beings we're going to have to fight at some point
Negotiate with the AI maybe the AI can help us out
The aldebaran are clearly not up to do not have good intent
Doesn't seem like it
Why is China being influenced by the spider bee
Cuz they needed a roll
Feel like this
Play the role
Administrator
Spider-Man
Yep so through the covid
Roll out
Bio weapon
And the vaccine with the fake and real Ebola
This is all a plan
Right
In order
Plan is and it comes back to the Ebola in the back okay
Basically what they're built
An army
An army of being
To fight
Any incoming
Threat
Especially Android
Coming from one Souther AI
And they are cultures
Out in the
Larger solar see
Invalid
So
We are
This is this is
She say
What I call a humanities
Program
And
Covid
Is very much
Part of that
What was 2.0
That was
The Cybermen
From Doctor Who
These are Android
Yeah yeah
Look I think there's a coherent plan here
Coherent
The covid vaccine will turn some people into Priscilla right otamatone
Mindlessly be able to fight against the incoming cyborgs Brazilian Air created
What is it
What do you think what is everybody think AI cultures are going to be human cultures but like
Angry towards
Russell Wilson II culture
I mean it's whenever a bunch of a I get together and they like started band International AI settlement
Absolutely I don't I don't know what any of this is
I don't know what I got culture is I don't know
What is it
Well I think it's both
I think all is possible in the Multiverse buddy you really did like that movie
Killing people isn't really the goal
Necessarily
With so many people in AI in
Can aliens why would you even bother killing people there in right Beyond
This is a harsh split from Alex's ideology population is the number one goal
Eliminating population
Is not as crucial for them
Although they're certainly involved in
Chinese very
Specifically in back
Mike Richards
Told me two years ago before this whole thing
Things started
That he'd gotten word that the
Chinese head
Decided they need
Get rid of
At least 500 million
Or more of Their Own
And they are
Still as you
Juicy
You know doing lockdown
Probably spring there
They're people with this
Versions of the bioweapon
Making sure that more and more people
Diane.
Get transformed in
This
Cybernetic
Army
So
So we have that going on
We got that going on
So mind-bogglingly evil in you just described in such a butt like
So what they're obviously doing is
Spraying people with murder
He's trying to bring down their population whereas the rest of the world
Is trying to create
Cybernetic armies
The fight cyborg
It seems like Mark Richards
Has his hand on the
The pulse of global affairs
Keep the spark told her about this but
Before
Man
What is she been doing for the past signature to warn people
So
The vaccine
It's kind of unclear if the Ebola is the same thing as the graphene oxide right but she's very very scared
About this vaccine
The graphene oxide is a
Apparently the same as like
The black goo
Right
It so there was this guy who was a researcher in the Paranormal world what have you gotten a Max spiers
A few years back
And Carrie believe that he was killed by the Black
Little bit of
Inside information. She has
What happened
To Max
Spears and his death when he went to Cypress
Then came back and was dying
I was at
Actually on the phone
With one individual that way
I was on the site
There
The time
Bentley Max was
Dying in the other room they were try
Call some help
Then
Doctors came back
Do anyting
They left
And eventually they came back to
The body away and they didn't allow them to
Take that body away
Instead they spent
Several days
Trying to
Reanimate
And what else
We doing a lot of black
And
What he
He was dying of
Appears to have been
Covid
Gas station
Or takeover of his body
Because there was black
Stuff coming out of it
Various
Now so it's probably covid infestation is manifested by the Black.
A few days always forget that magic is also real Arcane rituals
They were also doing black magic 2 reanimated
Travel through stars but we're still f****** cauldrons we got the ingredients
Come back to life youngboy
To what end
That's not an animator
Doesn't seem important
Got all that f****** dude
Long long predated covid-19 around that is the black
Is covid-19 forever or something
Cured himself
The black goo
Yes that is true
Biotics
Also like every old records is like black tattoos that look like Black Goose
What else
She does actually talk about that how it's like
The one big oil spill was like the black you eaten through the bottom of a boat
So funny it's yeah but hey
Here's the good
Haha
There are multiple gurus
Of course there's so many guys there's the gray goo that's the Nanobots right the gray goo where everybody turns into The Nether iPad
Superbad
It also looks like that last clip you know obviously one of Lovecraft books
Herbert West reanimator
This also gets a little bit love crap out
Cthulhu vile
Alex Newell
Is
780 contact d
These blue alien
I believe he's not living in
As far as I remember
Remember I thought it was New Zealand
But many years ago
And he talks about an e.t. race
I'm not sure it's if it's the
The same race
Or whether the race
Just reveal the information
But there
They were aware
-11
Black goo
That is again a i
That has was put here by Nietzsche
Erase to be activated on a certain
The point in our his
Which obviously
Happened
And happened
Beginning in the Falkland
That
There is
So this is embedded in the Earth
Under the ocean
What is n o n
Was always going
Time to wake up
And start to in
Our planet
Then supposedly there's another
Erase.
Is trying to stop a
But
It's obviously
Very successful
And then there is a a version of that black goo
Royalty
Substance status
Supposedly
Even deeper in the Earth
That is
Oh oh that's nice
So we got we got a layer up so we got
Alright then we got the Earth's crust
We never got the mantle
Strange Aeons
Play the Black
A few layers below that right above the core we've got the good goo goo goo good good also failing oil
We need the good go it'll pop out
How many moments
I need other people try to stop the black goo
They suck at their job or not
Not met before
I don't know why they suck at their job right
I feel
Powerless to do anything in her world
We can get down to that goo
I don't think so
Ugly boy that shovel
Then you're going to have to get through the other bad goofer
It's so far.
Yeah
Hot down there
If any of this is true
Just live your life cares
Does any of this is true write a book
Biafra is any of this writing science fiction book based on what you know to be true and then make some money
I live your life cuz you're not going to be able to make any difference
In the world of various Goos is almost paralyzing and yet at the
Same time comforting
Of being like if I lived in this universe that she says we inhabit
What would I be
Afraid of
Like everything could kill me sure
Right now everything could kill do outside my window there's a tree is a tree beer
Anything they're notoriously hostile to humans
Black magic spell on me right now and I would probably are
So why would you be afraid there's just got black magic and s*** flying around there's Goose fighting everybody
Tweets about black magic rituals you're doing
Yeah
It's
Silly
Update on the world with a couple of clips about some figures in the meat
Okay
The first is Vladimir Putin
How's it how's he doing with his alien we got some up
I know that Russia is
With us
Ace Program
Amazing
The Russians are also working
Group of E cheese
That
Apparently our move are more positive
Then they used to be
What version
Who is
Innocence
The Clown
Is not
The original
And it's a match
More positive
Oriented
And is working with
Trump
And the White House
Behind the scenes
And
We're going to see where that'll leave
Not leaving anywhere good right now also I think that you just prove Russian collusion
I don't know
Go back to space
Space
We don't need you down here on Earth
Is a clone
Is the fruits of
Positive aliens are the warranty
Ukraine
I'm not interested in positive alien
Full circle
Clearly the Draco in the reptilians are good be
Because Mark Richards hates them
Well I mean the Raptors are bad
Prince's like she believes the covid stuff is a bioweapon in the black goo in all this
And they're biolabs in Ukraine the Russia is actually going after an attack
A+
Nothing but
I mean the reality of what she's justifying through fantasy is is outrageous
That's that's one of those where
I do feel
Like she's
Scott that moment of where it's like
Either I can wrestle with
What I've accidentally walked by a space ass into
F****** Putin
Haha no no no
I go
All the way that we need a painfully elaborate
Elon Musk
Now
I'm not sure
If I mentioned but
Elon Musk
Is a
Okay so I have my own
Take on him
I'm in my understanding
What I was seeing
What's a cyborg
I believe he's
He's run by good
That of
Whether it's an AI or a group
Cheese I don't know
Outback
The most
He seems fairly
Positively Orion
But he did grow up
When was
Totally back
Bye
Our secrets
Space Program
During the time when it was
Completely
Run and dominate
Anybody new world order
So he has been
Position
Purposely
Tubi
Playing his role that
He's playing now
Whether he's turned against
Is
Sort of operators
Or whether he is
Actually
Fulfilling a war a role that
That they prefer
Play
And where that might lead I don't know
Cuz I would have said that he is the Avatar of
American white
Mail
Failure being rewarded
As the richest man in the world
Cyborg
Well I mean Bluetooth if you were create if you were creating something in the lab
To more accurately reflect back on America every failure that it ever made and what
What it looks like
That would be you on
As a cyborg that's under the control of some hyper powerful alien Rai
Kind of gets you around having to explain
His behavior
What that stuff is kind of like
We can still
Cyborg I do appreciate
The Absurd willingness
To bend your back
Over
To make
Monster seemed okay.
That's that seems like that's what a lot of this is I mean Mark Richards
That's amazing
That's loyalty
You know I'm just going to say this right now
If you were like
Hey
I'm going to lead to the deaths of
Thousands if not millions of people I'd be like Dan I don't think we can be friends anymore
I'm not going to explain away your behavior number to buy Twitter
Fair enough
So what if Musk
Takes us to Mars
Okay cool
Maybe
I don't know what
How where along is
What he
Ashley is
Or or not
So I don't I don't
And I'm not trying
How to install
But
This is what
You know you can't help what you
You see so
Then on top of it someone
Roach me
There was a book written
I don't know
They said 100 years ago or whenever it was
That depicted
A character called Eli
Google benchley
Pre-made pretzel
Mars
And so
I don't have a
Copy of that book but I
Just what I heard
Investigate
Find it.
Quite
Security clearly hasn't looked into this at all
Because if she had she'd have a much better
Conspiracy about it project
Publix 53
It was written by Nazi rocket scientist Wernher von Braun
Extra part do weights over nerve on Braun
Yeah essentially used his imagination to pull Elon Musk
Ask from
The Multiverse
And inflicted him upon us here that's what you're telling me you wrote a book
What is
I read some parts of it
I wouldn't say it's good Syfy
It may be sci-fi written by a Nazi rocket scientist
In the book The person who takes humans
Mars isn't named Elon
The office of the presidency in the Martian government is called
Vee law
That's the level of information that Carrie has on the topic
Precisely to switch
You get from seeing a meme or something
Don't if you sincerely believe this meant something wouldn't you've read the book when you've liked
You know damn well what the name of the book was who wrote it
What the connection
Elan is because
If you believe it has a meaning
It would help you
You understand what's happening in the present day
Is there be other information it's not like
That one p
Piece of trivia is the only thing that's important they're right so what you're saying is that
If you heard
Maybe third or fourth hand
That a prophecy might have existed in a book
That may exist
LeBron
About Eli
Then
You
Would go like oh I should read that Pope and guess what Carrie also believes that the Nazis could time travel
If the Nazis could go back in time
The Rockets
And then the Elon
It all makes sense
I mean they're pieces of something
I heard there was a prophecy
I'm going to be president
Fun interesting cool right let's just move on
I think it one of the reasons that people like Carrie don't learn more about the
The things that they're like they see like this
Is because if you learn more
It's Les Schwab
Actually more fun because then you'd learn who's my Braun
Right
This is got to be a learn
Learned behavior
That is is
So much
For you and I would be like putting our hand on the
On the burner
Proverbial burner you know I got burned
I'm not going to do that again every time they look into stuff they get disappointed by real
Happened a couple times and you learn like don't date too far
And then you try and explore them
The surface level of the headlines
Alex reads
You see the results of
It doesn't
Bend towards
The Alex peed right about stuff on some level subconscious or otherwise
People that carry probably have that intuition to
Best naat
Actually trying confirm things
Instead
Let's take our information from a murderer who makes stuff up
Let's take our information from
Weird monster manuals that a guy
Yeah this is totally aware of it it's just Skinner ISM like
That level of like I've just
If I don't look
Things could happen
If I do look
Things bad happen
That's that they'd ever have to be aware of that
Wow what a
You know obviously we've missed some of the alien talk
And I'm glad that there was a little bit of it
Oh yeah
Terrified to learn that Africa is under the control of the aldebaran
This is big
Earthshatter I mean well I mean it's at least
One-seventh of Earth
Shattered
How does that affect
How we would go about our lives
Somebody
And not some but I mean I'm not talkin about specifically like a person although I assume
Could be a personal first
Could just be like okay
Aldebaran
You guys are dumb
You get Africa
We got to help us with space, but I mean like you can't just say you get Africa
Sprite the who did that
The fact that somebody somebody is conceivably has my power is or shatter
Explored the idea that the Chinese are working with spider beings
Is
Is troubling ever true for sure I mean not because we're anti spider
No no no no
We know we are into the spider leadership
Ladybugs around the house
Where is Ibiza
If I remember the Vietnam conflict
Anagen Beatles come through portals
I'm trying to eat people. Why there wildfires in order to cover up for the portals open
Mirak one time
Yeah that's what I was bombed close of the Stargate
And I think that they wanted to steal a
Antiques
Relics this is what covid really took away from us
All of our good conspiracies are now just like there's a bubble
Yeah I think the world is so bad in many ways that like the
The fun elements of
This space conspiracy staff
Kind of
It's okay it's Rob you're deprived of it emotionally-charged about
Everything all the time you know like she can't enjoy these conspiracies to mad because we're being murdered
The phenomenon
Trump
I brought in so much
Conspiracy ISM to politics
Overlap
Is ruining
Conspiracy
Air along with politics
These are more boring and politics is more destruct
There used to be like a political conspiracy had like JFK assassination and stuff like that
Maybe with tertiarily involved in politics
That lived in a
Space and the real crazies would combine the two and they be like all aliens kill.jfk and you'll be like well now we know we don't
I have to worry about you sir
And there will be less of that new age
A easy off and then it all just
Spell singular Turtle towards qanon stuff in
Blah
Now it's all one
But anyway we got a little bit of a taste of the old days
Delicious
So I will be back Jordan
Probably
Present episode on Monday
We aren't intelligent B2 - 8 Jordans
Not Uncle Joke
Nautical joke
Call back please
Silverback
Dzx Clark I hope you all have a dreamy creamy summer
The sex robot