Damn important
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Worship at the altar
Text Joe.
Which baseball today my bright spot today Jordan some me call this trivial
Some may call this unimportant
About ND I was a grocery shopping
And I notice
Something that I didn't really realize existed but I kind of probably did at the back of my mind
I got a leprechaun
About lucky charm
VIP
Sauce cups
Softcup
Disposable sauce cups do I understand
Yeah in the like paper plates section
Realize date they would just sell
Like a big pack of those from a restaurant
You have access to soft I figured there be an embargo on just civilians buying sauce cups
Why would I go to a restaurant
I love it I love to dip
Dipping is a hobby of mine answer this is really exciting
It's made me think like okay
I got this bag of that
And that's great I may need to see if I can find reusable
Of the
Exact same size like why not
Let's go eat somewhere
MedExpress cost
No probably there are some that are
Oh no
My bright spot Danny's I had a great Friday
First thing first I finished my hand tattoo little bit darker
It's great got a nice little contrast in there added some Shadows there and then later on I finally got to
Speak in not person but in audio with that socialist
And it went great
And what
And the stream exploded power in my entire block shut off right
Suspicious
Haha
Sabotaging your stream
Yeah
Without a hitch yeah you were texting me about your power being out and I was
Like looking into it and seeing if I can find an update for sure that there would be something
It was it was weird to me how long it took for anything to show up on comed outage map
But yeah
Eventually it did and then how long did it last when did your power come back on
Do pick back up on the Stream
Unfortunate
Well I am glad
While it did
It was
I am probably next time there won't be a Transformer explosion
Unless it is suspicious
Triple-S cereal stream temperature today
Last week we decided
It was not
Anyone's best interest for us to cover Alex's response to the Uvalde
Right
The time has come
And today we are going
Going to be getting into that
Here's here's the sort of syllabus of of things today is almost the bottle
Episode you could say
Inasmuch as we're just going to be talking
About Alex's emergency report from that night
Broadway 24th
Hours after the shoot
Oh my God
Yes and be covering that and then on Wednesday will get into more of thee like
Continue to operate such a document of Alex's respond
Tas mother stop
It felt like it it had a stand-alone quality
And see what's going on and then as we cover more of the time afterwards can see how things
Maybe develop the reasons that I'm giving this
Caveat is because
As we're recording in present day
We are aware of a number of things that it's unfair to Judge Alex by
On this day
Like in terms of the police response write a lot of that conversation
That is awareness that we have that we shouldn't transposon to what we're covering today
Correct and it's difficult
Sort of
Segment that discussion for once
Supposed
And obviously I'm not trying to avoid it or anything of that information was not known
And you can really only judge somebody by the information that's known and what they do with it
When they do what they do is close reading within the context
Steady it is given
I got hoes to Bringing whatever it is we decide to bring to maybe this is being a little bit
Too precise with things
Things but I think in the
The context of
This coverage
What is this
Monumental
Traumatic
Baby bears that
Yes so we'll get to this episode but first tell the second to say hello to some new walk
Atticus Finch
Thank you very much I love you
Next amplexus Satan's middle management HR assistant
How about
Very much from the year of Our Lord 2020 Rob to thank
Journal policy walk
Look Coupe
I made it on the show so you can spot you and I'll probably walk
Thank you very much and we got a couple of technocrats here
The first even better better muscle urinate
Thank you so much you are now it's
Play a Creed
I have
Risen above
Miami
So take a little break now
A little break e for me
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I mean
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Real walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
A million times he is not better tomorrow
Nununu absolutely not
In the evening
Central Time
And in Austin
And
Give a little bit of a caveat warning
Maybe
I think Alex is a little drunk
I don't know if he's
Drunk but his
He is not
He's not communicating the normal way that he does
I want to give a little bit of a possible
Explanation in that Lake
Maybe he's just really tired
I don't know but there are there are mannerisms that are like
This guy seems a little bit
Whatever we're dealing with it is an Ultra
State
Whatever the case
For it may be part of the reason he has Owen Shroyer co-host
Sing with him
Because I don't think Alex could have handled doing this on his so they went back into the studio to record this year
I have a strong feeling that Alex would for whatever reason there was a there was a lack of energy
Yeah that was that was there and so
Of course you need
Handles a lot of this
He's doing
So we start off here at the beginning and Alex
I mean I feel like this is a little bit
Weird
Seems a little bit
Height almost
Special Report
Gentlemanly
I'm on Tuesday night May 24th in South Texas live coverage Ted Nugent
Infowars
The most banned Network
In the world
There is like a this is coming up
Now there's a there's
It feels unnecessary struck me as a little bit like
Yeah I don't necessarily appreciate a Showmanship
As a
Way to get people to drawing your broadcast Caesar sting of like we got Ted Nugent
It is
It is especially a a voice that says get excited
For what I have to say about this thing about 50%
Yep
Yeah a phone is off
Jimmy Carson was
Announcing like we've got Ted Nugent coming on after this year that you're not far off
Yeah I felt I felt like we were maybe not I hope this would be
Not a good
Start Special Report video package thing that plays after Alex's
Promotional
Writing
And here's where we start the report proper
Central Standard Time
I'm your host
Stella-jones
Troy
Shotgun
Ted Nugent
NRA board member joining us coming up
In the next hour
Emergency broadcast
It's like that
Has had a mask
Shooting elementary
Uvalde
Outside of
Antonio
And they are now reporting
18 dead
Three adults killed
Uvalde
Too early to say anything but it's very bizarre
Spell laugh
Westmont
Killed his grandmother
The border patrol is after
Cool crashes
Goguardian
Hilda
Fable
And then they were saying he was
He is dead
Is Alex doesn't like doing these Special Report I have some really good news for him
He absolutely doesn't have to
The only reason that he's doing this is to strike while the Iron's hot
Impetus
The drove his actions immediately after the Buffalo shooting
He was going to take the day off and have a guest host but he couldn't resist the attention of how large the audience was
In the wake of the shooting
He literally said that on his own show on air
Royce White is a former NBA player
Martial arts
As well mixed martial arts
Ilhan Omar
Over here
Ladies and gentlemen
He's got a special guest
He was set to host today but things are so hot
What's going on
Very very specifically
Alex knows full well by this point the tragedies are opportunities for him and he exploited them to the full
Who's driving this emergency coverage obligation to cover the story in a way that serves the audience and
Inform people
And what are the big tells about this is that he says that the shooter in this case was supposedly Tran
It's just like a person who attacked Dave Chappelle
Both of these pieces of information are not
True but Alex knows the transphobia is very popular in his
Larger right-wing Community right now so he can contextualize the shooting that way
And he'll be able to fold it into his other narratives very easily
The person who attacked Dave Chappelle is named Isaiah Lee India's assist man who has given explanation
A action
It might be because he identifies as bisexual or that he was on Houston Chappelle was making jokes about the
These things
He also told NBC news that quote
Another comedian in the show made a joke about pedophilia and that haven't been molested is trigger
This situation is a bit difficult to parse out.
Specifically and after the incident the person he lived with in a transitional housing
Accused leave stabbing him during a fight back
December
He's now being charged with
Attempted murder in that case
There's a lot going on there but one thing is clear that is deadly is not true
That's just a narrative it was concocted by the right-wing media.
Demonized
It was very easy for them to do that too because
Chappelle himself kind of
After he was attacked Chappelle joke to the person who did it was a transman
Playing on the very well understood reality that a bunch of his recent work has hurt a lot of people in the trans community
And two players on that idea that they would attack
Back in retaliation
Or something in there that's a facilitated the ease of that to that narrative sticking and you can see it being
Parotid by Alec
Let's do not
The shooting in Uvalde started at approximately 11:30 a.m. and only a few hours later people on 4chan begins
Circulating images of a trans woman that they were claiming was the shooter
Intentional effort to perpetuate in a trans hoax
People on 410 do this thing
Kind of thing all the time for a lot as well as discuss
Daniel's deposition
About how he was fooled by 4chan
Slight him to miss identifying Marcel font has the Parkland
Alex is doing the exact same thing here
Fully Illustrated that he's learned exactly zero lessons from the lawsuits
He's been facing
Alex's timestamp this very conveniently for us and he says that it's 7:08 Central Time
And from there we can see what information was widely available for him to operate off of
There were multiple trans women who were targeted by the
The smear campaign
The first of them goes by Sabrina and it's
6:16 p.m. she posted on Twitter that she was not the shooter even going so far as to post new pictures
In the same location as the photo being used by trolls
It makes sense that Alex wouldn't have time CDs new pics
Set Sabrina post-dated but there's no reason for him not to be aware that this was a hoax
By the time that he got on a
There was a second trans woman named Sam who is targeted by these hoaxes
Most likely ways that Alex would have possibly found out about this
Was that at some time prior to 6:39 p.m.
A poor by the head of Gabourey posted an accusation that Sam was
The shooter
This supposed to be made by an account called the nose
Switches apparently verified account on Gab
I took a little stroll through that account
And here's the first pin post they have
Quote a homogeneous society is similar to a healthy functioning immune system able to
Detective Brett
Anti-semite race
Also their bio starts quote
Noticing a noses
So it's really cool that they not only following this guy but also amplifying their posts are they basically accused
Someone of killing Elementary School student
In order to promote hate towards
Trans people
Think he was talk
Talking about specifically Roman
Patrician no
By 6:30 p.m. people on Twitter were pushing back against this and amplifying post Sam had maged that show The Chew
She's not the shooter and in fact was still alive
The bottom line is that there is no acceptable reason for Alex Beyond are reporting the story this way
This is one of the first details he's providing about the story so it seems like it's something very important
He's done literally nothing to check in on it
At best he saw something on 14 and decided to run with it despite it being sued for doing it
Exactly that about another shooting
Answers corporate representative testifying under oath that porch and is not a source he would use
At worst
He's reporting this based on Andrew tourbuzz reposting know they clear anti-semite transphobe and white nationalist account on
Who's just repeating random s***
Visa on 4chan already
Again there's no clear evidence
It's that Alex is not learn
Any lesson
Consumers lawsuit
Hemet is hatred of trans folks
Far superseded does obligation to report accurate information
You can see that just from the jump
Sitz bath
It's like I understand
Worse
Then if he was targeting individual
Like the idea that you can't
I mean
I guess you can't sue him because he
He saying that it's it's just a trans
Person
But ultimately that's more.
Destructive
That's
Looking everybody who's trans and saying that they're a f******
Murderer coming from Alex's mouth he's not saying that specifically at this point in time but from his
His mouth that's what it means or epic there's a couple things to disentangle a and one
Cuz I kind of I kind of agree with you because there is
A broad Target that's being put on trans people buy this
This kind of cover
And the sort of
Vagueness
What secondarily Alex does use some very
Clear distinguishing
,
That make it clear that he is talking specifically about Sam
Oh okay well then
That is a pets that a person whose picture is he stalking
Yeah so it's it's
It's
You have both
Going off
And
I do I don't know
I don't know why he would do something like that
Can't imagine being
So committed to being
Bad at your job
That you do this I mean I I I just don't
You know
Like I know I know that
The judge is going to see that very informational as soon as poss
I have your friend
I mean if you see that now in the middle of what he's doing now
Don't you just say f*** off
VA does seem to illustrate
Like malice
Continuing
The refusal to understand why the things he did initially were wrong
Absolutely I don't I don't know what kind of impact that has on
On legal cases I guess what that will remain to be seen but
Yeah if I were him I just probably wouldn't do that stuff
You would think
He didn't then his audience would revolt on him he has to he cannot
Not give a statement about this
All this
Now he doesn't
How he does not I think it's a testament to how much
He
How highly he values his knee-jerk
Patriots and being able to express them
That that is something that has
A far higher value to him
Then
Big response
Yeah I mean it's hard
It's hard to
You know
I tried to keep
Center in your mind at all times but the
End goal for all of these people
Is a society where they can just say
Always a trans person
It's Prince people's fault
Whenever they f****** want
That's what they want
I think a lot of a lot of cases yeah that's true I think
When you're looking specifically at Alex's coverage I think it's easier to say like
That is exactly what you would want to do
Maybe for other reasons too hot at least because that's a convenient way for him to not talk
Absolutely and I think you're going to see even beyond the transphobia
It's going to be grasping at straws trying to find any way to make this about something else
You got does immediately after this
Just trying to find other
Rationalization
Here's the
No one is listening the death
Children
It's terrible and I have four children when I'm driving
It tears at my God
Kristoff
We have 40 plus million people
Dynamite
Do Your Love Lockdown from starvation
We are launching
Massive Wars
We have all of the depopulation agenda going on and I predict
Accurate up from
Last week with Plato about 30 minutes
Jones
Predicted
Mass shooting
Black Roshe
And I shed going into the midterms
168 days out
All the pre-programming is the terror attacks the mass shootings are going to happen
They weren't happening
It's so transparent how Alex only brings up these talking points bite statistics about food in
Security in the developing World whenever he needs to use them to minimize an atrocity
Spinner sex with something he cares about
If you needs to complain about people wearing masks
When he brings up the issue of people starving and presented as something that's been solely caused by covid prevention measures
If you needs to minimize the murder of 19 children and Elementary School into teachers he brings up
A starving people to make that number of children look small
He's a spineless coward and I would take this a little more seriously if he seemed to care about those issues
Relating to food access in the developing world when it wasn't something he was using as a shield
Do not address the issue that he's supposed to
Recovering
Hold on.
Taking credit for calling this one even though he made a huge deal out of how the Buffalo shooting was what he predicted because he said black grocery
I guess if you get to claim that you're some kind of a genius for predicting that a school shooting would happen eventually than everyone in the world is a genius
Cuz we all knew it was coming
Dipson the number of school shootings in mass shootings in general for a while because of covid lockdown
There were less massive Gatherings of people in schools were closed in many plays
That's
Plenty of school shooting center
Alliston Wikipedia include 72 shootings at schools
Since the beginning
Alex's premise is that they've been hyping up this idea of school shootings in order to
To get someone to do one because it's
The copycat crime kind of thing
Globalist
Still trying to incite
Stupid because they're been all of these school shootings that have happened that were typed up and Alex has no idea
Even happen
Bunch of them happened in
Does home state as well he still doesn't know
For instance does Alex remember that on October 6th 2021 Amman open
Open fire at Timberview High School in Arlington Texas injuring four people
I've never heard him bring that up
Remember that less than a week for that a 25-year old dude broke into
Do YES Prep Southwest School in Houston in
And shot the principal
These things because you never heard about them and it didn't cover
If the media truly were hyping up school shooting
Alex's
There would have been wall-to-wall coverage of the tons of school shootings that have happened
And most people in the country never heard happened
Because this stuff is just going to become a twisted reality
Of our born lives
As was true in the case of Sandy Hook the horrific nature of what happened in Uvalde is a severe threat to Alex's political
Audiology
And you can see that manifested and how he's responding to this with a scattershot strategy
They're already a ton of excuses he's trying to he's trying about
See what's going to fly
He's asserted that the shooters trance so if that works out for him he can make us about his transphobic narratives
Instead of about God's
He's blamed the media for supposedly hyping up shooting
So he can claim that this was a case of globalist Mind Control
Was supposed to be in the back.
And if all else fails he's minimize the death toll compared to the number of people going without food in the developing world so if he has to he can
Retreat to that talking point
He has a moral High Ground
Oh you're upset about nineteen dead kid what about all the people in the developing world without a food not so righteous now
How are you
It's really transparent how much of a threat this is to Alex and he's behaving according
He knows damn well that isn't the sort of event that has precipitated tighter gun regulation in other countries in the past
Sophia through full-court press immediately Detroit create new narratives about the shooting while the cement is still wet
Muca
Yep
Asus graphics
Imagery
But
I really do think that it's a one-to-one comparison and it said good
Thought to have in your mind whenever he says shitla
Because it is
Bucked up
But whenever he's like
Listen I predict
Did this I'm so smart
Predicting all of this s*** he is masturbating with a
The dead child
That is what the f***
Happening
Which crackers
You know what that's what it is
Is Eddie gets to just say it because it's just f****** words
You know you don't see if anything's it is words
Absolutely
Disgusting version of DeSoto
Absolutely sick I told you so
199 saying and it's Cebu
Boo Boo Boo
No and it's
It's not just told you so I would love for it to just be and I told
You so
It is a
Look at how
Great I Am
Right
Do we did this with the Buffalo shooting we demonstrated how he didn't really predict this at that
Grocery store prediction about
Shootings that we're going to happen
Year ago when the audit of the 2020 election
Was going to drop
To rely on
He have that the optic
Pics of that but he was working with
And now he's trying to apply to this even though the circumstances are totally different
Hey it's all just
Just f*****
Stop.
Nope
So Alex has another theory about what might have
You've caused this
This is
Just
Awful
There are a lot of mentally ill people in AC mass shootings being high
Sandy Hook Sandy Hook Sandy.
Music My Name by the way
Attaching yourself to me
In the news every day and
Well that's something I could
To do too early to tell there's a lot of blurred stuff going on as this develops
That's disgusting and almost inhuman level of narcissism but Alex is displaying
He's actually claiming the coverage of the lawsuit against him over his claims about Sandy Hook may have been part of the reason the shooting happen
I understand correctly people shouldn't
Alex because that'll end up causing coverage of the reason he's being sued and then mentally ill people will hear this about this mass shooting
I should do that
Is that the argument that he's making
That's ridiculous I believe his argument is stop hitting yourself stop hitting yourself stop hitting yourself
Well really this mass shooting happened because you're persecuting me
I am going to Abby
Views you as much as humanly
Possible and then blame you for the out
I really just don't understand
How
You can see things and insist there about you
And such a discus
Spring fashion it's it's
II
It's amazing
Not in a good way
No it amazes know it really at you know it is something that when we talked to
Jon Ronson you know he brought up that idea of like
What are we judging Alex
Based upon
Do you know like we're judging him based
Step on human society and he doesn't belong
You know.
So so he just lives by a completely set a different set of
Existed
I still go back to that moment we were talking to him
When you he asked
If Alex work
Himself
And I said yes
Disappointed to hear that I think about that a bit
No Jon Ronson somebody who knows Alex course
Presumably has some familiarity with him and I did for him it was a kind of
A deflating idea that Alex doesn't just
Nope no not off the Dome it's not brand new every time
The same bulshit over and over and over again
CNA
Comedian multiple times to realize do they do the same
Kind of thing ever
Anyway
Alex's mother about why
The shootings happened to her
Sure 12
Not enough know you're like
45th
Ali got
In place within the borders collapsing thousands dying
Every few months down there no news coverage to speak of
And now we have
Have this all I know is
Where the season
The midterms
Right on time to Psychopaths
Strike
What do you think's going on on Troy
So there's a lot going through my head right now
And
Let's bring up the midterms
That are coming up with
Just mentioned I have no doubt
That this is going to be used
Promote
Beto O'Rourke
Running for governor
Stabbed it I've no doubt Beto O'Rourke
Pretty much running a losing
Campaign right now
He can barely fill a
School
Auditor
Really not even on
Auditorium
Google classroom
And so they need something to promote Beto and Texas
Cancel this is about the midterm somehow
I feel like it's B
Still pretty early of this emergency Special Report
Words speculating
This has some connection to
Midterm election
I mean
Wow, talking about when we would like
Is our last episode Project Camelot one we're talking about the
The merging of conspiracy and politics
Like it's just
What the f***
Yeah
What the f*** are you honestly doing
Yeah like deep down
What the f*** are you doing
So Alex has been building up kind of this idea that there weren't
These shooting
The shootings happening
And now the midterms happening
And all of a sudden
So he saying that we didn't live in America for the past 2 years
There's so many different angle
Kohl's Alex would I look at that okay so
We had over 200 mass shootings in this country in the year 2022 alone 200 mass shootings
But only two of them and made the media
The national press and that's
The one in Buffalo most recently and then
Of course this one today in Texas
Asian on Asian or black on Asian no cover
So hero and accidentally deflates Alex's entire narrative about hyping up mass shooting
If they're bent over 200 of them and there's only been major media coverage of
Tends to make the argument that the media is actually downplaying mass shooting
Alex kind of realizes that that's a point that you withdraw from this conversation so he throws out of distraction point but he feels that shooting
Things done by now people don't get coverage
Again this is literally the fraudulent talking point that Dylan roof cited as being his radicalization point
Towards carrying out the Charleston shootings Alex
Probably stop repeating it all the time
Hawaiian
Has no idea what he's talking about here
There has been media coverage of other shooting
Things this year
I want to go also playing games here because he knows exactly why there's been more media attention as it relates to be Buffalo and you've
Baldy shooting
First lady of all the mass shootings that have occurred this year these are the two with the highest death toll
By a considerable amount
Second there the shootings that have particularly horrifica Eric eristics that make them more painful.
The general population
Any instance of Buffalo there was a shooter who is a white nationalist who set out to Carrie
The shooting is specifically to kill black people
In the case of Uvalde though there weren't too many details available when I went on air
Do the f****** elementary school and they knew that at least 18 children have been murdered
Ono's these Dynamics perfectly well but he's pretending not to in order to make it suspicious that these two shootings
God more attention
And imply that it is something to do with the midterm
This is unacceptable Behavior ashamed of himself for this kind of coverage
The reason I act like this is because
This story and stories like this threatened their basic far-right ideology and almost every level it so they have to attack.
That reality when these stories exist
At all
Diane Betts
Why they're sort of warping reality around the the way they are it's
Yeah
I mean
You know it is it is also one of those things
Square
It doesn't matter what
That is going
Going to stay this
I kind of don't even understand why they bother with
Finding
Alternate explanation
Supposed to
Just saying
You know what yeah it's guns
Fault but we love gun so much that we're going to let your kids die whenever they had whenever they die
Yeah I wonder if that would play
What I mean I don't know why not everybody knows it
I think I think that maybe
You don't
I almost you have a great handle on
Maybe the psychology
Some of the people who
Are more drawn towards Alex's
Swirled obviously denial is a state of existence that you have to enjoy if you don't live in reality
With the rest of us
Delivered reality certain amount of denial is necessary to make it through
What you're saying is a blunt
Things
I don't know if I could argue that it would
Dramatically changed but I don't think that's
A mentality that
Even a lot of these supporters about the show would sign on to
Yeah maybe not maybe not I think that is gradually
You know I think it's just something that we don't want to find out yet
You know I think they would rather not find out if that's
It's going to fly just yet
You're deep in the hypothetical speculation territory for me real hearts
Territory
Oh and really thinks that this is the midterm issue
This is where it's kind of like all right
This is a
Non
Cancerous point that you're making
The timings weird right I don't know if you need to be making this point
Tonight
Sprite but like
40in to be like
Alright the shooting happened
Politically
This is going to be something that
Democratic candidates
Can use
I think that's a descriptive
Kind of reality
I don't think
Vet
Necessarily
That's
Like
I don't I don't think it has a lot of meaning
I don't think that night
8 is the time necessarily where it has the most value to discuss
It's not the same as a lot of the other
Conspiracy theories
What's going on
That's kind of where Owens heads
And I feel that really it it goes beyond the racial lines
With this I think that they're really drumming up the mass shootings as a new story here before the midterm
Because
The Democrats have nothing we have to remember it's a midterm election year
Democrats politicize everything to try to get people to vote so I mean look at all the things they've tried they tried racism
They tried
The abortion issue they pried you
Crane
It's all failed it's all flop
So now they're going to try the gun thing I think that this is their next big push to let's find an issue
That we can
Use people to go out and vote on and I think
Now it's going to be the gun issue at least they're going to try it
What about the leading cause of death amongst middle-aged men being Fentanyl
Which is all thanks to the open border so 25 us
Veterans wedding so Saturday
Almost
Cupboards or totally sad for what happened
It's a terrible thing but they know Stu
Statistically they hype up Madison
And I put mass shootings Elementary
Areas
Crazy people going to go do it
You can kind of see the difference
The Desoto Bass perspective that they're giving
Yeah it's talking about the coverage that will happen after the fact
Alex's saying that coverage of things
Cause that
Easy there is a difference
I don't know how meaningful it is but whatever
And you can see you though that I think almost maybe more importantly these guys can address this new story without creating the
Completely separate issue to use as a prop
100%
Talk about the shooting at the cover the story by speculating that the Democrats are going to use guns as a campaign issue in the mid to
This isn't an emerging
A report about the shooting it's an emergency report attempting to get out in front of whatever coverage other outlets end up doing about the
The shooting it's damaged
Control more than anything
And that's something you see again from Alex
Where's you know when you're coming up with other things
Shooting in an attempt to minimize the horror of what happened
Hours earlier
I weirdly don't hear them bring up covid death toll is here but I guess that's just not the brand
Also there's plenty of media coverage of suicides among enlisted persons and Fentanyl deaths
Maybe there could be more investigation of the first one but it
It's not something people are just ignoring
If you really want to do this s*** I can show you how pathetic this game is really easily
If your interest is just in minimizing the number of deaths occurred you could say that there were 21 people killed here and yes
That's really sad but
Between 2010 and 2020 an average of 39 people die each year in the United States wealth
Skiing you never hear the media tacos
About that
It's a fact
But also not relevant to the matter is only bring up if you're actively trying to get your audience
SS horrified by the horrific shooting that had just half
Yeah it's like it's
You know you would only bring up
In a conversation about the Holocaust how many people Stalin killed if you really wanted to let
People know you are on here
Yep
So
Alex
He's clearly very interested
In the pictures The hoax
Pictures of the shooter
Course he will end up bringing this up
Constantly
The reported
Shooter
Has now been killed birthday said he would capture
Auto driving on a
You got somebody images of him
And dresses
And all the rest of this stuff
But you're not going to see any of that
Yeah I know I'm sure we'll find out more about this individual and it obviously the individual is extremely deranged
Just how deranged will have to
Define doubt
I think that Alex think
You playing it safe by settings the reportage
I don't think that helps
You reported him as the shooter not the reported shooter
You are reporting that he is this
Then you found these pictures prior to coming and you sent them to your staff
So when I actually think probably has
Some instincts to not dwell on the pictures that match
Maybe
He's aware of the Kid Daniel's lawsuit could be maybe
Good babe
To talk mostly about psych meds
But Alex
Is on the other side of
We'll never know the truth about all the pharmaceutical pills that this individual was on because the mainstream media is funded by big
Pharmacy you're not allowed to talk about that kind of those photos
But you know Alex cute here
Let's talk about knee-jerk
So interesting to do in
Complaining about the media making
Knee-jerk reactions because 18 seconds
CUNY jerk reaction
It's being made by Alex and Owen
The first is that Owen is asserting that we'll never know what drugs the shooter was on because the media is funded by big Pharma so they don't talk about
In order to make this claim ons to make the knee-jerk assumption that the shooter
In fact was on pharmaceutical drugs something that he has no evidence of them
Has decided must be true because that's his narrative about eunuch
He also asserted that the media covers that stuff up because of their funding sources so even if it never comes out that the shooter was on drugs
Owen can still claim to that knee-jerk reaction
Because the lack of evidence coming out really only
Confirm the power of the cover-up
How to make no further need Durk reaction where he's decided that this trans woman who was the victim of a 4chan hoax
Because he's desperate to take advantage of
Every opportunity
Did demonize trans people
He says
Let's continue to go through those photos let's enlarge those let's put those on screen please
Before they take it down
Alex is making a jerk assumption that these pic
How do you spell Rose to pick the correct suspect that there will be a cover-up these photos
Because the media doesn't want people to know that the
These ideas that Alexandra disseminating aren't just inaccurate
What they're doing is creating a completely false reality for the audience to understand the shooting Within
It's really f***** up see how so much of the babe you're there engaging in mirrors past coverage they've done that's gotten them sued
And I suspect the reason for that is because they never needed to learn a lesson
From those lost
They always knew what they were doing was wrong
Promise
I'm starting to kind of feel
Is that like questioning whether a lesson has been learned is almost pointless
Irrelevant yeah because they never needed to learn they know
This is bad
Yes yes they're bad people
Who know they're bad but they get a lot of money for it so they are fine
I want to start doing a one thing I do I push back on you saying evil
Only because I want to try on
Sort of wash that
From our
Evil morality continuous meditating top prospects
I don't know I feel like
I want to I want to banish that
From Earth
Even though something could be
Descriptively thought of as evil
Alex has all this demon s*** and I just wanted to make sure
Stick to science
Math science
Nope no ideas about
About Angels and Demons
Let me throw it out at
Do this way his behaviors as well as theirs are unilaterally destructive and hurtful
Sure
Now you're getting
Close to Stefan molyneux with University preferable behaviors
Alright
They just really like to hurt people
It seems like it's profitable for them and they don't care
Sewing as a as a suggestion of a theory
Nobody wants this
I don't want kids to go to school
With armed guards outside
Believe me I don't want that but I'll tell you this
I'd rather have
Schools with armed guards outside
Then a situation like we had in Uvalde Texas
Another
Incel
Put those up from the store before they taken down
When there's a Duda skirt
There's a dude who he is
And
This this is reportedly what's going on
How to show so
Again and again we have the range
We have deranged crazy p
Skirt identification is
Kind of important
Because of the main pictures that were going around
There's only one person whose picture
Crews were
Evolve
When the skirt or dress
So you can tell what
He's talking about
Pretty clearly alright Instagram picture of the actual shoe
Shooter
Address
This Sabrina was the other transpersonal
Who was
Misidentified
In the larger
What is a hoax
Plot and they weren't shown
Like there was just
The face
In a bottle holding up
And so like
This is very clearly talking about this Sam
Sam has there to lawyer Sam needs to get Inta contact
I
Yeah I know I don't know if it's actual but it's definitely the intent of what Alex is doing any pointing to this hoax
Yep
So it's a little bit of a baby philosophy lesson he wants to give
And this is just stupid
We have deranged
Crazy p
And that's the reason we have guns we know one right here
Is a.
Military dagger
And I'm obviously really love you and your great godmother
AccuWeather
But I got up right now
Prophetically
With this dagger
That is in my hand and I stabbed you with this dagger
It is not
The daggers
Bald
That this took place it is my fault
Weather
Carter run people over
What are used to baseball bat
Gasolina burning building down
It is not the fault of the dagger the
They could be the hands of a good or bad person
It is the Fault
And a psychopath
And they're just
Pouring out like
Well and that that's what it is it's the Godless Society is
The lack of morals and Society it's
The chemicals in the drugs
Forcing kids into depression it's the hope
The New World Order
It's true enough that it's not the nice fault though and got stabbed in that hypothetical but this is logic
Jake for babies
No one's blaming the gun in the sensor that gun itself has any moral consideration in the situation
The argument is that with easy access to very powerful guns the people who are inclined to hurt other people
So much easier
How much is basically highlighting that by using the knife example here
Speaking someone with a knife is not going to be able to pull off a mass casualty event because people are more likely to be able to and
Can you be successful in intervening
Further people are less likely to kill random people with a knife because it requires proximity to the person where I shoot
Someone allows the killer to have a feeling of disc
Like imagine I'm nice gun
We'll probably not
Be just as big a problem as it gone
This is an idea that I was expressed enough that the audience was kind of nods and accept
But it's kind of dumb and it's
This is just like
Kannada meaningful Arkham
Yeah I mean
Time if you wanted
He wants to make it a meaningful art
Even if they want to make it a meaningful argument than what they're really trying to Grapple with
Is that a male-dominated society produces a s*** ton of violin
Against women
And that the
Overwhelming
Number of these shooters
It isn't driven almost
Ultimately
Bottomley I'd like
Deeply by massage
Well
That is a piece of information the probably isn't known about this shooter at the time of their October
What about trend
Merrily along with gun
Another issue
Be the idea of domestically violent
Man I mean if you want
To tell me that we don't we don't get gunk
Control except
Men don't get to have guns
That probably would be better than gun
I think I'll run into some trouble there but I definitely think there's something to be said for
More oversight of people who have had accusations about domestic violence
Limiting access to weapons so that there's a
That could be done in terms of harm reduction from that front oh yeah but
Book tabs
I can't believe that the Democrats are at all involved
With anything that's going on
We've all given up on
All of them
It is who gives up
Do you still need a bad guy if you're Alex
Samoan political party so it's
The best man
Ghost point
Spanaway the Democrats
Our politicians but it is it's the Democrats
Is the Democrats
They're calling to take your guns surely you're going to be hearing it for the next 48 hours or all week long
They're going to call to take your firearm
The Democrats when they feel threatened what do they get
Armed security
Nancy Pelosi calls for automatic gun turret
Machine gun turrets
Outside of the capital cuz she feels threatened
School at your house
Or your church
Or your business
They don't want you to have a gun
You don't get the protection but they get the
The state
Bonded taxpayer-funded
Protection of firearms that they want to take away from us Alex
Does the same f****** to in these dudes play every time there's a shooting
The dams are at the Gator Guns just you wait tomorrow there's going to be confiscations single time but then nothing happens
They build up entire world use on the insistence and fear that a gun grab is coming right around the corner because I never
They reap the rewards of their extremism pretending that it's in
In defense of Liberty but in fact it's just
Device
That story about Nancy Pelosi probably isn't
It was based on a comment made by Ken cuccinelli to government positions
Illegally
Twice
He's an astounding piece of s*** who while Attorney General of Virginia was a proponent of sodomy laws
Mostly motivated by a belief that homosexuality is against nature picture
He was also the subject of a scandal at the end of his time serving
Department of Homeland
Insecurities
Brian Murphy who is the head of the dhs's intelligence Branch came out as whistleblower saying that senior officials had
Directed him to alter intelligence assess
From The New York Times
Second highest-ranking official Kenneth T cuccinelli ordered Mr Murphy to modify intelligence assessments
To make the threat of white supremacy appear less severe and include information on violent left-wing groups
Anti antifa
If you read the report mr. Murphy filed its really outrageous
Here's another thing that cuccinelli was said to have done
In December 2019 Mr Murphy attended a meeting with misters cuccinelli and Glau to discuss intelligence
Sports regarding conditions in Guatemala Honduras
And El Salvador
The intelligence reports were designed to help Asylum officers render better determinations regarding their legal standard
Bishop Murphy's team at the DHS
Intelligence agency
Completed the intelligence reports
And presented them to mr. cuccinelli in the meeting
Mr. Murphy defended the work in his reports but Mr cuccinelli stayed if you wanted changes to the information outlining Hi-Lo
Levels of corruption violence
And poor economic conditions in these three respected country
Mr. cuccinelli expressed frustration with the intelligence report
Antique used unknown deep State intelligence analyst of compiling the intelligence information
To undermine President Donald J Trump's policy objectives
With respect
Do Asylum
So sure
People who may be in favor of tighter gun regulation may also have armed security for themselves if that's
Fair enough but it doesn't mean anything
Armed security guard license
Stan's not like
Armed security guards are just random people
That someone knows who happen
Get a posse together as your arms
Obscurity
That's what it says about Pelosi wanting machine gun
I'm not going to believe anything that cuccinelli says without proof
But I guess that's enough for Owen
Raising assholes wants to Outlaw being gay said this thing
So it must
Be true
Also I really don't care Ted Nugent doesn't allow guns at his
Concert so far
F*** you f*** off
You're done
F*** you I will get to Ted Nugent a little bit later that's what I know I know that it's coming up and it's just a huge f*** you
That you're going to say that
20 minutes before
It's just
Why doesn't reality get a say
Not even like once a on the show
Percocet info
I know but like it should have like one little moment there's any like a little flashing light that just going like
Surprise Isabel it's just something
Just some represent Palestine reality into a back room
Ford Taurus is sold.
That's not going to happen no
A white the shooter was a crazy leftist
Another deranged crazy leftist
That
Story interchanging every 5 minutes
Just went and killed
1 people 18
Children at Almont
What type of
Demon
Is being chased by the police and things
Okay
I'll just turn into this parking lot
And I'm the one to a school until a bunch of
Small children
I mean this is all
The paws
And now
Suddenly lazy
The gentleman
Lauderdale
68 days
For the midterms just like we predicted
It's now happening
I don't know what Alex even means by leftist anymore so this kind of Falls flat for me in terms of how you even respond to that
We know that the shooter was a horrific misogynist and threatened to rape and murder a bunch of women over the social media app yubo
But that's not Behavior that's necessarily specific
Take to the left or right
We know that he bought multiple guns and seems to really like guns a lot
John ownership is certainly not
Specific
Once we were consistently
Occupied with gun
From the available information I don't know who be appropriate to try to nail down any political ideology that the shooter ascribe to
It'll be
Further as a leap to attribute the shooting to any particular political motivation
More information may come out on that front end time but as it's just making that up and ordered a lump
The shooter in with his political enemies
And honestly it's probably mostly based on the hoax pictures of trans women that he got from 4chan
That's probably what he's facing
Also you again about supplying that the shooting has something to do with the midterms
In order for what
Anything to mean anything
You really have to believe that he's implying some kind of for knowledge on the part of the Democrats are globalists or even that they
Cause the shooting
I want to say there was a lull in mass shootings and then now magically just before the midterm they're happening again but even though it is contradicted
Already
Pointing out there been over 200 mass shootings already in 20
According to the gun violence archive there were 692 mass shootings in 2021 and
610 in 2020
These numbers actually represent an increase over previous years with 417 and 2019
In 2018
And one of the things today is
Is kind of
Locating about this
Is the specific criteria of what constitutes a mass shooting
And so you have a lot of these
But in terms
Of things like the school shooting
Events happened in Uvalde
There are less of
That kind of an event
Perhaps because schools were closed yeah
4A.
So there is
You could argue a dip
Innocence
In terms of gross numbers of mass shooter
There's not been
I was just making up the idea that there haven't been mass shootings
It's because he doesn't know or care and acting like this is a thing that just mysteriously started happen again for the midterms
Allows him to get his audience to think it was probably fake
Without him having to take the responsibility of saying
Yeah he's got a proven track record so now he can just kind of
2.28
You remember when I said all this stuff I'm pointing to saying that stuff but I'm not
Saying it anymore because I might get sued
Although I f******
I'm saying it fuc
Who cares nobody gives
Alex does make it a bun
Italy clear that he believes
The shooting happened in the people died
So we do have that
Sure
But he is also playing fast
And loose with
Is this orc
Castrated is it a false flag
It's just that Gross Middle Ground
Bulshit that means nothing
No it's not the Sandy Hook case
Consumer cell phone
So Alex
When is hosting with him
And is
Drum that you've beat
Eating is
Pills
Psych meds
Can't Pharmaceutical
Procreate
Will you can go back into the seventies and you still had
Rifle classes
At the average high school
And you had high school students bringing guns
The school they would bring their rifles
Keep it in the locker that way
With normal behavior and it wasn't considered a threat because you didn't have a bunch of kids on pills and
Because
And and here's here's my fear because there seems to be mystery still about the whole Grandma aspect in the odd thing reruns way
Play crashes a car runs into the school seen firsthand I've experienced this from
Friends of mine
Where
They'll start taking the pharmaceutical pills
Doesn't even matter what kind of mean
Xanax Ritalin like there's all kinds of different things it's all the same stuff and I witnessed in my own
Friends group
Before
We're friends of mine who never were on the
Psychotropic drugs in high school
Never exhibited any odd behavior
We got in the college
They started taking the psychotropic drugs
Because the doctor
Prescribed it to them
College C
Seems to be a friend
But half College in Toronto
These pills now
And an attitude mediately I noticed
Destructive Behavior but what it is is that
It's like a tumbling a
So it's like they'll do one thing destructive
And then they'll do another thing and it's like there's
Worse and worse
What are passing bills to kill babies a couple weeks after their born
And we wonder why people do things like this
Real quick people are trying to kill babies after they're born I don't see how that's connected to this shooting
Is Alex trying to suggest that the shooter was motivated by anger but abortion
Or is this just a spiritual thing we're because there's abortions in the United States this evil has been visited upon us
Yeah it's just in the air
Stupid
Yeah
These numbers to other countries where abortion is available
The Derby shootings all the time like there is here
To save it countries where abortion is outright ban
And would probably be the most prosperous shooting
Complete victory in accordance with God's wishes and so they are protect
Can from all harm like a rock
So the argument Owen is trying to make here based on his experience
College is that the shooter was on the psychotropic drugs which apparently have a tumbling of
A fact where you do one destructive thing and then you do another
So the thinking here is that he shot his grandmother and then the tumble was that he shot up the school
That's a fun fantasy for Owen but in reality the shooter 10th messages on Facebook prior to leaving his house by his plant shoot
Grandmother and then chew people up
What school
Also there's literally no evidence that the shooter was on psych meds and you get a pretty strong sense that he almost certainly was not when you consider
There is living situation
And how unlikely that it would be that he would have access to mental health care
Also psych meds don't cause the behavior that Owen is describing
He just had a friend who had some problems
Medication for it
Instead of trying to look at the broader picture because he's dumb
Any need something to blame for this tragedy other than guns and domestically Violent Men
Answer this is the outcome that you get you demonize
Certain vulnerable communities you demonize the idea of
Appropriate mental health care and
I don't know it seems.
You know it's not it's not a clever observation but it does seem to be one that is
Impossible in America but
If you don't
Deal with the route
Cause of a problem
Then you're only going to
Create more problems
And exacerbate the root cause of
And that's what America is
And Alex facility
Exact
Yeah
There's one thing I agree with Al
And its meaning
But Alex does say that this shooting
Looks suspicious
The police on their response
Yeah I agree
Some stuff that's suspicious here
I think the suspicions that Alex and I have
Might diverge B sure but I
Just going to give that as a meaningless
We agree that there was some suspicious variable
They're Fair
The globalists have lost the gun control debate
People understand that
Because there are psycho
The pass
Like this
Is the reason we need gun
Is the reason we need to protect her
Ourselves and I'm sorry
Big Public Schools
Elementary schools for these demons are now targets
Just like I said
You're going to see a white supremacist act on a black grocery store
Because you can see the pre-programming you can
Can pick it up
You can see what's going whoever's behind it how do we predict that
My answer is lead are studying in this whole thing is very
For the midterms
Coming up
Oliver on psychotropic
How you take the guy for
From the Parkland shooting
Dozens of times he was going to kill people
Screws That Couldn't arrest him
Because I'm a
George Soros
Appointed
Arlington district attorney
And I'm not saying it didn't happen we're saying
They let him do it
Answer same story over and over again
What are the things that really sucks is that because of the police response on the way that the story shifted over the days immediately after the shooting
Alex is consistent narrative about these things becomes a little bit easier for people to accept
Whenever he's not feeling very ambitious it doesn't want to make too bold of a statement Alex will always say that the police ordered to stand down
Surrounding events
Like mass shooting
He says that all the time and he's always making it up but because of the particular details of this police response
He may be able to convince some people that he's got the goods on this one
Order a stand down
Not really
Italic
Not in the way that Alex uses the term
Again this will be more of an issue for it
Future episodes
The reason I bring it up now is because I like season saying that on the immediate area
When ironically yeah considering that this would have been the one time the Optics of
Of it and the things surrounding it make the argument of
Be what Alec means by a stand down
I mean
Maybe even more the colloquial meaning of a sand down as opposed to Alec
Texas specific meaning of a stand down
The cops ordered don't do anything
That is what we are talkin
Alex is talking about the cops ordered we don't do anything because the globalist told us to so we can get as many kids
Today we get gun control or whatever
Those are differences
Morita detailing
Butter shooter episode
All that being said I was basically wrong about everything you saying In that clip
Shooters are always on psychotropic drugs there's no evidence of this shooter was and while Nicholas Crews had taken meds in
In the past there's no evidence that he had for approximately a year before the shooting
This is the standard talking point a gun fanatic used to derail conversations about shootings but it's not based
In reality
The Broward County State Attorney is currently Harold Pryor but he was elected in 2020
That the office was filled by Michael sat
The Narrative that Alex is going off of his about how Soros is paying to get prosecutors
Diaz put in office
Will follow is
Instructions but with sap
That doesn't make sense
Absentee been office in that office since 1970s
Alex also has a talking point about how they couldn't arrest Nikolas Cruz because he had a Hispanic last name but this is just Alex being racist
In reality this is referring to the fact that in Middle School Crews have been
Vandalize the school bathroom
And instead of getting arrested he was referred to an alternative disciplinary program called Promise
Students who do things that are bad but not super bad
And make sure that their mistake doesn't bring them into the
The criminal justice
The system
Cruise never completed that program but the fact that he was sent to this
Instead of getting arrested for a misdemeanor vandalism charge
Has nothing to do with the shooting and has nothing to do with his last name
This is just a racist or real could come up with do we have a compelling story for his audience who are always hungry for races story
And that's
What is anxiety throws around a lot
Accessible
Everything that he has surrounding
Shootings basically is all bulge
Yeah it's all bulshit and it's self-aggrandizing
And it's
Contributing to the
The problem I mean you're you're demonizing
Neuro atypical people in trying
To keep them from getting medication
Your your diva nicety
Wide swaths of anybody who just doesn't want to
Old s*** tons of guns
And then at the end of it you're saying like we got to keep guns
So
Andrew putting more cops in schools in
Increasing the risk of a shooting and you're creating
Sphere where discussion of
Sensible
Gun regulation
Everybody's guns are to be taken
You can't buy a gun ever again
Yeah
Kind of conversation is more likely to lead to outbreaks
Violence
Because of the tenor of the conversation that happens
On Alex's show
Because of The Sensational ization of this coverage
The prospect of making
Can progress towards a better status
This quote sure people can't stay armed
Responsibly
And we make it more difficult
For people who
Have a propensity or
Are more likely to commit violent
Guns
I have a harder time getting it
Will
That the conversation surrounding I will
Just end up driving for my dead body
Well it's important to
It's important to look at the way that they talked about this
And if you think about the NRA
The NRA and its behaviors
Identical to
F******
Philip Morris or whatever when smoking was going on
Whatever we know if you get us
Any regulation
Contort smoking
Then we feel like it's going to go away forever so we have to go is
Crazy as we can
You can't
You can't smoke on a plane they went f******
Over all of that
Add stop because if you get
One little thing in there
Then they're worried about that they think because it is
F****** knew it well and
People
Who were actually opposed
To sort of some of those
Restrictions about
Smoking
Once they actually came into effect I think
Score for them
I remember when I lived in Columbia Missouri
When they were having an indoor smoking ban
And I remember I went to
The bar I always used to go to Eastside Tavern
Yeah you can smoke inside it was great
You know you'd get drunk to do karaoke
Smoke
And I remember being very hostile towards the idea of a smoking ban go outside
And then six months later
I loved by loved
Right right right I couldn't see that possibility because I was
I was holding on to my absolutism about being able to
Have a drink and a smoke
That's part of the reason why you do these industries Maybe
Worried about
Because people might realize I we prefer it on the other side of this
And and again it's because
Cuz they know they're killing
That's why they're so f***
Talking Angry in trying to stop any kind of adjustment
It's because they know
Beyond A Reasonable Doubt
They are murderers
Craps
So here's a dumb s***
Well and it just becomes really it becomes a media phenomenon where they just
Just picking shoes
Switch shootings that they won
Want to cover in which
They cannot cover this at all and most people have no idea happen
That's what
Happens with 99% of mass shootings
This country
Is they don't
Don't cover it and so nobody knows it
But then they picked
Can choose the ones
But there's one solution I mean
There is only one solution to this out
And that is you have to have arms
Security that's just the fact I don't like it
Ecology School
There has to be armed security everywhere this is just Next Level stupid
Like I wonder if I can think of any situation where there was a shooting in the US where a bunch of elementary school kids were murdered
An immediate didn't cover it
So we
Just no idea
I sincerely wonder what Owen thinks is going on in the world if that's something he's going to say with a straight face on this show
Many shootings well obviously sad and something that should be taken seriously are locally
They Don't Really concern people outside of a certain geographical region so they don't often get much media attention from National
Even outside of their news mark
A lot of mass shootings don't result in deaths and often there aren't even severe injuries that isn't really something that like CNN is
Going to cover
Conversely something like a shooting with over a dozen
Child fatalities at an elementary school is going to get a lot of coverage
An absolute tragedy that where wherever you live nearby or not whether you know anyone in Uvalde or not
You're going to feel that
I am a we grieved
Together
And let's imagine the scenario that Owens talking about
What's my agenda
The shooting happened
And and all the major national media didn't even touch it
Do you think for a second that wouldn't
Become the next Infowars
Conspiracy
If the media covers a story they're pushing an agenda if they don't cover the
The story they're engaged in a cover-up
There's no situation where response to a mass shooting will ever satisfy people like Alex and Owen
Because there are acting from a sincere position
None of these things are actual argument
There's a performance of the normal deflection that used to bully people out of talking about guns
In the aftermath of
A tragedy
That's what the point about armed security
Let School District had all sorts of policies in place already and they didn't do any
Get our police are on the scene and it didn't do anything
Stop it
In 2019 Governor Abbott signed a law that was passed to allow teachers to be armed
Created measures
The Jardin Des curity at school
This was after a mass shooting at Santa Fe High School in Houston left 10 people dead
And there was pressure on Abbott
To do something
According to the Associated Press they did all this stuff about hardening the schools because it was preferable to the alternative
Efforts to create so-called red flag laws to keep guns away from people deem to be dangerous themselves
Penalties for negligent home storage
Were defeated
Solutions offered by Owen and Alex aren't solution
They're just like the Texas government passing laws to harden schools to avoid addressing gun related issues
Alex and Order creating their own fake solution so they don't have to get into territory that directly implicates their own ideology
It should not
Require superhuman intellect
To look at an arms race and think escalation is only going to
Escalate problem
So if your arms race
This is these kids are coming into schools with guns
Wasn't killing people so I'm going to escalate by putting armed security out front well
Now the kids who want to go murder people are going to have to find a way to deal with your armed security outfit
So then they do that
So then what happened what do we arm next
Why do we give the f****** kids gun
It's only going to escalate
If you act like they didn't Alex see the end of Batman Begins
It's insane how you know he has
It shouldn't be
It's so f****** stupid
It is
Stupid it is all of their ideas are nonsensical because they're not meant to make sense absolutely
But imagine if you had you don't have to arm every teacher but
The teachers that want to get arms
Take a class habit
Concealed carry make sure they're armed
One time
One time a shooter tries to go into a school and gets his head blown off by an armed teacher guess what
School shootings are over with
Because they know it's not a soft target
2 Chainz are less than 100 people a year
It's terrible we only children killed
It was 350 million people and is still
Mystical anomaly and something there I
I thought like last week we were mad at schools because the teachers are pushing CRT and trying to groom
Students
And now they should have guns
We want the teachers who teach trt
To be shot with gun
And we want the teachers who don't
Hcr2
Do have the guns to shoot
Is that make sense
No
It's always really coming off is about the stupidest a****** imaginable on the show
You really expect me to buy that wants one teacher shoot someone trying to do a school shooting the problem will solve itself cuz we've
People know that schools are soft targets I honestly can't stress how stupid this is enough
Very dumb
Oh I mean it was imagine if a shooter was killed in the act of a mass shooting then they it didn't all the future
Shooters with no like we're not going to survive
Sure for one thing the other place that Alex and the crew always refer to a soft target
Churches
Do you know his logic one would think that the minute someone trying to do a shooting at a church was
Confronted by good guys with guns
People shoot up churches
The Sutherland Springs shooting in 2017 with stop by Stephen willeford
And our neighbor who came to help and yet there have been church shooting son
There's another one in Texas even in 2019 at the West Freeway Church of Christ
Bernard volunteer security guard killed the shooter made attack
And yet even after that there have still been church shooting
Just this month there was a shooting at the Geneva Presbyterian
Syrian Church in Laguna Woods
California
The fact that aspiring Church Shooters have run into our resistance
Emily hasn't made the dining of the dramatic impact own is pretending that it would and shootings continue
To imagine that a difference exists with schools
Pure Fantasy
It's not
Another thing to consider is that most Shooters don't expect to survive their toy
Many of them kill themselves rather than allowing
Themselves to get caught so I don't
Take care of that much if there's a good guy with a gun there who kills them after they've been able to do a bunch
Cuz really their goal
I thought these dudes are supposed to be against the prison
Planet Mobility Rising the society
Turn schools into army base
F****** stupid
If your argument is
Remember there's only 100 Kids Country of 350 million
Then your argument should be don't
Do anything
Not like because your acceptable already know
Police in schools
Leads to more kids being arrested for no f****** reason leads to more trauma all of those active shooter drills
Only traumatize children and they clearly
So if your argument is it's nobody
Then don't do anything cuz you're only traumatizing more children to do nothing
For the children were going to be murdered
Can you create more of an environment that sort of
It feels carceral
F*** that'll detector isn't all over school like it's
It's not
At my partner School
The day after
What happened
Did they have a communal session did everybody come together and grieve did anybody even talked about their issues
Nope what happened was every single kid
Walk through the door was searched
Viciously went through a metal detector
With question with all of this s*** and then told to go about their day
Nothing they didn't
They didn't take my proposal
Which AI
A pitch to Alex actually
And that is that every school
Room
Is equipped with a
The mine
I like that the teacher teaches
With their finger right over a remote
X
Totally yeah that's the only way to be truly safe
And even then you want to be able to contain the problem so you got one mind in every classroom so if somebody goes into the classroom sure you have
To sacrifice everybody in there babe
To keep everybody else safe so you got to have that
Sure
So dumb
So but like Alex what he's doing there like
Vertiv
Talk about it
Statistics
Really shity
You might notice that he never does that when it comes to like let's say crimes committed by immigrants
I'll take a single incident like that
Extrapolate that out until being the
The greatest alien society and proof that we need closed militarized border
What year when a bunch of schoolkids are murdered he implores you to put the numbers in perspective
Because he's a callow piece of s*** just trying to push his right-wing
Politics has nothing to do
With the reality of the statistics or anything like that he's an opportunist
Yep
These people are a f******
Blight
A f******
So Alex
I don't know if you know this but he moonlights as a FBI profiler
At least that's the sense that I got from listen
Going on
People just leave are being told I'm not saying
The story
Changing all the time
Dad
But imagine it has been a white
Drug addict
Video game at
I'm not bashing anybody likes video games
We're saying the profile is
God can't get a girlfriend
Has a girlfriend break up with him
Who is generally a nerd
A trendy
Who is on psychotropic
Agenda Satanism as got finished the Bell
That then somehow is
Spiritually guide
Kill children I mean why
Would you go
And do this
Why would you kill innocent children
What is going on in
Selfishness
True demonic evil
And the answer is not giving our guns up
When the Children of the name Oscar
And the children of the Democratic Party
And the children of the abortion industry
And the children of this whole church
Are out there running rampid
It's a surrender to say
We're going to give up our weapons like oh somebody
Be somebody for their fifth
Cut my hands off
It's a fraud we know it's afro
No but if someone created a fist
Gun you might want to kill people
The children of the abortion industry
Eastern Annex
So I that.
Small correction it seems odd for him to struggle getting into the mind of somebody who wants to kill innocent children
Considering every time he looks at his daughter he says to her
I am willing to accept that you will die in a mass shooting in order to make sure that I still get to hang on to all my
My guns in that closet over
So at the end of the day you are life is worth less than those guns over there just in case you were wondering
Every morning when we say hi
I love those guns more than you being alive
I wonder
I know
I don't know if Alex is current
Child is homeschool
I know that his other kids went to public school
Play I wonder
Yeah philosophically they
This should be
Yes but I guess I don't really care I don't know why I went off on that
So Alex still pictures of the
Trans woman
Are the shooter
Gets dumb
Well and there's a reason why
If you look up a pharmaceutical
It's the origins of
Pharmaceutical Farm
Ikea which is
Old Latin origins of
Evil
And so that's why I pharmaceutical snake
In their logo be
Because they know sorry what
Feeding you
Evil pills
Holland's Got This Wrong
Pharmaceuticals drive both from Latin and Greek and the word just test
To do with drugs
One thing it's interesting those when you look at the Greek root words
Because in Greek
You have the word pharmakeia
Which can be translated as a poisoner
A sorcerer
Just because the word pharmakon
Is a bit of a catch-all meaning things
From drugs
The poison
Dispels an enchantment
Exist within live and where the word pharmacia can mean both killing or harming medicines
A magical potion
The belief is that this word is based on something that predates Greek
And there's a phenomenon among archaic languages where the words for like poison and medicine or off
I'm the same
Differentiated by context
Austin surrounding word
It's not super uncommon
These languages
He's going to be
There is a ton of words for evil in Latin and Greek
Depending on what sort of
Evil you're talking about but pharmakeia is not one of them
Also snakes aren't the symbol of medicine because of some connections
Evil
There's a
Referring to two symbols that are often used to denote medicine
The caduceus and the rod of it
Sleepiest
The first one is a snake coiled around a pool and the other one is the two snakes entwined around a staff that has wings at the top
One of the very obvious connections here is that
Asclepius is the Greek god of
Healing and
So that's Peppa Pig party
There are also two main reasons
Why the snake has become a symbol in the meadow
Medical field
The first is that in the Book of Numbers
People lose their faith
The wilderness
Start speaking out against God and Moses
I got some fire snakes to bite people
When the people realize the error of their ways and bake Moses
For help
21 verses 7 & 8
Quote therefore the people came to Moses and said we have sinned
For we have spoken against the Lord
Then against the
Pray unto the Lord that he take away the serpent
It's from us
And Moses prayed for the people
And the Lord said unto Moses
Make me a fiery Serpent and set it up on a pole
And it shall come to pass that everyone that is bitten
When he look it up on it she'll live
There's a Biblical root
To one of the primary reasons that the snake is associated with the
The symbology for medicine
The other reason is the metaphor of a snake shedding its skin and going
Old and weary too young a new again which
Is analogous to the doctors gold
People
How do I own is just made up a bunch of dumb s*** or maybe you read it on the dumb blog and he's pretending that it means anything
And using it to demonize psych meds which consists were to blame for the shooting even though he has actually no idea if they are
He's dumb
And a piece of s***
Moses is God was a lot more metal
You know fiery snake
Kind of Christian Rocky but
God was f******
Metal there's a strength in silence and poised and not using fire snakes
Yeah I always just love it when
They they do meme etymology
It sounds smart to people who don't
No
Yeah exactly two other people they would work on
Play Alex Steele
Pictures of real check
What are we going to do now
That magically there's a shooting last
Swinging Buffalo Bayou
And magically now there's this match and by the way the cruise really smart
Zooming in
On the stockings the guy was wearing or was
The picture behind it
Fred Meyer
Michigan
You were showing the incel reported shooter
Zooming in on his leg
Then what was it
Stockings were looking at or
Oh that's
Wow I'm dumb
A handprint
Could be lifted up
I have no idea what they're talking about
But because they're talkin about stockings
And legs
You know which picture that they referencing
Again we have this very consistent thread
Yeah that is talking about this
Specific hoax
This target
Write up a hoax right though
I think you can pretty clearly demonstrate that based on what they're talking about
So Alex
Is is is really dancing around like
Weather this is space
Aged or not
Send that's because he's a piece of s***
Look I don't want to say this was staged remark
But
We have specifically said
New Year's Worley mass shooting
That was all the pre-programming that mass shootings are coming and terrorists are going to attack him
We got to take the guns and I'm like well I would predict a lot of mass shootings
Right before the election and then like clockwork is happening
You know Timmy it's just very Opera
That's the thing Alex
There have been mass shooting guys plug into a Google Search right now hundred ninety-eight mass shooting
And it wasn't black
This is convoluted and with the point that Alex is trying to drive that is I don't want to say this was staged book
Come on guys I really want to say this is staged
I feel like I'm not allowed to say that it's staged anymore and I really do want to say that so I'm going to try and get you
Kind of give me some cover
To say that I can speculate about it
So whenever people are like
Claims that it was fake I can actually say we were just talking about and that's why I was taking a bunch of calls
But also like
There's this sense of like
People think I got I went soft
If I take
But also a very serious risk if I go too far in the other direction
Think I might be able to outlast this lawsuit until we get
Full fascism in America and then they won't be able to stop
And the other one has to put the brakes on and whipping like there were a bunch of magic
Call fascism then you're probably going to lose that lawsuit
So he has them pull up
The number
And it's just
When they decide to cover it mean that's all it is
When do they decide to cover it
You don't want to cover it but this one happened like you said tragically at a school
Mountain of rural area in
Texas so they figured hey this is a good one to cover
We can use this tragedy
I said
I bet it's an incel
I bet it's a
Did the dress
Like when Dave Chappelle said I just got attacked by a tranny
I was
And I'm not going to be mean to
Statistically these people are
Have a higher percentage of whacked-out f***
Income tell it Alex has a little bit of the burpees there
And like he's communicating weird
Some of the
It's it's hard to exactly put into words
But listening to him talk as much
As I do. This is a this is a weird Tony I had a happy hour after
Disney Orchestra tired but
I don't know
Again I have no interest in pretending that Owens
Sincerely doesn't understand why the media would cover the buffalo in Uvalde shooter shootings more than safe or no the BART
7th shooting in Knoxville Tennessee where four people were injured and no one was killed
It's a false premise owners using any knows damn well the bulshit he's paddling
I was interested in the notion that he put forth
These mass shootings are all in democrat-controlled inner city
I wondered if that was true so I decided to analyze
The date of all the mass shootings this year and see if what Owen was saying was in
Anyway I can
Here's what
The first thing I learned is that looking at the numbers like this is stupid
This is a no way a red state-blue State thing nor is it an inner-city rural area issue
Their mass shootings at smaller cities and their mass shootings in Irving
I'm not positive this means anything but since I took the time to compile this here are the numbers
Defining red and blue states by their governor
4 red states you have 102 mass shootings total with 124 fatalities in 455 in
For blue states you have 114 total mass shootings with 123 fatalities and 408
Overall it's pretty close
That being said Texas was the leader in every category with only California even coming close at
I guess the point is that I was curious about if what Owen was saying that's anything and a Consulting the numbers
How come to the strong conclusion that he's talking out of his ass which I should have just
Sometimes you just like
Make a spreadsheet here
Yeah it's
It's so f***** up how far they've won
That they don't even have to remember
Hundreds and hundreds of mass shooting
Like they don't even have to think about it they're surprised
It's the third so many mass shooting
When a large one like this happen
Alex has to be reminded exactly
Reminded that he's making s*** up about there not being mass shooting and it's just like man if you guys
Bored
Playing full-court
Preston
All of the mass shootings then
Man
Alex gets back to our system
Limits
The society in 2K
Give metal detectors
School's out before
The real thing to do
Is the arm
The teachers in French
Fulton hours
Showing a mass murderer liked
Just comes in there who's demonically
Democratic party going to kill children
They're obsessed with
Wiping them or killing them just one Renaissance
We have a demon problem
We have a satanic
Collapse problem the Bible predicts
Rolling over
Saying okay
You want to try to come after me
You want to try to kill me
You want to try to
Enslave me I am going to defend myself
Well that's the story I mean we have
Lost our moral compass
Did this is just yet another sign of it
Decaying
Civilization
Children out killing children
You're in a dick
Kaying
Civilization
Where does someone faint
Okay the cops are chasing me I'm going to go kill Elementary students
Sandy Hook
Everything I cover
Earlier
Kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill kill
Go to elementary school
So obvious what they're doing
This isn't about you prick
How old is Sam or simply
Let's just cut it
It's disgusting but that doesn't seem right
But it's not big enough
The part about
Alex thinking that his
Fusion cause this is
If they hadn't have criticised me than these shootings would never happen
Ion I mean like I think if I was someone in his life I probably hospitalized and for saying something like that
It's indicative of
Like
Really troubling thought pattern literally you can't participate
Society if I tell you
Literally everything is about you
Society can only touch you
You can't ever
You're never on the team society and you can only really understand everything that goes on in the world as an extension of you
Un
That's dangerous yeah
No I mean it's it's impossible to argue that he doesn't have a very severe mental
Faculty issue at least a dangerous narcissist
6th Street
Blah
20 way they decide they're going to take a break
Like to play some
Special Report
But first
Whenever couple special ports where come back
DeShawn
Steve Martin
First off
Owen would you like to lead us in a prayer for these
Dead children these dead teachers in the wounded
H like me
Sure Alex
Dear God please be with the
Families that are suffering
Tonight
In Uvalde Texas
And that community
Please God
Protect
That community
From the Satanic agenda
That is surrounding it
Right now
A little bit of a political Pereira
This is a little lies
Man Moses is God really would have blown him
F****** sky-high studio if Moses is God
That was real
God he would explode sewing wraps up his prayer here
And protect
This nation as we are going into the arms
Satan Lord
Please
Protect this nation in Jesus name I pray
I'm in all right you're absolutely right
Protect our little
Are coming
For our children
Every level
And I am pre-program psychos
Just like this on
Turn the temperature down
They go to kill children to make their final deal
With Satan
That's what do
Weapons
I'm being informed and watchful
Defend ourselves
Good response to a prayer
This reminds me of another Bible story this revised I think it was Elijah
Whenever God and ball we're having a whole argument
Garden ball
So the priests of Baal tried to light this thing on fire using the power of ball
Right and then Elijah tried to like this thing on fire using the power of God
So like she does it
And a ball guys didn't
And then got killed all the ball guys to just for fun
You know just
Like that would be here's what we do
Okay
Owen can pray
Right
And then I get to enact
Some form of Oz assault weapons ban
And we'll see which one is more effect
Apparently I think I'll be really difficult to to make
Alright
I was thinking you were going to just make up a Bible story
Call now and I was I was just thinking
If you ever want to make up a Bible story you should say that it was happy
Cuz no one remembers
Habakuk did
What did you do
You have no idea I have no idea
So Special Report
And then they come back
Calls
This guy
Seems like his tone is not good
What start with Sean in Nebraska with I think
A couple dollars on this issue it's
It's the biggest cover-up when it comes to these shootings and that's
What's the pharmaceutical drug free time one of these cells
And so I can travel
Go ahead Sean
How you guys doing tonight
That dude stone is a bit in
Inappropriate how to build
Conspiracy about the cover-up of something he has no idea about
Let's go to the level of bulshit workshopping that's so important
They had to do this special episode
Is entirely point
Atlas accepted into the audience's heads that no matter what
Hear this person was on psych meds
Cuz I made him commit murder and there's a
The cover-up about whether or not he was on those meds
If the media says he wasn't on meds
And they say he was on meds that means you was on even more
It's all just pointless meeting wasn't dangerous ultimately hurting people who are hurting
And needs psychological help but are being told that the meds
Will make them crazy
There's no proof that psych meds had a causal link to these sorts of mass shootings
Propaganda put out by the Church of Scientology
In that case you might reach that conclusion they were really heavy on
Yeah so this same color as a really stupid phone
Also on the buyback
People be done
You're standing on the buyback
The gun
There's no
Buyback programs in towns guns
Go through the roof
Because there's no
I just want to make a point of that
Complete idiot
When they say no question
That means that if you have a gun you're not legally allowed to own in a certain State you won't get in trouble for bringing it to a buyback
It doesn't mean we just accept whatever gone from
From anybody
Every authority to run these programs over they choose but typically how they do it is they when a gun is turned in
They run the serial number of it through the database of reported stolen gun
Number matches a stolen gun they can't destroy it without contacting the legal owner
And getting their permission
In some states you'll also get arrested if you're trying
To the person who's trying to turn in a stolen
1 gun
This guy says he lives in Nebraska where is a class 2A felony to attempt to dispose of a stolen firearm
So I'm guessing he's just into dumb memes and decided
Did there people out there stealing everyone's gone so they can sell them to the governor
Nonsense
That's
That no
Clovis Lodge
Right there because they don't ask questions
Lindsey Steele done
Right.
So then you steal guns
And then you
Giving them to the buyback
Program
Cuz I don't ask questions
And also I would what's stealing guns would be something that Alex
Thanks can't happen because you would be targeting someone who you know is armed I mean you would think
The possession of a gun stop a person from wanting to steal the gun Cara's here is your problem with the good
The guy with the gun
Scenario if the bad guy can steal your guns easily
That's an issue
A good guy can be disarmed
If they get their gun stolen very quickly
Who's able to
To steal your guns Just based on a desire to sell them back to the government
So stupid
Going to make sense if you're just like
It is the kind of thinking that should be
Isolated two people
In a bong
Circle
City grounds
Extra cash man that's what I meant you can make a little bit
It's like a like
People coming up with a bad caper
100%
Who's at Greaseman
Alright
Thinking about
A bottle rocket the other day and then
Just triggered my bike on it again so bad caper
That is a bad guy
God do that
Future man he's so cool
Future man
They get another call and this person has worked out a storyline
About the idea that the shooter was tram
Sure
Mark and Arizona was talking about Mike Adams go ahead
Yeah I'm Mike Adams just posted on naturalnews.com that the kid was a transexual
And I think you should
Screen
Yeah that they
They can you tell 789 year olds
Maybe that's where he went to elementary school
And he's just going back to where it all began
And so he was broom there and then setup
Open transition through high school and it drove him crazy stories. His grandma and then went back to
Start
Elaborate on that
Azita
Yeah so that's f***** up
This guy's just created a fun story for himself and narrative Arc
Based on
Oaks PA
Pictures and just what he assumes
Might have happened
To somebody in elementary school is f***** up
This kind of stuff is just not even it's not even unproductive
It's
It's not even counterproductive it's just I I mean it's
Astonishing
Like I really don't understand
This person
I'm like
Fundamental level
I listen to somebody say that and I
Do not know where I belong anymore
Kind of understand
What's going on
Because he's somebody who believe
Leave this b******* it's someone trying to make sense of the information that's being presented to him as
So can you come up with this
Explanation in his head
And I can understand that
What I can have a difficult time understanding is
Feeling like
There's any Merit
And saying it out loud
There's any Merit falling into a national radio show the night of the shooting
To share this
Theory as if it means anything
I understand the way that our brains
Works that there's a lot of times you put pieces of information together to try and create a story to help you understand something
Maybe they're necessarily isn't what the pieces of information that he has are bad and wrong so the story
Please come up with his bad and Rolfe course
The beat
Taking action
To share it is weird part I don't understand at all
Obviously I've spent
Many many a day concocting some sort of narrative to try and make some conspiracy theory makes sense
I understand him coming up with this story a plausible enough sounding
Drawing all of this b******* into a in a more grounded place of like
Are human pesos like a disc
The with the weirdest part of this this guy is tacitly admitting the trans people are
Discriminated against it on over I don't even know that's not fair
Stop playing the rest of his called but he's
He's talking about her about the idea that poachers made him
Like that
Jesus Christ
Whose anyway this is a useless use of time for alexandrite
Laccd
Useful for him
So
Alex does
Turn around the idea of false flag
The big questions are
How many
False flag
Shelves
Carry out late they can slap this everyday
Attacks
Synagogue
Black churches you name it
Who are liberals to demonize
America
Walt the next
And then you can buy tomorrow
Sunglow f***** up but also they don't catch
People doing that everyday
No pulse
I I mean
It is
F***** up
Currently
He's trying to demonize
Groups of people
I'm shocked that he didn't bring up Jessie Smollett
I am
I am a little shocked
Just go to
Yep
Yeah
So this next call is fun I guess
Alex Jones
Can't get no
And now you
But we're all pulling
That's funny because this guy is trying to express solidarity with Alex
But the way he's doing it actually invalidates
The giant argument Alex yells about all the time
According to Alex black people should have
No problem getting Justice in the courts because there's no such thing as systemic racism
Why this caller sounds like he's trying to push
What's trt
It's hard to believe that Alex doesn't shout him down and correct him the way he would have some left-leaning person were to try to tell him
Do black people are treated unfairly in the justice system
It does seem Alex should say
Excuse me you've never had any trouble with the justice system because the entire globalist fear is angled towards
Making sure you get away with crimes
As much as possible so you can't express solidarity with me
As a white person I'm the only one persecuted by the American justice system sir
I have strange doesn't respond that way
That would be more appropriate
So Ted Nugent shows up
Bad news
How you doing Ted when I speak
You know Alex
We spent time
Together
I I don't
Tab Hunter
And I
Eliminate
Presumptions in my life I
Look in the evidence and I embrace
The evidence
Supposed to
And I just
Cannot
Overstate
The Heartbreak
And I know you know that but I do
Think we should
Pivot off
Speedpaint
Right now
To allow power
6 to enter this
As long as we possibly
We can't we get all the answers
If not if Nugent isn't it to hunches and loves information he should check in with his nutty qanon wife
Also a little late to getting political
Newton should have come on at the beginning of a
Michelle
Something a bunch of fake shittin misidentifying another Mass shooter
Also
Ted Nugent is bringing up like we should
You know
Feel the pain and all this
That isn't a part of this
Broadcast at all
Nope recognizing the pain and really like not pivoting off it is like
If it wasn't Ted Nugent saying it I don't got probably be okay with the sentiment sure but it has nothing to do with what this is
Infowars coverage has been
I mean this is in the
Face of
The pain front
Owen said a prayer that I mean
Did it
Mention the families
Yeah a little bit a little bit
I didn't play the entire prayer for you I was a little bit also
Four Democrats and gun control
Yeah political
A couple minutes
30 seconds later
Ted Nugent gets political
I'm on with you right now Alex
I am not only
Dedicated
Compassion
Dailymotion about representing
The heartbeat of
Broken hearted
Vale Tech
You right now Alex
Human Bean
It has ever
Liberty
Is on television right now the man who
President of United
States
Treasonous man
Name Jobe
Yeah
Let's not get political
I think that like
Your hours near hours
Someone
Murdered Elementary School
Student
And
You're going out of your way to say that Joe Biden is one of the worst people was ever
I mean it's it's a little bit much immediately after saying you represent the heart of everyone
Craving brokenhearted Middle America
Call Biden is a snake
Also by the way
Clipper I brought up his wife for being a
Qanon
Maybe it seems like a cheap shot but his wife does come
Operator she appears later so there is sort of out of nowhere
From the right
So Ted this guy man
Love evidence of things
Either rigorous
I also love Dinesh D'Souza
Broward course I'm a huge
Porter
Believer
I bet
Scrutinizing
I researched
All my heart
Soul
Dinesh D'Souza
As documented evidence
Documentary 2000
20 election was
Dead people by the millions voted that the illegal
Voted
Troydan
Turn off collection
Replacement
20 election
Joe Biden
Not good
2020 elect
Illegally
Close
I've come to realize this I'm into evidence and I do my research
But isn't something that these people say
Sincerely even
It's not meant to
To be taken seriously because
It's not natural statement of what they
Practice
As much as it's a statement of how they want to be seen
If a catchphrase basically I'm saying I'm not a racist but
You know some research
Brandon how he's presented to The Wider world of right-wing ship
He doesn't have any evidence of anything
2000 Buell doesn't prove any of that s***
This is what I would describe
Pathetic virtue signaling be done by idiots who Wanna Be
They're desperate.
Be taken seriously as smart people but they don't want to do anything
22 Merritt
Be smart right you have to work at it
Like
Smart you know you don't have to read books or like learn things are like continuously
Locate yourself ever ending never stopping it's a practice
Being smart is a practice
Have
Being interested in evidence
And the things that you're talking about being grounded
It's something that you have to do
It's not something that you are
David Nugent and his people like him
A engage with that is like no this is a characteristic
Give me
And that's I think
Fraudulent but I also think that it's
It's never meant
To be really like
Serious
I mean it is it is nice to have it a Zan inherent characteristic if you are on this
S*** s***
Because even when you don't do any research
You can always be like
Do you know me I do my research
It's an inherited characteristic that I've established part of my backstory so you got that to rely on even when you're full of s***
Right
It's annoying
It is very annoying
So anyway Ted Nugent really excited because moderate Democrats
I don't really do
I'm struggling Ted Nugent understands that this is immediately following political
But Myra Democrats
I don't know what moderate Democrats are hanging out with
Moderate Democrat
Starting to realize the
The Democrats are
I'm telling you that this
The heretofore so-called
Moderate
They're finally getting their head out of their ass they're going wait a minute
If you don't have
Secure borders you're not even
When you facilitate the invasion
Fentanyl and methamphetamine when you reward coyotes
Traffic
Children First
And profit
When You See It Wide Open
If those departed had a hope for a
Democrat lifestyle
They're finally going my God
Current Democrat
United States of America
They are pure
They are trees
Did every Acworth
Indeed
Janice all the time as always
Liberal friends
They're all in woken up
They're all talking about
Donald Trump
And
So no matter how many frogs live oak Stave.
The dishes a suicide pact apart
Is big news
Wow I would become pills
Can't believe Alex
His wife's affluent tennis partner friends what eventually turned
Against populist ideology is like
So crazy just like
These these characters that don't exist on the show but
Exist as
Figments of Alex's imagination
I really do enjoy tracking down
Whenever Alex's wife's tennis Partners come off it comes from them
There's a bit like a Greek chorus
See you there there there in the background
And they contribute when necessary apparently I wasn't using them to do exit polling
Repulsive the country by way of
Tennis partners
Ted Nugent as something to promote
But he's doing it
A way that I would describe his dishonor
Wenoka
Art
We have
The weather
Chastised
Weed
We've got a
Hear what you have to
You do but if you
You believe in God family country Law & Order individual
You've got to get everybody in your life
To both those core values
We started
Hunter nation.org
Please my friend
Join me a
Hunter Nation
. org
Clearinghouse
Alex
Everybody in their light bulb
Greatest quality of life
Humanity your in United States
America
Particularly here in
Text
Oh man I remember when
Guys were saying Democrats doing like get-out-the-vote effort
Registration
They're just trying to steal an election by signing up fake people
Dad is yelling about getting people registered
Seems fishy
I went Soccer Nation
Subscription website Ted runs where there's some dumb
Content like blogs and stuff
But it's mostly just about him making money
He also brings together show their retail to co-host
The dump
I guess things are dried up since he doesn't have those TV shows anymore and his music sucks so you got to do what you got to do
On the site also you can buy raffle tickets to go hunting with Ted or if you like you can try to win the chance to hunt a bear
Baron Idaho
Great stuff
What are there past
Dream hunts was go I go shooting with
Trump's son
There's a tell hear that Ted is obscuring and that's it there's another website called
Hunt the vote which is where the whole registration
Hunter nation is
Website where there's a bunch of
Was dumb bulshit
30 cells on it
If you were actually focused on the registration
Some stuff as opposed
The advertising is on garbage
He promote
The other side
This is why I felt so good
You know even if it was
About promoting
Voting
You know that's still f***** up on the the night
That is a lie about promoting yourself it's f***** up
I understand that but he wants to get
Profitable
Yes
So Alex
Is trying
Desperately
To get tabs
To say that bad s***
Sure
Yeah this clip is really funny because I was just trying
Cat doesn't play ball Adam and Alex has to like
Put his tail between his legs and salt
I believe this is a real psychopath I believe the shooting happen
The question is
Though it's little weird
That we're right outside
Midterms
Harden's
68 days out
And magically this is all happening
What do you
Respect in the Bible
The Deep state has
As it comes out the Russia gate
And all everything else they do
Do blows up
Gut-level as an American as a patriot
Not just as a top
TV house
Pro gun guy in Rockstar
Father and grandfather gut-level
Ted Nugent they know they're losing
What do you expect them to pull neck
Well
The post on the nuts
So Mean Streets
SuperAmerica
With you
An accurate reading of that
Thank you for that we thank you for
Speaking up and race
America
Ted Nugent Alex Jones
You're not raising hell you might as well go to Cuba where you're not allowed to
The point being is that I know these
Why walked
Street Theater
Texas and I still communicate
My friends in all 50
Stacy
House on the phone today with Steven
Tyler down there
California
I'm on the phone with just
Raptors
Barberton cops
Teachers in Albany
Tri-State Non-Stop
Get ready for Rock And Roll tour
Both literally and figuratively
I believe that there is going to be there is no way Kenny
Taken place
Because of the cruelty of Art
Current governor
The cruelty
Honesty
Violation
Reconstitute
I believe that it's going to be a win-win I'm an eternal optimist
And I have great hope
People are waking up and
We are going to
Squeezing this way that is now headed
Syllable in the White House
Ted Nugent I totally agree with the old Shores got some questions my question is
Totally agree with you
The moment you are off this phone call I'm going to claim that there will be non-stop mass shootings from now until the end of the midterm
God dammit dare you say that there is
Positive things coming
Non-stop shooting from now until the end of the midterms
Talking Ted
Ruining my pocket neighbor let's go camping shut up
Gets involved in a proceeding
And she probably hasn't gotten one of the memos that Alex
Just put out
She manages just as smart as you are what was her view on time
Hey Alex
Right here
I agree with Ted
And you know
It's a shame but what's going on I don't know how anybody think
Is that if we don't
Change the way that
We voted
In the past
Why are things
Going to be any different
Can't fix these voting
I'm I'm
I'm scared of what's going to happen
No the voting machines were red herring no no no no
Machines were distraction by the global is so weird
Recent movie that your husband is promoting
Where is there voting machines in that one who cares
It's mostly about the mules of course
Sharmaine brings up a hanging out with
Trump sure and that's fun to think about
But Alex is really excited you want some hot gossip
When we were with pressure
Weekend or two things that he said to Adele
He said I think it's going to get pretty dark
Before it gets better
Before it gets
Light
And that
This had to happen
And so that people would weigh
Makeup
Wow so Trump said that that's huge
Yeah he admitted
Great time with the Press
Great man
He's not perfect
But compared to the regular
The politician
She's almost like
Michael
No I agree we'll spend a few minutes on that let you beautiful people go
At least tell me what about you
Lamar
Strange sycophantic that still kind of Israel even though he's trying to pretend that he's like
Not moved on
They still very much as I'd strfkr
So the nugents golf
And if it's back to business right
I want have some thoughts
About who could and could not own
Dunce
In the early American his
I don't I don't want to live in a war zone I want to live in a society where every I feel like I have to carry a gun around
We are in a war zone with all these other words for
I'll tell you that damn true I never going to be a Slave
The second amendment was written
That'd mean everybody could own a gun
Let's see why don't you finish that statement who couldn't own a gun in 1776 who was that
Waves
That's what it was
Slave
Couldn't own a gun in 1770
So they just want to make you a Slave
You're not supposed to care that much about slavery was not a bad thing
Exactly right
So you should also probably learn a little bit more about history
Slaves
Couldn't own a gun in the early days of America but you know who else couldn't
All non-white people
Regardless of whether or not they were enslaved like Native Americans
Also you be really hard press
Certified women who own guns
Although they could be culturally was
Very acceptable
Also anyone who didn't
Swear an oath of loyalty to the new country
Couldn't
And prior to the founding of the country
The colonies of Maryland and Virginia specifically disarmed Catholics
And I'm Pennsylvania joined in on that later
The early Americans targeted populations that they felt were likely to rebel against
It's remarkable really like Alex fetishizes the founding fathers and yet they did exactly the thing is constantly yelling weather global
Doing and then the globalist never actually do the thing
Yeah yeah so so what they were realized
I think Ryan is they didn't like the way King George was oppressing them
They overslept and then they looked at their own behavior towards other people
They have a legitimate grievance against us
We could do things better
Or
I'll tell you this that King George guy knew what he was talking about
During like the colonial times
A lot of that stuff like this arm and Catholics and what have you
But an eight
1878 New Hampshire make it a law that would disarm and imprison any Tramp that was quote
Found carrying any firearm or other dangerous weapon
Tramps would lose their guns
If all they did was quote threaten to do any injury to any person or to the real or personal estate of another
It was tough for cramps but I didn't leave
Against ramp
Anyways the picture of who was in wasn't allowed to be armed in the early history of our country isn't as cut-and-dry as on W B
That makes sense
Given that
I'm sure most
The stuff that he knows comes
Is from memes listening to Alex makes
Things up I mean isn't he supposed to even be like no slaves could own guns
Better whatever it is supposed to believe that all the rights apply equally even if you're a Slave
Because you choose to be a slave or something along those when I bet they wouldn't want to parse that out
Yep yep
They go back to call
This car has some really good advice
But it's also
Too late
Yeah I'm first of all Nina
Sick to my stomach feel like everybody else in
You can't talk that so
I'm not going to go there go to Hunter Nation.
Unfold in this you know we know how things change over the neck
Do they show any conclusions Alex like you have entire time
Bad idea to speculate this close to it so little information Alex
Don't do the show you're the middle of doing a
Do the things you're doing
It's a f*****-up perspectives on
Alex decides to sign off on that way
Hey
I've been listening to show for about 2 years. I really appreciate the work
Equipment
Xscape
Brainwashing through the media
In the Pharma companies get ahold of them
And whack them out of their minds with
With the drug
We need to take the kids out
Always thinking about Jesus
Because he's coming back very
Well I totally hear that statement on
Check that check so take your kids out of the schools but Jesus is coming back soon Alex like hell yeah hell yeah
Also take the kids out of the schools and also on teachers
I don't know I don't know what's going on anymore
And you should try and teach your children
Geometry
By yourself I guess it kind of makes some sense in his much as like let's arm the teachers but everyone's home
School so it's all the parents are I guess that's the work around here
Do all women
Not accept
Anybody on the last
Pretending that they care about the shooter
That's nice
This is something that frustrates
Me so much about the
They want to sit here and virtue signal and have their
The crocodile
There's any time they can
Can use
A tragedy
For their political
Advantage
I don't want to
I don't want to hear about a Democrat upset about
The children dead
The Uvalde shooting because
You celebrate 60 million dead babies aborted in this
You literally go out in
And celebrate
Your specials on TV you do parade
You launch confetti
You paint your face
You celebrate abortion you literally
Celebrating baby murder and they say kill that bastard
Expect me
Just sit here and have my emotional heartstrings tugged on by the
Do you have a conscience
They manipulate your conscience
Hey dick
Don't
Have an emotional reaction to what other people
Are saying
You have an emotional reaction to the events
Itself
Yeah it is
I don't know why you take
Any kind of
Like look
I have a lot of thoughts
About Alex's response
I have a lot of feelings about that in terms of this episode
Who is completely distinct
From my actual feelings
About the shooting
And my emotional response
And
Processing of it
Yeah
Does not feel
From the way they're doing and how they're engaging with this
That there is much of a difference
Between the response to the shooting
And their response to
What liberals
Arguing
Are you did
Just say why are you trying to make me
We care about this
It feels that way a little bit because you support abortion shouldn't you shouldn't be making me care about this
Sunday I mean
You know
What it is is name
Pants
Believe
That there is a
Different what you know like cuz they
Politicized they do all of this stuff
So they can't believe that there's a way not
They know that it
Would be better to not do that they don't believe that anybody isn't as
Craven
And they have to because if you recognize that other people are not as craving as you then you can't really justify your craving Behavior
So in this makes clip of the worm turns
Some information comes Alex's attentions and everything everything is different
Flipped upside down
That the photos going around the internet of the
Is the reported shooter
Andy to go pawn shop mini or posting photos of a young male in women's clothing
Play Migos Uvalde Texas mass shooter
He's a round firm and verify please stop sharing because
The event they are
Art Ramos
Tommy someone who had nothing to do with it
The images that they're talkin about or not
Sharing there's
Images out there
Locklear
Trans man waving
Flags and stuff we have
I've been sharing those
I believe though
You talked about
We've been sharing you
On the
Could be us
Alex is making a clarification based on Andino posting that this trans individualism
Can probably the shooting after he's already spent pretty much his entire show reporting
The shooters
And to be clear the picture they've been talking about this whole show is the one that was the 4chan hoax
You can tell by how preoccupied Alex has been about
Stockings in skirt
The picture that the actual shooter posted to his imps
Instagram includes him wearing
This is Alex realizing in real time that he's done the same thing that he did with the Parkland shooting
Sing all over again
He's taking some dumb shity song 4chan and he's participated in and greatly Amplified the defamatory claims that it innocent
A sun is a mass murderer
All it takes is a tweet from Andino to get Alex to start covering his ass but if you pay attention
You'll see the ant
Baby posted that tweet at
6:29 p.m.
Over half an hour before Alex got on air for this special report
I have no idea if what Alex did this x x
Symbol in any way but it's called splash of water to
To the face that brings into sharp Focus
Alex's incapable of or unwilling to learn any lessons when it comes to being responsible in his reporting
His priority is pushing his extreme right-wing politics and he does not give a s*** if he hurts people in service of making engaging
Sensationalized
And bigoted content
Don't forget that
Within the first
Minute of being on air Alex reported that the shooter was Tran
Based on a picture that he'd come across and sent to his staff which Alex specific
Berkeley said we're people in like a person in a dress
This is not the Instagram picture of the actual shooter the whole shows content has been based on 4chan hoax
I did this is just a sad attempt to cover some ass
And I think
That the way that Owen jumps in and is like
Instagram picture that reveals
Knowledge of wellheads.
That to me is so telling a lie.
Oh oh way we have to come up with an explanation for why what we did was
The other thing that andino's Queen is telling people not to do
Yep it's pathetic
It takes
Andino
To realize what they're doing
Is f*****
Like
It's sad but I guess
If the message gets across
Sure
Whatever
Yeah that's
That's so unreal back himself up more with like a man
Breaking news breaking story Woody
You going to do
Okay I was just alive breaking news event
Information
Not sure if
Salvador is
The
Well over the next
Judaism
Intel as it doesn't roll as they roll it out
Shooting all over again
What exactly is on wanting to know about the Las Vegas shooting
What was that because he stopped caring about it and has anything about the story a few years doesn't mean that everybody
Else just as pretending it didn't exist
Except Steve pieczenik he's definitely worth
Or happened at all
In August 2018 the Las Vegas Metro Police Department released a 187 page report covering the investor
Gage middle shooting
So curious about anything you should go ahead and read that
The FBI didn't investigation as well and determined that they couldn't nail down a specific motive which is
Frustrating
But it's not proof of any kind of
The cover-up
We heard in the Daniels deposition about how the audience loses interest
Austin stories that are a few days old
And that they have to tailor their coverage to accommodate that
In order to chase viewers and keep the supplement selling Infowars moved on from caring about that story
And what I want is doing here is
He's trying to blame everyone else for their own shallowness and laziness and covering stories
But yeah you lost the interest in covering this
Because it wasn't moving the needle
And now you're pretending that
They just stopped
Investigating it or covering
What are you
Admitting is that he does not do any research at all A's
He's only spoon
Fed
What it is he gets
You know like he doesn't actually go
Well I mean in I mean totally like
They don't go looking for things it's brought to them
You know they don't go they don't go looking for I have a question that I want the answer to I'll go look divine
It's either the answer is already is either brought to them
Or they don't they don't find it
Not really in the info
So
This guy wants to pray
So we have two players on the show
Keep this in just as a kind of
Contrast
Cuz I think this is a pretty decent prayer okay
Are you there
I sure am brother welcome
Thank you it's honor to be with you tonight
I just wanted to offer
People in Uvalde
Bored
We ask that
Cover the fam
These precious children
In your grace
And
Give the family
Accept what has happened
It's normal.
They're going to be upset
There's nothing we can say
Comfort Inn
But the Lord can do
And he will
We ask this
Your name
The name of Jesus
Jesus Christ Our Savior
And holy spirit
Amen
Diorite
Just running around
Oz responses s*** but the reason that I wanted to play it was
Because
I want to stress
Like
People pray on Infowars
I'm not opposed to pray
I just think that they use
Usually do it in a really
F*****-up way
That is generally self-serving and maybe pushing an agenda
I think that's what this color is doing is expressing a pain and a wish to
Express solidarity desire for
God's grace to help
The parents right
And I don't think there's anything wrong with it I think it's a little bit weird
How to show 2% itself as a new show at and for people to be praying all over it
It's it's sort of the difference of his style
Right right right
I just we make fun of a lot of the year
And people end up praying on Alex's show that's right
But I just want to be clear that there are instances every now and again
Maybe rare
Where somebody comes
Somber
I know and I respect
That I just
Know that
Proves they don't actually believe in or give a s*** about their religion whatsoever bring to the table
You know what the Bible is bringing to the table and he doesn't
Well damn
You're jumping to
But look
Here's that here's the deal
I just want to put these
Juxtaposition
Owens prayer
The scholars prayer
There's a world of difference between them
And I feel like one of the reasons is B
Because
Does an opportunistic Miss
And there is a sincerity
I'm feeling
100%
Is the
The relevant difference
I agree
Alex midici Mandino's tweet
The tone of this is entirely different lb
Salvador Ramos is the real shooter
Who knows if any of the
Who knows of these photos
Who knows who the guy in the skirts real
Who knows if any of this is
Because the media lies
So much
We have a right
To say we don't believe what we're hearing
Such a strange shift in tone
How much is clearly worried that buddy
Been saying this whole show the looks bad now that it's become clear that he was identifying the wrong person as the shooter
All this show has been like we got pictures the reported shooter and then straight demonizing Tran
People all the sudden Alex doesn't know if
Anything is real
He's gone from a sensational is bigoted propagandist perpetuating 4chan hoax
I'm so skeptical they can't even prove that the person
Sitting next to them is real
Who's the FedEx.
I mean he's retreated into a world of like
You have to prove everything
It's what he did in the deposition
You know he retreated back the moment he got the the moment he had to confront reality
And he cannot get away with
He has to not do what he's about to
Right
He immediately backed up and he's like
Listen I mean I don't know if it's
I'm not saying that I know it's
I said to go old saying is that there were questions it sometimes two people today that I don't know if it's this guy or that guy
You might as well be doing is admitting guilt
Before we get anywhere we have to try and prove that existence
It's something that everyone
Create the universe
Basically
Another caller
Glaring
The difference in bananas
And there's a real
So they take another call and this guy has a
Fun idea
That it's never going to happen
Alex I finally get
Talk to you finally in
I want to let you know
You
Owen and Harry
Need to go on Joe Rogan
Podcast
Quit this
Send it to him
Bellevue
People want you guys
All three of you
I know he want me on Joe Rogan's podcast
Friends Ojo
Pressure
Obviously
The highest ratings
Would be great
Kind of
Begging the question there but yes I appreciate it
I'm not getting back on that show maybe for a long time and
Yes
Just enough patience for me he does not want my lackeys
Oh no no no no no no this is something they call hers
Should really ask
Themselves
Okay yeah
Joe is
Fine
A couple times
Having Alex on
AMC has a lot of f*****-up weirdos come on
Weirdly
He does not
Invite on people who are like
A bunch of Alex's
Yeah it is is Wack Pack for a lack of a better term
Where's dr. marble
I don't know how they're going on Joe Rogan that's for sure
Skousen
Not going to
Broken that is unlikely
From having Rogers
You're still. Is vodka
Although I think I would be
That would be interested that would actually probably be the first time I listen to a Rogan episode is orbit
That like you know obviously rubbing his
Probably
Real interested in talking to
Really faint
Yeah it would make sense
I think Mike Lindell could go
Yeah yeah yeah whatever Logan needs a little spending money
That hundred million goes away real quick you know do you know what your spending I don't know if it goes with that quick
I don't know I mean like look I don't have a hundred million dollars
And
Mike Liddell couldn't pay to get on this podcast
So that's fair
So I mean like Alex is talking about like this idea of
Like
I'm not going to be on Rogan
Because he doesn't have access to the
Top
Tear
Annie Potts
Smelly
When you see video that Harrison made being pushed on Tucker Carlson
You have to pretend that it's not from an Infowars
Never heard
So Alex
We always talked about having the globalist
Playbook
In a way that is like I know what they're going to do
He talks a little bit more about this
I honestly think that the way he's describing this here
Is meaning
If they don't have totally
Controlled regulation
Is coming up for the midterms are going to have to do
Do something
To either curtail people from voting or
It just not even have an election
Crazy
Cheap
The globalist are predictable in that
We know they have the
These plans up their sleeves
How they're going to
Decide what they want to reach I can make
Patriots are known to do
Did the other side Playbook you don't know when they're going to play
Do we have the Playbook
We just don't know what play there
That means nothing
We don't have nothing
We have
Okay so when I watch
Let's say we were playing a football game right now
Tape 45-minute football game or whatever it is
Right so I know all the other teams play
Because I've watched them play them over and over and over again that means that I know exactly what they're going to do
We will win the game every time right
I mean like obviously though
That you have of knowing
Games plays is like
The way they line up a lineup will give you some indication of what
Play my TV
Two things yes
Alex
Engages with a globalist like that but he's wrong every f****** time
Right
Well I mean it's like if Alex was the coach of the Bangles
And I was the coach of the Patriots
And I had the Bangles
Playbook
And Alex had the Playbook
For like
I don't know the Cincinnati Reds
You know wrong sport
You know it's true
Catch the ball how do I throw a curveball
Did the thing that he's describing is essentially like if I were to boil this out until like
More realist
Stick language it's
I've come up with a bunch of stuff that icons
Stanley say the globalist are going to do
And I don't know when they're going to do these things
If they're going to do them
But these are all the things that I've decided by enemies are capable of
It's meaningless.
You might as well have a whiteboard and just write down random
Thoughts that he has a things that might be bad and then just write him up there and then if he doesn't like it
The Playbook
So bad news
Don't know
It's the summer of Rage
There's already
It's the liberal summer of rain
Okay so the liberal of Summer of rage is
Upon us they do this
Every election cycle 2020 we saw them burn half of America down to the ground
2000ad and everything
Betrayal the Democrats summer of Rage
So if you can't midterm every other summer is a summer of Ray every other summer is assembly of rage and it's always
Only the liberal
And the other summers are
Summers of
You know it's like it's that kind of thing when the electioneer is that on the off
Igear
It's the summer of reflection and
King stock
What happened during the raid
Immediately followed by the fall of malaise
Yep so we won't last clip here and
I mean if I were to put a button on
This whole
Show
It's been meaningless
Yeah but yeah I hear Alex explains why he did the the show
Owen great job I want to say great job
The crew we got to all those calls thing in Ventura
Would you like 20 calls at Ted Nugent on
Came in because those dead children important
And people trying to capitalize
On their murder
Are bad people
So we had to come in because we do by going to show up tonight to capitalize all information show
Conservatives
We as Christians
We have populist we approach humans
Don't show up
When the enemy shows up
We've given them a few
Which of the crew
Only worked 18 hours
You showed up
Mr. wolf over here
Been here since this morning run the Boom
You showed up
Airwolf
Everybody showed up I want showed up and will show up
Thanks your baggie tomorrow
A.m. Central
With American Journal Harrison Smith Alex Jones 11 a.m.
Owen Shroyer 3 p.m.
We will be here as long as you back us
And supporters amazing products
Infowarsstore.com today's the last day to get
Do
The deepest crystalline on a global trying to keep from you in
Such a game-changer look into it
It's 40% off of Albrecht 1225 percentile by itself
I got no roots
Down the Galaxy
Trying to profit off those are bad people
People who were trying to be opportunistic and profit off of
Baby boy
Christian's really love showing up after all those children and murdered to go try and make sure other children get murdered later
I had Ted Nugent wasn't crying
And I will direct people to his son
Description website
This type of thing or bad
Message received you got it
Exactly what you're doing
So
Obviously
Is is difficult
Material
Perhaps
Alex's
Stop listening
Like
Viscerally grotesque
Probably could be
In the immediate probably just
Because he
Knows that
If I were to put a button on this episode it would be 300,000 lb and I would drop a
Set from 10,000 ft above the Infowars Studio
That's what I would
Super reinforced
Obviously the main thing
Point is
This is it a tragedy
And
And obviously
Whatever
Condolences are appropriate
Very sincerely a heartfelt go after the
Families affected the community of Uvalde as a whole
I
Think that
There is a real
Challenge
In terms of talking about this
Through the lens of Alex Jones
Star next episode will be much more
Difficult
Because of the
Conflicting and contradictory statements
If come out
And the
The
The malleability of
What's been
Put out by the police
So much that worth
Best way to put it
I don't believe build
Sitting here now regarding this episode that we have
A concrete answer
I think it best occasions are probably necessary to get to
And so that will be more challenging
Vain
Say Alex's demonizing trans people in misidentifying
This person is a lot more easy
To say
This is what happen
Yeah and
I think that there will be a challenge
I will we'll have to cross that bridge
Yeah
Anyway I hope everyone out there is doing
Doing all right
We hope that things are
It said there's a little bit of distance
Body
It's still self
Self
At the moment you investigate cop lies he
He just find more
Like every every time they every time that you started like
Do this this was a little bit
This timeline doesn't make sense they're like there's a different timeline in their life
Save it for next time these thoughts Irrelevant for next time
Map
Until then
We do have a website Dan its knowledge fight.
Hunter nation.org
No no
Yes I did
Emilio Emilio I'm dzx I hope you all have a dreamy creamy sauce
And now here comes
The sex robots
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work
I love you