Damn important items swetik
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge like I'm sick of them posing as you're through the good guy
Nick.com
Sit around and talk a little bit about Alex
Jordan
Danny ever hear of a little country called France
You ever hear of a little game called tennis
Como esta
Just like last year but you remember I told you about last year and how they played the most amazing third-set ever in the
I got injured and it was so sad
Sure
Write the opposite happened this time right they played the most amazing tennis ever and then they kept playing the most amazing
Time to sever
And then Rafa
Play the most amazing time this ever end up with reanimated
I mean
That sounds like
Some great
Well I'm happy for you is really fun and enjoyable
That's great, great to get there
Same look at me summon things
I put it on my like a radio professional hat
Alright
The top 40 I'm having
A difficulty coming up with a bright spot necessarily so I'm going to say
Is going to be controversial
Frozen waffles
Frozen waffle
Yes Frozen waffle I had a broken
Toaster for quite a while
No I had not been able to toast
And I just recently
We got a new
Toaster oven and one of the things that I was like this in a while
Frozen waffle
How about it
Frozen waffles
And you know what is like a sandwich
You can make a brick
The sandwich 100 absolutely
Works as a great bread
Underrated
Also thank you to everybody who explained to me that sucks things are called a Ramekin break
Such an aggressive response Chumbawamba
Oh my God people will die on
Really took it on the chin on that one
So thank you everybody I know it's a Google Ramekin
Lynx
Jordan about May 25th
2022 episode on Wednesday
Cuz I kind of wanted a little bit more clarity
About stuff
Why I felt like we still really had
Are feet on Shaky Ground
In terms of knowing a lot of the concrete details about the
The police response about the actual Circle
Shooting
I don't think we have that bill
The ground is shaking around us right
But we can't we can't really put things off too much longer
And in terms of underwear
You know
Optional episode on Wednesday
Got it got to go to work
So what what I'm thinking
And I actually thought it was taking her out this idea anyway
Things down a little bit
Take a look at this time more completely I think
Especially this. Where these reports
Coming out
About the Bruno
Contradictory
The police are making
Is coverage over the course of it
We can see any kind of nuance or details that go on in his coverage
Yeah it is it is interesting to see how he
He would react
To each change in the store
Not in any particular rush to figure out what he said yesterday or you know talk about
I think this this could be a good exercise of our our time and
Eventually we might get to the point where you have concrete information about the police
Interesting
It's a good choice just because
Alex
Has to come out immediately knowing everything that there is to know
You think and then
The story's going to change so he has to come out and immediately know everything about that and then the story is going to change again we have to come out of me
At least there's no way he can keep his b*******
Whatever he has to do as a narrative has to be able to include that somehow or us
So make it include
Maybe interesting to see
I think this will be
Released educational in some form
So today we're just going to be looking at the day after the shooting May 25th
Do first
The middle-aged rat captain from the SS North Korean ballot boat thank you so much
Next legendary creature phyrexian Flash
At the beginning of your end
InStep draw seven cards
Each opponent
Maximum hand size is reduced by seven
Thank you so much you're an alcoholic
Thank you very much
Captain Carlos Danger in the crew of the darkslide
Next I told my mother I was brilliant issues that I was going to hell
Juvenile policy walk
Thank you very much like to say hello and thank you
You are now a technocrat
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
Miami
Go take a little break you down
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order and
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Belle walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologize to the crew in The Listener jester
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not
Nope you never will be
We start off here and Alex has some interesting
Thoughts
Here's my idea that the shooter didn't act alone
Okay
But
Well
It's a little metaphysical Salvador Ramos
Son of Rome
Caucasian doesn't matter their Hispanic
It doesn't matter
They are black
All have that shame look
Follow the exact same MO
Have the same criminology behind them
His friends said that he began
Several years ago
Called
He did not act alone
This evil force
Text people over
That's I guess Alex has decided that the Uvalde shooter is possessed by demons
Which is being used as an argument that he didn't act alone
So we're we're good solid ground here
Scraped little sunroom thing is fun but phileas is sun in Latin
Was Ramos not Romo
I do but summerly articles that did say robots
Like all that wild for Alex to have that name
In his head but
It was incorrect
I'm not as familiar with Latin as I am with Greek but I also don't think it's possible for a noun to be.
Decline the way Alex is making robots man of Rome
Is not a suffix
That's used in
The genitive case which is most
Most commonly used to show possession
Like elves
Son of Rome will generally be expressed as fully as Roma
Anyway Salvador's actually a name that derives from the Spanish and Portuguese for savior
And Ramos means branch
The point is that Alex is getting
Send mean son of Satan
So you can
Shoehorn is insane world you that his enemies are possessed by demons
Into the coverage
The story on a basic level
It's very hard to deal with the root causes of
The things if you believe the root cause of things is the devil right right you believe that there's a
Spira see it of one but it's actually a hundred demons stepmothers
The inequity of evil
So Alex is some details wrong actually kind of think
That some of this you should have been able to
To get right
And so he killed his grandmother
Aramis just like
His mother with a gun she'd gotten
Just like the left wants to abort the babies
Alex's great last Refuge
We're comparing everything
To the evils of his enemy is doing the board
If
Almost didn't kill his grandmother
He shot her
But she survived
She been killed you have to do like
No investigation into the story over the past 24 hours because
Most of the stories even the early ones involved the grandmother calling 911
And she was evacuated the hospital that didn't tell was in early story
But we see again the standard
Reflection instead of dealing with reality as it is Alex retreats to save her territory that he knows the audience enjoys
Mainly making everything about abortion and attacking his enemies
Because like
Haha this is bad but what about that
It is
It is so f******
Emblematic
That it is like
Okay we're going to take something that
Hertz people
Who are crying out who we can see the problem
And then we're going to
Compare it to something
Purely abstract
Just nothing
Physical just be idea of abortion is
Is the problem
Yep
I think
Seeing Alex be like a you-know-what
Ejected as a collaboration
Can because
It was the devil
I found this to be really kind of distaste
Baseball has basically doing clickbait
About the shooting
The day after
Headline the show is Alex Jones will exclusively reveal
Organization group behind
This psychotic
Devil
The organization
There's not there's nothing beyond that other than like
I'm tricking you into thinking that I'm going to report on
Something like
I have information that there's a group behind this or whatever and then
Is a bait-and-switch that you just like I hide safe
There's a shadow organization
Conspiracy behind this in Surprise
Yeah
Yeah that's exploitation
Definitely brutal problem
Mexico
Yeah the problem with Mexico's
Devil problem
The Grim Reaper
Play worship
Death and brutality
But still dominating and destroying an entire amazing nature
The same sickness
Mexico
Other countries around the world
Like what do you propose we do
Like what do you propose we do for this evening problem
Primor accrual
I just want people to think about it
Enterprise on
We still have a Satan problem what are you going to do I am going to tell
Tell people to Double Down
Look I don't mean to impugn religion or anything but people are already praying quite a bit and we have a problem Accord
Personally with Jude
Propose people to man who make laws to make sure the people are in line with things that aren't
I don't know about Allah
Ballard comfortable Terrace
Ridiculous
It's a
Terms of being able to have any conversation
Don't don't don't
Look at what
Look over here
The devil the devil
So Alex has some early
Misreporting
He's reporting on
And I think
There's an element of this babe
I mean
I think
A lot of outlets made the same mistakes
Is it was harder to fault Alex
For getting this incorrect In Heights
Focus in
On
Dishes man
And someone who reportedly killed his grandmother
Looking for the Border Patrol
Them
The building
Camo
This matches some of the early reporting on the story particularly the part about a border patrol agent shooting Ramos
Texas Tribune article about this from the 24th
Quotes
Law Enforcement Officers entered the school building and were met with gunfire from the shooter who was barricaded inside
A border patrol agent shot the gunman before waiting for backup along for SMUD official told the Associated Press
So these are the pieces of information that are being
Relayed by law enforcement to press
So it makes sense
I think in hindsight there's a lot of reasons to have
Yeah
Some questions
But
The dynamic is Alex treating this as an official statement is is totally understandable
This is one of the things that's
Good to highlight is that like
There is a difference between something like this
Something he's wrong about because every reason to be wrong about
And he's wrong about when he's just making s*** up
And I think
I think that gets lost sometimes because there are very few instances where he's actually reported on something that is wrong
Is
You would have
It's believed
Bye
Reputable source
Ironically even when he is sticking with the official
Narrative
He is still wrong
Wild that is amazing even whenever he's trying
To not be wrong
He gets even more wrong
Information about the police response called into question but based on the available information
Alex isn't that far off the
That being said he's still totally wrong about the
The shooting being quick
Even earlier information was clear that it was not a quick thing
Bet same text
Texas Tribune article points out that the shooting began at 11
And the school district tweeted a warning about an actor
Computer at 12 7
Yam
Over 45 MI
Minutes later
For some Conte
Again. It was not like a
No it was a backup but yeah I know
Nope
We have a double problem maybe a solution
We got 40 billion dollars
For money laundering
More
We've got the money
Armed police in the schools
The police
The options menu
Suicide yourself
Super cool he's complaining about
Can't relate that
It's All About Me
Narcissism
Completely Hollow and meaningless
Just a diversion from the point as opposed to actually being a solution
There's two problems with the prescription Alex's yelling about here
The first is that
He believes teachers are trying to groom all the
All the students into being lgbtq and even beyond that he thinks the public schools are
Tools of the globalist use them to get parents in trouble with a child protect
Conservice
Also they teach your kids to hate you and think you were racist
It doesn't track it all but
Listen to your position
It's just a way to yell about something that you think could be a distraction
Conversation
The back on regulation and domestic
Physically violent man
The second problem is that money is being sent to Aid Ukraine is from the federal government
Is Alex saying that he wants the federal government to arm teachers cuz that seems exactly like something he wouldn't
What happening
Free singing we can afford to do this by appealing to the ABS sensor Ukraine
Almost feels like he's our real point no nope I don't think he believes that these are actually solutions to the
Things that he is.
No
I think it's a performance
Of distraction pretty vapid really
For a while
I would say
We also have just the standard choruses
Don't blame me
Oh well it's not my fault right now we have this terrible event
Another person to shoot them up games and other person
Who killed his grandmother
And then went and did this terrible thing
We are all told we are collect
How to bleed a Blaine
For what this
Pomona
Collectively
We went in stop what was happening and got one of himself
Is it the blame
He's the good guy
You didn't do this
But we are to blame for letting Society become this demonic
How much is it
So I wonder how Alex would respond to this rebuttal that I have to his point
About know all the gunrunners aren't
Want to blame
Why is he trying to make all devil-worshipers collectively to blame for the ax
Hands of one shooter
Are your tongues people at their identify a Satanist to don't commit any violent Acts or doesn't seem like there's something inherently viola
Ellentube
Like I'm all for not blaming all gun owners
Because that's sloppy enough productive but
I want to know why Alex thinks so wrong Eddie blames all Satanist for the action
Comes of this one person who Alex
Can't even prove was into satanism
He was a Satanist
Nearest blaming the shooting on all satan
Easily prove that the shooter was a gun owner and I'm not blaming all condone
Alex's wanders engaging in the inappropriate levels of assigning Collective blame
Well if you think someone's going to do that
To you
Regardless of whether or not they do that it's a wiser idea to come back
Aces hard at somebody else with the same bulshit what claiming
You're actually the one who's doing
Do you want to take away someone's First Amendment right
To believe in Satanism in order to preserve your Second Amendment right to own a bill
Okay great great great great
Awesome just cuz the Amendments number two doesn't mean it's not number one
True
So we have on this something we see a lot of times after like
Sort of big events that are kind of do
Difficult for Alex to really talk about a nanny
Organic way like boilerplate
That stuff like
Teachers share
It's not my fault
Nope not gun owners Baltimore cops
Yeah kind of things you hear all the time
Is it one of the things that Alex will do is
He will
Take a lot of calls
Because it's
Workshopping
Figuring out right like
The colors can say things that
You want us to take
Responsibility for those things and he can push back on it and then kind of get some points for looking like sometime
Also if somebody says something he likes
He can repeat it as of the game from a high-level Source tomorrow
There's a lot of benefits for taking calls
And boy
He gets an exciting one pretty early
Alright
I don't want
Bob
Teacher work
With the student
And it says he was special ad says he had a
Speech impediment people make fun of
Because he got so
Demonic
But let's go to
To you I am you are who you say you are this is
Big break here on the shovel to hear from you
And I believe you but
I believe you based on nothing
I'm just going to tell you
You are 100% correct I don't even need to say I don't know if
Seeing any reporting
That he necessarily wasn't in a special education
Glasses
What Alex is referring to is that he had a
Starter and a lisp apparently that people had mocked
That
Kids are cruel
But that does not necessarily mean that he was in any special education
Program he may have been
I don't know that but from
Many of the articles that I've read That's not necessarily something that
Come up
Yeah I don't excluded as possible
Definitely
This caller
Maybe legit
Maybe not
Alex doesn't know
But he is
Treat me like it is
Another problem that I have is at this color is very vague
There's not really much to hang your hat on
I'm a longtime listener Alex
This is really hard for me to
Digest
All this going on
I've worked with students like that
Poison / 14 different districts
And I seen this counter for one end to the other
And
Whatever we might think
You know and you're talkin about an awesome
Texas
Great District great people
My heart breaks for them
Tina been a teacher for a long time
And
I just want to say that
You know
We work with these kids
We know who they are
Whenever we went to quarantine
Did it happen all of this country a lot of these kids
When
Cast
I think that's what we're seeing
Did you work with this dude you work with similar students assault them
Fallout
No I interacted with him
See how he was he's being so vague that Alex has to be like
What are we talkin about
Are you are you working with him
He says it was a number of years in the past Pacific
Think about that
13 different districts as a teacher
Special
Education
Teacher apps
You know maybe there's a possibility that that's some kind of a like
Like consultancy kind of rolls around to different schools I could not like
You're a teacher one-year here they are.
No no reason why you being a bunch of different districts
But there's a position I can imagine that
If it exists there
But it put that that to me I think they
If you were in that kind of a role where you're in a bunch
A different District
You probably would have less time intimately knowing the students
Marriott probably would have
You're kind of in and out
It seems like you would be I don't
No
1 reasons I don't know cuz it's not specific at all
Say anything and that is that if this is the day after
He's calling into info
He is
Yeah
I mean there's probably
So Alex
He's like
Okay we're coming up on the end of the
The first hour here and 1 second hour begin
Is that hole like little time where no one's listening
I'm going to put you on hold for that
Alright
Will you hold
Yessir
Please don't hang up Matthew
Utah
All because we don't do this
We are barely in the black
More bills
Oh man I'm not mad
For I guess Dave
Came up with new building
Overwrite
XO have these bills are larger than
$8000000 sure sure sure
Yep melt
Alright the very big Bill's cool man
Yeah so those other companies that he owns it should really started adding adding 2nd
So
Fun things
That next five minutes no I'm fat. Ian steps quite a bit cuz we're not on the radio for that
Other stations are playing their own
Top-of-the-hour identification stuff and
Look
I had Twitter I would tweet out that the teachers on everybody to turn it on right now then donating
It is a gift for me I know even though I have no way of proving what you are saying is true
We does
Using his own instinct
At the end of the first
Aldi
Teacher I
What he's talking about
So I have no idea this collars for real or not and neither does Alex
The idea that a special education teacher would call into the show the next day makes Alex feel special though so no matter what
But regardless of how flimsy evidence baby
Alex is always going to believe a color like
Best yep that's not to say that it's definitely a prank or a liar I have no idea but I also don't know
Information
It's program
This may be a real Caller work with him
Maybe a Texas special education teacher who's misremembering work
Working with him or it could all be bogus but the important
Thing is that Alex has no idea what the deal is
And it's very unwise for him to act like the
The lack of any vetting and acceptance of whatever claims are convenient for you
To go about doing a new show
I mean all the way
Going back to the Arkansas Department of Transportation is on the road
You know like just
Are you. Doesn't matter if this seems like work a cover it
Call some call makes enough sense to make a guess what
That part of it has decided to new address to looks like a demon
You just take whatever comes in and then f*** it is
Cares Act
F****** Zach Zach from the north
Dick cam
Where is Zaxby's day I don't know
He was cute for a while
We talked about this on the last episode
Literally every time
Shooting
Is that he claims that the police stood down
He does this even in other instances like the unite the right rally
Right
Various other things is always a police stand down that
Explains away issues that he doesn't want to deal with these don't tell me that ironically this time he is going to claim that there was no
Police Stand Down
Just like Cruz
Parkland
Oh my God
Yeah isn't that wild most down here isn't that wild that is so f****** crazy
He always makes that claim in this
This one instance
I think what this is
Where the simulation it's bizarre
This is like that moment where Rogan is like all this is too good it has to be true I reject this this is too good it has to be
I was pretty surprised I when I was listening and I heard that Jose
Wow that's on Fortune
Jennifer Alex crazy
But I think
Part of that is
Probably because the story of
The guy not waiting
For backup and going in his two good
Yeah Alex enjoys back quite a bit with a gun that's the that's the story that everybody wants to
To tell feel like he's obsessing about that story much but I do think that holding onto it is
More important than necessarily pushing a stand down
The needle of like well some people were told to stand down but this guy was the hero.
Yeah I know that's not going to happen
So this caller who's
The
Teacher
He has some
Making I think of Alex Wood
Really have a tough time with this
This wasn't a collar that he
Thanks has a big dick
Just start where you liking
Yessir
Special education graduate school in Texas
Domino's open in fours listener
I've been that way a long time
I haven't always occur
Agree with everything you say
But I do respect you
And so
Long story short
Those kids
Brian
Whenever they had economy was good
And what they do have there
They're very worn people
People
And so basically what happens is when
A lot of these kids
They needed our Direction
Structure
Lost it
Cuz they weren't there with us
And there's a lot of good teachers out there
This is really complicated Alex should really hate with
This caller is saying
On the one hand it's good because he's making shooting about the pandemic which Alex
Going to work with
Distraction from the idea of talking about gun regulation or building up red flag laws for
Violent people
On the other hand is colors entire premises so counter to Infowars ideology that Alex should hang up on him
SkyWars
Teacher in Uvalde
This guy is saying that one of the driving forces behind the shooting was at the pandemic happened in these students who needed the structure of
Public Schools didn't have
School anymore
And they fell upon
Alex hate Publix
He thinks they're globalist indoctrination
Concentra
Consistent
With his position to be argued that being in a special education program was proof that Ramos was being mind-controlled
The position he should be taking up
Alex should respond to this by accusing the guy of advocating for locking everyone up in school prison
He constantly yells but other state doesn't need to raise your children
As an attack on public schools but I guess in this case it's okay
That's weird
I mean he should borderline be telling the caller that the caller had something to do with it
You should be grilling information during the special education program and you knew this kid
How what what's going on in the special education program did you know jolly and west
Have you betrayed in mind control
This is where the college
Gets to Alex
Asking
Before like
Specific
And this color does not have
Not specifically talking about him but this is a big public interest
Your anonymous
Here
What did You observe
Disappeared during the lockout
Not really.
What what child are young man did you see
Vs21 that reportedly did this atrocity
So I saw him I saw more a social Alex to wear in somebody
A young person that has
They're going to be more
By themselves they might be social but they're going to be socialist like a select group of students
And so
He was more just
Tunisia
Removed from the situation
Especially at the end of the day
I would go out and I have students all over the place and I'm like
How I ended a lot of proactive educators
And I'll walk around and I just kind of get the 10
Temperature what's going on around the kids
Because I want to know what's going on
There's nothing like really
There's no real
Information that's being
Transfer makes me think that maybe he was actually involved in
The Texas school
6in Subway because
Who's someone goofing or like
Being a guy
The hopes I probably would have something a little bit more interesting
Yeah
No it does seem like he was like this kid was in one of my
Let you know
He's just like everybody else essentially
Yeah
I would be maybe fine
Believe me I'd like some sort of a passing
Like
He may be ran into a wall
That's kind of my vibe is that maybe he's exaggerating
Maybe he's not necessarily making everything up by
I think he might be inserting himself into the story where I think sometimes that's the way people process things you know like
You can't
Count the number of times when a like a celebrity dies people post like
I met him once.
Make things about yourself a little bit
It's not always narcissism a little bit of
Process
Scraping our own way
Yeah I feel like possibly that's
That's something
Here
Who knows maybe it is kintyre Lakeside and that's not good
2 is just like
The
Least expensive half hour
On this call
India's no idea who this person is he has no idea if they're actually
Who they claim to be right it does it's treated as automatically true because it's better if
It's not good cuz you open yourself up to
All sorts of possible
People who are doing hoaxes
I mean yeah once you do that
It's too late for you yourself up to someone f****** with you for 20 years years
Years of your life
So Alex has heard that Ramos
It would shoot BB guns and throw
First stop
This car is in what have you
Alex wasn't that bad
Or was he
BB guns
And worse group and it goes from BB gun real gun
But I did on Halloween run around and
You know people and then
Throwing a pumpkin off of a bridge
They have a pickup truck that killed people next
Years later
For things like
Alex's
Murdered people
If you believe him
The worst thing he's done is throwing a pumpkin off a bridge he said he literally stopped
Someone's
Gutter
There's blood everywhere
People he's murdered
According to him
What people in a coma
Definitely
Yes we are pumpkins
Don't go with murder that didn't happen
Alex claiming he's murder people
So
This is a just Alex
Expressing there should be more cops in
Some schools
From what I can see in the reports
Attack unit from the border patrol just
Almost like writing that area they respond
Before they even had backup
Which is a testament to how
Betrayed our law enforcement is
And I think the only short way in the quick way to solve this is too neatly
Police are not
And all schools
Agree with you stay there
They are so
That's not a good prescription for any
Nope cops do not make schools safer
Some May mean well in some cases but the empirical evidence
Shows that there
Side effects
Driving up Lisa
Schools that aren't necessarily positive
Yeah
Alex
Furious
We going to have mechanisms
Place
I don't agree with the
Purchase
Without going
Through some sort of
Mental evaluation
You're barely developing especially while standing on that
Travis autistic
Was he on the Spectrum
Violating this is further information
Unfortunately I'm not I don't want to comment on that Alex
18 year old shouldn't be able to buy guns that a psych evaluation
That seems like Alex will be serious about that I don't think he would like that if Chuckie Schumer tried to pass that as a law or
Suggested that was a good idea yeah I don't think you would like it if anybody other than this particular person
At this particular time
Headset that
Yep
Probably
Alex's suggest no some suggestions
Of
Mind control
As he does
Typically in the cases of mass shooting
It's weird since he's just gotten off of
Cassandra
Do special needs teachers
Allegedly worked
Program
Show Goes On
The culture is mind control
Solutely so living in
Culture is
What you're calling
Globalist mind
Control the entire culture so it's meaningless
So in order to stop school shootings
Stop culture
Right and so instead of that we're just going to do Stewart school shooting
I mean you just have to like if you want to stop this evening
Problem which is caused by the mind
Control of the globalist
You destroy Alves
Messages of culture that isn't
Pure God
Yeah
Everything is just Kirk
Cameron movies
Great
Alex getting really high with Mike Tyson
Cicadas around
So everyone's got to be homeschooled apparently that's
Probably isn't but that's the lockdown the lockdown was homeschooling and then they said that that was the
She's on your mind. Danielle
I'm just a happy
Homeschool mom
Boy I got to tell you
Sorry that's what you have to say
Day after
It's time to stop letting other people teacher
Econo Lodge shoelaces how to be a good person
Whole education
System is program
Or system it's over that's gone
To some degree
When you
Hear these conversations
What you should really take away from them is the solutions that they're proposing art Solutions
Cuz they don't want Public Schools
To continue to exist
If there are continued mass shootings
Constantly
Works in the favor of the right-wing ideology because eventually maybe it'll get to a point where it's just on
Unsustainable to have public school I mean
More cops in schools makes
Public Schools less safe so they want more more cops in schools over and over and over again
The issue is with the school
It's not with
The shooting
Ideology
Yeah that's that's why a lot of these
Attacks have
You know Ben
I'm not naughty shooting attacks
With the attack on the right-wing I've had to do with the school board
Well I mean it's
It's it's
Classic clue rules
You know
We have the person
We have the weapon and we have where it happened
So we can't do anything about the person
They'd rather die than do anything about the weapon
So we got to get rid of the place
Tim Curry
Great movie
So
Alex's had a lot of
Prophecy
And divine experiences everything that he said
Now we learn about another one
This is what he's never talked
What about before
It's really old iosol definitely didn't happen
You and shed
2 years ago the locked
What 278
On the verge of starvation
Nailed it
40 million people
Think about that
Telestory
I had a vision
When I was three years old
It's one of my earliest most intense memories
And
Starving African children
That were just crying out
Parents remember this
And it was real loud Shane
But it was ignition
To not let what was coming even bigger
Happen
And I remember
Spiritually feeling the Holy Spirit
You're going to help mitigate this you're going to help stop
Does your mission
Sorrow
And the desperation of those
Was
It was the most intense thing that ever happened in my life
Arnon nothing's ever been 110
And it was a lot more complex than then I try to
Demon
Friends are family and I I guess if you times
You said your parents
Like 3 years old
Oh man
God giving him a mission you think of maybe he would have made food
Food insecurity of the developing world are really important part of his career
Like you know it'd be the focus of one of his
12 documentaries Maybe
I mean generally speaking
If I was
3 years old and given a vision and the purpose from God 25
Fight one of the horsemen
Single-handedly
I would have
Not started Infowars
Right seems counterintuitive
Weird how this only comes up when there's some other political Point Alex is trying to make by using starving people as a prop
He doesn't really seem to give a s*** about the issue outside of that context
All you need to know is that before Trump
The only politician Alex ever went to bed for with Ron Paul who made the elimination of all foreign aid one of the pillars of his
Run for the presidency which Alex reported wholeheartedly
The elimination of foreign aid would kill a number of people that would be
So hard to ask
Given
How much of our a ghost
Things like the eradication of smallpox
Programs
And the humanitarian concerns of also
Astronomic
For Alex the image of people starving in the developing world isn't something that he saw individual knee was 3 and is informed his career ever
It's a prop you can use to push other agendas he actually cares about like agitating against covid
Restriction and minimize in the murder of 19 elementary school children
He's a colossal piece of s*** and it's degrading how he tries to wrap up his
Detestable politics
Near some kind of holy Quest
Compassionate God gave him in his childhood
Just horseshit
Yep f****** hate the
Does nonsense
I saw a commercial I didn't get a vision
Feed the Children infomercial
A cup of coffee commercial that would play
And it's just
Huh boy
How is it that you can if it's a human
A f*****-up thing
That you can point to a problem that's unsolvable as a way to avoid solving a problem that is solvable
What is it on solve the
Exactly
So how do we do that what kind of psychopath
Nonsense species are we
Insane
You can't just go
World population they're useless in Let It Die
If we do that
Weaponized
And we don't live those people up
We don't do that
Tell you now
Salvador Ramos
Hoses is the people trying to save people
True story
So you might notice until until sometimes mentioned having to lift up these people in the developing world but he won't ever really expand on what that mean
Inside outside of just insisting that the political positions he already holds
Well if the side effects
Active lifting them up
Like trickle-down
Yeah well I was the one who said they can't have fridges so I assume he
Just wants everybody to have a refrigerator
And cars
I burn a lot more fossil fuels and everything
What does empty garbage that he throws around
This these ideas like we need to lift people up
Not the feet
Lifting them up if it gets into some sort of replacement adjacent
It's like
Britain in the f****** early 1900 these like listen we need to bring these inferior mongrels up and you
Not how that what are you doing
You racist piece of s***
Also it's so cool how a day after the shooting Alex is imploring the audience to save the Salvador Ramos is
Society
You really don't see that kind of Grace and understanding being applied
Across-the-board for murderers that Alex talks about no
I was thinking about it and I honestly have almost no idea why you would say something like that
It's completely bizarre and probably dipped into fairly disrespectful territory considering that this is the next
I mean it really feels like what
He's trying to do here is a response to what
He's done in the past
Of like
Here are the things that I've always done and I'm going to try different ones today
And somehow it's worse
Yeah
I am you may notice bed by now we're no ways into this
The night before he was misidentifying
Why the trans women as the shooter.
Say I'm sorry for misidentify
Didn't happen just pretend it never happened
I never happened now that's why you do it at a special report that you know it's not on the air
So we get another caller this guy's weird
In Texas welcome here on the air
Hey Alex how you doing
It is
I just want to say
God bless everyone in Uvalde and God bless all of us
Going to these times
Another thing is
You know
Chicopee drug test
Call teachers
The scoreboard
Number to other liabilities
In the Doctor's lab
Mother in the school board's laps
Are they in a video game
Should we have
Hey Mental Health
Questionnaire
Games
Guns and have them transfer
Bygones have an FFL
Bgl video game
License
We're going to have to do
Jumping
Protect these children
Any schools
Armed guards walking around
Looking at their
And nothing's going on Garden garbage
Restaurants
Garbage
Jewelry shop
The jewelry is not worth our children or everything
I have no idea why this caller is suggesting all this s*** seems like just a list of non sequiturs
Yeah that's it's not like
No schools have armed
Regards
For the year 2015 to 2016 the national Center for education
Statistics reported 42.9% of all Publix
Schools have quote
Sworn Law Enforcement Officers routinely carrying a firearm
In 2021 researchers at Suny Albany looked at the school data from 2014
In order to assess what effect having armed officers in schools hat
They found that having an arm
School resource officer quote
Increases the likelihood of a school shooting
But they do point out that it's a small link
On the flip side quote
The introduction of an SRO does appear to improve general student safety by decreasing non-firearm related by
Violent offenses
Such as physical attacks
And fights
It's probably hard to attribute the slight increase in the likelihood of a shooting
To the presence of the officer
Seems like a pretty decent chance that the decrease in fights is probably due to them being there
Not necessarily the fact they've a gun butt
Security officer were tend to have that effect
But there's a big downside
The study also found
From the study
Quote
This benefit comes at a high cost of a
Increase disciplinary response
By both the school and law enforcement
We find that sros increase the incidence of in-school suspension out-of-school suspension expulsion
Police referral and arrest particularly in middle and high schools
For many of these disciplinary consequences The increased use of punishment is over two times larger for black students than whites do
And significantly larger for students with disabilities
Then students without
Disabilities
Sros also increase the rate of chronic abs
Empieza
The ideal just dropping an armed guard do a schooling
Considering the job done here isn't the solution
They're very troubling side effects
Exit appear to be related to that decision that need to be weighed against the illusion of safety that they provide
I think it's just much more complicated then the idea of like let's put it Army in there whisper
No I mean there that the problem is
Is basically this
We know how to solve the
But they don't want to do that
So instead they have to come up with
Something
And what they wind up coming up with makes it worse
It happens every time because they don't want to solve the problem
So his mother weird ideas
Do we not have mass
Extra
Any
Bulletproof blast on the
The doors
We have them in Bang
Psycho
Spiritually targeting Are Young
What
Actually drugs
Okay
These kids trying to beyond all this.
They shouldn't be
Too much dope
F****** yerrid
It's interesting that Alex is like
It's not police
Conspiracy theorist who was like
Episode of competing with Alex I would
Suggest maybe that
But look the globalists are really just creating the ID
Do you have that there's a bunch of psychos around in order for them to get it the police stayed in that you would accept
Yep
The whole thing about a police state is you don't get one until somebody convinces you that you need
Need one by using
I mean Alex thinks it's ganglion dialectic bulshit that's what I should be happy
Pretty right now
Is that they're making this to bring in a police state and he's like
Listen
What's not a police state
I want to stop a police state even in the face of violence either that you don't have any water
Over and over and over and over again
We see the way that Alex like
All of his Posse Comitatus ideas and martial law fears go away when it's Trump doing it
You know it's it's it's
It's circumstantial it's not it's not ideological it's not there's no principle behind it
It's just the
Pure into the presentation of principles and it's like Ted Nugent saying he's well-researched all of course you know it
Because it's about themselves it's about building themselves up as being both Heroes Intelligence being
All of these amazing things
Yeah and by not solving the problem would get to continue using that appearance as sort of a
No weapon
Anyway the same color is even more time ideas believe that
Yeah hip also is
The joke it's nothing more than an end
Apartment lies
And I know there's some
Advantages of it
But you ask anyone what's your name
They gladly tell you everything that's wrong with them
Secret
It's just a weapon
Well said sir thank you so much for the call Unity
Well said
Wow well said
List of things that don't even make sense
I need to drug test teachers we should Retreat schools like bank vault
We need to get rid of HIPAA laws
That's one of those things where it's just like this guy just knows words
But you just heard buzzword
And he knows problems
FAU just tries to combine them in like a note draw the line
Back of a cereal box game infamous
Powerful
It was a powerful
So you get another color
Pick-n-Pull
I don't know he'll just tell you what's wrong with them
Will voluntarily tell you the issues they have medical leave
Should be no problem that the
Sofia is all be disclosed without your permission you understand though that if I was like Hey I want a job
I don't tell people that I have
Don't hire him those laws
Protect people
Another caller and this guy has some some ideas about social media
And how it was Poppin
The f*** off the day before
This would be perfect
Replace for Alex to bring up how
You know he had misreported
Some stuff yesterday and apologize but no
I just wanted to make
Point
Yesterday
With the aftermath of the shooting
Social media was going crazy and of course you got
Liberal representative
Naughty
Representative
Senators and all that
Question to you is
At what point do they have enough
Vilified
And then go back on
Being a baby
What
They have no debate
I think it's interesting that they Scholars like it's popping off on social media and it's like a liberals being mean to conserve
You know Paul gosar shared misidentification of the shooter
Quite late I mean.
You know that's so that's a much more
Meaningful
Thing I was happening on social media much more damaging then
Libs being mad at
Conservatives are whatever
Yeah
But I mean
Narrative
What's so
Engrain from like
What 20
2014 on of just like
Liberals are always WeatherBug and they blame everybody after tragedy and all that stuff
Now and then like they just
Everybody who tried that just kind of
Stopped
But the conservatives are like well we can just still
Keep saying that over and over and over again it doesn't matter if they do it or not and we can do it but because that narrative is
Stronger than the medial even help them out.
They'll find one tweet
Of Lego Batman all Liberals are
Also like a lot of Alex's
People
Assertive in his
Same
Territorial politics
Revolves around aggrievement
Feelings of persecution and so projecting those onto the rest
The world feels right
Yeah so there's something that's sort of emotionally satisfying
Handsome millier
About
Dealing with all of these situation
That way
Totally fine it's just some Cirque
Circumstances were slightly different
Front with the shooting
They want open-air drug Market
All the pro-life people all the gun owners were to blame
It is in
This may sound kind of
The minute and I couldn't help but think of it
If that shooter would have went into a nursery in shop babies
Twenty-something pregnant women
Yeah they would have
Praise him as a hero saying he was
Pro-choice
We are at that point where they
5 years old
These people
The killing us in a year
That's crazy
I understand that
Maybe there's some
Cone that we don't quite capture or whatever that like
This is understood by some people as an exaggeration or
Some sort of
You like it and I was like they're legitimately saying like if you just shot pregnant women
It'll be totally fine with the Dems who want to abort people after they're born
Feels like that's an actual
Feeling
That's what I mean where at
We're at they're going to start just murdered
I mean that
F****** that if you can respond to a school shooting
With
The Liberals are so evil they want to kill babe
Then you there's been there then we're not humans
We're not should you cannot believe that I'm a human being
And I would be like Stokes if a guy murdered a bunch of babies
Yep that's not good now they're going to
Information
Again but again this is the stuff that like
Beautiful every reason to think this was a key
I need to get your opinion on this Alex I was talking to a friend of mine this morning
Enough money to buy those guns and all that ammo
I don't know I'm not versed on those two probably well more than me
How does that kid get all that body armor because it sounds like he was in a heck of a shootout with the cops
He got in
Before the special agent
I would think that body on
I don't know how an eighteen-year-old
Alarm security
Well trained border patrol
Very suspicious
Just because I was not the case
Answer that one that is a good question
Those things don't sound right
Yep you are correct
The cops are f****** lie
Ghetto Alex wants to get into a little bit of the news
Little bit add lights from a couple weeks ago but
The story is essentially meant
Attitude
Deliver the point
That
Nowhere
The Dam's like to make a big
Deal out of these things I can capitalize on but
When there ain't
Antifa goons go out
Do violence and share never get in trouble or get in trouble at all
No prison time
The man who shot Aurora protest
Wallet
Driving through the crowd
Shot two people
Call Amy
Drove into a crowd of protesters which is driving through them
Interstate 225 in the summer 2020
120 days in jail followed by
5 months probation
But it's all time served
Samuel Young
No prison time
Superman
Who shot Aurora protest
Just from what Alex reads there he's contradicted the no prison
X x
He said he did the 120 days is it time served for Alex to use
This was a situation where there was a protest at Aurora Colorado and I jeep was driving slowly through a crab
Cheapest speeding towards people murderous intent
That far cuz I don't know if there was actual intention to hit
People
He was not concerned for safety
The driver
And that situation this guy but Alice was talking about fired some shots at the Jeep
And ended up hitting two other protests
It was dumb
The guy's apologized and Taken full responsibility for his actions
And he never would have used the gun if it weren't the situation where he felt there was an immediate threat
Although its calculation may have been a little bit alright
Also the victims asked the court for restorative justice which the judge took into
Consideration
The person driving the jeep also didn't get charged with anything so all-in-all considering that the victims were
Severely injured in the fact
You know what other not
In favor of him getting any jail time right
Seems like there should be more of a teachable situation as opposed to one
Does use for outrage bait
The guy has different politics than Alex though so it's just proof that the left in
Globalist get away with everything while
Strike make a big deal out of mass shootings at elementary school
Left is getting away with everything if this
Was
A right-wing protesters shooting at a left-wing driver in a car
Alex will be like I wish he would kill more
Left-wing people driving in cars
Spoken about
So it's like I mean I just I just
Whatever you want to be true about liberals is what you're going to
I just don't I don't like
76 more calls
And this guy
Intrigued
I wanted to know more
Another thing Alex we got to get the hell out of this
Virtual world
This virtual world is blending into our third world or 3D reality
We've lost touch when you lost connection
There's no more neighbors reaching out to each other
Cuz I saw a couple neighbors having a crawfish boil method only get three or four neighbors to come over and eat crawfish with into them
Scared by the damn media
How is traffic
Yeah it stinks the major gets wet
We're loose
Touch with 3D World
Nicola Church
The love we're losing all that
The media scared people away from the crawfish boil at
On other shows
The theory is that this guy was not invited to the cross
He said that he saw some people have
I was at a neighbor's crawfish suggest that we don't have neighbors anymore and then
Then observe that his neighbors were having fun without him
What some
He didn't but he wasn't there and he didn't get an invite
How did you not know that only three neighbors were invited
I mean who knows how many words I didn't didn't show up but yet he can't know the inner work
Who knows maybe he did get an invitation
He was afraid to go because of these reported on
That's a fair point as well
Yeah I want a good Crawfish Boil I don't know I just
It's a
The Crawfish
Kind of
Kind of way to solve a lot of problems
Sure
So are we get another color or as a dumb idea
Feel something
Annual convention in Houston
This weekend
Republican
You don't think this is crazy
Call becomes an era
It's very
Is it
So if you listen to this show you'll notice a trend in that is that a lot of the collars are trying to float possible pieces of evidence
So they can use to argue that there was for knowledge of the attack and then they're trying to Workshop a motive
It almost feels like a reaching out to Alex
To get his Blessing on this reason that they're suspicious
Any pretty much unfailingly will give them the reassurance they're looking for it's a super unhealthy Dynamic like this guy is calling
Isn't it weird that the NRA conference is coming up in Houston
And I was like that is
Is very suspicious
Encouraging this line of thought that this guy is clearly on
If the NRA meeting has anything to do with the shooting
Prior to the NRA meeting
Scheduled to be before the NRA meeting which means there was a plan
That has something to do with being posed to the NRA
Back to the globalists back to the libs
Sprite
It's just Alex should not be
Just sew blanket encouraging of the thought patterns
Is there
Especially when they're contradictory shorts
Beach call
From call the call I know that makes
Violent video games in
Also yeah absolutely
The violent video games have got to go
That's weird
The same color has another dumb idea
A f****** after 2 that's so hard to wrap my head around specially that lady just being like I'm a happy home school
One parent right now you
You f****** psycho
Netgear that guy hat
What I understand
Being interested
Myself
Depending on the quality of the guns
Wendy's
Disappeared
Was it off somewhere where a communist cell was
Natick
John
20 years 20 plus years RI
That's
The saddest thing I've ever heard
Yep
That is
Start made me take a little bit of a like lean back in my chair
Who what wear
Forward stories let's see
Infowars listener
20 years
Long-time colors Plumbing
I forget I mean like yeah you have somebody who's listen to Alex for
Entire last
Two decades
They've called in to share in the experience with him
And the day after mass shooting
Disappeared communist Training Center has not get more just
That put that on and put it in an encyclopedia next to the next to what happens with this information
20 years of listening
My first thought is this guy was taken to a
Communist cell and trained on how to murder children
That makes sense
It's it's
I think
Indicative of
You know like people who have ID
Ideas
About
Conspiracies
Can call into Alex's show healing courage
You make it feel like they were in This Together working on this thing that kind of sucks them in a little bit more
Keeps them like
Gibson like getting guy that the validation that they're looking
Before yeah I mean you want to say that we're more complex animals but boy
Positive validation really goes a long
F****** way towards getting you to do weird s***
20 years in the trenches 20 years
So Alex
Now
Didn't happen anymore because this gas is on a totally different type
There is just so much going on
World government convening
Turlock
Fabulously
Thomas Ranch
Experience
Lawyer
He's been
There's a lot of successful lawsuit
Salon.com
Texaslotto.com
You can describe Thomas Rams a lot of ways but
Experienced lawyer is definitely not one of them
He just passed the bar in 2019 and is mostly been filing frivolous lawsuits
He's really become more of a media personality and Fringe right-wing talk shows and going on the reawakened America
Tour that was full of lunatics
Stand-up comedy from Jim Breuer
A September 2021 article in the Washington
The post describes his litigation history like this
All but two of the eight coronavirus related Federal lawsuits Rams his father in the early stage
The exemptions
These are the suit against a hospital system in Michigan that was withdrawn on September 10th
That's days after it was filed
And 10 hiyo officials that was withdrawn after a judge said it was nearly quote
Incomprehensible
Also before finally passing the bar in 2019 on his fifth attempt
Attempt
Works at a credit union
We're multiple women made sexual harassment
Complaints against them
One of them including an instance where he quote
Flipped his hand down the front of my upper breast and commented oops
He all-in-all seems like a real a****** and someone who's not a pretty lucrative hustle for himself in the anti-vax world
So I guess he's coming on to talk about the terror of my
Yeah
So that's where we're going for the ref
Oh man
Yep these f******
Guys
How do you
Step to a clip comes up
About
About this
Terrible things that
Pfizer is announcer
What I mean listen we was in Pfizer
You can swallow these ships and then we can track and it'll be perfect
We played
Monday or maybe Sunday
Wow we show the clip but he's already lied about it
Physically
He's claiming his recent like they're announcing message at 1 about track
Can people write this is a comment that the
The CEO of Pfizer made in 2018 about a bill of 5 mysite
Which is a unique medication used to treat schizophrenia bipolar disorder and depression
Oh I know
It contains the sensor which quote sends a message to the transmit information
Into a mobile app
This is disgusting the context of breakthroughs in medicine and is specifically in response to a question from the audience
So you can create the best medication around but
It doesn't matter the patient does
Take it
What's being done on the technological side there
Took off and dumb dumb anti-vax and covid conspiracy circles
Countless memes have been shared
With no context apply to people claiming that the recent clip
Melissa people do with the pandemic
Alex and Rams are just reposting that mean while
Send another doing
Some kind of reporting and embarrassingly
Alex decides it is where he's going to take a shot at the mainstream media for not playing clips
What a douche
Yep
4 years
Ago
And they're still claiming that it's brand new
And it's about the pain.
Right it's just recently found it and I'll lying about the context.
To push the conspiracy theories that they were already pushing
Yeah
That's weak s***
Yep if it's you just have to put like a f******
Hey all done did you see that video here's the timestamp
Shut up
That's that bulshit
Get out of here
So has another clip from the world economic Forum because that was actually in a talk
At the world economic forum
In front of Alex
I think it's pretty funny that I would because
It does show that Rob has a little bit of a sense of humor are you
Freewheel August of covid-19
Sexy movements
Conspiracy people
Her claiming said I had Pitbull
I wonder what it is
April
Ecobee
I know you will also Target
Pirate's plunder
But was arrested by FBI
Surprising things about the same publication
What is the previous one
So what they do is they put themselves in Criminal
Does that mean
You're not the target you are the target
Yeah I don't know that the target of misinformation
A target of our guns or something that's the most
Sensible read I can make of that Chasm really make sense
So yeah I just thought that was kind of funny that I
Play that is pretty funny
That the pope was arrested
That's pretty you've got pretty Steve pieczenik
I think he's referencing Stephen Roanoke
Has been arrested a lot of people in qanon have push that
Weird less specifically than Steve
And I wish I would like to see if the pope had like a LoJack
Back it out
Translate looked up his robes for a second and ankle bracelets
Displays and then they go to commercial
Realizes
Ifucking respond
Schwab in that clip
I miss
Is the worst promo I've ever
Super important Alex
Respond to that last clip that you just played
Because those two arrogant pieces of garbage
Bitter out there telling us what they're going to do
Is he being in Good Company
I got a message for you guys
I'm a nobody from a little town in Ohio
Yeah you are
A whole bunch of other nobodies
Little places in the United States
It stood up and we are at a much lower rate of vaccination than you ever thought we would be you thought you were going to
Take us over you didn't know
We nobody's
We are the resistant
We the People
Thanks to Alex Jones
Oh boy
Put him on a lookout Shay
We got a new t-shirt coming into colleges all over the world
You resisted lower than you could have imagined
Alex's bullhorn
Are vaccinations rated lower than you ever thought
Cool your goddess
Wow
So I just don't know how to say Eragon
Cantwell
So we get to the discussion of monkeypox
And it's pretty dumb
We've got
They've done getting function on monkey paw
Monkeypox
And I'm hoping it doesn't spread
Scenario happening with the monkeypox
That you know they ran their simulations they've been planning for
Been building up for all this nonsense
So here's my question
Is monkeypox
It's running around now
Is this at natural monkeypox
Or is this another game to function oops release
And we don't know that yet we don't know
The only reason the Thomas friends doesn't know what the
Situation isn't much boxes cuz he is an idiot
He hasn't looked
Intuit at all
He's a right-wing clout doctor for all it's worth another fun season of scamming for monkeypox
He plays his cards right
A friend has been a couple minutes on the subject before writing it substack
I can come on out
The show to discuss the topic he knows nothing about
He would know that samples from the current outbreak have been
Studied and are clearly from the West African strain that is exist
For a long time
Their number series about exactly how the outbreak is happened
A couple of them involving Raves and large Gatherings shared various countries share
More will likely be known
Specifically in time
What there is currently no evidence of his that monkeypox
Just made in the lab is a bioweapon or is going to lead to lockdowns or first vaccination
That's all
The dumb bulshit the people like Alex and Rams used to keep their customer base scared
And
In their customer base yeah you know it's
It's been a long time since we've had to use that old adage you know Raven Denmark means monkeypox in Florida
But it's it's
It's old
Strong
Still after all these years
Thomas Jefferson
You know I was just I was just thinking we're going to hear that
Over the next
Rest of our lives
Again and again and again and again
This is just like what they did with covid
Is going to dog us until we die
Sure you know like working at 4
Twenty years from now they'll be like all this is just like the gain of function they did with covid
It's just never going to stop but I think
Like unfortunately
You did have that
Exactly Namek playing out
Just in
Like under the surface
Conspiracy communities
With like terrorist attack like 9/11
That kind of stuff
Those
Conspiracy communities were just largely ignored they did not have as much impact on
People's actual lives
And so yeah I think I think it's more a
Republican Ascend awareness
Problem
But it is like a
This thought process is right
That's not new
Right right it's just it having an impact on people who don't choose to engage with
Dumb conspiracy world
Yep and that's on Fortune
A
And I think it's a little abet
Infowars
They look it looks like it could be a false flag looks a Mite been made and will happen if it's not
I don't think there's a God but hey I'm just going to say maybe I believe in the morning. But it was not monkeypox probably be something
There's going to be a next time
They're not giving this up
Defeat this evil
Continue lockdown
Normal
What's the summer rage
I did another sub
Let's not Overlook the summer great
Do you think Alex has talked about this
Spoken sparingly of the summer of Rage
I can't
I can't handle that being a present-day thing that is being talked about December 8th
Hang over here every year on Alex's stupid show
I think
I think this is a disgraceful
Text Dave
One of the things that I think is worth noting is that a lot of the
Shifting details
Did not necessarily happen in the first
Birthday
Some of that little bit
Further down the line
But you already see the nebulousness of this in terms of Alex's coverage
The day of when he did his emergency report we had this misidentification
And everything is like mad death
And now we have
Misreporting
That is understandable
About like the border patrol guy going in quick
Sure
I just think
Weird that he said that there wasn't the stand that I mean
It's almost like at validates him making s*** up
Because when he tried not to make s*** up it was wrong it was a lie
Can't be right no matter what make it up
Even when I try not to make it up
I'm foolish it makes me Alex Jones Is Right memes all the more bizarre
Will be back on on Monday and we'll track a little bit further down the road and 80 how things go as
As details start to emerge in the Alex S2
Deal with stuff that might be in his kind of wheel has to stay one step ahead but when there is chaos and can
Confusing that is something that he is
Well versed
In exploiting
And the cement
Stillwell
True
Long driving
We'll see what happens but until then Jordan Reed website
Jordan
Leo mdch Clark I hope you all have a dreamy creamy sauce
And now here comes
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work