Damn important
I have great respect for Tenaya Lodge Lake
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Celine even talk a little bit about
Alex
Jordan Jordan
Dreamy creamy summer keeps on rolling
Although I don't know if it would roll it sort of
Pirates black
It's Platinum long over the sidewalk
It is melting down hill or something
I'd like to give a shout out to
I have enjoyed and so this is a
No no no
Disqualified
Okay
Cool house house house got to street today churro flavored
Ice cream
Alright
I don't think it's
Great I don't know
Maybe it's good maybe it's not I don't know but I enjoy it
Play little bit of chocolate and cinnamon situation going on
Great I'll tell you that
If you like that
Cinnamon roll
I could do that also everyone stop sending me pictures of The Grey Poupon ice cream
I got the mustard I don't know if it's real or not I don't care I will not be eating it
That's going to be at the end of December that's going to be like the demarcation
The 70s you know
You'll know whenever everybody is gone to ship
That's the way you do it
We could we could well I mean September 11th so
They would make mustard ice cream
My right side and you would think
Today being today
That Rafa winning is 40
You French Open would be my bride
I thought that happened already
He defeated Djokovic
Because defeating Djokovic was winning the French Open
What he did to a let's call him a man but what he left with
Today would make him
Suggest that he was not
See the other murdered this man the young guy who was a Hotshot
That you were into
Okay
Made it all the way to the final the French Open. Would be good to do that and then Rafa committed what could be
He described his vehicular manslaughter with a truck
Oh dude only 16 games
In three sets
636 360
My bright spot
I don't know how to assess that as a tennis court but it doesn't sound good
Okay it's real bad
To see cigarettes in concert yeah first time in 15 years
They are
Absolutely as good as they were I'm sorry I couldn't join you I was busy working on this episode and then my computer crashed and I
I lost everything yes it would have been about
How do you qualify head
Well you would have gotten
Does e-cigarettes
That's true
But a good time
Amazing jump
You can't you can't describe it
Cigarettes my partner
She is not an interested fan of cigarettes
Imagination
But when you see them live
It's not
Just
That is likely to experience
Installation
I get the full on
Greatest track
I'm so Jordan what is not an art installation is the episode tonight
We are continuing our path through Alex Jones coverage
After the Uvalde shooting and
Subsequent Corrections statements made by public officials in Texas
That's when some of the stuff
Was starting to get a little bit
Mercure
The initial reports were very clearly like we got some of this
All wrong
I mean the weirdest part about living in the
The future now is that we know
What we're going to listen to the correction
Themselves are lies
Sure so it's like
We're going to hear them correct their own lies with who lies and we're going to be like this is what's supposed to be happening today
I get that and simultaneously
We don't really know even as we sit here today 100% of what you would really need to know
No in order to
Fully address
Some of Alex's claims that did this whole thing
Weekend we can deal with it as it as it appears and we can definitely see Trends and behave
Until well well perhaps some of
The fact-checking aspect of it might be a little bit
We may have to leave that for posterity to some extent
But yeah this is this this episodes pretty interesting I would say I think there are some
Very out of
Character moves
Interest that he make
Still not quite sure what I think about it I might need your help to
Through a little
Hello
James and I are here asking all the listeners to play we know the devil it's a great game on switch
Beam
Text Alex Jones The Lazy Man's
Guasaca
How to rack
Quizlet Harem shirts of Dune reference really absorbed
Thank you very much that's eating downtown Austin didn't get mugged
Thank you so much
I don't know Andy from afraid to ask
I'm a policy wonk
Spider bites and Audrey got a couple of technocrats in the mix incidentally there were requests
Play the old technocrat drop
More than
I was going to say which old technocrat drought so I don't know I've got one and I hope it's the right one
Caribbean black accident again I'm not sure which one is which
Been listening since 2017 and I'm so damn proud of you guys
Kevin thank you so much you are now a technocrat
Don't get mad at someone
Sodomites
Has a Caribbean
Jesus Christ
I don't know whoever made that one had a good
Forgot about some of those some of those comments
So Jordan today like I said we're going over May 26th
Somebody is missing in action
Good morning ladies and gentlemen and welcome to the
Alex Jones Show I'm Harrison Smith sitting in momentarily for Alex Jones he had a family
Engagement
Doing right now so he'll be in
Maybe 30 or 45
Some of the news here in the meantime but he is on his way
Sew-ins
It turns out Alex shows up
47 minutes into the show I believe
The youngest child graduation
Confirm like kindergarten definitely willing to believe that
Cause to take off work support that
Yeah I've no no shade
That's the saddest words in the world
Be welcome to the Alex Jones Show I'm Harrison
Underwhelming for sure it's not what you're looking for
You're looking a lot of times you get a strong sense that Alex is playing with lawyers
Or something but this
Brighten the right time of year for in the right time
Well that or anything
Listen to Infowars
Is going to go away
Daughters are forever it's nothing
And what did they broadcasted on the life
47 minutes
Into the show
Correction to me
Not also blaming the police we have a lot of inside information
Also been confirmed and we have Tim Enloe
Ashamed
Lee's trainer
I do actually use the Meghan Trainor
Police Department in courthouses
Contractor License
Continue
With this other stuff
Has a lot of sources a lot of mint
So Tim Enloe is Alex's security guy
He was also with him on January 6th with black water
Our our mercenary
Former mercenary Soldier of Fortune
Weird that Alex is coming right out of the gate being like we have a correction
Send to make appointment normal behavior for him
I think I should get one of these
The instances the correction is much easier to to swallow
Or someone like Alex
It's because
And everybody's making
Can Corrections
Left and right
I don't think anybody has been like
Wow I mailed it
Yeah hero people directions to people who just
I don't know what's going on I'm not going to say anything
Yeah it's until I think that he recognizes that temperature is there and he has a chance to Pivot off whatever narratives he's on it
Start over
True Freedom true freedom
And so here is basically him doing that
But he specifically
Has a lot of sources a lot of Intel
This morning
Was that
It was a hostage situation because he wasn't shooting peep
Class Hosta
Stitch
He killed the cat
Everybody saying all the police are out there
It's horrible image of your children and
Process
It's a hostage situation
It looks like the way Alex is going to try to make sense of the delayed police response in the new information that's coming out is by claiming that
It wasn't actually a school shooting but instead was a Hosta
Situation
I can kind of understand how Alex will be coming
To this point but they're still major holes
Open this idea
It would make sense to claim
Maybe the police
Thought
But it was a hostage situation
But even that doesn't really make sense given the information
Unavailable
Also just one small note
Is this is going to be a little bit
Murky territory
Alex
Steve
Openly talking about having behind-the-scenes secret sources of information
So the way I was looking
Cafes with like judging him solely by what's public information chair
Kind of can't be how we approach this anymore
And we can have a little bit more of Our Own
Actual awareness
Of information
So
I don't know it's not going to be
But he is no longer bound by the public information rules
So I on May 27th the Texas Department of Safety
Steven McGraw
Gave a press conference where he explains the police decision to not bark
Through the classroom door
This was the result of
The commander on scene making the incorrect
Determination that the situation to transition
From an active shooter to a barricaded suspect
Which might deployment
Different tactics
Explanation included a determination that because there were so many shots fired immediately there was likely no one alive in
In the classroom
And they possibly the shooter was trying to lower them in so he could
Commit suicide by cop
Sure
So that also
Has problems
Because there were 911 calls that they received said the people were alive inside
Make sense
Using that
Kind of
View
Kind of see how Alex could make a leap
Hostage situation
Sure
But they're still proud
The first
Is it
The police
Treat this like a Hosta
Situation
They allegedly thought there were no more children at risk
It didn't think
Shooter had
According to the statements that were made in my Prescott
And there wasn't like a hostage
Negotiator that came in the tin
Landslide a phone in or anything
Alex had some basic details in here wrong about the shooter not killing people initially
Ultimately
It's nice of him to do a correction but
He's going to do another
Why bother
At this point
In time
The correction you make is this
They started saying some s***
Anna doesn't
Track
Cuz that's also not the same s*** they said earlier and now
When we said that it doesn't
Those m************
Foodlion
You can't do that and I'll explain why later obviously
You know
You have to do something
I think
Because Alex is entire narrative
Of the shooting hinged around the idea that this hero cop
I took the took the shooter out quickly
And that was something that was sold on his show and so now you need to
More details come out people in your audience are probably going to hear these things
That are contradictory to the story that you told
You can't keep going
The same Direct
Can you have a slightly different direction
This
Is
An interesting way to
To do it
I think
Doesn't it does not hold out it's real bad
Listen to The Main Street
That was really good
Brandon the school first shot of people at funeral home
Minutes
Border patrol agent
The door
Shooting star
The doors
Steel barrel
All the shootings going on
Get the door open show
Obviously
The left is using this form or defund the police
Federalize the police
So there's no indication of the classroom door operate
It's the way I was just
Describing like some kind of a Panic Room situation
Where once a lockdown is initiated can't be opened except by a very specific action
It was just like
Colonel McCraw was very
We're of that not breaking down the door was a decision the police made based on a miscalculation of the situation
Any press conferences even discussed how Ramos entered the classroom
Lock the door and then unlocked it to momentarily enter the hallway
Only to re-enter the room and relock the door
Additional problems with this idea Alex is putting forth
Here are one
If the police had a convenient excuse like we literally could not open that door
That would have been front-and-center as an explanation for what happened because it would make a lot
Of the worst details of this police response
Easier to understand
It'll be like well
Now we have a new problem we need to look at which is a would-be
Over-the-moon constantly repeating like we did everything we possibly could
Fingers would be coming to the manufacturer of the door
And it would be a sensible deflection of of the conversation
Are guns weren't big enough to blow up that door
And we would have given more money to the car
Shuffle level of b*******
Nobody has bazooka
Just all the time
Sure that's what the second problem here is that that door whatever it is that has no bearing on the situation
If it actually was a hostage
Situation
You can take hostages in a bank vault or a treehouse
Like ultimately this
Just feels like a way that Alex is trying to make sure no one in the audience has too much of a bad feeling about the
Police
Like Mr play
Police state really it hits differ
In 2022 I think the one thing
That really
Disappointed
About
The the ideological re realignment
Is that
The left
And The Sovereign citizen
Adjacent types
Should be in
Accord regarding
Only
Just like
Be careful
You know like I don't know no
Not okay well not all the way like The Sovereign citizen
Hilltop the traffic stops alright
You can also. The other direction where you defend them
Questioningly that is kind of strange
This impetus on Alex's bar but I think I do understand
As we go along I think I'd get that aspect
Guns are more important than not living in a police state
I don't think that's
What's going on
I think that there are certain Dynamics
That are essential for what Alex is doing
That require him to not be
Critical of Apple
Anything you make site to clear
Okay Alex really is into this
New narrative that it was primarily a hostage situation and not actually
School shooting
But this garbage one on
For an hour
That's what's going on
Tails are coming out
Democratic Party
Ancillary continue to try to give you the best most accurate information
Come on
Monday night
30 bottom of the hour
In about 40 minutes from now
To break it all down
Calling is contacts
Contacts everywhere
So he's got to Enloe the Exmark who's going to be his expert
Portion of this episode
Alright he's interview with with Tim which is
Less productive than
View my
I don't know what you would think it was
It's fair enough trouble as soon as I started that sounds productive
Before Tim comes in there's other there's other things Alex
Complain about
Monkeypox
Oh my God
Other stuff going on
The new lockdown
Mongering
Finally a lot of leaders.
Today
We can't allow this
Turn off the fossil fuels going to kill
Collapses
The left just has
Policies they don't know what they're doing or mousy tongue
About to kill millions of people
Before our eyes
That is a very
Everything is going on while the media
Does it blows it up
Vermillion
The problem is
Can't really find a way to articulate what he's
Sing Mary cuz he's like Alright look there's a lot of bad stuff so why
Why are we allowing the left in the globalist right turned this into the worst thing ever
Also even if you just killed one kid it would be the worst time ever
What are you saying
She just wants
Get to the endpoint where it's like this is obviously the less fault and it's fine if you be humanize them in Uno
Get rid of all of them I think he wants
To minimize the shooting but also realizes that doing so is a really bad look and distaste
Facebook I mean if your end goal is to say
No matter what
This isn't guns fault
Then everything that you're trying to make up
To get there is going to get eventually
Stupid
So there
Look we all know there have been a number of things
That I have been put forth
About
The early police response
That has
But not held up
That is definitely
Understand
Yeah
Alex blamed the media for this
Media first reported
But the media
They shot the police
When is the school shooting
The police didn't know it was going on the side
Barricaded inside then
Here and there in the news they're admitting that's the case
So again there's no Stand Down
Lamport
And you will get to that eventually at some point
How to Alex's acting like the media wasn't just reporting what the spokespeople for the Texas Department of Public Safety
You were saying
He sincerely is trying to suggest that I would like CNN or the X who definitely did get stuff wrong we're just make
Taking those things up
The reason for this is because Alex constantly makes things up and he assumes that everyone else does too
He doesn't seem to have a concept that other people don't base their reporting on hunches Vibes and made-up decades-old
Prophetic vision
Like he does
But
I mean it would cause some
Confusion obvious
Reality behind that though is if you follow at equality Alec on Twitter he's obsessed with Copic
Ganda and the way that the media
Just accept unquestioningly
The things that the cops
Tell her just put it as their own sources
And that's where we are so if you want to criticize the media in this situation that because they unquestionably reported
A different criticism totally a different kind of valid
But he doesn't
No cuz that would be productive productive
Ain't this is what
I think part of a big part of what's going on and that is
Situation realistically would have some difficulty getting off the ground
Alex is trying to push this new narrative 40 Menlo has this inside Intel about I was a hostage situation but
This information is coming from where
The credibility of what Tim has to say rest entirely on the notion that he's relaying information from high-level law enforcement sources
Score familiar with a case
If that's the game you're playing you can't also be sniffing out a mess
Conspiracy where the police are being forthright about the response to the shooting
And if given inaccurate statements to the Press multiple
Full-time so far
If you attack The credibility of the police you're hindering your ability to pass off whatever information Tim has
Has being meaningful or at very least
You may have to explain why the information the police have released publicly has been iffy
And the information released the Tim should be believed
By making these inaccuracies and misreporting that's gone on in this case a situation where the media lied
You can sidestep the need to explain anything
Hannah gives you a chance to take a fraudulent cheap shot at the media while you're at it
Big part of
What are you doing
Yeah
I mean
You can't
Assume that the police are lying
You have a
Or even
Like if you want to put it
It's super benevolently
Fumbling their public statements so terribly
That they have to make
Fundamental
You can't have that and also try me like we have inside or police sources who are giving us the real skinny
Because
Then you have whistleblower so you don't have
Tide information
If the official narrative is bulge
And you've got a
On the background
Anonymous sources coming in to tell you the truth than they are telling you the whistleblower's report
That means that either
Everybody
The whistleblowers are telling the truth
Yeah yeah and it gets too complicated after that point
Can't do it
Never
Another school shooting
And realize
Is about
He is going to be in studio with us
He has contacts
Right now
Exactly what went on inside
That building when the police
Globalist
We expose them
Robbers and Killers you see all the time
School shooting last year
He was out the next morning from
Weirdo Alex amazing we went to racism
So fast
Yeah it definitely seems like a relevant detail in this case and not something that he's just bringing up because it reinforces the White victimhood theme of his show
White people get away with everything this isn't necessary for this
Going to throw this in there for
For fun so this guy because his parents paid bail
Like I guess Alex wants people detained without bail at being what do you want
He's injured four people after bringing gun to school and shooting at a guy who got in a fight with and in February
You're a grand jury indicted him on seven charges
Including 34 attempted murder
Like Alex is acting like they just let him go I mean no trouble
The impression that he wants the audience to have in their head fries he hasn't kept up with this case
Lying about it and he's like these black people just get away with everything
Whenever and whenever you be even when you like look
EBay further into that store you're like way to sec
Cash bail system is so f***** up how does this kid get to get out whenever so many other people would be in there because I can't
Like there's a larger question around that that he's not even f****** willing
Sure
As is always the case with Infowars stories inside a larger useful question
That is just completely ignore
So
Alex has to deal a little bit with the notion that they didn't let the
The parents
Yeah that one's going to be real tough to try and lie about
Let's just say
He does not deal with some of the
More troubling realities of
The paratroopers
Well maybe doesn't know
Right I'm not sure that the cops
Off to one of the parents I'm not sure
He thinks it's an unfortunate but sensible thing
Get Smart
Absolutely
Learn from this app
Just to say
It was a hot
Hostage situation
What was going on
And information changes we will definitely let you know
Monkeypox
The Western world and
More shortages coming as a supply chain
Breakdown
Now to keep Infowars on the air because our supply chains broken down Ark
Currently $8000000 in Bitcoin is not enough to get him to buy a little class
Wow
Pretty smooth
It's pretty smooth
And but if
If you buy my stuff
Then maybe the cops will do better next time
Palm Terrier horrible things
But not of those are why you got to keep me around listen if you don't buy my products then who is going to tell you when these Arab
I have made materially no
In terms of solving any of the problems that I'm yelling about
And in fact I have misreported on pretty much all of them
That's why you need to give me money to keep me on a hair
Excuse me
Libertango
I'm going to play you a clip
From 1998
And it'd be saying the same thing that I'm saying
Today
How do you feel about that
25 years in between
What's the I think they actually like
If it's somebody who's like we need to lower taxes
It's like it shows ideologic
Consistent
That's nice
But
If it comes tomorrow
Consistent Maybe
Expression anything throw that money somewhere else yeah some bad news
About the New World Order
Ladies and gentlemen we are back on this Thursday May 26th 2022 transmission
It is
Does give
Power of the UN over National sovereignty
Publicly
The UN has
Veto power over country's sovereignty which speech to the nation did Biden come out and was like listen
I love being the president of the Free World and I have an absurd amount of power and influence and all that stuff but frankly
I'm going to give all of that up
To some people at the UN I don't know why
The UN is going to just be able to veto
Just like I'll be like way we view of sovereignty
I know you don't it's so funny to me
How obsessed
Alex's with the UN
And then at the
The same time like we are one of only three nations
Absolutely hate for you and
To their face like an Australian in Russia
Constantly going back
Forthwith like f*** you Europe
Over and over and over again
Yeah and just remember this
Is just about the amendments to the World Health Organization regulations
Where they can do
Declare that something is a a health emergency
Even if a country is not cooperating if it did happen
Three weeks into his we need to demonize China for covid
Good thing he would have been like
Now we've got a
No cuz
Something true
Yeah
Are you being over selling this amendment might be an overreaction
Maybe
Florida.
So we have very few instances of Alex learning
That is true
However I think this next clip indicates
At least
Something
Interested
Dismantling
Where in the world in the body
I don't want that
American
Heads above other countries on average
Unless
You live in Luxembourg or sweatshirt
Luxembourg Germany
Luxembourg
A person could not
Live in a place like that
Lowest crime rate in the world
Luxembourg
In France.
Oh I'm sorry I forgot that was excited
Switzerland
Is definitely country with the High Cost of Living
Three of their cities coming in the top 10 of Mercer's cost-of-living rankings
420 21
Zurich is number 6
Geneva is 8
Is 10
I'm going to assume that this is a place
It's so expensive to live that suddenly getting an 8 million-dollar windfall
Still wouldn't
Give you like a years
Brent book Alex's willowshade he could afford to live wherever you want course but also Luxembourg
Doesn't make that list
I don't know until number 63 Luxembourg City is 63 on the way higher than
Luxembourg Chicago 45 I could afford to live in Luxembourg
Based on the fact that I have survived Chicago
By the transitive property I am a Luxembourg in Luxembourg
Theory
Smaller
Literally in their art
Someplace
What is
Sure
Anyway
The country that's all I really
So are we get to this conversation with the Tim Enloe
Ex Blackwater fella
Because he used a Blackwater Inn
Kind of forgot about all that mercenary kills people
For my dad I was just to be used except as a thing that we talked about
But then this guy is like I'm going to go kill people for money you stupid
Anyway Alex that's a conversation by getting
Something's wrong
We're here to get the facts on happened Monday afternoon in Uvalde Texas
Friend
Timer for the police
Also doesn't
Courthouse
You want to get more
Vehicle
Schram
Holding hostages
Confirm but it's not being pushed
Dad
The police just go down
I'm not sure what to
Confirm means to Alex but again the media didn't just report these things
Like they didn't make them up
They were Miss statements made by public officials that were underneath the things that got missed
Reported
That's an important thing to understand like when the actual media is getting something wrong it's generally because there was an official that made
Inaccurate state
When Alex get something wrong like in this case how we reported that the shooter was Trans on Monday evening
It's because he saw some dumb s*** on fortunate decided to run with it
As if it meant anything there's a world of difference
These kinds of getting it wrong and Alex hasn't even owned up to
To the fact that he
No course not
Disgraceful Monday night coverage
Absolutely I can put somebody
Danger
It is
In his mind it makes
Perfect sense
That's cuz it's like Alyssa
I report on my sources you report on your sources
I don't know
Government
And my sources are weirdo randoms on Fortune I don't know what is
What's so different between you and I
Because the weirdos in the government
Cat always
Be correct
That does not make him equivalent to a random person on Torch
Feel like Alex
Sitting across from Blake's
Buckhead
Edward armero
Heat like we're not so different
You know what to say
Simple fact
But Alex is getting wrong here
The first is that Ramos did start firing pretty much immediately
He was shooting at the school prior to entering and within his first minute or so inside he shot over 100 rounds
The door wasn't an armored door and there's no indication that this was a hostage
What are the things that worry
Please me about hearing Alex talk about a Hosta
Message situation is that there's a certain high-profile hostage negotiator that Alex is friends with
And this could be a way to shoehorn pechanec back into the show
I was worried about that
A boy
I checked Steve Twitter and it appears that he's never been in on this hostage
Degenerative
Something I was getting from him all right
But he does definitely think that it's a staged false flag possibly with actors
Spaetzle
Apparently Steve gameplay false flag on Twitter so he calls fingers
French fries
Instead of false flag
Alright
Okay
That's
Words
So Alex one of the main thrust
It really is running through so much of this
He's just
Just like he does not want people to like
Blame but
You sure with us to talk about this
Hi and he can give you what a sources are telling him and
You should known
Show again
Changing the song The Police
Izzy Izzy
It's just a little childish
To pretend that you
You can't have criticism of the police response
And also at the same time keeping your mind that the person who did the shooting his response
Audible for doing the shooting
That is absurd
That Alex has that kind of a expectation of people
Being only able to
Keep one thought in their mind
I guess f******
Politics brain in 2022 it's always
Everything is always
Distilled back down until what the right or the left
You're doing and it
It's this and it's that and it
You know what though here's a thought I'd just had was that you can only keep one thought in your head when someone's yelling at
Sinestro
So maybe
That's why you yellow people to try and focus
Kiss Batman 21 thought otherwise all over the place
So maybe Alex has an X
PlayStation theater
The audience can only keep one thought in there because
Through 20 years of empirical evidence right
Them getting yelled at by family can only keep one thought is I don't know
To look at his 25-year ass career and be like
I think we understand it.
True
So Tim
I got to say
The information that he provides
Sounds
Fairly similar interests who the stuff that is said by
Colonel McCraw
The next day at the Prescott
So I am not
Are off from believing that Tim
Absolutely does I have some police sources
Probably has
Line on the information that would be
Given now
Sorry this is such a f*****-up situation in our in our
Perspective of it
Because Alex is trying to Parrot the truth
When he never does
And in so doing is wrong
Alex has the source
With actual sources
Which never happens
Seemingly yes they're wrong
And it's one of the things that's even weirder about it
Is that
Know for sure obviously but it sounds a lot like
The information that came out the next day air
It's not the information that Alex is reporting
And I think that there was a weird distinction here right here's the basic gist of what Timber
The first one
In the very very early stages of
The investigation risers
Literally every hour every day
Bright sofa
At the entrance that is
Appears.
That's a Some Kind of contact was made with
With the shooter
He went into the
School
And then somehow
And then potentially lock
That door or somehow barricade
Door
Couldn't immediately go in after
The other thing is that I'm hearing is that
Guy ran into school
Start shooting
But now they're saying that he may have been in that classroom for up
Words of
30 to 45 minutes
Not
Is a bear
Call rather than an active shooter
Now that matches fairly closely with what the colonel said the neck
That does not describe a hostage situation. And there's a couple of very important
Distinction
One is that when in love
That he wasn't shooting for long periods of time
Is
True
And enough in terms of
It's like matching information that we have
But you also is ignoring the part where they were that over 100 round shot
Right
There is
There's element
Of this
That the mixing some of the wrong stuff with some of the stuff that would come out the next none of it adds up to
The conclusion that Alex's
Clearly using this information right build the hostage situation narrative
The way he's reporting this
He came in with the gun
Didn't kill anybody
I'm in an hour later
Started killing
Because it was a hostage situation
Will presumably I don't know what the goal was or what he was trying to hold them hostage
Thought on that
You can see hear something with that bed Dynamic is really really interesting I've
That Tim
Probably is getting information from the police
And Alex is embellishing on top of it
Yeah it is it is a little bit like
What we're seeing from the police
In this situation is
Very similar to like a f******
Teen
Like a teen who got caught
Not doing something and just really doesn't want to tell though the stuff that really makes him look bad
Each time they tell the story it's sure there's a little bit this
And I'm willing to admit that I made some mistakes here but
This is what I really didn't you're like no you f****** didn't
And so on and so forth
And then Alex is out here like a f******
Best friend he didn't do nothing he didn't even more is that
Yeah it is a little strange how much damage control Alex essentially doing
4 police
I just I hate having to live in a world where we live through all these Obama years where these people
Where the f******
We'll start shooting and we're amazing aware the f****** strong
Tea party s*** another whinging bootlickers
Trying to protect the cops from even the slightest bit
Accountability
The case also coming up later
Alex revealed a little bit too much about where is headspaces the police
Protesters are eventually going to cause a problem
So
Tim believes that what the problem
Homestead
Police just didn't have the tool that they needed to get in that door
Crazy people
That hardening once they're in to get the police off
That's exactly right
And unfortunately
At least initial
Officers that were on scene
Probably did not have the breaching equipment that
To immediately breached
Right
And so obviously.
Problematic
Have to look at it
You know there's already and you covered it
For the last few days ride
Cries about all we need to do something gun control
The usual drivel that we hear from the left
What we're really dealing with here is not taking things away
For example
Every law enforcement officer should have a
Breaching tool in his car
It well either battering ram or some kind of
You know like that sometimes
Pry bar
Seems like Alex with B deposed
To that
In the past
I know that
Militarisation Andover over accessorizing the police
Kind of one of his big issues
Yeah but also this doesn't match up with somebody information that we've gotten
Consent
The notion that it was a choice to
Not
Lakebridge the door
And that it was just locked
And they had to go find a teacher with keys
Said the school resource off
Officers with keys to every door in the
Most of them
If not all
Well
Well I mean what's the point of having a police officer if you
You can lock them out of your room
Fair enough
So
The tissue that you
I really have to get there
Sorry I shouldn't have but I should have thought
Yeah I know I sent that you were thinking
And you shouldn't do that
Seasonic which is great
The villains
Obviously
The police in Texas we know wanted to go in in
Kill this this is crazy
Obviously the primary responsibility for the shooting is on the shooter but this is a pretty embarrassing
Send presentation from Alex
Just the way he's going about
There's some very serious anomalies with this situation and his world's number one conspiracy theorist and
Arch-nemesis of the police state
His to implore the audience not
The question details of
Response a banana
I'm empathetic to the police and what they have to go through
Particularly on a day like that
But to pretend that the media is unfairly scrutinizing this thing or
The people are blaming them for the shooting
Dishonest framing
This is so out of character for Alex that I don't know what to think
The police have said that they didn't enter the classroom because they felt they were no longer kids at risk and things have gone
YouTube from an active shooter to a barricaded suspect
But this is severely called into question by the numerous 911 calls that people made from inside the room
Unless no one was talking
Do anyone else that assessment of the situation that they made shouldn't never
Have been that far off from reality
A detail like that is what Alex makes his living off of
You go back and you look at all of his supposed to submission to bypass
Best mass shootings and they're all stuff like that
In terms of Sandy Hook Alex made a big deal out of the erroneous claims from Wolfgang halbig like that they didn't let
The paramedics and EMTs into the school
And he latched onto s*** that flimsy in order to craft
Conspiracy narrative
And yet in this case he doesn't seem
To be doing the thing that he tends to always
I mean it is
It is
Almost
Cosmically ironic
It is almost
Cosmically
I have
Finally
Taken
One thing
From the past 4 years
Sandy Hook lawsuits
Which is I'm not going to question
Whether or not what's going on happen
And this is
She's the one
F****** time in his career
Well no it's not but you know what I mean
Like conspiracy theorizing about this
Even conspiracy theory rising in terms of the lease I think it's irresponsible
But
Having some questions about like
How was this misconstrued so badly
Where was the decision made that was so wrong
In terms of the response
How how did
Taking a full accounting of how this happen
Is
Something
You know himself on he questions thing yeah
Not doing that
Yeah
He's questioning other aspect
To this
And whether or not whether or not the shooter was
Isn't the Satan or something yeah
Yep
I don't know
Cuz it seems like the conspiracy is that afterwards part you know like it's
Fairly clear from what we do know and can at least
Concretely understand is that
All of these cowards walked in and
Drip just acted
Cowardly
And then later whenever people started questioning they were like oh s*** this
This is not how we want to be presented we're supposed to be like f***
King Leonidas in the 300 protecting the people
From the onslaught of the f****** Persian so they made it up that and they tried to coordinate
And then it fell apart cuz they can't
There's a lot of appearances
Yeah I have a difficult time
Fully signing on to what you're saying
There are some leads that you're making sure but
It's there's going to need to be a lot of explanation
Because
It's confusing it's it's a it's a situation that
Is boggling
There are there are
Potentially
Interesting explanation conspiracy
Totally I think one of our I mean ultimately the root cause
Is we have
An entire now 5th
Branch of government
That is entirely built around not taking responsibility for anything
I mean there's a problem there yep that's true
So look Alex doesn't worship
Bring the cops though
I mean kind of
But he's not real
I'm not hearing some
Worship the police brown-nosing position
Because I know the boys have their own prom licking their food
Do you like the police
Mobile control
Get your children like I do
How to get you in a gaucho
Keep some of your children
Graduation
Graduation today
You look at this you just can't imagine somebody
Plumber to come to your house and fix
The pipe
Police showing up
Then that process happens
This is a mess
You can't
Blame the
Plumber
4 knots
Fixing your pipes
What
Here's the thing
I understand that
50 part you know like Alyssa
If I'm Xavier telling me like oh no and I'm a soldier in Iraq imagine them coming up over the thing
Hang in there firing bullets at you there I would never be in that situation
They are because they
Spent their life
Training for it
In theory training if you yes
So if you're the cops
I understand that you are sick I would want to be there.
Yeah and I'm particularly empathetic to what you have to
Experience
So situation
It's like it's
Unsinkable
But
It doesn't remove
The
The sort of
Responsibility to act
Because that is your job
Yep and you have that training you chose it
You learned it
You did all the stuff and then
I mean and honestly you took our money to do it like we are paying you
So
So Tim has
Something of an idea
I think this is bad
Vsn ID
This thing I'm seeing in
I didn't tell you this before
Actually wrote
Kids superintendent
Yesterday right
About the shooting in LA
Everything in this standard
Oh you know we're so sorry about
Hearts go out
And he mentioned
Presents possibly at the school for the next few days
Priest police
Presence
Was an officer
Pretty much
Enclosed
Pistol
That was inside the school kind of walking
Bright
Equipment
Is that where
Freight in this country
Foreign officer
To be walking around with an assault rifle
The school wybie
Because it freaks
They think it's going to
A bunch of kids be famous
He wants
AR-15
Cops in uniform basically at schools
This isn't good you know the thing I was thinking
Is that
Sure America has the most
People in prison ever
And are worse than
Apartheid-era South Africa and are racist to enforcement of that
Policing
But
The problem was
Kids weren't already in
Like what they should have done is my prisons from the
Beginning you know like
You get you turn 60 you go to prison
You got an armed guard walking around with an AR-15 make
I'm sure that your
Right
That's got to be a every
Preschool
What's the best thing for
In for school security
I think these officers need to have a Arthur
Dwayne some lock
Or somewhere but they need to have them on their person
They're big boys that are black
Should be standard
Still don't have
School resource officers or police officers station
It's time that changes
Preschool America
Trained security officer or police officer
Security guard
I find this
Trouble light
It seems like parody honestly
The dissolution you have is
Like people sick every single school is got somebody toting an AR-15 around
Great
You know what's fun about
People with AR-15s do you remember earlier on an episode when he was like
Well we've got all these lockdown things and then
But then when they get in they
They can use the lock
Sound measures against you
Right now
Let me throw this out there
What if I can't afford an
Bright
I don't I don't work
I do I'm just a harmless
But I know where to get one
Weekly around all goddamn day
Yeah I mean do you know there are definitely stories of the good guy with a gun who gets his gun taken away from me
No
I don't know if it's seven-year-olds going to be able to get that AR-15
That but like
This is
It is parody
We've seen the same response from people
That like
Evereve School needs
Good guy with a gun now
In response
What's to the single-most
Apt example of why that's the worst idea
Haha
I mean like in the situation in the shooting
It definitely would not have helped
Like unless
I guess
The person who happened to have the AR-15
The Epic School
Who is the good guy
Was right where the shooter enter
Was at that door
Is there a different part of the school
The entrance still probably would have happened
And
I guess once he's lock that door
What you going to do
Unfortunately it seems as though our defensive measures
Are actually offense
Towards us
Maybe there's
Maybe we're stupid
Do that
So Alex needs to explain away a little bit of the fact that there was some Milling around
On the part of police
Sure these are these dudes say something that I just fine
In Capri in
Milling around outside waiting for orders at
Bureaucracy
Monday Morning Quarterback
I think what we all need to meet need to come
Come to the realization of his
If there is a report
Or if a subject is seen going into school armed
It doesn't matter it
That moment if you shooting or not
Pastor immediately
By law
Applause
Citizens
A police as far as how to deal with
Force is authorized right
I think I can
Empirical data now it suck
That no one goes into a school
Good intentions
The police need to be trained to respond to that
Huh
That's really interesting perspective for these dudes in 4th
For some reason they think there's a relevant difference between a person going
To a school and a person with a gun going to a school
There's such a difference between them that one is totally fine and normal and the other is someone who maybe should be
Be killed on sight
Because I possibly can today
Can't be up there any good it's impossible
It feels like a difference is that one of these people has a gun
And then having a gun of bad intentions
Because of where they are
This isn't something people like Alex and Tim should ever accept as a possible conclusion because
If you accept this
So many of their gun arguments start to fall apart if you accept this I mean
Stop it like just go f****** killed Kyle Rittenhouse
That's what you said is okay to do
But that's where you're going
For them is that they're opening the door to accepting the idea that there's something about having a gun
In a certain place
Write that means that your intentions are bad
And I can't believe that
Nope
Whole thing doesn't stand up to scrutiny
If somehow having a gun is an indication of ill-will
Yep
So teacher should be allowed and forced to carry guns with them at all times
And as we all know
People never leave guns out
Where other people can get them
Children are never interested in careers
I don't pick up guns ever at all
And definitely don't find themselves outside of the school
Tell
Those kinds of things
Don't worry about it
Problem solved I think so
So Alex has some harsh words
People who have been in their coverage
Again we don't know yet if this is going to be a training issue
They were waiting
Because they didn't hear gunshots immediately or weather
Couldn't get in we don't know
Another left another is just disgusting opportunism
Within a few hours after the shooting Alex relied on a 4chan
Looks to report that the shooter was Tran
Explain his part and a bigoted hate campaign
Throughout that broadcast Alex and Owen incessantly accused psych meds
The being responsible for the shooting with
Zero evidence
The shooter was even on meds
Something that they still have zero evidence up
Now he's trying to get the cops off the hook for their inaccurate statements by reporting that this was awesome
Situation of the media made stuff up
The soul
Feature of Alex's coverage has been
Disgusting Opera
Humanism
He can point the finger does nebulous Boogeyman of the life but he's just talking about himself
That sucks
No further to add one thing I will say is giving lip service to this
Being state
We're going
It is just a Monica
Weird
It is weird
I just can't believe
I think it's only people on the right who care about the mixture
They keep talking about the mister I care I care good bit about the midterms
Concerned I have I have some some worries
Interesting hopefully
Can make some inroads
But yeah
The sense that you get
Is there is a lot
Were the Republicans to gain if they could get all
Of Congress and
And die
Courts
Once they can cement their control it's never getting
Undone
I think that's kind of the way it goes though like it in
In Cycles when
You know the one party wins the presidency there's maybe a little bit of a
Demoralization come the next midterm because the president doesn't live up to the expectations of what you would have hope
They they do kind of a common phenomenon sure and
It's unfortunate because
Is a fairly important
Midtown Promenade
Yeah I mean
If I was
If I was the Democrats
I mean
The problem is they're all going to die soon cuz they're all so old so they don't really care as much but
Man if I wanted to ever have power again I would have done
A lot of the
Things differently
Look Tim
Has this information that he's bringing forth Alex
Is this the special exclusive
Information
And what is inside really interesting about it is that some of it is accurate
At least in terms of what is going to be reported
The next day
Press conference
And some of it is
Not
Some of these
Very off
Interested
These are
This is very off
So the latest
Which was
Posted about an hour ago she says that
He did Exchange
Borrow gun
Far was exchanged
By the school
And then he managed to get into school and then the latest report says
At around 11
43 am
Reported killed
So we're looking at
Wow you around 11 minutes
What time he was shooting or
There was
Fire outside
School
Until reports are in that
We don't know if those were
Inaccurate
But
It certainly gives a more
Timeline that what we've had so far
Yeah he get he gives that caveat but it's very it's very off
That's way off
Yes definitely
You had him shooting at the school
Around
Now so you have that
Which is not necessarily A
Exchanged gunfire
So you can't you know that's right around right before he
Entering the school
The 11 minutes 14 minutes or whatever he's saying there that is
That is very not accurate
I wonder how that's possible I mean I'm guessing maybe
You know there's a
Confluence of sources that he has maybe in summer
That some have some information that the police are going to reveal and some of it is
Wildly off-base
If I was going to speculate based upon this type of
Mustang
And what I know I would say that there's
Is a good chance that he's got some
Some friends who are into
Texas law enforcement
Yes but are not
Specifically there
And they have friends
Who were they
So maybe a little bit of a game of telephone exact
That's possible
Yeah I don't know it's it's bizarre though
Yeah it seems like this is a level of like
Secondhand information
Instead of my buddies who are cops
In the system there said there's this is probably
And what kind of troubles me about this is that like
That directly contradicts
The stuff that Alex is saying about the hot
Situation that went on an hour
And so I never discussed the discrepancy in the information that they're putting forth
Which I find
Hard to manage
Yeah
Call
But look I don't know why you yell cuz you can only keep one thought
Your head at the same time see that's the trick
Don't think about it
So Alex has a another thought about what we should do
What about the symbol thing of a fence around the schools as you pointed out
Portable Buildings in
Trailers that put up that doesn't work
The funds to build bar building or they don't have the space
Whatever the case may be
Because we gave them to the Capri.
Any barriers
Yeah and you know what there should be barbed wire going in
You know what no it makes perfect sense
The only way that schools would get
More money
Is if it literally going to build a wall
I mean it's just ridiculous
This
At the same time I think
My school when I was growing up had a fence around it was like decorative
Are you talking about is like some
The containment Joliet prison
I've been
By their 100 times they are describing exactly what Joliet prison looks like cuz it's even got the red brick
Look a little bit like a school with prisons you'll have overflow and trailer
So Alex takes a look at some of these shooters Pull-Ups
Some pictures looking at them that there
They're psychotic
Psychotic
What are the individuals that did that showing these are obvious psychotic
Yeah
There were abuses in the in the mental institutions in the US No Doubt
One who flies Over the Cuckoo's Nest the 70s
What
Exactly
Yeah we don't institutionalize other people anymore
One of the problems that were
Wow I never would have thought someone like Alex would be so in favor of forced incarceration in Mental Hospitals for people to state.
Beams inside
This is ridiculous because Alex doesn't believe in medicine he doesn't believe in
Psychologist in the very idea of locking people up an asylum before they've committed any crimes isn't direct contradiction
Obvious beliefs about the Bill of Rights
I also would caution him that based on his
Public statements
He might find himself
On the wrong end up getting it
Tatoosh analyzed
If This Were common practice that we're to come back
Oh yeah
There are still Mental Hospitals in the United
Midstates in One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest didn't turn everyone against them
The rest of the world doesn't have all their opinions formed by moves
The way that Alex does
Is true the issue is that most of the public
Funding for mental hospitals has disappeared
And private mental health hospitals often are covered by insurance plans
And Medicaid does not cover long-term mental health care
A large segment of the population has basically no access to these institutions in many people who would
Be helped by them
End up in prison be
Because they don't have access to these things that made
Prevent them
From
Being in a situation where they were
Grimes delete them
There were tonne of variables that go into the very sordid history of mental institutions and a lot of
These transactions
We're already in motion somewhat before Reagan slash
Fun date first aid centers
In his 1981 Omnibus budget reconciliation
Reconciliation
Which is where a lot of people playing crimes it was a big blow
Foursquare
But there were some friends already
It predated.
It's
My opinion on it is like
It isn't the full story to blame Reagan but
Why not yell at anyway not a good story to play Dragon
Can you fuc
Yeah but I'm not going to fight this one
Chick-fil-A app
But it's real enough that many people don't have access to the Mental Health Resources they need but the way Alex is talking about this
The stupid I need to point out a major point
Of belief
Is that like
MK Ultra assassins were brainwashed in mental health
I mean that people should be going to that
Why is he Jolly in West tests on people Mental Hospitals whenever he's just saying
Legacies just saying like we should have a prison for prison people in a prison for people who are
Crazy Irishman of Arkham Asylum galleries who haven't committed crimes
It's just like
Lisa from down the street
Yeah
I tried to get a raise
No I'm here forever dinner in there get her in there
So I called demons
I mean look at them
And if you look in there
You would not
Proper assessment threat assessment of these individuals is some
Something that is seriously lacking
They're suicidal drug addict
Crazy people
Call Dan
Everytime shoot about
Play military game
Oh it's the criminology it's a psychology
Profile
I never seen profile so clear and clear-cut Tim
The profile doesn't match
People
The only if it only matches because
He says the same things about every everything going
Doesn't matter if they actually are
I would love
For him to try and demonstrate
Bike the the everyone's into devil worship
These things are only there only a rock-solid profile because
The unerring
Talking points
Infowars
F****** good profiler if
You just live in a world where everything you say is right and you say the same thing every time
It's a lot simpler
Menlo is got another idea here about
Good guys
Yeah who have gone no taken away
His ideas
Shootings on the slide ride
Who was armed a good guy was armed and pray
Presents
Right I just sent it to him and you know the most the most
People that were shot
In a situation like
Now you go to where
There was no person
And Luca
Call 911
So you looking at 100
And that's just one example ride like
Play called 911 it's 30
34 people
420 247
4640 346 again right
The highest number is 9
521 + 1
It's like it it's just there's a huge to
So
Again this is just dishonest discourse bye-bye than them
Guns have
Continue to save
This is not how you would
Assess these kinds of things
This is just sort of
Take it back I want I want him in there and it's
Got to be down deep in the dark
This Slide the Tim is just
Used it
It's by definition cherry-picks because
He says that the top one on the side of waiting for the police to respond to the Pulse Nightclub shooting but
There were way more people shot in the Las Vegas shooting
There are over 400 people injured by gunfire that day so like
Why is that not on there
Well cuz that makes it really look like if you have a gun and are able to even better if it's
It's a good guy with a gun it's it's on the other side of the equation
What you going to get a snack
Sniper to get up there maybe in the hotel I don't know
Tim has made seem really convincing to an audience that already believes
Conclusion but the
The data doesn't back up what he selling
Instance of a good guy with a gun stopping a shooting you can fight an instance of someone not intervening or someone having
Argon used against them
On a very basic level the National Bureau of economic research released a study in 2017 that found that
Carry laws are associated with 13 to 15 per cent higher aggregate violent crime rate
Ten Years After adoption
Further
A 2013 study in the American Journal of Public Health reviewing data from 1981 to 2010
Found it for every percentage point the gun ownership increased in a certain area
Firearm homicide rates increased by 9%
The good guy with a gun stuff is fun to fantasize about if you're someone like Timber Alex but in the real world it doesn't have the
Statistical back
To be something you really want to seriously rely on
What's imagine a world where this ideology
Get so popular that you end up having a shooting
There's not one guy with a good guy with a Gun there's
10 good guys with a gun
It's probably going to be pretty difficult in the fog of that whole thing to know who's a shooter and who's a good guy with
It really chaotic if this was taken to its like
Logical
Conclusion
Anyways.
Blows my my 1% each percentage point
Equals 9%
Increase well we yes
But also
You'd have to factor in
It would be it wouldn't
Like whatever the previous
Like violent crime rate or firearm homicide rate was
We go up 5.9% of that
Right now I understand the crime was like 8
Percent
8 point
It's going up a whole percentage
08 % that's very different from 8.8
Percent increase
So
We we talked about this a little bit throughout the show and that is this idea that Alex
He's like why is
He's so
Beholding to the police right Terry Witter
Can I take it was like flipping my articulate
Exactly why
This is not a
Other places are good
Who controls them
Put the left with
That's why we can't just
Knee-jerk reaction just go with the letters tattoo place
Brianna percent
I think that's a really sincere articulation of what Alex really thinks
At this point in his coverage is so much of it
Ass kissing exercise for the police
It is mine the globalist in the Patriots are fighting for control of the police
The paramilitary group that holds the Monopoly
Only use of State Force
At this point the police are very much on Alex's team side as evidenced by their different
The protesters a month
Other things
Many other things any other thing
Alex knows that it's I can't possibly continue to get away with the s*** they get away with it
The police stopped going
Very easy on them
Head on sublevel
He thinks he can't be too critical of the police or they'll
Support the Patriots anymore
Elsa come to being federalized by the globalist
So then it's game over for Alex and his buddy
And then further I think Alex does have
Some
Ideas of
A pendant
Collapse
And needing
Vevo
Please
For Sunday the arm
Essentially civilian Army to be
Basically on their side
I'm sorry I interrupted
I think he's afraid
Criticize the police so I think not even simpler but his argument
Is at the end of the day
The police are just a fascist millet
So if the left has control of the fash
I took military it's going to happen to us
And if we have
Control the fastest going to happen to them
Well
Sure but I think that was
Underneath
Why he's acting like he's acting is because he's afraid that reality
He doesn't want to love to have
Control over whether or not the cops are going to allow him to
So yeah I think that kind of might be an indication of what's going on here although it's still soup
Super weird
They could still just so much
It's like out of line with
Really core tenants of Alex's
No
No no
No no no I know
I don't mean like I'm questioning you I mean like I don't know
Hi there it seemed there feels like there's there's something a little bit deeper in might just be a weird day for him into being deferential
Menlo
Like that shirt had honestly could explain a whole lot
Mixed in with this fear of of being critical of the police
I mean at the same time
Weird day to go from your daughter's graduation
At kindergarten
To immediately talk to a mercenary
Weird day
Whiplash
What I'm talking about Alex like just like these things are
Contrary to things that are
Deeply-held like core Infowars s***
Like this is one of
So we need
Equipment
And we need more and more drills at
Keysschools
Prepare for
NeverEnding Abby
It's always change
Dislike
Is something that Alex should never be supported
NeverEnding Mass shooter drills at schools
This is right in line with
His auntie police state ideology right there
That's insane this is almost coming off like a prank quite frankly because
This seems so disconnected from what supposed to be the bigger picture of what Alex is about
He believes these shooter drills traumatize children that are meant to train them to live in a police state where they have to
To comply with the orders of armed men
Arm shooter drills are meant to prepare the Next Generation to leaving tyranny and to train them to be afraid of guns
Which is why the globalist
Do them
And the girls themselves are usually also the false flag right that's actually believes that if
To run a drill
How to prepare for something you're secretly about to do it yourself
There are countless examples of disaster preparation drills or anti-terrorism drills that Alex's
Sister we're just cover for the globalist
To do the real thing
You should hate the idea of widespread never-ending shooter drills
Only because
He should think that would give a globalist
Unlimited opportunities
Cloak their french fries and a drill
Yeah we got to change I'm sorry for his game
It is
It is like
When the chips are down for guns
They are willing to sacrifice every other part of America
Yep that I think it's important
Probably
A way to still love guns
Not be this
You think it would be that hard
A lot of people do it
I would even say the majority of people who own guns
I like
Let's not kill people
I'm leaving to go that far
Probably
Yep
And
Alex's
You got news.
But he's not going
Oh that's
Snooze to cover in the meantime
Take our
Always
I want you to know
But job
Here's the bottom line
Newtonian physics show us what
Stop
/
Albert Einstein
We don't need the
We know it why that for every action there's an opposite Ray
What
Gloria
Moral duty
Stop playing with her sister
The rain
What
I will not use evil
Pinnipedia
Used good
Then why are you keeping the ring
Dimensional coin earlier
Michelle Alban x608
My God
Video that I forgot the play
Wow
Just wow
I am I hit a piece of information from you
Tween
The Tim in Lowe interview and they clip that I just played for you was a full segment
Of Alex promoting that coin the f*** out of here
You son of a b****
For like
7 minutes about the coin
I didn't have the time to get to it
And I can't get to the news cuz I have the ring of Mordor and
Having the ring apart of the the point is that the Ring of order will turn you evil rub to me
That is not cuz he's not a nerve like that nerd
Yeah it's a little frustrated
Yeah we come to the end of this I think that this is developing very weird
Yeah
Flicted
A little bit
Because I do think there's still an interesting
Path
Let's
Been going down
But I worried that I myself am not really enjoying dwelling on this subject
Jack matter as much as I am
And I wonder if the experienced a similar for the audio
So I don't know if
I'm not entirely sure if
For the next episode will
Continue down this path or maybe have some
Something to switch it up
I-22
Mix it up a little bit
I am all over the place
Scout and you ground
With
Solid factual information
And we do not have as much of that as is
Usually the case so I feel like I'm
Flying
Solo
You know what I'm saying
Yeah yeah part it's hard to it's hard to clean to
We'll see how it feels
Whether you like it or not
But until then we have a website
Leo on dzx
Clark
The sex robot
Stringtrimmers
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color