Alexandra Thurston color
We are
Sit around drink novelty Beverages and talk a little bit about Alex
Now we do have a hook
Bhajan popper style hook
Dachshund people on
Blues Traveler
Hebrews 12:1 of
Malu travel
BuzzFeed
Like the Blues Traveler official account
Has been like tweeting out
Satellite images and address
Lexus
Is this really just straight up.
Sing somebody was talking with her
Alright then
Bix
World world we live in
The least weird thing I've ever heard
All the time about how much you love gun
Always carries guns on him and
These high all the time
I did not realize there's a decent my address those chill
Hook brings you back
Rough River Lake
I don't know everything about Alex
Correct groups
Jamaican Me Happy Dan you know why these are called Escape
Cuz that's the name that the actual title of the Pina Colada Song
Escape
Come with me and Escape
If you like pina coladas
If you're not into yoga
We have
We have had
Bottom
As far as music already
To go over today so we've got it
Chose Jamaican Me Happy
One August
One was aspirational
Jamaican Me Happy
Is representative as we've hit an a
Actual record
Downloads
All these milestones in people
Finding us
Inexplicable utter inability to promote
In anyway messages got on Facebook and on the email and over Twitter it's awesome
Most of it's very positive and interesting stuff
A little bit of it awful
A couple dickholes tweeting to get a little bit
We're assholes
Escapes children's
You know what I owe you.
What's that I love first of all be like if you're not into yoga and
Can you do like champagne
That's in his personal ad that he's
He sends out the papers the story the song
It's not it's not for your response to the the personal ad is like
Yep
Enough about Rupert Holmes
The OKCupid
Yeah absolutely but
Before we do that cuz I'm sure we will by the end of the show
Oh that's not bad
Very unique styles of policy
Now I'm either already policy walk decided to
And donate
More
A secondary policy walk status
Which is I don't know policy
C squared 1
Unfortunately I don't have clippers
You're both now
Guys are amazing with
Intricate
Policies
Covered in North Korea I feel like we have to give you know about the intricacies of inter Europe
Country relations
Do you know about what's going on with brexit
If it turns out they both
Support brexit
Okay
An expert
Anyway
It is only appropriate that we are drinking
Seagram's
Jamaican Me Happy
Island style booze in the present
We need to check in and see what was going on
Really heavy as far as news
That's all of it in the history of America
Does not cover any of it
Quartzsite
The reason that this booze is appropriate
Self is
Is because
I didn't realize what was going on
Alex Jones has been in Hawaii for like a week
Posting on Friday
Drinking probably a lot of these Seagram's chiller
You know just hanging out on the beach
Sing with a little bit of extra I would go wrong that's a much better
Pennywise
Alex Jones
Wasn't Hawaii
You would know
Considering your
Missouri River
That's so
Well he wasn't White
Alex Jones
Some of the biggest celebrities in the world
And got an interview
Celebrity couple would you like to guess
No guessing
We're here was Heidi
Montana
Spencer Pratt
What's the popular
Play the cowboy show.
Great again I guess
Protocol check
Can I run into
Barracks
Jones in Hawaii
This should highlight I really think one of Alex like
Strfkr
MSN
Heidi
Spencer or like
These people know what's up
Not giving credibility buckets
Look
Hey get it
She was my
Third
A favorite character on the Hills
Which
Was a show which was a show that starred my
5th favorite character on Laguna Beach
Which was a reality TV show version of a TV show I never watched
Call the o.c.
Blake 90s were weird
I was I was aware that the hills was the thing are you curious about my power rank of people from Laguna Beach
Number 11 low
The reality show was Laguna Beach and The Hills are both reality shows has called the gouna beach the reload
It was a dash of Adam Brody show
COC
It was supposed to be a reality show version of it was a
The disaster
But my favorite character was she going to lunch
She seems like a really great friend never got into too much trouble
Lover
Number two
The guy named Trey
It's really hate tray he made a hat
And gave all the money to charity
You seem like a really cool dude
Chicken entree
What is the late 90s
Give him a bath
The show was on
Number three
There's this guy named
Upholster
He was not a main character on the show at all
But every time
Every time I had a Chiron under his name
It said
Something enthusiasm
So like when he was helping Trey with the hat thing or like
Number for
Not at all baby Lauren was
My fourth favorite who knows anyway
The hill sucked
And I like
Whitney
And Audrina
Raymore
Did Lauren
All right.
God damn fighting
She was terrible
Anyway it was a lot about the hell I spent a lot of time
I spent a lot of time watching those shows when I was younger
Get high
A reality star Lauren on the Hills
Friends with Lauren from the o.c.
To the Hills
And got a job working for a fashion magazine
And so she
I think she like lived next door
Whatever
Celery to accelerate the downfall of a country that could create
Spencer and Heidi
So they were friends she started dating Spencer and they're our friendship fell apart
Spencer / Lauren
Big betrayal
And I don't I know that reality show is manipulative interns
In terms of editing and stuff like that
This interview is going to prove
Even beyond that you can tell from their behavior in real life after the show how consistent it is with how they're portrayed
You can complain about editing if you want I'm sure they did some tricks
Also you
How do you spell Terraria
Hawaii and Alex Jones at
Because they are Proto Maga
Talkabouttd
No cuz that would have been
Belle I want to go back we're doing a second investigation
We want to fight Alex Jones went all-in on Trump
And we wonder whether or not hide
I know that but spin it now
That like because we were against globalism
Because we were Christian
Conservative
They edited me and turned me into a different character
And wrote me off the show
Cuz if you don't play ball with
The globalist there to take you out
And
Alright
Now let's hear this s***
Meteor hit
Hawaii while they were there unfortunately.
Is a little bit
Cuz Alex refuses put the mic close to Heidi's face in his Stanford misogynistic approach to life
He's pretty
Good with giving Spencer the mic
10 years
Yeah last time we saw you
We were
An hour
Pretty irrelevant
Relevant
Hated person that we know
An outside
You took our game and I was a little sad I was here
Super famous
And everyone cares about what
Nobody cares about Spidey anymore
Sweeney Todd
He did what
Serious
Reality
Start
Secret societies in LA
Movie stars
The Second Amendment
Second Amendment
Rich people have bodyguards
Bruce Willis
Oceans 12
Give me a Megastar like Clint Eastwood
Be able to be conservative
In Hollywood anybody else trying to
Brakes repair
Destroyed
Body
What is a start at
So we were chanting death to the New World Order
10 years ago
Documentaries and then about a week later
We are no longer on
Automatically
Since the Inception
If the New World Order is watching
We still will not accept chip
But
You know we will take
Gig in the
Established
Media
Bills to pay
A cell
New World Order where available
Never thought I would say this
Will take a check
For real
Be careful what you say
So at the end
Spencer is basically saying
Play ball
To him by the name that he
Himself even give himself that that's what it's called
Spidey
Spencer Heidi
Like Spider-Man
Explain that that's on me
Rat
I just want to check and Alex has to jump in there to do that horrendous fake laugh
In order to make
Another time later begging for
Hey c'mon
Will you do something
And I also know he's not joking
Cute. They've done
So many sad reality shows
Since they'll
They've done a ton they were on at least two seasons of Big Brother
It's a disaster
Well
Hollywood because of his
Christian conservative
Christian
Conservative beliefs
Do with lack of talent
Well
Response of charisma
They aren't
Like they aren't actors really and they're not convincing even when they're playing version
Of themselves
And playing themselves right there and I hardly believed
Just about acting
It's not like
That's all they do
I also
Spencer was trying to Launch
Now there we go
That included this song
I hate you dad you are not Jamaican me happy right now
The vocals are low in the mixed berry
It's like like Nirvana except for
Write what you know this
This is auto-tuned is f*** but when you get to the chorus I don't want to get there
Doris is pretty expensive
Really do what
Thank you guys so much for listening and now we will punish you with
Alright sorry I wanted to get to the chorus cuz if they it's like
They say I'm superficial they say I'm a b**** because I'm sexy I'm famous
I'm rich
In the
The chord structure
Piling on Heidi and Spencer I think they're total
Same horror
And have been for the better part of my adult life
I've been aware of them as
Mosquitoes
Stuck any blood out of Fame
Nintendo broke
When he was talking to Alex
We used to be the most hated now I'm jealous of you getting all the attention
You took our game
I need
The entirety of my experience with him
So
I love that Alex is like so desperate
Celebrity
This is except
Do you think
Alex
Admittedly they say they knew who Alex
Alex or Alex
Told them who Ali
Probably
Got into his documentaries at some point
I bet
Like no 911 road to tyranny or loose changes
The Obama Deception
Something that he's done
Look there they're idle
Fake celebrity
They have nothing to do they don't have jobs
True that is true somehow have enough money to be in Hawaii
Blues Traveler
Victor their Bungalow in Hawaii
Also by the way
Great look
In Hawaii like it doesn't look like there's much around it sort of secluded
Looks like they really expensive
Resort
Right on the beach
Well-known for budgeting
Inappropriate I don't know where the money
It's not important
Appearances
Yeah
Can we do that
I thought about it
But not considering it but I thought about the logistics of it and I think it would be miserable
Of course
Especially
Yeah
I mean
If you have so many people expecting something of you and
Evie
With some sort of
Smirnoff
Kind of promotion going on
Or perhaps
Jamaican Me Happy
Playerup
No no clubs like the big kind
Dancin everybody's
Canex
That's that's
Terminology
Corey
I learned about dare that was VE in the Dare program I believe
I don't think we're supposed to be in those clubs
I think the last time I went to
It's on like dance dance club
I was in Missouri is place called generic
And they played
Dance Dance Revolution
I did not but I did almost
Get into a fight with
The DJ
Play something decent please
America
Tyrese album it was like Tony
I'm the worst
They do go on to say that they were worried that they were going
Get killed
Like how celebrities get killed by that
Illuminati
Girl celebrities all the time
When they are no longer worthwhile
I don't care
Cuz I'm not here to talk about Spence
Delusions about Alex Jones
Alex
To deal with them Russians
Okay
This is an interesting answer on a beach
What's the deal with the Russian
Spell Mia
Where did they
Hundred percent
If you go to DC or New York
There are Russian
Chinese
From Saudi Arabia
Crawling out
And so Russia
Contrast
Constantly
I'll just use
Defense, they're transferring
Mozart ships
Infiltration
Mass acceleration
Total
Not true
Russia missile
Old world country
Mariah
Hollywood
Social engineering
Weather
Christian Roots
Globalism
Bolshevik
Corporate system
Trump
Russian contacts
Thomasville
Normal Court backgrounds
Turn on Trump
Should I take normal behavior
And blow it up like
Mountain out of a molehill
That's boring the s*** out of me
I can be both molehills
You know what is a great crime that Alex has just committed
Hawaiian boring is s***
If you're watching the video to of this Heidi and Spencer are not entertained
Rambling about
He's like going into being on the show mode daylight
What is it Daylight outside
Tell me the magic hour
Alex is 3/4 in the back you might be a little drunk
But be that as it may this this next clip I think is really telling
And halfway through
What
Within the interview
Yeah I think it is because Alex Jones is most comfortable around people he wants to impress
Okay if we let down some of his guard that he should have
And if he isn't
After a couple of these like Tiki drink
But
He asked
Heidi and Spencer
How real are reality show
Like what is the like what's the most real reality show
And then after that
Ask him a question
And Alex Jones accidentally shows
Of his cards
How many of the realities
Harbour Centre
Totally
I would say
The only reality show
Swallow
Shopbop
Joseph Pizzeria
Lexus
Spencer
Let's get this
He pulled out his phone
He is now
Video
Alex
Infowars
Has his phone out
Recording him and Alex
Being like yeah come on
Give me one of these outbursts
That's Berkeley
No.
Viral clips
Cuz I would love
Trigger line that I say
Worked up
Yeah there they are
Hillary ruling over my family
Ford motor
No she's going to fail
Stop nightmares
I'm glad I don't have no
How to display of how fake his anger is
Is undeniable proof that he just
I don't
I thought that was fake
It sounds exactly like a lot of times again
He's tired of drinking in Hawaii
Evan revealed that he dreams about the
I thought that was the big reveal that you had rights
If you're watching the video of this Tookie ramps into like
Putting it on
Incredibly fake
Try but it was a very short
He got the sense that Spencer was using him
Viral clip
They would just give him more
I don't know
It is a mess
I wish you would realize how many of the
Gaster
Accuse him
It's incredibly bizarre to notice of it you start to realize
All of these people are kind of just
Spencer in this case is absolutely
Just one of those fish you clean algae off a bigger fish
But he's just trying to get a meal
Yeah
Does he think that
Alex is
Help him
Just getting the attention is what he really
He's just
Attention
Become relevant
Especially with Alex
Vouching
For him is like a pro
It'd be in cool to talk like
Hip guy he was woke for vocals woke there's a lot of
Old white men
Who have
Military service in their background
And they never did before because they thought he was a
The fact that he's been at Publix ad for over a decade
But now
Because Alex Jones explained it to them know
Everyone presented them as being s*******
Because they were Christian
Conservatives
And that is not tolerable
To the globalist
So they had to attack
Publix
As opposed to
To Spencer having his own advice column
In like stuff magazine
Whatever it was stuff but yeah
Dark. In my early twenties
Anyway I was having dreams about Hillary Clinton
Paula Jones we had a sec
There's no doubt
But yeah
For Heidi and Spencer interview
It's a half-hour I want to watch the rest of it it's really boring
What sponsor does Niacin really stupid
Enjoy that
Also just be like
The ramp
Victim
That selfie
Victim status
That makes sense
Oh yeah the three of them together or what
That they are the only
Play victim who feel real bad for their lot in life
Where they are
In Hawaii
As we sitting at an apartment in Chicago
Shitbrix
A lot of Arts
Yeah
Ronaldo go to August
First 2017
Episode
Alex's return from Hawaii
He was I was there up until then
He gets back into Studio
And what a world is waiting for him when he returns from vacation
Let's count off some of the things that have happened
Since you went on vacation
How long is it going for
He was gone for most of scaramucci's tender
Scaramucci
Alex was around when he got in cuz he was you talk you talking about how great it was
Who's going to be
Prefix with gone
Okay remember that
Trump MIT advance
Influenced
Which
Again
A crime
You need to get bingo
Problem disconnected on the board
What's true Corners in
Unfortunately no free space
Well currently he is living in a freezer
SAR
We've got
What else
Invent
Seth rich
Priebus
Spicer
And scaramucci all gone
In the time that he was on vacation
All of them
No no
Oh that's right she's gone from like Wednesday
So they're all
All gone
John Oliver has done his segment on Ventura Alex comes back to a word
World where she doesn't know what
To respond to
And I think he's
Really depressed
Does his voice
Does not sound good
He can't get much enthusiasm for stuff that this should be
When you shine baby
You're under attack
But you come back from vacation you have that little
Cuz you're in a war
This is an infowar
Hey you can't have f****** lingering hangover from vacation
Getting in your way you have so much to attend to right now
With the most
Difficult job in the world
And that is cover up for Donald Trump
Attempted cover-ups
Keeps blowing up in his face Donald Trump that is positive
Meanwhile
Aah
Yo personality who you've already attack
And I hate
Doesn't
Inure
Perceptions
You come back to that world most respected late nights
Of any kind like he's the guy that
Golden Grill
Yeah
Do you come back
They painted him as so much
I didn't get in
I mean you can't do it in the 20 minutes
F****** TV
He's getting
Is that what your podcast is not what episode
Jesus
My point is
Is it if you were in that situation
Do you want your audience to really believe that
You think of it as a war you can't come back
Half staff
On the first day I correct
Swinging
Interesting narrative
I've stopped by to go over
Stacked deck of all of his guests that he has on everyday basically
Rodger Stone
The good doctor Feelgood himself Jerome corsi
Cuz I watch that Alex Jones face
And I absolutely
I believe everything he says
But that his shirts too tight
True
What else you got
His pills kill yourself
Course
Bone broth
Sure what you saw a picture of doctor
Jerome corsi
Add BBC off
Corsets
But also we got to guest appearance
He comes in
Right
Cast of characters for a little bit of a hungover Alex
Corsi and Rodger Stone are basically on everyday
Rodger stone is pretty much on everyday
Once a week
Or so it's a very standard rotation of
It's kind of sad
Like you think that if you had
You know
40 million fifty million
People watching week
You could get
Better
You could get people who actually have credibility with credentials who have
A track record of not being race-baiters
Track record of people who haven't written
Books about presidential candidates
People who have
Defended crime
By saying
Real people who haven't played the birther ship
People like Steve
Pieczenik
Believe it
Story which we now know to be holy
Constructed out of
Rodger
Seth Rich was
The night of his murder
I just Grace Wasserman Schultz
So wait wait wait so we have
You're doing that stuff
Their time
I know this is a different
Okay
Never heard this one
I got one
There were these three pakistani-born
6 / 2
They are Juan Brothers
They
What
She had working
And other Democratic git specialist
Well I don't think all of them work for her but they were all in like Congressional offices
TV show now
TV show
I don't know if we're going to be able get the rights from them cuz
Chris Rice
Self their brother's trying to get
Through America which is a different culture
So we got Fish Out of Water
People to we got all those kind of awkward interaction right
Big Bang Theory
My balls
Cuz 3 it is coming
So
In the show it's revealed they killed set
The long and short of it is there's a lot of rumors about stuff from what I can tell there is a chance that
They were doing some illegal stuff
But
At this point I can't find good reporting on everything
Everything leads back to like Daily Caller articles or zerohedge
And then they're getting stuff from
A lot of it does
Come back to room
I can't find anything really concrete on it
But Alex Jones
With the help of Rogers down
Completely moved
The Narrative of the Seth Rich stuff
He is now trying to tie it to this other
A sea of these Pakistani it expert
VA claim
We're working with the Muslim Brotherhood
They were taking all of this information off of the DNC servers
And confidential information
Funneling it back overseas
Some espionage
And we're being aided and covered up by Debbie w
Murdered all right this is
Written all over it
The reason
Seriously
Why would they hire that that
Business casual
Alex is telling you about this story and it's a Paul Joseph Watson article
And The Source on it
Is Rodger Stone
So it's all just in house
But they say Trump
Insider says
Rodger Stone comes on the show to credibility to the claims the teen making through it
Infowars.com
It's just a crazy cycle of nuts that fantastic circle jerk
But they have to do this
Because the news just came out that Rod wheeler the guy who was
The private eye
That was hired by a rich Republican donor
Buy with ties to Trump
I was
I mean who came out when the f****** thing broke
Like months ago came up and he said
They told me what to say I didn't I didn't
I didn't know any of that stuff
Did it wasn't
You seen the screenshot of that text message
Which one
The the one that they're using
The kind of corroborate that evidence of
Somebody
Wheeler like
Trump saw the story and he's really happy
How did I do that
I'm just not sure if it's
Anteater
Rock wheeler has already discredited on
With his behavior in terms of saying the things on Fox News
That's why they told him
So the idea that now he's saying Trump was involved with it
And stuff like that
You have to take a setback I'm not sure we can trust you
We want to believe that but
You've already shown yourself to be a liar
The only reason that I'm
Incline
To believe it
Is private Liars also
Character on
And the Great Hall and Oates.
The only reason I'm inclined to believe it is
That is a big difference
Between
Saying something untrue on Fox News which is illegal
And making it erroneous true
The president
If you're just making fraudulent
Possible
And then it came out today that Sean Spicer released
The statement that they did have a
That
Navigating with ShopRite
They feel like they're just
Look like at very least there was a
Concerted effort behind the scenes
To push this
The story
And now here is why I believe
It's
Literally ache
Conspiracy
I believe it is incredibly nest
This has to be defended at all costs
Fire the entire Opera
If it's
Shown to be not true
If
All of the Things Fall Apart
And they can't keep moving the ball to different places like this all on Brothers connection
Do that
With the
That's just a rumor
There's no backup
Hearsay
Nothing to do up in that stuff like that
Is it shown to not be true Everything Falls
Cuz that
Is what there
Do it narrative on
That's what they're they've already
Made it clear that
They think
Rich was the one who gave the emails to Wiki
Okay
So if they don't have that piece in there fake narrative
Then
Well
Super to point out
You at least your stories wrong your version is absolutely wrong
So they it
Very essential
And I hear the other part
That's really f*****
You start to look at
Who are the people
Who have
Vociferously defended
The Seth Rich was murdered by the DNC
Storyline
Build
You have Alex Jones infowar
You have
Mike cernovich
Cassandra Fairbanks
You have
Jack Purcell
Julian Assange
Julian Assange has
Repeatedly
Insinuate
Which is not true
It's absolutely not true
But
People
Are connected
In a propaganda web
But they're all pushing this narrative
Will be a huge problem
Mesa Falls
Because it's
So not true
You understand
I think I think
I think that this is one area where
The right-wing media is entirely a
Skipper we all know it
It's obvious
Regardless of whether or not you
Prove something is
Is true doesn't mean that
It's going to change their there
Look I mean they won't be able to stay in
What the people want
Black people jokes
Clarify
So that'll be levels
Simply don't live in reality
Trump and the White House are implicated in
Creating a fraud
With
This after Rich stuff
Yeah
Is involved with the White House
Rodger Stone
Who does Rodger Stone have ties to
Jack the Soviet
All these other right-wing dickhole
Julian Assange
It becomes
Cleared that there's a network
That is sharing information with each other
I'm pushing the same narrative
They're clearly a propaganda operation
With these tendrils
I mean the Russian Embassy tweeted out stuff about Seth rich
Feed
The f****** RT and Sputnik
It makes it
Very clear
That it is Russia
And that these people are on the same f******
Yeah that's true it makes it clear
What's the reason for it is who knows
The allegiances are there they're pushing the same narrative
Against All Odds
So whether or not the right question
Proven false
If it's not what's important
What's important
Is
The fact that this story came out
And they're going to be looking into truck
Being implicated
And having an active role in the campaign
Bring
Too close to the Spear of this
And so in order to protect him
And
Text this
Maga operation that they have going
Almost
Will know
They don't have to
But in order for them
In order for them to make sure.
Has to go down
The Dew is a
To create a new story
In order to be like
This is fake
This this whole lawsuit is bogus
And they're only doing it because they knew we were going to release
This news
Then he was hanging out with the all Juan brother
Okay
Alright the narrative
Are entirely
And then you don't have to
To deal with the Fallout that everyone else is experiencing
These Craven motherfukers
Are utilizing some dudes murder
In order to
Take the heat off of what they clearly did
It does that make sense
What are we
Go like
Do over
Like
We won't
All of the crime
Committing you can do
Trump is done
So we're way past that
They're just trying to get them out
Right
Howard like I can't
I can't
Really processed
Massive levels of
The only way that I can really get to the GOP
To do anything
Not being able to act
Unite long enough to go
Not only
Has he committed all these crimes but we're divorcing
So the only possible explanation
Is that they know
Their constituents
No longer believe
Reality that's possible or that it doesn't matter
The only the only thing that I can think of is
Is that if
To the truth
They will be hated by there
Lie swallowing audience
At least
Ride like 30-something percent of people who
Still
Don't get it
But like
50% of Republicans
Climate change
The point is
There's no going back from their FOX News application
They can't go back
Entire generation
A Republican
Before they can get pass
Ask the Fox News War
Yeah
Rational moderate Republican
Nope.
Kirk Franklin
Like Luke Bryan
How about yeah
That's nonsense
Does Heroes
McCain is
Been getting a lot of accolades for his bulge
I don't know if none of
I don't know what the answer is I don't know
How we get back to normal or anything like that I don't take a
The possible probably
It's like it's like an underwater cave sometimes have to go down to get back up
You can't go you can't
Push that push up
Glitter to drown you got to go down further
Bomb North Korea the Constitution martial law
I put more in the water
I'm going to go if military coup would also be no
Alex's
Elect
Erdewan Secretary of State
While at the same time being
I can't
Not as much as we have now
Not far off so this
S*** is pretty shameful I withhold judgment on the Autobahn
Brother stopped
Just because all the information I can find on it is
Is so speculative
And I don't know
I don't have any
It is
I put it at 95% most like
I can't find enough
Information
Discredited is what I'm saying I am certainly not in the boat of saying that there isn't
Corruption in the Democratic party too
Also do you get over someone f****** around and maybe like
Dealings
Big connection
Set up the murder
That I don't believe it all
You know all that other stuff
Anyway
I like it
Anyway Alex Jones
Has to Grapple with the news of scaramucci going down
So in this little clip and I believe
This is actually him saying a quote
From Rodger Stone
Like I accidentally cut out the beginning words that Rodger says this
I don't think scaramucci's going to survive
Tirades reporters
Buy fake emails
Spoofing reporters emails
To manipulate
Isn't a timeline on that backwards
A little bit
The the prankster the email prankster
I was actually was after right
Been fired
Well it have to be after
Did the New Yorker
Yeah yeah
But he also has it wrong
This guy
Thanks a bunch of administration officials
Other officials
And most of them gave him information willingly
Gave him his email address is personal email address
There's no protocol
We are
We are saved
And
Yeah
The dumbest group of
People
That is ever run anything ever
Totally
I mean it. Like at least The Borgias
Martinizing like
This is not the Catholic religion
Splendid office
Prodigy
Doing on a day-to-day
Some tweets that were arguing
Department
Nibbling on grass right outside bunch of little holes
I fell into one of those holes
Was talking about how I'll sudheer
The head of Iraq
Earlier
She acrylic cleric
Okay
To Saudi Arabia
That was the Crown Prince
I believe
Tweet I was reading was making the argument
The truck facilitated this
Because used
Virginia
And meanwhile he doesn't want you to know these negotiations
Going on
So he creates all this chaos
In order to distract you from the fact that they're blah blah
What
Credibility to this
And so I looked it I looked into it and no I mean it is it is rare it's been like a decade since
Know the difference
Between Sunni and Shia
No
So we're done
No yes
You can still be a genius by being like
Hey
Why don't you tell me what
Do you want to have
No nothing about this like the entire conflict and just be like
What would you like me to enforce
Both side let's agree on it now
What do you want let's do it
Do you mean that the Kushner israel-palestine talks right
Well you both can
Weekend weekend stepdad
It was because you were saying like
Incredibly inept
But there are people like that guy who wrote that tweet who create
Bees
Other
Reality is for people to live in these other narrative
Amazing stuff
I'm f****** up wildly in public
Northern make you think that is a bumbling fool man
Well imagine
So so like with my family
Voted
Mostly Trump
Like imagine half
To come to grips
You thought
You were a clever
Smart person
And you wound up voting
For the dumbest
Dumbass
Administration
Olive
All of the time that would be tough you would need that
Ointment
Fake ideas about Seth rich
Nobody wants
No
But that's a much better response than f*** how do I
I will not be made a fool of my response last time I
Fell for some
Are you sure it's going to Ria
Girl f****** let that XXX
I don't like you all night making me happy
I was not Jamaican snapper
You put
A song by Heidi and
Maricopa superficial
You got one I got one we're both at -1.4 this episode
Alright so
Look generally this episode is really boring
The August 1st 2017 episode
Alexis Park
Like I said he doesn't have the verb
Would or should have
Situation
But he does some stuff that I think is worth
Noting
And worth
Disgusting here in this next clip
He jumps into something about
It's a really good demonstration of his
Tremendous fear of Muslim
Let's expand on that
What we know with people like
Man having a
ShopRite now Mueller
Contacts
Play the Democratic
Islam
When they are responsible for 90%
Radical Islam was not on the list in the first place
Too broad
And also this is just that thing that he gets really mad about all the time that is what you like
Why what
You call it radical Islam that's the problem
The reason that you wouldn't do that if you don't want to create perception of a holy war and you don't want to alienate possible Muslim allies
Some people do
You thinks it's political correctness run amok as opposed to
Do good strategy
And then the other thing is
Muslims
Do not create 99
9% of a terror
Any
No it's really not
It's white people
A lot of
Eco terrorism
Turns out one of the largest portion
Terrorism
In the United States
Environmental
If you look at it I don't know who
I don't know
It's very complicated that is complicated
Burning down
S*** like there's a lot of arsons that Environmental
It's pretty wild
But it's a lot of lot of CO2 into the air
Cleaning arson
Scrubber
Mara
Make America arson
Anyway
Yeah it did the
Statistics really interests
The fact that that is a large
Trunk of
If you look into the terrorism
Actually
The broad definition
Statistics buttercup
A lot of stuff that you would
Think is Terrorism
Falls under that category
Vandalism
Stuff like that
10 item checkout
Absolutely
Sure
Someone listening without headphones to music on the train
And then we asked why is the Muslim Brotherhood being back to the Arab Spring
Why is outside and Isis being back
Why
Why is Hillary staying in the same bed
Aberdeen enter Islamic family
A woman leading the feminist movement
Linda sarsour
Are you a human
Why is it everywhere why is everything Islam
So his is conception
Yeah if conception is the Hillary and Huma Aberdeen are lover lover
They are they they be banging
Again rumor
And gossip
You know Larry presents there at the right time
Absolutely
But he also believes the cheese produced
Hillary Clinton in order to
To get her to be a mole
Working for the Muslim Brotherhood
Because going to have it even has Muslim Brotherhood ties
It's a whole thing it's Larry Nichols s*** it doesn't matter
That's a fun narrative I like that one and then the other stuff is super mad at Linda sarsour for being involved with life
She is a lady who
Tune activist
And she has been involved in like the the women's March
Stuff like that
Because you where is a job
And you just think that
Sharia law
And I having this Muslim woman
First of all
Head up this feminism
Trendys Mantua
Or even
Party supply store
Freak out
Yeah
One of his favorite Boogeyman Boogie women and
She has deep ties to George Soros
When is like a globalist operative trying
Bring Islam
Into
Dumb liberals
But this is really in that whole thing
7 District religious want to be beat up by Muslim man we all know that
Wyatt is the
You can still
B**** about Hillary if you're the
Is because
She's a globalist
So even if she's president
She's still one of those high-ranking
Members
She's not in the Illuminati
She's not president but she still in the
Behind the scenes
Yeah I mean Larry Nichols his whole thing was that Hillary was going to become president
Atlanta point
Bill
To be the ambassador to the UN
And within a couple months he was going
To be the Secretary General of the UN
And then as a couple they would control the world
Can you imagine
The right-wing outrage
A at a president
Appointing a family member position enough
You're f****** mad when Obama's daughter went to Lollapalooza
What the f***
Globalist
Playbook
Right there
Yeah, but
Application I guess
TuneIn
Trevor Noah or John Oliver
Casey Jones
He claims Muslims are involved in crime
And that Muslims are unvetted at some Muslims have diseases
When it's either of them thought about that.
This is the Untouchable. Group
It looks like they just infiltrated the owner of Chobani yogurt
New York
Federal Reserve board
So a couple things there him talking about
Hamdi ulukaya backup
He's not on the New York
A Federal Reserve board episode about him
That was that's not true at all you wasn't
Advisory member
Years ago
Business anymore
Upstate New York
It was the most
Nothing that could be nothing
Collection of business owners who give feedback
Federal Reserve
Boise
But isn't legally actionable
Of course not
Slander
It's a all it is is just trying to
To create more powerful victims for Alec
To be attacking
Attacked by
DB is
Stream again
And stuff like that
We went over that is your wouldn't be afraid of that if we all had vaccines
Particular like
Alex let me get rid of one of your fears
I think it probably did
You got soft
Killed but that stuff is from the same
Fear narrative came out of the Breitbart stories about Idaho
We went over that there were
Six cases of TV or something
They were all treated
We already went over that
Voice there's just a defeated Nation
And throwing up
And get this this next
Clip
He brings up something
Super old
Embarrassing
Is he talks about that
He talks about
How he was angry at Putin
M2000
And maybe you was wrong
To be mad at
Oh boy yeah
Next episode
Get real excited cuz the intro music
Hot
And then Alex's
Swear to God
Okay
After the intro music
Alex Jones talks
Substantially
But growing up I noticed people
You are the most boring three-year-old ever
Power trips
They just think they're invincible
I always make the biggest mistakes in business
In life Leadership
They're on the power trips looks on their faces
I wouldn't buy a car from them
They just look crazy
Hillary all the time
Looks insane
Walking around
What are eyes bugged out like she just started a bunch of
Buick nomad
With a bunch of other weird sycophants running around behind
I don't know what you call this psychologically
Nancy Pelosi
Every time she speaks almost George W Bush president
What legislation is in basic Trump
These people have less knowledge
Junior High student eating
Is from
Pics 8 months ago from the show
Slip of the tongue one-time Maxine Waters
I've said Korea what you meant kromia
Nancy Pelosi
Once you meant to say Trump
Well that means he's a junior
It's a slip of the tongue to happen once
And Alex is he keep saying
You saying that they
Keep saying
They just constantly having their senile they're crazy look at them
Create the perception
For his dumbass audio
You know 8
It's a little lingering thing
As opposed to a slip of the tongue
Yeah there's people who are are the ones
To commit the worst
Mistakes and busy
A lot of those people
Right
Somewhere in between their company
Say some
Flatout slanderous
Terrible if they
That say that.
They get clocked out by their own military
I just love the idea.
Generally speaking about talking about people being crazy
Cuz that's why
As well
Talking about how
Abusive to women
Muscling in
Anyway the other thing
That I wanted to point out there is his description
Hillary Clint
Eyes bulging out
Like she's done methamphetamine
Yep describing himself
He has done math multiple times
And he is surrounded by
Absolutely
Broccoli
Anyway
This next
Alex
Which one
Anyway this next one
Anyway reminiscing over
How do I convert 7 oz
43 back
So
Was played at the moment one of those John Oliver on Last Week Tonight this week put out a piece
I was a 20-minute exploration about
Pretty hard autumn
I did exposed
The stuff that we've talked about like how a doctor group is a chiropractor
The only difference is they actually contacted the school
I found out that he doesn't have an undergraduate degree beyond what we knew
That's great to know you know
Alex
When I saw that
Peace
I knew what
And it's not as bad as the Bon Iver
Because the bodies are still actively use
As propaganda
He can twist it and make it
Proper
With this site I saw the Avenue defense really easy
Like it's so clear what it is
I think I even text
Did you that what he was going to do
That's just what he's going to
To say that the globalists are trying
Cut off my money
They've already attacked us by taking us off Google ad
They keep trying to discredit me
And they know that they can't take me down I don't rely on Advertising I just rely on you getting
The pills
You getting all of my supplements
This is the great globalist attack that I've been telling you was going to come and that more or less is what
His response to it
But again he says that they're lying about
August
They are not they're not but it's entertaining
To do witches take him in contacts
And that's and they kind of
But there is a greater context that they
Like John Oliver did mention the globalist a couple time
Really I called Ian says probably glanced past that not realizing what he was talking about
But be that as it may
You might be surprised by exactly what
Really stick
And Alex is crawl
About
The Oliver report
Man
The vanity of
He says we sell the
That there altogether
Domesticated Birds
We sell the meat of dead domesticated Birds
Okay
Time
Coffee
Southern Mexican
Hi Mountain Knife.
Call Nate
Basically you're seeing what I was
Hoping you would see immediately
He's turning this
He's turning it into a coverage of dead Bart
Nothing is John Oliver didn't talk about the coffee
Article
And they weren't tight
We just sell coffee
Like
Yes it's B
Patriot blender whatever the mushroom
Weird
Stuff like that
That's what people are making fun
Not coffee
The fact that you have Vitality coffee
And stuff like that
He's misleading even in his account people are misleading you
Call Alex
The king of coffee
Indeed
$5 lesson they sell at Whole Foods we get from the exact same Chiapas
Years ago
It's a good deal
Wake up America Coffee they want to make fun of the fact that we sell things
So this is the other
I Celtics everybody sells things
Get it
Also I want
This entire time
She's already talked to Steve for about a couple minutes
And then he goes on this
6 minutes long and I don't have all of it
Is on Skype
Just holding and not saying anything from
Yeah
Do Skype interviews with Alex like at least if your
Like if you're on the phone you can at least like do something
I just kind of standing there
Just like I f****** wrote books
Tom Clancy
Delivery
Anyway back to this
So you can't tell because of the overlapping
Audio here but John Oliver
Of Alex sitting down with Buckley
Takes a drink
Be like
It's not it's very obvious
The second thing
Alex has picture in a picture going on infowars.com
So they're playing
The John Oliver video
And he is on the side
A video of him
Fake laughing
You'll hear laughter over this that says Alex
A team doing
Same fake laughter
Trying to show that like I don't care
It's Heidi Spencer level actor
Yeah
So much more
This is why the
A good grandma
I'm going to do an analysis of this today or tomorrow it's
20 minutes
Plug-in product
Did you count plugs on here and the ads
That's the standard for broadcast radio on TV
Okay
25% of 50
Average 30 years ago
Here is what Alex is doing
He is a big fan of double count
And so when
John Oliver says on one of the show's be analyzed
25% of the show was
I'm talking about pills are directly cell
Just say pills a placeholder whatever
Alex playing
15 minutes of
The show
Every hour
Is
He's not and that's not on it
We know the show is
No
Yeah
And then another 15 minutes is
Is that cuz we know
From we have a copy of his contract
Syndication
12 minutes
Which is available inexplicable infowars.com 12 minutes
15 minutes that are commercials that are on the show go to the
The station
In question they can play their own ads
Been 3 minutes go to Alex Alex
Theory
Supposed to be that
Is how he gets paid
Because there is no fee to syndicated show
Now what he's not taking into account is
But that is
The 12 minutes
Is very sensitive to run your goddamn show
That has nothing to do like you just give that up
The fact that you spend
I would say probably 25 is
Generous that's what I was thinking
Alex was lying about John Oliver actor
I'm going to start keeping track
I'm going to buy a stopwatch
And I'm just going to
Keep track
I can't do it while I'm watching a
Cuz I'm always
On my phone at work
I'm watching YouTube
Publix
Well look so Alex Jones is double dipping in the same way that trumps budget money
In the same way that Alice
And Alex Jones double and triple count audience
Then all that stuff with advertising time
And this is why people
Make fun of you for
Add so are they doing so many add
It's because it's on a
Beat the pig
That is
Appropriate
Is
Commercial time
Yep Showtime
Showtime
Commercial break
It's unethical for you to sell product manipulative
In in the what we're seeing right now
This is sold coffee in the middle of this what's
Supposed to be analysis analysis defending myself against John Oliver
Frozen
A completely Superfluous plug for the coffee
That's
This is 10 minutes of the show
So if this is 10 minutes of one of the hours
That's 16
Right there
It isn't the only place he did
Nope
Commercial time
Bayonet H would be 15 minutes
25 minutes of the hour already that's covered by
Some sort of
Commercial
Does another commercial probably 5 minutes less today
It's taken up by non Conte
And even then a lot of his ads
Like a lot of his narrative
Right
Like the like the financial collapse is coming
Dubai
Even his
Real show right advertisement
Antonym anyways
In the sense that a lot of his stuff is supposed to
Create fear
Narratives
Are built on
Bothering minorities and vulnerable populations
Making you afraid that you're going to be killed by roving gangs of black people
By making you afraid of financial collapse
Afraid of
The communism that's creeping around every corner every leftist around every corner
It is supposed to get you to buy food for your family calls it
Insurance you can eat
Boots storable food
B cells
Vista linium the
The
Colloidal silver the
I think he doesn't do that anymore I'm not entirely sure
Alright well there we go again but like all those other things all the pills are
Give you back your Humanity that the globalist have taken from you
Every single narrative is base
So
25 is
Absolutely not true
50 is even spiritually not true
So
Alex you don't understand what people work
Before
I actually genuinely
He doesn't
It's possible but you'd never be able to tell
Know that it's impossible for us to discern the line between willful line
And I don't get it
Cuz he's too much
So he doesn't get it
He wouldn't know that cuz he's on HBO
Which is owned by Time Warner
$20 last year ripping folks off on cable
Ivory
Every cable company charter
SVN
Whatever what's the one here
RCN
Is that it
Oii
Temperature in the world
Everyone hates the Malik
Rice is not special now is a good time to get into Monopoly
I think you and I are going to solve this problem right now
Whenever you have a single-source
For any kind
Product
In any situation
A lot of times
Good ideas
Literally
Hard to quantify
The amount of nutrients
50 bowls of chicken soup for serving and it's something ridiculous you can't really quantify
It's amazing or bottom but like
Okay
I don't know if
Get more vitamin D amount
You can't
Quantify it it's like 50 bowls of chicken soup hey guess what
You can't quantify
It's numbers
A ballpark
Nutrition information on Chunky Soup
Here's the nutrition information
You could easily tell
So
You can't quantify it
It's like
It's like a stardust amount of chickens right
Yeah
Brigan non-specific languages on play that s***
So he goes on
It's like the tears of children amount of chicken soup
We still haven't gotten which is really funny.
Elvis
Particular thing
Defend himself against these allegations
Get so wild
Cute he makes fun of the fact
Talking about
Attracted that's known for nerve growth factor
World. America
We can sell it
They're trying to make it a drug right now
Organic stores
Pitbull Japanese Mitsubishi mix
Expensive
Not doctor group
But I always think you saying Mitsubishi
Biopqq is only found in cars
I think it's Mitsubishi
Or something like that I think it's something like that
It cannot be Mitsubishi
It can't be a
I can't be a secondary car dealership
Stop
Four major networks
Are they control all of our media really. Right there
And put milk in it
Okay
Doesn't work with vanilla flavor works with chocolate strawberry flavor
Why is the super good knowing from okay
Is because it tasted okay before and with milk
It tastes like a
Ephraim
Wendy's
John Oliver challenge
You can return it
If you don't take it with me
I've got John Oliver challenge
I don't know what that is
Probably what it's going to be is a sale which we already are doing of course if you want to return it
That's decent business practices who is the girl who is
The woman on the show Millie Weaver
Did Millie Weaver that's about rainbow snatch
She swore by
I believe that was Owen
Troy who was bullying her into talking about how much you loved it
I don't know I don't think she's gone
Are you think she's gone I haven't seen her in Forever
Leanne McAdoo still occasionally making these video appearances
Over Skype
Through out-of-pocket Millie Weaver
Totally gone as far as I can tell
Ashley Beckford is totally gone
I don't know where any of these people are there they're in the Wind
Listen Millie
We loved
Loved it
Love it was revolutionary,
Alex has never fake left
That makes us
View no no no
View last part
There's a little more
Protein powder
My kids love it
They're so healthy bringing it
It's crazy
Huge discounts across-the-board infowarsstore.com
Free shipping will also can caveman
Dot-com
66% off one more thing will kill you and loyal silver
I said the full clip
Don't go
Someplace
Like a drugstore and get topical iodine
Because it's not the same
And people
You know what the store
Ours is a totally different type of iodine
Tower
Cam
Are funding
Narrative
Being reminded that Steve pieczenik
Is a respected man
Around town through all this
The world if they are like
If you have trained in audience
That is that dumb
I think they should all drink a dime
I think we should run that risk
If that is what they based on hearing Alex
Do we have a responsibility
You stop them
Resume Alex's open misrepresenting
I have heard on a couple episodes
I didn't have time cuz I'm a job
But I have a couple times
I'm saying
That other iodine
Not
Like the liquid top till I die
Pretty dishonest
Clips from the archive in
Somewhere fun
Yeah
Like every time
And Dad love you
He
I think he knows that Alex is in a weird mood
You spend most of the time that he's on talking about
What you talked about how Hillary's crazy and that Trump is great
Stop from it more was he was giving Alex
Pep talk
He was giving him a little bit of a down on yourself
Alarm
Yeah I think he knows
But he needs to
Alex is back from vacation he needs to get his head back in
In the game and the only way to do that is to
So here is
Talking about how much of a
Alex Jones
I would suggest you invite
Okay
Guatemalan
And you look like a sweaty biatch on it
You look like a disaster
And we're still waiting for you to release those unedited videos Alex
Spell please
Release those things to prove it
Manipulative Lee attitude
If you release one little thing
They just showed that they edit
TV show
I want to create a slick products
It's not just
Yelling about how hours
Even Alex
Don't get the Good karaoke every time
Yeah
Yeah that's true
Are you saying that the people who reposted are
Cutting out
Cuz I think they all realize it
Embarrassing
Call man
It's crazy
We got a new conspiracy theory now
Keep us away from the real truth
So you think
The global history behind Alex Jones
I want to cover up his singing
No I think they know that Alex is
Real power
Comes from his back
Apologize and thank our buddy Mike
Michael pointed out
Failed
Episode
Whatever Alex
That's
Randy Rhoads
I love that.
Of all the lies
If I would just get an apology from Alex about that we can end the show we're good we did what we set out to do
Alex does not have a strong wit
He'll be destroyed at any certain time
Couldn't
Convince people
He didn't agree with David
Absolutely
Nowhere
Completely unable to hold a conversation
Stephen Colbert
Because they put on a professional show everyday
Another reason that Alex think
Accomplished
An improviser
It's the same thing with people who are alike
The best Heckler there's ever been I'm going to shut this
I do this just
Just leave it alone like if Alex
Tried to talk to John Oliver
It would be John Oliver says
Brakes Alex Jones
Haven't you ever seen these people like Colbert or Jon Stewart on
Conservative talk shows
Devastating destroyed since career for like 3 years
The bow tie
It's just sort of indicative like I said this is a really boring show
Like I wanted it to be an hour of him responding
We don't know that cuz
Tuesday recording
But we don't live in
The future if it is we're going to have to convene an emergency
C-section go all over his Oliver
Library
This basic
Hire a writer
Maybe it's me
It's super boring
Because of these things that we're seeing it's all very repetitive
It's old stuff
He's not he's going with these things that he thinks
A good bit
Like the Nancy Pelosi
George Bush's presidency Linda sarsour
I like Hillary's banging Huma Aberdeen
All this like
You need a new act bro this is like a comic who's on year for of doing the same time minutes
The more like
If I'm
If I'm at 15 and I want to do something
The new and then I just
It just slipped out of my mind
Without
Next
Like I'll be
In the back of my head I'm thinking
Wait what was the bet that I was
Want to do it like I'm not paying
I would argue that it's possible that the
The new bit he wanted to do was this new Seth Rich narrative
And didn't have like the juice
To actually do it
If possible if that's the case that was his new bit and then just went with
Old classic
Is Jerome corsi on towards the end of the show
And they just
Do another old B mispronounce
And
If you don't repeat
I can just cut the funding out of
Let Congress have the best Healthcare in the world
Legislation sponsored
That's how you win friends
They're calling him a loser because in 6 months you can get
He's a total winner
Endorsing
No it's not but also
He's a loser
Trump gives up his paycheck
Which again is
Small Potatoes compared to watch
Threat
Or compared to what he's feeling
This is personal enrichment from being president has been
Give up his salary to probably
You know he wasn't Tech
We hired yet
That's hilarious
Like
This is this is right back to the thick of it
Where it's like
Look if you get fired next year it's because you f***
If you get fired next week
Cuz I f*****
There's some of that
I mean
These guys like
Rodger Stone comes on the shower
It's scaramucci was a political suicide bomber
He flamed out on purpose in order to take out
Spicer and priebus
Who are two globalist
Stronghold
He goes in there you bloat
I don't
I think he's just a loudmouth assholes who didn't realize he was on the record until it was too late
No heat
Apparently
You said he knew you was on the record
Well now they people say that because you said
He requests
Did the go off the Record later
Indicates that he would have known earlier
Totally possible that he just realized it halfway into the conversation
He had that brief moment of like
What did I say you can't work in the White House
What's the Soccerzone deck
You just cannot do it
What's that mean
To me that means
Perfect person to work in that way as
Absolutely
That's
I like it when
I like whatever that veneer of
Political speech
Is just gone
Hangouts to you if you want to be like
If you want to say what you want to say about Bannon
Uh
You can say it like
More poetically
But nothing
The point like Bannon wants to suck his own
Right with your friend
Even if we don't like the people like Steve Bannon
Scaramucci and don't really give a f*** if they gets fired or
Or drown
At the same time
Truck
Even if you had the road if you don't care
It's still really degrading to our
Really degrading
To the idea of decency
And working order
For these people to behave this way
Public videos where
The Japanese Parliament got into real fist fight
Sure I would rather live in a world where Paul Ryan got punched in the face I wouldn't mind that
Loses any fight Paul Ryan has ever been
Is there a possibility for arms
Fur like physical conflict
And that in the house
That would be a
Kamala Harris right next to me
McConnell is a physical contact were possible Within
Another house through Republican
Example for open carry
We found it
Do the other thing with that clip
He's just going back to the fannie-freddie Merida
I've already gone over the total
It is it's
It's boring
Do you think you just misspoke there because Trump
Can withhold subsidy
He just doesn't know that those are different
I don't think you understand the concept of money being fungal
And the government
That you can
Just moving around
Money that comes in is money that goes out money is money
I think
He does know that he's just trying to score points and pretend it is
Jerome corsi is reporting with
What's correct
Okay
Okay now I guess
Adjust exploitation of
I don't think the Trump
Does come out
Made any claims about Fanny
Freddy
If Trump knows about
I think you must
Galaxy probably heard him
I don't know it look where the crazy thing is
Tom president
The secret book
Right
Good teacher to Fan your own fresh
Spread your own Fanning
You get two points for that
22 - 112 let's get boring episode we've been covering
The Source material didn't do it for me today
I would have rather
Probably spent all the time talking about Heidi and Spencer
Quite frankly cuz it was it was
Blast From My T-Mobile early twenties around
Just watch f****** Laguna Beach and argue about whether or not these kids have brakes
Loser
He's got it
Talons like number 6 probably
Check us out over at knowledge B., to their website website
Content
Button soon
$2 for one button
I have no idea how much does a button
Work these are
We are not business and
$17
Shipping is free
Stroller
Button
I have no idea
Like button
Paramore factoids like that
Underscore fight or around Facebook
Email us at knowledge fight at gmail.com
Really really wonderful messages thank you
You guys are like the opposite of Jon rappoport
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work