Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for this knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
My rights Jordan is actually there's good become a little bit of an issue with the
Dreamy creamy summer summer as we all know is the. Of time to 420 + 9
Famous famous leaders
But there's an issue
What's up
Well Nightmare on Elm Street issue with the dreamy creamy part child
No
That is not the problem right
The problem is revoked
A lot of the cremate
Because I got the ice cream ice cream going in than others but
I feel like the dreaming it has not been
Like fully
Accounted
So you can start reading the Sandman,
I'm not
I'm not going to do that okay
Guy that sounds like a
Schedule
I'm going to get a bunch more
Clothes
I am not alright I'm going to get myself looking dreamy
Okay
I have spent no time on
In your life
Ever ever not what I have had a car
Constant
Aversion
The clothes shop
And I think a large portion of it has to do with like growing up weed go to
Target to get clothes and wear
Felt a little bud
Hassle of like
Trying stuff on to be rushed by my parents and
Didn't want to buy name brands at the make fun of my pants right
I think
I had
The beginning of the week
Week let's say
Other than like a teacher
Shirts that I could wear
I like this is no good
And so I have
From where one of the new shirts here I was I wasn't going to say Dan is that a new shirt I should have sought my floor
Floral print
Pseudo Hawaiian shirt but I don't get to say stuff like that because I'm famously the most
An observational person that famously famously
Is that a new shirt and everybody's like I've worn this to your wedding and it's like okay well you're right that's a good point yeah
This is one of the new ones
It looks great thank you we're going to see
See how Gary should get
How garesche
What's your garishness
Level I'm interested to find out what you believe gerrish
Old buddy Nikki gift
Could give you some insight
We didn't really become friends
Central High School junior high together
And so you could tell you some stories
Days where I would wear shiny shirts
There was one
Or just a fluorescent
Snot fluorescent
They're the kind of things that with the light would catch stuff on it
One of them was
Flaming dice
Headwear that the school that's a garish wow wow I will not be going that far as to descend
Is that when I think of you in junior high
I think of a slight
A smaller version of you wearing
Dice on your shirt and that is almost exactly what you looks like in junior high it's a smaller
Version of you so
Yeah you would already started to grow that beard in junior high it's true
But yeah just
Weather
Saturday
We'll see we'll see where the road goes
This is a turn that I'm not in my wildest dreams
I think a lot of people when they hear there's an issue with dream creamy summer
Play some iPad
No it is just adding a new wrinkle
My bright spot Dan is you know what I'm going to go ahead and say that it is
Your parents are behind the bastards this week and Sophie for having us
Enjoyable is nice to have that come out finally I just while ago
Text message like
So great to hear you are on the Masters you sound a lot happier than I was a few months ago
Yeah I've not had a chance to listen to the second episode
But we recorded a tiny little bit of a disclaimer
Because we recorded that at different time
It was in April when he recorded it and like
Like we were
Like app
Trials coming along the whole episode supposed to be about what's going on in Alex's
Update to the up
Longer than the update I felt very
Self-conscious about that but I'm glad that it's turned out well
Remember outside of our sphere that most people have no idea that
Is going on
So is there any
Yeah yeah for sure
And take jokes feedback my picture
So Jordan today we are going to
Be continuing our path
Through the Uvalde shooting coverage
Alex did a disgraceful
Night of coverage
It was
Ivd trans person hoax
Step and pharmaceuticals
Transition day
It's a situation our last episode
And today we're going to be looking at May 27th
Just Friday of that week
And so we come to the close
Of this week
And we will see where Alec
What develops from there
And
Because I work on Thursday and tonight is the the
Ouac debutante balls
I I I decided we're going to do is we're going to
Follow up a bit more with
The
Uvalde
Coverage on Monday and then for Wednesday
We will
Catch back up
Interior Alex
January 6th
Stop but yeah for today
Markee Pioneer 27th bar
Keep marching on
We will get to it before hello
The crime pickled not that crime pickles better crime pickles
I'm a policy thank you very much
Brandon
Is the reason I have difficulty with that is it
Brandyn
That why I'll get you
Celebrating a 20th
Brandon this one I actually think
I might have said before or it's entirely possible does a second person with this and that is
Bill Ogden
It might be a second person could have been in
Inspiring the next class of Barrister bill is essentially
Play the Top Gun of lawyer
I know a lot of people are going to join the Air Force after Top Gun
Lot of people same thing I'm going to get mark on the phone and explain to him what he needs an intimidating smash
That's a problem with lawyers they don't have enough
So are we got a couple of technocrats in the mix first one
Sparkling water is the literal Christian
Thank you so much you are now technocrat I might agree with that I haven't had it in a really long time
Website to find out where your highways
NY lotto
It's the devil
I also am I happy birthday on the 12th of June
What
I don't have Coral it says the globalist which the Poison by soda can
They requested in the Alex Jones voice
So that gives much your now Technic
Don't get mad and tell your brother
Someone someone sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much to all pick up late again because
Cuz I have it loaded up in the iTune
One-hundred-percent I saw you click it going I better say something real quick
Jordan is where we start on the 20th
Friday edition we have
Who is fired up
Really informative
The whole history of a psychologist and psychiatrist
Tragic events in Uvalde Texas
On
Speculating
Trying to get the facts into really look
What's going on
We know now that the official story has unraveled
We now know that
We have been lied to
Zedge
Women forcing their way through police lines to go get their children
Total disaster
So first quickpoint Alex is absolutely not been judicious in his coverage of the shooting
Do you want people to give him a trophy for not saying it was fake
Because he really wanted to and he resisted for a few days
Say no trophy to that that is that is very transparent and likes
Wondercide
Judaism
In reality you've been wrong on a plethora of different things
Different directions
He's been wrong in a lot of ways already
I suspect that he doesn't even realize how much of his narrative has changed since Monday and how each time it changed it was because something
He made up or misreported fell apart
But it's true that the official story around the shooting was definitely collapse
And at this point on
On the 27th
But it's important to keep a close eye on Whose official story
Alex is going to take game at and who he's going to blame
Right right
They're two big points at Alex touches on here about the
The story so I wanted to get to them one at a time
The first is about police for knowledge
Alex insists that the police or the FBI always knows about the
The shooters ahead of time and let's
The shootings happened
So it's no surprise for him say that about this one it connected to all the other ones
That he's made up in the past
For instance just recently Alex misreported that the Buffalo shooter
Been red-flagged by the FBI but that's
That's not something you could demonstrate at all
But it's been accepted as truth
Within the infos world because I was his repeated enough
In this case Alice is operating on an interesting space where it's
Easy to see the Optics I'm just assume that he's right
Do Uvalde School
When using the social media tool called social Sentinel
Which is meant to scour social media
And identify threats
The teachers or schools
Based on this
Detail Alex
Is making a leaf that a lot of people made which is that this software must have found Ramos
And no nobody's threatening
Hence providing for knowledge of the shooting
That that is ignored people left to that I think
That's amazing
CU lot of people leave it better
The conclusion on Twitter
Amazing maybe not the people who
Like I would
I wouldn't give that to like the media saying that
No that's amazing because the moment I found out about that I was like
Oh obviously that doesn't work
Well I mean I don't know if anything good more obviously a bit of scam well it may or may not be
I don't know enough about the software to say but I do know
Why
It did it wouldn't have worked in this case
And that is only works on their threats made to the school or they're made publicly by people associated with
The school
DP Golbat who is the CEO of social Sentinel
Company
Publication
Recode quote we are not currently aware of any specific links connecting the gunman to the Uvalde
Consolidated independent
School District or Raab Elementary on any public social media sites
Ramos was somebody who you could identify the danger online
But this software wouldn't notice because it's not
Designed to just flag every sketchy
Turn around
The threat that Ramos had made to shoot up a school was done in a private message
To a wooden
Anti-vax it
Of course there were plenty of Warren
Zion's online for in
Census
Threatening women concert
Delete
That's not what Alex is talking about
He's talking about direct for knowledge on the part of the authorities which is not established
Just another one that'll go on the pile of things that
Repeat
Yep
The second Point Alex brings up is that the police went in to get their children will not allow others
To do the same
I'm not sure exactly what Alex was referring to her or if he has any
Specifics
But the person who did go in and get their kids
We Gomez
Who
Does mention as the woman who forced her way past
Wait right
Is a totally f*****-up situation as the police had cost her for being uncooperative and then let her lose it
Which one's your rain
Into the school
It's just horrifying
To imagine being left with no other viable option
Haven't been more less abandoned by the people who are
Mental Health
Just terrified
Her kids were into different classrooms and neither of which were the two classrooms which Ramos was holed up in
Doesn't make anything any different
There were rumors going around social media that police went in to get their kids but there is nothing really solid evidence
Miss recorded details
For instance there was a border patrol officer who aided in the evacuation of students
Whose daughter was hiding in the bathroom in the school
So obviously he hoped to get his child out but that was part of the larger goal of getting out as many kids
If possible there's some miscommunication surround stuff like that right that I
Leave being
Extrapolated further
At least with the information they know now
Yeah I know I mean I heard that the cops went in and got their kids but I found it
Just at least a little bit like
I'm going to need
Evidence of that before
That's too good
That is one of those Rogan moments where you go
That's too on the nose
Right maybe
Take a step back
From that one
It's um
Understand
The kernel of that
Basically the Snopes
Article
Let's say
Traces that to a Shaun King tweet that you
From a local news person interviewing a police representative
And they said
That the police were trying to get their kids out
Sure
And that could refer to things
Like
Parents
Who happened to be police who were helping with the evacuation
Not necessarily like I'm going solo on the
Like
Like Miss Gomez
FYI I kind of didn't buy it
Is because
I don't think any of the cops have the courage that this woman
So there are some
Some details that Alex has that are a bit off
Minutes out
Body armor
But I mean
Umami
The police
Program to wait for orders
That more and more you see this time
Crap
This is definitely not accurate
But there's no reason for Alex to know that on the 27
There was a Wall Street Journal article with the headline quote Uvalde shooter fired outside school for 12 minutes before
For entering
Ramos Center Beast
The school at 11:28 a.m.
And on May 26th the Texas Department of Public Safety
Had claimed that he entered the school itself at 11:40
A more detailed timeline was presented the next day with the
The time Android
The school being 11:30
30k
Details will come out the letter x
Seems accurate but by the time out to officially announce
Information would lead someone to think
But he was outside the school shooting for 12
Right
That's embellishing the detail the police were in a 12-minute shootout with Rama
Part isn't backed up by the inaccurate reporting that he's operating off of
But the
The basis of this you can kind of understand
Where his mistake is
You know
That would be a very simple thing to follow up on
Cops have turkey
Keep track of how many guns
How many bullets
That is true so if there was a shootout we would know almost immediate
Do you know based on
Surveillance information and stuff like that
Something that is not super difficult
It was inaccurate as of the 26
The 27th is when that
Colonel from the Texas
Department Public Safety
I gave
The press conference
That laid out a lot more of the information
And that has not happened as Alex's beginning
The show
So
That's what I'm trying to be
Is overly Fair we decided to throw that out episode
Zion giving inside info
You know what are going to
I've been accused many times and will
Again of being
To Fair
Are too generous
What's the point if you do
Anyway Alex doesn't think this is a false flag
Good
Sort of you has changed his mind.
Telephone number of Stand Down possibilities
Study apps
Consistently sentence
Monday's labs
There's not a thing
First
Hero cop who went in and took care of business right away
I love that didn't work out
Until you had it was a hostage
Situation
So there's not
There's not a stand down until now
Cuz I didn't get it before because I like believes that they do not have the social media monitoring they would have known
Amanda
Further
Alameda to sand down which
He doesn't he doesn't go too hard on but he does
Touch on a couple times in this episode
And that is the bit of information about a school shooting being threatened
Years ago in Uvalde
Yeah well actually I had already by this point and said it is not
Alex is using the sort of image of that
Opportunity to know about this band share the social media they refuse to do something
There was a standout who is he
I mean how is it
That he's straddling the line between incompetence and pre-plan
You know like
If they know about him in advance
If they
Where is there
And didn't stop
And then
Continued until he is murdered a bunch of people
Then that can't be anything other than consent
Right
Are the cops
Incompetent
I think incompetents might be where he lands but sir like a benevolent
Hey this is this
Wil Wheaton
Seems to be a bit where he lands as we go through this episode
Straight to your question like from a like a normal per
Perspectives
Difficult to understand how it
That would not be
Complicity
If you believe the things that Alex is saying
And that's usually gets around that
Is that
The feds
Are the ones who are who know
Where is the local folk right oh no
Is the higher-ups
Trying to protect them from getting and also the do stop that
Lower down and local Folk
Not to act
When they would act normally because the higher-ups
Sure and they're the feds are
Protecting these
Asset drone killers they have
The point the finger and be mad at somebody
In the form of the feds brightness
I am and not being like
All cops are malevolent
Alex could be like they've been
They've been so conditioned to Stand Down by the
The feds over and over and over again letting these
These things happen
It's basically Alex's fault
Interesting
I'm not following your total train of logic
Hey man
Look we can't dwell too long on this because
The nuge is going to be on later I'll leave that
Again
So much Nugent
Man discussion about
Board member
Odyssey icon of American freedom
Reminding me
Psychologist and psychiatrist
You were going to do it
Police who they were going to do it at
Show me times
It turns out there are
Globalist left disconnected groups that are
You know that's going on
Buffalo News Fox News
Buffalo mass shooting
Digitally
Online
And the reports are
Talking to the eighteen-year-old.
Autistic
Vine on top of it
There's a real a real easy answer what is this
Retired federal agent
Braces kid
Is a racist
That's the important detail that Alex seems to be missing
The things I say
Tired to his capacity as a federal agent
Wasn't investigating this get use engaging in racist forum
Yeah uncle
Former federal agent but you wouldn't say that you was acting in an official
Is going to like
Wolfgang halbig
Big seminars and helping enforce braid Sandy Hook in
When did at the same Dynamic here
According to law enforcement sources a racist retired federal agent was an individual who interacted with the shooter online
Sharing racist s***
Allegedly he became one of the people who was given access to the shooter's plans and Target 30 minutes prior to the
But even according to the reporting on this in the Buffalo News
The news
Determine if the retired agent
Accepted the invitation
There was a racist retired agent who was invited to know about the shooting at Advance
But there's no proof yet
But he accepted the invitation
So he might not even known in advance
Simself chair
Basically the solid details we have here so far revolve around the existence of a retired federal agent
Hang out on racist websites a whole lot
That's f***** up but it doesn't really prove for knowledge on the part of the authorities before the shooting
Which Alex is trying to use this
To bolster credibility
Before I like what is that I would love for him to give these examples of
Of psychiatrist and psychologist or
Leftist globalist groups having
The foreknowledge
Prodding cuz
I don't think
Most cases stand up to that I mean I don't even know
So
But how does that relate
To what's going on here is the
I mean I know it's
I guess parallel but like
Why are you throwing that into this
For the Valdese
Situation
Because he's trying to say that
There was this
Fluent
I like the FBI was basically
The federal agent let's assume FBI
Plant who was
Encouraging this guy to do the shooting use coaxing
Robbie half of the FED globalist mean that there is somebody in the background we having
Undiscovered in Uvalde case
That's the vehicle
But again that comes down to eventually like they were in on it right
Like sooner or later you all get back to
They were in on it
Whoever they may be
You know in this kind of situation right
I think
One of the things that we need to maybe do a better job of
Is
Understanding that yes that is always
And when my bad my bad I was getting to into the tens place of keys
This isn't a false flag so we have to treat it like he's saying that but it honesty
Steven saying it's false
To write
Right and eventually when there's enough pieces of information for him
To craft that
He will
Pivoting towards that on this app
Episode more the
Then you have
In the episode asking you these questions is because
It does seem like The Logical endpoint of everything you saying is that this was either or
Castrated by the feds or it was fake
Yeah
It's so
Yeah he was like if something gets
Attention from the media then
It's not real
Because
Yeah you don't give media coverage to real terrorize
Brightright inspires more terrorism
If they are covering something and paying attention to it
That it must either be fake
Or they
Made it happen through
Once
Again there they're all in on it
Everyone
But Alex
And the good cops on the ground
Another narcissistic about that
So Alex says this is District
This just hit me wrong
Roses of Texas school shooting Memorial
What am I
Opportunistic pay
Okay
Wow
Seems
Probably because
She's the Royal Family
It's cuz he doesn't like the royal family specific
That's a sure it's
Royalty that is his main issue he doesn't like the royalty but I
Victor little seem a little
I think that
I don't know
I didn't follow
Megan
Adventure 2
Too closely
From what I was looking at
It seemed like she was trying to keep it real low-key
Volunteer for a day
The fact that I had no idea about it kind of says good things about that
You know what I think I think that Alex's wife
Tennis partner is just really interested
He's annoyed by suits
Yeah I could be a dozen
If that's just a dick thing to say for no
Yeah
So and then I hate royalty
So we're there
Sure
Well are they technically royalty anymore I think they accept
Alex isn't even on the houses on the side of royalty you shiting all over Mega
So there's that
So yeah that's true he's back he's back to the wall
Maybe I'll just wants more seasons of Suits could be
Maybe it goes back to suit maybe the tennis partners
One of the big points
Let's being spread is that the police didn't go in because they were afraid
Need to get shot
And Silas talked about this and honestly I feel like this is one of the few instances where his anger feels real
Yeah there's a difference
Police what's in it
Chaz cops
This is what truly disgusting
Police spokesperson
Makes
True
So you're scared to get shot
Vermont
When there's children
You are sworn to protect
D2 you have a duty as a man
Go in there
Surprise
Almost on the building
Didn't
And I'm glad they didn't
This is going too far
Come back with all of it in the end of Stand Down video
I think I was just constantly full of s*** so I never really want to scribes and Siri
But that kind of felt
A little realer than other times he's
The album I mean the real lesson of that
Is just
How shity
Situation is
That even Alex will say reasonable
Yeah it's something really remarkable about
What he saying that's
Kind of right
He's trying to derail things down like his auntie public
School Road in this like they want your guns but have armed security kind of talking points yet
Overall I don't know if I disagree with
Is that much
About what he saying
The issue is that Alex's Larry solution
These problems that underlie the
The problems that Keys touching on that kind of
I have some accuracy
If you try to investigate the police department
That's a globalist plot
Federalized
Any attempt to address poverty that might help
People who
Can't afford it station or whatever
That's just the globalist attempt to make everyone
So we can kill everyone off
The only Concrete Solutions Alex's come up with scent
The shooting are to arm teachers and Vanquish the devil
Has the second one is meaningless
Teachers is kind of all he's got here
You just keep everything the same
But arm the teacher
So we're left living in exactly the same unpleasant
World is no solution
But when things go bad
Teachers will have
Kill people
This isn't a solution
This is dumb it's just more Deadpool
Right but
Even
Slightly fewer dead people is not an Optimum out
Yeah it it's
It's just bizarre that yeah there are those moments week
Kind of feel like
Yeah you're touching
You touching on something real here and your anger seems
Come from
A place of
Like sincere passion about like
How's it going out wrong V
Did the
Did the situation people find themselves in Arabic
You got nothing
But yeah I mean
Okay
So I agree with you that is genuine
And I'll it was reasonable
I just
Don't
F****** care
If you get angry enough at the problem
That it's genuine and real and then at the end of the day you go home and you say well I love guns more than I love my kids so f***
Part of the problem
I mean the exit sound the overarching unreasonable Leti within the reasonable
Kind of difficult to ever really swallow too much of the alike
Well it feels like he's coming from a real place
Because
Define spit Dave that tomorrow he's going to save I'll kill anybody who gets in the way of my guns
Including my own kid
It doesn't matter
Well you know who's who's going to become a consolator
Mitch McConnell but we'll get to that in a minute do you know at I'm going to tell you this I'll tell you this one thing cuz it just popped in my head finally
About Ted
Is in the 90s
There's like this Flash
Game where you play as a reindeer
Right and it was a reverse of them to escape Nugent you know you'd have a
Person call so that the reindeer would be hunting people
Okay and one of the like
Hunter calls you know like a deer call like that thing
Would just be some guy going
Who wants
To meet the news
And it is finally reappeared in my brain
That that
20 years ago
It's now a thorn in my f***
King side until I die
There we go
If you're trying to get in that game in your reindeer trying to lure the newgen self
You can just yell I'm under a
Alex
Play the clip
Pier
The cop
Discussing like
Some of the tactics
This is this just goes on a weirdo
Here is the DPS spokesperson
Nerf
They do not know where the gunman is
Hearing gunshots they are receiving gunshots
Point
They proceeded any further not knowing where this sucks
Kill other people inside.
The kids are dead
They're overthinking all this
I just
Cowards
Not going with their instincts
You're not going
Politically culturally
Space
Send
50 something billion dollars to Ukraine now eligible 60 billion
What does that have to do with anything I have no idea just throw that it doesn't make sense
What's what it what what's happened
Yeah
Asphalt and they're sending money to Ukraine but it
It's not going to manly enough
Still harming elephants in
Circuses you know it's just one of those things where the
It's just wonder One the same exact
Situation yeah yeah
So
I told you earlier
There's a rogue gun-grabber on the list remember I said Mitch McConnell that's right
McConnell pushes gun control with gems
Authorhouse Republic
Unbelievable
Every time
We don't have
Mental institute
Ladies and gentlemen
Only got a bunch of money
But if you don't you're going to be on the street
Which has more of the argument for
Scooby arm McConnell is up to his old man Mitch McConnell
A+ ranking from the NRA
I don't know I didn't there should be a higher rank
He just gets to own the NRA
Part-owner of support number
Talk about mental health career it's remarkable how Alex again can identify a problem
Express that problem thanks
Suggested completely idiotic solution
There are Mental Hospitals but you can only afford them if you have a lot of money because Insurance often doesn't cover that kind of care
And US everyone needs gun
Yep that's all
Essentially what Alex is doing is
Accepting that there's nothing that could be done to make the world better the only solution
Must be able to protect yourself from Violence by enabling yourself
To commit defensive viola
It's taken for granted that insurance doesn't cover much mental health care and that these sorts of inpatient centers are Out Of Reach
For most people
Which is nonsense
We can do better
The government has the ability to change regulations on the insurance industry to cover these kinds of things
We have the ability to allocate public funds
Do the creation
For affordable Mental Health Care Center
There's so many things we can do that are just get a gun and get ready to kill people who come to hurt you
That's not
What Alex's ideology does here's basic
We condemn anyone who needs access to mental health care to not getting it
He's the crying how there's a crisis in mental health care in the country so he does
I have to talk about guns for when the rubber
The road and he needs a suggestion of how to address the crisis
It's just
This is stupid
Painfully
Blind
Blinds two possibilities
I mean
It's it's
Unfortunately the most common point of view pessimistic
It's
I mean what is that what it is what is it in quarters on nihilism what it doesn't matter way I mean that's
The problem is it said that was the whole thing it doesn't matter what governmental officials are responding to this with because their Solutions
They're just avoid the actual problem
What every single f****** people are every single person who studies
Is this s*** in Spencer
All of their time doing this is like if you want to reduce crime
Invest in the neighborhood
Improve people's lives
Don't murder them
And every time it's like here's what we do
What we do is we hire more murderers
Here's the thing
Like
Those people who are saying these these experts in
You know like
What's nice about their position
Yeah is that there is
A possibility of
Improve
It's nice yes
Courtesan
This is the thing that is essential to me about Alex's point
There is no point in doing anything other than arming yourself to the teeth
Do defend yourself from
The people
Who aren't getting the care that they need and end up
I guess her.
That's useless
Not that
Somebody who's already gone
Yes it's somebody who's already like Lissa
I don't care that I can go to the grocery store I'm going to steal your oil fill up my murder car
And drive a thousand miles to get away from the
This world yeah it's giving up
Cosby
Philosophical and political positions that Alex
Carrie's
End up
In that place anyway
It's against
It's against my own rules
The problems that I'm so mad about
So I can
And it's pathetic
It is real sad
Satyr
AutoZone this coin
Right
Gun coin
Oh my God the Gun theme coin
Good day
Yeah but look
It's not related it's a
Thousands of us attorneys in the
Arashi January Sixers
Border
Imma go ahead and tell you about something very important
We did not have this planned
Parallel that's happening right now
Subway
Designed over 6 months ago
Three weeks ago
Blue Door offices
Monday
What was going on
Bulls the truck
Did we learn anything from this
And it's it's I believe it's a coincidence
Are you sure I mean
How do you get that money
Maybe
Just maybe
If this coincidence
Happened
You know you're like oh my God this
Truck has come in
With these gun
Coins
On the day of a horrific shooting at a school
Yeah maybe you hold off on selling those
They show movies for like
A long time if it's going to be released on the wrong
Time trouble was supposed to come out around 9:11
Did not come out did they re-release
Big Trouble in Little China
I also the Dave Barry version of Big Trouble in Little China
Yeah I think you I think you sit on these coins for a bit
You got eight million dollars coming in from Bitcoin you don't need to price gouge your f****** people with these
Dumb silver coins
Like if this is so distasteful
And memory
It's like
He has to stress this over and over again like
Hey look it was not
Supposed to be
Play we did time this week either bad
Great
You're still doing it though
You could not
Do I choose to not
Yeah you're doing the thing that is a fair
I mean it because
The other answer if you're saying that I
Then what you're saying
It is more important for my bottom line
That I do this
Horrific monster
First thing I think about like
After a shooting
Probably
More eyes on me and more sales of a
The gun Second Amendment themed coin cuz I don't feel like the Second Amendment under attack if if somebody murder
There's a lot of people that's in Port
Need to buy a coin commemorating the weapon
And they did it with
F****** sucks and he should
I get I mean yeah
Any weights or else who sucks Ted Nugent
Is on and he has
Jamaica news
Suspicious American
Careers 2022
Uncle Sam
Legislator
Judicial branch
Against the American dream
Your friends have control over all of them
America
If anyone is a suspicious American it said f****** news suspect him of Ally
That stupid assholes forget about the
Decade of him saying that the government was the enemy of America during Obama's presidency
I can't believe that Uncle Sam
We wanted to murder and explicitly said I would like to
Multiple presidential candidates / President Obama suck on my rifle I can't believe that
This dark day would come when I
Shining City on the hill
So much
Ted 2
Get to that
Lace man
Really minimizing it Indiana
I can't believe we would
Really
Undercut
His is strong
Feelings about
What's that guy also the they'll spend money on Invaders gofucker
Yourself
Ted
Anyway
Ted wants people to learn from what happened
I would be fine if they glowed
I would be happier in fact I would be happier if the right
Gloated about
Controlling every aspect
To the government
But they're still
Teaching about it it's so infuriating
Part of the gang and retaining the title
I know how you have to do it
Anyway Ted wants people to learn
Regarding Uvalde
Information
Discount
There's all kinds of
The past that we seem to be
Ignoring and discounting
Conscientious citizen of America's only goal
What's wrong
Do anything wrong again
Let's have quality control
Instead of scrambling
Damage control
The ultimate irony here is that what time is doing on Alex's show is 100% in effort at damage control
They're two things he's trying to cover which are guns and inappropriate police
He doesn't want to talk about those things too much be
Because he's a gun fetishist and because
Reviewing the police response won't end up providing ammunition for him to use against the federal government
He wants to attack because he sees them as a threat to the gun
For Richie the fetish
Also 90% of the audience that Ed has if his
This point has some strong connections to law enforcement so turn it on that would be death
For whatever career he has left
Anybody who still wants to go here Wango Tango at
That's a cop
The effort to construct a narrative where the feds or the FBI it for knowledge of the attack which is
Is what tide is touching on
Here is an attempt to carry out damaged
Control but it's
Being presented as some kind of an
Exercising critical
Pathetic creep and honestly have nothing to say that's worthless
Something to them guys
A f****** worse
Yeah
I think that's why that distinction of like the feds had this knowledge in the people on the ground are good
Is important
Because Dad's got to keep his audience
How to get turn on Cops course
You can turn on these you never know again
People who will never exist
Those are the people whose fault it
That way we don't have to
To deal with the
If you thought for a second that as anything
You need to hear him say
This is kind of fun
Well that's cuz you've known I've always been
The world
Halsey
Freedom
Debate
In the world
Because they have
Take the devil's
View2
Michael the
Just support
Everything I say
For everything I believe
Yeah
He's Michael the Archangel of logic and Truth
Wow
You know that's like at my bad my Peak
I could touch
Weather in Annandale
Going to have to train for a long time
But when I get back there I hope to me
Meet Ted Nugent
If he is not on
Coke
Someone's got to distill his blood cuz it'll be a new drug
Batman I don't know
How
JJ's at mean the delusion doesn't even
Close to the words
Yeah even sane
There's a just a outrageous level of narcissism
Delusion of self
German word that is a paragraph long that explains head new
I was listening to Ted's interview here and what I really came away with was
He seems like he's
So much matter
Hey people like Beto
He is at the shooter
The police
Not mad at them nearly as much as he is it
Beto and Michael Moore
Los Magueyes
The Deep
Viewing of the sacred
Use that guy
Perfect
You got an animated Miss to his anger at them
That does not seem to be present
But it didn't even talk about the
Person who just
Killed 21 people
You know that
Bat
You are angry
At the documentarian
Who made a movie about the most famous school shooting
20 years ago
You're wrong
VA
If you wanted and I would be mad at him
It would be reasonable for Ted Nugent be mad at him
If that documentary
Had led to gun control
Then I could see oh yeah we should be mad at Michael Moore I mean from his point of view I reserved
That's a totally good point like Michael Moore did everything he could
He shot his shot
F******
It did not end up in the orwellian totalitarian and
Douglas state that he imagines
Him you like murdered Michael Moore's dream of being valuable to society
Ted Nugent doesn't have much else to be
Maddox outside
Hehehe
He's talking about France
Whether or not they have a Kalashnikov
Here's what I bring up on these
Paris France
France
Gun
Do you think
Banning of guns
French citizens
Were used in Paris
How
That
Band workout
Following that logic bring this up because he's the Archangel Michael and champion
He's allowing AK-47 that all his shows
If banning guns didn't do anything to stop this one shooting in France then
Certainly on probation
Does being useless
Yeah I think it should actually be a requirement based on his belief to have a gun
H-E-B requirement that he only plays venues that allow you to bring.
Go on his first date is at the Beth Deckard Hall in Florida and they have a blanket prohibition against
Any kind of weapon
But not even knives getting pregnant
Fans should boycott totally
Anchor Kalashnikov doesn't
Oh man
Probably got guns on stage
Probably draw 200 people at this point probably
You want to have 200 people with machine guns at your show safest way to perform
Next date is at the Florida theater in Jacksonville which also prohibits be carrying firearms
Inola
It's also again
That's crazy really the case from 2018 tells you all need to know where he is
Management specifically told the venue in Virginia
Not to allow guns in
He's a malicious creep doesn't live by any of the prescription
Humane Society take
Because he knows that he's really rich
He can afford to protect himself from the threats that his ideal Society implies
He sucks
Yep
I can hate this dude
It is
The
I mean
There's no other way to
To look at it now other than to say
Ted Nugent would prefer you live in a
Murder filled hellhole
And he gets to live on his
Compound was really nice guns
They would if he got to live on his compound really nice guns
And you got
Duluth you get to live on his compound with all the guns and everything and all that stuff and you don't live in a murder house
Hellscape what you live in
Is a world where everyone is armed to the teeth never feel safe
Right we all basically just live with guns to each other's head
It really does feel like sure safety
By never letting your gun down just feel like that's the direction the states are headed
Right like we could go the gun-control route
Or we could go to mandatory gun wrap
Even talked about like
How he misinterprets the Switzerland rule of people having
Having to have a gun
It's a prescription
Everybody
Teachers get groceries
Some bad guy with a gun shows up there
The teacher can't do anything he gets shot along with it what are you do you arm groceries or aren't on the Armadale
Exactly then you go from there until eventually everyone is armed
Teacher with a guy with a gun
With a gun you got on the student every single one of those student start teaching critical race Theory
Boy you got all kinds
To save your day
Rrb class how do we arm the pets
We give them gun mount
But Dino Riders
Anyway so we hired at Michael Moore
Beto O'Rourke
But someone else is getting a little flag
Obvious way
Great great
What
Grassroots
Civil rights organization
Because of a shooting
Set the civil rights organization
Country was founded when the Brits came to take the gun
He knows that I love what I'm sorry what
NRA
Event this is disgusting
Disgusting
Suicide
Political correctness that's politically correct Lee Greenwood
Can you hear yourself use no longer proud to be American
I can't believe it after a shooting
He would abandon the NRA
It's my understanding that the reason that he canceled was because of the shooting but also like
He had agreed to sing I think it was at a past year but the NRA convention be cancelled for 2 years right
Contractually was still going to be sitting at this one
I'm not doing that
Why would you
You think it's bad it's bad idea.
Don't Go sing at the NRA
Right that's not enough
You're done
He will not gladly stand up
The music is dyed all over it
Working man
What is things that I think is the most
Sad
Thing that you ever hear from people is like
You know the Ben Shapiro debate me AOC Huntsville
And that's why we're making a joke out of it with the demanding
Rampaul to pay you
Baby I was in that joke like 2 weeks into it every now and then I get there
I was like okay that's why it's really fun when we were actually able to keep track of the days
I always find that to be a sign of
Someone I looked
I think less of
When people are like
Demanding someone to pay
Possible for me to think less
So Ted
Beto O'Rourke
Baitme you
Michael Moore
Supply
Work is a storm skateboarding
They represent the anti-gun side
Go back to challenging people
Fist fights at least then you have an equal shot or I'll see you at the Town Square and said Don
Absolutely will do a charity boxing event or something
Play more appropriate on brand new Dodge
Two people
Talk like the idiots you are
I can't imagine anyone wanting to debate someone like Ted Nugent either like
Want to get yelled at about a bunch of nonsense
Imagine everything I say to be taken
Completely Iraq
You don't know who that is
You just signed on to this debate
Thing right and they're just bringing random guess
For YouTube
Like the chase
High-end
And then Ted Nugent gives his open
Opening statement and you listen to that man talk
Find a reason to continue staying there
You want to put you in
The Archangel Michael of truth I would listen to him talk I don't like what you're saying
And your whole like you seem unwell
Absolutely your adjectives are all over the f****** place I'm out of here
You seem like Gary Busey who didn't have head trauma and aren't a recovering addict
Which means you're worse than Gary Busey at least he has a reason
I also said I would say that I think the Ted just wants to do a bait
These people because of clout chasing
I would like a tattoo
Because there's a ton of people who are maybe more
Skewer in the mainstream who are like
You know twitch
Debaters whatever
They would be clout chasing for exactly
If you really want somebody
It is it is a little bit watching
Doing Infowars it being a different varying levels of entertainment
Clout Chaser evilities is like
Just Siri
But minor like
Scaling up
Doesn't matter how high you go there's somebody to cut Chase
Even higher
Like it just never ends
Yep stop chasing clout
So Alex Goes To Break here and he's got some big news breaking news
Because I'm
Dispassionate
Monday for full hour we love you
Five more minutes
From Uvalde huge news
So we got a confirmation that the standout has ordered and Alex knows who it isn't working
The break that f******
Okay big news does he know
Weather Uvalde School District Chief of Police
Has admitted that they
I ordered the stand down
Jurisdiction
Call the State Police border patrol
Call the police not to go in
Disgusting
So the police chief Alex is referring to here is Pete Arredondo who was the commander on the scene at the shooting
The clip with Alex is so excited about is the press conference that the head of the Department of Public Safety Colonel Stephen
McCraw is holding
Amazon air
Where he explains that Arredondo believe that
The situation to change from an active shooting to a barricaded suspect
Which is why the play
Didn't storm in
This isn't really the same thing as ordering a stand-down it's more a situation of a
Very costly Miss judgment
Announces World involved the feds having knowledge of the facts and ordering
Please knock
To stop the thing that they know is happy
The available information in this case doesn't match that at all but there are enough details that look right if you squint
Alex can Bluff his way through labeling this is
Then once the label is caught on that's all the audience is going to remember
Because how that word is used on Alex's show Bell associated with the standard
Stand Down
You'll be able to sort of
Color this with
Memories of
Ask narrative when you say little things in the audience has the
A full image evoke
Didn't their minds so you've got this little self can
Contain kind of thing and all the sudden it goes into a larger diorama
And once you get that thing to apply to something you associate it
And Alex will just throw that on the pile of
Bulshit associate
The dude
Got to go
Good out got to go home
Until we got another gas
Rodger
Single thing we said
Right here on Infowars
I turned out to be true
The entire Russian collusion
North Korea
That went all the way to Hillary Clinton
The real question is seems to me
After the trial in d.c.
Alicia's bombshell after
Why is mr. Durham going for the low-hanging fruit
Another words Sussman
Michaels
Bendy
Attorney
Appears to me to be
Patsy
Fall Guy
That's got to sting for Rodger that Durham's low-hanging fruit
In the form of the Sussman case turned out to be a dud
That was the Fall Guy in the
The Patsy and Durham couldn't even see
Secure conviction there man and Sussman got acquitted if that's your Fall Guy that gets acquitted
Suck
It's got a sting even more considering the tough man was acquitted of lying to the FBI which is what Rodger was
Convicted of and would probably still be in jail for if Trump hadn't pardon
I can't imagine caring less about this Durham s*** Rogers on to talk about it is
Is less than irrelevant how to make
How could you
You actually
Continue talk
Talking about that
Right
Like at on the that day you just an hour through
Seems really weird that Alex has confirmed that there was a stand down
And there's this cover at this brick in Newport news story
You know work
And some stuff out talking angles like
Uno
He goes to Rodger to talk about how Sussman is low-hanging fruit the Durham case
Which turns out
To be too much
Too much for Durham to handle low-hanging fruit Durham really could
Handle
Bohagon crew
That's true
So one of the things that I think I need to make
Crystal clear
Is it most of Rogers interview
Is
You know about
A lot of it is about
Stuff but not really anything substantial
It's really trying to make sure that people know
But Alex isn't a snitch
They don't want us questioning when they try to steal it again
We got the calls
Directions all alive
It is 1
Hundred percent a fraud
In a lie
Help those are saying
It is
That's precisely why I why I wanted to bring it up
Clear the air
Okay so he snitched for sure
I think it's
Still just responding
To the idea that Alex
That what's that on his show that he was going to talk
Everybody if they would give him a beer today price
And then people covered him saying that and then he did plead
The fifth 100 x 24
But then he was like oh everyone saying good I agreed to go and talk to them
If I got immunity
Which does
Kind of look like you have something to hide
I mean Mercedes tell you to tell that you want immunity for so you committed a crime and you want to
Tell on the people you committed a crime with clear that he is like I'll only go
And I don't have anything to tell them but I will talk to them if they give me a dirty so they can't set me up in
A perjury trap or something like that
But I think that he's still just
Responding to stories surrounding that
Because at this point they're you know we're still a ways off from
Today's
Coordinate
The January 6th
Stop
Comic
And the proud boys have not been re-indicted again and I at yet
So I think that this is just like
Dealing with
Selma
Segments of Alex's audio
That thinks
But he snatched
I think it's reasonable to think that he
Snatched
I I don't think that he has much to snitch about maybe I think is also a reasonable
Iiii take no position on
This
At this
Reasonable if you're in Alex's audio
Dance and your you think that everything is a conspiracy or suspicious of everything
Spinning that case
I think it's reasonable to think that he
How could you not think that he snitched I would be I'm amazed that you could trust her
You know like this is a dude who know s***
His buddies were involved like you've been through a lot with him
Deathstroke
Be kind of just say built-up safe
Nope sir Rodger is former Infowars
Employee he worked on the room where he hosted
Destroyer Owen Shroyer
Babe
You know because of this
Political persecution that he went through
He lost his job and Infowars
Ono which I immediately thought like lilacs could easily
Just give it back
Well Alex has a policy where he doesn't hire
Chicken salads
Set true I don't think so.
I think
The first Alex can't afford
Second him back
Really
Can stand on his own two feet now where is it the beginning of the war room
You're probably not going to be able to get many people interested in another showing for your show
So you dangle the Rodger Stone
Nothing there even though you didn't actually co-host most of the time
Rogers not coming back there
Workout buddy has another gig
What is what is Lye
Find your
My show my new show the stone Joan is available
Every week
Play from
Or Central
Five Easter
Are you can go free
Commandant
Lindale
If you want to help me in my face
Families are epic struggle for
For Freedom you can go to Stone defense
Shut off
Somewhat somewhat here that is disrespectful
Scrappy's on Mike lindell's
The stone Zone
Yeah I think that bite of even been the name of the show that he did with Travis Earth hide the comedian that we know oh yeah
Either that or the Stone Cold Truth
Because those two shows are like
Those are the names of the shows that I'm aware of it he's had in the past
BS Dogs Out
Hot man
The patties
That is the right
8 move for Rod
Michael DelMonte absolutely
Take that money
You're not
Who cares about viewers
Your numbers are down
Get the f*** out that's what you do you scam for money and you move on Glendale is a good movie
Depending on
How about you have to worry about about January 6th
Like that's really the line that I don't know what yeah
Yeah lay low
Scare Mike Lindell
Like finesse your associations with Infowars
The back of people's memories
Maybe Rebrand a little bit take a step to step up
Message you got to do is scan Mike window for
For sure it's it's a low. Right
Yeah yeah
So that's good
Can imagine
Ever
Listening to that show secondarily I was thinking about there's like I can't even I don't even know
Really what Frank speech is
I know it's a website of some sort I thought maybe it was a social network
Yeah I 100%
Heard Frank B
Beach Ono what is he doing good pranks beach.com
Taking a dip
Yeah
I'd like that that that doesn't make sense for a Michael until website I've never been to the website
So I don't know what it looks like
I don't know if it's an aggregator of like right now
I've never
Is braking on air
Pranks
Beach.com
We're going to get some boards
Okay
So we got
Oh yes podcast
Oh yeah I see that sale on pillows
Okay so these are the podcast with graham Ledger
Oh man that'd better with a ghost
Matrix show live Groove
Silco podcast
What do they talk about don't know who any of these Maple are
Ivory Hecker
She was
I think at The Blaze
Anime be laughed
And then Alex was trying to get her for a while I think
Who shamaine
Jermaine is on there well there we go
Qanon wife
Man
I wonder what her numbers are
I bet she gets like one point
2 billion
I would be surprised if she was stealthily the most famous of all of the people
Oh okay so
He's got
Tv Mike Lindell Izzy's TV a TV section
TV1 and TV2
How much money can you spend Pete Santilli
Alex's body and
Stuart Rhodes anime
Yeah got to show Trump speech here
I mean
I didn't think Mike Lindell was that
Stewie Peters
Yeah Steve
Amazon here
I think that means
They've got a mixture of like
Original content and it's a player I bet that they can sell their own ads on we got it over here let's talk
Talk about it with Will Johnson
Let's talk about it will Johnson was the guy who used to host Alex's show Firepower radio
Along with Tom Papa
I did not know that it wasn't for a short. Of time before it
Fell apart
We'll see how long Lyndale one into last
I mean who knows but boy there is a
This is a
Full list of winners just a who's who of who s*** me Powell TV
I'm trying to find like the bottom
Lobero theater
Did the Unabomber have his podcast on there
Does the Unabomber have a podcast
I think he's afraid of
Technology
The type who's going to get
Get into our ssb4 track though
That's cuz it's probably an aggregator to
Yeah okay I'm by Frank's beats.com
So Rogers beer it's not really all that impactful at all
And he's he's
A little he's got some ideas
Job
The police
Do you tip 20 years ago
Why
A video about the Federal Reserve
Video about world government
Shadowbanned
That was just
The process
Video showing
Anne koppe
Doing something wrong
Wooden block
Cummings our problems
So I guess what Alex
Might be the
McKay's
Like early YouTube may have carried out an elaborate plot
The Heidi's videos about weird Fringe conspiracy nonsense and then hype up videos covering police abuse
That could be
Or I would suggest that the more likely scenario is that his videos about the Federal Reserve and all that s*** wasn't very interesting and
No one really cared
Conversely videos of things like the police attack
Protesters at the G8 Summit
Probably could be more popular and upheaval
Little bit
There is a really simple explanation for the phenomena that Alex
Describing
And it
Expect his intricate
Conspiracy content
Was not really all that popular in the earlier part of his career where is be easy to digest stuff that actually had content
Contact with reality was much more interesting to a wider audience
Seems like he probably learned that lesson
Maybe there's a reason that for years and years as marketing push was as the 9/11 truth guy and the anti
Bi-State guy
It's because those topics are fairly universally understandable
And things that resonate with people regardless of how invested you are in a
Conspiracy
You can see in this clip how Alex is brainworx
Defines elaborate meaningless explanations for things that are pretty obvious when that obvious thing kind of works
Against his Center
Self
He would never want to admit that he should about the Federal Reserve really wasn't that good and didn't interest many people
It had to been shadowbanned
He couldn't possibly be the people are broadly concerned about police of using civilians and have an interest
Stories like that
He must be that the globalist are
Pushing those videos they can demonize the
So they can take them over
None of the shoot that he's imagining is real
And when he was a listener of his show engage with any of it as if it is
All you're doing is playing around in his imagination
He can be exciting at times
But none of that s*** has any validity outside of Alex
Yep I mean it's a point where you could be like oh s***
You've been shadowbanned
And and then
You might
Think that he's so right
You won't even check
And you'll just assume they
That you've been shadowbanned you don't even
No right I can't believe that I've been
Shadowbanned I can't possibly have low engagement on things that I put into the world it must be a plot
Are there is one thing I did like I remember whenever I was doing that streaming video games for a while
I have up
Words of nine
Butte on some of those videos
Cuz obviously because YouTube shadowban me and not because it's inherently boring to watch me play a dumb game
Time that I was doing stand-up if I tweeted
Things that I thought were really funny
Yeah
Never got any traction on any of those tweets get a laugh on one of my jokes
As the audience shadowban that gently the shadowy and then later on they would laugh at the next joke and that's the one that the
Liberal media is trying
To push on them
Totally
So Alex has gotten some information from this Prescott
That the colonel was putting out on
Stay straight on that low but I could
So the timing is still good
So
Beat the Alex got some of that information part of the information that was put out is
Turtle McGraw McGraw saying
With all the information that they knew
The decision that was made was wrong
It was a bad decision it was right right making him an enemy of the cops forever
And Alex has a really interesting way he's process
Shortcomings
Problems it's not to undermine the place
Um
Brazen
Cheerleader
Who's up there
Attacking you
No Biden has endorsed the police response
And Uvalde
Cuz there's a cover-up
The crew dead
Car wash
30 minutes ago
Getting that live press conference
Heard that Ashley
20 minutes
She's been on my desk
10 minutes
Haybuster
Have the Club start
Of what really
On Monday
As a system knows is coming out
Incredibly evil
They admit they're wrong
What
Wait what weapon place
What's a Roth IRA
Perfect
No no no
There's now no
You said there was a cover-up
That
Perfect job
Yeah that's weird
That's a weird thing for the press conference where McCraw says
All the information they know now that decision on the ground to believe that a transition
From active shooting to a barricaded suspect was the wrong decision
About how the police are usually good
Texas when you do something wrong you on up
Do it so if I understand correctly
It is
A cover-up
And they were ordered
Stand down there covering up that order to stand down and it's not a cover-up but they did lie a lot and now
Abiding is covering for them
Trying to cover up their lies
It's not cover up cuz it didn't go long enough
Yeah
You know Alex singing
Because no taxes you own up to it and stuff but
We know cuz we live in the future that a couple days after this police new Valdese
Stop cooperating with the investigation into the response
Which is where life without send me another text
Operate will apologize Webber wrong but if you try and investigate the crimes we do
We will run away and kill you
Announces bye-bye Miss come out and said that the cops did everything right which is evidence of a cover-up
I hate the police so when he says something positive
Suspicious
The White House Press Secretary
The president has the utmost respect as you all know for the men and women of lawn for
Just days ago he honored the memory of
The former police officer Aaron Salter in Buffalo was killed
Trying to stop the shooter
At the supermarket
I know that right now authorities are working
How to piece together more details of what happened in Uvalde
So we won't prejudge the results
From here at this time
Pretty sensible and measured response from the press secretary
It probably would be in overstepping and abusive exactly
Providing to unilaterally demand investigations order
Declare things to be a certain way before the facts are available
But the storyline is that the Vikings all in favor of the police and what they how they responded and he refuses to question
So in order to support the police and simultaneously be the best way for Alex to thread
Easter egg
Big knives that the police response
Wasn't good
While focusing on the appeal
Difference of repentance
On the part of the police
It's kind of brilliant
Really as a way that you can maintain your position
Yeah doesn't hold up
Do absolutely think it'll fall apart very quickly
But it does sound
To somebody who is inclined to already believe everything that you say is genuine
That
You are like
Listen
This is when we need to support
The cops more than ever
Supports the cop shows you that the cops are admitting that they're doing wrong and that's
The good thing
And biting saying that they did right
Yeah yeah
You maintain the positions that are kind of central to what you need to maintain
Lindsey
Stop
No guidance
So we have
A really bizarre
Development
I would say with
The
The shooting coverage
As a whole
I think
I think that this episode is where we're
Getting closest to like
I think he's about
You know he
He's Butte dipping
Toes much deeper into the conspiracy water
It's no longer a hostage
Situation apparently there's now the
Standard
Sam down talking points in
Nugent's coming into
Assume that
There's
All kinds of foreknowledge
Totally
So we'll see we'll see what I would come to this but that we've one last clip here and it's
Again but like Rodger coming on to complain about Durham
What are we even doing
To get on
Prominent scientists
Take over
And the new lock
Work
What's the weather tomorrow
Blockbuster films made about him
Lady from plandemic
Is on
So
Still doing covid
I think you might be doing a little monkeypox
Ambulance chasing conspiracy
It's done so let's what's the next
You know what really would impress me is if these f***
Who are going off on the covid
Conspiracies and Ivermectin
And stuff a front and center in their coverage is like
Also
They're weaponizing monkeypox
It was like 2 years ago
Yep
It's weird that wasn't the case
It is 8
It's going to suck
It's going to suck real hard
Because to maintain their grip
They're now always has to be a panda
You know
For a hidden one or the not really because
You do tend to notice
That
Okay
Here's what I would say
I think the covid pandemic obviously brought a lot of
Maybe new Griffey types into the pool
There is a legacy
Connors
But you do seem to notice
Atrend
Hey
It's weird
Why do you seem people are floating around to all of the things that everyone's mad about
Kind of transition from this thing to that thing every time Alex introduces
Somebody they've got a new expert label from compared to the last two years they were
All the sudden he knows everything but deep Finance
Yeah they say it's kind of that so I don't think they need to always have
A pandemic going on
But they do
Definitely have a Groove
Antitussive
Seem to work to their financial enter
Kristen and Steph
Not good
Yeah I don't care about the plandemic
Nope
Get the f*** out of here
On Monday
For a rundown
Some of the progression of the shooting
Conspiracy and we'll see
How that develops
When Alex has a little bit of time on the weekend
Jamil his thoughts over to rewrite again
Probably
Back to the register
Black Jordan
But until then
Bread website
Brussels
We aren't fighting
Japan Clark I hope you all have a dreamy creamy summer
The sex robot
Alexandra Thurston color