Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Sit around and talk a little bit
What's Alex Jones
Question
What's today is
Care package
Yes
A lot of Care Pack
Tonight
Specifically made it clear that I was
What's up I gave you the pickles pickle relish
You're fine for me what's
Sustains me is the heartfelt
Yeah it sounded all this chocolate that's all I can think about also
I'm confused by this
Yes there was a let everybody else decide whether or not
Kittens are going to eat kittens or if you should
So there is in this street
Pack of four cats
Spaghetti just a
Purina Cat
Tri-pac know for sure that the forecast
Along with it there's also something that looks like
Their gummies
Called cotton candy kitten
I don't know if this is for cancer for human
And I'm I don't know what to do with this you wouldn't feed a giraffe animal cracker
That looked exactly like a giraffe that's just uncomfortable
It has allergies
Point of like it's Palm oil-free is
Palm oil something cats can't I have no idea
I don't either
I don't know I'm going to eat all the money I don't care
Squeeze
Is Dan yesterday my partner and I went out and played tennis
For a while immediately after we went to yoga which was really cool cuz we had a lot of exercise
But she has gotten
Good
Atena
Raphael good well I mean like
You're so good she's got
You like we started playing a few years ago and
Barely you know it was fun to hit the ball is so high and you know that be fun we were playing yesterday and she was kicking me
My apps
Like eventually I was like
I think I need to play hard
In order to
Keep up with her
That's how good she
You've gotten well maybe she's been going easy on you the whole time and now it's finally f*** ever marry don't let it go off
Have I been getting played this entire time like this is the Ultimate Muscle
Married to me before she can
Yeah that was cheap
But she could not beat you at tennis before there was a ring on it
You know that makes sense a lot of women get to let you know they have those all the matter bad
So they're like let's not do this until we do
I got it
I mean I think it's who knows how you would respond
To being beaten atena
Casino
Years to beat you up.
A beautiful racket at me
Good heavens
Now that's not met any type of that time accountant
Because I don't even like winning it makes me feel by
Brightright
Like you you feel bad I don't like what was that case I would be
I'd be worried about losing
I was growing up my oldest brother
He was the one who had the temper
And so that
And it was all competition to you know like he was
Get kicked out of
Yeah yeah cuz he was so
Competitive and angry whenever so
Since then I've grown up with
This kind of like
Don't do that
And I go way too far the other
Yeah I had a friend
When I was younger who would like throw controllers and break them
And stuff like that when you lose at a game
And yeah that always kind of talked me earlier of like
You can control yourself and not break things
That's what I did Punch walls for a little while when I was when I was at my most
Axiom's mentally ill what I was younger that's true but
Line
As we discussed last episode
I would say wrapping up in terms of like a dedicated look
I'm at the response
Uvalde shooting
On Alex's bar
I think there's a lot of people who
Probably thinking hey why don't
What you cover Alex's response to the January 6th
There's only one at the
Of the commission there's a whole season of the
True
But the issue is
On Thursday that's when the
The first hearing the Primetime hearing was
That day
Owen was hosting
Friday the next day Owen was hosting
As always whenever there's something that is like
Visit we need to hear Alex
It's batch
Let the let the minor-league guys take the first hit see what they've got to throw out there see what people throw back at him
And then Alex will take a crack at it and steady for water and honestly who knows if it's intentional at all but it definitely
He seems to be pretty consist
Whenever there is something that's like
Is going to be nuts well over three examples and that means
Did the pattern
Cigar like obviously
Probably a coincidence
That's like when the new pope was named like Alex wasn't in studio
He's going to be named because it could be today or it could be tomorrow it is
Notable
Alex is out of Studio whenever the things that are like
But he might have some really interesting commentary on this personal connection that emotion
Might get him to reveal things that maybe he should
Recording this on
On Sunday
And Alex baby
Hosting his shadow this evening but we don't know by the time we recording this and
He'll be impossible to flip it around so maybe we'll have a January 6th
Committee responsible thing on Wednesday
Ideally
We'll see
We'll see what
If not maybe
Space nonsense
I haven't gotten we have gone to pass for a while that's true we've been in
The present to require some
Strip
June 6th
2022 is a day that
Something really notable happened on Alex
Texas show interesting
Should I
We talked about
Before the show giving a teaser
Baby shirt
Yeah you want to give it to you cuz this is what happened
It is so f***** up
Mistake
And all over my face
And
Say that tube to Chillicothe ashamed of yourself
So Alex is ashamed of himself all over that face
No
No I don't regret I refuse to believe that Audi interior
There is a bit of a protracted
Quote on quote apology in this episode
That
We'll see
The path that we get
To the
Apology
Of course that again and have you quotes apology
Sundby that's me says hello 22222 new Chi-Town thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
Thank you very much
Cookie suit from Mario Mario 3
Could turn into a statue in till
2 years ago
Watch
Wild straight up
Terrible
Jefferson from twisting Plancha podcast
The Build-A-Bear group thank you so much
Jordans
We're a couple of dudes who sit around and worship at the altar of ghosts and laugh at 1997
Is this dramatic
Pause
Or else
You are now a technocrat
Play the old one
Northstar songs
Someone someone sodomites
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much
We we start here at the beginning of the show
Paralysis headspaces in
At the job
Most people don't realize are living through extremely historical events
Until it's already
And I'm not a good
Dad
Very optimistic
I think that's
Not true at all how is it that we're going to colonize space
The globalist plan is to kill all of us and then colonize face by themselves
Well because you have to defeat the globalist and then you'll be able to colonize space because you will have
Ask God's test of the devil that is the global
Okay throw this out there
More than one human
Right cuz we assume the globalists are interdimensional demons
For the most
But they've got to have some humans working with
So they get off-planet
We're all human
Did we techno
Quickly get off when
I know because you're being possessed by the demons if you're working with the globalist
Demon possession Works into your jeans and you're no longer human
Covid vaccine makes you a genetically modified organism
I think it'll probably be the same
Send it all over Forest
I would take issue with Alex
Explain that he's an optimist at me to
That's definitely does not say
Number of times he said we're all dead we are all dead it's hopeless
Even when he stopped
Domestic it's like
Maybe
Only then I will be able to strangle Klaus Schwab
The good scenario
Pessimistic
So
Estranged space
As evidence
Bye
Science has shown that there are other dimensions more powerful
Energetically than our own holding
Our dimension in place
Show me the map
Lee
A controlled way
We know from history
We know from the Bible
We know from every other ancient texts as well and it home I found this one
No we don't
Everybody seen the meme that says
Hard Times make strong men
Strong men make good times
Good
X
Make weak man
Weak man
Make bad times
We had time she can reverse wow
That is
Bull
So I think there's some interesting things that you can take away from this first
Obviously this is
A little bit
Silly
The space-time evil Dimensions proven by match
22 believe it
I think at the end of their with this meme that he has
Hard times
Make
Strongman
I think that if you believe that
You to no longer believe like really in free will
Get like you have a pretty deterministic view of
Of stuff because essentially saying that
Do who you are in the hardiness
But you have is determined by your circumstances there's nothing
Good Times
Tuffman won't exist or whatever
I think that's a little bit silly to assume that everybody is
Is just sort of blowing around in the Wind
Especially it silly if you believe the sort of stuff that I like
Yeah I mean compatible it doesn't really make sense to believe that
The times make a man if you believe that God created you with all of your characteristics already
Contact at the beginning
Then the times make nothing
The times are simply where God plug
People in and out I guess
Yeah this this is a fine thing
Bruh meme
I guess
I mean it's
It's sort of a way of
You know
Contextualizing like
Hey
Things were tough
And I learn from them or whatever
People have to be tougher
In order to deal with
Kind of an inspirational thing and if
Keep trying to take it seriously
You're going to lose your mind
Yeah
Yeah I get it I guess Alex is reach nirvana of some sort that like
Life is a cycle of death and rebirth
I would have you know I saw a heavily edited a icon
Conversation so we know that's true
I think there's a weird that implication there too and that is
That like
Why would you
View fight
The death then
If it's just a part of the cycle that leads
Do the next rebirth
Like what's
The point make peace with the fact that the
Is death is coming and there will be a rebirth after work like is Alex really think that he
You capable of breaking the cycle of death and rebirth
What I mean is the wheel of the wheel of retardation I really think that next time Alex
She's not going to come back the way that he
He thinks he is
I definitely if you believe in reincarnation yes I definitely believe that that is the case
I'll tell you that right now come back as one of the kids
Children
You are your ancestors
I think there's a lot of convoluted nonsense going on here but
B b c this cycle
It continues and here's where we are man
Birdman make
Good Times
That's a simple way to go over to cycle but it is a known cycle
The humans have behaved in this way over and over again
What always happens
People start cheating on their husbands and wives
What people start having sex with the same sex
What
People that do that
Children I want to have sex with him
Then
I want to start sacrificing children
Well we're here
Ladies and gentlemen sacrificing children
I think that I think you're right that it is Judgement
I think I personally for your behavior what you are is the harbinger of attentive
What I do. Listen it's not personal bright you're just an example of how all men are weakened the going
Going to die in this time.
People having same-sex relationships is is a sign of the end time
This is silly and
Defensive
Clearly based in
A bigotry that he has an lgbtq community
I do think that if he wants me to take this at all seriously then he needs to have as much anger as he does towards
Drag queen story time anybody hoochie
Cheats on their spouse
He needs to have that as a
Consistency
Cheating on your spouse is also a heartbreak a harbinger of the Season X then
You care a lot about that
Infidelity Alex
Nope
Are you remarried you still be with your first wife
But yeah
I don't know why I find this insincere and just sort of a rationalization for him to be able
To attack the communities that he wants to attack
Yeah I mean the problem there is if you start looking at history
You'll start
Looking at that strong men weak men Meme and then start looking
Matriarchal
Society sets
Function of happiness in our joyful
And you're like oh man
Maybe we should not have the men part
Maybe that's why the cycle keeps happening is
Could you keep caring about men
Hartman wiechmann doesn't matter
I think also the
Some of that perception about the Hardman coming hard times or whatever like
Probably a lot of that has to do with our
Storytelling
Play whe
Hero worship
I would assume that it has a lot to do with folklore
And then meth
But yeah so there's sacrificing children
What he means by that
Because he doesn't mean it literally although he wants the audio
Be like yeah
We're here
Ladies and gentlemen
Gay strip bar in Dallas this weekend
Neon sign saying it's not going to lick itself behind little children
All sorts of other pornographic statements
So what other what other sexually obscene slogans were there on the walls and like
I don't like it
I guess if he wants to claim that
You can but
This wasn't like a strip show at all there's a there's a drag show in Dallas
It was at a bar that is true it is part of pride
But it was during the day as evidenced by the large number of adults
Groomer at people outside the venue
Pictures of
It said it's not going to lick itself
If this is a sign that's from a popular ice cream shop in Dallas
It's called cauldron ice cream
Grape it's their slogan it caught on it's really popular they have me on a hind
Yeah that they sell
People enjoy them
Maybe if I were the event organizers I would have considered taking that.
But ultimately it's not that big of a deal and maybe they couldn't
Take it down but maybe it's installed really well on the wall
And the bar wouldn't let the
It was that big of a deal cuz I don't know if it is
I think everyone there was probably aware that that's a slogan of the ice cream shop
It's super popular in town
So it wouldn't necessarily have as much of a hard sexual innuendo to the people that are there they would have
Familiarity with more of a soft sexual innuendo
I don't know I guess if that's child sacrifice
I don't know I don't know what
This is pathetic
Three-year-old is capable of understanding concepts
They can read
That's possible
I'm not saying the three-year-olds can't read
However
The concept of soft sexual innuendo
Seems a little bit
Beyond them that's just me I am not an expert on raising children cuz I have not interacted
Two children a quite a while
But I do remember that when I was in
Middle School
I rode bus 69 to school
And people made jokes about it
What
Call
Pretty blunt
Decent
Popular ice cream shop where this is that their slogan
Yeah people might
The kids might just be like a nice cream
Great I don't know anyways I don't think it's that big of a deal
Alex complains a bit about all of his
Is animes
And he just gets mad that the devil worship
Going to go on a while
But I just want people to feel
This
We don't we don't
Experience this
Much on the show
Turn it off after inactivity
I've spoiled it there's an ad
We're just disbelieve in this here we go
Devil worshipping pedophiles
Every cell in my body wants to get them off our children
Do it without you and you can't do it without me
We can do anything
We will
Devil sends the Beast with rice
That's because he knows his time is short
Let he who have understanding reckon the number of the Beast
For it is the number of a man
Someone hit that she cannot ignore this all ties together
Most important working forces ever done it down here
Sponsoring us
Read worse than I thought
Play off half our crew as we speak this month
Literally
I don't want to get into the red again
Real quick will get back to this but
I really do feel Alex's mentioning that he's big donors essentially saved his
Ability to do the show
You need to disclose who these
These people are conflicts of interest
I don't think that this is the case
But because he doesn't disclose who these people are you have to like start taking
Who could it be
Someone who's willing to drop $8000000 in Bitcoin on this f****** idiot
Alex says that all of these billionaires and all these really rich
People in the elite
They're all lined up in the side of the globalist
Except for Elon Musk
Which is normal for a lie
But then the other name he throws in his Peter
Teal
I don't think the Peter teal is the person who gave him the money but like
Because he won't disclose
Who this donor is
It makes you think
Peter Thiel is someone who probably could have access to millions of dollars of Bitcoin
It seems like
That is a possible person and if it is
Their implied reasons
You would give Alex that money in order to bail him out of trouble
And so
He needs to disclose who this person is for the sake of
The Integrity of his show the imaginary Integrity Odyssey I guess
But yeah that that troubled me a little bit
I've not heard him say like posit
Little things about Peter
Imagine him doing that I like literally
Peter teal exist as they've almost
Prototype of globalists that Alex believes it is responsible for a very chill
Effect on fries
He's a monster
Yeah it's an absolute
Do I know you did that I'm in no no not many people challenge Champion evil quite as well as
I'm safe from Alex's perspective
Yeah you was in the truck
What's the temperature in slapton infowarsstore.com there's a link
Founding member coin
You will get special deals exclusive documentaries reports
It's almost completed it is complete
You are the folks that financed it and
Cinemark
Obviously more than the coin does
Because your funds are operation you're buying a memento
Finish operation
1776 coin
Come and take it point in the series
Dot-com or AAA
To buy 33139
Supplements
Patriots out there with us
Memorial Day special is going to have to go another day or two cuz I just don't know what I'm going to have for sale here
This goes on like
3 more minutes
Incessant
It's so long
Why
Do I feel like I'm getting like a
Middle Ground between an apology and a
Sales pitch in an apology for the sales pitch
It's low energy it's
Here's the here's the thing
Be
Introduction of this is that like yelling about how he hates the demon pedophiles and what-have-you in
You can't
Beat them without me
And then this leads into this
Tracted sales pitch
About how the the Memorial Day sales still in effect
Easter sale for not having a different name for the sale
Which is essentially going to be the exact same
I have a spoiler to
Alex never has time to make a new special that happens all the time
He's constantly being like all know I haven't had time to make a new sale
It is just a new name
How many weeks away from Christmas in July special so what do we do with Apple pay.
It can't be like oh we're doing pride month special nope can't do that one
Interesting
Motorcycle made him do it
Turn around that would be
He doesn't entire segment
That is just a
And
Larry very much a bummer
Also
Different points
In the show he does have a different amounts of those coins
Still available very distrusting of how well these are moving available
10% there's like half left
I'll be at LACMA
The reality is
Let me just start going into it here
And
H1 properly I don't give a contact in my view
News articles yourself and decide what you think's going on
I feel like it's bizarre that Alex can spend an entire segment on ads and then be I got too much news to
Get into so much
News
Fine I guess
But
I find it fascinating that Alex thinks
What he's describing isn't what he just does all the time
I'm going to read some headlines I'm going to respond it for a second and I don't give a f*** you can go read it read it
Decide if I'm right or wrong
Alright then nothing happens nothing gets done
There's no progress nobody understands anything better
I don't know what that's like
Not his normal day at work I would like to hear him describe what he does
You know like what Alice
Today I've got too much news
So I can't do what I normally do
Which is dig into each store
I think he thinks that he does that really
Maybe
I can't I can't imagine
I mean he doesn't even realize it when he has a sack
Of news articles that would bring it out
And they're all the same story with different headlines from different
Like places
He doesn't do anything
It's all just improv based on
The headlines as suggestion
Yeah but the part that's written
Is the part where he says that he
He's almost going to do the difference
I need to make a new sales
Interesting
I don't have to deal with this
White supremacy
As rare as a leprechaun accent
Leprechaun
Alex believe I'm leprechaun
So
Somebody saw a leprechaun
Okay
So
He stated as fact
Somebody saw a leprechaun once so now everybody believes in leprechauns
Somebody saw a leprechaun what's going on
I mean
But it doesn't mean I can't just say the leprechaun
It's an interesting way for Alex
What you were saying is if his rare is a leprechaun realize leprechauns don't exist
Supremacy doesn't exist
Ariel
Or white supremacy is not I saw that series of documentaries
There was one where the leprechaun went to the hood
What is it
Hellboy
The Alex believe
Yeah and he doesn't believe in the most
Common ideology
What's up
Yeah it would be like if there were leprechauns all over the place
F****** kick you couldn't walk without kicking three or four leprechauns
Like a General Mills got canceled for having Lucky Charms
Baby like leprechauns would open windows and toss chamber pots filled with gold on top of your head
You wouldn't be able to walk without having an umbrella
Set of tiktok we'd have
Riddles
Do leprechauns leprechauns do not tell riddles
So Alex a lot of this is
Dominant sense
But they're also it a lot of
Beginning of the show on
Ends up getting into
Little bit hurt by
His example
Hundreds of Publications Reuters AP Newark
Thrown out of Bankruptcy Court by the justice department for being a criminal
Huge victory for the
Real companies
Devastating
For the truth
And everything's there still
Shooting
But
Is he is that
The table right now
Alex Jones
So we dropped me with Abby Lee bankruptcy total victory
This isn't at all accurate
We
To sum up Alex attempted to file bankruptcy for 3 his companies that don't actually exist
Except on paper
3chi real company
That was a little funny
Companies were among the name
Defendants in the case against Alex
Because it was really unclear how his businesses were
But none of these companies even do any business
Alex drive to bankruptcy
These companies because he knew that doing so would put a halt on the trial for damages and
Sandy Hook cases
Which is why you filed days before the trial was set to begin Intex
It was a desperate move on his part because he knew that was the only way he could buy time and ultimately because
The companies he was bankrupt
Didn't have any assets
It wouldn't make any difference to him if he did
Because that was the case and because of the new awareness of these companies that they aren't really real
The plaintiffs decided that they could drop these two companies from the lawsuit as a way to make it to Alex's bankrupting of them
That wouldn't affect
His ability to move forward
There wasn't anything that they could collect
From these companies on judgment anyway so it didn't matter
To drop those company
Cheapest from the suit it didn't
It's a 0
The trial itself got postponed still and that was obviously the goal
There's really no reason to continue with
The charade of the bankruptcy
The plane just dropped the you not existing companies from the suit and Alex withdrew the bankruptcy
Huiclaims so the case can now move forward and
None of it like it's basically like none of this would ever happen when it pulled
None of this matters in terms of what's coming for Ally
The soup being dropped against Infowars means nothing since he's still personally being sued and so is his actual company
Free Speech this
Is he now tries to move a bunch of money or assets around to these other companies that got dropped from the suit could be pretty apparent what he's doing
Likely result
In further legal issue
Yeah he's been sounds good if you know nothing about the case like his audience almost certainly does but if you've been following this
Is it all this is just complete bulshit
And
You know that he knows he's lying there is no way you could say these things
Sincerely real company
Right what is that
Say it say that in any way that isn't obviously you saying that these are fake
Right yeah it's it's a Patel
Companies
Sprite
Operation
But you had didn't specifically say to me
They were key real company I must insist
What is that I must insist
His company is very real
Do you have teeth fake companies as well because of the important fake company
And Alex Alex G a bunch about how like
I tried to open up my books to
To show them that I don't have the money they think I do more seriously if he bankrupted himself
Speed systems didn't do that and that's the reason the trial
Is coming up at the end of July and he's going
Facts about matter that these fees other
But he's depressed
By whom
The system
The last few months
Jones is a fraud
Jones has filed a criminal bankruptcy
Jones
One document
There supposed to be a deliberative body
They're supposed to get
About
They smoke their own dope
And drop
Angler challenges against our main companies
Hakeem a real company
My mouth is a lie like them
When everything I do is try
The lady doth protest too much
Wild
Is a little this is a little dumb
I know you are but what am I is a lot shorter way of saying that
It's really uncomfortable to
To hear a man
Use a lot more words
To say I'm Rubber and you're glue right
3 something
Compelling about this if you're a listener of the show Infowars LLC
Because the company is named Infowars everyone calls it in
The does a logos
Be
Notion that the Infowars itself was dropped from the suit
Would give
People that
Perception that like that is the main real company but it's not
No
Yeah it's
I see the value of the spin that he's using
For his audiences
But it's also a deliberate choice to name a shell company
A fake
Akeem fake company after the name of your actual business
I don't know
Anyway
At least people
They think that I'm a liar
Just a liar
I'm not a liar
No now I've done almost 700 episodes of a podcast
Thoroughly
Talking
Maybe too much
About the Myriad lies
But he tells like
There's some repetition in our show
Not that much
Not as much as well
It's not like
We talked about the same bulshit everyday
We really don't it's a new one
Fabulous lives
Literally
Losers
We're good
How many lies you spew
And there's millions and millions every day in millions more every week
Because they know they're getting their best shot
I'll tell you
These people just think up the biggest lies they can
Now they screw people
I don't want to live anymore
If Alex wants to know like what he's got wrong so we can do better I have
700 episodes of a podcast
I I mean
It is
It's one of those things where we've developed
Atone
A voice
You know over centuries and thousands of years
In order to communicate emotions
Since you know that
Wait wait without words
At no point in time in human history
Has a good person
Never been like
Up in your face screaming
We're good
And you've been like yeah that sounds right
It seems rare
I'm not saying it's not possible right I bet I bet it's some point it is having baby in the Wild West
Everybody was rough I'm going to throw this out at you in the Bible
Which he's supposedly likes you know that whole like
Don't say you're a good person
People know because you do things that make them think you're a good purse
Instead
Faster there weren't a radio show in the Bible right
It's true
What all would never have become Paul if he had a radio show
So Alex would never walk along a road
Nope this is the context that brings
Alex's
Apology
Essentially he is in the state where he's complaining about the media lying about him and his cases fry all this
Be honest
I am not a liar about
Striving
Right act
Into that leads him
His
I have egg on my face
Yeah I am ashamed before we get to
Alex just have to discuss his own weaknesses a little bit
Interested
You don't think I don't know
Karma is real
What
That's why we're so different from these people
I'm going to get pissed and Bash somebody
We're good
I got to keep that under control
Pressure
My mind
Sometimes
I couldn't control that make mistakes
Far fewer now
Maybe your perception is just different
Maybe you're really rich and surrounded by people who don't check you anymore and you are
Still making the
Exact same missile analyses
Of whether or not the things you're doing or good
What you can
Can do so there's two ways to go about this
Alright
You can
Do good things
And then people go wow
You're doing good things
Or
You can give people a lot of money to say you're doing good
Thanks better than options
Same thing
I think I think we got a
Titleist
Fear of Alex
Intensity violin
What's the f*** ever
Sometimes his brain tells him evil is good
I don't see somebody who is
Even when
Trying to make sense of the world in a way that is like
Like I'm I know I'm telling you a lie
Right now and my brain is telling me that that's actually good
So f****** confused
This is Atkins
Fuse
Scared boy
A billion billion dollars and a radio show
It's really really shows the danger of Dentistry
Cuz he came do you get a rich dentist dad
Enables your b******* you know what it is is here's what it is
Exactly it is the Twilight Zone episode where the kid has the second
Powerzen
Adults all around him are just
Enslaved to that child wins
You don't do anything wrong and you might turn into a lamp
Dealing with with Ali
If that kid grew up
And everybody was like well I guess we just live
Just now thinking about you
Be happening if it wasn't for 911
Alex's career would not exist
Really without that long stretch of
Building up a weird Community around 9-11 truther is
He would still exist but like
Mostly on shortwave or something I can that
You know it Manish right area like I don't think he has the capability to keep did write a book
The appeal of like a Behold a Pale Horse
He's no Bill Cooper on that level
Notary
And maybe
The terrorists wanted
Maybe all along is a long game
They did 9/11 in order to facilitate the creation of a
I want to hinge
Conspiracy theorist in Texas
In order to destabilize democracy I'm not joking when I say I really do think that
That's going to be going down is it like the most successful terror attack in history because if you are
Destroy the United States
It's hard to believe that everything we've done to
Since 9/11 has not
Gone that direction
Going through my head trying to think of
Two other
Terrorist attacks
Dear me there is like a recently by us and we lived through it so like
Leave me to be like well maybe not but I would I can think of
You know I don't mean successful in terms of like compact Philemon
Exactly like in real terms
That event
Stoked
Everything that led to where we are now the militarization of police
Ice Homeland Security
The f****** of rise of the far-right
The massive amount of islamophobia leading all the way back
Lgbtq homophobia all the way back
Like it goes all the way around and it all happened around that one specific thing I have a lot of faith in
Being unable to
To create bad situations that I have some
I have to hold on to believe that we would have got to a terrible place
Even without it
I think you could see a lot of the the soda ripplewave
From that
Play I was just trying to make a joke about the terrorist wanted to
To create Alex go
So Alex is really bent out of shape about how everyone's lying about his court case
Even though they're telling the truth about it and he's lying but they're lying so he
He's telling the truth
But in order to like really make it real that he tries
To do a good job stripes
That leaves us
Us to where we had our cliffhanger
I made a mistake
And
Always right
I'm ashamed of myself
Don't say that tube to Chillicothe look he's ashamed of yourself
That's how I feel
Good
I wish you felt that way more generally
Yeah they're supposed to like in this very
Niche
Yaser fake situation
As we look at this apology I think we're very clearly going
To see he is not apologizing for anything
Transitioning a narrative also you blaming everybody but himself
And he was driving and he just got bad information from all the Liars out
Subway
Some summer someone that's part of his
That's that's amazing to me I mean obviously has to be that he's not actually a shame
Country ideas
That he
Could be like ashamed
In terms of like what a relative of shame mean
Is you know like what
Is my shame relative to what that man must
Feel if he feel shaky feels no shame I think I think we need to talk about I feel ashamed
The missed
Right I think that's one of these
Really expressing is like
I wish on this one there was another
There's another way I could have covered this ripe really think I f***** up based on my own brand
Right that's basically what
The long and short of what we're going to get
Yeah I mean
He's going to say
The first episode
This is this is
Completely alien to Alex's coverage he's going to apologize for trying to tell the truth yes
That's exactly what he's going to do yeah and also that he was too tired to go to U-Haul
Aldi
You was going to go because too tired
Hours
Just want to believe in Texas and I want to believe employee Shall Believe in the system
And
I'm out that it was a lie
I just
Lazily went along with it
How to make clear before Alex tries to do any kind of apologizing
The first is that he did not just go along with the mainstream official narrative which happened to end up being inaccurate
How it was all over the place treating 4chan hoaxes as serious reporting and making up at the shooting wasn't shooting
Was really a hostage situation
Alex can easily be forgiven for the things that he missed reported based on faulty information that is coming
From official sources
Did he expect anyone to take his Corrections / Pieology seriously
He needs to actually understand what
He did that was wrong
He'll never do that because it really penetrates his entire facade if he lets the audience in on the front
Secret to be just making s*** up all the time
The second thing that's important to point out here is that Alex is literally admitting on-air that he reported information that he knew to be in
Accurate because he didn't want to criticize
Alex recognize that the lasting all of his imagined enemies are being very critical of the police
So he tried to be the opposite
That defending the police even when he knew he was saying was a lie
If you listen to this show and you take Alex at all seriously this should be a massive wake-up call
This is not
Alexandra got something wrong
It seems saying that he actively and knowingly lied on air because
It was better for the position he wanted
The take
Hit me feel like he's doing the correction and that somehow indicates that this is a unique situation but that's nonsense
He's already couching this as an apology for
Stating the mainstream media's narrative
We just pretend to take responsibility will ultimately Shifting the blame away from yourself
Onto them
Well I mean he literally just said
That it was
Lazily
I love we reported Lakeside report allies
I knew those were false
But then I went along with the official story
Lazily
That's a thing you can do
Oh no I was just too lazy to tell the truth
Today so I figured what I do
Is go with the official lie
Afara far more reasonable thing to say in a situation like this is
I mean like what
Most media Outlets would probably say and that is
You know we got reporting that came from sources
Cuz that's our official
We
Didn't have an Avenue to dig
Further into this right the very serious situation
It's our first time discovering this
The cops lie
We've never seen that before so it's really blowing our minds you know right
Here's the thing
Even though a lot of outlets Miss cover this in terms of like
Basic factual information
They also were reporting
This is what
Bespoke
People are telling us
Which
He's true
When they say in the basic level that is true when they say reported
Official sources have said
They're not
Sing the more making it up
They're not coming up with their own narrative and then saying
Heating beneficial bears as a way of taking stock of that
After the fact
The mistake that was made
Easy to dinner
Take an inventory of the
The things that we're done
Alex can't do that because in reality
Recognizing the things that he did
The same as other media Outlet
One thing that he didn't even bring up
He said it was the media lie
He said it's the media line he didn't bring up the
The cops themselves were like
He kind of touches on that a little bit later
But it is a murky gray area for him because everything needs to be the media's fault
It's got to be the media who is lying but they were
You know it's all stelter
Map somehow of course
Yep I knew it's yet he's going to he's going to tell you all about it right after
Commercial messages
Arkansas processor we're all having
Uvalde smells bad
Alright
Volkswagen
When we've ever gotten to the place we were always going to
Right
I mean it's an inevitability the sun rises you have to pay taxes and now she's going to say something will f****** false flag
So long
When I see this being treated as like an apology or correction I really really don't feel like that
Is what they say
It is a I could have gotten away with calling this a false flag and look at all of these Dynamics
That would have really fed into my ability to grandstand and I didn't
Because
Oh Sandy Hook
Maybe
Maybe it's cuz he's proud of Texas
Call Freeway Auto
School shooting where you are already being sued for lying about 1
You don't like
His time and it turns out this is the perfect
And only time to lie I have
This friend of mine
Who is the parent of Liberty
Veronica
If he tells me that it is not because of the lawsuit okay you literally and we'll hear that a little bit later
Colfer f***
The only reason you would say it's not because of a lawsuit
Because you know it's because of
And you know that everybody is going to Steve.
Obviously
So Alex comes back from break
And
I think he has some pretty dumb thought
Real quick
Through the glass Darkly rose-colored glasses
No amount of
When the tragic event
Unfold it in Uvalde Texas
Publications everywhere
Will Alshon say this is a false flag
I know I don't always stay
Publications everywhere
I can't imagine how narcissists
Sick you have to be to think
That the first thing on people's minds
Like who are in the media wouldn't
Might be one of the first things on my mind
Short but I am in a very nice paste
It is not the
Thing on my mind
The tragedy is
Obviously
Far more
Important then
Sorry about this
Eventually
I will for sure but that's something that you have to get
Like something in the garage that you have to go pick up and you have to
Mow the lawn your first thought
It's not oh I better go mow the lawn
After I get over the the horror of the the situation and try to get a handle on like what's going on
She'll be like
And it's not like I
My engine is more like
F*** Alex is going to be an a****** like whatever it is going to be awful to listen to
Opening up those are those episode we were not earned if he was going to say that it's a false
It's like we were concerned that he was going to blame somebody who is trans
Who had nothing to do with that night
We're worried about not whether or not you think it's a false f******
Can plaque
Is who are you going to hurt
Because of it yeah yeah
Yeah I bet it is again just like a manifestation of his narcissism
Quite frankly the way that he's behaving here already on this apology
The idea that people would
I have a reason to speculate whether or not he's going to call football
Absurd
So Alex thinks he was just covering what the mainstream media was putting out which again
It's absolutely not
Even his mind yes just because he made up
Some stuff along the way that's just him
Adding a little Zuzu as it's bleeding between the Lions
Maybe if you're really Jenner
We have the
Buffalo white supremacist shooter turns out was in constant communication
With a former federal agent
That obviously leads to
Obvious
Isn't the reason
Two weeks ago
On Tuesday after it happened
Hero border patrol agent killed him
12 minutes
I'm in well we're not sure and
Who's 45 minutes
75 minutes
But they stood outside the state police local police all of them and held the families back and they lied about it
I was misled
And the governor said he was misled
I said okay looks like
I should have gone down there
And I should have interview people like I used to do
It's interesting to think there's a chance that Alex really thinks that all he was doing was reporting
What the media covered
There's a small possibility that's really what
He feels but it's not true
The night of the shooting Alex's coverage wasn't based on any news it was based on a transfer obok 4chan hopes and his major consistency
That the shooter was on mind control psych meds
Somebody was making up and wasn't based on any reporting any still camping
Street now
He did get something's wrong because of Miss statements by official
No reason to expect
Intuit known
There what he was saying was an act
That has happened bit but
Larger picture a lot of
The stuff he's been wrong about art
Things that he was wrong about
Because I'm an honest man
Steak they've been things that he was wrong about
Because the s*** he was saying wasn't based on
Even as time went on and you needed to explain away into
Consistency the new information
Mainstream Media or the official narrative
When the initial timeline began
Fall Apart
He had Tim Enloe his former Blackwater
Security guard
Come on the show and give out anonymously sourced information that helped Alex reframe things
As a hostage
Situation
CNN or even Fox news reporting that
And then
Alex covering
That's not what the situation when he even said he had inside sources that were his
Security guard gathering information from sources which Alex took
And created his own story out of
That's independent reporting.
The mistakes Alex's made in this entire situation or his own fault largely speaker
There are a few mistakes that he made that are ultimately completely forgiven
Because there were two states that almost any reporter would make
And I think it would Alex wants to pretend it is is that
The same pass
That actual
Aboveboard
Reporters
Explicitly from their deposition
Since that they are nocturnal
Well
Depends on which deposition
Second point
Do good would ever come out of Alex going to Uvalde
He wouldn't have sniffed out any truth or done any reporting
Even in the prime of his career he wasn't capable of that and now when he goes anywhere
Misreporting the video of him yelling
To create the whatever story he wants
Winston's remember when he went down to the border and got in front of an immigrant charity vehicle
He captured literally nothing on camera but reported that he bravely put his body on the line to stop human trafficking
When the video is mostly him complaining about seat belt laws
That would be the best
Case scenario him going to Uvalde
Some kind of disrespectful and self-serving publicity
Also nothing about the Buffalo shooting the shooter engaging with a retired federal agent indicates that there was provocative
If anything it indicates that there's a retired federal agent who's a race
That's not signs of provocate
Touring Alex
But he's bringing that in
And he's establishing that
As a precedent
And he can use
To say that this was a false flag
Follows almost
An identical path to the Aurora shooting
Being used
In advance of Sandy Hook
Barry's AIDS
Similar relationship here where Alex
Can talk about
Things that have
To do with the Buffalo shooting and the provocateur
And the audience is meant to imply it in their head there
There's be direct
Connection between drawing
And as we know from
Listening back to a lot of the Sandy Hook.
There were periods of time where he was not comfortable
Necessarily
Directly talking about Sandy Hook because of the horror of it right
Could be fake who knows we know the Aurora one today
Feels
Very similar
Yeah it look it's a little bit like
Like a like a placemat you know like
These two pictures
Find find the things that are different about them
Like it is like he has two completely different pictures and he's like find the things that are the same about
It's a completely different picture of a completely different person
But if you see they've got an earring they both got earrings at the same
But what if
One of the picture
It doesn't have an earring
Drawing
A victory
What if you just imagine there's an earring
What if you yell at anybody tells you that there isn't any
Well then you will be rich
So I guess not because he's getting
That he did that
That may need 50. Say it a second time
Smollett and Bubba Wallace
But I still kind of just stayed out of it
Because
Situation
We won't be liked
Consciously
Gulf of this
Because it's who wants to be
I'm not impressed that he would invalidate you know
Accusations of racist
Acts
Not that it's not surprising that he would call
Smollett fake and
So he can
Dunno claim that as a victory when did
It's just his knee jerk
There's some real mixed signals going on in that clip
That's a man
Who has a background report
That nobody even knows where it came
Came from like 100 something page-long
Grieving
His actions were influenced by the fact
He's being sued for lying Button Elementary School shooting
Everything he says after that make me think of his actions were deeply influenced
By the factory being sued for lying about in elementary school shooting
He says that he stayed out of it and then something like this happens
Begin his actions will be
Implies that there's something that was
I'm not cover this situation the way he wanted to and I don't believe anything to do with grieving parents
Conscious it was unconscious
He's shown nothing but disrespect for grieving families
Alex needs his audience to think that he's not been weakened by the Sandy Hook cases so he'll ultimately be as defense
He needs to be about that issue on air
He won't ever directly say that he didn't want to get sued again so he wasn't going to call the shooting fake
Because to do so would to tell Abby to tell the audience
He's not offense
Is reporting based on personal
Now you might be thinking that he already said that he didn't cover this correctly because he had faith in the
The police in Texas
Admitting the same thing
But here's the difference
And that case the reason he covered it wrong is
Because he had a faith
If things that the audience
They love the cops and they think
Texas should be its own country
Conversely in the case of Alex changing his coverage
Because of fear of lawsuits
That's Alex being week
And if you accept that you have to accept
He might not cover all sorts of issues
Might cover other stories knowingly in accurately because of some fear that he has about consequences that the system could
How can I watch
Possibly be a person is willing to die fighting the globalist
If he's willing to fundamentally change his coverage
Out of fear of losing some money
I get it it's complete
Completely
Knocks.out the underpinnings of his own fake personality
Cannot
Admit that
He will change his behavior for anything
Yeah I mean hatab doesn't matter how bad it is it doesn't matter
What it is
He can't say that I have learned a lesson
Because he's presented himself to his audience as
Someone who can't learn lessons at all because they already know every
He can't learn lessons
Because he wasn't wrong
Exactly
Yeah and the end
For him to then have to be wrong
And Afraid
I'm not going to follow that dude
No
So I think that obviously
The way he covered the story out of a fear of getting
Wingsuit again
I hadn't
Play obvious
How to
Play the things have gone with the
Changing statements timeline shifting and what-have-you
Brightness sweet spot
You and I kind of has to figure out a way to
I be like yeah
I really should have
LOL I dropped the police this is such a weird situation for him
I do think the way that you sounded up was pretty good that like
I tried to tell the truth I know it is that really is it is him being like
Man
This was the time
For me to say it's a false flag
Because legally they couldn't do s***
The cops are lying so if you want to get on me you got to sue them acid
You know like there's many ways of
Something being fake that aren't legally actionable
Totally could have done that totally
Because of the circumstances that are surround
Is The Gunshot this is that because he
He didn't call it a false flag
More people are going to stop
Baby yeah maybe
I think that what a coward
So lucky
If you drop the ball here
We drop the ball we gave the police the benefit of the doubt because it's Texas
The
Head
Police chief other school district
Is in hiding
To the city council
He won't talk to the Press
He won't talk to State Police for Texas Rangers
He won't talk to the feds
Who knows what app
As it turns out there were police in there for an hour
It turns out they weren't outside
None of that was true
So what the normal media did
Was give the police the band
That's not what Alex
Also I have no idea what he saying that there were no police at the school
It's not accurate at all creating a nude
I've apologized for not calling in a false flag now I'm free to make up whatever bulshit I want
Almost spitefully
I'm looking at the comment section on this video cuz I was released this section as a standalone thing on
Alex Jones admits he was wrong about Uvalde shooting
Anti going through yet somebody
I heard there are no birth records for those kids in Uvalde is that true
There we go
A lot of shoutouts
Steve pieczenik
Wow
I guess Las Vegas is didn't happen I guess we're going to bring that back
Oh my God is Steve pieczenik going to come back and talk about this
Maybe
Wow
Wow door seems open wide open now based on the comment section
Alicia and I think you can even get a little bit of a temperature
Nobody died that's another comment
Great
Grab
Yeah these are all people who would like finally he's going to claim with the false flag now
Excitement I'm getting smarter than
Right I hope that leads to some
Non retention
Did you would hope
So lucky what he's now
Shifting things and now Alex
Is blaming
These police
Good
70 + minutes
The police stand around
Sitting on their hands
Songs in the ranch
Of the school district
Shed so it turns out wasn't in radio communication
Dereliction of Duty
That is
Serious
Ham
In
Languages
We don't cheat the police
Tell me what
This is shameful
And this is disgusting
Strikes me that this is ultimately completely thin and false and I think they're two contributing factors
For that one out exaggerate everything because he desperately wants to make his show more interest
Time to Alex feel the need to exaggerate this situation so it makes his audience more able to criticize the police
By using hyperbole Alex is able to distinguish his complaints about the situation from the complaints his audience might hear from Below
For the main
Stream media or people who are supposed to be globalist
Cuz when they criticize the police response Alex wants to have something distinctive
From them
In order to to provide that above all
I just
Despite
The fact that right now
We can all across ideological lines
Agreed
The cops
I think we can all agree that there is
Definitely very very strong indications of that there should be a thorough investigation of
What happened
But Alex still can't agree with
It has to be something
It needs to be more
Extreme it needs to be above that and it needs to be a narrative of his own
For instance Alex's with Commander wasn't even there
Which isn't true
Pete Arredondo was on the scene and he was one of the first inside the school
He didn't have his radio with him but part of his explanation for that was that he didn't think that he was the commander on scene
And it's not other agency was taking the lead
And you were supposed to be there acting as a first responder
Right now whether or not you believe that or not or think that's
Appropriate or not
That is an explanation that he is given for why you didn't have a radio and then Alex's just
Completely wrong about him not BFF
Yeah he's wrong about that
They're very valid and productive arguments to make against the police response
In theory lead to discussions about how to improve things
But Alex's critiques are mostly surrounding fake issues
If you're a listener they shown you here indignation about how the police chief wasn't even there
You're going to be poorly prepared to have a conversation about this
Whatever
You're going to try to make about the police response
Seriously
If he wasn't even there was part of the If part of your list of grievances right
People is like oh you don't you don't know you're talkin I mean that's that's
Have a good one though
Put in there early
Because that'll
Be real good when you climb with the false flag
Like the guy who was telling people to stand down was
Even there and said he was there obviously that's a false flag
Sure
I mean it'll just be
And I honestly want to say that I think the Thursday
Very decent chance
That Alex doesn't pursue this line
Too much further
Like I don't know if there's much of a market for him now in a
Conspiracy theory
But there is some
And establishing a new narrative surrounding this
So if something else happens down the road
He can be on the Alex Jones side of this
Supposed to be weird side but he's been on here
Selectman
There might be a chance
This is shameful
And this is disgusting
Who the hell knows what happened
Really suspicious
Really suspicious of the whole thing in the timing and the midterms and all of its commitment with the feds
White supremacist
Yes you have to have this storyline about the Buffalo shooting
Fades and is being covered up right timing
The midterm midterms
Yeah it says you're getting your getting all these pieces of the standard Infowars false flag
Conspiracy
Starting to
To gravitate and circle around
The story
I mean
Honestly it's just sad
Cuz
We all knew we were going to get here
I know
Do you mean you remember like ham
Viewer
You're confused
For a second about Lake
He wants to call this a false what
Absolutely you could feel it in his words
Could feel his shoulder start to shake when it like
He tried to get it
There's a very similar dynamic
21 Lake
Before Stefan molyneux
Said that he was a white nationalist
Like everybody like
Please get to the point where you say it is as if they are white nationalists already
Just come out with it
This is a
Maybe this is a false flag going on
The timing the midterm don't make the Buffalo shooting the feds cover-up
It's all there man you've come up with
Bulshit
Connected those bullshits
In order to
Create the appearance of a conspiracy
But the tax
But he's putting into this board
REO
And the string is
It's all done said yeah this is going to go down as one of the more surreal couple weeks of Infowars cover
And their entire his
Probably because they were trying to tell the truth
I mean I think
I agree with you but it's too generous to say tracks Healthcare
They were trying to do
A better
Based on what we were described as
Better
Silent Alex is ashamed of himself
But that's not all
There's also
Estate
Nae
A country that is a shame.
Luxembourg
Concrete
All we know it could be entailed
What
Just like the witmer
Yeah
So we're back to
Dinner before Pizza Gates I got to I got to figure out what's going on with this stuff
Sandy Hook
Same thing
Can I get to the bottom of this
Nope but
You can also see that is part of now the constellation
Do things
But he's bringing in
Talkin about the Uvalde shooting and he's bringing in these other things that are safe for him to say
Parfait
In order for him to
Go to transpose the fakeness ought to the Uvalde shooting
Until it's more safe for him to actually
Fully say that
Have to say this is fake
I've established
A career
I'm saying things are fake so if I just
Reply
You got
It's very transparent
And it's Alex
Get pretty mad
The police followed the criminal orders of that
Police chief
I need to be a nag house right now
Now
14 minutes down proper 70
Wow
That strong words strong words from a man with a
Vocabulary
Again
Yeah
I don't know I feel like
This is meant to be an apology correction
Sure and what it ends up really being is
I knew I was right about this and I did it's sad because of something but it's not the
Lawsuit
And you know who's really to blame the media and the police
They did me dirty
I'm always right
Phil you can't apologize
And be Vindicated
That is not how that go
It does on Infowars baby is true
You're right
I am apologizing because I was to write all the time
I apologize for being self-aggrandizing right now but I won't
Very
Prairie
The fascinating about this that is
Yo
On a certain level
When Alex makes things up
It's full of s***
Irresponsible and dangerous
I already tries to do what normal reporters might do
He can't
Eddie still f*****
Yep
How we end up here
It's it's like
It's like somebody was taking a baby step towards learning a lesson
Okay
I got it
Sandy Hook
Is going to f*** my brain out
So guess what I'm going to do
I'm going to button down
I'm going to really try on this one
And I know your your face says that no
But I will look
Is that the lesson isn't or it shouldn't be
Is going to ruin me
It should be
What I did was wrong
He learned the wrong listed played it and then
Learned another wrong lesson which was
I should have just been an ass
I should have just been a slightly different kind of a****** cuz I have
Trade my friend and now I have to explain why I didn't do the thing that everybody knew I was going to do eventually course
Yeah
That sucks
Yep this is what happens when conspiracy theorists are brought low
Yeah
Yeah I mean
Close to handling this s*** Shakespeare was a moron
If you fix that meant anything it went out
Accident in the f****** web very very sad
Shameful
So I think
You know I am not
I'm not sure it was as revelatory as some other things that I got mad at Florida
That's right I got mad at Florida.
I'm pissed off at Florida fire Florida
Oh hell you back to Spain also the rest of the show is Alex interviewing
The guy who's attacks weirdo
Whatever
Broker content
I don't know if this is as educational
Necessarily it some other things that we
Focused and moron but I do think that there is
Freddy
Play a narc
Since the
The shooting
And it did go diff
Currently been a lot of times analysis career based on
And you see that all roads lead to Rome
In Rome is calling a stock
Kind of depressing
You know I mean
This wasn't
So much like the information heavy as it was almost a character
Their study
Is a slice of life
Kind of what happens
Whenever people stop
You know
Acting fake
Start getting real who's real world Austin I'm pretty sure that's what that was a season either
Somebody cool
Another episode
In the post Alex
Trapology world
Tell them we were outside
We are at Dollar General
Leo and bcx Clark I hope you all have a dream
And now here comes
Lukas X robe
Alexandra Thurston color with huge fan I love your work