Jordan swetik
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Around worship at the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about to Alex Garden
Alex Jones
Is that how it sounds
So what's up
What what how did we free damn
Jordan Jordan what's up
What's bright spot today buddy
Brightspot it's brutal this is the least most anti-climactic Brightspot
So I decided to give
Fire Emblem
Three houses attract off
Tactical type game like that style of the game is different than any
Eye of the
The things I've messed around with in the past
I took like it's like a moth to the flame
It's a very fun super structured in the characters in the story
Is a lot of fun as well and I meant it
It's great
I heard there's a Dynasty Warriors version of it coming out later this month I'm so excited about that
Zombie playing at the new came over to record heading minute
10 minutes to have this game forever because
Scratch that itch
Final Fantasy Tactics
Was
And I was I was telling you that it's been going on for 20 years
And that's not a joke a few months ago whenever I talked about it on the shelves like s***
Play that for a while when you talked about it on the show I didn't even put two and two together
My response that was I've never played a game like I don't even know how to imagine
And now you do I do a lot of fun and now you're going to see yourself here in 25 years being like
Fire Emblem is like 100% legal CD image that I found
Final Fantasy Tactics
This is
So much
That it's so good
It's so good
It's a quite a well-done
My experience
I am going to get the right Tea Party
I was going to get a perfect
Score on one of the Tea Party
One of the things that you have to do or candidate
And you have three speech bubbles and you have to choose topics for conversation that you think they
Might enjoy bad personality
A real person
But yeah it's a lot of fun times
It's been a long time. I think we've had same bright spots but at different times you don't like when I said Taskmaster was privately
Later on you know that kind of thing but this
This is a simultaneous
Unequivocal Breitbart
Yep
Jordan today we have to do it Wednesday so we're off the beaten path a little bit
I feel like the Uvalde
Shooting coverage kind of came full circle
And we got to where we inevitably knew we were going yeah
And the January 6th
Commission coverage
Hayes hit
A dead end
Inasmuch as Alex is still out of Studio
He's had to fill in Harrison filled in the other day
Anderson was like as not yet unfortunately I don't know anybody
How do you do a dare suggest that we celebrated event
Yeah good got to run cover for you
And so we're left a bitten alerts of of of
What to do over I dipped in the past a little bit I need a little more time
To get the next class episode
Together so that that'll be forthcoming
Jim Bakker sucks
Nothing really new in Project Camelot world and we just went back there not too long ago
So I have to find something to do and something popped up and we'll get into it here in a moment
What's a hello just knew once
Actually this is interesting today we have
For technocrat
Jesus Christ yeah so we
Play all four play the drop
Coincidence or just go through in the order that things come in and hate here we are
So
First
Pej Holdings
Thank you so much you are now it's
I'm getting married to a Yeti by driving my van
Thank you so much for now it's Steven Universe
The archivist P Andrew not Torres
You are now at
I have
Risen above
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe today
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Real walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologize to the
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Be better tomorrow he's not
Is never better
You don't even gone he's not better yeah that's true
Bob thank you all so Jordan
I don't I don't want to I don't know how to tell you this
But this is going to be a little bit of a off-the-beaten-path
The best
Thing ever it might not be it it's not as fun as
You know space and covid-19 pyres of Bellevue
Get into it
Describe four
Visual Harvey
What
What did the toad do to you
Oh my God is this recent Wars
No
What all no blame to me in detail
Hoodoo
What did the total do you have any conception of what
Possibly be about the first X-Men movie there is a mutant
Call Jonah.
Okay
Well I mean there's there's the toad mr. Toad's Wild Ride
Is that what you talk about the mr. toad
Drove me drunk into a tree
A boy
I'm all out I'm all out I've got nothing but what the sprocket at this this is about being a high
Play on toad Venom
Okay
Alright
Now we're having a good time we're going to be looking at
Alex talking to Mike Tyson
God you know after the last three episodes ended with such a
Narrative closure
Almost you know like it's almost like a novel
You know you see this
Struggle
You see the hero's journey
Call Campbell
Hero's journey villains dirty
I bet
Ever to have it just kind of energy now you're in that same Lurch when you finish a good book
You know and you just kind of like
I don't know what
Do pick up like a magazine
It's really weird Jordan Alex was a guest on Mike Tyson's podcast
Just called
No
Few months back I believe back in April was when
Mysteriously the episode has not appeared to have been released interesting
You can go to the podcast website there's a long list of episodes with gas like Alex's mortal enemy Piers Morgan
Your shield and
Baddest bytch Trina
Astro
Trick Daddy
I watched a little bit of her interview and it comes out to
The Trick Daddy
Gave her the nickname the baddest
He also
Last time I saw
Trick Daddy
Was
The people
Pointed out that the guy
Who's making
The documentary about the proud boys
Kizi
Very famous rap video director
Also no s*** yeah and so in the take it to the house video he makes a cameo
Daddy is talking about how he wants one of his video that's crazy
That's amazing so Trick Daddy getting these in the zeitgeist
People
That's the problem everytime I see
There's plenty of people in the world I find out that there's just that popping up everywhere
Love kids
Stevenson bike more controversial guest
Tyson has had on like anti-vax do Robert Kennedy Jr
He was on fairly recently
A self-appointed ambassador to North Korea Dennis Rodman
Well I mean
You know somebody
Got2go the worm
So on June 1st
Paul Joseph Watson Road in article for his blog about how the powers-that-be in big
I could put pressure on Mike Tyson and got him to not release the episode
Sounds about right as we all know Mike Tyson is notoriously a pushover and how many caves even the slightest them
Model pressure described him as a fighter
We're in the middle of his
Very last
You know
Comeback story you know Tyson's got one more fight in them
He's one day away from retirement and his best friend comes out to like you know manager him in the corner
I mean this movie ends with him dying obviously but that's it mean podcast form
Actually talk a whole lot about him dying
Good morning
He is not hitting have any feelings on a helmet on the question
It's a very bizarre
So I've seen a lot of these podcast we're bigger celebrities have Alex on
Mike Rogan or Logan Paul
A complete shitshow
Invariably gets
Wheatley wasted pretends he has some really deep insights to offer never says anything of substance
Heaven sometimes takes his shirt off
It's been reported by Alex that he and Tyson took mushrooms and smoke weed
Before and during the podcast so I've concocted a little theory of my own about why this episode has
Them come out
I really think it's probably really bad
Not like dangerous an offensive bad but like embarrassing and low-quality type of bad
Leaving all the other qualities of the man aside Mike Tyson
Can handle his drugs
He's pretty much high as hell all the time now and I would not be surprised if the way alok
What's active between is being
Bucked up
To his very transparent and over-the-top strfkr E
Made it feel like maybe they didn't want to put this out episode out to the public
Probably might be
I guess man
I don't know I would do mushrooms with Mike Tyson and put it out no matter what anybody said I would not
Not do either of those things I would do mushrooms with Mike Tyson and I wouldn't put it out
Are those things either
I'm not going to pretend that I watch the full episode of Tyson's podcast but I skipped through a few of them and there
Really different
I've been the short clips that Alex's released
Of his time with Mike
One thing is that the guests are generally big stars themselves
Express admiration for Tyson in his career
They are tripping all over themselves
What's around him
I don't want to so over-the-top and it comes off as being very insecure and out of place
I think
If you even just watch these short clips of it they come out come out they're so different
Sand Lake
Mike Tyson talking to Piers Morgan
Has Piers Morgan is ostensibly
Considering himself to be Mike Tyson's equal in this conversation conversation about there
Careers share and like Mike Tyson's asking him questions about journalism right often like
Yeah it's
I am in an opportunity
44 like an actual conversation
To happen
I'll be at between
Piers Morgan in Mike Tyson
Bizarre collection I mean just
Fine yeah yeah
The other thing is that a number of these guests don't try to do drugs or drug with Mike
Princeton Piers Morgan wasn't taking shrooms
Remember thing we've heard about Alex's interview he tried to keep up to like show he was cool
Which is really stupid wow
That's what high school kids do when they're older siblings friends and it
To go wrong I mean that's though he's a freshman in college what are you doing
You wouldn't you do it yourself killed
Mike Tyson
Did the toad has two weeks got so much head trauma there's so much s*** going on yeah
I don't know exactly why Tyson doesn't put out this episode of the podcast
Maybe it'll come out sometime down the line and like this whole pretending Alex is being censored thing is just a really useful marketing scratch
Entirely possible
Like one way to build up anticipation for the release of something
To tell people they can't see that thing
Exploit our desire to have things were denied access
Release the Snyder cut of this podcast
I think that's a possibility and it's more
Likely Vitale
F***** up and embarrassed
Whatever the case earlier this month Alex released a half hour video on video which is titled exclusive
The censored Mike Tyson Alex Jones podcast info
Alex recorded the interview himself and he was releasing his side of it
But that's not what this video is
It's because almost everything it in fours involves
Clickbait
This video was an interview that Alex shot with Tyson after they did Tyson podcast
Behind-the-scenes stuff
From Tyson's podcast actually kind of implies that Alex does have more video
Then just
This little snippet
I pay some of my hunches about Alex's Behavior being embarrassing in a mess based on these
Space on the eclipse of him
Very shortly and embarrassing Mass
I want to take a little break E from the horrors of the present-day might because Alex seems to come back to work
We're going to check in
And see how this interview with Iron Mike Tyson
Let's do it
This is done it's done
Right after
It's not like
They just
And then like five minutes later
I think it's pretty briefly afterwards no s***
Yeah okay but actually kind of
Makes me think that
If they did shrooms it wasn't
March
Like I know that rooms are going to make you
Freak out necessarily or
But
I don't really see
That much
Mike f***** up at Miss going on for Malik
Gotcha like I think he's holding it together fairly well
Babies on the Comedown
Could be
Yeah I think
He's really f***** up on
The clipse
They have of
Mike show
Which leads me to believe yeah maybe there was a longer gapless
Remember
Or Alex's faking all that s*** when he's acting all f***** up
Cuz he thinks it makes him more interesting one of the two he was smoking oregano kind of situation
Or it could be he wouldn't have shot
Long f****** shower
Yeah yeah
I know that sometimes cocaine can leveling out
One way or the other
So here's where we begin begin is Alex doing a little bit of an introduction
He's sitting there looking at the camera at Infowars Studios
And here's what he's got are at
A month-and-a-half ago
Mike Tyson
Then I saw his evolution
Variant
Fob remote
I've learned a lot
California
Podcast
It was incredible
He said Madison
The best interviews ever I got
Past
Last week
On FaceTime
He said Hayward
Going to call
Troy's Greg ice
We have a contract
Put pressure on them
Absolutely
Sure
Censorship
There's a conspiracy
As always
Sure some some big
YouTube exact was like
What's that
On Mike Tyson
Where will allow Robert Kennedy Jr. Come on in.
If if any of that is to be believed it's just addictive how toxic out
Amenable to advertisers that be king of anti-vaccination
More people more late
People know who Alex
Alex Jones
So I don't
What are the things that I think I would really like to
The Press Alex
Specifically
What has Mike
Tyson talk
Thought you would like to know the
Give me specific
Yeah I did something about perseverance I was willing to let that one slide it hit my ears uncomfort
I was like you know what you probably could learn something from Mike Tyson I feel like maybe I'm being a little bit discount
Maybe I'm curious what they are
That is a good question
Life lessons
Yeah I don't I think Alex is all the s***
Actually I bet Mike Tyson was likely
Check your bag
Don't take a carry-on they think you you think it's going to be smart
So here is the Alex
Setting this up
Really
Stand up again
Really really die
Call America
Look it's one thing of Alex Jones
The interview
Powerful
Loving it
Really incredible
And we also took
Is Wile
Cure
With excerpts
You only find it right here
Video
So here it is
I think
Actually from the context that will get of a clip
From Tyson's interview
I think
That maybe they took like a small amount of mushrooms
Before the show
And then Mike Tyson has a brand of edibles
That he refers to as like shroomies
Buckeye
Yeah might have thought
That was approved
Then he took on air when it was actually just a
I really don't think you're allowed to
Take shrooms on air
I don't know what the laws are now
That is a good point
So I don't have a whole lot to go off of but I would guess from all the available contact that this was not a powerful interview
I will see you in the interview that Alex release
Between Heaven Mike
The two of them approximately 0 chemistry and most of the top
Looks like Alvarado
Also I don't think it's actually censorship at all
If what Alex is saying is accurate then what happened is that at
Company decided that releasing this episode would have a negative impact on Advertising
So they didn't put it out
I don't think that's necessarily a good thing but it
It's not what Alex wants to make it out
Mike and his team decided that the easiest way to make this thing work was to sell Mike celebrity to a bigger company
Who would then on the podcast and Michael
This team would be paid by that company
The money becomes a news from advertise
Which is handled entirely by the company that owns
Podcast
And if they understand that having a friendly interview with Alex where the host does hallucinogens with him
While the Sandy Hook trial was set to be taking place
Cuz they recorded
You might end up getting some pushback
From your advertisement
And these companies that own podcast
Don't just sell ads
Podcast by podcast
They have a ton of shows
It sponsors by bulk
Add time on
Yeah this is one of the reasons that Spotify was so Keen to get Rogan on an exclusive deal and pay him so much
Having him there exclusively on their platform was theoretically going to provide
Great boost
Do what they could charge
If Ison has Alex on and they do drugs and pal around talking
While simultaneously The Grieving parents of murdered children are facing Alex
You can easily see how some companies would not want their ads to be on that show
Mike's podcast is owned by a company called multimedia and without being rude to the other shows on that Network
I don't think that advertisers are banging down the door specifically to buy there at
It's very reasonable to assume the Tyson is a large part of their ability to sell add package
Just for this podcast Network
So someone pulled out of his show they
Probably wouldn't stick around for the
The other shows on the network
People decide what their priorities are in life and their careers and then their choices reflect that
In this case Tyson's team sacrificed creative control and ownership with their own podcast in order to have someone else bigger
How to make money off their show
You can call that censorship if you want but it's really just the downside of the arrangement
Tyson is chosen because it's preferable for him
Yeah
Do you know remember when podcasts were a new exciting medium and then they were like what if we turned it into the old one
It's one of the reasons why we have very Big Ben
Consistent very much to never even liked open emails or Flopper enough ads
Like no there's not
It's not something we're interested in because
That does
Open the door
Like if you're on a network
But all that works
Run different
Obviously have
More of this and some have less.
Open up the possibility that they can say like we own your content
Yep because they generally do
That's part of why they buy you
Yeah do you make a bit of money on these but also ultimately at the end of the day if they say no then
You can't just
Put something out yourself
Yeah your phone your show it's going to be funny whenever like everything collapses and all of these
Cast networks can't afford all of their fun Studios and all that stuff
And we're going
Going to be like looking at people from
The same exact place
Smell like beef
Workout for us
And we'll never reach the heights of
Some of these things
We'll also
You know I made it the bottom falls out of podcasting and ever has to record in their home that's what we've been doing all along.
So we are prepared pretty much never does the prediction I have you'll never see Alex popping up
Up on the show that has to worry about Advertiser
Except for shows that rely on couch courting negative attention
In order to
To stay relevant
Those types of shows will have Alex on because their advertising model is
They have outraged bait
Gets them attention
And feed some sort of people
Talking negatively and then people fight
And that gives them more attention and higher rating
Alex is perfect as a guest for something like that
But other places that have different advertising bottle
Central ion
People not being like
Pissed off at them right
I generally don't never ever see him
It's hard to
It's hard to justify that
It is because
If you're one of the if you want to that like a the Red Scare or whatever one of those podcast
You know it's like
F*** it
The people who advertise with us
Are already playing with fire
Like they're already choosing to be on the edge of Decorah
So I don't know if over that it's not that big but don't know if folks like
Sam Tripoli you know that
Contempt
But Alex has been on
I don't know if he has ads I would assume he does probably
You're already on that edge
You know if your
If you're shows
Yeah Target
It doesn't want Alex on their f****** word you know like yeah okay I get it
Meundies
Has a problem with Alex
So anyway the interview start
Let's hear and you'll notice a sound effect
This was not added in po
The Relic
Music
Listen music
What you doing Mom
The family show
Thank you very much sir
What year show
Are you hiding something
Bad news
I'm good
Jessica
See it
I think we all want to believe that were good judges of character but that can't be true for everyone know
I don't know Mike
Personally so it's hard to say but
You did work with Don King
Alex's
It's cool so my money is on his radar not being brave
Get a good judge of character they imagine that North Korea is pretty stoked
About that
Also two mics
If you want a better sense of what sort of trash you puts out
Please try to watch his show a little bit
You can lie to you and give you the impression that he's a good guy
I'm at the game
It is it is funny is he hiding something
No
He's broadcasting getting public
Look for everyone to see he's hiding something from you in person because
Like
That's the image
Of the person that you wants to be
Eddie knows that most of these folks like to listen to Infowars
I bet this guy's a good guy now
Absolutely not he's just not going to go to info and most people get so goddamn bored listening to his show
Especially if you have things to do
If I have anything else to do
I would never be able to make it through an episode of his show
Also you notice of Michael lights up a joint immediately and you get the sense that Alex's
Really wanting him to pass it
Yeah
Yeah I'll tell you what lesson I didn't learn from Mike Tyson
Alright
Bogarting the joint
Puff puff pass
Just a little ironic
I thought I was coming
What
Here we are Mike
Seems like you're in your Prime right now
Seems like he's a good shape I also like it's just funny for him to have a coughing fit the joint
You're in the best shape of your life by
There's just a
The position that it's under a minute is great but listen to you now
Look at the lines on you you pulled on that joint for an hour man that's amazing
Yeah
I mean the the joint
Obviously a man
Rihanna whatever possible mushrooms they've taken
Pretty heady conversation
Spring deep stuff
What about Mike Tyson his energy
So positive
He's so happy with any Shea amazing things always true
What podcast
A
Before I forgot to it are there aliens you already bringing up we are the aliens
Yeah I think so I think so I think
Are you phylis I think I teaches a Time
And the more we dig the deeper would become and then the Movie 5
You know the movie Deep
The Moby Dick movie
We find out about
Define. Maybe
Maybe like
Starting up
Turkey
My dog music other than Africa
We have the city
I'm sorry what what just happened
But how does that debate with Africa being the Civil War
Yesterday
Histories are lies that we agreed
True
Wow
The deeper we dig the more we learn about ourselves literally about archaeology
Yes we found a city in Turkey
He's literally saying
That if you dig deep into the Earth you're going to find old right I think it's not metaphorical
But also like definitely predates 7000
Even so
My custom information wrong here
So this is about a city that was discovered underground beneath derinkuyu in Turkey
Which was actually was rediscovered in the night
60 check
The complex of underground tunnels under the capadocia region
Present-day turkey
Which tries to be part of like a refugee
Plan where people could hide out from
Invading Army
These totals in cities are not 9 thousand years old
They're actually closer to 2,000
A old
In 2020 another complex
Who found under the city of Midian.
And it's believed that this was a place were persecuted Christians
We're able to hide in the 2nd and 3rd centuries
This is about as good as this interview is going to get
That's complete nonsense being thrown around the tips into the Supernatural and paranormal
Because Alex is so desperate for celebrities to like if he just agrees to anything tight
I agree medialized
Does history lie
I don't know if there's ever been a series of
Words that is made me just go like
Oh goodbye
Actually an interesting thought
Inasmuch as like history absolutely does lie at every historian knows that
The study of history
Does ink
Include the understanding of bias
Ants in in at least as it relates to
To like sources
But you can have
That's one of the reasons why it's a fairly complicated field of study
And you want to have
Contacts
You'll have multiple angles on a vent
Some things like that
Yeah I bet I mean inasmuch as
Alex's is discussing his
Actually
There's some truth
He just wants to say that the things that you're taught are true in order to denigrate and degrade the idea of an objective
Reality
That's why I don't want to listen to
He himself has an agenda of defeat
Credibly read anything about history and be like
I bet that guy nailed it 100%
Just not true I think every everybody who's serious about
Starting history with
Give you a qualified version of history is full of lies or whatever
In the present let alone
Stuff that happened several thousand years ago
Almost feels like several thousand years ago might be easier easier right at least it can't happen anymore it's already
Exactly
So we can do some philosophical talk here this is heavy
Show in
Nnn
Can your years on Earth what do you think the ultimate secret is
Start
I want to see notes while you were speaking
Earlier but
That being born is dying
Cuz once you die once your boy in the process begin
We Can't Stop from dying and it's so beautiful cuz if that's
The Kongos on in the process
The Bangles
So many Beautiful Moments
Lyndon Diner becomes
Like you're sit with Mike Tyson and sharing his tobacco with
That is a man
That was Alex's way of trying to give it to him
You smoke it
In front of me had obviously I can't have this conversation unless I'm getting higher.
Ridiculous is awful
I don't understand this is an annoying conversation at a house party
Alex Jones
Why am I why would I leave parties
I went to college
Actually I've been sort of Alex's position here which is somebody saying this kind of stuff
Alright whatever but they have the weed
I agree with you put up with
Bizarre esoteric brightness
Like what like when your weed dealer would would come over
Images
And then be like are you going to pass it and you're like no I just bought this from you
Yeah but come on man so Alex
I think Mike wants to ground this conversation and some kind of like reality
Personal Alex wants to think global
Okay
Married
I am
Cumming Georgia family
You worry about your kids
What's your view
What's currently happening with
Directions to choices
YouTube have no chemistry
I I just can't imagine like f******
Edward Murrow
Getting f******
Blasted
Hi what's up with Equifax
Ginsberg right before they did it interview and then he's like Alright
What's your feelings on
Vietnam
Also noted geopolitical scholar Mike Tyson do you think about what's going
My god with Russia
I wasn't comparing him to Ginsberg as much as just who it would be super productive to ask the question to
Probably not Mike Tyson
Guy who was known
Fighting
Prison for rape
And then now is kind of
A drug weirdo TV series
That's true yeah
So he's had a big career
Yep
I wonder what
Stoned out of his mind Mike Tyson
Some things about Russia
The conversation
Mike brings up is actually interesting one what are your feelings about like the world that we live in
Family
Mike would offer something else that get his feelings on the matter but its family
That's kind of a human conversation
List of a given taken more of just a f******
I will give you this answer
I want to know what you think about poop
TubeMate
Why wouldn't she
Yeah so yeah
We are thinking like oh we got to get to business
Yes
Well might be a matter of like Emily having a
Very short time
But Michael put up with this I have other things I need to do
Like record voice over for the cartoon
Alex actually does want to know about
Mike has a weird take all right
How does Mike Tyson
Almost in the
Korean War
60 years at Ocala has ended
Go there maybe broker preschool
Zelensky in
Imma look at
Like this
If compellent steelhawk any grab
It's not opinion this one that says
Robin grab the bird and I can stop them from killing that
I stopped him from killing a
Should baby died
So who am I
, right
I told my kids who used the wrong but how you
Something's going to die
I think that's a real knowledge of thinking multi-step
That is the real nice
On one level
No cuz that's what we born to do this is all born to have everything that happened right now
Is ordained by God
And then we do with it
85mm people
Every DLC
Perfect yes.
I'm guessing stuff
Wow
So if I understand correctly
If we don't
Allow
Putin
To reconstitute the ins
Tire USSR
Then
Hit hit
His kids will
Not be able to eat anymore sure
Okay
Yeah if you if you deny someone Imperial ambition right
Equivalent of a bird
Right
That is what do you want from Mike Tyson
Who like fine
But why are we doing I also think that the philosophy that he's actually espousing is a is a horrifying
A way to live
Complete application of responsibility to do anything 100% it's also internal
Convoluted in ink
Consistent
Because if he's saying it's humans who get in the way and everything is perfect and you just don't need to interfere
It should not also be true of poop
Why is he acting in somewhat isn't his action
Out of sync with this
Natural wonderful Evans
Inflow that he's discussing
You know now that you put it that way
What weather what are the limits who has moral agency
I feel like at a certain point
This is this is a conversation
Between a guy who I think
If I sat down and talked to
I could probably get to agree
To what I say
And I think you could probably do with both I mean maybe without
Well I mean depending on
What level of
Fury
But
But then Alex is just agree to whatever b i c
Says so Mike Tyson is a very seemingly easily swayable person
At this point in time
Maybe
I'm not sure I don't know enough to say but yeah it's possible
I think that
From the other episodes of the clips that I've watch
I don't have any really good sense of this
But I think it would be possible for you to sit down with Mike Tyson
I have a bizarre but okay conversation
I think you'd I think almost anybody would have more chemistry with him than out
Alex
Like everybody else that I've seen on the show I watched a bit of the Eminem
Piers Morgan
Bit of Trina course
Just some other ones I watched a bit of it
They're actually going back and forth
There's a little bit of interplay between them
Just alyx
What a weird
Situation also thank you so much
Can't believe the Dennis Rodman ended the Korean War
He did not first off
Until because why would he
Or how could he
For what
Hung out with
Honestly it's kind of in Dennis Rodman
Work personal interest to end the Korean War
He won't get to hang out with his Rich buddy anymore
Also here's the other thing
If Alex were to accept
Tyson's philosophy and worldview
He should not be fighting the globalist
Right because if he does clearly the bigger hot
It says everything is as it should be doesn't need to kill that big Hawk
Strong murder the week in order to feed their kids
It's the circle of life
That's why you have
To let Millions upon millions of ukrainians die honestly I do kind of think that that is
In line with
Like some of the stuff that I see
The spouses is like a natural hierarchy and that it is correct
Which is bizarre
But we'll get to that a little bit down the line
Here is a after this it goes to a clip from
Mike's podcast
Stupid Alex recorded
A little shroomy
I can actually explain this here at after this clip I think
Bookmark
So what
He has ears shaped edible
Allentown
Bury the hatchet all the way with her maybe she'll get the cut or something
Is B
Alex is grabbing the bag from him and insisting on biting it
Like to be a good commercial for you or whatever
It's sad
Pink
Maybe the ear looks
It's a little bit like a mushroom or something like that seems to be like maybe
What are you getting at maybe they tried to put some of the hallucinatory chemicals in there maybe they don't know maybe it's got a little bit
It or something along those lines I don't know
With the little shroomy
Maybe I don't know it is but it's just a weed edible
Yeah it is a little bit like
You know I watch them getting Doug with high and ODed Benson did that
Show at Largo and you would have
Very famous people
Get high together on stage and then the
Beehive state
And the fun of that
Is the natural tension of like
Is somebody going to get too high
Who's going to get too high
Somebody does but everybody else just kind of freaks out I do not enjoy that natural tension
This is detention
Everybody's got
Wilbury too hot
That is the clip from the podcast that hasn't been there
Are you hot if that's
Indicative of anything
It's like this
This is just not a product you'd want to like
All right maybe we can have Alex on another time if he controls himself or something but like
Yeah this is just this is
There's a difference between like Alex
Being fun and weird on Rogan show Maybe
Him being kind of embarrassing with Mike Tyson
Know him like Rogan does
It comes off sad
Yeah I wouldn't put
A lot of hallucinogens in front of a person with
Absolutely zero impulse
Control
Teachers
To get back to Alex's interview
Seeing in the last decade or so
Interviews in Lagos
You're doing and I've learned
You said a lot of stuff cuz I know a lot of philosophy on History this
Original
What
You're definitely not plagiarizing
Suppose you're coming up with
Assassins
Plug is a zeitgeist
Just like you were plugging was like
Intellectually Eldersburg
Zeitgeist
I just followed
Still the fighting
The spirit of fighting cooking so many different arenas
.
Speedway
Something Clicker
So what do you think you're
What is your current fight
But me
Me and my behavior
Okay alright
So I think the one thing that Mike said so far the constitutes like a philosophical thought is that idea that life is
His innocence gradual death
That's not even close to a ridge
Let something like Arthur schopenhauer said that dude died
18:6
The entire School
Existential nihilism
To probably agree with Mike to its
Unique it all here just to Stone dudes.
What about stuff they don't really understand
But they surrounded themselves with people who are too afraid to tell them Bill like
This is high school level stuff guys
That's mrs.
Deep
Kind of
Telling that you think it's
It tells me how deep
You
10 to go
I mean
Okay
Just cuz you hit people while back doesn't mean you get to grow old into a guru
And I feel like a lot of people who hit people awhile back feel like they get
To grow into a guru
And you don't
You just don't
So
Bat like
Stolen Valor of somebody wearing a black belt
Who never earned it is the same as that Valor of
Beat pretending to be a guru
Philosopher philosophize
River of actually learning
Sure
Sure I mean
I think I
Don't try to think of other people who
Fit the mold you're talking about
I guess Isaac Eddie Bravo John Claude Van Damme
Well
He was
Quality
The muscles from Brussels
Had a lot of ideas
Steven Seagal
His name what
I listen to it on the dollop
It's Segal
He changed it made it sound like that cuz he didn't like us sounding like he was a Jew
BoBoiBoy cuz he is
Alright got lucky socks
Cinema in the movies
He sucks
Anyway
Alex brings up hallucinogen
This is where we
First encounter the toad
What about hallucinogens cheap big corporations now
Studies at Reading
Mushrooms are they dressing healthy
Synthetic drugs
You it seems like
Thanks for being
More empowered
Better
Mike Tyson
As far as DMT as far as
Mushrooms
As far as the
How how do those fit in
How would you describe I would be a junkie right now
Custom
Dreadful disease right now
And this is Jessie
Take me to my height
Potential
Try to read
The toad saved Mike's life
Alright
Specific time
No it's
From old TV shows and cartoons are people that lick toads
Yes the same thing
It's just that
Elected totally saved his life apparently this is caught on a little bit
Oh yeah yeah is this like how Ayahuasca with a huge thing like 10 years ago and everybody's like
Preliminary research going on
In terms of
It having add
Advantageous psychologic
Benefits
Right there are there are some indications that
They like psilocybin
Can be very helpful for your therapeutic
Ecstasy is amazing for MDMA supposed to be
Locations that are being
Explored
In terms of the toad you are
But
Keep it
And like I would if I ever got me high
I would feel great
And I would take with me and it would be my emotional support toad so would help me there to you didn't stumble upon a toad
Did it talk in the cartoon made
Mike compares
The toad to like ayahuasca
And
Did the comparison is
What's how would you describe mushrooms
Vs code versus
DMT
Marshall
The owner of the
The stuff
That's a part that's a party medicine
Guard right away and he's telling you s***
By the way
It is no
Hesitation you don't got to wait 30 minutes don't right away
Ogmod
I haven't done it but I escaped but they doing that you give you game so much courage
Hey buddy
Hey buddy Ayahuasca is a
Everybody says that but it's good if you want to do the real s*** buddy
Actually I'm glad you brought this up because you don't actually lick
They found a way to freebase
Did they kill the child
What did you eat
I said
The god butts
Describe four
Magician visual RV can
What
The toad
You sit down
Define
Fursuit
Be Busta
The bus
From the puss
Toad
Find Stan
Cooking
Crack looking pipe
Smoke it
Let It Go
Dogo City
You going to
What'd you say
Mortos
All your demons
Okay,
Codymen
Alright okay
This is
You know right time when Alex Wood box
The idea of people who sit around
He would make fun of somebody who just sat around and talked about freebasing toes
Velvet I
Got to take that toad puss you
Make it into a fine sand and then you Freebase it like Accra
Good Lord that's that's
So he described
What it's like
I understand what you saying of the effect
Of it being
Positive or possibly freeing for him
Exactly what he's describing could lead someone to a mental breakdown like jumping out a window
Was like it was like
There were a thousand knives in between each one of my fingers
Because that is really difficult to interpret in a positive way
What he's talking about is a psychological effect
He had that I
Think you could interpret positively
But also it's very easy to imagine someone experiencing the exact same thing
And it breaking
So I don't know if I would be so
Quick to describe this is like
Did you say
Edema
Is Willem you experience everything that you be
Are you afraid to tell somebody cook
You have opinions about you and Ivy
If you have to feel the effects
All your troubles
Naked
Olivia
It's just I I cannot take you later
Is my prince know your
Yes just letting you know this is who you are
Deal with this
You have that feeling you don't see anybody you have that feeling that
Open
That feeling of Freedom like that
And in Philly
Completion
Homicidal
Beyonce
60 * 11
What is nutmeg
Different
Yeah it's not go ahead
I can handle
No
Don't worry about
Okay
He's done code 60 times a lot of times to do toads
A lot of a lot of experience of
Feeling like everybody knows all of the things you're ashamed of
There is a way that you can look at that as like
Well
What's the big deal
I can I can withstand any of this is a liberating feeling that you possibly
Could come too
Or it could be the most intolerable feeling you've ever had in your life
It would be the scariest idea of it to everybody knows everything about you
I don't know I don't know how people respond different
Here's what I would say to you
About that exact
Text feeling
And who it is
Spring to and who does not freaking to
It is freaking to
Celebrities who everybody already knows everything about that men make up bulshit all the time and they have to deal with it anytime
Diamond anywhere they want to do any
I would even bet that some celebrities who would not be
I think it really comes down to like
The way your mind experience
Yeah like I don't even know if that would be
Yeah cuz I don't know if that would be a universal experience for people to have
What are the USDA ratings
Yeah it
It's strange to play
Get Thursday like
There's a
Level
That would be different
Between different people of like
What are the things you don't want to tell.
Cuz some people
It's kind of like
Trivial stuff in for some people it's like while I killed so
Well for Alex would be like well I didn't
And everything I'm saying it's a lie and has been for almost three decades
Put like
There are differences differences in terms of self-awareness
Like
You might not have access to
Things that you shouldn't feel guilty about
In some cases
And some people have too much access to things to feel guilty about things that they don't need to feel
I all that worried about and I think they'll be difficult
In the toad scape
Do I
Parcel
I mean based on what
Mike Tyson is describing I think
Toad would absolutely kill Alec
Alex Jones
Brain-dead in an insta
If it works the way that he says it does.
He would suddenly be flooded
With
An unconscionable amount of sin
In one mole
So many fake plants
The total perspective Vortex for all your good
So look you asked if it's standardized
I'm interested in Mike gets his toe.
Dino's real talk
Cuz obviously we're talking about surprise
Shamanism
He's pretty much like that
The toads in the message
Well
That's amazing amazing that a shaman who does nothing but give people
Toad knows about toads
You got a toad shop
The Mushroom Kingdom
Not a good one that's
I think I would go
Yes
Cochon might be sketchy dude
Who calls himself instead of the toad dealer
Well he wears different clothes that dude expected dealers that you are glowing outfit
Corner
You want some
Baby
Oh God I'm so out of touch with stuff that I didn't realize this was coming back as like a big hallucinogen
Tell I was listening to this on my
Look into this I looked it up
It's
Recently become a lot more prevalent but
It just seems so silly to me because
It's it is the same thing as licking toads
Yeah I like maybe one of your dumb Friends lick they not hallucinogenic toad finger
This is funny
Just licking toes if you just hear that's pet stores
You're just don't want to actually lick the toad and get all the
Pee on their on
On top of your
That's weak tea
I don't like you got to
You take the good with the bad asthma Tyson himself
I would say is that toad is going to be able to feed its family rights like going to Laos
I am going to McDonald's
Exactly come on powerlix code
Another clip now from Mike's podcast Alex recorded
This is some deep stuff
Stuff about geopolitics
His back
Show me the word the word
What is ecology
Family show host Alex Jones
Giving Nancy Pelosi analingus
Everybody was like
And think it feels like they're laughing at him
Absolutely it's not like this is a funny guy
Look at this look at this Village
I'll look that you're really got
Man
Also that's a co-host who's asking the question
He didn't know that bite
To go into Ukraine cuz I didn't
No no no he didn't do that
Yeah I would have been a very weird thing for a president to have done and then to put in
Listen to the news
What are you going to do
Well you got to rely on Alex to come in and do some drugs and tell you all about it if I didn't get my pay
Text information from somebody who just took a weed gummy ear then where am I going to get it from
So the Pelosi talked continued
I know
Label
No you're not true
Well I appreciate your
Your time
What about one of our mutual friends Joe Rogan God
This is annoying wow
You know the thought occurs to me that Alex and Nancy have more in common
And then Alex
Or Nancy have with the rest
Rest of the world
Yeah that may be true
People with 100 million dollars are really only relatable to people
Let's see
The detachment
Certainly from
For both of them
Oh yeah
Creature Comforts are available
Like
Tap water
I think they're doing the right thing
But ultimately often are are making problems worse
Borderline sociopathic whenever faced with an actual problem
Analingus
Both of them love it
Yeah that's
Look at it if this is indicative of what the conversation was like on the podcast itself
I'm putting that
Baby Akshay
Coming out
Fit with Tyson's other shows has right next to
Revolt tattoo right next to it
So
Ticket to talk about Joe Rogan
Does a Taurus their Mutual buddy
Got to come up that's my credibility
Well I appreciate
Your time what's that about
Mutual friends
Joe Rogan
What do you make of all the attempts to
Cancel him I didn't want any bigger
How do you stink
How do you think some people is so
McGuffey Blasphemous for your soul
And dignified
They feel as if
I don't want to hear that damn say that not even directed towards
Eva wanted to fight other battle that don't even care
Concerned
You know that I don't know if that's the root of the world everybody wants
The fight
Jalalabad
At the fight something
We can't fight something fire self Achilles overdraw
The state of our country
Physical
Altercation
Yeah and so they see jogging Biggs they decided Angela Villa
Listen
Is this country must
Advantage of
Yeah that doesn't sound like somebody who thinks history started 9,000 years ago Envy one of the deadly sins
Never heard of it before
Don't covet thy neighbor's wife
That's
Thomas Paine
Port on The Federalist Papers
Sure sure
I don't find this that interesting
Thankfully things start to pick up a little bit and
Next clip
Why is America
The most successful but also the best
But also the most evil
Because I'm
The meaning of life
Successful
If this was
A perfect world
We live in a perfect world all the
Group switch
Kill each other baby driver
And then we stop mating
And then we'll all die
That's what a perfect world with
Imagine her having everything in the world with
Button
Play the war was struggle
Is life in the
Did happen listen this
I never wanted to believe this
Plus my studying life and woman
What was his name
Perfect
People need to be
Hit the bottom
Cheetah dab to the top
And they need
Yes
There's a lot going on there
Perfect Society
We would all die
Right
I don't understand
Necessarily what basis there is
Wow
I mean
I think
Maybe
I'm going to be real generous
Maybe he's saying that the only way for society
To be perfect
Is 4:30
Tubino Society
No
Do you know
If everybody's dead
Vince society's perfect
Not at all if we had all of our material needs handled it taken care of
We would turn into roving
Communities of
Fighting people who kill each other
And then everyone would die because we would stop
Reproducing or something yeah I was trying to trying to avoid we stopped reproducing even if we
We were in like gangs that were killing each other
People at War still f***
No
No they don't
We got we'd all be too sad
From having
Too many of our needs matdan
I mean look I don't
Really know what to take away from that other than like
Clearly there seems to be a belief that
Aim is what makes life possible
If I'm really grasping
Poverty is essential for in an order for
The world
To continue to exist as we know from early American history life is suffer
That's one of them four noble truths of the tenth
I think the
Bizarre
Also the idea that god-ordained some kind of a hierarchy
Border or whatever
Is really dumb
Because
It's changed a lot
Overtime at what point in time
It is the natural pecking order at
Is it under a monarchy system is it
Under a feudal system is it
But whatever we've got going on now in the communism
Who's to say which is the the system that God ordained
I'm going to throw this out at you
Maybe what he's really saying is that things are going pretty good for me right now
I get the feeling that there's a little bit of that
Maybe I would be more interested in fighting for other people
If my needs work mat right now
And also I think that there's a really
Troubling
End result
Of his thought process here which is
This notion that everything is as it should be and you shouldn't
Fight things and all that
There's a little bit of a few no sort of a spiritual Detachment from
Stuff that can be pause
Legitimately what he
He is advocating
4 would have led to
Civil rights never happened
There is a
There is an application of any responsibility to
To further the amount of people who
Alright enjoy
Here's a here's a modicum of freedom
Here's what I'll say based upon what he
You saying
I'll go the opposite direction he said that a perfect Society where everybody needs are met we all wind up dying
I would say it's a society built around his ideas
One with rampant income inequality
With a ruling class
Rapacious Lee treating the world
It would would actually lead to
To everybody killing each other and die
And I'm just throwing that out there
Based on
Last year
Fight
No actually not fight
More things that don't
Directly affect you
Why does everyone care about
Info but you're not transfer your problem is people just
You want to fight that's all it is you just want to fight you don't care about anybody
Bordering on
Nihilistic worldview that find objection
These are deeply held belief
But he has or if they're just High kind of what I was thinking
With a cam
Versation going the other way you be like well obviously everybody
They should be taken care of in trans rights are really important and I don't know I don't know
Held beliefs
Empowered
I don't know anything about empowered by Muse
I'm I'm enjoying this
Life in
Looking forward
Death as well
Will you talk about looking forward to death my we don't want you to leave this plane
Anytime soon but
What you want
When people lie
You're right so your geek
Oh absolutely
That for what I
What I believe death is death
Def Leppard I believe
That's when I really began
I think
Positive
Saying about making
Peace with the reality of death
Text relizen process
I don't really feel like I said Mike's doing
God I can't wait to be having a lot in common in regards to like that
You know this all this whole thing is
The cast in this is all
And everything is created as a trial and then when you die you get the good
The difference is that Alex thinks you go to
Space and you fly around strip
And Mike thing
Thanks you hang out with a toad
I mean it's pretty cool too
And if you lick it even when you're dead you get high
I so that's worth it
Wright's liquor
And you think you're all alive for about it as opposed to take Internet yourself
God
Why doesn't actually walk to die that's
The distinctive navigate to make
But you're not
You're not going to check out the concert
If I want to go somewhere
I'ma go somewhere I'm not going to have any Grammy somebody's going to
Amelie after your kill me I'm not going through all that
Please take my money I know that
Crap
Is just
This is Alan my life
Free
I'd like to believe it's free but it's not as attempted
I got to tell you
Mike Tyson like
The biggest philosopher in the world right now.
Your point
What other
I'll call you I miss really awesome
And even though people if
Think this is stupid Nietzsche
Psychic
Alright
So did he say that him and his psychic like Nietzsche if you want it
Alright that makes a lot more sense of this whole
Giving someone life
Is giving someone death bulshit
Also
Describing there is like a really likely situation like
A Mugger is out looking for someone to Rob and he chooses Mike Tyson
Gigantic man with a face tattoo who's considered one of the best
Punchers in boxing history I mean obviously you burgle into his house
Gone what kind of idiot would Rob
If I were like I would live my life free from the fear of that happening throughout that did not trouble me too much
It would be interesting to have
0 fizzy
Nicole
Like threat
Ever
Maybe you have some from a weapon or a sniper what are the odds of that are pretty low
Also I don't want to be a dick here but the idea you may not be free but are trying
Bfree that's nowhere near a new philosophical idea
I think that's kind of a problem with the information space that this interview lives
It's not grounded in any kind of education on the subject
Exeter being thrown around like this is
There's like freshman-level philosophy class ideas
Literally just threw out
Young and Nietzsche
The thing every freshman
What class has especially freshmen edgelord tight
Haha
So we're coming to the end of this interview and I would say that if the other episode is anything like this I would not want to
Who put it out myself
It's just not worth the hassle and the
Quality of content makes this show look like an amateur operation
We are an amateur operation and I would still be uncomfortable airing this is an episode of our show
Not do it
Alex the calculus is different though
He puts up nothing but loads
Trash and there's no real downside for him
The quality of content isn't important than the infowar as evidenced by The Unbelievable volume of unwatchable videos on
Banned. Video
For Alex the quality is irrelevant
He was able to record a thing with a celebrity
He knows that thing is going to drawing a lot of attention
So that thing needs to be put out regardless of how little there is going on in it and how
Dumbs
I mean
Yeah it doesn't he doesn't
Want people to listen to
Intuit
This is Bonfield talk about
Exactly he wants people he wants people on Twitter to clown on him for being such a drunk
Dum dum he want
People to be outraged or whatever he doesn't actually care if anybody listens to the podcast
Is that people keep talking
So are we have a couple clips left
One of them is Mike having a interesting
Take on covid
I doubt
Bi-Rite
Grover
Because of the stuff
I never knew it what
Covid-19
I asked
I don't know I don't know
Politically correct for me to fit in
Could people have died from it
I know it's a viral disease where people died at but
Me myself person I've been around thousands of people
A couple of times I've been in the same bus twice this year
I've been around a bunch of people hugging and kissing eating with
People who don't have mapping
I'm okay
I do have
Love and hugs
Ubermensch
FYE
None up so why do you think you never got it
I don't know but this is what I also know to
A person that has a disease can.
Psychologically faster than a
I really know that
I know that
That
You know Mike
I have a case of like an asymptomatic case or
Maybe a mild case that he didn't
No really knows almost
Text Nate if you might have gotten
Vaccinated and I could have
Taking his risk
Significantly
Lay down but not
It based on what he has said so far I highly doubt
But that he would want somebody to
I think you're right
Open triple back
And I'm fine
I'm literally
Mike f****** Tyson what are you up to say
Yeah I think you're probably right
I'm not going to get it is stupid
And then second I don't know
If I trust fully that he never got it
I haven't been sick
Very careful I wear mask
Avoided
Areas
Especially indoors
You know this.
I don't know for sure that I haven't gotten
Cuz I could have had a case that I didn't identify
There's there's it is entirely possible if you did I didn't like neither of us have
Tested positive
That does not mean that we tested when we may have had an asymptomatic case
So I mean Atlantic City odds
For Tyson
Significantly higher based on the description of his his behavior
Wow you know what that is that is kind of a
I don't know I suppose a childlike way of trying to view the world
Old is kind of what I'm seeing right now is just
This idea of like
Well it whatever happens happens and if it's not happy
Nothing to me it'll never happen
And all of this like I don't have any
Concern
And while I understand that not having
Concern can look like
Like freedom
What it really more is is Narcissus
That might be another thing needs to happen, could be
Sorry about my Scorpio during the Mike down for this
Because I think this is actually going to give
Caviar into your wheelhouse
Here and
I don't know I think I think
You might have some things to learn from Mike
I could even believe some people could even
What is that
Projecting something
Can get themselves
That worrying so much
I confess believe that they have covid-19
They actually get it
We're themselves
After
Puscifer
Who did was China
That's why I became Buddha Kitty
Panhandle
Make sure you get to a Christina cell phone
Afraid
Delete The Saturdays
Wow
Why would indeed
Wow indeed that is that is a wow moment for somebody to say
Wow I was born to Wild you brought up the four noble truths earlier
Oh just my god wow somebody who has a passing interest in Buddhism
I have three statement
Mike Tyson made in that last click on the Buddha scale
Yes okay
The first one is he became Buddha because he could
Handle that people were suffering
How true
Do you assess this statement to be
Well
I would say
Not at all true
I mean
Sidarta wasn't like
Stokes
The super-rich to really concerned can you possibly be
If your solution after being super rich
Is to go sit under a f****** tree
Motivation wasn't entirely
Like he couldn't handle the people were supper or like what the fuc
He said there's no such thing as suffering God did not create suffering
Oh well let's start with God
Let's chat with for free
What's that truth again
Life
Louvre
Seven things that he said
The Buddha was like there's no suffering God didn't create it
Quite the opposite little bit off
What is a it
Self suffering that we suffer from
There's a way you could kind of make that work cuz cycling is
What your desires are if you want to say that Detachment is equal to self suffering and that
In that regard
Stretch
Kind of get there that like
Yeah yeah
It's it's
Close to accurate is you're going to get but
Beaten ocean that there's no such thing
Real fun
Is bananas also the idea that he's mixing it up with
Yeah I mean
That's kind of
That makes
It does seem like his knowledge of philosophy is just a
To Jumble
That pops out when it comes to branch
He likes young man but he's not eating as much
Sure but
To throw that out
That's that powerful
It definitely deserves a wow from out only throw this out at
How much
Does history lie to a stand
Mike know something that we don't know
Yes I told him
The Buddha actually said there's no such thing as suffer
Pissed if it towed was actually I'm a Tabata
So we come to the end of this sort of wacky when
Some interesting
I really was impressed
With the most
He's like
Little
Vibe there was
Between the
That was
Eddie Bravo like there's at least an electric chemistry between them they could make something like kind of fun
Fun to watch
Flagrant 2 podcast
Those dudes were going along with him
Like they were taking his energy and coasting with
Where is like this is just two dudes who like
Are it like not incompatible.
They're not like
They're not vibing at all
Question answer
Answer with a pot
Like there's no give back there's no like
You know any moment where it goes
And here's what I and then you go back and he goes back
That sounds right
Actually they proven that
How many goes on to the next question
Cuz he doesn't want to follow up with his b******* because then he's going to get into a ditch
Anyway
Maybe we can figure out what he wants to say about the killers
But until then we have
I hope you all have
Have a wonderful and three me and
What the sex robot
Alex
Birthstone colors