Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge
Flashlight.com
Acknowledge
Jordan Jordan quick question
What's up
My brakes
Is McCreary summer continues to March along and
The same people
Oh no you're coming after talenti gelato now this is a different story
It's tired territory impossible to open
Cut open the f****** container
I was considering doing a week and going over it all the flavors
Find separating the wheat from the chaff
But I realize like there's some players earning really want to try
A birthday cake sprinkles I don't know I mean I have that birthday cake
Cake ice cream sandwich that was just like
Frosting flavored ice cream is disgusting
Yeah but I did try to
That's the trigger is a 2 year scotch
The cheers is to the salted caramel
Laird
These are all the Laird was
Sort of
Chocolate cake
Good
Strong
Good stuff
Then there's a peanut butter
Wanda
That's amazing yeah yeah it's horrific I ate a little bit of
That's that's a testament
I do hold 20 responsible for
They made it
But you know I'm not too mad at
That you could some of these other ones are alright in the ones that I don't
Want to try like birthday cake
Also a little deers
I would have had it cuz imma I'm a big peanut butter person
But
Ice cream terms by partner she's allergic to
Do peanuts so never have ice cream
Make ice cream in the house
With that type of flavor so I've never got
That's it's good to know that I can just skip
Talenti is b******* peanut butter the peanut butter crunch
The layers
Black
That's a big deer
My bright spot is yesterday my family did a classic
Platter of celebrations
Little sister's birthday
My grandfather's turning 100 Centennial
My partner and I got married in like
It was just
Take your pick of what you wanted to celebrate we'll all get together on a day will bang it out
It out and it worked
Is good stuff good to get it all taken care of
None of this Lego will see you on Tuesday and then on Friday nope
Get it done will see you in 4 months
Sweet yep I like it I think a lot of other people
Probably would rather see their family more often
But I understand your situation and I
I know you're coming from
Cake
Was that birthday cake 20
There wasn't even there were
There I think there might have been cake
But it was never brought out
And all we had
Around we're just
Candles
Because
If you would assume like a they were going to try and do the hundred candles thing quit on that
Candles around and no cake anywhere
So I think they just bailed out
Disappointed
We have episodes
Talk about
We are going to be going back to the movie talk about
August 4th
Some reason Stewart
Of course first Alex is still on his
Work vacation
That he had it on chair so
Probably be recording us on Sunday I would guess he'll be back on his show
Today on Sunday
We won't have time
To flip that around until Wednesday so
We'll check in with him when he's back
Simultaneously
Project Camelot episode that could be made but it might
2 deep well of crazy done in time
And
Man
I have lost my interest in Russell Brand
That is unsurprising
Ivy I think that there is possibly an episode and like covering him
He bores me
Yeah no I saw Get Him to the Greek
I'm good
Yeah I died but I had enough I already fish Ali convinced myself like who this
But really fast
Do you know what it was
He's just famous
Yeah
Get kind of annoyed
Do because his his videos on YouTube
Fake hunt
Instantly have clickbait as titles life
So It Begins my God
She's over and over again f****** joke
Anyway yeah it's kind of boring
So we're back in the past
And
Stuff going on
Feeling about the Iraq War
Has Beth application re is it re-bath application now update on that
Are you still in control
First you won't believe
Thank you so much
Is a quick break so that Jordan can take off his
T-shirt and Nestle himself in my beard
No idea what that
Thank you Mary
Biking fit like a pen
Yeah or a joint
In the past like
Smoke Shack
Yeah you're my beard
And sneak it into a concert but a human
Is your tests are on the other hand I could bury myself in that there's no doubt
Next
Thank you so much
Couple of technocrat
Self
Henry not but be that as it may I declare myself the 74th sorts of fall
That's the name
You are now attacking
I'm a policy wonk I have
Risen above
And then we're going to
Comeback
And I'm going to start the show over
I got plenty work for you
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
Horse you rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to the
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's not even in the past even though I mean that's not true a to the Press
Isn't he is somewhat better
There's a couple of things actually revealed over the course of this episode that are like
Man you had some really f***** up positions for a pretty long time
You've just done a pretty good job of
Obscuring
How to restore off here on August
4th and Alex is talking about
A
What do you know
Certainly this is going to be
One of the most serious situations
Over several years
Knox
Job
Redact
NRA
What's the point of alert
And it smokes
Amore in Rochester
Call Anna
General
I was thinking about 2,000
Yeah support Gore or bush
So like
Obviously not guesswork Bill Bradley
Who's in the primaries against
Score that wasn't happening
Volcanoes against
Bush in the prime
Raise
Alan Keyes was covered in the GOP primaries
I know that Alan Keyes unable come together on
Something yeah
Guest-hosted Infowars of the past year but
First part of 2009 that I remember it is we don't
We didn't have that
Republic
Can primary cavalcade
Debate stage
Did you know where we had sixteen different Republicans saying dumb nonsense at each other
All stupid the same way you had a number of folks but they withdrew like before the primary started yet
Exploratory campaign
Puppy panting was trying to run
Yes absolutely explored the idea
McCain to use ambush
Functions a little bit better
I think then
100 people on stage
But it's less entertaining
Sure might not be what we're going for right now
So this is a bill that Alex is talking about the gun bill
It did not pass as has been the case with literally any proposed gun bill that's come up at Alex
It is about to pass
And would leave the door to door confiscation
Everything all the way up to a child
What are the great
Consistent trans you notice when you go back and listen to Infowars from the past is that every proposed gun bill is apocalyptic
And all of them are set to be passed any day now
It's ridiculous as an act and it's weird that it never gets old for the listener
Bush never did any of the stuff Alex
To claim he was going to
He let the Clinton assault weapons ban lapse
He didn't Champion any other gun legislation
But it does
Kind of makes sense for Alex
To think that he might
Primarily because
You clearly just getting talking points from the NRA's press release
And in the interest of total fairness as recently as May 2000
Three that had commented supported
Extending the 1994 gun bill
The thing is that in the real world Bush can't just do that on his own it would need to be passed by Congress
Howard subscribes to a very narrow strongman theory about the world and us
Because Bush said he's in favor of one thing it must be the case that it's going
Come to pass
After the 2002 midterms there was a 51-49 republican majority in the Senate and a 229
9 to 200
For Republican majority in the house
It was safe for Bush to Signal support to the idea of gun control in order to sway Independence to the right
Wow being entirely comfortable that no gun Bill had any chance of making
Get through either House of God
It's the governmental equivalent of having your cake and eating
YouTube basically is
Where he was going
Absolutely I support this
This thing that I know is impossible to happen I will never do anything
Text that I will sign this thing that is
Essentially impossible
I will sign this unicorns face
The moment you put it in front of me I promise you that
In the 2000 GOP Primary bushes whole brand was meant to be compassionate
Conservative
I'm part of that is not having
Sing this Hardline Gunn absolutism
An element that strategy was probably informed by the fact that he was running against
John McCain
Who had a farm or outside or character than Bush and appeal to a
Han more voters that were closer to the center military history so you can't fight him on that front
There was no way Bush could win the
Congest off the supported
The Fringe right so he has conservatism as a strategy
One might argue that he had some actual inclination toward reforming gun laws but that seems like both
The NRA loudly endorsed Bush in 2000
M4 and they actually strategically withheld their endorsement of him in the 2000 election
Because
The New York Times quote
Polls suggest that the NRA will popular many republican areas is viewed negatively by large numbers of in
Independence Suburban voters
Who mr. bushes
Just trying to court particularly women
Sincere concern in 2000
Open for a new candidate but much less so by 2004 when Bush was the incumbent
Well we were keeping their love of bush quiet on the surface they also the NRA had a vice president who said that if Bush got
Selected quote
We'll have a president where we work out of their office
So
This this notion is
Is a loaded
Alex
Basically
Political maneuvering that bushes doing
In terms of
Placing himself in a place where
Independent voters could be drawn towards him
And there's no actual consequence
To the is exactly what
Bushwood
Like that's the strategy
Make Alex look like the conservative nut bag
Compared to Eureka
Compassionate conservative
Not bad
Rallying be like really far right in a certain direction you kind of make sure that the status quo
Remains the Same
That gun Bill never makes it to your desk
Don't ever have to sign and let's be real with
Those right-wing lunatics if they vote they're still going to vote for
What are they going to vote for somebody else get the f*** out of here.
Al Gore
You can pencil them in whenever you want Ron Paul wasn't a factor in that Elijah
So there's more more talk of this gun bill
It's basically one of his his primary points
I'm going to warn you
About the most
When did Ann Coulter
Sovereign
Almost identical
Record
Thoroughly
Border
We're in the very very
More
Millions morgue
So this bill HR 2038 was introduced on May 8th
It's 2003 3 months prior to this episode that were list
Coming through right now
How's my birthday
Hey happy birthday it's literally nothing had been done to move it any closer to passing sensor
That's been a lot like my birthday 28th 2004 a motion was filed
Title resolution
769 which sought to bring HR 203
To immediate consideration on the house floor
These sorts of discharge petition
Require 218 signatures to pass
How many think this one got
At the point Alex's on are pretending he's covering a news story about a bill that's a real threat to cut ownership
You should have every reason to know that this is a dead Bill already
This isn't news or analysis its manufacturing a threat to scare you into thinking someone's on their way to take your gun
Relying entirely on a Guess Who press release from the NRA
Yeah great
Yes
Weird thing about going back into the past so often is remembering that at that
Time. I did not have
The tools necessary to like
Understand House 2
Stupid and transparent all of this
Really what
You know
Like I'd ever so many things back in 2003
I think I think I was in such a conservative family
After 9/11 I was one of those people whose like yeah 94% of people should support
It's a good thing I was 12
But the time sure can't really affect the political process
Yeah Amy I think
Do I look back in
There was a. I wasn't even in like a really conservative family
Listen to conservative talk radio a lot
The passive
Nature of listening to it
I thought like Sean Hannity had a legitimate point
Neal Boortz
I would immediately say oh these people are lying to make millions of dollars and it's a baddie
Yeah yeah
It's a different twist.
Big news about Personnel in the White House
By the way
They're going to put another
Background
And
Program
Alright
The hell right
Really on his way out he stayed in office until
75 when he resigned possibly at Bush's request
At the start of bushes
Enterprise
He was replaced by Condoleezza Rice who Alex hasn't mentioned up to this point
I don't know if you think she's a
Trotskyite
Listeners are the kind of people who could be so sensitive
Covert racism
Have simultaneously unaware of what Black Ops are to the point where he could sincerely think anyone would sentiment
Email about that
Someone possibly should send him an email about his obsession with the mysterious secret truck
DIYs
And how that sounds suspiciously antisymmetric though I think maybe
Maybe that deserves an email it would have been
Three interesting if colon polyp was
Is a trotskyite
That would have that would have changed
Things a great deal as opposed to being a lying war criminal
That does change
Yeah police
Alex
But was it all in Alex's head
Like I was last week when
Be careful
Involving
Because there's no pun intended
This is all in Alex's head
He's getting mad about imaginary people having a completely absurd response to something he's
Self as the victim of these imaginary people
And here's the reason he's doing
Alex wants to inoculate his audience to the possibility of them hearing people accuse him of being a race
A lot of this content is flagrantly racist and he understands that on some level
So he knows that it's inevitable that people who listen to his show will end up
Hearing
From other people
That is racist a s*** I agree with you
The goal here is for Alex to take a
Completely obvious example of something that isn't racist but includes a trigger word that he can protect someone
Call him braces for sale
In this case black
He pretends the people will say he's racist for saying things like Black Ops with a listener hear someone accuse Alex of saying something Gracie
Their immediate response will be like oh sure
Like how he said that he was a racist good to use the word blacktop shaft it gives them that kind of
Defensive posture
Read it really is
Exactly like how they think
Vaccination
It's like okay I'll take a little bit of dirt
False racism
And kind of make you immune to that so then whenever the real racer
I'm already prepared
Yeah
I think I think it's more for them to be able to
To withstand criticism from their friends
And family
Who might be like hey
That stuff you're listening to is pretty f*****
Remember all the things that he didn't say about Jews cuz he uses the word globalist
Imagine Dragons
Yeah, buddy
Put two and two together
So Alex is a big news source mrs. this is the other thing that takes up
I would say a large
Part of his
Content
Within the show you have the gun bill that is not to be but is the biggest threat in the world
Illusion they're bunch of phone calls
That many have this store
Washington
Pulling in now
Courtney
From European
This is not a lengthy article it'll be less than a page of text
But it might appear longer cuz Alex just print out websites and the 4matic there could make it look larger
My God
He hasn't read it so he has no idea how long it is or what it says
Steven about
This is an op-ed about how Supreme Court justices have appealed to Legal ideas from
From other countries are legal bodies in their decision
Notably about one of the things they bring up is the recent case Lawrence versus Texas which invalidated so
Sodomy laws
Country inmate same-sex relationships illegal
Across-the-board
2003's have their way
It will be overturned
On the Texas GOP
Statement of intent
Like we're going to criminalize
Homosexuality
Lawrence versus Texas going to take that back to court
Oh man that's crazy
Yeah it is wild
Go to Just
Jenna really wrestle with the reality that that decision was in 2000
That's very recent begins with a
They could break into your home if you were gay
And then arrest
For just
Being there
Would not be
Impossible to make
While
Anyway Justice Kennedy's opinion included a point they quote
The courts past approval of sodomy bands was out of step with the law and other West
Democracy
And made mention of the European Court of Human Rights
This is not the same as the Supreme Court being told what
To Dubai other International bodies but
It's a fascinating and really depressing thing to think
About
This makes
The point that traditionally the United States has seen itself as the innovator in the world in terms
The freedom and human rights
But the country quote
Now has much to learn from the rapidly developing
Digital tradition
Of other democracy
Abdicated our place know if Alex thinks that's
The same thing
As getting your marching orders
I have these examples that they use in this article are not like hey
The Bedrock of my argument relies on
A precedent
Pointing that out in the
The opinions of like a also
Everybody else
Doesn't do this
Crazy nonsense
This is fun
Conservative legal Scholars are largely opposed to even citing International opinion in terms of the Supreme Court but it's
Important to recognize that this isn't the first time it's happened nor is it really that groundbreaking
Conservatives like Alex hate
Legal experts in this article aren't thrilled with the thing quote
When the courts
Starts taking things like that into account it revealed itself as more interested in making policy that in
The fix text
The Constitution or statute
That was a quote from you
The guy who worked in Bush's Attorney General's office is most remembered for his memos that the hero justifying torture
Because they would have tried to make policy again terrible
Big Picture This is an editorial that someone wrote about an interesting thing to think about as it relates
For the Supreme Court
It's not hard news and it doesn't say anything or prove anything about the court being under the control of some foreign body
Alex doesn't read any of the stuff he covers though so he's just reading the headline in
Skimming the first two sentences of making up the restituted purposes
As always
Goes wrong
Because he tries to read the article on hair
And unfortunately it doesn't really go his way
So here he is
Beginning to read that article
But not jump
It's cutely written cuz it's an op-ed
It's written by someone who's trying to engage the reader in something less formal than news copy
I sincerely don't think Alex knows the difference between opinion and fact-based Report
A 2003 or even of the present-day I think he's still doesn't know
You legitimately trying to pretend that this op-ed in the washing
Camden Post is announcing that the Supreme Court is under the can
Control of international bodies
That's one of his
Top stories
This is his only source
That wild
Well what they're doing
Is there soft launching it threw up
Tell me if you made that argument I would say
That's stupid
At least
This sort of honest about the point he was trying to make
Brightwood just come off as like
Are you f****** serious
Virtually keeps read
Ono and the presentation that he's trying to make is that this is announcing
Write our courts are under the control of like the
European core sure Cuban rice short what have you
But
Because he keeps reading
He gets to the point where they talk about how Bunch people aren't into this
Right
And that that doesn't go well
Here's the thing
He just ignores it
He just pretends that he's not reading stuff that's critical of the Supreme Court
Considering European thought that is
Powerful stuff
Court
Is dropped
European
Colcord
Group meeting
Computer screen
Turn on printer
Margarita
But it is
Use of international
Amorphous
Illegal
It reveals itself as more
Interpreting
The Constitution
Previous
But we are
Weather is not
They
Crew
The Constitution
Xbox
Hyperbole
That's not the right one
When did what
When did
Emma Watson
Legal
We're going to follow the European model
Wild bear sweetly ignores
Song minutes of him reading this article that's critical
Snot stuff that's a bunch of Hyperbole and they say it's about globalism
Taking our sovereignty
It's
Legitimately Unthinkable to me that someone could get away with
Being this transparently bad doing what they're
Pretending to do and people just there like
Yeah
Are you guys making sense
If you listen to the words
What's he saying
This is convoluted
Please textbook abuse
That is a literal person
Telling you something that just happened
Is not what you saw
Definition of gaslighting
This article is announcing that the
The cord is under the control of the European
But also I just read 2 minutes
Conversation about Scholars
The people who are making
The argument that I was literally making about this article are making it in the article
And there's like a whole bunch of that article to but like house scalia's really against this like people Eva
Even citing European fans as a as a reference
I like yeah
That this is stupid absurd to live in a world with the internet and then
I think that the Supreme Court
Is yours going to never look out it it's other legal Scholars anywhere else
So we are
Get to Alex talkin about death pen
Stuff
This is one of the questions I've always had
You're with Alex that I think is like
It's weird
Make its position on the death penalty is always been strange to me
Because at times he seemed to be against it
Which makes up
That's based on his
So the political and philosophical beliefs
All the times you spin in favor of it
It's been confusing to me
And in this could be kind of spells out
What is hot sauce
Another disappointing
3 years ago
The boys crown
Somebody
That's a really Illuminating clit because it shows clearly how Alex's position on the death penalty
It's only really that the objection that he has is that he doesn't trust the government with producing evidence
It's not a moral objection it's strictly logistical which doesn't make a whole lot of sense and it makes me think that Alex hasn't
Walk through this position very much
Should be a primary concern whether or not the state has the ability to take up
Life for committing a crime
Why would you want to vest that kind of
Power in the hands of the very thing you would consider yours
Sworn enemy how do you think it's been taken over by globalist
I could see Alec being in favor of the sheriff getting a posse together and taking out two suspected murderer before they're even
Arrested
Position at odds with how he presents himself
And his school of thought
The things that he says would meet his high standard of proof which would justify the death penalty
Concrete pieces of evidence
Eyewitness accounts are notoriously inaccurate so basic an execution on that seems pretty unwise absurd
Alex you think that confessions are often suspect
Because they could be cool worst out of people by overzealous police
Yelp so you wouldn't want to
You're not necessarily
Use that solely as
The basis for an execution concrete information
Videotape is all good and well but often inconclusive in terms of being able to identify people
Yeah it's probably fairly rare that that's going to be solely what you're able to convey
Somebody
Alex
What's the death penalty in principle Because he believes in violent retribution
What is laying down here is just a list
Types of evidence he looks for to make
Peace with it inside his head
Ridiculous he thinks the people who do things should have
Violent consequences
Like I don't
The government to do this
However I do think that a judge and a courtroom should the
What what are you f******
Talking about
It's this
Dumb idea that I think a lot of people in Alex's middle you'll have
Maybe there's even a little bit of his mentality on the left
Piano baby isn't
Helpful
It's not like the government is somehow a thing
Like the football
Yeah it's people who work
It's not like a witness who is
I don't know
Works for the IRS or something there's still a person
Right now there's a governor
There there is a cop see what happens is
They don't capitalize their names
Okay so then they're both Holden to the government because
The $600,000 in liens placed upon their name
At Birth I buy a maritime law
Is Almighty
The story of the German bank robbers is being a little bit misreported by Alec
This is about brothers Walter and Carla G
Who were executed by the state of Arizona in 1999 for a bank robbery that went wrong back in 1980
They weren't illegal immigrants the way Alex is trying to prevent the situation
They were born in Germany but their mother is
Flight to the United States when one brother was four and the other was 5
They've essentially lived here their whole lives
But they never become US citizen
The brothers were robbers by trade and the bank robbery had
Just after they've been released from prison
For robbing a string of supermarkets in Tucson the year before
They were trying to rob the Valley National Bank
Bank in Marana Arizona
All of the details of this crime Raw
They showed up before the bank open
And there were no customers.
They didn't shoot anyone
Because the the gun they had was a toy gun
They did murder the bank manager when he couldn't open the safe because he only had half of a combination but they didn't
24 * with a letter opener
They attempted to kill the other person who was in the bank
Get the time to cousin employee they've Dawn Lopez
But they only managed to stab her a few times which proved to be
Not lethal but bad
The police didn't around the bank and then the brothers gave up
Another employee showed up and thought that they saw something suspicious going on inside so this other employees
She wrote down the license plate numbers of cars outside
1 mg last
And the police showed up
She gave him the plate numbers and the cops track the brothers down that way
I was just basically taking a real-life case and transpose all of the elements
The bank robbery movies onto it of what happened
No he believes every bank robbery is they opening 5 minutes of The Dark Knight
The Joker showing up everybody in the other address
100% they drove it out and even though there is dust on it
School buses
Nobody was the wiser I would rather if Alex
Just relay the
The plot of Inside Man
I'd love to see him try to explain that plot
Got to Be Wild
Anyway this case is actually really really
And the way it played out in the courts is something that's worth talking about
And it intersects with Alex's ideology but before we talk more about that
Let's see if he understands what happened
Okay cuz he
He definitely doesn't understand the cry
But then what ended up happening
In relationship to their death pain
Penalty
Let's see here is how I'll explain
We will follow
In the world
Court of Human Rights
So that's what Alex so
Ginsberg after this case was howling
The people naturally I saw the best minds of my German generation executed
So-so
Then
Justice Ginsburg Ginsburg
Well
Constitution. The window we got to follow the EU we waste on the go-ahead
On the day that Walter Legrand was set to be executed Germany filed with the international court of justice seeking a provisional
Court order so the US would pause the execution
The icj did give this provisional order
From there the Supreme Court decided that they didn't have any jurisdiction
Hear this provisional order since it was the state of Arizona that was carrying out the execution
And the federal courts
A lawsuit brought by another country against
What's the state right
A bunch of argue
Even flew around about whether or not executing the men would violate
Vienna convention
The u.s. party seem to take the position that international law wasn't legally binding
Heather the actor
Being
Word actually violations of this convention
Yeah then in 2001 the icj ruled that the US had violated rules about Consular relations
Because the Legrand brothers were never told by Arizona law enforcement that adds
German National
They have the right to
Contact the German consulate for help
Yeah I did
Informed of that ability to
Bummer eventually contact the consulate the delay was argue to have hindered Germany's ability to
Protect its Nationals interest
It wasn't the case of Ginsberg just saying that we need to bow down to International Court
Ebix it was a situation where the icj determined that the US had violated an agreement that we entered into willingly
With other government signed it
Yeah
And if it's
It's a bit more complicated than the presentation that Alex
Does making
Obviously
Because he doesn't know what happened
That is that is
Just kicking and screaming about the idea that
People respect the opinions of other
Yeah yeah especially when it's there
Nationalism
Yeah
Yeah and Germany was probably like
Don't
Kill people
That's I mean we don't do it I think there is an interesting
Sort of
Discussion to be had about the German Nationals
Aspect of it cuz I lived in the United States
Essentially their whole life
Technicality
But I don't know how meaningful it is in terms of like
The
Like refuting the circumstances
Well in terms of
Change
And eventually how much people
AppleCare
Is very little I
12 years later and Alex's essentially forgot all the
Details about crime all the details of the Court thing that happened
It's just
Yeah Beldum
Weird situation to have to have like six
Courts
Just argue
Made-up nonsense back and forth at each other
Like. We can't do this because of
Some dude
Arizona Phoenix Arizona going to kill this guy anyway
Call Beth
C 150 years ago
Sorry
So Alex believe that all these European courts and all this stuff it's all
Kangaroo court
You know that term comes from
Australia
Alex knows
Oh yeah
Call boy
The police
The people of the island
Nation
A kangaroo court
Side issue
Why do we say
He loves that but
Yes I've read all of Carroll Quigley
Really get excited for toilet reading
Bugatti characterize this book reader
This is not where Kangaroo Court comes from
It's an expression with a definite American origin although the kangaroo itself is deeply associated
I'm sure when you were just randomly guessing a classroom
So there's a number of theories about how this term came to popularity but none of them are close to it Alex has a
One is that in the early 1800s
In an area of Vicksburg Mississippi called the kangaroo District
Answer the name stock from that you wanted. People believe
Another theory is that the term comes from the characterization of these courts
Jumping to conclusions much like a kangaroo Woodshire
The third idea has to do with these amateur trials over being held
And the California Gold Rush
These were primarily for prosecuting Claim Jumpers
Okay so there was okay
Kangaroos again
So none of these
Involved
Mike McCarthy
That's what we're saying about the Magna Carta appealing to a non-american
Tatoosh indocumentado
You might as well be on Arrow painting about how 13 states make it illegal to ride a horse on Tuesday or whatever done
He's a f****** child
Who fuc
Exact
That's the level of like Source he's relying on for history lesson
Silas take some calls
And one of them
This guy
He he
He's just
It's normal to
Feel helpless
In the circumstances in the world
Promoting out
There we go
And then we get a little bit of a cameo
Very special animal
Infowars
Prison Planet
And handing out to your website
And elsewhere but get off
I guess that's really all we can do
That's my parrot actually I guess it is a neocon yeah
Haha neocon parrot that's funny
I appreciate that very funny lower-tier SNL sketch
For sure
I guess the joke is the Neil concert
Just for pizza and I would assume so I guess that's probably what they're going somewhere
It's not the first time the parrot interrupted
The call by the way
Weird
Disorder consistent thing where
The solution is always promote Alex
Right really stick it to the globalists are do things that
Bring more people into my Revenue stream
Does that make them feel like they're doing
What they must give them that feeling of
I am doing something to fight the global and it's not just like me
Being part of a multi-level marketing
It's not me propping up a propaganda
And I think the reason is because Alex does all that stuff about how like
Hey my movies at a 90% rate in waking people up you must think like
Well then why do we get this message the more people will wake up
Sure has opposed
To the more people will
Give Alex rating
I'm so Alex
Another call from a guy who is anti-nra now
Nice to know that
Hang out to dry
Dirty laundry
Play I love America now
For our gun rights
And you're one of those
Greater than all of this
That's what's going on
And all people really
Blind
What's going on to
Articulate
Illustrates how helpless Alex has made his listeners
Everything I was just covered so far on this episode is completely fake and based on nothing
Is all about the Court's being told what to do by Foreign International legal bodies as a load of s*** based on him making
Things up about an op-ed that he didn't read
The entire fear about gun confiscation is based on a bill that's me
It's languishing in committee
For the last 3 months with no ax
Actions taken
He's done nothing but misinform and yet this call her experiences what Alex is doing is informing him
Really a testament to the power of branding
What's really remarkable
Just color is saying that Alex is a hero in informing the people about threats to their gun rights
And the NRA is not a good organization
But if you've been paying attention to Source Alex is basing his entire coverage of bush
Intending to re-up the assault weapon
Openspan
Eat these basing it on the legislative action press release put out by the NRA
He's relying on them for talkin
Points and yet he and installers are pretending like they're not doing
Anyting
The support gun rights
Yeah it is it is interesting to me
And also intensely disappointing end
And horrific but
It does feel like all of the butt
Is that they've been pushing for like
The past 50
All of those conservative button
Get people to
To do things that
Like okay so not only do we just want people to support us we want certain people that do support us
Vocally say that they don't support its end-to-end
All of these buttons can be pressed in the only thing that
Difference is just a principal lot harder now
You know
Like they haven't developed new techniques
They're mad at a videogame level
Smashing these button
Yeah yeah
And I think it's it's interesting to be able
To go back in
Ncv sort of
The more finesse
So Alex
Skip another call
And this this called
Is the press the s*** out of me
What's this
Google business
People there about what
What was going on
Happening
Look up your website
Find out later
And no man that
Derek
Perlier
Tell your later
I remember you you tell me about
What was going on
I had to go see a shrink
I told you what was going on
It got took your brain took it out
Problem
Call Gary Wright
Such a bummer
If you believe this caller
He ran into somebody who our year prior he had gotten into like Infowars type
Material
And the guy was like I had to go
The therapy
And then this is like oh no it's a sign of weakness
Taking care of his mental health
Could probably you know
This is indicative of somebody who got into this and it just went down
Terrible
Rabbit hole
Well I mean it's actually a very encouraging story really the interpretation
It's being given depressing
That is the people who left the Colts and they're like I can't believe those apostates
How could they do that how could they go get therapy and live
Well develop life
Yeah
Terror
Bummer
Like I don't know Auto real level that the damage that this is also doing is encouraging people who are listening
To experience
Any instinct
To Veer away from
Infowars as that
And not just that
Any
Doesn't necessarily mean
Infowars help it could just be like
Hey man I have been really depressed for the past soon they'll they're like no.
Still dig out your brain yeah they might try and get you off of the Infowars you know why you're depressed
A warring enough
Promote promote Alex more Jesus but it's
It's for Alex and he gets
So Alex that has a weird analogy that he makes
That he thinks he can use to deprogram left
Who are against
God help man I'm scared what if he gets me
He's not he's not going to and then he has one of the saddest weirdest
I've heard in a long time
Anna Gunn
Monopoly
I want
Job
Herbal healer Academy
I don't know how many
Thing we never
On real
Dealer.com
Ford.com
He looks like a
Like what he was trying to do was get out of
Describing any of the things she had no idea he was reading this is too long
He had no idea what he was supposed to be selling so you start
How great the pamphlet was all look at the color
It's almost it's almost an anti ad
Where is like
He wanted to say like this is too many pages to sell a good product I'm going to be honest with you
Actually such a bad commercial.
He comes back from break
Doing another's results
Call them
Oh you can get classes
Actual specific
So did he get you
Well
I mean
Here's the problem with that are
It's not
That
Malaga
Metal
What do you mean
Well here's what I was
I was just thinking that Roman centurions did not have guns to begin
True so that was a big problem Alright and then
Yes
A lot of people were f******
King Arms
Monroe
It's just a lot harder
American example
What about the Native American
Example
I'm going to throw this out at you
Maybe the problem
He's not
Fundamentally
But they don't have guns
True there's a deeper
Problem or systemic problem
Right
This is where I kind of come to my point about it not being an
Cuz there was a
Active
Genocide
Whose campaign
Of that against
The people who hit existed and lived here prior to the the calling
That's not happening to Alex and his dumb militia 40
Bounties out on all white p
If that were the case I think things will be a little bit different and also if there were just like
Common Sense type gun reforms and we're going around in foot
Time
The colonists
Then I don't think it would have been
A problem
I will say that
If there are bounties out on left
Just sitting for years
I might buy a
Until there are literal bounties out on anyone who believed similar things to be
I don't think
And also let's not forget that the Trail of Tears and Indian Removal Act
The only good presidents in US history
Really care too much about whatever
Sort of bizarre Garnet argument
Yeah
You know
You think
That you wouldn't harm an American Indian but my favorite President killed most of them
See
Now what do you think about Gunn good point yeah you got me
Cool
So
I have a surprise guest to Pops in
This is this was weird this caught me off-guard
Diaz
Agave
New homeowner
Interrupt
Programming have a good program
DNA for me fingerprints
Erector spinae
Driver's license
UPS science news
Preparation of
It's also we're going to be on my website Maybe
Find a public providing School
This came out of nowhere
Want something came up earlier on the show at all
That's a real strange things
For somebody to call in and be like Alex
Did you know that a horde of Pegasus are flying over the country to start murdering all of us
Do posted on the website already
Remember like his wife was
Basically
Running a whole lot of Infowars
Back at this point
Yep radio show called call to decision radio
He's not really a figure in Alex's world anymore
That's really strange since he's pushing all the same s*** like covid vaccine conspiracy than anti-abortion
Extremism
You think they'd still be like really tight
I don't know okay
One of his guests is
Coach Dave daubenmire complete lunatic who we've covered a couple times
More bizarrely though
In the last week he had Larry Pratt on his guess the guy from gunownersofamerica
That's only weird because I haven't seen Larry Pratt on Alex's show in a bit
It feels like
He's not on my Alex's gunship talking Rolodex
And I suspect
Because Ted Nugent's there for that
And Alex is nothing if not a strfkr over the
Alex
He wants to take more calls
Buddy cat
Because there's no
Call
Be covered
Do that
Cuz I want to play
Wait what
What is vertigo
What are some plugs
That was a rollercoaster ride of what the what the agenda is going to be I have no idea what's going to happen
I'm sorry I can't take calls I'm going to do some plugs I'm going to talk to Carol from Indiana
But he does get to them headlines on some news
The news
Much and it's because the show grinds to a f****** halt when he's reading headlines
It's just horrible the energy is sucked out of the show entirely
When he's talking to callers or riffing around and making
Some stuff up and yelling it's kind of fun but they're not that old reading headlines of being like
Are we even doing the reading things that actively disagree with his
Point as
Yeah
Normally he does so much more preparation via does regular
Stories
Don't worry
Do you believe
What are the major Russian
Iranian
Okay
Well
That's ones
I mean that's a low bar
Sure you did not clear that
Not still thinks it's saddam's kids death was faked
Yeah we're fake
And that Saddam
Is living in Belarus
So
Good good
This was something he consistently
Has been
Reporting and saying he believes
It's nice to know that he's always
Trusted Russian
Intellivision because they would have him
Oh yeah well yeah he was Gaston like a roni and
TV shows
I think the amputee on RT inch it so like
Trust those
Media spheres cuz they accept
So are you telling me that it's entirely possible if not probable that it one point in time
There were several Iranian Infowars
Yes
Death Valley
Yeah so you're smoking news
What a weird thing to be
This one
Not good
Continuing
Before
Movie on Delta
Because
The corrupt
And
So this wasn't the criticism the Jewish groups had the criticism wasn't just coming from Jewish groups
There were
Whole Lotta anti-semitic tropes that at least
In that movie and there's just a foundational problem of trying to make one story out of the four gospels that
People have suggested
Mel Gibson should just not have tried
To do that
Didn't they win best adapted screenplay
Gibson's a Holocaust denier in his claim that the second Vatican Council
The one where I was
Decreed that the Jews were not responsible for Jesus's death
What's a secret plot
Orchestrated by the Masons and the Jews
W Whittier
This is absolutely ridiculous and the Holocaust it's all maybe not all fiction but most
He was asked
Quote why do the
Jews construct Holocaust museums
There are too many survivors
It's just a gimmick to collect the money
They have to go where there is money
And here's another quote of his
Quotes they cannot admit they were wrong
Riverfront
To Killing Jesus for all of history is the Jews still actively a
Play Christian
He is
Score by being a Jew he's anti everyone else
That's one of the Wilder things that I've ever heard of a person say out loud
In 2010 Winona Ryder told the story about meeting Mel Gibson
Jewish people came up in conversation and he asked her quote
You're not an oven Dodger are you
This language and worse was reported to have been used regularly by Mel Gibson reported by Joe
Joe eszterhas
A screenwriter who was working with Gibson on a film that never got made
He also said the Gibson called the Holocaust
Quota mostly a lot of horseshit
Of course in 2060 yelled about how Jews are responsible for all the wars in the world when he got pulled over for a DUI
Was that
Seems like this is
Family
Maybe there were a lot of anti-Semitic trope
In The Passion of the
If you watch the movie and you don't know who made it it's still a bit affected
There are some decisions that are like
You consider
Who made at
Okay
Yeah presidential
You remember how many youth groups were bussed in to see that movie and all those
Children wear jeans
Hollywood antisemita
Tough
Good to see that Mel Gibson still getting somewhere
Anyway
Have some thoughts
About
I don't know how else to put it
Navigate agenda
Promotion
I want to make advertisement
Oh my God over
Concomitant
This article that Alex is talking about is about how successful Queer Eye For The Straight Guy
People want to buy product placement taimane
Right I don't know Vidal Sassoon products
Fashion product of some sort would be
Yes
Clothing line or you are
Stuff is what this is talking about it's not like
All of the government is paying
Gay content
This is popular people enjoy it
It's getting high ratings out to people who want to sell their product
What's our buying time on this
You're just wrong the entire family
If it work
For the Bush family
Will & Grace would never have made it to air
Fully funded that first step
So do you know that
You know that
I put the first season of Will & Grace was on
PBS
I forgot.
Look man this is ridiculous like
He's pretending this isn't just like
Commercial
Somehow offended by
Buying add Time auto program
That features homosexual people is somehow an Insidious conspiracy for him
This is this is pathetic
Yeah yeah you know
The attitude where we're pretty convinced we were pretty
I convinced that the attitudes from even the far-right had kind of changed over the years
It's been 20 years
Not there haven't been
Ton of hurricanes because gay people are fine now you know like it
And then you just realized it
Stop.
Talking about it or slightly different what exactly
Play they didn't they didn't change
Maybe less overtly like
Identifiably hateful
And then just sort of
Keeping keeping the fire going
Underground
Yep brutal
So here's the the end of our adventure on August
West 4th
I think it's just kind of like a nice
Thing that resonates to the present
Call
Portland
Alex is saying the false
Flag attack
Power grids going down everything we're about to happen so they can blame it on
Yeah it says all that kind of s*** for the last 20 years
Yep pretty regularly so
Alex's prediction
Constantly good kids
When you've only got one response to things it does happen over and over and over again doesn't
Yay
It's
Careers bad
20 years
Damn
Man imagine if we
Still did the novelty drinks thing
Mrs. Davis
Bats I'm struggling to come up with Breitbart
Things are getting less bright before time it's not your fault it's not your fault
Is good
LOL boy brings us to the end of our 2000
3 Adventure
Dele
Will be back on Wednesday with the present episode
Maybe he'll have like a scrapbook of
Pictures from his trip
Maybe he'll have a 15 about running into a globalist weird outdoor location
Sure certainly not a Hots
Cuz you. Matt
Automatic story already accidentally wander into a gemstone
Gun store something along that be like a new AG Store got a name that he doesn't quite understand
He thinks it's going to have like
Hot peppers are Barbara
Q sauce
Everybody's
Just looking at gems that
Might make your day by
You know
And then he thinks it's a conspiracy
Nothing jams actually work
I would like
Sittoo's on the West Coast
I'd like to hear about him going into like the woods
And I Oregon or Washington
Running into a globalist then introduces into Sasquatch
I'd like a Sasquatch.
What if he was at West Sasquatch humping
Who is Bobcat Goldthwait
Yeah that's the s*** right there the only reason he went to Florida wasn't
The Oaks hang on to that he was looking for the skunk ape Oh I thought it was looking for the Loch Ness Monster
Really doesn't have a sense of dread Bilderberg
That's what's really going on it would have been a better career for life
I want to find all these beings like I got to find out
The Scream
Animals that don't exist
Which Cryptids are into the Second Amendment the Mothman Mothman balad man could be
I carry what else we got these for sure there is a frozen North they got a hunt absolutely
I got rifles
Haha what else do we get our boils in the 90s they don't like guns
They can fly they don't need them
They planned on people that was most of the show
Trying to think of other cryptic
Why am I having trouble
I don't like Cryptids I might just probably like
Cindy we will
We're also on Twitter
We are it is at knowledge underscore I also forgot that I had so
Are we going to go
That's right
A wonderful dreamy creamy summer
And now here comes
The sex robot
Holding
Alex