Important
I have great respect for its knowledge by knowledge I'm sick of them posing as if through the good guy
Knowledge fight
Alex Jones
I guess it's the same things out.
What is Chicago
Summer days
I'm going to take 100° something
It's a mess man we don't have Cooks right on the ground
Had we all had
That heat wave
Last week it was
Yep just
Complete disaster
One day like Sweater Weather
X100
This is a mess reminds me of how it wasn't like in my youth
You know before whenever everybody was like global warming there still winter
There was always a bit of seasonal variability
But it does definitely feel different
Normally anecdotal like oh you know the past it's not like the way it used to be this really does know there's
I thought I need to go pick up a
Prescription and I am intentionally waiting till after we work order
As if the sun will be down by then
Exactly at 9 p.m. or something but
Yeah I'm still trying to bank on that
Fingers crossed
I wish you the best
I'm not sure if my bright spot is but I guess it's
For whatever
What is similarly low stakes
I told you know my partner made to the end of the school year
This was the first real day
That she did not have an alarm clock on
No I wake up at 6:30 I cannot go back to
To sleep sure
So
This
Morning
I slept in until 8:45
Greatest day of my greatest day of my life on Earth
Crazy late I don't know if I've seen that side of 9
In a while
I've been off at 8:40
Congratulations hope you enjoy whatever. Of time.
Somebody else's maybe not been waking up early all right Alex Jones
What is a happened
Yeah we expected him to be back on Sunday but he's been
Still gone
Say he was going to be back
We're recording this on Tuesday have been back today I'm not entirely sure
I was gone Sunday gone Monday
Angel talk a little bit about that and some other stuff
But I really do I really hope he flag
Is Hangover missed a flight
Let's
Do first doctor Marvel doctor marbles liquid liver tonic thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk
Thank you so much you are now a policy wonk
Is a appropriately long
An apology and a happy birthday
Do Ethan from Mimi your future wife
Supposed to be
I don't know sorry
I'm a policy wonk
Rodger Stones bikini wax
Thank you very much. I said that no message did include an apology that I had to say it so
Let It Go
Next Nicholas are one of the top box
Engineers in the country and erstwhile tequila sunset
Text confusing as it is almost pleasing
Baba Yaga the only friend Alex deserves
Thank you so much
I have
Risen above
Miami
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f*** the horse you rode in on
All your s***
Maybe later on West Broad
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
Maybe I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back here again
I apologize to
Yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
We'll never know if he's better today cuz he's walking nowhere to be found a boy he's in the Wind
Man if he fled that be great I doubt it
Ohio
We have a couple of Clips here from Monday's show is hosting
The fact that Alex is not there
And so here is the beginning of
A little bit of a breakdown discussion of
Where the f*** is Island
And you're wondering where is Alex Towing
You told me Alex would be back
Well yes
The plan was for Alex to be back
Problem is we're living in Biden's America
What
Collapsing civilization
That were in right now and so part of the
Symptom
Collapsing Society
Are collapsing civilization is
Flight cancellations and what is being now called
Travel Army
Getting a man travel Armageddon price
Canceled flights in Alex's apparently this is a reason that he's not into
I think you probably just partied a little too hard
By the way by the Russian regime
Do you need exact same hiding place that Saddam was not the real ground
I think I think he probably just got drunk and missed a flight
Conspiracy though according to Allen
I like how we can somehow condescending towards us like we're stupid for thinking
How dare we think that he should be back this America
Well
Cancellations are ahead
Sure it's a chore
Alex is f******
So rich so goddamn by your own f****** play this is a
The level of irresponsibility that is shocking to come from a celebrity and media personality
And why is Owen delivering this instead of the phone
You drunk cuz he missed his flight and decided
F*** it or if he's in Belarus no Wi-Fi
A little bit more
So I'm not trying to
Talked at length about why Alex isn't in that's why he's not in
The real story here is that
It's just yet another example
Oh how everything is collapsing now
In just a year-and-a-half of democrat control and the Biden wife
Everything
Collapsing
Including
The ability to fly
Stress-free
And easily get from one airport to the other
This is fun for Owen and all but like I don't understand exactly how we're going to make this Biden's fault
Cancelled because of weather
Cheyenne like
I guess that's
Possible no that's
We're at the level of like
Oh that's Zeus for you you know I got struck by lightning what you going to do that Zeus
Do you know like you're just you're just saying a name to give cause to your troubles
Insulate heightened levels of cancellation
It was just a
It was being experienced in the United States
Across-the-board
In the world's right still running rampant through everything
Transmission is f******
Up
You know
And flight load is is up
And there were multiple holiday consideration right
Yo it's just it's not the only thing I can really think that could really like
Stick to hear is
X putting out bad vibes that makes sense I would accept that
That almost undercut your own argument when you say within a year-and-a-half of Biden
Is it
It's like
Fine is not done shittin a year-and-a-half so if you're complaining about now because of
Maybe it's cuz of the
Recent past
No no Biden's destroyed the airline industry
. it's kind of amazing
And a lot of money in the military
I know where he is doing
So I'm doing today we're going to be talking about August 5th 2000
Three on the past but I have to be honest
Yeah it's not a very interesting episode
There is not a ton
That goes on
So thankfully
Something came to my attention
Okay I would like to give a hat tip to my friend Ali
About this
This to my attention
Sing
From 1998
It is uncovered
From the internet
That in 1990
Was hired
Or maybe I don't know maybe wasn't even paid for this who f****** nose haha
But Alex Jones
Did
A public service announcement out of here
Teenager
Trouble
Impatient
Any credit
Gina Was Naive about the
Responsibility
Personal finance
Nothing can
Show me more important
Show a person starting out in life
Getting a proper
Personal finance
Work
Teenagers aren't
Notorious
Forgiving into their desire
Without thinking ahead to the concert
Before they know it
Teenagers
In over their heads
No more money
The lake and pay
And have to turn to parents
Relatives
Or outside credit
Counseling agent
For help
But that does
Doesn't have to have
School responsibility and credit card management for teens
I don't know
I don't know what
Could bring me more just like simple pleasure
So stupid
Free Infowars Alex had already had like a public access
I think you found it in for
So this is this is before that but like
Obviously a weirdo
But yeah this is I was a PSA
Those made by company called Lucerne media and they shot it at the CBS
Studio in Austin and Alex is the host
For whatever reason real there's weird
Painfully done Recreations of like
A-Team
Who got a credit card and went to the mall and talk like a kid could get everything and
You know it's just a fact fired alright alright this is a bit like finding out that girdles did a PSA for Nottely
Leaving your pets in the class you know like wait what
Suit
Super ripped Alex Jones. He's not all that ripped in my face
Okay but driving the middle stage bodybuilder and sick next weirdo
Keys and he's standing in front of
Would be a green screen but with like a bunch of bills and credit check
Post a link to the video of it cuz it only has about 300
Earthquake
Is at the end of the video
There's a list
Of
The other videos in this series
At what time is called herpes it with you for life
Spektru
Smoking and all the biggest issues
It's an open question whether or not Alex hosted all of them
And I think that there's a good chance that he did ohmygod
Now
I was able to find
The smoking one
Haha at a library
In Danvers Massachusetts
Start a VHS tape
We've got to the show Sarah Shahi
There's a friend who is doing VHS to DVD conversion is that right are they in Danvers Massachusetts
You could call somebody and have them mail it to you
Maybe but I don't know if his library in Danvers is going to just be us
Card for that Library
Danvers Massachusetts
Haha
We'll find a way
Maybe we have some enterprising listeners in Danvers Massachusetts
I believe there's another copy of it in Idaho at a library of America
I want to find all of these and see if Alex has the impact
We host of all of them because
It would be truly bizarre
To to see him talking about the dangers of smoking and herpes
The problem is if you get all of them together in one place then the dragon will emerge annually
Granted a wish
Write my wish will already have been granted
You and the dragon just a Thursday
Stare at each other for the rest of time fine with that.
The upside of this is it's pretty hilarious
This exists
Inside of it is
Alex is pretty boring
As a PS a pitchman
The Lola
Then increase the
Poppy later on
This is
Legal notice
Famous carefully
Is my mama
And you missed the July
Due date
Will charge you a
Dollar
Another
To make a zoo day
The holiday
When do male
These are the kind
Add up
$10 piece
Cost
Hundred dollars
In the long run
Pretty boring easy easy with dollars
Tell you grants from the government man
Is it
What was Vince I think is really interesting about this is that like
He's not yelling about fiat currency
I'm talking about the Federal Reserve about financial issues literacy 14th
Needs to know more
About big fat I'm going to be honest I had several overdraft fees when I was 19 years old and
I could have been served by this BS a educational program it should have made its way
Problem was I didn't see Alex Jones at the right time in my life that's what's gone
When he was giving helpful messages
But read your pill
Nomads
Imagine a world where this show at you were like
And I know everything about Alex Jones that I'm like the only thing I know about Alex Jones
Is how not to get overdraft fees hot ttr90 but Alex Jones if you saved me $70
When I was a team
Okay alright
I just think that it would really funny if they gave him a little more creative control able to be like
Read the Bell jar that you know you pay your bill on time and also three Senators Federal Reserve
My friend Ron Hall about
Iamgold
I don't know I think that would be a bore fun way for him to go is to turn his full conspiracy powers on just
Overdraft fees and be like
Method Man let's get into the weeds all right there's no reason that they should be able to charge you overdraft fee
They're creating this feed order to make more profits for them and if you know anything about the Bible you'll know that Jesus
Said that you sorry is wrong I think if I remember correctly that the big issue that Al Franken champy
And in that book why not me
Has fake run for president a president one of his big issues was ATM fees
Honestly getting rid of ATM fee
Bino maybe there's something to that
The grief
Warning
In this TSA and I think that
They speak of off weird knowing his career trajectory
That $10
Car with a bad check
End up causing
$60 arm
Give that check also
Other chick
One of the most
Important
In life
Good credit rate
As the world
More popular
Computer
Important
And what
We are
A person
The first thing
Check Buy
Warriors car salesman other people
Make the city
It seems very weird but
He's stressing so much like you've got to keep your credit rating good
The social credit score that he's a little worried about liking
Hey your potential employers are going to check your credit score in order to see if you should be hired
Used to be furious about that
How is it that you can read the John Birch Society and still do a PSA for financial literacy
I'll tell you how
Because at the end of the day the John Birch Society is more about
Then it is about anything
In 1998 Alex was
Desperate
Nordstrom
Psa's for things
Essentially
Incompatible with his worldview I mean he asked his dad for a radio show that's pretty incompatible with his
Pull yourself up by your boat show
Ultimate really is
You know this include some advice that he should have taken himself out no
The primary way to
To avoid all of the
The problems we
Don't call Scotia
Spend more money
Considering it has a business that 250 billion dollars in the hole
His own company
Or whatever to spill
Meto ironic a little bit
I don't fully believe in the simulation because
As if it were real then we would have heard him be like
Listen
I'm sorry but
Columbine really happened and if anybody ever claims that a school shooting is a false flag in the future
They're really f***
That would be that would be too on-the-nose be really weird about that
Coincidence goddamnit I get what you're saying it would be
Evidence of larger powers
So anyway that was just a little bit of a delight to to experience
Had this out a little bit cuz like I said
August 5th
Not much
Not much going on a couple of
Actually important things
To bring up and it's good to have them
Kind of in the immediate time after we talked about the last episode cuz they relate a little bit
A the first thing in this actually does this links back to his episode from August
West 4th
Donald
On
Order in Spanish
He got the videos
World Order
Quite a few other
No offense to Gary Busey but I wouldn't use them as a citation when I was trying to list people who believe the same crazy stuff
Bible Essure
Busey's famous associating him with your ideas kind of makes me trust your ideas even less
It's fun that Alex's thing that the Gibson family knows about the New World Order though
We talked about hunting Gibson Mel's father on ended
Horrible anti-semitic comments on our last 2003 episode
But this actually deserves a little revisiting
The point that Alex is making is at Hutton Gibson knows about the New World Order
This definitively means that Alex is asserting that he and Hutton Gibson are of the same mind about this globalist
Pharisee and I feel huge f****** problem
In an interview from 2004 on a show called speaker piece
Hutton Gibson did expound on his thoughts about the New World Order
And here's what he said oh boy
Quote the Federal Reserve and those foreign bankers who owner currency in charges for it
Before in Bankers who run the international Reserve like the Rothschilds and their allies in this country like the Rockefellers who were
Jews and others who on the money
There's a book out not too long ago listing the big Jewish families in the country which lists the Rockefellers
Has Jewish and there was no
Add another point he says quote
I don't know what the Jews agenda is accepted it's all about
Control there after one world religion and one world government
Alex is an idiot but he's not this kind of an idiot
He knows with Hutton Gibson think so New World Order is and he's signaling his agreement here
On the one hand biscuits
Be indicative of Alex's own crypto anti-Semitism but that would be difficult to prove definitively
It's easy to point to a mountain of circumstantial evidence
Inside his head
What I think is more important is that you better believe that any anti-semitic or Neo-Nazi leaving listeners and no
Know what Hutton Gibson believe
And hearing Alex Express that they're on the same page it serves as a wink to that Community they well you might say globe
Blessed and pretend he's not a bigot
He's only doing that because he can't get away with saying what he actually knows
Believe
Alma Guerra cuz they'll get in trouble
And just to clarify you like I hadn't had been self
Publishing a newsletter titled the war is now since 1994
So a lot of his beliefs
They they were the Private Matter even if it's a lot of it didn't become the subject of mainstream public debate
Until around the time of Passion of the Christ
He was still a figure that was known in those circles right all right
So I find this to be a little f***** up
It does feel like
Alex has
Like I
Chaotic you know those
You know those alignment chart see no lawful good local news like
Alex just has all the chaotic alignment locked up he's got like
Mike Busey on hand he's got the Nugent right next to
He's got Charlie Sheen like nothing anything chaotic blank
Alex has a hole
Call Dre of people to feel back on I'm good
Kinky fried
I mean
Bill Ayers
Is he chaotic though Weather Underground vertical chaotic chaotic chaotic
He's very knocked out he's very lawful
Lawful good
Borderline lawful neutral anything he just showed up one time for a bizarre interview
Christopher Walker
Can how about that he showed up there was an accident
Cooking with the Bells
So on our last episode Alex talked a little bit about
This idea that Jay Leno was going to have a makeover by the
The Queer Eye For The Straight Guy
Yeah
Touches back on this story but
Wheatley change
About how
The story that he was
Covering yesterday
On the last episode
EB with
He messed up but now it's completely
The actual article is about how Queer Eye For The Straight Guy was pulling big ratings and sponsors were paying a lot
To get product placement on the show
It was also mention the Jay Leno was going to get a makeover from them
Obviously the reasons Jay would want to do this is because he wants to associate himself with something popular and make himself appear to be more
More with the time
Or maybe he has an agent with a connection to the producers of queer right whatever the case
It's a marketing opportunity for him
Alex didn't understand this story or he willfully misrepresented it on
The last show that he's created a touchdown for the audience
He's writing a completely new story that has no connection to reality at all
Apparently now
This article is supposed to be about gay
Paying for product placement on Jay Leno show
I'm not sure what that even means but the point is to imply that there's an organic popularity to anything that involves Gabe
Hey people anytime you see anything that involves gay people existing on TV or in pop culture it's only
Only because special interest groups have
Paid off the producers to include that content
This isn't this blunt and clearly bigoted is him just saying that he hates gay people but this is no less homophobic
The mentality that is advancing is one that really does look at the public existence and popularity of media-related
The lgbtq issues or people
As a conspiracy with subversive aim
It's disgusting and this kind of thing should really be well remembered when Alex is doing is bulshit song and dance
In the present-day about always tolerant on gay issues but at same time
Violently auntie transhire
He's just faking whatever tolerance he present until it's safe for him to attack gay people again
That's
The song and dance the game that he's doing is
Pathetic yeah and it should be
It should be so simple and easy
To see through any kind of like all the gay agenda with cultural
Fine
I mean
Listen to a queen song Do you like that or not like that what do you
I would watch it out of culture
What do you want out of culture guess what
If you look at it
And honestly it's going to be a lot guy Freddie Mercury was only because the gay groups made him
Do it think I get them off of your favorite songs
40% made by somebody on the lgbtq space
A.
. at least
Yeah
What he's doing is is pretty f***** up
And when you really look at it and you recognize that the story that he's basing this on is
Just about like
Companies wanting to pay for
Product placement space on a popular
It's
It's remarkable that he's able to make this
Level of homophobic content of something
That has nothing to do with absolutely
Videos of this content
I got it could go back so much further just a listening somebody listening to like the f****** shadow
And hearing an ad for just
Baby wipes me and like all these women are putting ads on the goddamn stuff like I don't know
I bet they did I bet they did I bet there was a women's pant sad but maybe entire country explode for
A couple of weeks
Yep
Probably Christ
This isn't all that meaningful but I thought it was
Kind of funny
About what
DeWalt
LOL
A good to talk to you
How you doing
Listen.
I just had a little power
He says he doesn't know
Who You Are
Business
Book
Being advertised
Sonic website
And
Explain to him
Mistreated people on
Tim Storey
I've had
So
That's heartbreaking
As heartbreaking as wife he knows who I am
11 is that about it now I know I would feel I would feel pretty terrible if somebody was your first sex
Ex-girlfriend she doesn't even remember your name anymore
That would break my heart
That's about the same
How much he cares
So this call
And we go to commercial
Commercial
Here's where
Alex says
About
Very
Griffin
Overall
I'll call her I called and said that he had a personal conversation with Joseph Sarah that was insulting to me
I'm going to take you in one of my
Primary sources of information
Tiberius
F******
No reason to do that just had to just
Could not stop himself from their likes no reason to believe that this color actually talk to Josie why aren't you
Nobody gives a s*** how dare you know what that daily sucks now
How about that
But you also is doing this so strategically where he can still like except
Like just using WorldNetDaily contact good writers still
Like a progressive DVD you know like all I love everything that they stand for I don't like the word Progressive or DEA so I'm going to get rid of them
It's it's entirely just a guy who's been wounded
Just lashing out excuse
Just stabbing people such a sad man
How do you spell pathetic
It is not even close to the levels of pathetic we're about to
Oh no it gets worse
I would say a large portion of this episode is
Circling around the idea of a Malcolm in the Middle
Episode that Alex has not watch
But someone emailed him about
Okay now hold on
If I understand this correctly
Pre break
Bad Cranston in
And that's what Infowars
A lot of it yet
So here is Alex
Complaining about this
Episode of
Malcolm in the Middle
Broadcast
You might
I brought up
Dwight military
No way to find those out
Breville
There is just like I've noticed a trend that I have kind of now
I'll listen to Alex on my response in my throw-up man
People doing
This is ridiculous oh yeah
So this episode of Malcolm in the Middle is called garage sale
Promise of the day
How
They're doing
They're having a garage sale strategy
Through the garage he finds his old radio transmitter that used in college
Talk about goings-on on campus
That's what you got to do to be cool yeah it's so he tries to recreate his old youth.
So he he
He takes back on the title of Kid Charlemagne
And starts ranting about that off
Kid Charlemagne he's sitting in like his backyard doing this
Doing this show
Get pulled over by the police for running a stop sign
Haha something to do with his show
And
He creates an entire campaign
Against this the single stop sign
About the stop sign
Does not say the military industrial complex
He says the military-industrial country club complex
Because at the stop sign that the country club my coat in
Not even the garage sale ends up happening
Yeah
I had somebody buys the transmitter
And so the dad
Gets in the car with the person to put the transmitter
So he can keep doing his show
And then if there's a black van following following them for doing it on
Unlicensed radio show
I need to do with like the contento putting out
He doesn't get dragged off into a van right that's the that's the central humor of it is that
He thinks it has something
Things to do with the content is it actually does it's just at the Pirate Radio Show that's not my
So if you were say somebody who I don't know has a radio show that you feel like
Was lambasted
Did buy that
Particular program the only reason that you would be lambasted
Where if utery
Where to react
Did the exact same way that
Yes all is almost like Alex's embodying the thing that's being satirize
Act which is right really sad it's really sad
Right and I hit you in the face you're like I got hit in the face by
About a clown with a pie that's hilarious but whenever you run as fast as you can toward the pie and then slam
Why did the Cubs do this happen
Right and then you scream butt of the sea
Eyes are always in my face
It's just pathetic
Man
I do
Can you imagine
How
Ridiculous it would be if every time I saw it like a
Movie with a podcast on it and they were like this idiot is an a****** and I was like I'm mad
The reason that you identify with that is if you are an a******
You bet yeah it's a little bit of self-consciousness coming out
Obviously later on there are instances of
TV characters even like Jay Jonah Jameson who are obviously
This is not a 2003
They were.
You'd be something worth satirizing is already like
Sort of an image of a pirate radio host
This did exist
In the Zeitgeist before Ali
Sealab 2021 had an episode of radio host
Newsradio
Something that predates Alex and I was just pretending it's all about himself
Does he's a sad
Sadman past the point where you should be doing psa's about credit card
Well you know be narcissistic about the level of Fame you want not about the level of Fame you have
You know what I'm saying that's why
Caller calls and describes the episode of Malcolm in the Middle
Alex is trying to make this really important
Experience
W Morales
Blue
Well
Garage door
Business
Bi-Mart
Stop sign
Is Alex going to look like
Well I
Far as I can right now
Violation
It's remarkable to think that people feel
Like folks like Alex can't take a joke
Yeah and this isn't even a joke directed at him no no no
Is this is so
F****** stupid yeah
That's that's
That's a radio show where you call into your grandma and explain movies to her
Alex is talking about let's be clear episode of Malcolm in the Middle
Kohler his scene analysis very seriously asking him what do the Men in Black Say
To the father
Yes against get some dialogue deal out of
Why
This is being treated as though it actually happened
Tell me what the Men in Black said
The TV show that we were watch
What did the Men in Black say you mailed me about
Can I have third-hand information of
Jesus
What if
Petty loser
Oh my God
So I'm glad I grew up in the intervening 20 years
I was just two guests on the show one of them is Jack McLamb
Who started the police against the New World Order
I organization Patriot figure
About it right
He does bring up that he hasn't been a cop since 1986
When you were tired cuz he got injured in 1986
And that he says it's 22 years prior but it's 17 years prior
Discrepancy at the recess 22 multiple times
She was born in 1945
And so that means that he retired from the police at 41 years old yeah I believe
Maybe give or take a year
And he was in the military
He was only a cop for like 10 years that he'd been a weirdo
Conspiracy theorist
Cashing in on this career IHOP
Right I always thought like this guy was a company who I am
Decades on the force and then retired with like this expertise and how everything works within the police
Call pretend ears maybe right like I know that's not
Like a short time but
It's not Stolen Valor but it's
It's
You borrowed without asking Valor
With that
Is it appears that he was probably a cop for a very short time got injured on the job and then has received a pension for the past 50
The goddamn years
With which he has running weird to see royalty fairy country
Except for the fact that I was like wait Smith is strange
Always thought that he was a cop much more recently than 1986
Oh man back in my day we used to only follow hunches
Poliisi man I saw this episode of Malcolm in the Middle about a Cop who retired 17 years ago
Wait a second
To his other guests
Is this guy
We talked about this on a 2003 episode
Couple back the policy analysis Market
Was the thing
That was putting together where they would have expert
Who could bet on
The idea of future things that could happen
Like leaked foreign leaders who would be deposed
Things like that it was a market-based approach to
Try to predict Ram
It was not a thing where people can make millions of dollars and Swiss bank accounts but that's the way Alex has covered it
Two Democratic senators
We're really mad about this
And so they brought attention to it and the project
I was canceled for it even beginning what I think you mean to say is that honorable far-right page
Patriots came together and their Louis
Voices were loud enough that
Those two Democratic senators were drowned
They still stop the bill anyway story there probably be told coming years
However Alex has a guy on who is created a parody
Of the policy analysis Market
Run
I want to
Oh hey guess what
Even if the kids didn't get off the ground either but even if it did like
How does this not have the exact same problem that you're complaining about the dod for doing or DARPA for doing
Might have your somebody who's batting on a the government's going to pull a false flag
What's stopping you from doing it
Can't you just do that terrorist attack then cash it on it works the same stupid problem that Alex
Does identifying
Yeah you know when you bring it up like that
It makes sense
But on the other hand
How about we score minor political points for no reason on something that won't happen
Another project is closed
But there is an issue about how ads are set
I would like
Speakers urged his guests
I guess it does explain that
Shut up
Like a horse
So
The awesome
Determined by how may
People
Directions
So freak sample
Call Butch
Which country were going to
Falcon people that are
Hundred dollars each on
Aron
100 people better
Hundred dollars each
North Korea
12:50
In favor of
The Rock
That simple folks
Normal
Produce what the
Pentagon
I hope
The odds that ever
Any given
The collective
Wisdom
The people who are
Cruising in the mark
This is entirely stupid because it actually does the opposite
888 the cuts out the entire point of the policy analysis Market which was
It would only be open to people who have expertise
And then it would be a market-based
Friend
Forecaster in theory based on people who have expertise and a lot of knowledge around
Policy issues around 4 in
Relations issues
By opening it up to people who are just looking to gamble or whatever
To the information that you'd be able to derive from it
The second barely the issue that you have with this is like what country were going to attack next North Korea or Iran
What happens if the house get the money obviously there's a big
Like the house get something naturally get a taste of course otherwise what's the point of running
Really if you look at it is this guy doing an ad for his gambling operation
Grift
What are you talkin
This is one of those
So stupid ideas that you have to stop somebody before they start trying to talk about it
Cuz they are try you can see clearly him
See him like a horse right he's trying to explain it to himself in a way that
Sound incredibly stupid
What is happening
Yeah yeah
Hey here's what we're going to do like that's another thing with the original Pollo
The original pan
You know it's like
That is only something that incredibly smart people would think up
To avoid doing the thing that they already know is the actual solution you know like if you wanted to if you wanted
To do good stuff for everybody you could
But that doesn't make you personally as much money
So let's try eight market-based idea of how to figure out whether or not a war is going to happen
Not like let's not fight Wars
Sprite and it may not be in a surly if a war is going to happen but regions where there is the most likely
Play Outburst
I think that actually this color does
Really highlight or not color
If you was like a collar but he's a gas now it does highlight
How bad of an idea this is
Yeah
The the policy analysis Market itself
Makes sense
Subway
Because it makes sense
Inferior
Yes that's a better way products
Only makes sense
Because of the restricted user pool
It doesn't make sense right
Bass
Is the version that Alex is recovering and Reporting
Drake version of it where it's like
I get rich scheme for me
For people who are whatever
That doesn't make sense
Gambling market for people
Like it it does reveal have dumb
Short squeeze
All the people who bet against the war lost are there
Full like
Isn't this fire me to bring this guy on here to take your money in a different way I just don't understand
Absurd
Sunnyway this episode
Thin
It's like quite bring it too much Beyond in the middle
Not a lot going on and honestly you know with the waiting for Alex to show up I thought
Thought you be back
And so
You know that
Was a bit disappointing
Ipsa
You know certainly coming into my life uniform
Any answer
We said we would have a Wednesday episode
Promising to be back
We deliver
Exactly because
Helicopter
Business hiding out trying to record Another PS a lot of smoke
Come Friday with
I guess we'll see what happens on Friday
If not we'll have something that's a little thicker
Then Alex complaining about Malcolm and the f****** middle
We do indeed it's not right.
We are on Twitter that I'll just go fight and I go to bed Jordan
I need a
Hope you all have a wonderful dreamy creamy summer
And now here comes
Holding
Alex, first in color with huge fan I love your work