Knowledge party.com
Pray I have great respect for this knowledge B
Knowledge
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex Jones question what's up
Today Jordan is not
Today but it will be today when your little angel is in its tonight
Tonight video
Fire Emblem
Dynasty Warriors Style game
Releases I believe midnight
So I may stay up and play a little bit
I am very excited about that
A Dynasty Warriors Style game
These characters
I'm enjoy the s*** out of
I appreciate that in
The patient of this you addicted both of us to a
That is it that I like about this you were like all I'm excited for this game and then both of us
Because of you
Snot
Entirely
Because there is the other Fire Emblem Dynasty Warriors Style game
Another Fire Emblem game
Get some Briley already with the characters in The Dynasty Warriors
Damn that's already out
Oranges
I just gave me three houses at Rio because people said it was really good
And it turns out they were right
I was coming out so shortly
I'm sorry that I've also flick
Look at that apartment was very helpful and I'm not going to go outside for a long
Tell me why would you
Get the f*** out so yeah that's my bright spot I'm excited play
I've not the first time that I have
Pre-downloaded a game
Really like before it came out so it's there
Yeah
I don't know
Lucy will see how that feels on the other side of it
I had that way
I had that one locked and loaded I think you've done
Ff7 remake for sure
I ordered like six months in advance and I was
Refreshing the download every time
Last night
Doctor
Estranged
Very bad movie but also incredibly good movie it was itself
It turns out Sam Raimi was allowed to make
Force of Doctor Strange
The Evil Dead
He's so totally allowed to do a Campbell showed up
Real talk just slammed his head into the Multiverse situation
Yep yep quarter of it Evil Dead
I mean there's a zombie possession like a whole thing it's all in there
Quarter of it everybody like you know half of it is a Marvel movie and you're like fine you're going to shoot
Equalizer what
Rodger sir
World is going to be threatened with blowing up or something
And then the other quarter Was A Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy
So is Mos Def
Hanging around at the moment where they go through the different realities male go poop
You know they didn't even have any recognition to me referencing Mos Def
What do you mean
He was a prefect in the movie of course my friend
Alrighty never got the hang
Well I'm glad you enjoyed the quarter
Of that movie
Today we have an episode to go over
And all I can
Can say is
Finally silac
To the studio
Oh yeah that was good at that is The Rock
But now how would I finally returned
Protracted litigation
Yeah he's back 20 seconds
22nd
You was gone that's a good very little to here
From him even to even interview like call-ins or anyting
Sparse appearances
Give me a lot of stuff
Over that time so I was really excited
Did the jumping
Get down to it
Right we have
Beyond going January 6th Commission
We have
Worsening situation with the Uvalde police response
Absurd
There's a lot that we need to hear what
Got to say about it yeah but it seems kind of obvious to me now that he spent the last two and a half weeks
Licking toads
The only thing that makes
Yeah
Could be tripping on a spirit Quest
I'm just going to say this ahead of time because there is no
Reason to
Tease anybody
He hasn't talked about anything meaningful at all
I was so disappointed
I really hope
Deborah
The board Lucy pulls the football band
B b honestly I was reflecting on it but I was trying to fall asleep last night
In the dark Twilight
I really think this is one of my least favorite we had on the show
There's the constant
Push and pull of like
Alright he's going to be back
Liscio's backup there's important
Things on the docket
And then it's just
The deflating
Yep
I never like to put out like a under an hour episode even if it was not
P. No you are haunted by it
I think it's going to be January 6th Style
Commissioner
We're going to have to get
Witnesses involved were going to see what
Owen's going to zoom in working to be like where the f*** was he why weren't you on top of me
It's going to be revealed to Paul Joseph Watson emails me about not
Doing episodes under an hour
So we can talk business on this
To see what did happen
So first Rodger Stone secret sultry
Thank you very much
Kristina with a K thank you so much you're now a policy wonk
I'm a policy wonk
Robin the prophetic
Opera
The closet King in the big picture boys are behind the Davos group thank you so much right now policy walk
Spider-Man Hills pastry chef specializing in dreamy creamy stachys of Snackeez to eat while you're sick
Calls thank you so much you're now about to walk
I'll take that $100 to do an audio version a version of Cujo thank you
You smart you are now taking credit and no
Dingleberry Borger shorts
Rex with his butt and stuff and such but also his side's a karod
Thank you so much you are now a technic
Four star don't get mad until you're brilliant someone
Sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
Jesus Christ
Sometime
2 seconds into a go wait what is happening
We get back
To Alex
Occupied
Alright
Sitting
Here we go
And then we realized
But maybe something else has been
Been going on
No
Welcome ladies and gentlemen to this live Wednesday June 22nd
Worldwide
Broadcast
In this chair was a great job
Owen Shroyer
Wawa
Dealing what
Operational
Because all
Small companies
Find ourselves
Exercise
The First Amendment
Chair
Absolute attack
This operation
The entire country
Yeah so he's been back
4 days apparently but deleted
Yeah yeah
So unlikely he had two of their stories
This is amazing we need to do with anyone tell the truth ever
No
Turns out my parents are moving out also
Finally can tell the truth
Yeah I don't know what I believe
But Alex's story seems more likely
I meant Owen Sound
It's more likely as a
Cover for him
Being back
And is being like a s*** I got to find a way to make this
100%
Boat stay afloat or whatever like well I'm sure Alex
After having
You told me
To save this
Will not throw me under the bus
Tomate immediately
Won't do that immediately nope first thing he doesn't throw up
And then the other thing that I really enjoy is he's like yeah I like to thank Owen
Great job getting the silent treatment
Best place to put a
Buddy buddy
Going to the beige is Buddy the billionaire or his wife
Nope
The movie star
No you're not going to be
Owen that's how sad it is for you
Nope nope
I'd like to recast
Gilligan's Island does Infowars
Obvious
Alright so we got
Then I think that would make
Corsi would have to be the millionaire
Super Champ X2 crazy but the professor is wife do I have to turn on the recording whenever they do
Video log horse from the reality that's true
Duo
I think
Do professors Rodger Stone
Okay that makes
He's not rich though
Really really trying to get legal defense fund
Astro
I want Gilligan
Tubi
Paul Joseph Watson but this cuz I want to see that silly side I have
Your Castor give to see if there is something like this
This is the first time you're casting
Robin Williams in a dramatic role I walked your moment of British slapstick
When I was younger
I feel like there's just a mr. beams Iditarod
Begging me to come out
Maybe if he was allowed to
Indulgent that then he wouldn't be such a piece of s***
Yeah
That is possible
Ironman I guess there aren't really many women
Who don't get fired edit course
Plastic Ginger Marianna Marianna
He's clearly rainbow Snapchatting not there anymore anymore
I would kick those two off the island
Yeah
I mean Savannah Hernandez is around
Cannot be an employee at some point
Recurring cast no
He's like a recurring like oh my God how did that person fall on the island again
Yeah yeah
All right what was done to the bottom of this I think we've done quite enough
How many more minutes do you think we got a few more thoughts
But
Get to them Alex wants to set up a syllabus
That's what he's going to do for
For the day
And this is because he hasn't prepared s*** he doesn't do anything
He's ill prepared to do the show
And so he wants to take
And I intend
The bottom of the hour to give the number of
Call today
Very specific
Today
You call in on the specific subject
I'm about to lay out which is
How do we defeat the globalist
That's a huge giant subject
You're out of you on that subject
Dolphin emu
What is the worst thing they're doing what is the number one thing they're doing we need to stop
Devaluing currencies
Define the police
Borders
Coming after our
War with Russia
Bio weapons
Preparing to release new bioweapons they are releasing new by 11th or
People live
Their bio nanotech
And that is babies
This idea that Alex
Thinks he's being targeted with like what kind of car
But the two topic
Pixar
Do you want to complain about our imaginary enemies doing and what ideas do you have to stop our imaginary enemy
Those are so broad, open-ended topics
Be just bring up a topic whatever you want
Add cream storytime our how do we defeat the globos we stopped those
And then they talked about that for the next 45 minutes it does not
Could be any
It's the silliest props
It's just a blank piece of paper basically pretending to be a prompt wouldn't be allowed on an AP exam
Alex is up to
He doesn't is enough
Do my job for me is it very interesting way to open our show anything for us to complain about and I
Call rif with you for a little bit
And I will be good
The reason Sports Talk Radio is better than this is
Because it's Sports happens everyday
Yeah I don't know what I'm doing today so you guys do and there's things that we are not going to talk about like
Never happened
Not even hearing
So let's say
Babies
And
This is actually kind of scary because Alex has in the past
Kind of
Said that that
Appoint
Edwards
Which murders
Let's go ahead and start that hot War yeah
When they come for the baby
Right
And he also stressed making stuff
Corrupt FDA
At three different rounds of
Firings
Because the board would not even authorized
Authorizing his experimental injection
Do people on
Alburnett boosters
The dishwasher great
So you talked about this story before but just as a refresher course in September 2020 12 ft
Officials resign from the organization over frustration
Administration was
Handling the rollout of booster shot
This was dr. Marion Gruber and her Deputy dr. Philip
Krause
Their concern wasn't about the boosters being a dangerous conspiracy or anything it was more of an organizational.
Dispute with Gruber not agreeing with the white house or the fda's head vaccine officials handling of the
Situation
Hayden field input was being directed
Correct right and that's where all of this stuff happened with nakatomi Plaza
That's the only reality that's behind the
Entire story that Alex
Does weaving
Two officials resigned in September 2021 and Alex's turned it into a protractor
2 case of removing dissenters from the board over
For the course of multiple rounds of firings Masters
This wasn't even the biggest Reza
Ignatian from the FDA in 2021
Back in June advisers resigned over their objection to approving
It was a new Alzheimer's drug
That they felt wasn't effect
Yeah
Three people instead of two
Yeah but that doesn't have the headlines
Ends of like oh they're trying to say
So there's two things I want to point out about that clip that we listen to
The first is how Alex takes this kernel of Truth
In this case
Spivak tattoo FDA officials resigned I months ago
And then exploit the fact that his audience vaguely remembers that happening to build a gigantic
Pick narrative on top of
Just about everything he saying he was made up from his storytelling imagine a
The 2nd
Something I want to bring up his wife
He's doing this
The news item he needs to cover is that the FDA and CDC voted unanimously to approve the covid vaccine
A children
And Alex needs a way to explain that
It's kind of impossible for the argument to be that their well-meaning but misled doctors at this point and the best way to explain to you
Uniformity of their approval
Dissenters were weeded out gradually until this point
We're the only people left
Committed by a weapon in Susie
Right
This kind of thing can be important for audience
Control because
If you're Alex you don't want the listener started
To think about Howard
It's possible for the things Infowars to be saying to be true
Simultaneously
All the official bodies in the world completely disagree
With the story
Yep
Much of the time when you hear a conspiracy theorist a propaganda say something that you know to be untrue
It's wise to ask yourself what's motivating them to make that up
Sometimes it might just be for no reason but other times you can clearly see the structure of the game they're trying to play
And that reveal some of their priorities
Concerns
And I think
You know
That's
Do that comes out there
Yep yep that one breaks it
Pretty obvious
Hey you know this thing that's
Listen
I know we're on year 3
Of me trying to pretend that this is not a problem
But I'm going to be honest with you
They're all trying to kill us again
What the f***
Yeah
Yet use this it's cyclical
How many years are
Probably few more you're probably right so we got to Alex
You got chemicals on the brain
And
So he starts talking
Talking about bisphenol-a
That was his favorite chemical again complain about
Plastics
And products like
And give you a massive
Doetsch
Looks like Marilyn Monroe it makes them look like
Bloated dresses
So is that the
The most feminine you can get
Walked around the shopping mall
Least you're old enough to remember the girls
Taller than the boys
Tell you all this there are tens of thousands of studies
University in medical one of them
Bye
Design
Send the u.s. men and women's height to grown at approximately the same rate 5%
Sorso in the Years between 19
1914 and the Press
In other countries were actually quite variable going in both directions
Women increasing more in some countries and then another
This is nothing to do with bisphenol-a but this does reveal an interesting dynamic
How it's probably notices taller young women Because he believes that women are supposed to
To be small
He may walk around the mall and see a tall girl that sticks out to him because his ex
Patient events
It's a burden
Instead of asking if his expectations are wrong he stubbornly insisted his biases and gut feelings are reality and then
Women are supposed to be
Be small so the fact that this person he saw was tall must mean something is up
So there are
Concerned
It's about taking in too much bisphenol-a but they are quite with Alex
Suggesting
This is one of his classes
Hyperbole situation
The FDA is done
Constant monitoring of the studies a new research that comes out of a BPA
And they found very regularly that low amounts of it could
Theoretically get into food
I ended Asian food packaging
That contains BPA pets
A safe amount
The reason
CPAs in these materials is because it serves as a protective barrier for food
Why do you need this
Well for instance if he comes in
Metal cans
The risk of the food being contaminated by the metal itself is a
Much greater risk
Oh that makes sense cuz in the past people used to have metal stuff and then they got can
Contaminated all the time or liquid or acidic
To bleed to the metal Coronavirus
And you end up with food that has a greatly diminished shelf life among other risks sure answer this is General
Really why
Some packaging has
But a lot of people have forgotten that
You get a lot of
Flavor
From
Exactly
Clear that bisphenol-a is as much of a dangerous Alex makes it out to be
Concerned about it
There are
Fairly easy ways to avoid it with just a little bit of strict
Either shopping
If that is something that you prioritize it
I don't think it's the worst thing ever to be like
Hey
I'm going to live a Greener existence or whatever and I'm going to try and avoid
People don't even want to have preserved
Biking I can understand that as long as you're not going too far with a
Like Alex is wearing
Conspiracy to make women big
Yeah there's a part of me with all of those where they are there like this
Chemical is in your stuff
Personally my view on that is
There's really nothing I can do about it if it's bad enough
People will let me know
You know like I can't know everything about enough chemicals
And I can't know everything about enough not chemicals to think that it's better than
Chemicals I don't know enough of anything about anything
So if you're killing me just let me know
Please have the courtesy
Can I smoke
For years I even stopped
True
Alex might actually be gay
I can see Britannic hitting Alex with his hat is nothing
That is tough
So Alex has this complaint about bisphenol-a
And there's millions of prestigious studies and hospitals and everything universe
Yeah and so he gets into that
Do you know it's
Nonsense
I tell you all this there are tens of thousands of studies
Prestigious University
Knowing all of this
Bye
Design
Why do you need that many stuff
What they're doing
Fox News
Adeline
Wrist
Healthy PA says that goes into what it does
Washington Post
Forever chemicals are in name that are given to pfas
Sore / and Polly
Fluor o alcohol substance
Bisphenol-a is not one of these pfas is
There is new information that's been coming out fairly recently that indicates
The pfass are not good at any level
Where is we'd kind of assumed the lower levels of it would be
Not that bad
And maybe it's not catastrophic
Right they the number of
70 parts per trillion or something would really consider to Safe level
So like be the
The James
It's being
.0
000000000 72
Point 000000000 infinite repeating chances are it's real bad
Add something
But also the US has been working to phase these out for
4 years
EPA is a big part of
Deleting that campaign
Alex's muddying the waters here because he doesn't know the difference
Prince between BPA and pfass
He also knows that the audio
Doesn't know the difference so articles
Can be presented as
Prestigious studies about a separate chemical
And it doesn't
Matter
The goal of spreading fear is still achieve and no one
No one will be the wiser
I would say that
Instantaneously the moment you say there have been studies at every major university
Bat bags
The question
Why
What is it about this Saturday
Sure but I mean
So was like 50 major universities are done with it
But f******
The University of Wichita I still like god dammit I don't believe these
Motherfukers for a second
We're going to get Dave
The one guy that we have who does this s***
To run his own double-blind study can I ask you a question
What's bigger than 50
Do you want
What's bigger than 51
That's
You can always have more prestigious study
Doesn't make a difference
Suspicious than anything else in the history of the world
I mean we've been doing this a long time and I know that you know that Alex is just making this up
Know when called to prevent studies get a Fox News article
I'm some University see it like
F******
Oxford
Harvard
Stanford
You name it University of California and so
Computer universe
Eastern Illinois
Just like I can't handle this
Is Liars
I could see so much as being like what let's try and recreate those results
Yeah and then you get 50 people doing that
EBay tell buddy.
So this is a longer clip
But it's talking about like how he needs
To stay on air
And it's just it's a it's a little bit of a ride
But you were
War news
I want to get to
I'm also going to start taking your phone call start of the next segment
There is a lot of news about their attacking in full
Autumn control corporate
Organizing
I'm in modern
There's a small part of me that thought because of the way he's building this up and he's like all right I'm just going to do this now
Begin to talk about
Infowars
Basically the main
Main one
It doesn't matter it's not what happened
Populism
Fierce People waking up
Leadership
Nazis are bad too
Shut us down in silence
False allegations of straw man
And they can
Demon eyes
Populist movement
Infowars
Mobilizer
For their people
Neutralize
What
Unified dislike of him
Benjamin Netanyahu
Falling apart
Broke
Yesterday
Keisha unifier of the populist movement
Can also be used
Energize opposition
Infowars
He's good at UniFi
Populous
Infowars
You can use it as a weapon against
Everybody
Party done all this
My work is done
Because
False
Products that I used my God
It was
It was all a plug it was all going there I knew it without their eyes
I felt it happening I felt the moment it was going to happen and then when it did happen I was still like I can't
Holy morning
All just a rationalization for why you need to buy his s*** that's all I've heard him
A million times that he's achieved his mission
He's ready to die the Odelay
Do you think it's too late for the globalist
The Awakening at as happened and he has done his part
Like I should quit tomorrow
I'm ready to do it no no no no
He has to stay on air because if he doesn't then a fake version of him will be created in order to demonize the Patriot movie
What it is
It's about protect
Sing the rap
That's what it is
You know you got it I'm going brown
With my reputation intact
You you guys need to know here
Dunedin
I've done my work
And now from now on
This is all just fundraising and and me getting mad about
People talking s*** about me
It is him very like you just said listen the only reason we're on air
Is just so they can't f*** this up when we're gone
Don't use me to attack Trump or DeSantis or whatever
I'm just here as a placeholder so
Give me money till I'm able to stay doing that list
Protected my own image
Good protect your own image to who let the people who are already listening to you
It's a lot like
Whenever Netanyahu was running apart
You know and people were like we don't want him in here anymore that's a lot like Trump
Because people don't like a part
Right
Isn't it
It wasn't like
Mass disapproval of
People it was like
Corruption scandals more apartheid
Yep
So look there's big news haha
This actually is
Alex has more to promote them
Then just as standard bullsh
Okay this
Nelly
Very successful filmmaker
In her own right
Great filmmakers as well
How do you
Almost always
10 pieces
But she
Power
Entertaining
About 2 hours long
Come out
Late July
Enter going to be endorsing it and then pushing it
But it's very next month
See what I'm talking about
Has a lot of backing
She brought some tears to my eyes but
Here's the first trailer
Infowars.com
Scott Adams
The well-known guy what
Cartoonist
Analysis dealing with it
Play the trailer in the comments back
Imallexx
You're about to see is true
This is reality
Queens
Stranger Than Fiction
The most medium person in the world
He's a performance artist
I need to know about house thorough this documentary about Alex is
This is the first time I'd heard about it
This is the first time I'd heard about his well I don't think I'm entitled to be in every Alex related piece of media but I do think that if
You're a documentary filmmaker is trying to make a balance documentary about Alex
Stunad contact me
Yeah I've been doing a show about him for over 5 years I've watched more of his stupid show then just let anybody on Earth
And I've been cited in multiple published books and news articles about Alex
Without sounding too Conceited the fact that I'm not in this documentary is a red flag that this isn't a documentary
The puff piece about Alex
This trailer
Definitely makes it seem like a white boy
Alex Moore he's a filmmaker whose most notable work is 2020s TFW no GF
Feeling with no girlfriend
It's a documentary
Summer criticized by film of covering the subject matter irresponsibly and I would say that all indications are that this is
Even more so
This is
Wow
Yeah it's not ego and in fact it might be more the most
Indictment
Ends of your character that
There could be that
If you're making a documentary and you don't involved and then your urine
You're just insane
Extra sketches crazy
We got plenty of emails
Will say no problem
Or maybe
I might have said no to this
My daughter wanted to be involved
Popcorn Time
I think it is indicative of a lack
Interest in the topic of interest in seeing both sides
Quite frankly I think that
The number of the criticisms in the information that we provide
Disgust is not what the normal criticisms of Alex r
The normal criticism that he gets are very easily deflected by him
And that will probably be the extent of the
Both sides
Better going to be in the documentary
Will be about his
Very
L istorie and career lying
Constantly Weathersby
Making stuff up on air
From Reading headlines and decided he knows what the story is
Clear clear pattern
Of
Very very racist
Coverage of stories
Discount Tire
Kind of stuff that's not going
Tubi
Then I going to be covered
B flip
Sloppily about various stories
No I mean
Here's here's the thing okay
Here's a story of a illegal immigrant
Who found a gun after it has gone off
And killed some
That's the after he picked it up but
It wasn't his gun
And here's how Allie
Discovered it
That would be a very simple and short documentary
And that's the end of what you really needed absolutely
Coverage of
A racist
It's against a non-white person and the way Alex will justify it and be like
Yep
Going through houses and stuff
Racist violence is wrong now there's a reason for This Racist to be racist
Right and then you have the coverage of like the Kate steinle
And
How he
Made up a story about how this
Undocumented immigrants saw this white woman that was so beautiful
And he was so mad that he couldn't be with her so you have murdered her
Like it
F****** insane
Stuff that needs to be the counter
Bailing for
In the documentary about Alex
It doesn't need to be like he's a fake character
Or like telling the truth
Too much of the truth about who he really is
Bebe
I think it's almost irrelevant
Victorville weather
He is or is not anything in his heart
What he's done what ya the product that he is put out is a certain way and he Bears responsibility for that
And that's that's the reason that you can't even put that one example in the night cuz if you're trying to both sides that.
Scale example
So far down like
Oh and now he's
See they called McCloud
No he's a racist
Things like the making up operation locked
Totally unreal thing that we're talking about
Things you see in memes
B******* like clips from his deposition
Yep it's
I don't know
I will Reserve judgment cuz I obviously haven't
Seen this documentary
Text tears I think your judgment is pretty well it is Alex's promoting it it's
Not going to be something that is
Is that worth
The Damned
But
We will be covering it
I know
Moyer's going to really wish she did is they contact
To do a boy
And this guy
That's a weird weird thoughts
Alex women
Volume
And speak
All manners of evil against
Call sleep.
That you have become in the United States
America
People are
Place where no one
Event
Ashamed
You're not ever
I've been listening to you you've been
Chilling on your show
You're not you're not hiding the fact
Figured you're a flawed human being
You're really defeating them
From them the only weapon that they have
To use against you in that sure
That's not nearly the only weapon wow wow if you think that's the only weapon we've got my friend
Yeah little boy
Ashamed
Of the things that he
These quote-unquote telling on himself about
That shame and unprocessed
Just feeling videos surrounding that guides
A ton of his emotional out
Amazon air
Like this is this is
Premises
What Alex does
Just off yeah you remember all those times or he's been like
That's the shame for being
Himself coming out
Because he's a failure
In every meaningful sense and he understands that but
But he does like money
Or the the fill your hand Adam shift holding rant have many a number of years
My dog died
Yeah it's so Furious and drunk
3 hours on are talking about
Crystal skulls covered in jizan I had to do
Alex gets another call
Oh yeah
This person bike
I don't think the
Necessarily anything
But their existence isn't
John and I are welcome
Call her
Just been listening to you for about a year
And man you've been buried
On on my life and I know so many others and
I really missed you last week hope you got some
How is
Is it possible that you could
Start listening within the last year I think
Betty's on
Something
I have a certain amount of empathy for people have been listening for like 5
1520 years ago
There was a time
Yeah you could trick yourself into thinking like
This is the same show I used to
Or whatever like
At least pretended to be covering more serious issues in the past
I got so like if you started a year ago what the f*** is your problem
What do you hear
You know like what is it that you listen to that like click
It's inside your brain that makes you go
This
3 hour
Self-love
Not often love
Bvsmp
Yeah it's
So it's something that I find
Amazing
I don't I don't know how that's possible
I think it's
Scary
I don't know how bad my life would have
Have to be
Till like listen
220 21
What's Jones and be like
I mean but
You know content-wise
But it's just not entertaining it's it's
F******
It's so boring
Rhea is dumb
True
Screw Alex never tries to recast Gilligan's Island
He doesn't have his much Whimsy only weapon the people can use against us that's true
Call are really sure but he has a story about wearing
Alex
Alex Jones was right
Okay made him a rockstar 100%
Speak out and one easy way that I did that
Jones Is Right t-shirts
Trump rally in Memphis
Weekend I let me tell you
Like a rockstar walk-around
T-shirt on
Best Buy
Get me one of those shirts
Car seats my wife and I we had
Two stage left
Real quickly
Don Jr comes out
DC the shirt
It's like a
It's like I was highlighted
He's just locked in on me
Talkin right to me
Wow
Man
Yeah
Glisten
So like
When we saw that yeah
What was this like
15 years ago
There is a moment where I really believe Karen L looked at me
And it was like
That's really cool
Now I didn't happen
Or whatever who cares
Right doesn't matter
But if that moment of my life where I was idolizing one of the most amazing Rock
Stars of our era
Right
Where instead transposed
To Donald Trump jr.
I would be very very sad sure
Horrendously awful
When I was living in Colombia
Me and my brother were front-and-center
I got a high five from Ghostface
It was like. Junior was talking
I lost track of how I was going to make that today
Dammit
The Collins band
Before
This shirt
What I hear about this
You a rockstar at a very specific place
Like a trump shirt
It makes me so hot done Junior can't take his eyes off me my friend
Oh my God
Alex does I think he's come up with a branding
Opportunity
You want to see what it's like to be outshone
Alicia
Ball-peen hammers
Police shirts
Because you're going to be off shelves that point
Usher
Adventure for yourself
I think he's trying to bring the shirt as an adventure more than anybody is ever sold
Mister Ed
Brings along a even like
2% chance you're going to get hammer
I do I do like noodles people like this is
This is an Avenue of pitch
That he couldn't take without
The caller
Hey listen
Buy the shirt to feel like
Me for a date
Cuz that would suck stupid
Oh my God
You'll feel just like me so persecuted it's so cool
It's a rollercoaster you put on this warm
This is just
The brand new
The last caller brought up how he warned Alex Jones Is Right shirt in the adventure of the evening announced
It's a lot of meat on this phone
Let you know how awake
Humanity is in your area
You could wear one in
R1 in red areas
Chose
The globalist are and how we can win together if we just stand up
Also you might get stabbed
If we just stand up together and people where my merchandise
I mean
Are are the globals really that
Week if it only takes
X201 people to
To kill someone wearing
Alex Jones Is Right shirt
You know what I'm saying
It's
I mean it's not necessarily a fatal stabbing
That's fair
Good
Could ruin the shirt
But that's good for Alex
Cuz he just got b l another shirt
Belle Fourche
Yeah
It almost works better if people have a more negative response to it
Jeans with the knees already
You've got a Nightfall with you
Every every shirt they sell comes with a pack of stitches
Comes with like a Band-Aids
Blood transfusion
So that I mean
Like legit that call
Fallout from that College
Commercial service Cherokee Stroke of Luck for him
Another call and this guy's got some ideas
It's about how to win
I've got three things
My mind
It's hard to answer your question because they're all important
Justice
You need to get rid of the DA's
Bi that's not doing his job
These people had a fear of
Houston they wouldn't keep doing that things like
Spraying chemicals on releasing things
Number two
Phone companies
Bad breakup
Me to bring back.
Truth in advertising rules
I think we need to deal with the education
Acting schools,
Sam's teach the truth not
Propaganda
Weather Wonder
Motorola G3
I don't know but in my mind
The rules and laws we have
Before
Keep doing what they're doing
I like to try and find some Middle Ground
All agree that maybe some big media conglomerates should be broken up like Sinclair
Not a hard sell on my
Hey break up large media Corporation
Not destructive I think maybe that
Bangla newspapers
Yeah let's let's
Diffuse that a little bit I do think that this guy I wouldn't want to
Team up with that project
Also truth-in-advertising rules still exist a reason that you get the letter from like some
Somebody changes I don't f****** to paste
Specifically true that advertise the girls still exist
Thing he wants is more truth out
Schools at the bad idea and then I want them to regulate the supplement industry
I think it's dude just mad at the FBI because of January 6th
Cuz they're investigating conspirators
Soros owns all the VA doesn't seem like a real I'm still looking
For justice for Fred Hampton guy on the FBI front
Pazzo
Yeah I'm just repeating s*** Alex's said
I bet is
True
Now we get another call
This guy's got a fun Noms de plume
Digital Dave in Wisconsin
Thank you Alex
And yours my brother my beloved wife
Family and I are old
Are you
And all of your
Family members and all Infowars talented anointed staff
Warriors
We are grateful
Thankful
I want I want I don't want digital analog despres
Digital David
The singularity
8-track day
That is like one of those is that a generalized sign of things getting
Much worse more prayer on one info
Yes it is that is a sign of
Something
Troubling
So yeah Alex
Like I said there's a lot of marketing
On this episode
And so he decides to really lean into it and play that trailer again
Oh no
War film coming out
In Late July
This is really fun time and get Alex at
Good Late July happens to be exactly when the Sandy Hook trial was rescheduled to start that same that way Alex Meyers
Is pretty lucky
In terms of that timer
Documentary is a Twitter account
Retweet A lotta Infowars type
Folks
We're really excited for the film
I said to look through the people who their host there
Following
Here's some of the notable names
Alex's wife
Mike cernovich
Michael malice
How's the Red Scare
Documentary propaganda
Superman turned
Sure Paul Joseph Watson
Scott
The alt right
Steve Jimmy Dore
Russell Brand
Glenn Greenwald
Jim Dale
There's just a murderer's row of shitbags on there
Pizzagate veterans
How how long how
How are they
Man they're still around
I'm not optimistic that this is going to be an actual in-depth documentary look at Alex's career because
If it were Alex would never have agreed to be in it and promote
Professional and personal tracker
Go to being in a bear sing liar I don't believe
We'll be hearing about it on it
Absolutely
But are you welcome
Albuquerque
I'm going to keep my mind open don't let Lucy put that f****** football down dad
Lucy walking up with the football and hanges
Rubbing it gently with a nice little cloth making
I'm sure it's all nice and smooth
I don't think that I need to be in
NFL
The point
That are important
Bring up that I would bring up our things that should be in the film
Documentary about Alex will be lacking if these things were thin it would be perfectly happy if anybody else
Springs those and I don't know that somebody doesn't
So I will I will Reserve judgment until that point but also
I can't believe that Alex would be a part of
Something
That would just
Have the critiques
That that that
Need to be back
Looks not
Beat around the bush
Moyer that I mean the number of how not to
To cover Alex Jones episodes we've done kind of
It suggests that
There is a responsibility Gap all across the board whenever it's covering Alex Jones for the most part
Sure it's a concept is there in terms of like
He goes on Rogan and they get like a ton of people watching
It does Stephanie gets attention to the people who have him on
Flagrant good numbers
And all this s***
You could
Reasonably assume your documentary-maker like a big new documentary about Alex
Tubi
Yeah would be something lucrative
People who get a lot of it
I think
Vet
You know if you were able to time it right around when the Sandy Hook trials
What's going on
Good idea certainly
It'll be a topic
Conversation that a lot of people are interested
But you also have to know that if you watch
His appearances on things like Rogan
He's only going to be involved in stuff that doesn't involve heavy pushback
He can sort of be in control
More or less of the entire
The entire situation
Absolutely
You're never going to be able to get him in a lie Carol Morris style like
Give
Type of documentaries
Absolute
Confirmation that Alex had milk
Control over whether or not
Something woodwind
You know what I'm saying like they didn't film something of Alex
It's that Alex Wood
Want to be in the documentary and then
Be like
Hey let's just put this in without telling
That didn't happen
Certainly.
So we got another another caller here
Idea about what the most
Important thing is for the
Infowar
Most important
Read the word
Listen to
Warriors spread
Read the word
Videos
Or you guys
I just try to keep
Keep breaking fruity Fran
Family
It may take
May not feel like it
Gotten anywhere but we have
Screw the most important thing in the fight against the globalist is promoting Alex giving money to Alex and alienating people in your
Your life who might be able to help you see
That this s*** is no good
I mean Daddy
That is how that is how you do it
Gases how you f***
Go from
That's absolutely no I mean if
You want
Give audience
Then you literally make them your captain
And have the
Believe that the only way to
To save
Don't world
Is to promote you
That's a
That's amazing
That's like the most evil wait-listed hey
I know you
Do you want
Try
Some f****** lucky charm
But if you don't eat Kix
Everyone you know will die
That's one way to do it
It's weird sales pitch
Just work enough that it doesn't matter
People just
Stay in the pattern do you know people are social animals and when they stop feeling social and then they start
To try and find
And social.
Trapped in the self-worth
Yada yada
So I've been watching the Jigger e-cig
Exclamation
Thursday
But I'm going to have to referee record
But the prior was
Really really
Hard
They interviewed the ballot workers OD'd
The poll workers were counting ballots
It's in Georgia or mother
Who had been
Singled out by the right-wing media
And one of the things that was
Particularly distasteful
It's all about it
I'm obviously the stories of how it affected their lives and how they
You know basically
AR
Afraid of their own names now
Terrifying
Really I think is the resonant image
For me is Rudy Giuliani
And his behavior surrounding
That
Yeah and the way he put a Target on Zapped
Racist weighs about
And this next clip
Let's go talk to Derek in Virginia
Hey how you doing Alex
Hey I'm you know I was wondering
State
Selecting Rudy Giuliani
Attorney General
Attorney general I don't believe he would have had Russia
I don't believe we would have had Ukraine
I don't believe it would have had
WrestleMania
Mistake I believe in no one wants to admit that but
Gravis
Mistakes
3 Giuliani would have been a lot better
Attorney general than that then the other two yet
I mean yeah disagree but yeah
The idea was consolidating power and all that s***
Somebody who look like you would be as
Corrupt as they come but then he ended up work using himself
Okie doke close yeah he chose the guy who was famous
For doing the one thing that he did not do that one time
Yeah I mean like this color is correct I mean Rudy would have gone along with any
He would either does he would have helped overthrow all sorts of s*** really feel like what
What would have really helped
Cuz if you just over
The government
Why do you got to go overthrow the government I mean I think that's what store roads have been saying for years
Not just a pack
This
Said it
Yourselfin age
Rudy Giuliani up there
Anyways 2024
I just need to
Remind everyone
Infowars Canon
According to the story
Rudy Giuliani was instrumental in covering up 911
So Alex shouldn't never
Be interested in like
Water under the bridge Tower Bridge
None of this has any kind of staying power
These storylines don't mean anything tomorrow
It's pathetic
But it's what happens whenever you live in like movie Worlds the shifting alliances make things fun you know like all of this
Why is my enemy and we're fighting but we also respect
Maybe later on we'll be on the same team and I like that old bull
Palace intrigue
Yeah there's an episodic nature to fix
You know like
Maybe one Sherlock Holmes mystery doesn't necessarily affect your other one
Continuity between them
Right right
Exit some of Alex's bulshit Works in that way we did 9/11 to
Start at to the Death Star
Right
And then later on you find out he's
He's a good guy so why not
Blonde
Okay
Close your eyes members
Maybe something was revealed that it was a false flag or something like that later Star Wars movie
Okay
That's a relief
It's all good so callers have to go
They're getting replace
Leo zagami
Try to get your calls I appreciate you calling in
Okay buddy
Alright I get it
More things we need to buy from you
Is he
Wellington like that few months
Got surgery and was in a wheelchair
Stepping down
But I don't think a lot of that is very official
He's got the pope is going to step down
Stop I was like what the hell is he doing
It clicked in my head yeah
Now layout as we know we know a lot about Leo's history
May or may not
But it's funny to imagine that he does when he says something like that
Illuminati
Whistleblower
What a time to be alive Leo
How you do all this years ago
If Alex knew Julio zagami was
20 years ago then he would know about
Alright alright BJ We Are Young
He would have been
The leader of the Church of Matrix ism
Is goal was to start the new Holy Roman Empire and overthrow Christianity
Is I'm the only real religion in the world row
He was Jesus
Did 9/11 single-handedly although he worked with Osama bin Laden
You got to have Fred
He went to the Vatican and they said
That's right they were like holyshit Leo
How do you know so much is also said like
Wewo
It's too much used to Good Taste too good
Yeah I mean the Messiah is on Infowars right now and that were
Treating a poorly because he has
Come into his power yet
That's the problem
The naysayers early on
Write our retribution will be Swift and so
Severe I'm sure
You didn't know you know s*** about this guy until until he came into your life a couple years ago you dumb
Play fuk how f******
The Pope's going to resign
There is not much left to this
Papacy.
Probably probably end in August
Before that
Because
He of course you wanted to wait
About it
I like
This
You know we've been
Saying that he's going to resign for a while and he's been resisting cuz he's waiting for ratzinger.
So I think that would being applied
Here is that
He wants to wait till ratzinger's that's the right thing or doesn't become a pope again exactly
Implied here
I think I think Leo is warmer Pope's of the understudy of living folks
I think Leo
He's not saying this
Cuz I think it would be insane
To say out loud
But I do believe Leo thinks that
The Pope
That if he dies before Christmas
Singer he's going to
Hit the folks
That guy
Right on my heels
Covid-19
Papers.co P continuity
Yeah
I can find it at the fish hope emeritus
Oh wait wrong with this serious stuff today we need to be considerate
Disparition
Prophesied
Long time ago yeah
Operation of the Holy Mary
Moscow
Will be the beginning of the end for mankind
I accepted my segments
Portable food is essential
From Infowars right to here
And I suggest everybody alright
Alright
Okay
Batwing
From him doing in Italian
His natural diet I said to him doing a weird Italian
Pitch accent is like
And I forgot my throat of a food right here it's like whoa that's not okay bad just happened there
Don't know if I text as much of a difference is you
We got a ghostly Apparition of the Virgin Mary made a prophecy that if the pope sets foot in mouth
Scouts of the beginning of the end
Alex Jones
Everything is f******
King sales
You talking about
The Galleria sale
Caught talking about
Virgin Mary
Prophecies turns into a
A chance to sell f****** dehydrated
Good food
It's awesome
I love
Prophecies like that
I just want them there's like
Make a prophecy like that and I'm
Putting the pope on my back and carrying him to Moscow tomorrow let's f******
Can do this
If I don't care one way or the other
Right that's what I'm saying it's the world's going to end if the pope gets to Moscow let's just do it why are we waiting generation
You're supposed to accidentally stumble into it over with man
That's what I'm saying
Yeah I don't I don't know I mean I think there's an argument for let's not risk it
I don't fight I don't know
We have some news
Got the stuff is just so dumb
Haha
$20
Figuring out what a weird coin
20 euros
Imagine that
And on top of
Of course
Texas season
Do you want are also linked with the elect
Technological world
End
Demons with
Chile
Even sending messages
Incredible
My area
Ecstasies of this facility
This is troubling
Demons can text
Oh no
You know the the later when the Generation Z gets older they will not believe that
Demons live in technology cuz they've never lived
Through the modem
You know they never left do
Demonic
Alex
Pedal didn't no response
After Leo
I was going to say a little bit overpriced
The Vatican
Charging people too much for a coin
What kind of month
Sister would do that
Right
Maybe maybe Leo didn't read the room
I'm sorry what my slip here and
It's a little bit of a disagreement
Between Alex
Sandalio
They have different ideas about what to do about the
The fact that the cities are all going to burn
Turn themselves down
You know the trouble is coming
Leo believes that there is no way to save these cities were going to take control over
So there's a little bit like if we were arguing about what would happen if the Cubs
Murder-suicide of their entire team
That kind of
The city's unfortunately are in the hands of the enemy
Of course of the demon
I don't think we need a crack
So we need to
Prepare
The city's this is something I always say
Global's can't help but abused and suck off of a destroyer
Remove ourselves
He'll destroy the cities we will then inherit
And then they'll burn themselves
That the seat is might become smart cities in the handle side
Bible Satan and he's a robot
Ono Ono
Yeah
If the pope ever comes
Chicago working to be heads of Cypress evening is robots dad
This this is the
Roller coaster that is a Leo zagami sentence that is what it is because
You're like what you do want the city
Can come in and take control of their
That sounds bad why would you want that because the alternative
Of course
Organize the tools of cyber Satan and his robot army
Absolutely
All of our cities are going to go to the way of Sodom and Gomorrah cuz we weren't hospitable enough
To Leo zagami and Alex Jones you mean that we didn't book
Leo zagami to do a DJ de Noel
And Alex's film didn't play at the music by I think that is going to wind up being the downfall of fall
Probably
Let me
Idiots live in their fun little Chris
Christmas Carol
Sandwiches return
Yep I don't know what to tell you
Are you know what I feel like you left out the word triumphant
I didn't
I mean that it wasn't if if I did leave it out it was intentional
Cuz I don't
Auto trying to sell things
And just
Calls to avoid
Really exposing that you don't want to cover any of the stuff that's going on
I mean
Yeah cuz once he
He starts talking about any of it
If he doesn't have come
Control Chicken Go Wild
You know
Yeah if he doesn't know any of the
The story is totally
Beatles
I also think
We're applying and projecting rationality on anybody listening
Lifespan
Just making s*** up all the time why would he speak
Awareness of the stories he's covering Natalie doesn't
You're right it doesn't
Probably just a comforter
Birthing like a personal sense of
Pride the very least some sort of level of space like I ain't know a new guy
Disagree
I think it's like a half
Easing back into a show cuz you like the listeners will really just do most of it with
Call Jay
I'll just be able to play around with that right most part stay back from vacation trailer for this documentary over
Over and over again and then have Leo zagami
Say a bunch of stupid s***
And yeah so that's
That's one way to do it
Hey dudes
Advise but but that is definitely a way
Yep
Come back Alex I'm glad he's
Studio cuz I feel like there's a bit more normalcy
Yeah you know I
I feel like
Is there a Wii now 10
Confirm he didn't
Right
You know right
Open question is
Open close
We can also confirm that some of that $8000000 went to a nice two week vacation
Probably somewhere
See if he gets back into shape
Gets himself to a place where he can be interesting
Next week
We are on Twitter that intelligent or fight night go to bed Jordan
But until then
Emilio Emilio
I hope you all have a wonderful day
Alex
Birthstone colors