Damn important
I have great respect for knowledge B. I'm sick of him posing as if
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Put the altar of Celine and talk a little bit about
Alex Jones
Quick question for you today
My bright spot Dan is it is the beginning today as we speak of us Summer Games Done Quick
And it is the first time they've been in live
Grouping situate iPad that's how I
Better whatever it is with a real audience
Since since
The thing that happened I watched a little bit of it
It's fantastic
Lily is heartwarming
Well and it's for Doctors Without Borders
Add stop by.
I am blown away by
I mean just even people who are good at video game video game
Not that good at them
So people who are good
Worry me
People who are able to do those
Speedrun games
Yeah seems like that would
A long time of sucking up water to get right
Very impressed
But
You're obscuring a lot of stuff
A lot of time spent like
Screaming it
A deck of cards video games
You get to see it end
Because you can play a video game at least at a at a basic level you know
You can really see
How amazing they must be
The really good ones are
Imagine
You can't even think about
Playing the sax
The phone you got no idea to make your fingers do that s***
How the f*** do they do that you don't got to read how do you put your mouth on that thing
Even with the second one I guess I can't even conceive of that difficulty
Kind of be like
Wow is relatable yeah it
I guess that's an indictment of Our Generation
And everyone can relate to video game
Today my bright spot is you notes
3B creamy summer everyone knows this
It is taking the World by storm
The beginning of this year we've had conversations about this privately
To find a way to make it
Me and a little bit more than just me eating ice cream
There was an idea that I had
Each month
Of the dream creamy summer we would
Support a charity
Of some sort out something like that
You know I think that things
Kept happening
And
Kept being like well this is what we
Support
Is right
Oh the overwhelming
And everything here things kept happen
The first time we talked about it was like
3 days before we were going to go to Austin for the trial
Probably that whole thing happened
Ever since then it's been one f***
Something after enough
Yes yeah finally decided to make a move on this and
So what I have done
Is I've we've started a Kickstarter
Kick-starting starter
If you get 10 bill
There's a GoFundMe
Set up fundraisers for a charity of your choice
And there is a charity called apiary that is involved with logistical and practical support
For people who are looking
For Reproductive care
And so what I have decided to do is set up a dreamy creamy summer
Fundraiser you can find I think if you just search gofundme.com dreamy creamy summer I think it
Should come up that's what I change the name to
Obviously on the episode but yeah
I ate some
I don't know
Make some positive attitude Sports
Org
Hopefully
Helping
Yes
Episode
Turn on purpose
Don't mean to do this yeah 22 also known as
What a day
What a day how do you want to put a day like that of course
Is David learn that
It was official that the Supreme Court was overturning Roe versus Wade
That second part will not factor into this episode because Alex was on there
We have Alex's immediate response to the news that Rohit been overturned
Yeah I think
A lot of people might
Expect something a little different
Then what actually
I mean I think people might expect I don't know ticker tape parade
3 hour long
Remix of You Belong To The City 3 hours
That that's
Probably
Some of it's interesting some of its not and we'll get into it here in the moment the first
Let's say hello to some folks
So first sorry for missing the wedding Den dog and tradwife thank you so much and I apologize
Thank you so much you're now about those who walk
Thank you very much
Very much Veronica future corporate representative
Make an apology on this one a little bit late
Maybe 2 weeks late or so
But anyway Emma
Charlie wanted to wish you a happy birthday
I think I want to be in
Called in any of those witches
Nonchalant
Not a happy birthday was on the 12th
Belatedly
Objection form
Fell asleep to it
I am the Schmidt asaurus Rex thank you so much
Your knowledge
Technocrat
I have
Risen above
Miami
A list for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She wrote in on
And all your s***
Maybe the Nashville on West Broad
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
I'm Yours
Walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Back here again
I apologized
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
He's not
Alex
So we start off the episode
Alex comes in with music that I don't know I wouldn't say that he's never played this I'm not sure but it is
Definitely not a normal song The Way by Fastball
It's an INXS song
Okay
That somehow even more weird
Especially for like
Here's a pretty short list of like the
Beginning of the show Bumper Music
So this is a little bit weird the vibe is just off
What
Oh they're scared freedom is rising
Human intention is increasing to Manatee is Awakening
Tacoma
Are you trying to DJ a prom
Why am I angry already it's very strange
Goddamn
Slow dance at bulshit what is happening notable
Vibe shift wow
It's not what you'd expect
Hello it's me
If this were the case in his own life when he was younger
We would never have had to deal with any of his bowls
Well we'll get to that a little bit later okay
I believe that but before we do
Big day for Alex
And here
Supreme Court decision
Why did the Supreme Court do the right thing and
Overturn Roe v Wade
That we have
3D modeling
3D scans in HD
Pronounce twenty-plus years
A babies in the womb
Psalms even 23 months
Playing
Dancing
It's over 75 to 80% of people
Intensifying
Would the youngest generation
What's the story about why the court overturn Roe v Wade is absolute trash
They did not determine that fetuses are babies based on 3D modeling or whatever
The f*** Alex is saying because if they did determine that then they would have made a ruling that decided that states can just decide
If they want to allow murder
And that isn't what they did
No they didn't
This decision that they made is a flagrant violation of many people's rights
And there will be cases
Ad nauseam
Challenging abortion laws
And various States
We will see how
Yeah number of Base
I was reading about from the congregation Ladora Fedora Jewish
A progressive Jewish synagogue in Florida
I bet
I was getting a bit of coverage and
I think I think
Produces some interesting question
I'm just so bored
Them having to
Pretend
Now that they still have to pay
Pretend write a note
It says we want you to cancel abortion in this place
Why are you going to pretend to have words that make sense in-laws
They're all
Did you read their f******
Cramps
Nonsense in those decisions
Does like hey you know I know but took them
That's what the depiction said they didn't say was a result 3D modeling of dancing bear
They don't need that anymore they don't need any excuses the Galaxy some NyQuil and watched a Lima
Bellini baby baby
Angry too Alex is also completely wrong about the general population's feelings about abortion
Hinge
2021 Gallup poll
Found a record-high approval rating for abortion with 47% saying it was morally acceptable
Recite wanted abortion with limit
32%
Completely legal and only 19% thought it
It should be illegal
Pew research found a 2022 poll that among the
Younger demographic
Between 8
18 + 29
74% supported abortion
Being legal
And in fact it was older people who were license
What
54% of those 65 and up supported legal
Alex is lying and the reason is fairly obvious
How long abortion even on a state level is
The pretty unpopular idea among the general population
The only group
Really his strong opinions in that direction are Conservative Republican
These are really the only groups whose opinions Alex thinks
Help so the world that
He creates for his audience to experience is real
Is a world where those positions held by those groups
Are projected onto everyone
That's what he's doing
I'm here and he's
Literally in
Converting
The
Yeah like this group 18 to 29 is 74% in favor of abortion right now it's saying 75
The 80%
Of the youth
Opposed to it
That's very possibly just misreading but either way it's still in a
You can't possibly believe that if
You better young person
I don't I don't think it's a misreading I think it's a understanding that he's already
We'll adopt
Whatever
That the sort of
Characteristics of reality
He presented to them and it is nice for them to be like
Awesome
The Next Generation
Totally on my side so validate that I've had enough
Generation is coming around tonight
And it's just not true
It's very sad salute
Anyway there was another Supreme Court
Decision that I was about to New York
Concealed carry
Laws
Spell
Alex is thrilled about that decision to imagine that one is more likely to get a ticker-tape parade
Confusing
Paradox tour
Apocracy in the
Just on a whim
Much of the
Slavery legal again
Historically
What does that mean
We all know deep down
He is true
But they gone
And there are
What's the party stage
This is why I had occasion to important it was 350
Wow everything is a state right until it's not
Free fun
Play cuz I mean you know that whole 10th Amendment movement that Alex was so into 4
Years and years campaigning it so
Thoroughly when
Democrat
It's where an office and what-have-you
Kicking to the state
All the powers that are relegated by the fans
Fusion
And
You know.
Concealed carry
Seems like that should be a state issue according to Alex's beliefs
But who
Well I mean it would be it would be gauche of the democratic party or really anybody to point
Clean outside
They only change the venue whenever they're losing
So if they're winning in the federal government and states rights do matter but if they're losing in the federal government
It's almost like they're just short sore losers or
No
Not quitters
Bring up here
The first is that states insisting they had a right to allow slavery is what caused the Civil War and Alex's ancestors
Put on the side of the people who wanted
Needs to be able to enslave people
This would be a quirk of family history normally but Alex's frequently brags about being related to
Confederate generals
Also he believes that he's literally his ancestors so if his belief system means anything
He fought for the
Conspiracy
At least spiritually
Second Alex's position is inco
Because he's misleading about his act
Position
He doesn't believe that abortion should be a question left up
To the states
He knows that's a position he should have
Based on his fake libertarian politics
His actual position is that he wants
What's the federal government to ban all the
Because for all the Fanfare he has about how the government is evil
If he feels that the power of the state can be used against his perceived enemies
He makes peace with the feds real thing
Yeah it seems like it have
Almost
Immediately if you believe that abortion is murder than you can't believe the state's right to
Pure and simple
The people like Alex of used to obscure their actual agenda is and make it easier to trick people into thinking
But they were more moderate than they actually are also States should be able to decide whether or not murders
Fine check what the f*** are you talking
It is buckled
It is you know
It's the way to convince
People who
Would just rather not
That's more what it is
It's not like
Tricking people into believing that they're better it's
Just more like
Oh he said that woman I just don't have to think about it I can
Just leave them alone
I'm sure you know his murder is a strong emotional trigger
And
States rights issue
Effuse
Do some of that maybe make some think that you're not involved in people's Act
Play ultimately want to roll back all sorts of things right all the way to
Sodomy laws contraception being illegal abortion is legal in Illinois
If Texas wants to ban abortion no big deal except for it's not going to be that much longer before it's banned everywhere
This clip has nothing to do with anything
I just thought it was weird
Soylent Green
That piece coming up
Hey my man
Knowing what's out there
How come you didn't
Well at all
Bulshit
That guy I honestly don't
Care what Alex thinks about David
Saying stuff like that makes me think of you. I actually kind of like the guy
What
Absolutely
Least weird
Hey
Where
Politically aligned in a different way than our
Aeropostale
I mean for now Pub
Play yes I would you say that you have
Become a Satanist
Do you worship the devil
I mean I don't really worship anybody
The larger issue I have with the world
You're in the minority of wildly I disagree without
Operating system in Ariba National
Nationals documentary
A large portion of Democrats identify as Satanist
This is about selfishness about devaluing human life
This is a big victory for
Share articles and videos
City of evil and Corruption and collapsing borders V volume
Humanity is
Coming back
Humanities
It's going
It's progressing
Humanities going away
That's what you manatees doing
Eventually
Yeah I don't I think that Alex is talking about hail Satan
Cuz that's a documentary that he's brought up a number of times
Okay alright
You think that
I mean I'm just guessing
I'm here but I would assume that most
Most of the people
In the satanic temple
They
Describe the politics or believe in electoralism
Would probably be more likely to be Democratic and Republican
I like they might be saying
Taking that from the documentary and then assuming that all Democrats are
This is this is
Yeah well I mean it makes sense to Alex
To think that there would be a church
Satan
Right
Because
Titans real
Okay
But there is
Right but
He means it in one way and be the thing about a Church of Satan
Is if you want a literal Church of Satan than those people also have to believe everything in the Bible is true
And they don't believe that
It's an ironic point that their makeup
Enough
I just got a funny image of Alec
Text thinking like
If there is a Church of Satan they meet in like
Cave
Only like we have rugs
We do the whole thing
We sacrifice something we light a fire
I mean
But even then he doesn't know that modern Satanist we've got those candles that you're there just electricity man
If LED TV screen
Soylent
But so you want to take it out
Pretty specific
Narrow issue
I will
The number out
Specifically on Roe v Wade
What do you think the pitfalls are and what is the left
Violence and Vengeance and insurrection
I mean first of all what the f*** do you think your audio
But second
Obsession and preoccupation
That we saw all over right with media
Of
Framing the story as
The left is going to be viola
And I think that that is a wonderful way for them to delegitimize protest
From left
And
Yeah he's on the Vanguard of that stuff but these are the talking points that he uses all the
The time
That his
I guess become acceptable for people like Tucker and
Other
Folks to use
The tragedy
The Democrats from actually
Doing anything
You know is they they're they're like the Democrats are going to be like
And then you know
It's going to be a good
Three years that we're going to have
I think two
There's a priming
People who might counter-protest
Folks
I liked on the GOP and the anti-choice if you're going to counter-protest to make sure your arm
Heightening of tensions
Expectation
It's just right out of the gate
From entering things with that headspace
Cuz the idea is that they've escalated before you even got there
Right
I mean it's just a preoccupation
Respond
Call Zack
Demonic
Drunk on the blood of children
Avenue Sacramento
Taken away
You know
Hit anytime
Familiar cues I think we've I think we've made a huge mistake
This entire time
I'm re-evaluating
Moved into cities we should
Just stay that mean the trees absolutely we never should have come down from there I would have argued that the ocean would
Probably been better
Clarinet
I'm sorry we're just telling us what they're afraid of
Maybe if we just leaned into their fears they just run away
So we all have to become Satanist Satanist
We are blood all over and run towards conservative
I honestly think well here's
It might be fun as a thing to try
There is a
Problem of what
You do then
Well it is not a long-term political solution
Kind of structural
Plan
Involved in
Yelling
Yeah
Get some sort of a response out of
The truth
So Alex isn't confusing ideas about abortion
This really didn't
Makes sense.
Other states to have these abortions on that other countries
We as a people are
Master and he's alive
And there are the arguments they have
Early abortions if they were really just doing it
A person's poor or
It's done because they loved Anthony value in him and himself
I think it's weird that Alex seems to
Be presenting
These rare situations are ones where
You know maybe it could be okay get an abortion early
In cases of rape or if you're poor
That's strange
Well I mean it is strange considering that we
With this ruling the only people who won't be able to get abortions are for
It's almost the opposite
It's weird for any kind of conditional
Because
If you believe the things he pretends to believe you can't
You can't
Murder people if you're poor I mean are you talkin about
Listen okay
Abortion is murder
And you can have one if your poo
So if you have too many kids say like
Between the ages of 5 and 45
If you're poor
If if Alex
Believe
Any of the things that he saying I don't understand how he would know
Rationalize one being okay but not the other mouths to feed so I'm going to kill it and I'm
Going to drape myself in its blood and the Run doors Alex
Fail to see how this could be a position he's taking
I'm seriously at all if he has his belief
So I went to As We Know
Has been involved in a lot of abortion
Do you have paid for a lot of them
Believe in 2050
Team that we found
He was talking
Think about paying for abortions for women who even
Didn't want to
To get them
Pressured them into abortion
F****** weird but here he
Backup this
His past with abortion
Man there's just some things that it's
Don't
Fit
I was extremely promiscuous when I was young
And did not have any trouble with the ladies
And
Abortions in a lot of women
A lot of murders involving a lot of murders
My dad's a murderer
I just moved out
I got a job I need some more money
I just gave you money for an abortion a month
What is your problem
Stop killing my
That's why I need money
And he was just like you're out of control
I want to shop
For several years and
Soon as I stop
Just chasing women around
Then
My mission basic
Materialize
So we've talked
It's 100 times a repeating particularly on a day like this that Alex Jones of all people
Should understand the importance of having access to reproductive Healthcare
If the world he wants to exist
Existed when he was younger he wouldn't be Alex Jones
No one would know who he was he wouldn't have
Career and the globalist to be running around
Completely on a pole
In order for him to be able to carry out his allegedly
Play Holy mission of fighting Klaus Schwab or whoever you
He reveals to
The big bad guy
Season Alex needed
Did the two have access to
Also the story about his dad is something we've heard Alex start telling fairly recently but really let the
Details of that story sink in
Alex was so irresponsible and it was such a routine thing that his dad knew he needed money for an abortion just
Because Alex asked him for money
The right-wing will often accuse people who support abortion of being irresponsible and using it as his control but
Seems like that's more something that Alex did
It's
A little bit weird
I mean
Hysen
I did well with the women and wasn't trying to get people yes you were
No no there's no way to know how people get pregnant
Biewer Yorkie
You're being irresponsible I mean what is he going to do use a condom
The f****** part isn't the problem is people if they're on the pill
What's he going to do
No he's got to get in there and it just like Onan was told by God
You got to keep that crap in there
Don't let it Outlook leaving all this aside for a moment Alex can straight-up go f*** himself if he wants me to believe his b******* about him get
Celibate that's being like when the mission
Became clear
He needs to get his Cosmic and spiritual back story straight because this thing is
Full of holes
Is that school and so he got celibate and then his mission began
None dare call it conspiracy alligator 12 and that woke him up to the New World Order and started just calling
And I thought he was younger is dead buddies over to talk about their insane anti-communist bulshit
Alex knew all about this from a young age
I thought he was a Satanist for a while and then try to record it. They tried to recruit him into Satanism and he saw 3
Through it and that's what I thought that
Microscope got ambition in a vision from God and God told him everything that was going to happen when he was like
Pretty sure you said that with him like the last month or two
You know I'm starting to think psychopathic
Liars aren't the most reliable people
None of his matches up and none of it makes sense because none of it's actually real
The truth is this
Kind of my assessment of of some of this picture
Alex comes from a zealot as right-wing household and his dad is a huge
Society guy in Alex's you
Whatever friends right-wing Christian nationalism he was a
Supposed to and indoctrinated into
Open question
But he's brought up folks like the holocaust-denying preacher text
And the British is realist
Preacher David
Smith is inspiration for his beliefs of the past
We should give you some kind of a sense of what was going on
Rebelled against that income
Credibly tight Wildcats
Until it came to a point where he
Couldn't
Maybe it was related to his Outburst of violence getting him in trouble like when his dad had to move
From Dallas
Or maybe it had to do with his out of
Control impregnation streak but whatever it was
He came back in line and adopted the extreme right-wing believes that he was raised
But the things that you did and engaged in during the time that he was rebelling are things that plagued him with guilt
Or at least that's the presentation he wants people to see on the show
During his youth he got into Satanism so magically all of his enemies worship the devil
During his youth he done protected sex with apparently
Countless women and impregnated many of them leading to them
Pain
Abortions in
What do you know as an adult abortion is magically the blood sacrament of his Demonic Enemy so weird almost
Easy to to see through really is
A lot of Alex's ideology can be boiled down to being a racist and having
Completely idiotic politics build on John Birch Society related books
In the more recent past
Skimming headlines and meme
But a lot of this stuff is there too
Simply transparent
Is more or less him acting out
He thinks that he was a baby
What he was younger and was having all these abortion
Political enemies
And it's pretty
You know it's a little bit like
If Alex
Verbal Kent
In The Usual Suspects you know
And that moment where he walks away and he
Gets rid of his limp and your like oh my God
Keyser Soze
That's amazing
Right
He's just a masshole
Who just really enjoyed lying to the cops and he was just reading the thing behind the cops and just going
I'll make up a fun story for you and then walked away and he just went the whole way home
I also like
Yeah but it's not stuff that he sees on the wall it's like
I don't know man I just think that this kind of behavior in demonization that he engages in his destructive
That goes nowhere good
I think a better use of his time and resources would be
YouTube learn
To make peace
With some of his past
Sprite and maybe stop insisting that everybody else has to pay for
Cuz he was the one who
Did the things that I actually don't even
I mean for the most
Part don't think or
Necessarily a problem
You know I
Think that
If
In a few was pressuring people into getting abortion
That's pretty f*****-up
B I think
That just
Getting a bunch of
People pregnant
Baby
Irresponsible and maybe a best
Yusuf
Are people's emotional energy bud
Whatever I mean it's your life dude
That's how he has long as you're not say
I don't know
Starting a crusade against Auntie against abortion that culminates
In Supreme Court Victory destroying the basic right that we've had for the past 50 years
I didn't ya do what you do do what you do
Yeah I think he
I don't know I don't want to over psychoanalyzing but that was a little bit too
Too close to that but
I just see that the way that he has these
These bulshit thing
From his past really feel like they're informing these
Right positions that he has
In the present
And he's
He's not
Some sort of
Brilliant Mastermind
Shouldn't be too hard to
To see through his
Poorly-built
What's mine Ciara
People just don't care to pay attention and he yells funny things sometimes people to
Just kind of think he's
Funny
Anyway look the timing of this
Just before the midterms
Don't tell me we're going to talk about
The f****** Midtown
Ohmygod ohmygod I hate everyone
And it won't
Bible prophecies
Shootings at abortion clinic
The blame on us and tried legitimize their culture of death
So the prediction of false flags at abortion clinics or Rally's is a very obvious attempt to preemptively justify any active Iowa
What's that are committed by his ideological allies as being fake and
Just the last trying to make themselves look like they do
He's doing this because he knows damn well that far right
Extremists are very likely to attack abortion-related Targets in the wake of this ruling
Even without the ruling attacks against abortion providers has been on a giant upswing in recent years
The National Abortion Federation just put out their statistics for 2021 and they showed
Big jumps in the numbers of assault and battery cases
I am stalking cases related to abortion providers
And just like clockwork this weekend we saw some violence Direct
Did that the portion
Supporters
Jean Lugo a cop running for Rhode Island States assaulted Jen Rourke his democratic
Make appointment adipro Choice rally
And Cedar Rapids Iowa a truck drove through a group of protesters running over one woman's ankle
Video circulated of police shooting tear gas at protesters in Arizona fire and canisters into a crowd
From the windows
Set the state capitol building
No need to perpetuate a false
Swag there's already plenty of violence coming from anti-abortion people of the state
Also Alex is saying if his ruling will galvanise the Democrats for the midterms but there's a few problems
This idea
The first is that it seems to suggest that Alex thinks that the Supreme Court ruling might be a false flag
He said that the timing of the latest mass shootings were suspicious
Just because of the midterms
But
He's noting the timing here to which is
Weird so he saying
That the Supreme Court release this ruling in advance of the midterms
In order to
2 galvanized
The Democrat
I mean I don't know what other implication you could bet the only thing
Right that's why
The possibility
Alright he's addicted to being a weirdo
As I don't think that this necessarily is going to get everyone super jazzed about the Democrats
At present there is the only viable alternative to vote for other than the GOP so that lesser of two evils Dynamic is still in
One place but the criticism about the Supreme Court decision that I've seen
Has been directed as much at the Democrats
Republicans
And I criticism as well Warren
The Democratic party has an ample opportunity to take action that would have made access to abortion more secure and no steps were not
Democratic
Conservative Supreme Court nominees who were
Clearly lying about their opinions on Raw
People like Nancy Pelosi should get a particular bit of criticism being the leader of the party in the house
For the message
Inside by her support
Only aunt
Detroit's Democrats in the house
I think I think that a lot of criticism
Fat
Talk about this
Before we started recording like
Yeah haters are going to hate
Yeah I think a lot of people Justice
Expect that
This is what the Republic
Composition
Most
A lot of the criticism is
You f****** do something to anything make ever
Wasn't
The inevitability that we would reach
That we told you we would
It's
I mean I would have I would be stoked
Somebody just come out and said I'm sorry
Sure I would've been stoked of Nancy Pelosi said I am sorry we screwed this one up
I don't expect Nancy Pelosi
Prizer painter or something
People in Congress who may have said that we just don't know
I think the
Realistically there is
Far greater chance
Of people feeling jaded
And not
Voting
That's based on this
I think it
Is any effect
What you expect in the midterm based on the results of seeing is
Yeah people getting obviously angrier
Protesting
But not necessarily Translating that
Into electoral
Support of demek
No the Democrats had
Decision leaks
We already knew this was coming
Delete
We knew it was aided already happen
Abortion is already been gone
And the Democrats had so much time
To think of a thing to say
The day it happened
Right and the best they came up with is
You're going to need to vote and give us more money
So no they are not going to do well in the midterm
It's if they wanted to Galvanize people they could have come out and they really probably could have been babe
Somebody to come out with a f******
Fire and brimstone as let's march today let's all go we're Congress you join us
We're going to overthrow the capitol
Obviously not that far but something something like that
Instead they came out with
I'm going to fart my
Dance
Party pants
Exactly
What a message
I think that we've had a few days since this
Do you know
And
Maybe that's not enough time to really see
Some actual good leadership emerge
How would have hoped it would have a bunch of
I don't know I think
You know I'm not I'm not
Advancing the idea that people
Shouldn't Vote or you know
Try and avoid
Beauty School the about voting
But it's
If I were to look at this from an analytical perspective
I think
That
You end up probably having less people vote for Democrats
In the midterms
Demolish I think I think
The effect of this is the exact opposite
What Alex's
Disgusting
And the
You know false flags at abortion clinics and all that s*** is just him covering for his buddies
It's a real bummer couldn't be more simple and less
You are insane
But
In 2008
We overwhelmingly voted in the Democrats
The most popular president of my lifetime
Was the president
Who had promised
Codify Roe v Wade into law
He had a supermajority
He had it all baby
And the moment that he got elected
They didn't do f*** off
Aaron said they f****** bailed-out Banks and all that s*** it's over for the Democrats
Happened he had another shot they could have done it earlier they can probably f****** do it right now
What they want
So they won't
It's a mess so they're done
Also is
You know he wants
People pay a lot for gas
Turns out
Who's the president
With his controllers
Loading up in his notes and is teleprompter to tell you
And tell me
Use policies
Causa
In the stores and sells the food and drinks
Alcohol
For sales are legal
I think you're so stuck
They're now going with that in the news while he's right
The gas station
Kris prices when
And why should they announce recharging about 10% more than they should
Actuaries I'm not defending
Future
In WoW
You
It's so weird that Alex is mad by
Endorsing a holiday from gas taxes
Weirder I was going out of his way to make
Make excuses for gas companies engaging in price gouging
It's so wild it's almost like
You'll be mad at B No Matter What by next
Billy doesn't he'll support the gas company's no matter what they actually do
Because ideas
Give me an 88 might as well be biting
How dare he say that he's going to take
Percent off of gas prices
Now everybody's mad at all companies for increasing gas prices by 10%
But I'll tell you what you know
Because Brayden lowered race
By 10%
Future they're going to have to charge 100,000 more percent you just got there doing what's best for us
Let me know them and not you go f*** yourself
Go fuc yourself
It's really weird
I'm heavily invested in
Is another way of saying what you just said I honestly don't know if he is but like
Is emotionally decompression
Estranged
So here again is another dishonest framing of the left
Response to the Supreme Court
AOC running around like a chicken with his head cut off in front of me
Blac Chyna
Abortion ruling here is
All of it is just dishonest
Framing
Call boy
Honestly
I mean
Look
You have
Constant gas to talk about white birth rates
He has Nick Fuentes on his
Is f****** website as his own channel on there
Calm down
Calm down buddy
Sound like an a******
The giant race
So Alex takes a number of calls
And try to get the temple
From time
I know that we've heard a lot of people call in and pray
No trays on this episode
But this
That mean
Just constant talking about weird ideas about God
We as Believers must continue to recognize that God is still in control of this world
And we believe
That he is in control
And we need to update
Abandon the evil
Pranita abandon
Sickness
Taking over this country
And get back to
Because God will change his mind and give us a reprieve
We just
To recognize who's in
These people
Evil
Abortion
Agundis now freely for
40 years
Mom before I even knew what it was they
And it's time
Now
God to take
Slices
Stop this overnight
Directions
We will begin to be blessed as soon as we begin to make the right decisions in Reverse this
Your behavior changes God's mind
I believe the message there was
We need to remember everything is in God's hands
And that there's nothing we can do
Alex's message was
Well you should change your behavior and then got a like
Honestly that also is what she was saying
She was saying that everything is in God's hands God's in total control
But your behavior will do
Dictate God changing his mind
You're in control of God
Right
Yeah
Everybody's
Beliefs and religion I'm telling you this right now
Five stars
Go home
Seems like on it on the surface as a pretty
Like
Decent point I guess
Except it's not
It's okay
Then the stuff you normally hear
Alex doesn't understand a lick or what he saying
Alex
Thanks a lot
Time long time
Fan
Whole note
Endeavor of trying to let
Play abortion
It's a colossal waste
We're never going to agree
You know there's always
Both sides
One way or the other
Lost Boys
How do we deal with
In lieu of
The whole notion of abortion
Day or night
We need to draw Linus
Collectively
Draw line in the
Civil Right
Molested
Outside of that timeline
Existing laws on the books
Extrapolated or Quantified for me
Here's when I'm getting it
The people running the abortion
Operation or anti-human eugenicist
But
The whole movie humanizing devalue Life
Is the entire globalist agenda so I see this as
A very positive move
Human should decide to protect children and
The week
Good enough and informed enough to not make bad decisions
And then abortion would be obsolete by
Alex absolutely doesn't understand that this collars at all cuz he's not really that good at processing things
Right
This caller has a proposal that seems like a rational solution
But it's actually just a way to rephrase the exact same problem he saying is a waste of time
He says we need to decide at what point a fetus has human civilization
Anything that's done to it past that point would be subject to already exist
Claws like the ones against assault or murder
That sounds good on paper Until you realize that the argument would just shift to trying to litigate exactly what that point is
In all the nuances and caveat that caller recognizes exist now would still exist
Right now that point is when it
Doubt right if I were to
Suggest that the point should be at Birth this guy is not going to agree with me
If Alex says that Concepcion I'm not going to agree with him and we're right back where we started trying to legislate the point at which
Abortion should be illegal
No it's
More of like okay
So we've got
Say
What do you want to go with
WhatsApp
Say about four and a half months
You know
Out of the total number of months
We'll compromise somewhere in between
I say
19 years of a
I appreciate this Dollar on the one hand because it does seem like he wants to break out of the reactionary mold that Alex lives in
But I also kind of resent him because his position
Fourth something
It sounds like it's smarter and more moderate than the
Standard position
It's really not
The same
The problem that he's going to run into
Because he's a big dumb
Is no matter what
If you want to say
Oh we're going past
And we're going all Civil Right
We're not going to abortion
Right-wing assholes going to be like
If you have sex with a pregnant woman than your molester
Sting the fetus
And that's going to be illegal
Because that's how f****** stupid
Oldham
How would you end up defrosting a fetus
You did what you gave your social security number
Disputed can't sign a contract
How about that every set everything if security number and then what if your
Like a parent
And you start like a Tik Tok channel of your
Like fetus in the womb
Hey demonetized exploitation you can only work that
Fetus for about 4 hours per day if you go any longer than that you got to get twins
The grinding up into in some really complicated territory and some Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen territory
It's just funny that Alex
Does not understand at all with this guy's say Alex is trying to put together what
Person is saying to them only really come up
Quit talking point
And that
Is even a problem when
Explain
He's just points that he has already
With you Alex
Pro-Line
And you know there's always
Expose
Sexualize our children
They won
Right that's why I'm saying Fraulein in the stand wasn't that
Third trimester
Say okay this baby now
The doctor or anybody molest or kills or does anything to that baby
Existing laws if we have on the boat
You're saying you're saying
That it needed declare third trimester in human declared has human right to that point
What
What's get all the arguments
National news
Hypocrite
You didn't go to prison for 10 years
Go to prison
I have murdered my children
I don't
Any national news shows have ever talked about Alex getting an abortion or paying for a bunch in his
Past literally just got it's just it's just
About us
We're the only people who bring it up
Yeah one else is talked about it
Nope
And I don't think that we publicize
Things too much outside of just talking about it on the show when it comes up because I think it's kind of
Something that I think is important
I don't care the problem
Apocracy to it in the bility to learn a lesson
From the outcomes of his behavior
And recognize that the access to abortion that he had when he was younger
Is what
Facilitated his life
To be able to go the way it did
I know that he like
To play this game of life
I wish I could have all 20 of these sweet children
Here in my life and I've I'm deprived of them luxury that he gets to say that now because he did
Didn't have those 20 children
She had access to reproductive health care that he is now trying to
To deprive everyone else up
And that's the problem not
The fact
If if whatever punishment they
Decide
Whichever it may be
Whatever
Legislature wants it if they said
Let's make this retroactive as well
For the past 50 years
Do you think it would still happen or do you think
Let's call it
90% of the Republicans would have been f******
Equalizing that same goddamn
Oh my God
It's old people saying I want the next year's to be
Worse
I want the Next Generation
But suck
And die
Miserably because I don't get to be rich forever
Or I want the next Generations to have
Asturi win
Lindsey's
Battles that were won
You know the blood in
Sweat
Pictures of
People who came before us
Skip
Amaya
Kind of
Shity
This caller also is shity
Paul in the great state of Michigan are on the air
Hey Alex
Weave
We taking the beach
This is the Victory and now it's
It's time to move on through the mainland
So you can pick
The part anyway
But it's it's raising awareness
Raising awareness
To agree with me right
Analogy of Landing in Normandy perfect Starts Now
Yeah it's her like take this and you know other things that have already been set on this show
This is something that's really important to recognize is a mentality of
The people who are
You know now
You should be very worried about
Yahoo
This is viewed as a begin
This is viewed as a beginner
And what
Next
Is all of the
Stuff that has
Maybe both
Be able
It's better afforded to all manner of folk in The Help
Lgbtq + community
Women
Are afforded
Reproductive Health Care
Housing rights
Less than a year
There will be at least two or three states where gay marriage is illegal again
We're less than a year and I think that you have to even look further than
I think
Discrimination type laws
They're going to
Rollback would be surprised
If it's civil rights
Becomes a question
It's going to be on the docket
That's for sure I
Just
Think you should be aware that people
Like this
Exist and are not uncommon
That
Rolling back row vs way it is landing on the beach at now
Yeah
You even hear the mentality that Alex
Express earlier
Gay marriage
You could give them a little bit and they take exactly sexualized
The whole idea what they're saying is that they're like
We were so nice when we let gay people exist in public and now they want more
Well I guess we'll just have to teach them a lesson
Your rights can be taken away
So we can update on abortion laws
From caller
In Wisconsin did Thumper
Tell Alex
I'm calling from the great state of Wisconsin
Listed here
Pretty that within the last
Planned Parenthood of Wisconsin has
Abortion
Because of a 18-49 laws
That's been on the book
But it was nullified by Roe v Wade
But now that that's been overturned
Being an abortion-free
God
It doesn't matter though we haven't totally stopped yet we're trying
Clinics in Wisconsin have temporarily called off performing abortions because there's an uncertainty about the legal status
At the moment
Focus their efforts at this point with helping people get appointments out of state
Organizing transportation
For that one
Also the Governor and District
Attorneys of the County's containing Milwaukee and Madison have said that they aren't going to enforce anything
Governor Evers
Steven said that he wouldn't point
NEPA is that wood
He has the governor will be open
Waving prison sentences for anyone convicted of
This will likely end up leading to a Long Dong
Court battle
Smitley lead do the band going away
There isn't strong political will to enforce
173 gears
Give you some idea of how long ago that was
Louis Pasteur was still alive
Ivan Pavlov the guy with the dogs
He was born here
There was a proximately 35 years before the invention of the fountain
Yeah
So why they're such cowards
That's so weird to me
I don't know why everybody is being so cowardly about
I mean Planned Parenthood f*** you
Don't shut down
What are they going to do
Tell him to come get
Why is everybody letting laws happen like they mean anything anymore honestly the only thing that matters is who's enforcing
And when
Well I would say
I guess
Probably what you answer to
Would be that there's a greater risk
Of cause
Greater harm
If you don't
Follow that
It could be used against you too
Harm your ability to provide the care
That you do provide
And from illegal stamp
Sure
And while I understand that
I'm just guessing that I would also like to say
Win-win-win we're Assuming he's still able to
Facilitate
Carol by helping title transfer for out-of-state
And such
I don't
Know if it's the
The biggest eel in the world
I don't know
I just I mean ask
After you read that opinion
By Clarence Thomas
Not good I mean it's very clear that
Laws in this country the Constitution
All me nothing
It doesn't mean anything anymore
I'm not sure I fully agree with that but I do think that if you read that opinion
It is
Something that would
Save the needs to be a point where people put the foot down
Because they're signaling where
Possible things go
What do next
When is now haha
From that standpoint I do kind of get what you're saying about like Planned Parenthood to saying no
Continue to operate come get us
Come prosecutor
Trial we get the whole f****** world they're making us
I understand from that perspective
But then again I don't run
A gigantic
Multi
Tri-State organization
They could have some kind of
Exposure somewhere
And you know
There's a net good
That is done by Planned Parenthood
And if there is some kind of way that doing that would
Hurt their ability to
Vikare and other places
I'm saying I don't know
I'm just guessing I totally understand I just I'm just at this
Like what happened
Needs to be
Treated
With the reality of what they just treated it
Which is that it is D-Day on Normandy
And if we act like this is something that we can go through in the court
That's where the problem is
The courts are a problem
Yeah
Color from Wisconsin which you're mad Wisconsin
No I was just fun
Flashlight to bad Road
Do this discolor
Man this is out of control
One more thing
I just wanted you to know that I do
Pray for you and
Make a year and a half ago I was praying because
Now I know occasionally you go on one of these Rants and
Should I be listening to this
Amarillo conservative lady I teach Sunday school and
You know it should I be listening to that until I asked
Not everybody is a
50 plaster old Sunday school teacher
But I need Warriors
Nobody
Nobody fight
Lights for the babies
Nobody fights
For my children
That makes me so sad
Makes me so sad
I just
The number of steps that it takes
To get to that
Point
I mean
Listen Whitney it's like the opposite of the Sands Fang
When there were only one set of footprints is cuz you walked as far away from
From Jesus
Through s*** at his face
Run towards Alex Jones
The thing that surprises me about
The clip like that in the car like that is hurting
Instincts are good
At the beginning of it
There is something
If you are aching
Conservative Christian person let's say
You're listening to the show you should be asking yourself should I be listening to
The exact shows f***** up
He is
Angry
Blasphemous
Concern should be there and
The rationalizing it by praying and thinking the God is telling you that Alex's
The best Champion for the babies
Is
This is
This is the reality of the kind of stuff that's discussed on Infowars
You
Teach Sunday school
At a church where they believe that
There are interdimensional beings
Invading trying to steal your soul and then possess you and make you go bad
Then yes you should be listening to that
Alex's
Mushrooms with Mike Tyson
Really protecting the cat
Yep nobody fights
Thank thank the Lord for that
Because there's nothing
We should thank the Lord for in that is that
But Alex didn't end up going to Satan
Cuz it was closed so it was close was it
I can do that
I'm not claiming that
The power of God
You have the power of six
Here's the deal
I had constipation
Quiet you have constipation because of the streak of the devil why either share at the shift
At the shift until I love this I love this f******
Stupid idea of like I had the power of Satan but I rejected adjusted
You accepted that you didn't know I had it
But then I was like now I'm good
I got too many women pregnant with this time I made a deal with the devil and then I experienced what I wanted ice
I want to take it back I mean he does realize that you don't get to
To take back a deal with the Devil
Like that's the most in
Part of the ironic punishment
Also the devil likes
Let you test drive a car
Just like hey man actually now that I see their ironic
Consequences for this I want out of the deal and the devil was like
We got a 30-day card
Oh no
I didn't use capital letters
Sovereign citizen typo loophole with the Devil
People who listen to
Recognized is just an expression of a single person's entirely insane inner turmoil.
Refuses to deal with
Because he's found a way to make that turmoil profit
Alex acts out his behavior hurts people and it doesn't matter because without that
Turmoil
Alex isn't interesting
He's just another extreme-right dumb dumb everyone can write off and ignore
Like Joe Rogan isn't having G Edward Griffin on as a guest
Drily discusses burter s***
Flagrant 2
Phyllis Schlafly to come on and get drunk and talk
S*** with them
Buchanan isn't going to be a guest judge on kill Tony
Like this is like Alex's it would be on Dancing With the Stars
Yeah
Unfortunately probably
This
Like insanity and nonsense
Is
What he does
He's only
The only thing that makes him interesting path
A cernobil from
Anybody else who's just
Another idiot
F****** dumb dumb reading headlines and then
It is it is a testament to the
The power of
Somebody just shouting all the time
It should be harder than that and it should
Seem like there's more
To it
And I don't know if there is shouting isn't the only thing
There's also like I think it would
One of the largest parts of his career has been
Finding the right gullible people
And insisting that he has secret knowledge he can bestow upon them
Also
Is
Maybe one
Of his
His car everybody wants to join a cult
That's the problem how many people just really want to join a cult
Yeah they want that to Arcade esoteric info
Comforting somebody knows what's
Going on there's an Allure of the thing that you're not supposed to know that you were being told you can do and
Remember recently Ted Nugent was on
Remember what we talked about with Lee Greenwood
Yeah what happened with him being cancelled at the NRA confer
He hates America
Separate the art from the artist
You can say it is
We're coming.
Grandstand for onboard stand for OB lorestan for a poor people
Bill prosperity
Alright
Proud of you
I thought gold was playing couldn't be reversed at this point everyone was dead already
Has more than 7 billion people were going to
Every loans by World we're on the way back up baby
Boy
Anyway calls in
Buddy from
That's what I think I don't convince okay
Bumper in Michigan bumper thanks for calling
Oh yeah I was calling in just
I'm going to take
This was done on purpose
Supposed to turn the woman out like
Hornet
For the next
Boat
To try to keep power the house
California is
Corporate-owned un owned
Chair and that
They're going to do with me
Abortion
Free
Why the women out
Cancel women
California already have the Women's Clinic
Set up with the bank
Hey Ya
Makeup
Streamliner pipeline
Dry cleaning for organ donations
From the motor fetuses absolutely
That is the most
Correct anyone has ever been
About any
Well you know
You are totally correct that is their plan B
Alright
Is this caller this next caller has a really interesting point in
Supreme Court decision is great because it gives
Choice
That gives you the choice to not have a choice yeah I was going to say what choice is that
It's really just about the war
And y'all are doing really good on call
All day outlook
Weather of the robot Rover
Weight station was organic
Orchestrated
5 p.m.
A choice
Turbeville
Or serve God
What a great choice
God says you're either hot or cold do not be lukewarm I'll spit you out of my mouth it makes it a very clear.
Chase online
Open
This is a good thing
It's so wore out in the open between the devil and God
In your head
Cool
Love my back
Conscientious objector
I love
That just
I realize that I have the choice
Between serving good or before Friday
I can serve good or I could
Conserve some evil and have a little bit of an abortion but now I can't have any abortions
Can I serve can I serve with a side of vegetables
How about that
So f****** stupid
Anyway this caller goes on to talk about how he's a felon and Alex is not live
Listening to him cuz
Based on the details he's giving
He might have committed something really f*****
The Supreme Court decision is great
I am a convicted
Nonviolent
Non-farm
Non drug-related crime
That narrows it down
My life has no value
Founder of
I'm still trying to hold
Strong
In the Wake God
Wants me to be
And I recognize
I'm not committed
What's wrong
Didn't know what I was doing
It is long story I didn't know what I was doing
ATF off
I'm sorry what
There's millions of innocent people
Constitutional
You shouldn't
What
Stop this you got to stop rationalizing for your callers
Explicitly said that his crime wasn't gun-related he pissed off at UPS and it wasn't related
Anything violent it wasn't guns and it was a
Drugs
This leaves
Very few options well I'm going to go ahead and say that there was a bomb
Is
Kinda thought I had was you got in trouble with the 80s
Let me know what you were doing
8 it's not drugs
It's not guns
It's not viola
It will it's not alcohol or tobacco Firearms alcohol was involved
Trouble
Yeah it mean if it's a bomb
Yeah or some sort of a racket
Tearing kind of
Operation like a fish or like he was selling
May be settling down
Yeah that's a good point
That's the part I could have seen it being like a non-violent crime or sales or something
Firearm-related
Anyway I don't like Alex
Do you think I chose some freak unlock
Look it up cuz Tanner is enough of a like
Like
Not super common name
I figured I could find like Tanner ATF or something I looked around and found a couple people who got arrested for supper
Definitely
Yeah
Figure it out and I realized
What are you doing
Probably a bob
Alex
There's a lot of
Legal things going on
You know we have the Supreme Court
We need somebody
Common
And talk
Truth
No no
What do you think
Is it boring snow
How dare you
Junior varsity
Oh no and I was typing soon
Forgot about that
When you're looking
Dislike world-changing news you need to get somebody with gravis
You need to go
Get somebody who's like a real heavy-hitter
Aman about
Great job
Harrison Smith
Just how out-of-control
But then
Editing videos
Today's ruling on Roe v Wade
Yesterday's ruling on the Second Amendment saying New York understates can't bar
Concealed carry
Big deal
What is the aftermath what does it really mean
America this weekend
Judge Joe Brown
Judge Joe Brown It's he's actually judge
Yeah yeah yeah I always forget which of them are actually not actually for a long time
Wait longer
Yeah
He's also 74 years old boring people I've ever heard
No
Steven
I'm not endorsing anybody like
Personally I don't know if any of these people a problem or whatever but like
I used to
A termites life where I was home
Allah Allah
I didn't go to college
Free year I just worked at a movie theater size generally there
Or later shift anyway
And
You know the feeling
Things about these judge
Alright
Kind of like the you know standard Opera
Mills Lane unwatchable
Is going from Celebrity Deathmatch
I don't know what's going on never heard you never heard of that one
1 South is fun
Animal Court
Judge Joe Brown
Was so boring
Yeah it was not good I'd much prefer Judge Mathis
41 Hughes in Chicago
And so like
Hometown there was a there was a feeling of like I'm in Columbia
I can get on the Megabus and come with me
He's not one of those New Yorker at late judge
Now and I think he was a little bit more entertaining
Cuz I mean you're doing a
A TV show
Brad was just kind of like well
If nothing else is on
Alright I'll watch
It's very boring
Yes
Yes quite
He is
Really really really boring everybody like
Small claims court
What a weird thing for people to watch on TV it's the precursor to True Crime
Gateway drug
The courtroom let's go further back
Stepping stone that ruined our brains
Speak now I want some enterprising True Crime people
To go back through the seasons of Judge
Follow up on these people what is their backstories where-are-they-now like do the whole thing cereal
1 case
Absolutely look
I think that there is a
Bizarre preoccupation with the lake Court shows and what have
I wasn't immune to it when I was younger I enjoyed watching
But also we shouldn't talk because everyone loves when you cover a deposition
I read mysterious
Judge Joe Brown I was
Seriously considering not even talking about him because he was making me fall asleep
But he is such a bigot that we know all about
It doesn't start right away but there will be some mornings
That he uses some slurs you know I wish it would be more surprising that a judge was a bigot
Yeah
Man this guy
It sucks
So here is the first thing he gets into
This is where I was like wow this is just born
Questions but where do you want to go from what I just laid out
Let's start off
With New York's reacts
City mayor's reaction to
The ruling about
To snore
To be armed and
There's a good thing
Blythe
Arlo this mayor
Get shop there and not our but the Lawless
Advocates
U.s. Supreme Court
I wonder if these Hypocrites on the clown show with
DJ Shakes committee would be interested in that because that's
What they were accusing
Mystery
Really
It sounds similar sounds exactly like that
The j-6 committee is going to do that cuz there's
Boxing on January 6th
No no no
Let's see what they should do as they should look at their investigation and instead of doing that one
Take all the things that might be similar to investigations
And do all of those
And then let
Trump be president forever also extend
Things that aren't similar at all
That's a good idea but only for Democrat
Alright we've been doing some of these televised hearings drop everything let's investigate every Democrat
Craddock governor and throw them in prison now
There's some real lgbtq opposition
Let's say from Joe Brown
But there's also
Some opposition to Good Humor
Showcase
Inconsistent
Selfish
Sean immediate head
Pleasure without any I'm just
Standing
Or respect
For the other issues that are brought up
I mean
Which more revocable in that and then I tell a joke about it
See you whenever you see your human
A man or a woman
No you see a successful
Somebody
Somebody is born
Somebody mature
Family tree
And then you get the next
Generation so he spoke want to cut it off because they can't have
It's just a
Absolutely
I
I'm flattered
Well
See
Okay
I don't understand what his point was
His point is that
People want to f***
Too much and they don't have kids
No the last
Is endorsing lgbtq Plus
Issues and supporting those communities share because according to Judge Joe Brown this will make it so noisy
Screw anymore
And there won't be any people because
People on the left handle
People reproducing
That was basically.
Behind
Oh okay so
The entire left is trying to destroy
Breed it
More
Also interesting take on
The support for providing access
For puberty blockers
I don't think that this is a joke
Remember
89 years old
In this state they were talking about having to Bertie block or soda person
When is never getting to the point where
Buy a pack of cigarettes
Military decide to have their balls cut off
They've been allowed to take
Don't want you to know
Give me the best part of your life right there
I need to go just all of us
Every Woman
Needs to turn to your part
Partner or whomever man within a and radius of you
And just kill them
I like sex and I like the carnal pleasures
But
I think it would be
Humiliating
Boners are the best part of life
This is a judge and a
God-ordained
Crusader against the globalist discussing their love of boners
Just want to remind everybody that every judge I have ever met
Or have learned anything about
Has had
Such a punk
Legalmine
Reinhold
You know just a well
I mean he was great
Yeah I I don't think you're going to get much analysis of law
Three cheers for boner
Yeah it is fun whenever you remember that judges are just money
Everything
Everything with Power Road
I was looking up how long he did that show I accidentally stumbled onto
How much he made on that chicken
Millions of god dammit
Yeah
Steve
Here Comes
Warning
Coming up trans slur
Coming up in this next clip here's my
Conspiracy theory for your Dan I'm I'm a judge
I have had the power
Of life and
Death over another man
And what I'm telling you right now
Is that the left
Wants to keep little boys from having boners
That way they won't know that borders of the only reason that men exist
Completely pointless there's nothing else to do with your life it's just boners
That's the left
What we want what kind of cases
Is Judge Joe Brown dead
Before Eve
Went to pee because they're definitely wasn't
The cases on Judge Joe Brown show
It was more like you owe someone $200
He was but he was probably more like this
His parking ticket is is a waived
Look again there's a slur coming up
And also just
Is really disrespectful attitude towards trans people
There's another thing to it
Part of this whole thing with the tranny thing is that
Situation
The next time the Titanic go down without
When he goes down
Don't have that kind of man
And they want to deal with
Oh
I got on a dress
I should be able to get in there
Position
Smashum
I'm on the other side of the ship
The Sharks do to women and children get away safe
Lifeboats are here and there's a bunch of men in dresses trying to
The girls
And women
I mean like
Quite frankly
Bigotry aside which is
Condemnable in disgusting
That is like
Bad open mic comedy
Yeah
The level of processing and
And thought that is
Like I could
I could see somebody
That
I kind of had maybe later
I recognize them vaguely from other open mics
Yeah
Someone who I would not want to be friends with me
You know you end up accidentally having
To see them cuz
You're both at Kohl's or whatever
Get you
In trouble
Closest Rowdy enough to fetch it's not going to fly
Some other open mic
To me like it seems like he's
Trying to be funny but it's
Time
Itza it's a failure and he's also expressing position
He clearly hold
Yeah
I went from having
0 opinion about Joe Brown she wanted to throw a brick through his f******
Can window really quickly at The Brick at 8
Very little time and all you had to do was say one thing on
It was really I've heard a bit
In the past
From his show and then also appearing couple times
And it's remarkable yeah I went from I'm so bored by this guy and his
Dumb bad humor to like
Holy s*** out guy is hate
No that's a man that cannot live in societies suggesting that trans women
Folks
Who cannot
Bear giving up their seat on a bus metaphorically or like you
A space on a life raft
I am so that's what's motivating it and so you should Chum of the sharks
Behind
Disgusting
No yeah that's meant
Horrible person
The statement of a man who cannot live in society
But you can't live
So however that needs to go down
Well you've got millions of dollars
He doesn't leave with the rest of us anyway with millions of dollars
So Judge Joe Brown
Sports women
I would argue that he doesn't
From fiscal
We have this thing I have a motto
It's all about
Protecting Womanhood
And promoting manhood why because the women are resource
Bear the children
50 women at the same time so we've always had this thing
When the population goes down the more successful then they get around now we have
The man can procreate they go off we go off to the war
Doors
We sacrifice ourselves
Wives and families and
Life goes on in your jeans
Because the mother birthed
The children
She could have been pregnant when you lost your life
Bandits what it is beautiful
That's nuts I mean he
Is expressing his support for women
Based on Timothy resource resource
Not as people
Yeah well and what he described men as is essentially
Useless
Pointless
And
Should be gotten rid of because once we got cloning baby we don't need anybody to fight the wars
Did anybody have any kids we don't need any man
To protect nobody
Get rid of
What's the Brave New World alfredo
I mean
And it is a very antiquated
Sort of way to look
People I think
I mean it's borderline he's like well you
You can see from the way that
Their chimney shape that they're actually very weak
You know what their brains don't
Yeah exactly
I think
When you're starting to look at
All women that is important because they're a resource
Sure.
Not see the evolution but also I do believe it is but also yeah f*** off
I mean I think it's
There's a problem here and that is we have
A guy who's supposed to be a legal expert
Keys talking
A lot of nonsense
Tom at the same time
A lot of the nonsense that he's talking
Seems to be
Supported in some ways by his
Extreme bigger
It seems like that's the
The part that's real things about these laws
Are not real
Because they are
Extends even further
Ordinarily
You can't
Discriminate against anyone because of race
Call her
National origin religion
AIDS
Medical condition
And
What we have now is a different kind of thing when somebody says I have
Annex
I can make
I can be lying through my tree for the
Michelle and I can get
Declared to be a woman
Troubling
So I think that's really dumb
Worry I actually worry about Joe Brown based on the things that he saying
A lot of it just makes no sense in this is kind of a good example of that
As fast as I can tell he's suggesting that there are these categories
But you're not allowed to discriminate based on
And now they're adding this other one that people can
Can choose to opt into
I guess so they can get protection from discrimination
The problem is if they already
Are protected by anti-discrimination laws
Well people traditionally vulnerable don't realize this but they're just as protected by Auntie just
Termination laws as the group's
But they are attacking
Well they don't know it because
Cuz they're not the ones usually being
Discriminate
For instance the same rules that protect gay men from being discriminated against because they're doing bad would protect I had
Sexual ban for pigs
Discriminated against
Because there
Heterosexual
But that doesn't make sense
That's because heterosexuals are the only people with power and everybody else have died
The same applies in the case of trans related discrimination bills
You couldn't refuse to hire someone because they are trans and you also couldn't
Refuse to hire someone because they're sick
Discrimination
Across-the-board
Joe can be all against this notion of anti-discrimination laws for sexual orientation put
I would imagine he cry bloody murder if he was applying for a job and
He was told that they only hire gay people
Discrimination
What is a white as I get to be discriminated against
I'll never learn this lesson
Anyway
In Switzerland
You have to own a gun
You do you have to unlock everybody has to offer
Joe Brown
Informs us that
He can kill you with a
Every able-bodied man from 17 to 56 is required to have a military
Grade 9 m m
In his possession
And a machine gun
A fully automatic
A real
And two hands
Grenades and Barry since Andre rounds of ammunition
They don't have any of these
Crazed old running around killing folk off in May
Not every now and then
Change for a 20
But I'm wanted two of my get off
Violent crime is zero
It brings it to me now
74 years old
But I've been to
Martial arts
Or
55 years and my shoulder
Open some of my associates
Probably train very quickly
A lot quicker than we could kill them with a pistol
Seems to be a trend
Very
Capable of violence
Once people
Just hypothetical violence that they could inflict on people
I'll tell you what everyone on Infowars
Their hands are
F****** Lethal Weapon right
I will tell you this.
Alright
I haven't
Been in a fight
Since I was 11 years old and I got second place
In a karate tournament ice
And I will absolutely beat the ever-living s*** out of Judge Joe Brown
If he would like to have a fight
At any point in time to Chicago
Email me I'll give you my address
Get the f*** out of here I could beat up at the death with my I'm glad that you're saying
Because I know of hubris
And I don't want there to be video of Judge Joe Brown kicking my ass
It's okay there's there's people
Martial arts
That are fun like exercise and you do katas and it's very important and it's meditation and then there's like
People who fight
Brighten ethika
Lili different picture
And if you are a mixed martial artist who trains at fighting alright
You can take any karate master
Murder that
So fast
It's a different thing
I don't do any of that and that's how easy it would be to be
Beat the s*** out of Judge Joe Brown
I would love for him to take you up on that just all my God I would add that would be great
All that but I think you'll be really funny that it would be futile.
Take my licks and laughing as hard as everybody else
Because Joe Brown sucks
This makes clear pee discusses how lgbtq folk existing essentially is the reason that the country is in
Decline
We're going over a cliff because we've attempted
Escalate
Free in favor of these people who want to
Let children in 15 cups
Stop lying down
And the other thing is is this
This thing about bullying look at
Back to the Future
Dog just bothering
Standing up for himself
Bully in his mouth
Instead of
Running roughshod over from we've always had this thing
In Human Society of boys
Becoming me and had to learn up
Stand up
It's cruel that process of that they're really afraid of men
Yeah they don't like it
55-year campaign
Emasculate
Bullying goes down exactly like Back to the Future
Always a movie my man
Yep
They just can't understand
And they have the imagination of
Lava rock
Like the idea that see there's always been this way so it makes sense
You take an older larger kid and you haven't beat the s*** out of a younger kid
And maybe the younger Campbell fight back and learn a lesson or he'll get himself or the other guy will continue to beat the s*** out
Life
It's just like the movies
It can't get any better than that it couldn't be a situation I didn't believe him because his dad didn't beat the
Then later on when they grew up they work together at the f****** shop nobody was
The boss
Just down the street
Brown listing off the people who
Men and hated man
So dumb one of the best Impressions I've ever heard of my life
This guy
Adomian 10K
55-year campaign
Emasculate
I heard just starting back in the mid-sixties when I was with you CLA is an autograph
You had the lesbians who hated man
D
Feminist who hated it they work men
The beta boys that hated it they couldn't be real man the gay folks
Didn't understand being a man
It ain't you got that anti-war crowd in there to Chad war is a man thing
Girls show their emotional
And shout and let it all hang out
So you get all of these together and they started to tried to and
The emasculation of the gun
Impression
I thought for sure that young George Carlin head rich
Return from the dead
I thought it was like
A clip from Cheech and Chong
I guess according to him it's impossible for gay people to be or gay men to be men
Guess the thief
Beecher and Hallmark of masculinity in
Boners
Boners he loves boners
Motors inside of a woman
Is the only thing that man is
Don't let me be frank about something
Judge Joe Brown is on Infowars cuz no one else wants him around
He's not somebody who is
Like we want legal Scholars
Come on we want somebody with a real good position
It like boners on the most important thing in the world
He has
Nobody
Knocking down his door to get his analysis of January
Or the Supreme Court decision
So he ends up on Infowars
Simultaneously
No actual scholar wants to go on Infowars
So you end up with Joe Brown being your expert that you get when there's some kind of illegal thing going on
Both of these parties are pathetic
Can they meet each other and that's why this conversation is happening
Cousin no one else wants to be around
Alex's show is a black hole for credibility
Judge Joe Brown
Is
A piece of s***
Drop slurs in the middle of interviews and no one wants him
So
To you you deserve each other
The show sucks
And that's my
Yeah they had a Rolodex somewhere like we meet up bigot with judge in front of their name
And reinholds
You've got moderate views
F****** in the wind I'm trying to sue him
Are just busy gambling on.
Yeah you went on a late-night Bender to the bed on
Supreme Court has made me lost his shirt you would have lost everything
This episode is really interesting to me on the sort of
Pretense of what you would expect it to be versus what it actually is
Frank you know there is the expectation that it's like haha celebration
Obviously it was like this hoorah like f*** you liberal tears and all this stuff
Kind of think like
This is the vibe you're going to get out of Infowars
It's really not
There's much
More of a like
We're now in the war
Down whatever like we push forward and kind stripped-back
Even Moeller technique
Yep
And I think that's troubling
Because
Seems to be where a lot of
The rights head is
And
Yeah they're not going to be done
Until it's only straight white
And even then they're not going to be done
Cuz then it'll be
Straight white men with
Brown eyes are bad people or the other or however you wanted to go the
The main point of these people who is we should have the power to do whatever we want
Long-dead
Before it comes down to eye color is probably true
That's probably true
But hey
Will be back Sunday
Isn't that up
Think if we do Wednesday episode it'll be not
I think we might need a little bit of a reprieve
Yeah but
You know like I said the dreamy creamy summer trying to position it in something
That is positive so
Help with that please do or I mean Friday
If there's anything else like other organizations
Is that you are
Incline towards
Support them
Will have the
Feel like you need to
Support this one just because it's
Something good
We have
Totally promoted
Please
Give
Feel drawn to get
And I
Cognitive dissonance
Fellas
Will be this Friday okay
Set with there's some live stream of some
Description from cogdis folks will be making an appearance on
So yes
Yeah we'll be back until then
We outside
It's knowledge.com
We are interest and I'll just go find that go to bed Jordan
TobyMac but until then and bcx pork hope you all have a wonderful dream creamy summer
What the sex robot
Alex
Birthstone colors