Air Jordan
I have great respect for its knowledge B. I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
The altar of Sweeney Todd
What's Alex Jones
Jordan
Jordan question for you
Unexpected
As we all know
Mccreamy song
Right did the worst put on notice
Is that everything should be dreamlike and cream like
Oh yeah
A GoFundMe that was raising money for apiary
Abortion access
Logistics Group
And
The initial goal at $5,000 I thought that was unrealistic you are being very pie in the
Guy with that 5K
Yes and we hit it
Quite quickly no more than that
It's it's B
I can't thank people enough for their generosity is is at
I'm Blown Away by how how
Consistently I'm I'm surprised
By how great our listener
Thank you all so much
Search for
I mean that goal of $5,000 with the expectation that kind of like we're doing this until September
September know what to do
We keep it going until September or if we launch a new one at some point
I don't know
But there are some reviews of ice creams on there
I have
That's why people are donate I have been celebrating
The success of the fundraiser by eating some ice cream
Most recently as we recording this is the chocolate pretzel McFlurry
Right can't tell you what I think about it it's over on the fundraiser
Spoiler alert it sucks it's really bad
Go to that GoFundMe page for the review of a McFlurry
Blurry it's a chocolatey pretzel mix I've just spoiled the review
My bright spot Dan is in a similar vein
Bye
Today when you were reading their list
Breeding podcast
This evening we will be doing will be joining both the scripted
And conspiracies podcast
Tripsy
To join them for their 5:30 Central
You're much better at this than I am
And then later on after that will be doing the same similar thing with cognitive dissonance guys a lot of
Maybe too much
Play some other time
Kind enough to invite us to join them for their fundraiser stream
And that route 730 so won't be on at 5:30 and 7:30 and you can listen to us this morning I think his being placate
In between those two live streams we will actually be live streaming us
Throwing my couches off of the
Oh you know what we could do we could live stream an episode of Watch
Magician
No we couldn't
Episode
Alright
I want to come on you
I'll be happy to come on anytime
We have an episode to go we're going to talk about June 29th 2020
Two interesting
This episode
Yes obviously there's some bigotry that will be flying around
For sure there'll be some things that are annoying
But this episode is actually kind of a palate cleanser
In Subway's
There is a narrative Arc to this thing
That does not come to a satisfying conclusion. But it's still
Pretty fun
Okay
It's so you know I think our Monday episode maybe a little bit
No obviously Rocky
VR territory.
Tougher things
To take in
I think this will be a little bit to bit lighter
Pause
But before we get to that let's take a little moment Jordan to say hello
Please please please can you play Daddy shark thank you so much
Play the old Tech
Minecraft thing that has a shark in it
Next crystal is not mad at the
Ewok
Thank you very much
NextStop Minister christer Halverson the Duke of kidderminster thank you so much
Very much
Makes Jordans
Alex Jones is paying bill for his gummy worms
Play music
Happy first Father's day and happy birthday Joe
Nico is going to be an excellent sacrifice for the globalist thank you so much
Don't get mad and tell your brother to someone
Sodomites
Jar Jar Binks has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Thank you so much
Today we're going to start off with Alex
Trying to get into some news
I think I think this is probably what he
He kind of wants to do as a news for the day
Just went live and Infowars.
Come
He almost no attention here in the control Western
The organization of
New World Reserve currency is America commits economic
Suicide
That report
Next segment.
But also
He later refers to Bricks as brexit
Sophia's
A little bit of a confused
So the story is about Putin saying that the brics countries would be considering creating a reserve currency from among their currency
But it's far from like a complete done deal
A reserve currency is basically a currency that many countries hold a bunch of in-store which eases the ability of those countries to do busy
When is International
Currently that's the dollar
For much of the world
I've been turning somewhat for a while
What are the motivating factors were the brics countries do wanted
Create their own holding currency to the US froze at Russia
After Putin invaded Ukraine
Russia as well as other countries like China realized
And the target
Could be them
MMA dendup moreless excluded from much of the world's mark
This talk
Of the brics countries making up their own basket currency is interesting
But it also isn't probably as apocalyptic as Alex
We making it out to be
It would be somewhat expand the influence of these countries economically and if
Might hurt us economically in terms of somebody
Possibly unfair advantage
Due to that but they still heavy
Huge way to go to
Ketchup
To where the dollar is in terms of
International holder
Also Alex should be asking himself some
I know he's wishy-washy about China how they're going to working
For the devil one day and breaking away the next day
But he should be in favor of a brics currency for the most part
He loves
Amphibian bricks is Brazil
Who's President bolsonaro is one of the only world leaders that Alex supports
He should be on that team
Yeah that's his deep well I mean
The problem is the enemy of my enemy is not always my
My friend
But then when my enemy is also my best friend and my friends enemy is there
And my friend
Is my enemy
Then you're f*****
So what is
Bricks to you
See now we're screwed
So make it British
Yes of course
Ecuador
Not much of a handle on this. What's going on
Video about this that Alex season is like
List of things that I could touch on and so that's going to play that record
It's another headline to
Zelensky demands 5 billion from a
For security in Europe whatever that mean
So much
Insane news breaking on the Ukraine front
This is one of those great instances where it becomes really clear that Alex doesn't prepare for his show at all and he just cold reads head
Blinds that makes things up about them
This headline doesn't say Sidious but Alex's misread it and the pigs
Fast on his feet
He throws I'll be whatever that means to imply that selenski has said something weird like he wants money from NATO C
Natural headline here is quote
Zelensky demands 5 billion from NATO
Sites Security in Europe
Site
Does not get back to this story either
It is kind of amazing you really wouldn't hear from any actual news person
Whatever that means after reading out his story that you've chosen
Clearly one of your lead stories
Starting off the show with like this is something we're going to get into whatever that f****** means
Next
We're going to talk about 8
B161 whatever the f*** that s*** is who knows
Will get back at you
What are the reasons that I like so
It's kind of like
Not going to go back
The news is
It's got the the man Rodger Stone
Coming in
And Rodgers been done dirty
Okay alright they did him dirty
Rodger Stones going to be joining us exclusively at the bottom of the hour
You're about 23 minutes from now
Rodger has been massively defend against Elijah
Claiming the Trump called him
I told Mark Meadows to call him and 2
You called
General Flynn
Plan what happened at the Capitol
This is absolutely ridiculous
Did not call Rodger
Mark Meadows did not call Rodger General Flynn it is
Made up
Why
I've had
Grand jury
About a phone call
Supposedly had with
Stone and Flint
The phone call
Cuz you know that you got my damn phone.
So this is to do the testimony provided by Cassidy Hutchinson
And who was an aide to Mark Meadows Trump's chief of staff
Underoath
She testified that quote I'm under the
The impression that mr. Meadows did complete both a call to
Mr. Stone
And general Flynn the evening of
She couldn't defend it really say that the calls were made and there's no direct evidence that these calls were a plan for the riot the next day
But in her capacity as Meadows AG knew that her boss was told to contact
Stone and Flint
And it was $0.04
But he has
Alex is getting close to why the committee might be interested in
Been talking to him no more it's not really
Maybe about his actions on the 6th
He released an interview with General Flynn which he filmed on the
The evening of January 5th
If you watch that interview there's a number of Clues
About where that interview might have been filmed
41 there's a painting behind
Flint which is a reproduction
Samuel morse's painting
Sing the House of Representatives
Which is firmly
In fitting with the decor of the Willard Hotel Rudy and all those folks had their war room
Anticipated
There's a painting
And it's definitely not the original of this painting because that's in the National Gallery
You can tell by the acoustic
But it's not that
Not in there
Additionally that evening
Flynn was photographed with Rodger stone at the Willard Hotel wearing the same clothes that he's wearing in the interview that he did without
Finally Alex Rodger and Flynn all spoke at the same event that Eve
Also speaking at night where Jack pasovic
George Papadopoulos
And Ali Alexander
Who introduced Rodger and took a
Special moment to thank him for being the force behind stop the steel
That's a bad
That's a bad look
In retrospect
Alex was there at the Willard Hotel that evening
Based on everything I can
Until
Really seems like that interview took place
At some room at the Willard Hotel
That's not good if I were him I really wouldn't want to testify either not because I suspect that he's actually knowingly and
Involved in any plot but because of the fear that I might
Accidentally offer up some detail that
Super damn 100% that probably doesn't know
He knows that's dangerous to his Allied
But he knows that all the people who aren't
Caulking around tonight
Shouldn't ocular salute
Rudy and John Eastman are talking Rodger and Flambeau plead the Fifth
He's doing that to Alex man like
Nothing weird happened
What time did you go to the bathroom 8:15
Totally what would happen if we get jammed up by some
Document
That's my
It's kind of my feelings be asking about a phone call that he had with them
Because based on the evidence he was with
Exam on January 5th
He's right there if not at the Willard
Which I'm pretty sure that interview was at the weather
If not there
Then rally that they all spoke
Where Alex Galvan have tomorrow would be the globalist to Waterloo
It really seems like you knew what was going to happen does
Also I was watching back through that rally and it's really funny
Ali Alexander introduces Rodger Stone
And then a rap group
Comes out
I use that term very Loosely they come out and do the Rodger Stone did nothing wrong
Rogers up there like a
Pinstripe suit looking like a f****** huge melon
Vanilla extract
TMNT to happen for the good life
For the turtle
Are there more raps about turtle
High tide time will tell. Only
Hutchins
Open testimony
Really
A problem for a lot of folks
I thought you kind of just have to fight back
Bob with a badger sound like
She's made everything I have course
Reason Rodger join us not just that
The wheels have come off their deceptions
This Cassidy
Hutchinson
That's why I sound
Trump
So she's gotten angry
And made all the shop
None of this is true
No such thing happened he didn't plan of the from the car and grab the wheel
None of this is truly sitting way in the back
She Wrote This handwritten note
On what Trump directives were on January 6th and it turns out she didn't
They've already got other testify to that I mean the woman is a
Liar
We just see this going on and on and on
Committing crimes Underoath
Come out
But still didn't call her on it
The matter of this handwritten note has to do with a note that was on Meadows stationary and it was a message that they wanted
Trump to get out
That was essentially that everyone should go home
Trump lawyer Eric herschmann claims that it was actually
Play He Who wrote the note not Hutchins
I don't think this matters as much as Alex thinks
Like for one thing Hershman isn't saying this under oath and he's Trump's lawyer so I don't know how seriously I want
Sacred flame
Also
This is kind of
It kind of makes things look worse
For Trump
In essence you have two people
One witness his own lawyers who were saying that they wrote an o with a message for him to tell the rioters to go home
And yet he did nothing
Kind of looks weird
Well I mean if you get a note from an aide
That says tell everybody to go home perhaps
If you look at it and you say
Who gives a f*** with
Does AIDS fake right
But if your personal lawyer gives you a note
That maybe makes it look more like you should have listened
I think that story about Trump trying to commandeer the vehicle so he could join the Riders that's an interesting image
It's important to keep in mind that all Hutchinson was testifying to is that she heard that story
From Tony ornato
The Deputy Chief of Staff
The secret service has disputed this event happened but are not OS
Not to this point disputed
Telling the story
Hutchinson
There are threats to untangle here but honestly this was kind of off the beat
Important about that bass testimony
Looks like Alex have to deflect from other really damning stuff that come out
Alex I probably go this route to not because it's wise
Because there's no
Really much else you can do
You know the problem with
That is
That salacious typed
Detail of
All the president
Trying to strangle a secret service agent
Get you f****** headlines
Times for sure sure
But
That's Alicia s*** is what the right
Feeds off of it gives them strength the game like
Magical electricity Powers being able to
To focus purely on that and not on anything of any
Yeah it's it's unfortunate that you're getting headlines and attention
I realize I'm having interesting thing
Jeff and
That's the only way that
They do this this propaganda machine confunkshun
It's just dry analysis is really boring Alex can't do anything with that
Literally just like sequence of videos
Place with evidence
And 0 eyewitness testimony at all really
Yeah I just like
This is what
And we have the
Exact timeline of events have you ever noticed that Alex has never read off like a legal document or a bill
Are you bored by that I can't do chitlins
Adam Schiff
Is on this January 6th
Committee
And we also know that he is still needing to feel
We're still waiting years later
For him to feel his hand
But yeah he's a known liar
Is that Alexa has
Proven I guess not really but anyway he he's making phosphate
But I guess it's really
Peas in a pod or birds with feather fly together
Because you have shift on the committee
We know of
I'm sure there's more
Totally falsified documents and emails and change the words around
To say something completely different
She's testifying she heard Trump say
I want to join an armed Insurrection and take the capital of her
10000 National Guard
Alex knows damn well that shift didn't do that the Trump didn't order security for the capitol on January 6th
These are just well-worn talking points
He's repeated enough of the audience assumes they must
Keep saying this
Years are we on
For this
The irony is that he's accusing Schiff of falsifying statements but
He's actually doing the exact same thing as it relates to Miss Hutchins
He never said the Trump wanted to join an armed Insurrection and take over the capitol
That's a Alex's
Also in terms of other witnesses that Trump wanted to join the protests
Alex himself had said that was
The plan
Trump said he was going to
Going to do that from his speech at the ellipse
During the very Committee hearing that Alex is covering they played recorded testimony
From Trump's former press secretary Kayleigh mcenany
Who said quote
I believe when we got back to the White House he said he wanted to physically walk with the Marchers
He wanted to be a part of the March
In some fashion
So I mean
There's plenty of people who definitely
10.2 the appeal
Intend
Sure sure but you know it's more
Fun
If you really lean into the fascist element of just telling people to think that they absolutely saw in Kansas
See at any point in time they want did next
Oh yeah that's really important later this
The good trash
That's when you know you're getting
The Rodger Hopsin
Hello I'm Rogers
Around
She alleges that the president
Told his chief of staff
Mark Meadows
Call me and general Flynn
January 5th
To discuss
Oshkosh
What was going to happen
I never spoke
Miss Hutchinson only said that it was our understanding that the calls were made
Her testimony
Still be completely accurate with
No Lie
Also Rodger is making up which he's testified about going to like why the calls
Those were made
Rodger claims it so they could tell the Trump what was going to happen on the 6th
Asked directly quote
Do you know what they talked about that
To which she replied
I'm not sure
Liz Cheney asserts that quote
The night before January 6th President Trump instructed his Chief of Staff Mark Meadows
Contact both Rodger Stone and Michael Flynn
Regarding what would play out the next day
This wasn't necessarily based on any testimony provided by Hutchins
Then they could be
From other investigation that was carried out by the committee
Rogers problem is with Liz Cheney but the goal for the right-wing media right now is to do whatever they can to Moline cast
Hutchinson
So her testimony isn't taken seriously
Rodger takes
Words that she didn't say and describe them to her in order to further that goal
Roger's been at this game for a long f****** time he knows exactly what he's doing this is just
Bulshit
It's sad it feels like there is hard isn't it quite
The same way any
He doesn't take that thing Glee with
With a complete piece of s***
He doesn't seem as angry
No Andy has to pretend he believes in God all the time
It's not
Yeah there is something else
Guess when you've been to prison
You're delivering only by the like gray so he home
There is maybe a wake-up call. Like maybe it's not so fun to be the Joker
Thing I've done
Yeah now that I'm living with the
Consequence
Says I'm starting to think
Hold on
When I was
Reaping
I was like
Hahaha this is
Great and then I started sewing and someone was like
Stop that you're fine
I was sewing my consequence actually
Twice
So anyway
List Hutchinson she's just
But angry former
Wow you talk about Reckless
Yes
She said all these things
After this. Where she makes all your assertions against
She was seeking to join his staff at Mar-A-Lago she was speaking to
Does the disgruntled employee know nothing to see here
Who is Intuit
Okay
You can't
Both be an employee of trump
And
Be
Not described
True
Do any employee who speaks out against him
A disgruntled employee
I think he's any employees if you have
A three-tiered thing
You have current employees who are afraid to speak out
You have people who are respecting their NBA's that they were forced into it I don't say anything
All three of them can testify to the same information
Most likely
You can be a disgruntled employee and definitely tells
The truth about your disgruntled
Honesty that's
Why you pay people off
That's the whole thing
Does he give you a lot of money because you're disgruntled
And you can either tell people what your
You're distracted about
You can get a lot of money
I don't have any /
Particular reason to distrust the account that be such a
Some gave you don't have any
Particular reason the evidence
It's being thrown around by people like Alex is not compelling it anyway
Heather is a debunking
But I also am not
Getting all up in like the key grab the wheel hysteria smell like
It's not it's not
It's not worth it
To get really excited about these vibrant images how many times are we going to do this
Oh man that's just too good
True
Yeah
We don't need more of that
It said it's not productive
Nope
Play some social media while though
It really does Alex like
He's going to break down this f******
Committee
Mnic
Sure sure if you want to hear the evidence that proves the things that I'm arguing against you can go find
This is not a court of law my friend that's also it's just
I don't know you're responsible but it's
Glaring videos
I'm going to get into this immense like you with that
Especially not
The stuff he doesn't
So we all Rodger
Freedom for all animals of the sea
No
The purpose of this is just a relay
Warriors
Show for me this means bigger and bigger legal
I've already as you know
That my legal obligations under their subpoena but I pledge
Because I have anything to hide
Extensive experience
Jewish immaterial irrelevant
Into a crime
Hey buddy that's not what the 5th is 4
Do cats purr when you have
Probably done a crime
Isn't just like
Hey you never have to say you never have to answer Eddie
It's
Views of the amendment
I think that this is
Just sad and obviously a fundraising opportunity for them
I think it's very funny that ND
Hyper
Masculinize
Toxic
Bulshit like
How strong you have to
To being dominant and all that stuff
I'm a warrior
For me that means
Higher legal fees
Do I do appreciate the absolute deflation of being a warrior
What does pays an extra 10%
The price of my b******* going on inflation baby
So here's where everything turns
Yeah
And what I say turn
On a dime
Oh man
Cuz this
S*** goes nuts
I think he announces sooner rather than later
I think these kind of
Probably accelerate
Odyssey just needs to stick to his
Before he could move out openly and frankly I do think he is sizing up
New National poll last week block and Associates in the Gateway pundit shows that Trump
Easley dispatches all-comers
Is his race to lose
Five more minutes weather in God's name
Launch
This is too hot wow I have got my first
Actual exclusive story that no one knows about
And the only person telling it to me is notoriously liar rogerstone and he's not even really
Telling you it's not news
Will become the rest of the show
Of course it will
Spend the rest of the show obsessed that he has the scoop of course
And it becomes that he's going
To announce
On the 4th of July
They're saying
Okay this Monday
Trump is going to announce his candy
Tennessee for 2024
Almost entirely the rest of the up
Now the more I think about it the more it really does make sense in like a
Cinematic way
Everything's a movie to these people
You do it on the 4th
July and then for us we get the added irony of recognizing that in the flag of
Freedom
Is fashion
It'll be great
Am I also think that it's on brand with like just how
Flagrantly disrespectful it absolutely
Self-aggrandizing especially
Yeah
Let's think about
I mean hijack the news cycle on the 4th of July and make everyone talk about me
Let's remind everybody on 9/11 I had the biggest building
Things in case anybody was wondering his brand
Of the
I don't know
I would not be
That surprised if it had totally totally but
I would not Bank on it based on
Oh no I don't think I'm sure has some inside information
If you are throwing out
Movie pictures which is what Rodger was doing
Then that is a great pic
Eagle Fence
Betty White
Trump wasn't gonna run
Oh now
But now
Rodger Stone help prime the pump to get
President-trump
First rule of Fight Club
Iran president
He told Rodger and many others just now come out
Six months ago
What's the second rule of Fight Club
Yeah
I don't know how many others to Lagoon
Feel it growing
Play within the last
5 minutes of him hearing Rodger
You say that and him think
Think about it 45-second imagine
30 other voices in his head God I can't believe that Trump is going to run start with a story
Feel-Rite
Absolutely
It's just expanding of proving the Dell as we speak
Trump
Trump is intending to declare
2024 Ron on cell.
Rodgers said
Aftergold
Flexibility
When you get a big giant
Kahuna news-record like that
Oh my God
It's like Elvis's got Marilyn Monroe in the bed and they're about to
What
Is this is this or is this not a family show
Elvis
Tired or just
Really on a lot of barbiturates
I don't know I don't know what he's talking about me
F****** obvious
UK so
Texaco flexibility thing or I won't or I don't
If this does not happen
I'm still right
Kahuna story totally no one and no one else has this gluccie totally I'm going
Going to get all the press for this bright but also I should tell you it might not happen
Not announce on the 4th of July that's because
Cuz technically
That wasn't the best mood right and maybe this is not news maybe it's
Not even gossip maybe the level below gossip
Rodger
Liq
S***
Available
Cowboys
You make everything up
On your own
So you think whenever you talk to a man who's a champion make a rapper of everything on his own
I'll be like maybe he's making
You you gotta understand though I think Alex really didn't have anything to talk about
And two keys Federal Way
F****** excited
On July 4th
Run
You talk about blood coming out of the eyeballs of the left
Insane
So I'm glad
But here's the deal
What's
May make
Decision
Tactical flexibility
Not tuna
No
On air at this moment everything is true and false at the six
Okay so there's a presidential run in a box
Claire's or not
Also man when you say Rodger Stone isn't a bullshiter
I am trouble
If you say that you been
Lightning should strike you
That is the one thing where if there is a God you just can't say that
Bright I think that if
I don't know I'm trying to think of
Anybody that I respect
Return to imagine them being ignored
Crystal Dupre straight-up guy
I would instantly
Call into question everything I've ever said
Could not be worse process to think that you should
Say that out loud to me
That is something that if I'm around you you
Buried under a rock
Outside not be a greater bulshit
The legendary right that's insulting to him
It's a decoration of his
Career as brand is legacy
Hazel
Champion bulshit he is a historical
Bullshiter
He'll go in the record books
So look elsewhere the rec
Alex's famous Wok
On the Greenbelt
Those are
It's been awhile since we've heard about launch
Really cool fossils although
Time cool
Conch shells
Huge beautiful houses
The Clemson thinks it's either shape
So I'm hacking long
Scrabble up
Embankment up to that
Old here
Good story
Define
Advil
I'm just processing report
Done
Processing
Trump is going to run and then announced on July 4th right
He's got a gun to your head
What
But he's got it locked and loaded right now about the
Bontrager
And so
Yeah
I mean
That's a whole nother subject
In fact
We got Alex Stein who went to New York and left
Shut down a free speech we got incredible videos
Call Brad
All-time situation
Yeah man
You got to clear the deck
You got you got this kind of big news
You got a you got a not talk about all of us
The things that you spent
1520 hours of work preparing for
You got to throw all that out the window because
Is this
If this is
Career-making
News breaking
Don't
Understand
Even if it is
Then you're just telling me right now that a man we all knew was going to run for
Six or seven months
Citgo probably was going
Emily was going to
You're saying that yes he's going
And then he'll say it
Official I guess I mean that really news here's here's the two things that I can think of
That like would be exciting about
Is now you actually have to have a conversation of
We actually support Trump
Sure and I think that could be difficult
To have with Alex's Auto
Because a lot of them have turned on him
A lot of them
And now it's your turn.
And then come back as a doctoral candidate
So there is that like we really have to figure out where we are
And that could be child
And then the second thing is the notion of doing it on the 4th of July
I think there's a troll excitement that Alex is getting
With like oh my God that'll piss off a live
So much I think that is a big part of the in a lake
He's really going
Going to
Isn't that fun
That is the fun I mean
Yeah of course he's going to run and he's going to win by a
Billionaire he gets to say
To the right wing
For the first time ever
I delivered
On Roe v Wade
Well nobody else gets his head I appointed the three lunatics
Who throw their own feces up in the air and watch it land on paper and call that there
I think that he delivered
Yeah I think you come
2A
Serta very weird
Thing about that like
Taking credit
You can
The justices
Yeah that did it themselves
But he appointed them
Yeah but
I think you could make an argument to Mitch
McConnell really has more total there was not running
President know that's true
People
To run for president
And get all of that attention you have a grand old time with it
You're so powerful mr. Trump
Very attractive too
Walk of the Republican base can you imagine if Obama delivered on universal
So Healthcare in 2009
We would have amended the constant heat still be f****** present if you ate any politician it delivered on f****** and
Anything in the past 30 years
Pahrump
Also some other news that he's going to try to cover
I'm too excited
Really even pay attention
Anything
By the way I meant
Video clips
So you got doing the Lesser pull the yard
Thanks
Shut off
What's the password
The
Flash
VA board
I'm sorry what
Did they do that
We're just going to stop even doing trials or studies on things
Okay
CDC rainsong EPA
Everyone okay
So
Baskin-Robbins
And Wendy's
At A&W
And everybody have decided to open One restaurant
EPA will be running out of it
This was DC is there
Stop
Wouldn't make some mistakes if you're just making s*** up all the time
You're going to make some frog wine
Who is drowning
And he is flailing
Pasta
CA EDD
Noble experiment or trial is nothing
Did you want a new pill
Well it will give it to you but what about a rock
This wasn't on the national news
Is this was just an article that Alex Kim the headline of
That was published in the epoch times
The full headline is World Health Organization behind FDA scheme to skip all future clinical trials
For covid-19
It was a lot of bulshit that doesn't even live up to that leaving aside the insane nonsense Alex's reporting
He's looping in the EPA apparently which is reme Court decision right
I don't think so
Yeah
What's at the root of this is that there was an F
Ta meeting where one of the topics of conversation was the idea of being able to
The create an adjust
Will covid vaccine the could be flexible
Do the changing distributions of differ
Variance
Auto coverage of this is just completely meaningless
It has no relation
To the actual real word
Wild
Trump running
EPA FDA
It's just saying all those letters
Is in a row is very very funny
You know what I'm telling you right now I bet if we go into his office
A lot of those fossils and shells that he found
Rocks man almost
Got2b 2 like the his story was about like
Not find a
Watch
Yeah that is that is interesting stories about hurting
Is back that's what's important
Defy why he would climb out there
Yeah but I do believe that he didn't find a Shell today
Let's see that's believable
So look Alex's pumps
Obviously
He needs to spread the bug around
He's got it he's got to make other
People really excited about this whole Trump thing
I'll make this decision
Owen Shroyer what to do
He doesn't rain instead
But at once a year
Call Owen
Boxing or lifting weights
Obviously I was going to be covering
2024 announcement coming on Monday
Whole Food hours
Alright
Cool. You know he's so he's so excited because the campaign part is
Fun
The campaign parties
EPPICard
Bulshit
Nobody means any of it
You can argue about it well if you can argue about Trump promising something that you know he's not even going to
Try to respond rallies everybody gets excited
Excited it's great there is actually to spoil a call from later
Someone calls in and says
I'll just go ahead
Because I think this person makes
A really good point
North Carolina let's talk to Neil Neil thanks for calling ahead
Call Alexei first of all
How to say that no one
Would like to
See Trump declare faster than the media
Because
Was it will boot
Who's their ratings
Skyrocket
The media includes Al
Like Alex is excited for this because there's
A prospect
How much more he's going to
To be able to
Drawing attention wise
The pie-in-the-sky
Element of this to that is like wow
Trump runs
They probably can't prosecute
If that gets derailed I might be unless hot water
Yelp
So I think I think there's a lot of different
Aspects to this but
I think you're right
The campaign aspect is much more
Funland Elijah
Just later
Oh yeah yeah everybody just wants to get attention so you say
Flamboyant nonsense
Get it all out there and then if you actually do get elect
You just say that you didn't mean any of it
Here is a description little bit longer but it's where Alex
Terminix
Bswift like
I like it
Anomic news that'll affect everyone of us was bigger than anything we've ever experienced
I mean I shutter
In Anger at myself
I'm not running around 24/7 myself
Getting prepared
My pleasure smart but it's also week
What
Because it thinks about itself and says you get ready to protect yourself
What button
I don't use a spirit
Lightyear
And fight the tyranny
Then all the horrible stuff will happen and then some
That's an interesting thing to say
Experience
The vast majority of your time
Starting to stop evil
Fighting
And then sometime being prepared
But we better the season now
It's not about stopping at anymore
It's about getting
Prepared
Rick's announces new world Reserve currency is American to Mexican Onyx suicide
Are all amazing I mean
I'm in a good mood but I'm not mad
Is Grand Slam
Muhammad Ali
Favoritism
Infowars.com
10 phone calls ahead of Alex.
I'll get to you I want you
Alex
Please don't look 20 up
Cuz we do that
Men
No
But
Phone calls on what do you think
On this
Wednesday June 29th broadcast
Someone to talk to Donald John Trump
Is right now to an hour
On July 4th
In 5 days
It's incest
If I said anything in that clip anywhere near a hospital they would not let me leave the house
I think it's pretty
For the course for him I'm basically just making excuses not to do your job.
Play the gris-gris report at with people about
Runnings
Total I don't want to see if the audience is into it or not
Frankly if they might not be true
Weirdo for a bit
I'm he's just he's so emotionally abusive
Like you can feel
That clip
Being like
Everyday
Just called man
When he's in a really good mood he's so nice and he's complementary but when he's in a bad mood
He's just so mean to him so apparently unfortunately
The entire work staff is now devoted towards
In a good mood and that doesn't go well
No
Never any good at
Alex seems to be like like I mentioned obviously the incentive of
The ratings and what have you they would come from Trump running the course
There is also that legalized
Give me the toll-free number
The first
You're 60 seconds on what do you think of the exclusive
Ramification
Wild
What are the
Dinos
If he announces his run
Historically that someone
Prominent
This is so big
That sounds like Alex saying like if
If you run
He won't be punished for the crimes that you did that's 100% that
Cool man so weirded out by this I'm so weirded out by this and it's not because
Anything but I just really have always
Spelt
That if you lose a coup then you die
I just always thought that's how it's supposed to I'm not saying that it's supposed to work that matches to the workbooks
Has seemed like that's the projector
You win or you die and it's not like a
Did not even personally just the way the system works
Moore historical times to it seems like that was what
The coup attempt or would have want
It's kind of humiliating cute
Anything cool buddy
That's how do you know the Japanese do it right now to is this school that is
Pretended like it's
Sinatra
Coo and there'll opening didn't go well
Well I'll be there trying to retool their their f****** service staff
Another going to try again
That's as we all do
Yeah and then they lost
The counter coup so they have to
To do the
Counter counter
Counter
Haha
Fresh Wok
Anyway it seems like Alex is also excited like I mentioned earlier that this is just going to freak out though
A f****** live
Just a freak these people out
Brought him into the ground
Y'all go see Santa
All planets align
Trump right now is planning
His second run for president United States
Only ever ran for office and became president first time
What
Abraham Lincoln
That's not true
Just any just for the site like
Trump did try to run for president before
Also I think Alex is saying the Trump wants to announce his run because he's jealous of the attention that the scientist
It really does
That would be a motivation
Heady narcissism 100%
Look
Whether Trump announces on Monday or if there is tact
Medical flexibility
That is always true wishy-washy
Tactical flexibility
There's one thing no matter what always true
Can the holy spirit in Gaston effusion
20 hours a day
Hours a day
8:15
Not a chance
I want to get to you and I got to get through us to get to you
Do you want to get to your family that I can get through you first
The one thing I want to do is beat the Satanist off 1% I am
Mulan
I want you to go now
Infowarsstore.com
Build our community
Is the best prices ever
That is
That is the rename this the Trump announces his candidacy
Like when he's in a good mood
He selling s*** like a
Televangelist
The day is coming
Close and you will need to send a good mood to his likability to
We've emotion into salesmanship is like
It's a little more on point
Also man like this dude doesn't do
15 hours
Of preparation
He doesn't do 15 minutes
Separation
Cold read headline
He said NATO cities
Adnan said whatever that means
20 hours of work yeah
Come on man if you would have read the article within that
20 hours
And maybe if you're doing 20 hours of work maybe spend an hour
Focus
On reading one article you can do that
Mmu do what you have
Rouladen
So maybe spend an hour
Clearing your head
Before you get on air
Good luck breathe a little bit relax
Do some guided meditation end up
Screaming at the crew or probably about I'd be a better use of time Shirley
So now we're going to take a call
Because Alex doesn't want to work
10 calls
No work
15 axle
I mean
There's only one thing you want
What's the talk about
Global Link
Exclusive news
Only call and let somebody love you and you have open free-for-all like yesterday
2 hours was amazing I love
Free for all of the wild card
Today's on Wildcard
Day is one topic
And one topic only
Is Trump
Monday
But as of now
Truck is intending to announce on Monday global eggsclusive
Tomorrow's news today
I would say that
This is sad but also
Response from the audience
Barely mix
Are there some people who are like really excited about Trump
And then there's some people who like
He's really old
We need somebody younger
Great
He did some good thing shaft
There's some people who are just like
Yeah he
Got the vaccines rolled out like
Like what do you want like we need somebody
Not him sure we've done this already so I don't know like it gauging
From the calls themselves
I don't know what the temp
Mature is with his audience
Using that as a represented
Example I'm not sure if they're like
Pumped for Trump 2024
I think it would be wise for Alex to be more in the sand
You think so
I think everybody fall in line
And I very much doubt DeSantis
Falling line regardless of which way
DeSantis he's going to
Look
I just
Find him to be callow
And it's going to be revealed whenever trumped
Decides to make him feel like a tiny little girl
In the the primaries
He
Handled Marco Rubio
I'm like yeah I guess I I don't I don't know if the scientist
Could fight that
I do I do I feel like you need Jesse vu
Ventura to go up against a professional writers
Professional professional
Right angle
Yeah
It's just going to he's going to wilt
He's going to wilt
He's going to get made
Fun of and he's going to get all prickly need to be like
No I'm not and everybody's like oh you're a child
Your callow child
Maybe
But
I also think
Probably there'll be more insta
The two channels
Support behind
DeSantis then Trump because I think the
Probably rightfully so
Most of the GOP could realize a we can get everything that we
Could get with strawberry Leaf without a lot of this headache
With the
Future
And that makes sense
Unless you think
Perhaps
Apps that are unintended
Sequences to making your entire base insane. That is a problem
And that is the power velen
Forest the night make it very difficult to predict
Sue McMahon
Alex wants to cover the news
Because Rodger Stone
He told me you don't
And now
JonTron
That's a huge piece
He had to take calls and not do any of the news
Can't do it's Rodger talk some s*** Rodger said something so the entire three hours of show that I admit
Tequila sleep land
Add 100% for sure
Poem Every Vic minute-by-minute outline to make sure that I stayed on topic
Just can't do it every every break
You know every segment
Is like building
Everything is one topic is another topic
D at the top of the hour
We're bringing them all together
Rodger
Years away deprived of this hard-hitting news
Oh my God it's can't cancel all of his
Appointment
That's the other guy named Alex Stein
I don't know if you know who this guy is
Is that dude who made some videos of himself like rapping
Sing a council meeting
Things and stuff
They went around on social media
No
Yeah I'm not to target audience for engaging with those
Remy guy who hit things with hammer territory
Play Usher more malevolent
Yeah I had no incredibly cerebral comedy or farts
No in-between no middle ground
One or the other guy sucks
But Alex wants to know where he's at on
Sadly people are dumb Alex you know this so this is my only in our thing that worries me about Trump is there so much bad
Trumpet DeSantis doesn't have not I love Trump I like eventual Trump As Trump runs I'm buying from
But these people
Are so dumb
Use fake evidence against Trump that they don't have onto Sanchez
Do it for me I mean I'm willing to bet whoever is going to going to be on the conservative side
But I almost think Trump will be more powerful
Being a kingmaker
Buy running for president first night now
On time
Alex
Right now Primetime Alex time we never committed a crime Ron DeSantis
100% not possible to find dirt on that guy so this dude Alex Stein came into prominence like I said by filling in
Filming himself doing silly raps
City council meeting
My sense of the whole thing is that people saw the videos and thought they were really embarrassing which led to them sharing them
They're making
Fun of him and now he's got it cuz they went viral and he had a lot to him
I think that he must be doing some
Smart right
Triggering people exactly
Desperate loser I guess did some comedy but it's
Funny and then tried to break through by being on a reality TV show called The Glass House
Back in 2012 but none of it really amounted
Happy in the era of covid Hebrew
Pretty astutely realize the people were making videos of themselves
The council meeting
And they were going viral
Pretty easily
It's a free microphone where officials have to let you speak
So he came in and acted like a complete stew
The juxtaposition of it
Was really a luring bait
For people on social media idiot who they can't
Stop from doing something
Idiotic bright and then you have the stuffy councilmembers sitting there being all official
So I poked around on this guy a little bit and honestly I don't see anything other than an a****** who is like will do
Just do anything for attention
And it seems like he would agree with me
As a Dallas magazine article quotes in
From his time on that TV show The Glass House
Quote America should I turn
The most epic villain in the history of reality TV
Nobody in this house is going to do what I do because I've got no shame
That's true he seems pretty stupid too considering if these evil globalist can just make up stuff about Trump
Chances in 2024 why can't they make up stuff about the Santa
I mean
I mean these things is no answer like if it doesn't matter who you are
Just make things up
About you
Do you know how we know that
For sure because the right calls everyone a pedophile
I think went through its time is actually trying to say is that Trump has done a bunch of horrible ship that the media can remind
People love
Whereas most people don't really know all that much about Rhonda
There's a there's more of
Familiar with him where you'd be able to have a bunch
Step stick where is
With trumpets
Just like
A laundry list of
Remember that
Wow I really can't I can't believe that I don't remember that
Every now and again
Suddenly I'll remember the Four Seasons in be like
Fine
Fascism that's what we learned
That's what we learned
Weird it where is DeSantis
Notsobot
So I really don't like
Alex Stein
I think you sucks
If I was on a reality show if I was down on The Glass House
The problem I would have been
Kicked off of media Coronavirus
Camera operator all the time be like
Check messages
Can get it
Get it now it's really funny
Get it
Naruto
Cuz that thing
You got it
My grandpa used to say people in glass houses shouldn't throw stones
Better
There might have been another layer on that show but I'm not sure if there was I think it might
The reason I'm confused is because on its own is not a joke
That's what he said
Anyway
This guy sucks yeah I really don't like him
Use the word
Syndrome is a real thing
That is the biggest crock of Lies I've ever heard in my entire
Higher life
And if you look at the schedule
Exactly
So does not caused by vaccine
Also something don't send room is a code word that people like Stein or trying to associate with people who have died
Who's also got nekoba
It's basically an attempt to create branding
For that right
The problem is it's unto death Sunbelt death syndrome is a real thing and it long predates covid
There's an umbrella of things that encompass
But it's generally people died unexpectedly in their sleep
In some cases the cause has never determined
I thought to be due to inherit at the heart.
Disease that have gone unnoticed
You can probably literature on this going back
Alright this is a propaganda branding exercise for Stein so he doesn't particularly care that
His actions are treating real people's deaths
As the butt of his joke
I'm being like oh you want us to think
This is a real a real thing
Is a real thing
Rick
Anyway here's what I'm saying
I really don't like this guy
Partially because of his Paula
I think they suck
And then partially because his whole game
Is sober
Boring and transparent
Like it really is just about
Trying to get attention
Yeah and the way the people go about pushing back against that often is counterproductive
Because it gives him more at
And I think that
You know I think it's cheap
It's a trap
Keep playing the game that's a trap
I don't respect that at all
Why
Does the kid
Eat the worm
He doesn't need it for the $0.05 or whatever he needs it to make the
People laugh and give him attention
And then they laugh and give him attention
And then he does it again because he knows
Inglot get laughs and attend
That's what it is
And he's just never change
From that five-year-old
It's the worm it is very well maybe
But whatever the case he's using it for evil and I got no time for it disrespect
Quite a bit
Agree
Yes a correlation doesn't mean causation but anybody with half
Realized
That's a lie that's a bold-faced lie
Wow what correlation does mean causation apparently
Wow I mean those few stupider things you
Pretzel why
Not that's wrong
That's a lie
Like we've known for centuries
Correlation does equal causation
The greatest trick that Archimedes everbowl
Website
Like
Make graphs of
Things that are unrelated
Run parallel to each other
There's a Litany of examples of things that are
But don't.
And if you sit there and get high
Stare at them and be like
Is there a connection or mustard
Alex
You know that there is absolutely
Cells in a conversation
Information about apparently they approve the Trump is running
And he's going to announce
Here's what we know he's running
Just announced today six more women say that he raped them at 11
Yeah I'm in a situation that's the problem is people are able to decipher
We can say that the
Sadly Alex you know this
The mass population are all dumb down on antidepressants have no idea last ride up and down the road.
About their bills are worried about the inflation
I don't know what
6 women
Stories talking about
I don't think that's a real story
I think I was just making that up
In order to pretend
The Trump is being subject to
Brighton attacks
Right which would make his argument about the July 4th announcement
More plausible to his
Conspiracy
Mind riddle
Right
Right I think that's
What's going on
I don't know what the story is
About 6
Nope
I don't think that
He can make up
Just because
I'm in fukkit
Sure
Sure it's plausible very possible possible that the globalist would make that up in order
Besmirch his good name
What is really stupid
Because
Clearly
In effect
Previously
Made up in 6
Additional doesn't
If that's
You're if the globalist plan is like okay
Well we need
Every breed perforate
But we need
Sure
I don't know
Talks a little bit here about the inspiration for his work
I'm killing your mother in the hospital deny her treatment with push you over the edge
I appreciate that and I just showed a good friend of mine is Gavin McInnes and I was on his show and he actually said it you're not in jail
She said your mom dying was the best thing that ever happened to you before so I was the worst thing I would trade all the you know
The Hanson Clayton followers and all the 70 guy for my mom in a second
Cobra back
But I will say this is a dangerous man because I have nothing to lose and that is the most dangerous person is a person
A hundred percent I have no choice but to fight back in this culture War
Yeah right so yeah the mom died of covid-19 in October 2021
The doctors didn't deny her care but
But he's decided that because the hospital allegedly gave her a severe they kill
His dad rap
Spoke to Dallas magazine and said quote it traumatized him
I totally broke him down
And he's reacting to that dramatization
He's not the same person after that
He says he is but he's not the same guy right now
This article by Jonathan topping is
Fascinator
I recommend people check it out they want to dive into a very sad story about
And wear some of that come
Also if you're friends with Gavin McGinnis in 2022 that speaks volumes
About you
You suck
If you're friends with Gavin McGinnis you deserve to have Gavin McGinnis
Just tell you that your mom dying is a good thing
That's you get it
You earned it
You deserve it
I think that there are you know
Comedy friend sometimes there's a lot of chop busting and trash I feel like that's a little much
Maybe your mom dying is the best thing that ever happened to you
When it's been less than a year particularly like
F***** up
Now these the only time that's acceptable is
At the funeral
Because the added level of immediacy makes the
The funny part
You know like it's so naughty
It's not supposed to happen
You know that kind of thing
But if you're like
Two days after
Don't make that f****** joke to me and especially when the joke is that like
Because your mom died
You've created this
Attention to where you're monetizing bothering
People you literally have
Supervillain origin story
Which is
Maybe not true
Anyway
Look this dude he loves
Confrontation because that is exciting content that he can post
Calm conversation with somebody
Boring video trailer
On the 13th
And I'm going to be at Capitol Hill I'm going to go confront all these politicians I'm going to Elon Omar you married your brother I'm going to say I'll see you're my favorite
Big booty latina
I'm going to get in all these politicians face because that's what I like to do is I like confrontation
It seems like maybe confrontation for him is just
Being racist
Yeah I mean
Harassment
Assault
Sure
Booking job Tim pool
I just
Feel like
If you
Somebody who loves confrontation
Choose this word but it's my brand
Use at work you're literally branding that's what you're at
Kind of
You're telling people what your branches has the brand
Yeah
Confrontation is yelling hey ilhan Omar you married your brother
And harassing
Sexually harassing
AOC
That's not meaningful confrontation
There is
Meaningful confrontation like
No some of Michael Moore's early documentaries here
Meaning for confrontation
Congress
How about trivial nonsense and lies
No go fuc
Yourself man in front of
Tanks
That's good confrontation
ATS it's hard to be
Beat that confrontation
Ross
Nixon not
Here's a here's what I would say if
If the dude in Tiananmen Square had instead been like
Hey tank you got a fat ass and then ran away that would not be meaningful a couple thousand dollars
On YouTube
Totally yeah
And I'm doing it all for you because I want to protect freedoms
Right
So I regret to inform you he's also
Yeah well that's
How do you transfer the owner making that decision
And that's a problem
Is it to transfer a big meme let's
I'm going around online for a long time
Email
That was enough
The Dome now that's not an original thought that is just delegitimizing
Transit
I would say so far we have not heard any rich
No thoughts
Gives just
An attention
Any looks at other people's ways of getting attention in any does
Because he's already got an extra boost from the very early stuff he gets
To consolidate is its fan base
Skip
It's a it's an economy now
So we can do really insane collar
Okay now I'm in
Spine is still there
And this guy calls in
And like for the 1st
Half of this call I did not know what was going on and then it gets real good
So might be down for that
Brad Stine
Just a couple little things
We got to just throw that out of our brain
I just get ready for the roller coaster ride
Cuz he's coming back and they're going to form the new American
That's right they got hurt on the Patriots
In Florida
Golden Ox
South America form up with
You're on fire but he can show me Trump
Crash
Poison shot
The second thing you said where's the proof
He's almost whitelock
Would not confirm that he was at the island
Well it's supposedly there's some story that he wasn't on the actual Lolita Express that he was on the plane with Jeffrey Epstein One X
It doesn't matter
Discolor I don't know what was going on there I could
Walking with them right or if he is excited about Trump right
Seems like it's impossible that it's a pro-trump call
Because he did not cease from South America, and join them in Texas
Are you saying I we got to give him some slack he was on the Lolita Express right doesn't seem like a sincere point to be making
Doesn't seem insane because he's able to moderate and be like six times
He's not here
Keep going with that manic energy nope it was
Performative in some way that makes me think that it's someone f****** with Alex
I think so but also drop absolutely was on those flight locks
What does the name
No way that Alex doesn't know that
Elaine Maxwell
Trial it came out that he'd actually flown on Epstein's jet at least six times more than it been previously known
He's flown on Epstein's
A bunch of times at so I guess Alex
To decide whether he's going to pretend that isn't real
He's going to make an excuse for it and pretend baby it's not a big deal
Or
He's going to follow through and abandon
I'm going to guess he's going to go into pretend plan
I'm going to go with number one
Just amazing principal Alex Stein is showing there
Who cares I mean there's literally make our entire brand this
Pedophile panic
You called everybody thought of playing with
The arch pedophiles at we
Okay fine so he was on a plane with a pedophile
And knowing what we know about Trump and everybody who's gone to Epstein Island
12 comments Trump has made about Epstein in the past
Yep
Come on guys she's described the man said of Epstein he likes them young
Where is very excited
And just because this caller things have hit a little bit of a little bit of disco
Open now because of this
A little bit
Not like a really terrible Tales
Basketball because the show's almost over because
He can just
Bucking tonight
Halloween Express according to flight logs
The Democrats of confusion grab the wheel
Of the Secret Service limo and it's not true
Just like I have a black tongue it's not true
Talk to Trump
On January 5th
Had talked to come for over a year
Trump definitely was
Well reported
No it wasn't like
Crump
And then the sea was like a little bit right
Reporting from licking Miami Herald
Do you know that that's that
It's well-known and Elaine Maxwell
And also you know who else was on
Bill Gates
Sure but also you know who else
This list
Yeah I was going to say
For no reason at all
Robert Kennedy Jr
Roberto Junior
And like I said I bring this up for no reason
I had it I was doing a charity event for a children's health defense to charity Robert Kennedy run
And it's charity basically a performance for a Robert Kennedy
Fundraiser for his fax chair Robert Kennedy Jr was on the Lolita Express
And he was allowed to have
The children's charity
Saving the children from vaccines
I'm not actually sure how much
It is a children's charity
It's for like anti-vax
Experiment
To stop children from having to have that scene
Are we good
I think it from what I understand I think he might have only been on the plane w
What I want
Yeah but still
Anyway look
I only killed one guy but no
Once too many
So Alex
Alright now listen
July 4th
We're really excited about this
He can't do that
Because he was
Except for one time
Putlocker
It's not a big deal
Trump fluent
Express which means he fled the island
The flight logs they've all been checked on that airplane
From Newark
Into Palm Beach
And that's the only time
Donald Trump
What is playing
Palm Beach
Or any of this she says he hasn't
Actually one of the flight
The Trump took with commercial flight to he was on a plane
With Epstein
Epstein was it sabse was in the middle of me plus
I can't believe you're on the same flight why are we both flying commercial right now on some level that Alex is
I think that there is one
Answer this because
Is an erosion of his
His
Previous
The point that he was making
Look a little deeper Alex
That if you can find some of the
Very clear and
The obvious things that have been reported
So you pretend to Arch real
Dumbass
Yep anyway
Trump
On Monday tomorrow right
Tomorrow
Tactical
Flexible news is today that's what it is
I mean look
If it doesn't if he doesn't up announcing
Whatever I don't I wait still not news
Yeah
Man I wonder
I think it would be
Astounding if he
It'll be amazing because Alex had asked
Cuz like
How
Chaotic that
Like I said
Disrespectful
Absolutely
Care like
About
Beautifying the country of that much
Yeah
I mean
Even if you take the
The country out of it
Barbecuing
Totally
Firework
Don't make
Fireworks about yourself wearing a better wedding dress
Good good what good way to put it
So we will see on Monday what happened
Also Alex Stein sucks don't pay him any attention oh
Back
Until then
Back-end
Many things
This evening button
Then
Mio Mao
MDX
Hope you all have a wonderful dream agree with some
The sex robot