Damn important
I have great respect for its knowledge by I'm sick of them
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Ultra sleeve
Alex Jones
I'm excited because I have to go down
Cancel flights of stairs but I forgot to another building and write the basement of another building
It's such a hassle to carry this heavy hamper
Of clothes
Until I found one that has like backpack
I text app
So I'm up to do laundry in the future
At least for the first couple of times while still novel right
Bag Styles keep it fresh
I think you should have a slacker
That's good be tough on the stairs
Lot easier
I have like a couple of slinkies
Work
They said last week you know sgdq Summer Games Done Quick
I just wrapped up and they finished with Oprah
$3000000 that's amazing
So cool about it
Is that yesterday
They went from like to point something
In
24-hours
3 something
That's that's great
It was Doctors Without Borders absolutely it was in
Incredible to watch it was so cool
Much of this at all
Have to be a summer game
No
It's got to be like Mario Tennis it's more like that is when it
Right right right
Tropical free.com Country Tropical Mario ROM hacks
I made out of this game called Celeste
Jordan today we have something really fun
Also what a curveball
Here's the deal
We're going to be releasing its it's the 4th of July
According to Alex and Rodger Stone on their big exclusive from
Last week
Trump is going to announce his candidacy
On the 4th 100% will guarantee
Pylon
More about this last
Trump actually doesn't
I found something wonderful
Okay well thank you very much
Please give our regards
If possible
I will
Yes
Yes yes
Found a Colorado
To believe it was Swatch watch
That's great that is correct
I can't
I cannot wait to talk about this
I have watched
So much
Project Camelot try and find things for us to talk about
And this
The best
I felt like somebody who'd been walking through the desert who found water
About this guy
I hope he's not some weirdo problematic horrible person
Cuz I like him
Own hour in real good territory
So all this get excited for that I'm very excited
That's great idea
The first small losses and boodoo would like one from the horrible man
Christian Berry's tastes disgusting without whale butter happy birthday
To the hollow bone
Beelzebub of
Killer whale Island we all love you very very much that might be late. But thank you so much your help I was going
Kind of doctor doctor
Squirrel Girl from Star-Lord
Dreamy creamy black thank you so much
Very much help here in the mix
Watch too loose change and its consequences
You are now a technocrat
I have
Risen above
My enemies
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty of words for you but at the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
And f****** horse
She rode in on
All your s***
Nashville almost broke
Maybe I'll just be gone a month maybe 5 years
I'll walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
That's really what I want to do
I never want to come back
Apologized
To the crew in the listener's yesterday that I
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
I'll be better tomorrow
He's going to be a lot better of trump announces we will leave that to the
Another thought
Let's just
Bask in the wonderful Daughters of squats
Hi everyone from Project Camelot and I'm here
With major Solomon Berg and we're going to be doing what might be
Considered a groundbreaking interview
His dealings with
An awkward l.dre
That is comprised of what we know of as in some cases
Sasquatch in some cases yetis
You know him by a lot of name boy
I'm with it I am I am very much waiting
Dr. Sullivan major Sullivan bergton
Solomon Berg I have to say is one of the more likable people
Come on that's great that's great seem like he's a bit weird
And I don't believe anything he said but if there's anybody
Who I've kind of wanted to believe
I think it's him
If Sasquatch is talking to somebody
I don't think it's a right up top I don't know if he's f****** with care
This is a prank
Alright for sure
Of course
He's a major
He's also apparently quite an accomplished researcher and anthropology
Ura
I guess a doctor of a
Your apology and also a major
Are you a major in the United States army or navy or what do I major in
And where you're located or
I have maintained the title major
Could call Outlaw status
Laugh
My last
Posting was with United States Marine Corps
Call
Okay
Less than a minute into this interview I am
Ifucking hook
Not a major
Better believe I am
I really do and I have title even though I we've lost
Off the Grid
Okay if
If you are f****** with somebody
Right out the gate
You're nailing
Fantastic
So much
Carrie's content is this
Dumb s*** qanon nonsense and talking about 107 and Izzy JFK and like
I don't care about this
I do want to hear about vaccines I want to hear about
Squatch absolute
Listen bobcat
Goldthwaite
Can you do as many hours on Sasquatches he wants I'm going to watch every single one of them and I'm already at like 8 or no
I will keep going many late-night drunk conversation with the comedian
Jason Earles
Back in the day
Kohl's
Black Kraken
Is the name of his group
Here's what they were setting out to do
My last
Posting was with Eli
Marine Corps
Call
Which as I mentioned to our previous phone
Was
A kind of military
Really are argolis
Push the
Boundaries science
We did a lot of what I guess in the
Paranormal research
He does not elaborate on that
Cracking
Ideas
He has not he does not explain how he pushed the boundaries of science kind of
Espu would assume
Sure there's a little bit of telepathy or some of this stuff territory
As Willard later
It's kangaroos be Saturday
I don't want to spoil anything of course.
Give back story about how he got into this this black Kraken organization is true
Kraken
It goes back to when I was in high school
Hell yeah
I initially was recruited into the
Program
In my senior year of high
High School
Was
Planning on
Enlisting anyway
I was going to do ROTC
I was contact
Acted by an
Bet you all
That I have known
Throughout the years only as
Owl
Sorry what ad
Who phoned me that
Attitude to my test scores
Cabal
Leaders within the military who were looking to
Talent
What kind of test scores are you talkin like an F18
I think
He was really amazing at Galaga
Obviously clearly what happened because like if you
If it's just like you had really good SAT or ACT scores like almost every high school as someone who
One of those absolutely everybody would know somebody who
I don't know baby it's have other weird tested psychopath
Tester something where they like tesseract
Acumen for you know becoming a Super Science Soldier and that means that you have to be willing to like
Eat your parents toes you know like an ass
Here's a test that most people wouldn't pass what's the high I'm owl
Hahaha
Fat
That was an immediate failing grade your right here on your test
Out of here
Gets involved
He goes into the military
He does not get into comp
He was overseas
Little Rock
Alright and
I was never in
Combat
Women
Shaklee
Although I was present as a
Cultural liaison during
What became known as the Stargate incidents
Baghdad
In
Return to the states
And I was doing
Civilian work really happened time research
I was informed about a Mars program
And I spend
Play gear in the mall
Program
Where
To Earth
I'm sorry I am sorry
Yeah I'm 100% going to have to say right now
Unless he is saying that we 100% can use Stargates to transport from Earth to Mars instant
Famously this man
Is relativistic Lee speaking
Much older or younger than either of us and I can't remember which way it go
Smokey does explained that the engine and like sort of the cut like
The combustion system of the spacecraft
After they were in is basically what they do is they explode nukes behind it
Chipotle
An egg every
100000 miles or whatever I like it yeah so she was doing the civilian work
In between what he was in the military
Right
I was at Temple University
To Temple University
And James doing some more research there
I do have a civilian identity I did have a civilian identity
Temple University
Sullivan a bar and I
It's a very interesting research in the area
She was an animal communication
And it was
Zack research
That got the attention
My colonel
Lionel Sperling Getty
Black Reagan
Because
They had
Captured
An entity
Oh my
Sopranos ferlinghetti
Activate right now so he's working with owl and black
I like that man
So yeah they had to get him back in Chicago rapper was ferlinghetti
Beeezzz doing this animal human communication research
Got to get him back
Berlin Getty comes out anyway
Like bird apparently speak to giraffes baby soap
The Entity is on you man
Maybe dress will get into this later
Obviously this entity was
The Squatch
Captured
An entity
In
The Pacific
Quest
Outside of Seattle
This is the being
Bad
I prefer to as squats
Do you want me to clarify the
Determine squat
Watch is
Human
Oxidation
Oven noise
That these creatures make when they're very young
Human
Individual names like we do they have
Title system
So you earned your
In their society
And
Before they earn their
Title The Young Ones
Are just called Squad
This doesn't make any sense this is like really maybe my only motive
Contention with this guy because
Watchasort for Sasquatch
That comes from the Salish language
The word Sasquatch
Which means Wilder Harry banned in their language
Actually teach us the word for today
It's a good swing I like it any good imagine if it was actually sas-squad
She like SAS was his title he's still administering of servant to the squad
Community
So he's a Sasquatch and then there's obviously other ambassadors of special ambassador
He's a cultural advisor I think this is all coming
Going together
So we got
Squatch communication with
It's out there
That's a young one
So we got another one that we hear about here
One of the elders
Of the species that I have never had any direct contact
Which I know of
Through the overmind connect
Action that we talked about
Further
Please is The Wizard of Oz
This is a
Very very old male
Squatch
His hair has completely gray
He's been a recluse
For hundreds of years
These are very long-lived creatures
Adolescence last about 200 years
They're adults
Be as much as a millennial
This is Wizard of Washington is
Super lucky that it went gray instead of having squat pattern baldness
Yeah The Wizard of Oz YouTube Buddy
I love it
I don't know I think this might be overload I think I might
Explode in my brain from having
Too much fun dad
It's a delightful story he tells
Normally live where I live now
I am going to cry
Keep your tears because we have
I'm here somewhere
But I don't know if he can talk to giraffes
Because I don't know how to classify a giraffe
Technically he actually has a distinction of the kingdom phylum
Alright
So at a certain point the military brought you in because you have
Some unique ability
Screen with those abilities are
Yes so
I am
Kind of sensitive
I have developed
Secular
Telepathy
Communication
Which is a
Effective
Between human beings
And other play
Placental mammals
That have
Membrane structure
Call dacor
Corpus callosum
So if a giraffe does
Then you can telepathically to a giraffe
What
Is
See this is why we need to interview
Because Carrie has to handle the easiest question in the world
What's the funniest thing animal is ever said to you immediately immediately
Man we're going to get some jokes later
But not from animal squatches sense of humor. That's for sure
The scotch is practicing his tight 5 is that okay
That's great I like it
It's basically those
Turkey commercial
Yeah that's what that's what do you think
I feel like that's racist
Beef jerky is canceled
You were confused at least you made a little noise when the overmind was mention
And I don't know if we have a full clip where he totally explains
But it's not like a hive mind
But there is like
Collective
Convection
That do squashes have in their mind okay
And he was able to tap into this over Mayan
The overmind I referred
Was
Something I discovered early
And my communication Squad
The overmind is a kind of
Collective consciousness
And it is
It's a hive
They retain their individuality
But there is a sort of
Communal
Web of
I would describe it as
It's
Very comforting
Antique prints
From
What most humans experience in our very hyper individualize
World
So he individually experience
Personally experience
The squad
I don't know what that would be like to be
Do wild horse watches
His brains they have a
Parts that are more empathetic as opposed to ours where the more language centers you know there's a much much bigger comparative
Oh s***
Well you should do some research into that like I will like
What are the things that's kind of challenging about this is This Guy's real name
Yeah that does sound right because he did say that he used to have a civilian life
Assume that this is a taken name
Codename some sort
Which makes it difficult to pin down some of the things that
Can you sing like
In this next clip he talks about how he tried to publish papers
I would love to get my hands but I don't know what tool
Look for Briscoe pit name probably isn't
Where would you begin
I tried
Published papers
About
Communication I was able to achieve
And
I believe I used the word laughing stock
Talk with you in our our
Phone call
So
They have another name
For me
Doctor Dolittle
Well yeah so
It's raining
Either we're talking about
I'm trying to get
Good research
Probably because of the subject matter
None of my peers who are response
The peer-review
Are willing to take him seriously so I couldn't get it
Published
If there was research that showed
Some ability to talk to animals
There would not be like
People not taking it to your gallery
Yeah I know people would go ape shitt
Yeah
Kidding me if something was found it would make it through.
Able to be tested
Do you like listen
This is crazy
I admit
It's crazy but this is a testable hypothesis so f****** let's do it
You shouldn't be too offended people call you Doctor Dolittle now that's fine
Pop culture reference
Sino doctor Dolittle's the good guy
Just wanted to call you Norbit
Yeah that's a bad
Hercules
Dave
Meet Dave
Pluto Nash the one I was thinking of yeah that's cool you know it'll be called and I have a lot of lot of bad
Names and that's a Louvre
We need to talk a little bit about going tomorrow
And I would say that there's not a lot of details about his trip tomorrow
I want to know more about it
It was a year of his life
Now you went to Mars
Before you got involved in the whole sort of
Planet racist
Expect at least as far as the squad
Yes
I know my audience
It would be particularly interested in that so we can just start off
Get that
Out of the way so that we can do
A bit more into your
Current
Situation
Describe how you got it
Going to go to Mars and then what you did there and Sons
This goes back
So you 2010's this was asked
Sure
My service as a liaison
Is the Middle East so I returned to the states
And
I was contact
Did Again by Owl
A towel set
Deposition
That was off work
That might interest me now I had already
So when I was 18 and I was in.
Black Reagan
Then show me the rods
So I was aware
The krays
Well I did tunics to I knew about Grace
Say I knew everything
But I had a bass
Gadabout
Bx10
Ugh
The US government and Military
Involvement with
And
It was
During my service in the Middle East
That I learned
The greys were essential
Mercy
Yeah
I'm going to be honest with you
I told you about my brakes
Watching For All Mankind
I want to go to space so bad I just dream of it like the idea
Knowing that the Earth is absolutely
Tiny in relativity and yet actually being able to
See it
How could you be like
Yeah I think
Graser mercenaries if you work tomorrow
Yeah and I'm like
Experience of being on the ship it's like I was asleep the whole time or like
How long did it take
He totally cryo something you knows best deal on the details
That's kind of fine I guess I would like to know more
But I mean I wouldn't believe it if there were detailed or not so
It's not really the push
Right in movies it's always either the travel is just completely cut out and you cut from one location to the other
The whole movie
So I feel like we're in the cut for the most
Was later brief
And told about
Chins
To Interstellar fact
The guardian
Alliance
And the luciferian
I believe that the luciferian alliance
Centers
Around Draco Empire
And the guardian Alliance centers around
The pleiadian
So
Wanted to
Paolo Conte
Goodnight
She was kind of reminding me that we have a
Grandeur Duty
You know in the universe
As
A planet that is
This ongoing struggle
Between lightning
Darkness
So
I
Position
I travelled on board one of black
Break-ins Shep's
2 Mars 2000
Big one small one
30 people 50 gear
On the Martian surface
How I was
Baste an underground compound
Underground
And the recall
Sintonia
It's some parts of Mars you don't need a suit for insomnia
I feel like we got more of the Y
Yeah he answered some of the why he went responsibility
Still just don't feel like I know much about the
You know they had to change their name to the guardian Alliance cuz the former name used to be offensive to in
Sure
So these are the people that we know about already
Please Alliance
The Draco are the evil one right and the Pleiadians are the Guardian Life
So we already we already kind of know the players involved I mean I feel like if
We were to get into specifics between the two of them and their ideas of what the specifics are between
I think we might have some disc
Disagreement over what's going on
Tamar's to be an archaeology
Even studying some archaeological sites and like sites of
The battles that happened in the past
Because this is why I started to get like
This might be an elaborate Rowlett
Well you'll probably see
My
Research assistant was with Matt
What time
His name is Daniel Jordan he's a
Master sergeant
Daniel Jordan
Jordan and I
Combee area
4 degree
Which had been left
By ancient Martian Sol
I'm not indicating Martian as
Species
Weird
Talking about Martian Nationals this was
In an ancient vampire
Square Mars
Was a very Cosmopolitan multi
Cultural world
And so
Many of the
Martian soldiers armor
Referring to were in
Fact human beings
They were transferred
Cremation Earth which was
What time
Kingdoms like Atlantis
Sure
Weird feel like now we have to comb through our own Cadillac to see if there are references that he made threat arrest of it
We're too dumb to miss like I'm sure I don't I don't know I don't think so I think it's
Probably a coincidence but I was like
That is just
Unfair you know we've made the joke before but you actually are a witch and I'm going to burn you at the
I don't want to I don't want to take out the couch I totally understand
Solomon Berg
Found something he was able to actually smuggle back to Earth
Excite
There was one artifact
I was able to
Smuggle home
It was a stone
That appears to have been carved
Buy a Teenage Human
Conscripts
In the army of Mars
Used
To smoke a martian cyclic
Herb and then discarded
Back of it
Ends before the senior
Artifacts I was looking at it wasn't
I suppose that you would imagine is like
Ancient power generators are sentient computers and
You know none of that none of that blasted
It was it was just
Bear basic
He found a martian Hash Pipe
This is an
Listen I know it's too late but this is what Tammy future Martian conscripts
But if you smoked then you'll want to go home to be here
How did this toad get here
So you you said that I what is this Pompeii because you like the library
Have to be that everybody is Frozen in play 100% Terry has a similar concern about the story
Know when you
Monument Academy
Scription like that where you say
He was a conscript
Pretend
How can you know this where you working with remote viewers
Are you yourself
Seeing it as a remote viewer
We did work with remote viewers on Mars
Contingent
They were able to
Visual
Fractions
We analyzed
Stop since the residue that was found in the pipe
Daniel Jordan hats
We spoke some of that
He werewolf forecast on map
Why would anybody do that
We found this resin on an ancient Martian pipe
Daniel Jordan's going to do a trip report
The high was a little bit Speedy ladies gentlemen
But this is one small smoke for me
Claire's
What certainly won't kill you
I mean it really would have been a lot cooler if he was just like you know Olympus Mons erupted and then there was a pump
A you like situation that would be great and it said
Viewers
What carries Evenflo first reaction is like what did you have remote viewers not like with their archaeological ever
Evidence
Did this remote viewers and Rhythm Hit
So there's a bomb shelter
No. We're done talking about this but there is a joke about where
Lindbergh is right now
Now is she aware that you're going Pub
Daniel Jordan
Understand
You're still in in
You're still working with him is what you're saying
You still part of
Project black Reagan
What happened was fast
Forward
When
The issue with the Sass
Squad Squad Squad came up
Me too buddy
Me too
That's
When projects black
Can't use rail with my team
Okay
Okay now we've kind of made a big jump
Bracken
Yeah they went rogue
Is a real place to be with the squad
Israeli government so now they're hiding out in the bunker 80 clicks outside
Tel Aviv Israeli government has to keep squash Under Wraps otherwise people might stop believing in the
I'm I'm telling you once you see a squat you know that God is real
Sasquatch opens Minds much like toad
Quite a job
Terry wants to reel him back a little bit before we get into talking about how you quack snap somebody
Cherries like wait a second
Okay we got to go back to this like war on Mars stuff all little bit reason
But here's one of them
You know we can't I sleep
Actor Buck from
Deciphering glyph
We have been able to glean some details
We know that
There was a Providence Human
On Mars
That was under the leadership
Individual
Special X
Human
Anunnaki
Dihybrid
Crystalyx
Ascended
To the top leadership position
Mars
And
Keystroke resentment
Between
Two other non-human species both
Which claimed
To be indigenous tomorrow
Probably neither of them all
One of them was a
Trog
Sure
Which what what are
Like I don't know
Draw me one of those glyphs Yuri you said you started them you speak the language you got remote viewers you got
Ancient texts
But I do I do think that it's pretty
It's interesting that the way that this guy is presenting this ancient site
Is that there was a person who painted two groups against each other
In in there is it there's a sense
Of him recognizing that that is a bad thing
To do
And I think that that's
That's important
I mean
Here's
When when we see the
These types of
Like
Transposition
If you might you know like these ideas of the how people react
Walking to the situation
Currently transposed onto aliens doing an MLA
Process that information right
This has a different type of self-awareness
Let's do it then what we have
Seen before
Yeah it's what I feel from what we're listening
But also I think that if
If you're doing that kind of
Almost met a reading of the stuff that's being discussed
Oftentimes the
The actual conversation that's happening on that other level that metaphorical level is like really f***** up
He's actually talking about her
If it is metaphorical
There is a very positive message behind it
For the most part
I mean he's basically describing some sort of I don't know populist leader that comes to power
Susan uses a imaginary conflict to stoke resentment and then groups
I being a boy that just seems like I've never heard that before crazy
So you might be asking yourself
How does guys start out talking
The animals
How did that work
It is
One of the tests in high school no
I'll be honest
I've done exactly what
And I have not been successful
In the course of
Developing the
Techniques
First start
Experimenting
Conversation
And
Progressed from there to lab
Detroit asks where I'm at
Dolphins
We discovered there was a hard limit
That we could only
Achieve munication
Using this technique with
Central mammals No Malice
Stared
Hours
Kangaroos
Terry quietline
One of the other things that
Admirable about his world that he's painting is there are rules
Parameters to like what he's talking about
To do with the corpse
Does callosum there's like telepathic tendrils
In there and if you stimulate them he's able to talk to
The placental mammals
No it is it is that like any great science fiction
Always has the same basic fundamental
As long as you establish these rules in the beginning
And do not break them
Then you can do any imaginary bulshit you want to and he has he has
Fairly decent rules established tell me that you've tried staring at kangaroos 4 hours and failed
This show you one
You won
The show
The only thing that really take issue with so far as I want more details about Mars
Etymology is very much
How long have you how do you know that
How do you know the squash is telling you the truth
So in 2017 I was in the military found themselves a squat
And probably 2017
The US Military
Captured
One of these ants
He is a young male squats
What do you call a bath
Hey
He is
Approximately
300 years old
And that is in squash terms about
Like a twenty-two-year-old human
Soyo
I just I love the throwing around to terminology
It's a bachelor scar
I do,
It is always fun whenever you you like
Hear an actual scientist discuss like AAA
A grouping of animals that they've been studying for 4 years and I'll be like
Bachelor's of the seal Community are now challenging the dude you know like that kind of thing and then you're just like
Say that about Squatch soap
No squats rolls off the tongue
A good butt
For the future like I do like that
Sasquatch
Look up flower on his lapel get ready to go to prom or something
What is squatter's rights
Cuz the military had taken
StayWell
To use him
Quarryville
Somehow
They wanted to use them for propaganda
So black Kraken have to step in and save that's why
Seem to light
That
Both of these
Since I mentioned earlier the interstellar factions
Add an interest
In
Using the existence of the squash
And its species history
With both
T.i. Drake Allen played in a
Fires
Propagandistic
And because of
Government Center
Tration
By Draco
It was
A decision we made is Prague
Kragen
To remove
The squad
Trico insolence
Here
In the Heights States going to remove that squat
This this
Makes me think
Alright
We're not the only one
Hook spent an inordinate amount of time
In the Pacific Northwest looking for Sasquatch
I think aliens have also been out there looking for The elusive squats
Yes I mean yeah because they want to use a propaganda absolutely understand this correctly
Things will be sort of teased out in this conversation
The squad
He's a refugee from
Both
Draco and
Pleiadian territory
Sweets right right there here
We on other planets do we don't know that for sure
But they're here and so
Both of those groups want
To use the existence of these
Refugees against
The other
Rights and so the Draco are in charge of the US government I'm so black cracking felt that they need
Did you remove the squash that they could
Use them against the Pleiades
Right right right
Is under the
Anunnaki
The leader in Israel
Question territory so it's relatively safe in a certain way cuz everybody's trying to get have their own
Israeli government is pretty certain deeply involved
Specifically full Draco reptilian half-human more or less
The nebula space it's a good place to hide
And that's why they went there into an underground bunker 8 years
It's watch underground we need to have more respect for swatches if not only are they
Evading humans
Indeed the entire universe
Sure
This point they're only doing it because of the
Help of black cracker that is fair
Otherwise they would be found by the US government
Remember anything that happened Tire Blitz
Intergalactic propaganda
Because they displaced
Beer bisque watches
I'm trying to figure out
If
Finding out that it's watches real
Is worth
The trade-off of
Discovering it's being used for propaganda
I don't know if it's the psoriatic no matter what
What I was saying that like that this kind of meta conversation that you can imagine it
Is happening when you're talking about these aliens mod
Implications on the real world
This guy
Look at what he's saying metaphorically
It's positive stuff
I mean it's stuff like this cuz you never f****** hear this from any of the other alien weirdos
On the intergalactic
Descale
There are
Two major I would call them alliances or coalition
And one
Is Central to round light work
And the other is centered around
Domination
But within
The framework
Abdullah lightworkers
There has still been a history of
Conflict
So
When we talk about
Radians
Summer
When I
Engaged
You know less
I would say movie with more no more credulous
People I have
Heard Sadie and subscribed in almost exclusively
Like
Heroic
Or even religious terms
And that
I think
That says more about us than it does about any extra
I don't think
You can judge an entire species based on its government
You absolutely do not hear that from anybody else on this
It's f****** show for Carrie every uniform they all are the same
She literally scanners her brain all over the space
Nope
No she didn't freak out. Hurt anybody physically
I think
It's possible
Here's a couple thoughts I have
First of all
Absolutely dominated you on Project Camelot
Out of the park no amazing
Second
He seems like he can
Really spin this
Pretty well like all of this yarn
And to carry is got to be looking at this like
He's a lot of information and awareness of a lot of the touchstones of things that are
Like in my world's right
This guy I could use him
I could use this guy Mark Richards in my prison and I got to go talk to him know I can get
Hugh Montezuma from that Israeli bunker
We can talk
And he communicates With Sasquatch Sasquatch can tell him things
He can get into these watch over my man imagine the information that could be
Be comic telling you this is
Almost
Exactly what if I were f******
Cooking with Carrie
And I'd listen to all of our
Camelot episodes like
Over the span of a couple of weeks
Man that does see this does seem like a formula
That makes a lot of sense
There is there is a
Areal
Is this where an audition
Basically
Mikey's
Killing it
Fairly soon
Remind me to eat seems prepared to know what it is she's interested in
Aware or at least Knows Alot About That World exactly is a lot of words
A lot of
Concept
But also it's so admirable
That it does also feel like there's a weaving of
Empathy
Weaving of
Decency
Through this as opposed to a
Looking at things and such a black-and-white way with aliens
The silence
I mean it's implied review
Carrie 2 or fake
You know like
Date with many people
Call Pleiadians Heroes
I think it says more about us
You
That you reclaim that they're all evil
I think it's very clear that he's that's a straight-up
It could be read that way it may not be it depends kind of I guess how much
Awareness he has of all the fairies app
But he has behind his
Discussion of aliens
Really.
I don't think it's necessarily notices
Or would notice that too much that I
Van alien
Like mutually contradictory
Take refugees
The Pleiadians
Their empire does have but his
History of expansion
And
Squatch is feces
War refugees
But they were also refugees in
So neither neither Empire has been
Take really good
Heroes are
Why isn't westerheide I think this guy is arguing that swatches are the original space juice
I think that's what I'm going to skip to the next
Show squat
Creators create Ian's and Draco with suspicion
They were willing to consider you
Because you were
Kind of neither on one side or the other
So to speak
Bright Eyes
I think squash is comfortable with Jews
As I think squash sensors are kind of
Kindred
Dammit
You know we are supposed
In in the universe and so they
Actually a rogue
Species that became a rope species without a home for many many years
Squatch was very comfortable with me
That makes sense that is exactly right you have
You have 100%
Created the correct there it is to build around this watch absolutely
Dyaspora history
And Heritage weekend we can connect on that level up being refugees like
It's
Great
I mean it's hard not to take a look at his story and say well the United
Chase's incredibly anti-semitic along with Germany being incredibly anti-Semitic
And then well then
Played out the way they did
Kia
I also think of another good button would be there's no Heroes it for the squad
Sasquatch that is a little bit.
If we're talking about space
Eastern and Western
That's not really matter
Makes me think
That it is
Intended to be
That seems like a little hat tip
Do you like this is metaphorical
This is videos
Or not refugees into the Ukrainian refugees as we speak
Don't know if I want to go that far Sam convinced
Bears
There is a sense
But it doesn't make sense if you're talkin about
What is in space
We can always fight over authorial intent
Terms of practical applications this does seem very 121
Unless unless I guess there's a possibility that like these space people they just talked about like
The Earth as the West
You know like maybe where the west of the Galaxy
I don't know anyway I get strong metaphorical 5
To win over Squad
Because of their shared services
Similarities in Heritage
And then also
I have
Steaua lot to gain squatches trust a lot of it was involving humor
Now that was really what you know what works
In order for squats because swatches
A Sapient being
In order for squats to really let me in
To his mind
I first had to get to squat
Humor
Can I tell you what I did
Yes to make squats
Please
I wore a gorilla mask
Okay and I was expecting more
Yes
No laughter
As is
Species
What
Pretty sad
Gorilla masks
I was hoping for a little bit more out of that but is great too because it's not over selling it
You're right you're right but I mean it it would have been it would have been nice if it was like listen
Swatch
Let me introduce you to
Jonathan Winters you're going to f****** love this guy he does all the voices come on
And he's already Charmed One State be a date there we go
I just I find this incredibly Charming but also there's a piece of it that's a little bit weird and that isn't like
Your first instinct is to put on a gorilla mask when you tried to talk to a Sasquatch
That's how do you not think that's
Seem like you're
Because just this mean that Sasquatch has an edgy sense of humor
Is he doing Apes
If that would happen if he Al Jolson in the Squatch
I was worried about that a little bit
I got into swatches heart
So there's not many female squatches on Earth
Apparently mostly males and as explained
This is probably just a coincidence based on
The ship that landed here
Probably swatches all over the place as refugees scattered
Squatch is here mostly men
Take a piss
Now that they have an interesting social
Structure
Females are sedentary
And there are relatively few females on Earth
This isn't their natural setup this is more
Just
Because they're refugees this is who happens to land here
So there are about
40 Adil males to everyone at all female
So the
The males are nomadic they roam
They
Beauregard jobs
Stay
But how did they land here
Didn't you say they borrowed a spaceship
Shipper something
Over the years they've
Acquired many ships
Alien civilizations
So they don't
They don't
Have their own
Like indigenous Lee Designs
Sweet
They do have a number of advance
Spacecraft
Keep it in using cloak
Yes apparently
Some of the younger squatches are passable is human
They're humanoid and they're only like 7 ft tall for the first few hundred years
Almost like tall person and you look up and you're like all you play basketball in there a little insulted and then you know they're human and then they want to fix
Fix your car
Jobs
Do you know like it
Is there was a squash plant
Hey whatever if it's wouldn't be the way
They necessarily organized Society
And in the same way there's a discussion about how like
They don't build any
Anything here but they probably would
Right all right
Are I'm sorry they're more in the woods
A lot of them are human society
They live in studio apartment
Spitballing here do they have a rum Springer
You know what I'm saying I'll just bring us squat spring
Like what kind of escape from swatches I wear shoes lacrosse
Don't want to return to the forest
Sure
But here's the problem
Was that
If you're going to go and explore what it's like
To be in human society got to shave
Throwback
Take a while for spots to throw it all back
So obviously there's some grass
About how the f*** did you sneak a Sasquatch
Is there gunfire did you trick somebody
You can't really talk
How did you
Escape from the US
Where you assisted by
Other soldiers
You know
This is where we're edging up on
Fun things I can't directly comment on
I can say that
I
Committed what
To be considered
Grimes
Where
Now
Issue
With
Being charged with anything is that
Say what
Newegg knowledge
To acknowledge
That's why she exists good
So because they
Can't afford to blow that cover up
They can actually
Proceed with any
Tradition
This is why people who are involved in these clandestine things going to say
There's nothing we can do
Formally request Israel turnover the Squatch beef
He's gotta
And as we all know there's no way for anybody it is real to suddenly find out where you are and then murder you
Doesn't sound like it happens though I want
Beastly understand
But you can't get into the
How do you
Steelers Squad
You have to kill at least a couple people right I mean like there's got to be a pretty heavy security
Throw this out there maybe
There was a whole group of people who would come to understand and love this watch so there was the entire
Black Kraken
Maybe they convinced some of the other people or they could have used telepathy of some sort to convince them to continue helping them but
It's entirely possible that
Everyone would have come
Passionately help for this watch
The ships
Squatch has
Maybe that technology exists
Why can't you put it on a little shirt
Cares let's go get out of here walk right out
Able to tell by this point but
Berg
Connection
Wrist watch
Emotional
He cares about this
They don't tell me that they goes any further than that
No.
Poetic as hell
Looking at Squatch was almost like
Looking at a missing link
But not just a missing Lincoln
Connecting us tomorrow
Stars
And for future
The
The initial
Communication
Flourished into something
I described it as emotional
Developed an affinity
The squad
I have come to recognize
Traces in myself
On an order
Like a star
So
Like the
Who played Ian's
Starseed connections
They have
Been active
In the evolution
Of Life on Multi
Worlds
So in an intimate way was
Squash
So in an intimate way was the squad that really does have the ring of a f****** documentary Bhai
Richard Attenborough
The Squatch
The squad is a missing link not judge
To the Past
Stars who are future wildly poetic
Guys got the good delivery
It'll be heartbroken if we find out later that he's some kind of a real a******
Very brutal
That is going to be really brutal cuz this performing
Is outstanding it really is
So now we have we are all just watched we are all my love
Yeah absolutely
We learned of a new alien
Animal do you think this alien is similar to a kangaroo cuz that would really be full circle sure
Be appropriate
It is not a placental mammal
I really feel like I've we need an octopus a mollusk type
Alien right to far-off
I've learned
Very intriguing diverse life
Forms that would have been represented on Ancient Mars
Carlton days
I'm aware of it
Bubble fish
Like species that lives on gas
Right on
The atmospheres of gas giants
And they
Are controlled by a benevolent
AI
Well it is also said that the Draco are actually controlled by an AI
But they're stopping at
Statement
You can say that again
Cute exchange Auto.
Is winning her over
Feel like maybe
Maybe these people are so easily influence you just have to make up a less
Evil
Evil space idea
Annabelle just be like yeah that sounds right it's possible that's it that's the trick
This is so malleable we need to lie to them in the right way and it'll go well it might be a model Ford
Dealing with you and odds
Did you create a
Conspiracy fun game kind of totally
But that leads to like positive conclusion
I don't know I don't chase the Squatch metaphorically
So remember that
In life you can choose to be many things
Be a bachelor
Oh yeah
So Carrie has a quest
All right so you're coming out and bringing this information out
Do you think that
Maybe you're being used
To do that
And then we lose the track of the question I've ever had that doesn't make any sense but okay
In your group
Or even outside your group that has
Sorted orchestrated this interview in such a way that you can talk
About this
Which
It's been going on for several years
You know and an end
In a certain sense
You you become or you could
Become a kind of a political football
If people even acknowledge
Interviewing your existed
Oh they will be a reason for that
And one of the reasons that I can see at least at this moment because
You know as you know in the greater
World scene
We have this kind of you know dark vs light
Drama
Being played out especially in heightened terms within the United
And so you know
It is an interesting
We call it playing the alien car
Right
So
More local
So-called alien species you want to call them they may not like
Charmeleon but let's call
Local alien species
Because that's what
The conventional
Person watching as my
You know you're not going to stay
They probably
And I know that
Sasquatch
As an alien species they just
You know but they also think they're
Bar between they don't think of them as a whole
Population
Coming from another
You know coming from
Outer space
Atlantis that they
You know how to leave
She gets completely sidetracked from her political football question into like
Other people can't conceive of aliens coming from another plane
I'm sure some fine okay
Everyone wants to think that's watches Justin
Man
You know I feel like this guy's really under selling how important the overmind is in the fact that he was able to tap into it
Cuz if he can tap into it that would suggest
Just about anybody could tap into it
I think we could all tappendorf then we're all just watch over by tapping into that right now
Because that's what the next
You might be Daniel Georgia
That is what happened
So on this tip
What's going on is that
Harry
Is asking
All right so you can connect
To the squad shirt over mine
Can
Uconnect
The other people
Who are telepathic through a canoe
Be a conduit through which
What would you ask can you teach me how to access the squash mine
Well
Is it a lot of work
Power
Okay now I want to ask you strange question but
I'm sure you can handle it
So you've been in touch
With this
Overmind of the staff
Sasquatch
And in so doing
Do you feel that you have therefore
You know kind of like you travel
In that mindspace
So you can
Conversion that mindspace did you at least commit
You know learn things there you said
About their histories Deborah
Right
And I assume
Perhaps you can send and receive signals to individuals within that mindspace
Squatch can I I've not
I've been able to do that but that
Distantly I'm still learning
Alright
And
So that in a certain way
Let's say I'm talking to you and let's say you're in in telepathy
Communication with another human
Not necessarily me but anyone
Do your
Even close to somebody
And yet your telepathy
Because once you're telepathic
You know it's sort of a natural inclination to try to be telepathy
West
Anyone you have an affinity
So if if you did that
Would they be able to ban happened
This overmind
Through you
If possible
It's
It's one of those situations where they at
You know what they're looking for it is little bit like with the Target in remote viewing
They have to have a card
So I am I don't understand exactly
The big picture of what is being a
I think that's fairly clear
But here was with weird
I thought
For sure
He was asking is can you get me into the club
Basically like I am telepathic I'm psychic
Can I can you vouch for me to get ahold of
Let me over my you connect to it all connects through you right
She's asking for a conference call
But I thought
I was wrong
Cuz this question has a second stage to it okay
Terry's actually a little bit suspicious
Alright well what if that
What is that
You know. Mind
Wanted to send a message
They could send it in.
I can use you
As a carrier
Too bad send it telepathically to other humans
They could and
I might not even know that that is what's hap
Oh s*** I got twice
Setting this up let's say this interview
Isn't it
Possible that that's what
Oh my god really possible I don't know
I have to
To admit the pause
Stability
Plausible
It's
Works as a
Hypothesis
So that's some great disassembly right there I love that that is great he was thrown for a loop and then he
It's like you know what
Let's give it a truck that I love that I don't know if it's an indication of like
Really good improv chops
Or somebody who actually sincerely believes this or whatever but like
That that question being prone to you being like
Hey you know what is my baby that is what's happening to me doesn't seem like somebody who's like
Complete liar
Like I would like someone who's trying to pull a fast
This is at the very least not agree
Right because he's definitely say
No yeah
Definitely not what's happening later
I am not being used as an unwitting conduit for squash to get a message out over your show part of all the
All of these characters is at least a level of North
Exorcism that has them being within that like Dominator roll
I'm still learning I don't really know how to do that
Humility totally this is an interesting thing
And if if you can
If you can cut contact
I'm down
Sure I'm down for it
Hi if somebody could get me out of the woods Wisconsin
These squatters want to be in the woods
Concerned
And the reason is
Because
This overmind
Could be
Theoretically infiltrator
Now
Where that is first concern as well. Where is squat
Israel
The Anunnaki are they going to turn the overmind evil
Worried about we got now I am worried
From me thinking it's just like I carry wanting to get the get in there herself
National Defense
Issue we need to destroy the overmind before the enemy infiltrated
Okay then let me ask you another question about
I did ask you off
As well
Squad
InTouch
Telepathically with Anunnaki and I think you
You said no
The answer is no
But that
Is
More bikes choice
The overmind
Can't
Work
Against
You are well
Silvermine cam
It can influence you but it's
Make you or any individual
In it
Do something against
There will
Do it
It's not like the unlock
Can
Invade
The overmind
They can't they can't
Stairway
Through it
They can't prove or set
Squatmax let the man bikes
Okay
I'm relieved
I love this watch
So far they've got things pretty well figured out question answered
I am no longer worried about Bruno Mars Attacks from the Anunnaki
Find is is I mean
Unbreakable
He still has some concerns and that one of the big ones
Of my buddies
Tell me about all the help that other alien races
Star giving to us
There's so many Technologies and Secret
The world that the
The Raptors are giving Mark Richards and what happened
But that's not the case with the squad
Why
Why isn't the squad helping us
Well the squash is living in peace and harmony with the f****** environment why do you think they're not dropping
What do you think about helping us they got to work two jobs
They haven't been able to the humans haven't been able to develop
Kind of
Species to species our working relationship in which they might
Be able to be assisted by
Stop squat
We have there
They're very rare but they do work at
There are humans
Who are
Aware of what they are
They've worked out a little
Barter systems and trade deals
Labor
You know
Is good I actually mean in in a substantial way
Such as
Helping with our space
You know exploration or things that they might actually
Know about
Their longevity and also they could be like
I don't know what Nietzsche human temperature
So are you know there's lots of
Interactions that they could
Could benefit
Our world with
Also
Having to do with you know educating
I don't know the United Nation
Unfortunately would have conceived. But you know what I mean
In other words directly
They did try
There there has been times in there
When they have done that
With on other
Finance
Michelle the benefit
Arc'teryx
Experience and their their wisdom and then what happened
With other planets but it always seem to
Backfire
Xenophobia
So
The
The hatred against
Them
You know that
The fear of them
There are other nests
Being different from
Play Danzig difference
Greg house
It was always
What's the matter
How they contributed
The planets where they lived
On earth now there must be
Conscious so they're much rarer
Alright
Once Bitten Twice Shy is this watch and it's hard not to say that if you're
Answer to that question is just space racism you're dead on
There's racism Q why would they help you you captured and kept him in a f****** at military base
No jailbreak taken across the world into a bunker
Father with the human race you moron
Yeah and they've been burned before which makes sense why you be cautious
Let you know as more people
Squatch is able to trust more people
You know there may be better
It's been a recruit in terms of these things that carries asking about
You're asking too much of the squats right now very strange
To be in a world
Where are most of the time
Aliens are a thinly-veiled ways to attack the Jews
And in this Cirque
Circumstance
Aliens are a thinly-veiled way to explain the Jews experience with racism as they've gone through the over history of the world
You you can take you can take it on that level and then you can also just take it on another level that is
These aliens the Squatch is is
Being used as a
Entry point in a way to understand other ring in a way to understand the experience of people
Who are unlike you and like
Empathy
Teaching
I mean
Stopwatch
Maybe if we change our attitudes towards the over
We will have learned help
As opposed to you just being like
Why can't we just capture them and steal their ship
Demand help they're not evil alien
Right
So we don't couple
Clips left in this also is just kind of I feel like this is a good summation of
The sort of mentality that's being presented here
Is there any questions or statements that you haven't made that you would like
How to make on his behalf
It's time
No just that we are both
Salisbury gravy
For the opportunity to present
Our side of the story
And hopefully I'm bring a little late
A nuance
Into this hole
Complex situation with draco's
Playdium
Cuz I think
You know some of the the reporting I've seen Elsewhere on that
Has been Dairy
One-sided moralistic good and evil and
I want to go I don't know about you but I'm
I like The View.
Storytelling II like
Text Dad
Edaville
The antagonist in Star Trek whenever really feeling
I try to see the world is
People maybe
Antagonist
To us but
Ultimately we're all sentient beings
We all just one
Life and dignity in
Freedom
Yes no
Not even a aliens don't want that
Aliens and you think alike
Oh they're all just uniformly
I really think that it should not have taken us this long
To get that very simple message out on Project
Episodes of we thought about project cable at not at one point is somebody good like
You know there are civilians in all species everywhere just trying to live a good life
It's very foreign concept 2 episode I've listened to
I also I am so
I am much like the squad
In terms of bird before and I'm so scared of being positive
This is so scary we can't ever have anything nice
Yeah but he seems like
He's a guest unlike any that I've heard very much on the old Camelot
Here is maybe possible reason why
This last clip
Like I don't understand
This is
I will also
Say that when I was six years old e.t. was my abs
Absolute favorite
Movie my grandfather bought me
Lchs
Casaba
The one that one
Light green
The garnet
I must have worn that cassette out watching it
200 *
Alright so you already had that
You know sort of
Abilities that your abilities were sort of
Really yub
Became what you became minister
You already have the ability
The abilities
Predominantly
I would say I have a curious mind and I had a
Predisposition toward
A
Sizing with
The other
Trying to understand
Beings that were different from me
I was always very fond of animals I was always
There was active in a lot of
Peanut
Massive Justice causes
You know I've always been
Passionate
Advocate
That's for people
I joined the military
Because I wanted
Be part of something
Think bigger than me
I saw stand
Genuinely
Help people in need
I've always sort of
Seen my role here as being of service to others
UCare
You can kind of feel that
Yep you know like dip that kind of comes out in his conception of the alien Universe elderly
There is a helpfulness is a caring there's an
Progressive
Justice
Totally
Link to it absolutely he comes it this
From the perspective of
Like caring about these aliens
Where is so many other of these people are like
Focus seems to be on like weird political intrigue
Among these alien
The relationship he has with battles
Spacebattles is that he went
To Mars and found a pipe
But some Soldier thrown out years and years and years ago
And honestly that's a very exciting thing
She is trying to learn from the aftermath
Civil War as opposed to being involved in it like
Like Mark Richards
Flying Minerva through
They care like that Forrest Gump in his way through the goddamn spaceworld the act like you've got the Millennium Falcon
Text battle
Yeah and I
He's like a really fun today
Fundamental difference about Lake
How you relate to the topics
But you're talking about
It is it is funny
Because
There is a like a current
Movement among historians to like re-evaluate a lot of these narratives that we've been
Constantly hitting and whether or not any of this b******* actually even makes any f****** sense
That was written a few hundred years ago by white men with a lot of
Ax
Sister grind
Right it seems like this is such a very similar idea of reimagining space
History it's not white male-dominated
It's just that's what it is it doesn't it doesn't paint the Pleiadians of the absolute Heroes
Like sure they're lightworkers and maybe they're the good guys
Per se
But they're still expansionist
Displaced the the
Porter
That might be my next tattoo
Birthday
God there's something really refreshing about this and I wanted to
Cleanse of pallets of
Things
Listen to enjoy.
About Squad
What a fantastic
Journey that was
Crate
Yeah I better not be a piece of s***
Jeremy
Please please just don't let us have one
Where in end if you are just run away ever erase your name from the internet and
This let us all believe in the good news is like
He seems open to like coming back
And carry obviously have him back
So we could have a new Mark Richards on our hands a positive influence
Fantastic
Here's the other thing that I think is really strange is like how much can he possibly know about Carrie
Because he's coming in with this like I've always been a passionate defender of like Progressive social causes right
Justice movement itself like that
Kelly's f****** straight-up qanon & Beyond hundred percent I don't understand how
Anthony I think it still could be a possibility that it is
Definitely could be a coincidence but I'll be goddamned if that's not a
F****** big coincidences pretty big sizable
Yes yeah absolutely the prank is disseminating a positive message within the
The world of Gary's alien nonsense so I have no problem
Platforming this prank
And I hope you all did too and will be back
Join the light.
Until then
Jeff will be back but until then a Mio I'm Leon dzx Clark
Maybe maybe I'll throw this in I'm crystalyx
I hope you all have a wonderful dream creamy supper
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color