Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
Knowledge fight
Nick.com
Worship at the altar of Selena little bit about
Alex gold
Maybe we are Dan what's up
Apartment here for a bit
If it's longer than I've lived in most apartment
That's my life that's definitely true for another year and so one of the things
Is that I'm doing
To keep things fresh is moving things around
Great way to move without actually move exactly reorganizing some of the room
In this
It is a type of desired effect
It's freshening things up I feel
I don't know I'm maybe I'm telling myself that I'm not sure
Don't be mad when you're trying to convince yourself of something that it would be good if you believed in the first place I believe it
Cecil there you go
I feel like a it's like
Alright it's a whole new place
Vibrates but dead is about the band Beirut
So there's a song on the album no no no
Which I haven't listened
Listen to it forever and I found again
The other day it's called Chevrolet
That well
Call Gibraltar and it has this great upbeat just got this
Fantastic 1
What kind of things
And then it has three huge downbeats that's the repetition
When you walk
To this song
Everything is going fine you're just walking along with the beat and every time again
Get to the three downbeats all the sudden you go
And then you back and then take another step and keep walking
It's my favorite song
To walk to because
You can't stop the
You can't stop yourself you take a step
On the first downbeat
You kick your foot out
Can you take another step and you keep going
I
I defy you to listen to this song while walking and not do that alright I'll take you up on that challenge I'll let you know
Episode 500 tire world
I honestly think I'm going to have no trouble not doing that
Everything's going to be really disappointing for you to learn how it's just you
You're not now is that
But this song is too powerful even for you
Okay we'll see
B b that means there's not
You might be pleasantly surprised to hear a little harder
Pleasantly surprised to hear this episode
Something is a little bit weird
Here substantially more stuff to cover
Quite frankly because here we are
In the
Aftermath of their of course there was a shooting in Highland Park Illinois
Outside
Chicago on the 4th of July parade
Cancel
I kind of
Thought for sure
Alex would do a special report that night because he does that sort of thing
4 weeks since our last special reported up call.
For sure he's going to have probably have
Been too late
By the time
The news break
Looking forward to a been on his show
But that night
He could have picked out some marginalized group to defame with
You would think
You would imagine
But it never
It never materialized
That's interesting and so in reality we really just have a little bit of stuff
Before his show on the 4th
And then the fifth
We're going to be going over today
I think it will be less interesting than you think
To approve get into the episode
Surfer snow pants run thank you so much you are now policy wonk
David mncourts azaleas
David David Watson Watson thank you so much you are now policy walk
Great alias
Thank you so much
Text Mike at Zia internatural ability destroy everything
I know in love thank you so much you are now policy
Very much
Next your own play coin thank you so much
Thank you very much I'm told that's an anagram
Cakes and thank you so much
I'm a policy wonk you've gone the disc
It's been awhile
Exxon
Melissa
Thank you so much you're now policy walk
Thank you very much Mikey B's thank you so much right now
So Jordan
Forget it stays episode here isn't our contacts dropped
From Today Show
Okay
Alright alright
I've honestly
This may be the first time that I've ever wholeheartedly
No reservation
Agreed with Alex
His big boy pants
There is no.
Makes me think of that to a contestant on that season of the Taskmaster with mustache
Its skin tight is the funniest person alive when he tried to fart for roughly
6 hours
It just doesn't get too I just don't understand that bad
So we're going to start out here on the 4th
You should know about the 4th but I didn't realize
Until he was a little bit too late is that it's the best
Alex just re-aired
The number of his interviews one of them with dr. zelenko
Who is a recently deceased
Hydrox
Chloroquine and Ivermectin
Covid annihilus guy chair
Another one but
He did do a little bit up
Brought that was
Fresh contact
Us under 1776
Chess Astorian
Unfortunately has taken control of the major 5
A shooting the media
Oblate science and medicine says Douglas MacKinnon
So I'm not sure exactly how you quantify relative amounts of tyranny but I can tell you that certain groups of people
Definitely aren't living under greater tyranny
Today than they were in 1776 status
Are all the people Alex pink
Thanks though
This is an article written by a guy named Douglas
McKinnon who Alex
What is discrediting as a historic
Contributor whose also written
The couple of books
That are thrillers
Makes me very suspicious
Artist profile on Simon & Schuster's website it says
Ryder
Naughty speechwriter buddyrider
For both Reagan and h.w. Bush
Quote and afterwards in a joint
Command.
The Pentagon where you at a top secret government clearance
Alright so
He wrote bedtime stories to help Reagan fall asleep and then we had a fake
Magical power on the Pentagon is with these folks
Like Steve pieczenik were Thrillers to Thrillers of being a right-wing commentator is
They go together successfully inverted reality and fiction to the point where it makes more sense
Sense for them to come from a fictional background than it does a reality
Background right maybe
You can find a load of shity takes on his author page on Fox News
Here's some Choice headlight
How long will I be allowed to remain a Christian three and a half weeks
It was worth
Why Trump's unconventional approach will help him win big in 2020
Quote milkshake attacks are not funny
Let's needs to condemn pranks before it's too late
I told man
Noticeably absent
On this list about things like the unite the right Rally or anywhere
Concern about groups like a proud boys
Exercising
You know
Forgot
He was
And I will admit
He is roughly 400 years old
And he was a super slave
So yes
He does he pursue
Recently lived under less tyranny
Now the clinic 17:7
He also wrote an editorial a few days back
Real July 4th fireworks
Don't let the left
Cancel Independence Day
Oh my God we were so close to
She was mixed in like how he thinks that the US needs to have a permanent base on the moon
Which would be a flagrant violation of International Space tree
Also in 2016 he had a vision where he claims that the story of the 40 days Jesus spent on Earth
After his resurrection were released
He seems like a cool guy
Weirdly years back he used a bunch of by lines for the Huffington Post
Little bit different let's drift
He posted up headlines like quote GOP leadership should have condemned the racist joke
Quote why does Washington ignore the ultimate global warming threat
I'm cold
I am a Conservative Christian who supports gay rights because they're human
Almost like he had a brand adjustment
Anyway he went on Fox News and he had an interview where he was promoting his book
Call the 50
D6 which apparently is about the quote
56 Patriot to risk it all
Call the sign the Declaration of Independence
He told the interviewer quote last July 3rd I wasn't even thinking about writing a book
Then on the 4th of July last year I did a little bit of a video tour on some of the more Liberal site
And on-site after site I saw guest on the left called not only for the cancellation of the 4th of July
But the cancellation of our founding fathers and the American
Flag
You can't let that s*** Slide Man bright
Anyway this Fox & Friends interview did was essentially a promotional piece for his book
And the others sensationalize
26 17th Avenue
It's more or less just another attempt to drive attention at Book Sales analysis
Who's playing into that
It is kind of funny
You know when he was at the house
Kingdom pociask
The question that he would himself answer later which is why
You can't ignore climate change
And then he starts to work for Fox News any realize
It was a s*** ton of money
Here's the thing that's kind of bizarre about that happened
Then post think he was actually not work
Did they used to have that contributor portal where you could write your own up and you just do whatever the f*** you wanted they were so
So stupid he was doing
I don't know
Capacity you didn't have like a freelancer contract I don't think with the post
I think he was just like
I'll write this huge trying to find his audience anyway it wasn't being a good dude
I wasn't having a little bit of it like I listen I'm okay with just a little
Okay
Nike slippers our last run
On the 4th so much fun if you just did a compilation of Leo zagami
What time the game on with the champ was right around before
With his very beautiful wife says they keep talking about I love it
I smuggled in b y
This is where I really should have figured out that Alex wasn't going to be there for the rest of the episode because
This is
Pretty early in a segment
And if this is usually saved for towards the
Douglas
Fox & Friends interview
Campos
Because of the last Stranglehold
Inflation education and Science Center
Not the rebels.
Establishment
As bad as the tyranny
Boston 1776
In many ways it's way worse worse
Because the far-left control over the five
Major megaphones
Our society
I don't need to read more of that table play the club
Coming up here in just a few minutes but I
Wars cost money
Prosecute this war
The New World Order without your support
Don't want to ask you on this shall I force
Pray for me
Global Awakening
And to support us financially
Unpopular us into submission
What sounds right
Especially
Upper-middle-class nouveau-riche
Realize you're going to lose everything in this inflationary New World Order
Neo-fascists Global governments
Directing Communists policy to the Grassroots
If you will simply realize that
And say no to it
The most important way to resist it is financially
Shell products
Enrich your life your immune system
This is outrageous
I mean
Sad I didn't notice I had a fee
Feeling of it that was like this is too early in the segment
You must be trying to get out of there I really should have
Not listen
Those other interviews
Yeah you got to give Alex
Bunch of that money
Actually outside of the cravenness of that ad pitch
Clippers schedule
It's so bizarre how like Alex just weaves his own editorializing into other people's attitude
How quickly he lost interest in this story
I'm weirded out by some people not being like hey man
I would prefer it if
You just quoted me accurately even even people that he's
Ostensibly friends
I didn't make that up
Yeah makes words in people's mouth
I guess no one really
Tell really cares they make up everything anyways and I also don't take him seriously
I mean it's all all APUSH
I think what we have
To do
Is mixed some of the Bill of Rights
Conditional
But lacking in the sky
You never have to quarter soldiers
Unless you start talking s***
You know oh we're under more tyranny than we were in 1776 guess what you quarter soldiers now
Like I'm fine with that kind of Bill of Rights I'm sorry would you rather cortical just done
Alex you keep talking about how you have a ranch on internet
Congratulations well done
So we get to the 5th and now the shooting has happened
And
Honestly whatever
Expected
I'm just go put my cards out on the table I would have expected this to be his top story
It definitely is brought up immediately
But it's not covered that much
That is the most worrying sign of culture I think I can
Inconceivable
It really is the most worrying sign that this motherfuker did that s***
And even Alex Jones is like listen
We can kind of gloss over this
This one honestly
It does feel like there's a lot of other things he'd rather talk about does he does deal with his a little bit up front
Island
Illinois
July 4th
Description as all the other Mass shooters
Has now been caught by the police today
Chase
This is the world we live in ladies and gentlemen
Walked in there to die by the human Smugglers because their families
The second half of the money
I was about to contract
Changes
Sure
To do that
Dumb question that Alex is posing and it's honestly one of the more pathetic attempt I've seen him used to try to deflect
Attention away from gun related tragedy but I'll bite
So why is it that people don't want to ban tractor
Your trailers after the
These migrants were found dead inside
But people do want to ban guns after a mass shooting at a Fourth of July parade
That is a really complex and interesting question that I think it'll take just so much time to answer in a lot of his
Historical reference
This is right
The truck itself
To kill those
They were trapped inside it
But if that's the standard for being used as a weapon
But I guess that you'd really have to just
Any enclosed space
Yeah prisons would go away real quick to everything you can be locked inside from the outside that's got to go
You can easily see how this is not really sensible but then again there is a possibility that the government could pass regular
Racing the manufacturers of these swords
Need to require some kind of Fail-Safe to make sure people are able
Duopa
Open them from the
The inside maybe that's
The conversation
Regardless if you assess this is a situation where the truck is the weapon the logic
End up sprawling it
The Banning things like
Escape rooms in bank vault
Yeah very bizarre
The notion that you're trying
You know honestly I kind of
I'm warming up
To the idea
Sure I pick if she want to stay rooms or later someone's going to die
It's a safety issue
Secondarily
These need to be Reggie
Authorities were able to locate the people who own
The truck by a simple check
Roblox
Any sort of
Effort towards furthering gun regulation is the Ulta
For Alex so that's not something that would ever be tolerated with.
Third there are cases of groups of migrants dying in trucks basically every day where is it
It seems like with mass shootings there are
Migrant deaths are unacceptably frequent but most of them are not in trucks like this
The reason why it's a
It's kind of leads to the larger issue and that is that
These people tragically dying in this trailer is not the result of someone having access to a trailer
It's a symptom of a bigger problem with witch
Stupid why someone would be in that trailer to begin with
Alex loves
Talk about how the border is white and how Biden
Just letting everyone in
Which really raises the question of why people would
Subject themselves
Was being smuggled in a super dangerous trailer
Putting themselves at this kind of risk if they could just walk right into the
Alex wants to make immigration more
Difficult and make border enforcement more cruel
Which will have the effect
Making people more open to using Desperate Measures to enter the country
It does makes tragedies like this one more likely to happen in the
The future
Similarly he wants there to be no gun regulation at all and wants everyone to be able to have all the guns they want which will have the effect of
Making people
More people like this shooter on Monday heavily-armed
Did able to keep carry out
Horrible Act
The future
The situations that Alex is trying to compare a hero
Analogous at all
Dinos
He just doesn't really have much of a leg to stand on in this
Situation so he's grasping at
Straz
His tragic
Situation to another horrific situation
That his policies
Hurst preferred policies
Time towards
Increasing
He can go f*** himself
Yeah I mean I just don't
No I I don't know if there is any reason to
To talk
I mean I don't know if there's any reason to have any arguments about guns
It's already everybody
Reset everything
We're just going to watch people die
And nobody's going to do anything
I get where you're coming from
But I think that kind of apathy
He is
Something you got to fight again
Because
You could end up
Stopping yourself from putting effort into things bitter that they could have a positive outcome
I mean
I think
Problems arise whenever it is some
Thing that no individual can any longer do any
Nothing about no individual can make a
Yeah no matter how much you organize what it
Requires is other people organizing another people organizing and so on
And it's it never never
Can end
Yeah I mean I think
I think
Tigger something to that in the in the sense that
Communal organization is important but
Still
Individuals can make differences even Within
The communal need for organization and is much as like
You know it seems
Assertive
I don't know dismissive to be like every dollar counts
Or whatever
It does
Realist
Sickly if
A lot of people
Throwing a dollar to something are absolutely
I don't know
I do I get where you're coming from I get what you're saying but it also I think I'm not being clear at all
And that's because I'm being incredibly cynical and
Run me I mean more
It is
Not
Valuable to discuss
Guns
It is valuable to
To discuss organization
That could be fair there's no point in arguing with anyone about how do guns Bluff
At no point is a math is done
I need to organize people and not talk
People with an
About that
I think that
That's something I could be more on board with I think that's a different point than you were making but I
Because I left out the part that actually makes sense
That's a good important part to add whenever your sense of usually powerful
So Alex really just kind of
Talk mostly about the Border
And what have you
I saw a headline
All yesterday
UN agency
List
Texas Mexico border as the most dangerous
Land Crossing in the world they give us at istics in fact
It's twice as dangerous as the next
Most dangerous
Border crossing
In Arizona
USA
Thousand-Year on both sides
Not even a radar blip
So Alex is actually talking about a correct headline here but he's making stuff
The International Organization for migration runs a project called The Missing migraine
Prince project that it seeks to quantify and record the number of deaths and disappearances there are among migrants around the world
They recently released their numbers are 2021 and the u.s. Mexico border was the most deadly and most dangerous
Border crossing in the world
Wake up call
And also seems to run counter to Alex's ideas about a wide-open border
Alex is making up the detective
Cuz Mexico border is the most dangerous in the arizona-mexico Border came in second
The organization didn't report numbers like that and this is just something Alex's to make him sound like he knows more about the
Tiffany actually does
Cuz he doesn't know.
He's also completely fabricating the tens of thousands
Number
This report with cheese
Exciting says
The fakir document
Quote 1238 deaths during migration in the Americas
In 2021
With at least 728 of those deaths
Occurring on
The US Mexico border
Far Cry 4
From 10,000
Yes yes
This is a really good
Cut-and-dry example of the way Alex report stories
There may be a kernel of something correct in that this report does
Exist but the details you selling the audio
Answer generally things but he's just making up to paint the picture he wants them to accept his real
Others
No a reason
Why and that's
Because you want to
To create this thing
That is
Over the
Top bad
What attention away from
The thing
That just happened that is
Traumatizing
People
And is threatening to your world tonight
Is obviously buddy
Thousands dead a year on both sides
Not even a radar blip
We have less than 150 people killed in shootings
6 killed in Illinois
21 killed in Uvalde
And the media will the hell out of it and their will
Moore capito
Highly suggestible individuals on soccer
Individual
The shooter
Bobby
YouTube channel
I watched all 26 videos on again
Talk about depressing and scary I sent links to my producers
7 a.m. this morning
What's on the big stream Lee hunting iWatch
Every one of them
He did animations about mass shooting in schools
Screaming in blood
He made music videos about the same thing he even got into the school
They went two years ago and shot a music video
Inside of it
So you can see here one of the main reasons that Alex tries to paint the picture that this report was saying the tens of thousands of people are dying a year
We're on the border on both sides because it's a way that he can minimize the impact of mass shootings
The reality is the mass shootings are bad and happened a lot and are such a problem that you have to lie about something else to make
Make them seem insignificant in comparison
You know it
It's kind of an interesting mirror image of all too often
End the conversation
On the
Is it Spectrum
Afghan rice
B or a political rights
Insofar as most people are like
Listen
There problems with the Democrats
We need to choose the lesser of two evils
Where is on the right
The strategy is ignore the lesser of two evils
You need to be
Be way more afraid of 10,000
People dying on the border
Ignore this lesser of two evils you know
Whatever that is I don't even know about that
You know it's a fascinating mirror
That's interesting
I was struck by Alex's insistence that he watched all of the guys videos as you were as well
He seems to really want him
Make clear which is weird that he watch them
I don't know why
Well if you say I watched all of them
Multiple times
Especially if you're Alex
Hideout
I also think I think I know what your video from a school that he's talking
I'm about
I don't think I was actually wasn't actually the school lockers on one side of the wall and then
The lockers are a door
I don't think this is a real classroom
I personally did not watch all of this guy's content with the amount of a lead me to the conclusion that
I was unprepared to make a conclusion about what was going on here
There may be a fair amount of content available from this guy but it may be awhile until there's any
Motivated him to do this
And I don't believe that watching a few YouTube videos
Which I don't even try
But Alex did
Would make anything
More clear
I don't trust Alex
Is assessment on this
I don't really trust
My own assessment
Because I don't really have a concrete one about
What this guy was
All about I mean from
All that I've learned
Just discovered what a Nazi
Cat-boy was
Was so go from the way late
To the party oh well
Congratulations and welcome
A really nice to not be there for a while
Just watch all of these videos
Now we have
At least 50 video gorilla van I watched over
Repeatedly
I should have
Call krunal download a man but it was 4th of July
Bastion before I finished
They did get some of the bad ones
I'm sure somebody
I really don't want to subject you to that
Launching
Music
Pretty pretty good beats
I hate you
I hate you so much
Deep in the bottom of my soul I want to
Hates it's really weird
I mean extra do you know what that echoes
Who's awesome
F****** Buckley
Now
It's a good pizza
Of the videos that good beats that Alex is talking about
That's very strange repeatedly
You trying to get out of that really don't know I did for clues that have man I don't know
My first thought is good he goes to a dark place but
Maybe posted my first thoughts go to dark places to eat
Maybe he just really really did like those because
You got to rise above
Do you see a lot of pee
People pointing a lot of things
The shooting and Alex doesn't want to do that
The left trying to blame the right wing
Probably trying to find the last one
On the Sky last night
Hours watching the sickening videos
The haunting videos
Music videos
Shark videos
Pieces
Most of them about shooting up schools
Tell you that
Just like all the other shootings
And it's 100% driven
Machine the mass shootings the media that being hyped up
So what was the other two hours
Spent four hours plus
2 hours was it 12 hours
I mean that was whenever he played
The Beats for his kids
Oh sure you want to give them
Kind of like a good
Basis for hip hop music and really kind of
What's the temperature appear above
The Fray and acting like he's critical of
Fingers but you have to understand his ideology
Exist in a certain way if you do
Florida State vs devils
He believes that the Democratic Party in the last as a whole or either knowingly working for Satan or has been tricked into work
For Satan
Or possibly somewhere possessed by literal.
Twenty says in the last
He's blaming the left
But doing so in a way where you can pretend that there's a larger point
To what he's saying
It's essentially an analog for most of his career attempting to appear to be above the left-right Paradigm when in reality
He's just a far-right extremists in his only complaint is about the right-wing is that he thinks that they're secretly part of the left
Yeah I mean
Well and the way
He treats
Oh the left is blaming the right in the right is blaming the left you can
Argue that but what he's really trying to say is that
The left
Is blaming the right because they're demonic monsters and the right
Needs
To calm it down for a little bit
They can't be blaming people just yet we got it
Listen I understand guys
Nice but right now is not
The time
Corvette
The the left is blaming the right
And the right who are blaming the laughter actually secretly also the lab
No one is where I am
Right
So this about 284 the shooting for now
This individual
Bobby cremins how is the definition
Also like to dress up
Adjust likely white supremacist shooter follow the same Mo in Buffalo New York
Constant Contact
With a retired
Federal
I will bet you my bottom
Dollar
Individual was under cultural massman
Control
Direct Control
I mean
Pretty easy back to it probably
Hello
It's impossible for him to prove anything
Yep
So like I said this is about it
He said his piece
He watched these videos
It's demonic
He's a weird dude who dresses up like in this bih
Probably mind control right with his bottom buck
But it's not going all the way in
This is a false flag is just saying that the kid was mind-controlled by the
The government's so it's not a false
Black
Probably mine controls for sure by the
The culture video games and music and what have you
Yeah and then the media covering mass shootings makes
Copycat
Effect and undermine control
Probably on psych meds MKUltra
So where we are
And then the rest of the show for a bit
Takes a different time
The most dangerous land in the world is the texas-mexico Border
Iran is involved in this later
I'll cover this coming up
Whole string of Texas counties and towns are going to declare an emergency of invasion
And total collapse and call for aid from the states
Federal government
Texas is in a total
And complete
Emergency
Holyshit
Wow
Yep
I mean you know it
Is
So unsurprising to go races
So quick
Boys a distraction technique
Pop this point in the episode I had high hopes
Yeah
I had some kind of hope that this is Alex reporting incorrectly
Somebody who was actually trying to declare immigration and invasion
So it's somebody who's going to try and
Declare immigration innovation
That sounds right
View imagine
Really f***** up
Pick up clear how f***** up it was until the interview at the end of the show actually happen
I don't even know if that's true anymore
You know now that my imagination includes that there is no bottom I really don't know if they can
Can surprise me with anything at this point
What if you walk in
Nuc
The Crawling chaos
As a thought
That would Shock Me
I mean I think that would have to write
Hotep might be the crawling chaos I can't remember
Sure sure but I'm fairly certain that it's a magically impossible for me to not feel fear around that
Yeah I guess so probably
Sewing
I'm going to cover this press conference about calling immigration and invasion
And today on the War Room 3 p.m. and they have the press conference
Owen Shroyer will be carrying
The Press
Conference live 3 p.m. central
Infowars.com show
Feed section
A band
. video
Hope you'll share it
Protections just calling for Aid
Listen to WhatsApp
Texas
Harold's the collapse
Are the United States in the design
Speaking of that
I want to talk to Lester Zoe very very clear with you right now
Wow
I told you three months ago
Save money by buying food then because food prices
I only
100 different types of high-quality nutritious food
Ready to ship you at the lowest price you're going to find
So I need to point out that Alex wasn't selling his emergency food buckets as way to save on grocery bills in the near future
Yeah I doubt that using all kinds of fear base sheet to sell this food
The sales pitch was awesome that your family was going to starve to death because there would be no food so you needed to buy this stuff
I was going to make some things
A bit more expensive
He said he would barbecue your ass that was why you were buying food because in 10 days
Alex himself would eat you or with covid there would only be Lone Survivor
There's nobody to man the grocery store
Stop the dollar is going to disappear in all of its value and then
You can't buy food in 15 days
He wasn't liked by storable food because milk is going to go up by a dollar and a half per gallon
Yeah
I don't know I find this disingenuous
So there was
A shooting
At a parade
Fourth of July parade
There were
Lot of people hurt
Here's how Alex
Going to spend some
Spend two segments
Right here
In my
This is mainstream government reports and mainstream news articles
Created synthetic aliens
Any plant or animal DNA but out of nanotech
Alright
So that's where that's where we're at we're going to complain
About immigration being an invasion and we're going to approve the scientists are inventing aliens
Wow
I really think this would make Infowars listeners change
The channel
I don't know I don't think they're looking for
I mean especially if there's
Mass shooting
I think they go they're looking for him to make up some conspiracies
Do agree
But I also think that maybe
Here
Is keenly aware that there's enough of an Internet economy for that that he doesn't
Neither need to do that
Entirely possible it might be a risk that he doesn't
Feel like he needs to make look big swings on these kinds of things come back
Tomorrow it makes him a little more interesting
To prove that aliens are being made by
Possible especially for people who want to pretend that mass shootings are no big deal I don't even know why we're talking
There is another reason he's doing this no guy that later
Nanobots
New
A multi-faceted thousand prong
Genomic
Cultural biomedical
But it's all been
And blueprinted
In WarGames
The Rockefeller Foundation by the Carnegie endowment
By the United Nations by John Hopkins and that's how we know all this
I didn't just say oh look these documents what's happening
Whole shows in in writing books and making films
I mean no exaggeration
And then I bought YouTube
1670 years ago
I was only around for another year-and-a-half after that
The last time I checked Google video
You had 80
Million views on
Thousand years left there killing knows we haven't posted man on video for free
If you don't watch it you're going to want to throw up in your mouth
Song quotes
Reparations
And then after that
8 9 10 11
There are hours of videos that we played here
Where I specifically read from operation lockstep Rockefeller Foundation
I specifically read from the UN document in stay
So you spent nine hours talking about how full of s*** endgame is and how most of the quotes Alex covers in that are actually fake
They're just from like memes
Some stuff
Watching it does make me want to throw up in my mouth though but mostly because of Alex is overwrought narration
Invoice
God it's embarrassing it's really really annoy
So Alex gets no respect for me for predictions he's made because he ignores all the millions of things that he's gotten
Totally wrong
If I predicted that every team was going to win the Superbowl I don't get to pretend that I'm some kind of a profit because I only
Acknowledge the one prediction that was correct well you bullshittin
So I mean
Also operation lockstep still isn't a real thing and Alex has never and will never recover the documents he bases his
Is conspiracies on in any detail because if
If you did so
Those conspiracies would collapse immediately
The only thing that's holding them together is the audience not realizing that the
Actual documents don't prove anything
And the actual basis for the conspiracy is just stuff Alex
Is making up something's better service political
And ideological world
Because of that flimsy Foundation Alex
Keep moving
And never spend time covering anything a death sentence
That would instantly reveal that there
He's no doubt
Anything that he's talking about
Destroy the illusion that he's created
Before the audience
Yeah
It would be a surprise and I think what would be really interesting about it if he
He did just come out and say I was making all of it up
Is how no one would believe
I honestly don't think
He thinks he's making me say there was a come-to-jesus moment 44
For this fella on the road to Damascus or whatever
And he's like listen I got to come clean
I don't think anybody would believe him I don't think he's messy
Sunseri to believing is b*******
Not anymore
No I don't
I don't think so and I bet
To some degree it wouldn't have mattered early
Yeah
Yeah it's a bummer
But damn probably true
How to spell right
That it's suspicious
It is kind of suspicious
Keep us off of the general internet
Absolutely
It's not the way jump set
Jones is one of them
That's how he knows this he's wisdom
Such a crutch and then that is so wrong because I want you
I know what I know
You can do read operation lockstep for 2011
You can read sparse 20-25 20:28
So this is exactly the kind of criticism valix that I hope to eradicate from people's by
This is the kind of criticism
But Alex is more than willing to bring up an address on his show
Reason is because in order for someone to be making this criticism of Alex already bought in
On the underlying premise that Alex has been right about every
In order to argue that he was secretly be a globalist or some kind of limited hangout or a Honeypot
You have to already accept Alex's framing of the world and by doing so you've lost any ability to actually make any mean
Leaving for critique
Of what he does
Alex is not right about things
He's a malicious liar who primarily just makes things up
The most work he does about the stories he covers is to skim a headline and then improvise an explanation for how that fits into his world
His understanding of the primary sources he relies on to build upset worldview is horrific
And none of the documents he uses for his points say
What he claims they do
Alex hasn't just been wrong about stuff
Is almost meaningless to quibble about rightness or wrongness because
Really the criticism of Alex that's most cutting is that
He's just making up most of the stuff you talk about
And none of it has
Any value to anyone in the audience
He's welcome to surprise me and actually address our criticisms of him on his show but mysteriously that never happened
He's going to do it
So weird for the pettiest man in the world to never bring up there's a podcast that's release 700 Appisodes of the past 5
Five years but he's a liar and a piece of s***
Response time pushing back into meaningless Anonymous criticism that
Even if the audience accepted it
Filippou's Alex
Genius
And his conspiracy worldview
So weird
I think it's an ironic
Point to say it
Suspicious that I'm right all the
Have you know cuz yeah
Yeah
Yeah it.
Not usually on my suspicions of somebody who's right all the time in the sense that it like
Oh you must have inside information
So much as I am like
You're probably making this up
That's why you're right all the time because you have control over what happens in this narrative
Yes of course you're right more than
Find address conspiracies about his conspiracy
It's still within the game I mean what's what's funny about it is that Hebrew
Breaks into the consciousness
Almost like what he's created a completely fictional world and sometimes it'll touch
The real world just the slightest little bit
And then people be like holyshit he's right
Pittsburgh world is in the real world you know
And it's just that it's just a tap
So really his pettiness
Next
It is
I want
Really stress out Patty he is
Because
What are you talkin about the scientist
Creating aliens
I don't do there's another reason he was covering this
Alright
Budget some really big news right now nowhere to take calls starting at
Bottom of the hour
For special guests joined this on the
Decoration emergency about to be made
Texas
Collapse
Interesting declaration
God works in mysterious ways
And what they make fun of me about today people discover Dimitri tomorrow
So
Is big news is that someone posted a little clip of him and was going around on Twitter
I was about him to clarinet dependents from the globalist and Evelyn
That's the big news is that he went viral on Twitter
That was not as good as Bill Pullman's but as good as some of the other ones
Declared its independence
She cleared a lot of Independence
Right
It's a shower I was thinking I was like
Him declaring his independence from the globalist
Is essentially like if you have a job
And you quit that job
Emerald alright
I guess you quit that job
And then like 2 months later you quit that job again
No not at all but I've had a lot of time to think about it
I've decided to quit it better this
I know I do I said I had a better the second time
Years later you're all old men just walking in going like
Now that was matching the job doesn't exist
The situation wherein with Alex declared as a dependent
I appreciate people who are late-to-the-party who like
Post clips of him declaring his independence demonberry share
Because
It is novel and its you know if you don't listen to show you don't know that he does this s*** all the time
Everybody likes a good Independence Day speech. So anyway
Yes he has had this video the people have been making
In front of and so he's going to spend
And two segments.
Talking about how aliens are being created by scientists
Because the video went around making fun of him you know there was a shooting at a Fourth of July parade
No
But that didn't happen
To him specifically of your time my guy
Buddy's time
Alex's kind of
Complaining about the
This video going around but
Is this is this I mean
Gleefully right like look at how to look at how much people are talking about me right
He did specifically for attachment
Just go viral ridiculous
It's on MSNBC it's on CNN it's on ABC
It's on Newsweek it wasn't
Alex Jones claims aliens want to make humans into cyborgs slaves the same
Walking into one of his advance and he's walking bipedally
All of his minions
To the VR goggles
Those are cyborg slaves St
Sounds right
People love that turn my coin but
It's a metaphor
What's happening
Okay there's a picture of Mark Zuckerberg in a bunch people as we are goggles on
Cool he's walking bipedal
You understand
Okay
So today when they took off the goggles and got up
No they had to stay down while Satan
Sure and then Satan left and then they could stand up
On the VR goggles where to Blind them
From Satan's beautiful ladies Lucifer obvious
The lightbringer
Aha
Solo
Alex plays of the clip of himself
And then
This is this is shocking
Because
If you listen to this carefully
He's essentially saying
I believe everything
In this clip
Literally
They took me out of contacts I believe all of this
Here is the
Forklift out of context
Ida Claire
This July 4th 2022
Let me a Declaration of Independence against the Alien Force
On this planet today Waging War against humans and our biology
And our very future that is attempting to exterminate the majority of us
And force-feed
Minorities is left
To merge with a I can
Computers and become
Cyborg slaves of Satan
3 days out of 7 days
Lithia Springs
Most of messages are anti-human
Ninja babies
All of this is to get you off balance and not standing up for what you are who you are
At the base of it is the transhuman
Play few minutes in contacts is I didn't go right into the top of alien I'm talking about
Sing I believe the Bible
Prediction the mark of the beast all this that it is a
Dimensional attack
AAA
Collaboration collaborator human
Places by the
Principalities this Earth
To build the advanced technology they need to that estate
Boys
I'm exposing Illuminati called
That's not why
I think he's saying that
They're making fun of me in this out of context
Text clip
So
I'm going to play the full clip and then they'll be convinced that I'm correct
Right
Yeah
Look I mean like
Reasons date like
You know you can play with something sticking out of context
Because that thing that is out of context does not
Accurately represent what it is that you're trying to just communicate but not only do I believe
Everything
Want you to know that it's crazier than you think
I want you to know that I believe
The demons
We're stranded here
You
Think you can make
Make fun of me
For me telling you only a small bit of the truth
Come on man
Come on man you don't eat
No has his one of his trademark
Sure of
Headlines
But he thinks proves his point
And it does not come out
Just less than a hill of beans
A few minutes on that I took it out of context
Real quick he did play his full clip
Independence Day
Flying Saucer is over
New York City blowing up
Show me show you an Eaton
Anybody watching some TV or anybody to radios and record this
You do look up every one of these articles and you can see it for yourself what I was talking about
Here's one
This is the main religion
Eclipse
Looking forward to the end of humanity
Covid-19 Shuttlesworth failed species must merge with machines
That's not too accurate depiction of that article at all
Is greater technology and health availability
Stuff like this
Eaton company
Inequality is going to be addressed
Certain things and maybe
This idea that we have
Of overcoming disease and
Some ideas about transhumanism
Maybe a lot of these ideas are actually not as good as some people
That's actually what the iPad is about but Alex
Might as well be about this before we just
Craving sugar nobody Alex loves the title though and it works for him and it's all that he remembers so horror
Yep
Then there's more
Nbcnews
James Lovelock says
Nbcnews I shouldn't be no more humans humans will be obsolete the future you will accept
From Human to cyborg are you willing to augment your body
Why the future doesn't need us wire
Cyborg thing is just this guy James Lovelock who
A guy was like
Yeah
It doesn't mean that cyborgs are going to replace
And then
Is that article from Wired Magazine but he lies about all the f****** time
He believes that it is just be the whole article is just the small Passage
Where are the author Bill Joy quotes
The Unabomber
That is what he has taken away from entire article
Yeah
Boo
You know I would
Wonder how Bill Joy feels knowing that
He was the mouthpiece for the plan of the globalist
Does he ever think
Wait
I think I might have been you
You know it I don't know who Alex Byram
Please do Alex Ybarra
Yet so there's another clip
Alien life-forms artificial genetic code
That's what I was talking about
So this is just an article from 2014 and it's not about a life form in the way Alex makes it seem
Researchers just a fused a modified E.coli with some lab-made nucleotides
It's and put in
We're able to
MoviePass down when the bacteria reproduce
That's really cool
And this is a clear example of Alex just having headlines that he likes to go back to because if it weren't
He wouldn't use this catchy headline and he would know that 2017 the same team had a
Further breakthrough where they quote
Announced that they're semi-synthetic strain of E coli is the first
They both contain the unnatural basis and its DNA and use the bases
Instruct cells to make a new Pro
Or he would know that last year there was another paper published about this ongoing research that's been headed up by doctor
Floyd
Romesburg
I also know anything about this story but the headline works for it so he just incorporates whatever he wanted his story
Basically always do
Yeah I mean
If you wanted to pull that story out and not be like all there's a newer alien life-form and more be like
Has anybody ever
Red
Any story where
People played God before just throwing this out here
Has anybody ever read a story where people played God before how did that turn out
They played God
What happened next I will get to that a couple a couple of citations down the road
But here here's the next one that Alex is misrepresenting
NASA watch Space Station
T
It's got dozens
Uplink
Systems on the space stations in zero gravity
So there's a story from last March about four strains of bacteria that were found on the International Space Station inside
Three of which were previously unknown
Science
NASA's most certainly not yawning about this because the idea that bacteria could survive in space Hazmat
Vacations in terms of being able to grow food in space
Which would be a
These are not newly-created life-forms and it's pretty well understood that these bacteria came from Earth
And we're introduced to the space station by way of a passenger or cargo
Research on them found that they were genetically and taxonomically similar to bacteria commonly found on rice
Put this in perspective so here's an expert who spoke to
The guardian
In every spoon of soil or stool sample there hundreds of undescribed microbial species
I'm sure they're still hundreds or even
Sons of less characterized
Maybe even unknown microorganisms
Aboard the ISS
It could be a game-changer in terms of space food
Could be something that's kind of interesting but not really that big
Whatever the case reality has no connection to what Alex is talking about here
This is nonsense
Right
Aliens
In zero gravity
Don't think
Can do that
Spy
I mean mainly linguist
Reasons
Place where reasonable people can disagree
If we're arguing
Look there's a lot of headlines that Alex Reid
Any number of them are kind of like I don't even know what this has to do with n
Anythink Wright
Right but there was one other one that I think is worth
Mentioning because I
Maybe it's closest he gets to anything that seems like
Huh
Alright
Okay maybe we're in messy territory
Wooden robot
The credit chain reaction
Chain Reaction hell yeah
Eating a real headline but it's not really accurate to the story
These robots can't reproduce
Per se
But they can Clump things together
So these are basically
Clumps of frog stem cells
Switch can respond to certain stimuli that researchers give
According to one scientist quote
At the moment they don't do much
We can get them to walk across the
Petri dish very very slowly or Swim through watery fluid very very slowly
There's nothing going on inside at there's no brain there's no digestive
However researchers have noted that they have a tendency to
To Clump things
Together when they were introduced into their petri dish and the idea came up to
To see if they would do that with other frog stem cells
The scientists added some new frogs that sells empty xenobots as they're called
Peed in fact
Text Club these cells together
Effectively creating a new xenobot
This is not what Alex is describing he's playing fast and loose with a headline but
I would maybe say that we shouldn't go too much further down this week
Hahaha you talk about that play God
Ticket happen
They're out to
I was reading an article about this
Beneficial outcomes
Stat that are kind of in
Christine about this
In terms of
Being able
No I deliver medicine places in your body that number of applications
Guys
Come on, read a book the most responsible scientists to be doing is listen we're not crazy
I'm sure they're not
Crazy
Who said we were crazy
This is where I
Kind of
Drop into Alex head
That place where reality and fiction
Yeah just a little bit just a little bit when you got frogs
Stem cells but somehow are pushing
Other frogs
Like that's to be like good guys this is fine now
Qualitrol I back you know I have dabbled in writing
And and you know
Maybe sometimes a lot of those books about people playing God or more about how the writer needs Mara detention
You know and I playing God and then everything being
Find us
Sounds like the narrative tension is like
What the f*** did we ever need God for
Let's find out how to kill that guy
Now you got some
Yeah I agree with you that if you're ever making a story and it involves playing God it has to go wrong
There is no reason backstory
Happily ever after short story
I loved it
So we get back to the shooting now because Alex has got a piece of news
Is that makes this able to
Recover right
Well they just had a press conference forget the video for you in the next hour
Highland Park Illinois
Shot and killed six people into another 60
Do photos and videos him dressed like a woman
Folks this
Yes
Mars Attacks
Actually aliens
It's a camouflage
Joan
Alien alien to humanity
The future alien
Everything we stand
This is legitimately nuts
This is the last segment of the second hour and Alex's done almost
0 coverage of the shooting
Happy Fourth of July parade
He's a giant deal and honestly it's essentially a meatball just right over the plate for him to cover
This is an attack on the founding of America
The target reveals the motive
Tommy's I can't handle
Did the Red White and Blue
This basically writes itself for him to the point where it's suspicious how little he's talking
I'm about it instead to spend a half an hour
Complaining about how someone tweeted out a video of him declaring independence from the Devil
But now Alex brings the shooting back up because he has a hook
He's heard of a way to make this a part of his transphobia so it
It's not quite so threatening for him to talk about it
He can always fall back on the meeting was boilerplate Minecon
Control psych meds type talking points
That only goes so far
Particularly in relation
Do an event like that
Has all of these other Dynamics
By making this about his abject hatred of trans people Alex more comfortably talk about this shooting
Because he can scapegoated vulnerable Community instead of dealing with the actual issues that underlie the
This tragedy
In reality it's believed that the shooter dressed as a woman
As a disguise to help him escape the scene
Particularly because he has
Notable facial and neck tattoos which
Could be covered up with a wig scarf and makeup
He was not dressed as a woman he was arrested as Alex
Proclaiming
This is just
Alex trying to turn this into a trance phobia narrative which you notice he also did
In the immediate aftermath of
Yeah yeah I saw that
I saw that one
That that one going around
And a couple of times
I really do believe if somebody said that to my face I would
Attack them
Like my my I was twitching
Listening to him talk
But I will viciously attack you if you say that to my phone
It's not enough fun
Nope
Before YouTube
Kaiser Dino
The New World Order Kool-Aid
110 percent
As well alright return your phone calls
Wow it's so weird how I look bring that up earlier when he's bragging about all the videos multiple times
I was just a vague accusation of demons and devils
But now that he's heard that cremo dressed as a woman to obscure his identity escaping this
I guess I remembered all those videos you totally watch
I know that this is a lie because I went to such an aggressive transfer but if he had watched videos where cremo was dressed as a woman
That would be the only thing he talked about for the first hour of the show we would have gotten a report that
Yeah yeah that would have been our special report imagine that it did probably would have if he had that hook
Earlier on
Yep it's
It's disgusting
Alex
Yeah it is clearly lying
Wendy says he watched all these videos you know that's a lie you already know this makes it even more of a lot
Compound lie on top of
I got one guy who's a weirdo
Thanks for all the products
Hi Steve.
I've got Alexa Breeze and all my rooms
And my wife
Tickets a little sapling that's not running so
Used to that now
Thanks for keeping us all there
I guess the one thing I want to bring up is
Have you ever heard of Jonathan kleck
No
San Antonio
And he's got a line on all this stuff
And I got to tell you he's really
Help me
I listen to you during the day and I listened to him at night
Quicker click
Collect
Jonathan kleck
Yahweh is giving a bell ringer
Do
He's got the
Is that the explanation for all this
Transgender
All this stuff
Alien
Pretty pretty
Bible fact
But he's not he's not one of these the end is coming
He's really well we got to make the end happen no he's the end is here
It's already it's already have
Before the fire
I watched a little bit of one of his videos
Mostly to figure out if this was him calling into Alta showed the same voice
But I didn't see him doing some really weird
Attempted linguistic breakdown of Bible verses
I also noticed that his YouTube videos have about like a hundred views on them so small audience
100 more time
Conceivably
It's from looking at his website that this is
Something good know that doesn't sound like
We better be super nice
Two people that doesn't sound right
So yeah we get another call and this guy wants to
Talk
National Mall
Hey John. I got three main points I want to make one about my route Mount Rushmore Trump
And Flack
Mount Rushmore
Radio cultural Warfare
W look at Mount Rushmore we have the founding fathers Jefferson so on so forth
You're right now putting up
Crazy Horse monument
Crazy Horse
Monument Lewis
Time in
Scalping
The 7th
Calvary you know when we fought in that region
It's a cultural war and then left is
Winning the culture War
If that's the cultural War that's being taught here then yeah this guy is making it pretty clear that his side is just in favor of a homogeneous
Play culture
I sure hope the other side is winning the culture War
Also Teddy Roosevelt and Lincoln are definitely not founding fathers
Forgotten Boardwalk
The Crazy Horse Memorial is not like a plan to destroy Mount Rushmore it's
Just another Monument nearby the people have been complaining about for decades
I went to Mount Rushmore when I was like
13 and I remember people complaining about the Crazy Horse Memorial then
They started working on it in 1948 and it's not even close to being done
And it's just this
Perfect Grist for the racist Mill
Yep they're just
Cannot
Stop complaining about this
It's a good indicator of
Whose socks
If you complain about the crazy horse motor maybe that's not true generally of somebody who wants to Finn
You should genocide
It's impressive that the heads are carved in Fairmount
You know Mount Rushmore
But I really want them exploded I really want that blown up I've been there
I mean what are we doing what are we doing
What I say that it's impressive I kind of mean that it was
Always ago technology was different back then they manage to do that
That's pretty cool that is
Physically impressive
Seat of
Again
Genocide
It is a
Part of the genocide
Bolton Roosevelt on there because he made national parks
Okay hold on now
This guy
As a story
Makes me sad
Hey Alex first-time caller Kelly appreciate what you do listen
12 years ago I was driving down the street
A block down the street and there was a mailbox
And it
Said it was an inside job and infowars.com
That's all it took
Everything you've done in the studio
Where work
Everyday
Batman
Put that sticker on that
Mailbox for a reason
And it woke me up
Took me 12 years
Trying to get the balls
To go down there and introduce myself
It's kind of weird
Situation
And
The neighbor it's not a city block
Long story short
Dr. sebi diet
On Thursday
And it was
Fourth of July weekend
I'm going to go down to introduce myself
Balls with down there banging on the door
The most old man thing I can
Probably ever stay in my life at 48 years old
Young girl answer the door I said hello is your dad
Today my name is Bill
I live down the street
And your mailbox woke me up 12 years ago and I want to thank you for that
And he lit up like it was the 4th of July
It was
It was Fourth of July weekend
It really was
God is like this ad
Man that is
There should be more
I was thinking about some of the Dynamics at play here and I think I would be kind of a
Afraid
Knock on the door too because I know he's
Supercar and probably a little bit suspicious of people
Little girl answer the door I'd be like Jesus Christ Don't Shoot Me
Cute little girl I'm cool yeah I'm just here to talk to your dad I got my hands over my head
Christ yeah sticker so no 12 years of my life has been stolen from me
I saw a sticker it blew my mind and now I put up with this nonsense how am I God
Yep I would love to just put another sticker over there
Alex Jones
Mayonnaise
If that story had ended with them kind of like
And we
When on a date
I mean if they did more than the guy the guy brings him some Infowars
T-shirts
And they're good friends they're happy now
Rear weirdos together and I guess
This will one day be a terrorist cell
That's a long it takes
So
We get
To this interview
But Alex has with this guy
Who is
They're trying to declare a Mexico border invasion
Okay
I'm interested in this
Because I think
There would be
Be unintended consequences if you do
Declared that Texas was fully under invasion
I would assume so so I'm interested to see where this goes
Man
I don't know if you are pretty late here's introduction
Houlihan is a great lawyer and a patriot
Who's been spearheading
County Citizens defending freedom
Will be covering an area that would shorten the war I'm coming out at 3 p.m. central
Genesis an incredible time right now
So in addition to being
Involved in this raises nonsense Jonathan Houlihan also recently was trying to run for the 8th District housing
Texas
Which he lost the GOP Primary for back in March
He came in third
So I guess he lost
Trying to stoke fear
I Am brand immigrants as Invaders because I guess he's
Think that's politic
Yeah I mean
What else would it be it wouldn't be some sort of like
Almost
Bland office
First job where you kind of put
Together an idea of what it is that
People generally have a
Taste for and then trying
Improve their lives
Addison and all of that stuff
So I I didn't know what to
Expect
From this
In terms of like what
Nails pretty
Ongoing for 4 months and months worth of organized
To declare an emergency
Retiring invasion
Enforce the Texas governor to act
Governor Abbott
Situation
Article Article 4
Section 7 as the commander-in-chief
Allows him to repel invasion
And under the Federal Constitution
Fattoush under the guarantee clause
Section 4
A free Funnel Vision and guarantee the Republic
That's not happening
So you also see the states have War
Douching
Content Clause 3
This legitimately
Seems like what he's
Suggesting is like a military repulsion believe that he suggested that
Texas.
Declare war on immigrants
We're going to pretend that that doesn't mean all of next
And
Mexican people living in Texas
Because here is the problem while there's a lot of problem there's so many problems
Everything he saying is a problem
But then when they
They get into talking about like
What is this look like
In concept
You really start to get the Japanese internment
No not that one
I'd also like to see the
The state of Texas enter into more
Contacts
Arizona
And then really
Security standpoint have the state with people act
For those that don't know this
The UN says most dangerous sport in the world
Totally collapse
U.s. garbage lost control by Design I mean it's on record
It's got to be. We can't just keep waiting for Washington
What do you think David should do in this emergency If he if he doesn't try
I think Abbott should
Do what Dwight D Eisenhower did in the 1950
And deploy
The entire Texas National Guard and entering a contacts with other states
And shut down the Border completely
Not to put too fine a point on this
And I'm very sorry to use this language but it over what was called operation wet back
They're ran from 1953 to 90
B54
And like the deportations of between 100,000
Two up to over a million people
Many of whom were US citizens of Mexico
It's a historic shame on our policy decisions as a country
This guy thinks that this is a good model for what we should be doing it's a really f***** up sign and it's indicative of
But what he actually walks
Yeah he doesn't want increased border stability or security
Deport masses of non-white
People
Howard Hughes Eisenhower for inspiration on this one what's your ex
Actually doing is using Andrew Jackson
A inspiration on this one
Well f*** it and you're actually using etc etc the
The point being
It is the trailer f***
It's and it's
Expulsion
Of indiscriminate people you've just deemed to not be American
Is a racist Witch Hunt
Scale kind of things that has ripples
Through generations generational wealth
Is disrupted and
No people are still feeling the effects
Pics of that fat Mass deportation
I even now 70 years later and he wants to do this again
F*** this dude
Alex
For being in any way sympathy and promoting it
Goddamn
I was going to say that's such a stain on our f******
King history
85% of history books pretend it never happened
Now it's probably doesn't know about it I believe it
I want more clip here and this is where I just said I hate all of these people there was a deeply traumatic
Mass shooting
That just happened that your
Giving short shrift to. Even really talking about except
A little bit later you're able
To turn it into part of your transphobic narratives
Really just new welfare
People be brainwashing
And I have a swim bothers me the most about is the smile on their face
I bet they know that there's a rule of laws broken down there's no consequence
A literally former Soros group
I can find few things
It's more distasteful than the idea that this guy
Running
Alex opening spearheading isn't kind of like in charge
He clarifies that he's not really
Like the one in charge sure he's clearly
Charged enough that he's the person who goes on it forwards talk about this so
That's something
Part of his motivation
Is he feels like immigrants are smiling at him because they're getting away with
Floating or flaunting their beating over the law
That's in your head my man
This is this is a product of your hatred of them
You need to
You need to do some
I'm looking in the mirror
Cuz this sucks
I just I mean
That's
That is such a penny capsulation of like
It's 2020
What are we doing
What is how is this possible
That
People are trapped
In the f****** Civil War
How is it possible that we're just
Said that there is so many people who are like
Oh because magic Sky God you can't control your life
Sing to me cuz they don't think they lost
Yeah man I got us
I'm glad that Monday's episode was fun
Because
There are few things that I can think of that are less fun than this
Yeah
Obviously it didn't come up as much
As you might've expected but our hearts
Go out everybody
In Highland Park
And yeah
A lot of people
Who live in Chicago have connections to Highland Park so
There's obviously is very close to home
Although it is
It is not Chicago proper
As we
Point out
Everybody who
News from suburbs
It it
Just just awful and
At the time they were recording this I don't feel like
And I really know enough
About it to really
Fully discuss it so on sublevels
It's maybe
A blessing that Alex doesn't talk about it that much
But what does talk about suck
Navel gazing about how he went viral
Nonsense about his
Ideas about alien life forms
And then some of the most
Troubling
Commentary
About immigration I've heard on his show
You know I think
Something that's really scary about that is the way that
His
Stuff is
Treated as pseudo mainstream to
Folks like Tucker
I'm like
Whereas
Maybe in the past you could look at some of the stuff you saying
It's insulated to this
It's not
So much of that anymore
And
The ability
For this
To pick
Piggyback from Alex
To some other platform
To get behind this idea of declaring an invasion
Or something
Like it's really really scary
And I don't like what
If
Trump announces his candidacy in 2016 on the
Unjust
Hey might as well have been like Eisenhower was
My greatest idea for the borders
Hey that's I'm not mean we forgot about that
Declare on the
No that's truly there TJ
Flexibility
He doesn't know why not
I don't know but it was his big scoop
He was so excited it was a
Exclusive it was so exclusive it didn't happen
It's so exclusive Trump didn't know nobody told him
Yeah
So we will be back
On Friday
Indeed with something
Hopefully
Better
Well
We are also on Twitter
We aren't understand Alexandra provide negative Jordan will be back but until then
Clerk I hope you all have a wonderful day