Hey guys this is Jordan
I'm glad that Dan is holding down the fort while I'm not there
I'm just so you know
Over here and London
And they do not know who Alex Jones is
And so we are all living a better life
Holding
Galaxy color with your trip and I love your work
If you heard my partner
Here is in London he's on a work keishin
As the Alex Jones
Very funny man I think I called you
And informed
Over over text messages earlier today
Hello that you were having
Comedian extraordinaire Storyteller fungi
I want to I want to welcome you in
Two occupied Illinois
Behind Enemy Lines
Much like Jordan know almost nothing about Alex Jones
His existence
And that there is now a podcast about him
Podcast about her but only one by one of your friends
That's true
That's what I understand
You know what other
People
Chicago
So he's either rail
He definitely is
Over the course of the last
Two weeks or so
We've experienced
Do a lot of
Special Report
Weave weave
We did that for one episode
We covered his wife 2K episode
Why do you not get radiation just happened now finally
He's back in studio and everything
When is
Back to perfectly normal crazy
Awesome s***
A lot to talk about
Because even
The normal
Reporting some
Insane
His reaction
He's got to go one step further than everybody else
What's the Baseline becomes nut
You've got to go super not covering
Federal do is one day in the life of Alex
But because
You know
Davis Kind of Blue
This is a January 23rd and 24th
Eclipse will come from those two episodes
You know this is after the inauguration
This is after the women's March
We are at this point if not heard what Alex thinks about the women's May
If you have any predictions
Actually you know what
This
I appreciate that Alex give the globalist
We'll explore that throughout the course of his entire show
Vista it's this idea that there's a bunch of really rich people behind the scenes were trying to turn the world into a one
One World Government
It's New World Order s*** Illuminati's hits all buckled up within that
But it have to do with
Yo using um
Make a world government and then everybody's slaves across the entire Prison Planet
The new Hunger Games
Ritek
He can't
As you'll see by his use of diction
You could not sit down and read Cohan
Thoughts about what to experience
But it with an open heart open mocking much like you with this podcast
So here is a his first thoughts
Play the gentleman I want
Also he has bizarre intro music
Bold choices
Woody's coming in and out of commercials it's insanity
So that's
The James Bond style
We've got a
Demoralized washed servile
Worshippers
Just live such bizarre domesticated week live
Alive
Basically
I was looking at look like
Young-old you name it
During the Trump inauguration
Weird wimpy dies
We know exactly what's going on here people don't want to talk to him
Twist whatever I say
We know what this guy's up to
Can you believe he's left his apartment it's like what you see the campus preacher
College
College proselytizer
Brothers
Brother
No good is going to come up getting involved here
Experience something else
There is also a huge lie
Women
Trump supporters
People
What is Portuguese
Ahead
They think they're really cool
So Alex is really worked up about race
Stewart takeaways from
They don't want
Trump
But you said they were at the inauguration
Yeah but there's like protest
And stuff like that
Outside is narrative
People
In general I'm not making linear
At all
Are scared of Alex
Leader of the pack
Flexible
I want to f****** but who is to dangerous
There were only attractive women at the end
Inauguration protest marches
They're all
Fat
Ugly
I don't know I saw a lot of pictures of the marches I wasn't able to make it out to the one in Chicago over the weekend
Vibrant happy people
Yes very energetic
Play all look like George Soros
Actually was paying them they were that happy
It was crazy and take away from that like people who have debt
That racial part
Is
Gorgeous
It's better if it's kind of a rhetorical strategy in a lot of people do it
Kind of accidentally say something f***** up
You better go harder at
Aroused
Right
I think Alex does that to process
My sergeant
Is that why would I say that
Bad about him in the negative about me
But then the opposite of that is when he's like I'm not saying nothing about women wanted to f****** to brag
So here's what you should know
On the last episode covering his response
The inauguration
He posted one clip where he interviewed and Incredibly well-dressed black guy
And I'm sure that's who he's talking
I think that is because of how he starts this next clip
He references the other person
He talked to in that clip
Okay so I am certain
You really only talk
Do those two people
The most eloquent smart
Refocus people I've ever seen
Hillary supporters
They were lost puppy should totally freaked out
Control
Out of their minds
So
We can take from that is the Indian do than talk to you in that other clip
He references the same
It's insane like his references
Are the specific only people to talk to
Generalize it as a big crowd
Right of like all the Indians that were there
He talked
Hillary supporters
Who used to be fans of his ex.
It's the same thing with the woman wanting to f*** him thing
You don't either was nobody who was like I want to like you but your races now I used to love
So again these deranged white people are leaving dumb black people into dangerous
It's this it's that same like real
Pointing finger harder at wife
People he doesn't realize really what he say
Write down some
I took a note it says whacked-out does not equal
Refused
Will get there on drugs probably
The wife's not white people
Liberal drug use
Using lsd-like coffee generate in whatever way
You know that can be like a umbrella where your brain just fills in the gap
Whatever you want
It's also interesting we go from
There's power in their eyes to the confused
Hillary people
Confused white people whacked out
Trump supporters
More articulate than Alex Jones
Here's some more thoughts about the the Trump crowd though
You know what he said Chinese and Japanese he had to resisting dirty knees
Guarantee there's a part of the back of his mind is like
Don't they look at the
Right back
It was amazing
Weakness
And the enemy
And now this
Wow
We did all that now
First of all
Document
Debunked
The books are all of the ideas about like a huge
Global cabal come from
Exist
And for centuries they've been poisoning the water
And doing all these bees crazy things to us
Like
Trump becoming president
If there's this big evil organization
But if you're feeling right now
I appreciate I suppose his attempt at being woke
He's really he's going above and beyond
That there is diversity and the audience as
I thought for a second
Do you know this
Prism she was I guess he was just going to stop
Chinese like all Asian
They're going to need an
On Facebook
That is exactly what my thesis has been coming to about the existence of Infowars
It's not much news it's not so much entertainment
It's to teach you how to argue poorly
For indefensible position
Yeah that's already kind of
Where I've been
O'Reilly's
It should tip you off to this is how f****** repetitive
We are going to hear every single time
Yeah but almost everything separately crazy yelling stuff you repeat
Like 10 times
How long is the show
They are four hours with commercials
Everyday
Thankfully most of the time is spent selling weird stuff on it
Sounds like colloidal silver and iodine
Super male Vitality pills
Call Skip the people
Poison them
Oh yeah the Illuminati wants to poison a take these pills the FDA hasn't looked at
So actually I was thinking about this and I was like why you know
Why would
These Elites be afraid of trump
And I realize now actually I have an answer
Got the big break before he walked out because I said the president
The president
Information
Trump walks out Trump goes in like this for the Raven comes out
Long-term Eugenics program
There's a species wind program going on and
And the Donald Trump is going to know what I've reverse-engineered
And more
Look at his face when he talks about
Unlock the secrets of the universe
Unlock
The secret skin disease and illness Morgan eradicated
And you can see
He looks like he's about to break down he's got a ride
Because now he knows
That's one Theory
Another theory he looks like he's about to break down because he's f****** out of shape as hell and 70
Plus years old
He's the oldest
Like third fattest
Grover Cleveland
Was also
Who does the global Eugenics program that's been going on
And Alex has reversed engineered all this stuff
From sources
Moment you realize
The reality up till now is all been a big joke
Existence of matter
Now what
Insight
It's great but
Yes
Do you believe there
Is a global Eugenics program going on
Run by the US government
In concert with the Illuminati
You getting turned on to some important
We're going out for your break
This next clip that we play is offensively
But it's also delightful because
Alex Jones
Stock
It's a fake crying
You fix crying
A lot
And he doesn't miss CLEP
Almighty man
My soul cries out for them
He's talking about the protest
Okay so he's feeling bad
No no
Hands over his face when like
But still is trying
I'm sure he's not taking
I think you might want to
It's hammy at back at least level
Call myself you're saying
Help you
Because
Controller
I want to be clear I didn't contact
Someone who listen to tons of Alex Jones
I would assume you be asking me what is he talking about
And I can't answer
I don't really know we don't we don't have
Previous contacts
This group
High IQ
Half zombie half
Jihadist protesters
The Christian Heaven Christian God are real but they have defied
Worshipping a false religion
Everyone else in danger
I'm really glad to like really parts that out because I couldn't I could not have
Express that better
Perfect
That's exactly
All I took away from it was
There's no way anyone jumped out at you
Yeah
Is she saying he was at the women's March
I mean he was therefore I guess a short. Of time to get the fly back
Austin
On Saturday morning occupied Texas
Booty calls
That's a that's a blue City
Yeah it is
Because
There's a part of me that doesn't think that he's really since
You know what I mean
And Austin's a really Kick-Ass place to live
Does a Cool vibe
You're full of s***
Good place to live
Yeah I guess so
Queso
You know what he's lost a lot of weight taking his supplements
Oh really
Taking the
Will cudna as you get older starts
Takoma Park
The double-helix starts to something like that
The way that they've explained it is you know how your shoelaces little camp on it
The aglet of your DNA starts to come off it starts with light off
I'm in much like your shoelace coming apart your DNA starts
Are pills in order to keep the aglet strong
Who knows how much longer you could live
Probably way longer than you would have before
Make sense
Mason
Bottles of the special pills that keep the wax tip of my DNA held together
U-Save Auto ships
He'll just keep coming to you
Nootropic
To be fair
Nootropics that sounds like the name
Aldous Huxley novel
311 album
On the last episode we did a lot of research
Didn't do a ton of research
But we figured out a pretty good theory
That Alex
Was drunk
Over inauguration
There were a bunch
Videos
Let's see what I we hang out with some drunk people
You know how we've been some drunk people know.
But they give off and he was giving off all these
There's no doubt it wasn't the last episode
It's at the end of the episode
Dead to rights
We also talked about how he got thrown out of the inaugural
Because I watched people escorting him out of the
The crowd boy now
Obama
Defend women I saw being bloody
One of his narratives about the inauguration is that these socialist jihadist
Control
Whatever the all these people were beating up old women
Old women
Specifically
Okay and there's a there's a
Like a picture up on infowars.com
Illustrates
And the lady was a cut on her thumb
Right here she's a little tiny cut
That's sir
You know like people are being bloody expect like
Bastian head price
Latest not that
Anyway
Like my cat
Section multiple newspapers
Podcast
Months ago in July last year
And then added I was drunk
And the police were escorting me up
No no no I wasn't just drunk
It was a beanstalk from Austin
All the way over there and I came off a magic beanstalk
So did you get what you did there
No
He tried to defend
How silly the news that he was drunk was
By comparing it to a story that no one wrote
That he had traveled by Beats
Scott so crazy
Another clip of Alex drunk
In DC over inauguration weekend
This comes from a 5 minute video of Alex walking around the streets
Just with a microphone
Last like 3 minutes of it as him giving a limp
Handshakes
Like supporters and fans
Just like dudes coming up and be like can I get a picture and it is like
Who's doing the
Play Rob.
One of the employees of infowars.com
RV places
Shoot now
Issue
Butts
Lyft
Is some
Drunk
Rambling
I think you'll enjoy this
Watch the program
Transmission
Doesn't make you a lion or a tiger
That's a drunk dude
Oh yeah that's for sure I dropped guy
He's wrong
The new Atlantis
It's like it's not a Francis Bacon book
Philosopher wrote about how America
Like we back at me like early days it was
The conceived that America was the new Atlanta
Because everything was going to be like technological in advance
Like
Come on man
He's slurring his words
Shadow is Scientologist
Our ancestors living
Star system
And getting Transmissions from God
You are assholes your guide
You got a message
You're not a lion
On the street
Is about Free Speech issues
She's like you have liquor on your breath
Sweet cakes
Kate
Yeah it's pretty
Because he was
The jury has decided on
I'm not sure if you got kicked out of somewhere for his safety
But
It really looked like he wasn't
Going
From the clip I saw
Easy brings this up
Take a note of somewhere
Like it's a Mario because the communist
Attack
Butts
Hundred percent
Inauguration
And
Alex backman Studio like
He is risen
He is now at this point he's introduced his thesis that he comes back to over and over again the idea of these protesters were weirdo
People are great
But along the way
With his his verbal jazz style
You've got to throw in some other weird s***
About gender roles
The news here
Brock
It begins Brock far left
Plan Trump impeachment
Administration
I'm going to shut up
Shuffling man is a good man
Is there anything all that
That's right
The globalist want to end
You know I got to go to them
On this point
Men are not happy
There was that one guy but that
Junior
Seahorse
You know that
So one of the other things I think is interesting about this clip it's important to point out is you can tell who
Listen to Infowars by words that are being used
So like
Put out a tweet
That called the inauguration historical
Instead of historic
Right and that is Alex Jones does at least five times
The show he says business historical
Which is the incorrect use of the
Yep
I don't remember the exact form
Adjectives
The adverb adverb
Sounds right
Doesn't work in the account
Text Betsy Davis
You you would not misuse that word like that is a very weird word to misuse
Yes it is deliberately an off-day
Yeah and in this case this is another one that Alex does is groveling
I'd like to be there girlfriend
The p**** man
Not something
Not really you don't have a direct object
Your Bravo
Haha but
ABC News
He says that reporters are groveling
When they're backpedaling
Because groveling to be established
It's not proof positive but it's a pretty good indication that Alex isn't lying when he says
Metropolis
So
Enjoy look forward to
Cuz Trump's uses
Language is
And pretty sparse
Huge words
Terrific
Good just got to have that
Throw it in there
So
Another part of the
And Alex make a very weird
Admission
In this clip
That I'm not sure he knows
I'm not I'm not positive
Exactly
He also has
Ashley Beckford Lee Ann McAdoo
Reporters in this conversation
He's brought them in studio now because he has to talk about like women
Springs in
This is a business about abortion
At this point
To talk about abortion
Porter's the women
Infowars employees
Right
A hundred percent
This is interesting
Because this is more than
Washington
That panel is like tonight and one lady
Speak up
Like alternative
Saddened
TV props Minnesota propaganda
The Facebook
We have to
I agree
And also
We need to say that for us but they do
I will say
People who are involved in Infowars
Lee Ann McAdoo is incredibly attractive to me
And it's a troublesome
And waterways
Please do and then Ashley Beckford
She could be doing legitimate work elsewhere
She's pretty talented and like a decent reporter
But is doing this
I assume for a job
I'm not entirely sure she seems to have some chop
But anyway
And that's what plant
By basically
Was
Women and kids
Stranger
You know for the distributor woman which is beyond but we don't have to worship the baby I'm not judging by the
National worship
Yeah yeah you have your
Your jaw is on the floor is that from looking at or what we just heard
The ladder
What
What we talking about
To gorgeous woman
Very good-looking late
Is great
Pretty fun
Yeah and they didn't they seem to
Bad a verbal I added
No please
In the video you can see them sort of look
Are you stalking
I'm sure he's very sexy
That's multiple abortions
Yeah boy
Yeah
To be someone who is
Crazy anti-choice
Yeah and then to like
Admit flippantly
Yeah you're kind of a f****** hypocrite
Entirely and I'm sure it was not
I'm sure it was not a cool help a
I'm sure it was more like
You're getting
I would assume based on his understanding
Which is
Mommy's not going to have a baby
I mean
Buddhist will be
Be showing on this
This is something I've said for a long time
2 mi
Christian friends
Trump
Single-issue voters
Yeah
Space force
It's probably been
I don't remember the exact quote Vietnam
Was like his personal Vietnam
Dog and everybody not raw dog so before the 80s he was
F****** getting it in
On
Rap
Wow
Hansa
Like
What's the date
Probably tons of s***
Just going on
Explain everything that's going on
Right he's cuz it isn't crazy stuff
If you don't
Just like you the most
Healthy individual
National weather looking like
Looking like some old hippie doctor
Do you know
How do we know that
A real badass
But the question that we all got an
Well one way we can tell is how do other people
Who are badasses interact with him
Okay
Alex hasn't talked about it
So just wait
And their lives are better
Which prison for beating people to death
Promoters
Love Donald Trump
I'm respecting
At this point
Ashley and LeAnn are both looking at Trump at The Alex Jones
What are you talkin about
At this point they have gone
Confused
Like what
Why are you
First of all Duncan
There was murder
Used to collect on a gambling debt and beat a guy to death
So
You know maybe it's manslaughter
You the bad dude
You right yeah
Where's a lot of flag shirt
I think Alex might be taking the wrong lesson
Do you think you know
Even if you have me on
Michelle but I think you might be right
I appreciate that
Also Alex has more thoughts
I'm telling you he's just
Enfamil
To be fair at the end I was like nah
Insinuation
Good enough
That's good enough for marketing
Yeah he's a vital man and
Who's the black guy runs over white dudes
Yeah I like having have to come back to race
I don't think so
I don't know
It would be inappropriate for me to say that
And I don't think that the evidence really necessarily bears that out
But I think he's beholding
The song racist lies
But he doesn't realize that
But he believes
But he's kind of big on the idea of white genocide
Basically
Okay
Subway
This does come up on the program some
And it's interesting that he
He equates why
Takeout
And murder a guy
Mixpak
CR80 years old and Incredibly insane
Trump standing
Next really looking at anything in particular
I don't want to make fun of the old
For like being old
Right batty levels of old
They're really with it
You take the
Infowarsstore.com
Love it
This point we're onto the next
They we are now on the 24th
And Alex's
Material a lot of stuff that we didn't cover his reputation
There's just a lot of saying the same thing
Over and over again
Fuller more robust lies about what happened at the inauguration
Capitol Police
Do not let
People let the protesters beat people up
So first of all he saying that Obama
Relinquished power at noon
I put someone in place who wasn't going
To defend the public
And
He was going to make it so people couldn't get in
And that is why that one picture looks like there's nobody there at the inauguration
Because there was millions of people waiting to get in
On the perimeter
Yeah yeah yeah
But good because they needed to Stage that photo op
Insane
Like Obama lock credits
I mean
Bushel
But it's not Obama globalist
Sure the globalist at the George soros's of the world we're actually doing all this stuff
Obama just gets credit
A figurehead
What do they do I have H
I'm women being beaten up and attacked and then blocking us from trying to get into
Inferences
Here's how I know that that's not true
They post everything on infowars.com
If they have hours of footage of people beating up old women at the inauguration
Hotel room right now
Bulshit
F*** you
Try to travel miles
And guess
People trying to block the entrance
A report on this
Everything from MSNBC
CVS
Running what stories
And they show video
Photo
Complete
Is it true what do you mean
Specifically that was Alex Jones
I want a hundred percent don't give a fuk
The only things that he put up where like blogs
Show any proof of the New York Times reported on it
Which I can't imagine them caring
No
It has a real like
Victim mentality about a lot of stuff
While accusing Democrats of being like
You guys are all just you know your victims
System you're willing victims
Do you think
Cabal
Stopping you from doing everything right
I don't care if
News sources
Looks like they did
I don't care
Isn't bad reporting
I saw the video about being thrown out of
Where did you find the videos you too on YouTube
And like I said if they're saying
Is there if they didn't do any Research into the circumstances reporting
I guarantee he was drunk
Drunk
Heck
And so like him being like I wasn't thrown out and they want to stay on drunk
Come on man
Give it up just
It's fine right no one cares
Only care that you're tonight
So here we go
22nd 2017 2016
Caption what a bunch of communist
Call lawyer call me
As I'm walking towards it there's bleeding
Facebook
A game of the knuckles
We get there at 9
The police
Nope
I love that
New build a house of Lies
Can you imagine being his lawyer
Do you think that his lawyer is as crazy as he is
Christ I can't believe
This is what I do
I think it's either the most professional person in the world
Very unwell
Possible
The Trump's doctor of lawyers
It's a it's like I'm not funny
Better Call Saul
Simpson
Solar from
I just keep picking his name
Dewey cheatem & Howe
The law firm of Dewey cheatem & Howe
Go on a little bit longer in the end this
Segments of lying
But sounds right
This
You're going to love what when what happens happen
Here
Trademark
Transition
What's going to happen I love I love like a catchphrase
The trademark
Is it beautiful
Women start coming by the first one
KK cuz people are
Self-hating
Free government
Created
By Design
Globalism
Iceberg in the freezing water
Your condition morons
Rid of Obamacare
Sprint
I need to raise money tomorrow
You like that switch there
Switch
Screaming about nonsense
That is not edited at all
Single clip that is
Awesome
Traffic like
Racial
I don't want to call
Tubing like you are all in a brain-controlled cult
I meant getting into this this fun
Because you're in this call you can't admit when you're wrong
I think he's talking about himself
Eminem
For like a charcoal drawing of Donald Trump
Is that what that is
It's so great how he does he's really in passion of yelling
Picture
Just please like
I'm going to get my points out scream about him
Also we got these new pills
You're giving up the Game Malik
There are people who don't like you
You're making it so easy
Right
It's kind of like
If he runs out of steam he's got his thing in his back pocket
Just got to sell this
We've got these second pictures of trump so we got to do this thing
I need money
Brokers
I would love someone I'd love people to donate to my patreon
If you'd like to go ahead put your patreon
Patreon.com freezing point
But I'm not going to
Throw it in everywhere
I think I actually just did what's it
I'm not trying to
Plug you slightly what is the patreon for
Just giving me money
Yourself your rent
Show me pictures of
Don't know Tyler is drawn before the election
Drawing of
Understandable
Portraits
Yeah they're great
Okay alright good Breaking Point free bampos bomb world
Tell me what's made was it during his first or second term
Living in the world today a little bit worse
I was that Carlin's hardcore history
Came out with a new episode
Exercising Astoria need to study these really long awesome well-researched
Podcast about things in history is about
Do you like sort of creation of
Nuclear and atomic weapons
Appropriate and dark right now
I'm listening to it just made me really bummed out
Okay
So
If you want to go and do that but if you don't want to be bummed out
Alex
He ran into somebody
Who he has said some really f****** horrible things
I don't even I didn't remember all the specifics
Is Dad of being involved in killing JFK
I was so busy with all the news that
We play it right now
I was leaving Saturday in d.c.
I was waiting for a bus
Look
Come out
Cruise lives there
Ted Cruz coming out of the dark hallway cuz the lights were off down there for some reason
I always make the joke that you like
Interesting interesting is that you look like an undead
Creep
It's a lot of great things I mentioned that the short interview
Route to Colorado
Landslide
He says he believes Trump is part of the new era
I just goes on from there
It's boring interview
They cornered him in an elevator
This interview is taking an elevator
It's insane to see how sad Ted Cruz's faces
But he does not want to be in that elevator
Oh yeah I bet
It's like Alex Jones always impressed by celebrities and doesn't care about insiders and
Stuff like that she looks like a kid on Christmas
Like he was so excited the Ted Cruz was there at the end of the interview he's even like
Bill got a billion listeners now
Real quick
Levels of impression
The program
Is way more than Glenn Beck
Reasonable
I hate so many different
People
I have
100 cans of soup in
Tree.com
My daughter's hate me
They won't kiss me
The boys of Sky Sandwich Works
Izakaya
Government over something people wanted
Never support Trump after he
You f****** really went after my wife real hard
And my dad
Both bucket cutout
Supported Trump and yet I know I can't
I called called Fort Rob
There are pictures of me with the saddest
Puppet look at my face
I can't get the stink of this guy on me
This packet iPhone elevator interview
Can you tell what kind of iPhone by Anita
Cuz I feel like
5S
Any of the sectors I'm working with
Okay that's good
Technology very well I'm real
The time
Only felt like an iPhone like
2 years ago
Oh yeah
What is podcast
More advanced
Are there podcasting friends
No it's something that Alex takes seriously
Tell me
Sex
Here is where we get to what I would describe as the fun part of the show
I can't wait it's been fun so far but if we're just now.
3 clips
Are cuckoo bananas
So if everything else up to this point
Has been
Reasonably sane
Yep
Succubus
Go to Alex's thoughts about like
O'Gorman even sure how to
Explain what this is but
Enjoy
About the fact that I always thought people were good like I was
Perfect
I'm a very worldly person when it comes to
And I'll let you say I'm certainly not gay
But the point is when I mean
The point is
And
God's creation
These people are crazy ladies and gentlemen
Remind
What would you want to try and parts that one
Which people are supposed to know that already
What's the central theme of most of the show that gay people are out to get you
Yep
The gay people are crazy
And
They might be crazy because they don't
Beauty
Donut world
I like how he has to say three times in there
Decorations of feminine
Yeah
Roundabout way of saying
You like women
Instead of just being like
Cut and dry
You can just say that
You're not gay
Is not an attack on gays
Truth like if I say I'm not gay
I don't
Nothing wrong with gay
Seinfeld episode
3 years ago
We took care of that ideas
This clip is a little bit longer
It is
Absolutely
It's
So
Strange
The thought process makes no sense
There's a
A bodily function
That is
Bizarre
He doesn't pray
I mean
I just can't believe we're facing this lovely a lot
Little bit longer so
Destroyed
And that's it they're people like to neglect this mental illness
So make me
Dog style haircuts
Haircuts
Brock go out on the street
Ground and tell those women that it was pumpkin pie
Do you think he was trying to do with Bernie Mac there
Gross
They're disgusting
Little scumbags like this
Tots for so long I mean there's a global overthrow of
Overthrow you
And you think you and your minions all your people and
You think you
Can talk about doing violence does get away with it you got another thing coming
I just know how either works
Their spiritual spider webs
I think you have some big wires
Realize that Alex Jones is a religious zealot
Really weird way
From the last episode we found out that he believes that everything is energy
Not totally in line with Christian teachings
I want this girl who believe
Everything was crystals
No she might now at the time crystals aren't really big
Okay
Okay is this in Springfield
Okay kind of goes along with an ostracism a little bit another is sort of
Influence I don't know what brand of Christianity everything is energy I'm going to be honest I think
Very bad
This for very long time
I think a little bit
Fanfiction the spiritual spider web
That's not in Deuteronomy
The book of Jones
That's right so this clip is not nearly.
The craziest part is yet
I think the left hit some big wires
And some big spiritual things you have coming up
Just released that
Door over there
Amador
Outcomes
What you're looking for
What do I put peace out there
Obama and Michelle
Walmart for you friend and Madonna
Please smugly preening well he says that cuz he's obviously like
I don't mean
Is it
You like the first sure I wish peace and long life for
Obama and Michelle
He's gone on long tirade about how you believe that
Michelle is a man
No the first tranny and stuff like that like
Are you f****** serious not kidding at all it's it's horribly called her Michael sometime
Incredibly offensive
Yeah that is but I wish them the best when I'm trying to make a false point
About my my honor or my integrity
So
Again I'm sure Alex Jones fans have got a short memory
Very
Crazy
Studio
Okay
Brock at Hillary and Obama
Who's David Brock Brock is the guy who runs Media Matters
For America
Watch Dogs
Mixed martial arts
America
Then Alex is mine
Do they take money from George Soros and the open society and stuff like that
As part of the globalist network David Brock
Is
The global.
Funneling money
Do the priests like the propaganda arm or whatever
I think David Brock's got a lot of issues but Media Matters is generally a very well research
Site that
Not all they do is watch Fox News
Watch Glenn Beck watch
Alex Jones and debunk Tumblr
Stuff that they say
And of course I picked
Anything whatsoever
Also fun little tidbit
David Brock
Ex-boyfriend is the guy who owns
Comet Ping Pong
What is the center of pizzagate
So nice little fun connection there
Spiritual spider webs
Spiderwebs
He's got no doubt
Tragic Kingdom
Does a girl in the world map
So here we go this is where you start spraying
Father
I'll also keep
They're fighting good
Apologizing
Such a spectacle
We should pray for their slaves
Earlier
Collector collector piss
What's the stop all that
It's so fascinating to be where he catches himself to clarify stuff
Are we leaving the CIA
You have to clarify that but he doesn't want to walk back like
No not all crazy people leave their crap
Oh man I love that Federer
Play following a prayer
Within a prayer
He never said amen
All that yelling at prayer
God
Also also I like that he's trying to mansplain to God
About to how evil other people are
Yeah the guy doesn't mean that he knows
Yeah I got nose
Eagle
So I don't know man I think I'm evil I don't
Ebony fast
32 points in his next clip you'll probably hear it too
They like to keep their crap
Keep their path
Like
You could hear in the clip
A blurt laugh from
Cuz as I was isolating the clips
I just lost
Craigslist
History happening at the eclipse
I laughed
So hard hearing it for like the third time
Incredibly offensive
Said that he's really good at doing impressions
And that his kid loves it when he does a Cookie Monster impression
BookIt
Do you have a wife
Perfume does the other wife
He has a wife
Yeah there was a with Leanne McAdoo
Years ago but I don't know if it's
Substantiate at all
Good to speak gossip rag talk
Kia
It started
Matt with all due respect
Man without you you're very attractive lady
As this clip is we're coming to the end of our Clips here but this one is
Insane
It is a nice
Impression on the part where were the revisiting that Alex has ability to do impression
I've always liked to hear about the
I should clarify
This is after he had shown a clip
What he described as the mentally ill protesters
At the inauguration
Okay if you just showed
One lady
Out in the middle of the street with tin cans
Tied to her waist
Slamming something against the street it was
It was a crazy
Who is the person who believes they are holding people who just got married
Level two
If you saw this you not think this is free.
Do not think cuz of the protest
Crazy person
And he's like yeah they just get out there and they do this
This crazy stuff in the people gather around them
There's no one around
This isolated Crazy Bruce
Yep
Relatively
I suppose
Sure I would say
At least 150 ft
Of this lady
The people taping
Who work for
Who do crazy things that gather a crowd
He starts by saying he feels bad for this crazy person
Not because she's crazy but because she's indoctrinated by the
The globalist
Put cigarettes out on her beating
Robert i-card
That's where I lost it
Crazy
It's the best
Oh man
So you don't think that was a very good impression
I don't think it was a good impression I'll say this I could tell what he was going
Miami
The man's voice really offended
His own voice is the pimp okay okay for black women
Secondarily offensively
Right
And if you were to try and tell him it would be like you're a dumb
Brainwashed liberal
Dead behind us
Busted
Through before we get out of here I would like to take a moment we got a we got a missive from the road
Jordan is on his work keishin
Out there London
Good ol
Joy England
From from London on the ground
And so far
We have a fight for knowledge
Iran knowledge fight
And knowledge
From across the pond
I'm recording this from
There is zero occupiers here
And they would know they've been occupied before or at least bombed by them
I'm speaking specifically of Nazis the ones from Germany
Not the ones from the United States
Who currently holds power
Over
Over all of us really
It's strange being here and
Blamed for Trump
So much as I feel like the representation of
You know what I'm saying
Trump so much here because his hair offends them personally
It reminds them too much
ORS fake tan his fake tan reminds them of the
Relationship
With the son that I have with an old high school classmate
Where is
Do I know you I just I just don't want to see you again except for short bursts
I think I think one of their big issues has they do feel like
You know we we one-up them
Like we have a little bit of a
With the UK no matter how much things change
There is still that kind of small relationship there where
You know with one vote they said hey we can destroy Great Britain and we said oh yeah yeah
Like that we can destroy the world how do you feel about that assholes
America
You know they they read the news
And the news about Trump
Even though
You know they had something
And the Supreme Court
I don't know if they even have real quartz wigs
They rule that you cannot actually trigger article 50 that's the brexit law
Without a congressional or parliamentary
Like
The c word
You can use parliamentary
Rules to actually vote on article 50
Without a parliamentary vote
You know
Everybody's fine
Brexit to happen then they could put pressure on their Parliament
To keep that from happening
But that's a very non British way of looking at
The facts
The majority of people now don't want brexit to happen
Doesn't matter to them
What matters is that
The right way
Adjust is so British
Yeah we don't want this to have
We have an opportunity
To keep it from happening
But how about
NFL
Is Jordan from the road
Alex Jones
Sister Alex
Okay
Georgia Lotto
Probabilistic
He always Records On
Flame
Text her on an iPhone recording on a plane
There one more clip
And it is
Where I think
Alex gives up
Too much
Of his insecurities
I think they're showing her on full display
As if he hasn't already been doing
But I do almost every second
But I think there's something you haven't really
Securities about
Necessarily
Sure that's fair
And I think he accidentally says
Something that's very true
Surrounded by a bunch of things that are
Ridiculously good
And it's just crazy
And there we have it
Isn't that an interesting set of sentence
That is
Przegryw
Well the if that either or statement
Drew
Yep
And I think
That's why he has to reassure himself
Alex no
No
And the part that he said before that like the story of it being like
I was doubting a man
But my God wanted me to be on the show
That's what convinced
Choppa's on an episode
It's G
Doesn't do like a super long interview but he tells Alex that he thinks his record is impeccable
You can write about a lot of stuff and that he promises he won't let
It's really really scary and super depressing
It was funny back when he wasn't present
Things are a lot funny
Jokes
Whatever Jen
We've come to the end
The two days in the brand new experience
I feel like from watching your face
There was there was a moment of overwhelming
Like I think
The middle especially there was a looking
Are these the feeling of you didn't want to go further
There was definitely admit
Shock
Happy surprises
As well
I don't know
Surprised like I'm glad
Any children as you can
But not divisible by
That's pretty cool
Glimmers of humanity within the shell of a
Horrible horrible man
I can't imagine
Either
Very tranquil or full of yellow
She can't turn it off
Well me and Jordan have been speculating that a lot of these products
Who sells super male vitality
There's a really decent chance
That in all this aggression
And stuff like that is
Bridal
Uncontrolled testosterone
That doesn't turn off when you leave
Your performance
Studio
That's
Dangerous
Is very dangerous
I know
Finish hair but
You feel like he doesn't deserve it
Football pro
Do you think you will go back and explore Alex Jones ever again
Not on purpose
Cool cool cool
I think I might I will be more acutely aware
And probably interest
If something about Alex
Crosses
These in the zeitgeist
Definitely a new story about it
People are
Tweeting or Facebooking about
I'm sure
You got a little bit of
Also this is very
I would love to
That's kind of one of our messages
You are really summarizing things are providing some contacts
Some jokes along the way laughing at his dumbass
Experience with you cuz I'm creating this
Pretty much everyday
And I would recommend no one else do that if you want to get some of it
Listen to this
Yeah that's fun
I think everyone says
On the spot
Music you want to listen
That's what I've done here
Legitimately if I could listen to if someone else was doing this I would listen to this f****** thing everyday
I love doing this so much thank you for all for listening
We do appreciate it very much
Knowledge fight
You can follow us on Twitter at knowledge underscore
Gmail.com
If you want to get in touch with us
Text
Prague cards welcome
It was going to be brain battle
Buds
But knowledge fight 10
Good stuff
Yeah
We'll get you next time
Goodnight
Holding
Alex