Alexandra Thurston color
We are
There is a twist
One big one
Yes how long are we going to do this
Never again
Enjoy this while it lasts will never do that again
I do a lot about Alex
Today we're going to be doing
Episode
Before we get to
You tell us what we have for a beverage
Farmers aloe vera artist
Strawberry
Flavored drink
I don't want to put
Too fine a point on this but I smelled it before we started the broadcast and I
Kind of
Smelled a little bit like stomach acid
This is going to be
Ingredients list
Water
Next ingredient.
I regret aloe vera gel I'm done
Is not a liquid
This is another coconut juice situation
There is there are things in there my brother
Difficult
You brought us back to me
Terrible place
Swear in liquid
Your day and that means
And it's your fault it is
Jordan I love you
I'd like to give a shout out to a couple of thank you for
We appreciate it
Try Farmers aloe vera as a
Action cases
And you need to bring some aloe vera
Also would like to give a shout out to other new donator what's up
John
Do you support the show button
The show with an out-of-context drop
From Alex Jones
Sometimes we don't do a good enough job
Doing these out-of-context drop
Desirable
Fired understood the last opening last time
Sometimes
I do not
Find something that's great
In terms of an out-of-context drop from
Sometimes there aren't
Best route to make up for it I have to hear is the first one
Very
Very uninterested in prayer
These also why are you in
Of course not and you should never lie
Let anybody know
Yeah it's pies bulshit
To do this is why we got it and just because he's religious humblebrag
About like I don't pray everyday
Also free
Screams on-air 4 hours a day about how like
You got to get with Jesus
Hey let me tell you
Do you know what is
Rachel Perez
The app that the SharePoint stay for our prayer
God
And
Whatever God that is
I hope that unspecified God appreciate
So here's the other out-of-context drive from Alex Jones
As
Can get
Take a royal flush of Ameraucana chicken
Is it was American royalty wow
Sickening
Sickening Americana
Vestigial twins
Is a second
Admission that American history is
F****** horrify
Or just like
Cloth type live
But be there
I would like to keep
Both of those out-of-context drops
In your mind as we go along
Pray everyday but
Try to make them feel good
Not as good as calling the popo devil worshiper of course
McLaren
Then he is American royalty and both sides
Eva's family
Are straight
Flush royal flush
Americana
Did he go to Aunt
Or how do we know this
I think it's Dia dentist father probably just told him
Some b*******
The 6 smartest boy in Texas
This grows up to be a
CIA dentist
Gives birth to the world's most
Bulshit rap artist Brown
Bizarre to be real
Somehow it's wonderful
I accepted it
Today we're going to be doing over the period of September 29th
To October 2nd
Have you noticed
Is an investigation in order to
Better understand why the f***
Did Alex Jones sign up with
With Donald Trump
It's unclear question 1
How are we on the third quarter
The fiscal year starts on October 1st
Who knows
Clear you're asking that because if you haven't listened to all the episodes
Alex Jones through a 28-hour live broadcast
Turn order to make
$1000000 in the money bomb the money bomb
Before the end of the fiscal year
Odd
He doesn't support Trump yet
He's been going back and forth
For the better part of three months now with the I like it I like what you saying but I don't trust him
Kind of stuff
Rodger Stone has not yet arrived we worked out the timeline a little better
New Trump campaign after the first
Debate
Because
Trump got into that war of words of Megyn Kelly
And there was a lot of backlash
Things are getting distracted
From the corporate
Principles of
Campaign
What which is what I don't
What were the core principles inline filter supposed
Rodger Stone left the campaign
I told you this earlier
I want to be
Really clear that this
Bizarre
I don't know
Rodger Stone left the campaign
The second week
Beginning of the second week of August
Yes Brown August 8th
August 10th or so
First debate
Alex Jones within a week of that
Does his pivot
On Donald Trump
I'm not saying
Not on
Before that point been talking about how Donald Trump
Was
He wasn't really rich
Who was the frontman for
Consortium
Ghostwrite then he goes to Europe on vacation
He comes back after the first debate
And within a couple days of being back in America
He says
I'm going to give Trump a chance
I'm not saying I'm supporting him
I'm going to give him the benefit of the doubt
And it was all
If you recall predicated on the idea that he said something negative about Hillary
Which of course you did already.
Right
It seemed superficial and probably means something Rodger Stone left
And then immediately almost immediately
Could mean something that isn't we don't have
If we don't proof know we do have some
Suspicious
It's an interesting piece
The puzzle
Never made that clear on the
Michelle
To do that I'll bet now here we are I mean that was in August now we're at the end of September
And still he hasn't committed
To drop although you have had diamond and silk
Ready very pro-trump of loggers
He's at them on
They're basically just
Trump picture
I'll tell you what
We're not going to learn anything about his position on Donald Trump today
Of course he doesn't do anything
This time.
Well I'll tell you what
All right now that seemed a little bit can
I'll tell you this
Detox
A lot
About Russia
Industry
From September 29th
To October
Second a lot about Russia
Yeah
Yeah America
The whole campaign
Happening in America
How about Russia guys you like that place right
I don't
Call Amy
Real meaningful discussion of it at all
Nothing
Here's here's
How do you start
On the 29th
Report headlines
New World Order Ralph Smart
Obama
I have been scanning over the editorial piece
Out of New York
But not with some of the other parts
I'm going to go over
Claiming Obama's Obama's
Obama's
Russia is on the verge of economic collapse
Kind of horses
Russia is fighting
Forest life
Continue to put out to the West
Baikal
He is refusing
Russia that's been thrown out of the G8
Mega Buneary
You know why
Sweetie cake perfect
Grayson and Ascension
Murder turtle
Buster's
Maricon
I mean yes Russia is good old-fashioned Mafia
Style government
You know what you got to give it to
Chicago when the mafia ran things right
People got hurt
Yeah
If you want
Astoundingly pro-russia
Really crazy
Discuss
Any of the options exist
He's not discussing any of the reason
I got thrown out of the G8
Who got thrown out right the why is not important
And you see how
You conveniently get surrounded
To deal with any of those issues
By over demonizing the Imagine
That's literally the most
And by comparison
That's what you would want to do if you were trying to defend
Terrible person
You would make the alternative even worse yet
The best Hitler had a few bad idea
Wasn't as bad as the literal death
Globalist behind World War
I bet Hillary was a bad guy bad guy
Setup looked Germany was no Paragon of
Anything like that
Autocorrect
I find that clip very
Troubling
Weird it's not good
Real quick
It's very
Sing to me the way he will eventually
Wendy's getting going to
Defending
Like you said your trucks. Perfect
But
Same sort of
Rationalization that he does
Historical revisionism about Hitler revisionism about Putin
In order to defend
This is not good whatever it is
Like
Even if it's
The worst thing in the world
He will
Edibles
Right
And then make up a reason that the globalist there were
Absolutely
Basically
Stuck in my craw a little bit but not as much
As this
6 clip
Series of two clips
First one
The shot
Second one
Chaser baby
No
Al-Qaeda in Syria
Syria bombing Syria
This whole stretch
There's going to be a lot about
Putin being a genius a good guy in
Propping up
Is gassing and murdering his own people
That guy
The people according to Alex Russian propaganda
Crazy imagine
Is not shared by the rest of the world
Interesting or anything like that
I don't know what was going on with
The Drudge Report
In 2050
But I do know that some of these narratives have been
Repackaged in present day
Breitbart have been on
The same
Yeah well I'm just saying that
I cuz I remember a bunch of people going on
Talk shows
The time cuz the
The party line was
Look at how much smarter look at how much stronger Putin is that Obama
Because
They had to attack about something
It wasn't like full-on supportive Putin it was just like
Wish we had a strong
Dictator like home
Clips about
That whole issue that will get to eventually
Lambs on that Spectrum, or actually supporting
I will see you first
Here's a shot
And I will get to the chase
All right folks engaging in concealed
Carrie
Cashman
And it's just as important of a civil rights is Rosa Parks
Texas
Justice Seminole
Yeah man
How do you like that
Just like
Take me home.
So is
Carrying a gun into a public place around with gun
And that's exactly the same as people standing up for the Dignity of a race
Survival
And so on and so forth
Not being a fire hose
Austin Publix
Positive
But that's what I like
The thing that boggled my mind was right before that when he's like
Concealed carry people have been protecting Society courses entire time
Dumb dumb
Cuz everytime
Every time you're walking around in public the only reason
Constantly getting shot
Is because the people who are afraid that someone else in your surrounding
Probably has a gun
That keeps the bad guys at Bay
The concealed carry people are protecting
Society
Quibe threat that anyone could have a gun
You know what that make
Yeah totally
Bat signal
Even if you don't know you know you don't know if the Batman is coming
For you you may be trying to
I like
Ocean
Totally
That's a perfect about we live in
I would love if Aaron the Batman Universe
I don't know something about I think it's a bad idea and we're going to find out we're going to go
Go through an investigation of Bruce Wayne's childhood
6 hour episode 13
So the other thing I'd like to say is
I don't believe that evidence
Suggest that we have a history of
Abusing people who have guns
In this country
I further don't believe that you're born with a gun
I don't think
That
You don't get what I'm saying the difference between civil rights is something you're born with that you know being a part of a group you don't have a choice
About with Alex
You like guns a lot made me with a
Whether it would be in my
My hand
4 in my
Do you remember that
Parable
From G's
I'm rolling out to talk about
Jesus
Goes out to the desert
For 40 days and 40 nights
He's tempted by the devil but only on night one
Cuz he get his kneecap
Kaplana
That's just Kotori right take him out
Bought it from a survivalist
That was the shot
Here's the chaser
Others join Confederacy
Interesting okay well there we go
Maybe like some of them or neutral although there is a little bit of that regret
Season
Is it like we have to
Wrestle with
Which group of admirers more
Speaks volumes
Gummy okay
Alex
You have a
Family lineage
Present Behavior pattern of someone who believes of the Confederacy
You're like Rosa Parks have a gun
You dick
Whenever the
It look
Say what you want
I will
Seceding from the Union
Is very similar to Rosa Parks go into
The front of the bus
Sure
Okay
Rosa Parks
Would have been
So that doesn't
No
Does the bus have a gun
Betty White
I like that
That's racist
An amazing episode of The Magic
Teach you about gun safety
Miss Frizzle just getting into
Bus shaped like a Glock
This next clip is really funny
I hope it's funny
It is Alex Jones
Trying not to get mad
Aerosol
So fake
Funnel boy
Heidi and Spencer there but I do believe that ends with an a
Okay cool
Then we don't have to worry about
Control my temper right now because
Yeah
Stupid
Culturally religiously
YouTube
Good save
What about your tasteless
Trendy frontman
Whatever the new correctness is this month's this week today
Before you actually end up getting mad cuz I want to discuss that a tiny bit
Correctness generally complains about now
Is every one of the big day
Campaign the people are on
Political correctness is whatever the
Globalist
They're telling you to
Except
Now
And
I think
He
Is a idiot
Because
People have been to
Discussing trans rights
For 50 years
We do have a lot of evidence
To prove that
Right
Particular case
This isn't political correct
This is
Something that people have been on the Vanguard of for a really long time
And now it's starting to
To make more inroads
People are starting to realize that the
Argument
Very valid all the time with the
People who rail against political
You're not allowed to
Just say something
Right which is which
Bart of witches
I want you to say the n word
It's that you should
Sure feel like all of the things that the n-word means
That stuff is still in you whether or not you say it
That's true
Correctness isn't too
Monitor your speed
But it's to try keep you for being the horrible monster who says those day
To some extent
Yeah but even beyond that cuz I think that's
A little highbrow
Teddy
I think on another level
I don't want to get
Haiti on this pot
Alex wouldn't understand that what I'm saying is
On another level it's really just like
It's not Bandits
Do that
Like
You know it's bad
Motor less
It's not some sort of magic
Magical
What you say
Being able to say the n word
Diagram
That doesn't have
This word is banned
Yesterday
Yeah but
He was saying that his book got banned
Facebook didn't get banned
Schuster whatever just
We don't want to do is keep advocating
For pedophiles
Providence podcast
But I will say
Text you about this
You really mad at me
Opolis
Really Charming on Infowars cuz everyone else has no personality
Nokia's calling Glenn Beck a queer
It was that's not
Better
Better about this moment
It was pretty fun I let out a little laugh
Where do you live in the muck
Yeah yeah
What is the spectacle
Alex Jones has this guy on this show and they're just like
Gay Bash
The hell defendant
Glenn Beck
But this one you guys
You guys get this
Totally clear that I'm laughing at the absurdity and Novelty
B-day Bash
We won't be talking about that cuz
Please give those ding dong more
It's just total cultural Marxism
It's just whatever he say this week
Shredded
Pogchamp
Emergency Center
Resettlement
Army manual
Alex is misrepresenting all of the
These documents you can go find them
Very easily it
Mostly stuff about best practices for before in theaters
And stuff like that turn large population
It's a very boring
Process you and your family
Helicopter
What Rehabilitation
Fake laugh
Who You Are
The noted kindness review
Traffic
Frustrates me.
That's all
He asked God for helping I now believe
Yes
That's his little prayer
Count of you should be a broadcaster
Quite frankly if you can't control your
I'm not saying that Alex
Should be off the air
But he's obviously faking these
Oh yeah
He can't control his emotions
Booty's presenting is a mentally unwell person
Really bad
Really complicated
Anyway
I want to get back on track
His next clip
Sommore
Hy-Vee is now the main leader of the world
Tells the truth
Over and over again
Cool world
He's mostly talking about
Describe from a code of morality
If that allows for literally any
At least
Billion dollars
Alex note
Wonder why
The globalist admittedly
They are in that stage
How's the protocols of the Elders of Zion
That would put
That level
Right
Like Putin
Secutor the protocols of the Elders of Zion
Perfection right
I don't know union break
Populist wave
And then becomes the autocratic
Tater
Oligarch friends
Like getting that done in that the Playbook
Unfortunately
Unfortunately the Jews
I mean as Russian
They didn't pull it
No no no it took a
Immoral
Very moral
At always
Is mostly referring to their is the Putin to just giving a speech about how we are
Okay then I'll know the
Because it matches Alex's narrative
Which also
Conveniently matches Russian
State television
He's taking his international news alright
Right in that actually leads us to our next
Squidward just kind of
Premiered second episode
We went over with Alex's doing on Y2K which way
Was disgraceful
Answer your mongering to
Concentration camps being set up at airports
Wichita
From history
Multiple power plant meltdowns
Space command
He had a
We are out.
Department of Transportation
Is out there everywhere
Didn't Street right now
It was disgraceful
Listen to the Y2K app
Episode 8
Call you later Ivar's to the podcast
Has
Ascended to power
Big thing
And because right around
New Year's Eve
Miguel went out
From
The Prime Minister position
Yeah but
Wasn't there time.
Somebody else
President
Can force base coat
Losing power
No
And the Y2K episode
Discuss
Bomb
He was the vice president
Ammo
Exactly
Moscow police
Caught
With
A plastic explosive and then they said I was part of a drill
Engaged
False
Vice president
But there's not total proof of them
But I was told by a lot of other Russian
Define away from chechnya
Vitamin Putin is not trying to force vaccines
Yeah he doesn't live here
How she can be a man
Western beef ribs
And one world
Collaborative
Really fascinating there is that
So much less proof
Things that would make
Putin look bad
Then
He took
But it's not a hundred percent proof
Wavy level up
You know what it wasn't Putin
I think I would like to know a little bit apartment complexes were bombed
Areas in Russia
Between the fourth and
A September in 1999
Coincidentally just a couple of months
Before Vladimir Putin
Impreza
It was a big part of the power grab
Because it was
For the second
Chechen War
Which was
Putin wrote power on
Interesting
There were 293.
Mostly word anybody in the bed
Almost 300 people died over a thousand were
Pretty seriously
Or mildly injured
How long that Spectre
Now the thing that I think is more important
Is
Is that multiple people
Who have come out
That it was
The Russian government
And the SSB
Be what the
The Secret Service and Russia at 3:10 to
They've died
Mysteriously
Not all of them
But enough
What it is
Very curious
Alexander litvinenko
The guy who got poisoned with polonium one of his big things
It was Putin
Udit batra
I also Boris
Berezovsky
He also died under very mysterious circumstances
There's one other dudes named never be able
Go to pronounce
They all died
But seriously
People
You talk about this
As though there's
We're in people who challenged him
Or criticize him publicly
Wind-up toy
I need you to provide at least
64 more examples
Three other
Maybe punta.
Maybe he will take your 63 and I have this one too
Hurricane
There's no way
He filed two motions for parliamentary investigation
In March
Commission to investigate the bombings was chaired by Duma Deputy Sergey kovalev
The commission was rendered ineffective by the government's refusal to respond to its inquiry
Two key members of the kovalev commission
Now
I heard the guy whose name I can't pronounce
The commission's lawyer
Mikhail travoski was arrested in
Convicted in a closed military Court
And released from prison
We probably got some good
So
Some of the circumstantial stuff that surrounds
Mysterious deaths
The commission
Being completely stonewalled and then multiple people who were involved
In the commission dying and very mysterious circumstances
Around
It doesn't look good
For Putin net worth
This is a lot like
If
Instead of firing Mueller you just killed all of his staff
Right like that these lawyers
Mueller
Unfortunately everyone around him is dead including his family
He is doing his best
But yeah we don't have good hopes
Currently no one knows where he
Yeah I mean it's it's
This is
Very with
Derailment
Scope in the pattern of
What happened
Right
In Russia
You think
Made up and
In Russian
All the time
Assassination why
Clandestinely
And they try and make it look like it wasn't
Well I mean
Message
Sometimes sometimes there is a bullet in the forehead on Putin birthday
Yes but I mean it's really
Like its soda
Intellectually dishonest for Alex to be like
You know what I got no conspiracy theory that but
What time is it
Right sometimes you get it wrong
False flag
Sometimes you get everything else he's ever said in his entire jury Financial collapse
Gold an ounce
Man
Been great if we were listening then it was amazing
We could have put our very small amount of money
And made $49,000
Cuz it wasn't like one grand or so for an outside so we could afford one grand
Maybe.
Anyway
This
To hear this sort of pro-putin rhetoric
Cuz
Even with his aunt like
He qualify
Vacations
It's still ReSound Ali pro-putin
Absolutely the only reasonable position to bake
It look
The prism of History looking at the bombings
In 1999
Is doobie that was a pretext to go to war in chechnya
So you could have a power grab
Yeah that's
Essentially would happen
Very much
So
Even
He even says you know like
Maybe
You still did it
Just wipes that away
Immediate it wouldn't matter
Cuz he likes
That's cool
So after this call
He gets on the blower
For calling
Alex
He sounded so much like you
Translation
Nrt
I would have thought you were on the stage
That's not good
Sop
Speed it sounds exactly like
That's not good
Also why was he watching
I don't know
Pride is probably a heavy overlap between his audience of people who
Go run watch Rock
Chlamydia
It's the kind of thing the Alex
Encourages
All that is true
Americans keep hitches narratives from
Russian media
American Media isn't telling you the truth
Yeah you're listening
And you want to look into one of Alex's stories or maybe there
You know it's linked on infowars.com you want to go try and find the source
You go and you end up finding an article and spotting
Negreanu dirty or something like that
You know Alex is telling you this is the truth everyone else is lying to you
All of a sudden you're going to
Associate Russian media with tell him
The truth
Alex
It's only more proof that you're onto the real source
This much time shirtless is Alex does
Stroop
Hair
Alex maybe wearing a wig maybe wearing a bulk
Any of these things could be.
So he takes another call and shockingly also about food
You're on a roll
Hey how's it going
Beginning of Putin when he was first running his re-election campaign he's running around his shirt off
Horsebacking
Shooting guns up you know just
Completely demands man everybody
You know
I'm a man right
Being in charge and having strong family
Promote an effeminate Obama on purpose
I think it's healthy
What I'm getting at is they're doing it on purpose because Obama what does he do
Lillian gay
Person that had infected to everybody good defense department now
Completely masculinity
Military
Servile
A knock-kneed weirdos you can imagine
What it what is he talking about there what is the plan
Having a gay person be an official position
Damask
D masculine
Gay agenda very least gays are being used
Agenda
That look pretty
If you want it look if you're going to put anybody in the defense department you wanted
Distance true
They know what they're doing
Also maybe the other thing I would suggest
It's put somebody who's qualified who can do a good job in there
Regardless
Whether or not you want qualified people in office
Competent
So well Tillerson is
He's doing a great job did you notice out there
Neither is anybody else
Kind of like
Tillerson is one of those dudes
He Fades into the background a little bit cuz there's so much swirling b******* that story came out
What about in like
Couple years back Exxon
With while he was
They are broke sanction
With Russian Bank and Trust Company
Do you realize that he went on his little
Hiatus
Right after
But no one is like
You don't get to take breaks like this
Apartments
What are you doing
Bright
Pennywise
Glad
We don't have a
Text Barry
Now
BattleBots
This before the election actually happen
Absolutely
And now I shall go
Trump didn't want to be president he wanted to win presidency
Neither does any of these other people
Time and energy
Department
All you really want is to siphon money and resources as much as you can
And really every single person that you bringing is a risk
Love them like soda
Talking you out
We are into October
Cuz on the 30th
Paul Joseph
Watson
Really funny moment at the end of the 29th where Alex is like
Tomorrow
He's not mad or anything
Paul Joseph Watson
How's the hotel tomorrow
Cuz they will be late
I'm going hunting
We're going on
I haven't taken my kid hunting enough
Lego Hunter
October 1st
Episode
You might like alright
29th of September use in a weird mood he's going to go hunting with his kid it's going to f****** watch off him
Everything will be back to normal and gets back
People know
Betamerica
Anime love
John of a perfect
But compared
Absolute
Phil
Culture and Society
Is good
So
All you need to know there is
You can just ignore all the negative things
Things you saying because those are really even negative
-2 Alex
He's a strong
Malek's restaurant
He's Abu
A straw
What strong man doesn't have
In the world to be strong
You got to make sure that you have killed Italy
One dog
Absolute has killed at least
Three dogs
I mean he's there he's
That's f******
Also he said the program like that was a positive
He's going to repopulate Russia with a breeding well this is that sort of racist idea about other cultures
Without breeding us
And that's going to be genocide by
Buy just population numbers
It's David Duke and his elk talk about all the time about it on Alex's show even
Talk about how the birthrate among white people
And Africans and Muslims are outbreeding
The white
Man and eventually they're just going to overrun us due to numbers
I would argue on one hand
Again just projection
Well if we have the numbers that's what we did in the past
Because we have it coming
Yeah cuz we did it already
I guess if you want to use historical precedent that does make sense
Sometime it like
We're not in feudal times
Anymore
Most people are evolved enough to
To be like
I don't care
What race
I'm not joining a race
This group
God you would hope so
Anyway I believe that
Is encouraging the family and encouraging White
Breeding
Great
And that's going to defend
Never says it but that's what he mean
But the other thing is
He's like saying that
Incredulous
If he said if Alex's breeding program
What I hear
Is
Putin is creating Russian chimera
That's why I was a little bit confused
There's a lady gums
Is creating human
Not human
But animal machine chimera
So we got that
So I wanted to point out in that cliff
Craigslist
I do
Coming back
Used beyond the machine repair
Alex is incredulous in his voice
Are you saying
Putin is the leader of the
Reworld everyone is saying that
Americans
Love poop
Jesus great
You saying that in that sort of like disbelieving voice
Because
He's reading that from Russian media
He thinks that's what the world thinks
Because
Russian
Media is reporting that that is what the world
Crazy so I'll Jones is
He's a responding
Propaganda
By making
A second layer of propaganda on top of it
Quite frankly
Cuz even though Alex
Being incredulous about what he's reading on
Hotspot making s***
Goes through the top
Fluoride in my water
Nonsense
Knock sensor
Sorry
Take a point
Garrett -
This show also
Involve
A very interesting field
October 1st
On this episode Joe big
Is out on the University of Texas
Chris Austin
Because there is an anti-gun protest
What's going on
I have
Good bit oven
Information about this
I know exactly what went on
Are there was a
Concealed carry on campus
If University
There were a bunch
Two people
Students and professors
They started to Triumph
This legislation
I tried to move
Against it because
Campus
Pull up guns is not a comfortable place
Wasn't this immediately following
What was it North Carolina
Then she
Robot Shooting Sports Bar investigation
Call and there's one in Oregon on October 2nd
I believe
If it's a first
As
Sia but beer doesn't Alex
This position is that
If you take away guns that don't allow guns on
Campus they need is a safe
It's for bad people with guns
To go
Target
And they can just shoot up people on
School campuses
And my argument to that is
You should have like
Cops
Show campus
Was cops were armed
And stuff like that
Cuz that
Official
Everybody should have their gun safe
This one as I said I'm
I've gone from let's be reasonable to
Let's take their guns
River City fist fights
Some college
No
I didn't go outside
Asbury
They saw a lot of his fights on campus I saw a lot of really heated fights
I know the testosterone flaring a lot of people are experimenting with drugs
For the first time in their life
The idea that people who are 82
220 on campus
Does verily
People who are older students
Baby veterans
He's coming back
Something like that
I know the different situation
And those kids that I'm talking
About
But like those young kids were volatile and growing
Handful of new experiences
I really don't feel comfortable about the idea of them being armed
In the off chance
Heated argument
With somebody
Thing that he
Is that people walk around
Knowing
That there is
Concealed carry and so they feel like oh
We're protect
That is the complete opposite it all
Campus
And you knew there was
Concealed carry laws how do you not kind of have in the back your mind like
This person have a gun
Do they have a gun right now
People down whenever they go into the f******
Class like
Situation you put professors and what you have to
To give bad news to student yeah
If you fail them or they come to your private office hours
Stuff like that you recommended incredibly uncomfortable position
Where anybody could be armed
And you know what people get thrown out of school for grade
And stuff like that
No but if you're allowed to have guns on campus
All sorts of like
Okay so I wrote for my campus paper
Talk about this on the show
Deathreats what that's not what I want
That was another time
One time I made a joke about Rosa
About how I
All the kids that on the back of
So I don't know what the f*** she was complaining
Right I was intentionally
Obviously misrepresenting things for
Communicate
This guy who was a member of
The student government
Did not like me
Because I had written an article about him and his friends
Hey use
Fun
In order to take it
Tripped
To sxsw
They claimed that they were
Define could come get booked on Tampa
I saw his pictures on Facebook they were just drunk
Respect the game
But at the same time I had this campaign
Against
The student government
Because I think the student government stupid is there
Uncovered that and I wrote an article about it
So he decided he was going to try and get me kicked out of school
I wrote that joke about Rosa Park
I am
Based on that
That joke
He reported me to the student judicial
And I had to go have a meeting the guy
That was formal
I got a confidential letter
That's great
Confidential
You wrote about your my, of course you did
Breed of his letter being confidential so I had to go and meet with the
But it was just one guy
In that situation
I could see that too
Situation being very uncomfortable and I'm just one of a thousand people that that guys had to meet with
Yeah over the years
Two fights or get arrested for something that may have to meet with the school
PowerSchool
And that could be f****** heated as s***
Because if you get kicked out of school and your mind is
I was certain
Bent
That could be like someone taking away your life
Well think about the places where guns are in
Like
Like Court
Right
Do you know why
Good people a lot to lose if you're crazy you could do something really stupid
Like that if your argument also also just trust everybody say first
Just to put a button on it I did not
I made a mockery of
The proceedings
And I've got it wrong
I know
Move.
I think there is
Very good reason for
Especially public
Universities
Do not allow
Concealed carry
I think the arguments that we've made or not even
Let's go to
People who are inactive
World
Would make
Rather have open
Open carry Lincoln
Cuz then at least you know what f***
Castle Heights
Well then we turn into the Deep Space 9 mm
Biggs and Alex Jones
Call
About 10 people on the stage
Call vortex
Federal screaming gun-free UT gun-free UT
So
They're showing video of a sparsely attended protest
Bloomberg
I actually have weight
UT Austin
UT idiot crowd
But the speakers were flown in
That's really interesting and I can actually tell you that
Because my dad is super involved
Noggin for you
Yeah
The part of the organ
Innovation
I actually texted Amazon
Anybody from Bloomberg
Welcome letter
So firmly believe
As I do too
The new place on college campuses
Professional
Let's
About
Cops are okay to have gone
Wherever they are because that's
Part of their job
But my dad is part of that he is involved the organization he assures me that no one
Flown out by Bloomberg
At all
And tell my dad if you want to talk about him being a ship go ahead
Throughout his life you've had a very consistent
Protest streak
He has been very
Left
Dry wind causes Wednesday
Back when we lived in Missouri
Every single Wednesday
When they were busy
My parents would go out in protest
On the busiest corner
Columbia
With about 8
People 8 to 10 people standing around with herpes
No war in Iraq
Next time every f****** one
They do that they are committed to goals
Committed
Causes high principal
And standby
He is a good example
Of the people who are involved in gun-free
These are not Soros Bloomberg shills
These are UT professors for deeply
Concerned about the idea of people walking around
Randomly with guns
So f*** you Alex
.308
So also the other thing I want to talk about
But I need to get more information
For my dad is that
Alex talks about two people got arrested
Test2 counter-protest
Got arrested
And they make a big deal out of it there
What have you removed for trespassing
DaVita permit to protest
Some campuses
That's pretty Universal
College camp
Some campuses have
Specific places where it's
They had a permit
She had a permit
These dick holes that showed up
What's the difference
I wasn't actually at that protest I was busy
But
The other protests the next one
I was at protest
I need refers to it as
The dildo protest
I know but it's
In Austin and like I know that Alex will bring it up when it happened
We get there I'll call my dad and get a lot about that but
Everybody everybody concealed-carry dildos is that what it was
I hope it is pretty good
Know what I do
And is after this Alex
Back on his
Not good
Not right
Migrate
I think that he might not be able to
To tell which is which
At a certain point
In order to save face
He wants to be like I'm the one who started it there following
I am now Putin
B**** by accident how he's going to sell the Trump stuff
Americana sweeper Sal and stuff like that
For Trump
I think that's kind of his big moves and then of course
Get together with the strongman
It's always about the
The big strong
Yeah
Eclipse from August
1st August 2nd
Which I think is
F****** amazing
But August 1st
Recovery
Bridget Lee interview
Joel skousen
On
I believe he has
Okay that
That Looms
This next clip is f******
Wild
You say that close
I can get it
But I mean
He's going to say what he's going to say I considering play clips of Marty saying
I could have
Does sound insane
He could get a sit-down interview with Putin
I don't know maybe he has what world is Alex
Get a sit-down interview
If he actually does
That implies to
To me that he has
Connections
But not directly
Indirect contact
Maybe he's talking to Rodger
AirStone off arrabon
I like Rodger
A connection to the Russian
Maybe he's accidentally slipping something like that
I don't know it's weird
I'm not saying that
That's because
He even he even if he says it's probably North
Which means
He wants to do it
Yes
That
The idea of him
He would get on
Plane to Russia
Vicente
If Putin
Actually sat down for
51 Megyn Kelly
Spencer Pratt it's he's pissed at Megyn Kelly
Sean
I told you that October 2nd
It is amazing
You did tell me
I'm just going to let Alex start the show off
And I think you'll see a mediately why it's so awesome
And then I guess
And I have not had a lot to drink
Budweiser
Melon board
Broadcast today
The worst
Abogados actually respect that
Guys
I am hungover is she
I think we're going to have a great show
Just like Eddie
Convince him
Spell check
I think it's going to work
The co-host the show with him
Could you doing such a s*** job
He's fine
Jager
College
A bottle of Jack
On a Tuesday
I've not touched
Demon Yeager
Weird night of
I was buying you
He's not good
He's just doing weird
Kind of
Hey they just not being able to handle his normal job
ISO about
10 minutes in
Joe Biggs comes in a tape sidecars
Nothing
Yeah
Cuz he accidentally would have told too much
The truth maybe like I feel like that's what it is
Just like
I quit
It seems like you guys
Like let's go to break I'm done
What's up Joe Biggs in there just in
It does feel like that sort of thing
But
You get that like
Sit down
On the floor and then rolls
It's the perfect opportunity for him to be like
Child
That's their product
Calm children
Tom's babies
He knows not of this
Child
Alex
Do you still want
He wants to try and do is f****** job
Today's top story
Courtyard top storage
It's not that far in trips
From China
Iran and Russia are piling area
Growing Al-Qaeda
No that's our top story
Warriors
With the state department criticizing Russia
And the Pentagon criticizing Russia
Got to remember when I get home
Al-Qaeda
She's misrepresenting that but he's also
But the top stories all these people are critiquing Russia and shouldn't
He's getting defensive
It's not that China and
Laundry list of
Made up
Globalist countries
Troops into
What was it
Siri Siri
America
The bad guys
I hate them for somebody who loves America so much
To burn to the ground
To buy into Russian propaganda about
Indicates that he doesn't really have that much do Siri
He's not really American royalty
How
The South rise
Again
Russian backing
Well there we go
Why else would these people who hate America so much
Love so much
What they're trying to do is secede again
If at first you don't succeed
I will I will take a negative
For that one as well
I don't think you're joking but you might not be too far off what Alex would like
Don't
Mayo Clinic
Just to be in America
I'm thrilled about that
Royalty
Americana
We tried to leave
Everything Russia.
Based on bulshit I saw on
State-run media
So
Clip is just a great example of Alex
Being hungover and
Just being like
Awfully
I don't know what's going on in his head
I have no idea
But this is
This is wild stuff
What do you think
Sunlight good for you
Every doctor until 20 years ago
Your kids sick you're sick it out get some sunlight
I feel you
The sun will set you free lessons
I literally
Wives tale
To describe what
From the castle
Down there in those Palms by the castles
Drink your blood
Will torture you
Realized the Sun
What is the people that hate life
People are from
The globalist hate that song
The sun will set you
Favorite
Just blowing
These people are literal
Right that's a really important
I remember Jackie there's about how
Renfield
And that's how we got
That's how
Right
AutoTrader
3 carb
Let me teach you this lewer
Choppa Choppa
It's like I don't even know how to unpack that in terms of like
What are you thinking literally mean
Play in this case
In this case what what extent mean is he saying literally meaning literally or literally meaning figuratively
Exactly like it does keep mean literally in the Sun
What's that
These people like Obama these people like
George Soros
Never seen in sunlight
They're literally like News-Sun
And they are literally going to drink your blood
Is he saying that cuz if so
This is stupid
Literally has the Ring of a man trying to
Convince you it is literally true talking figuratively that I guess you could say that
The sunlight is truth
Or something like that and drinking your blood is now your SNL
Making your life energy away Phelps
But I don't think
Yeah
That's what we're all about
I have drunk
Play Blood of several
This next clip is still hungover Alex quite a bit
This is after him screaming
I want to fight with Hispanic I want to fight with a Catholic to think I want to fight with the Muslims
Yeah
How to draw Scooby-Doo
Back
I cut out that part cuz
Constraints
I accidentally started the clip at a certain point in like I'm not going back for the rest of it
It's just one of them
This is my job this is my job job
Anyway the rest of this club is pretty hilarious
It won't matter call the stupid stuff they put between us
This isn't saying that if we all see the truth
Stupid s*** they put
You're doing Alex
Once we understand it was all done to us on purpose from a trip
You can break that transfer just like that
You decide
She's all about free will
About something
I'm not copying the matrix it's an allegory it's always been true
All I'm offering is the truth nothing more
Because once you realize the True Heart of this
It's going to change your world forever
You're not going to be able to just sit there calmly anymore and do for your bumbling life. About fantasy football where I can talk to
Your body's
When you hit the rock bottom of the situation
Going to get the billion miles you stink and things
There's no coming back from that
Your secret
Already in a Rabid wolf
Choice to make
Imallexx
Sincerity
From the rabbit hole
You're already
And you can be free any moment you want to
But you're going to go if you're not free when I get into that rabbit
Secret
You're already in the rabbit hole over
Weird
I don't even know what that voice is
It's gross in the world
Where am I
First of all that like I'm not ripping off The Matrix
Directly exactly
The other thing that I love is that like
Once you
Did you get a million miles you of everything
Well
Dirt bike games from the your perception
Alex you might
Think that you have a million miles you
Euro
Distrustful narrator
Secret
Set the secret
He can just be out of the rabbit hole
Allegory of the cave
Probably
The Stranger
He loves that
Is Billy Idol
Goodnight for
Alex
The secret is that a Rebel Yell will set you free
This next
Alex is talking about this Oregon shooter
People if they were Christian
They said yes he was coming
Taliban
Yeah that's always been one of those things
Add pops up
Whenever people feel like
Discussing a little chat about that
Evan Alex Jones
Says something
I think any Christian
Should be probably offended by
Any real Christian Wood
I would say this
Fort Worth
But
Is your why we were come back like doing something
Of course just to keep
Things calmed escalate
I'm being honest about lying here
News
Scripture
Start with Mark
Whoever is
Call Tristan
Generation
The son of man
Will also be ashamed
In the glory of his van
Interesting
Let's go now to Matthew 1033
Whoever denies me before men
And I will also
My father who is in
In heaven that was pretty clear
Pretty clear don't deny Christ I am not a Christian if you are
They made murder out of that girl
Columbine
She said yes girl
I feel bad that I don't remember her name
Super knotted to Christian propaganda
They made a really
This girl was
Cool
Felt so committed
Did Jesus
In the face
That is the idea of religion her Everlast
Sing reward
Where is Branson
If somebody were to have said no
Jesus
When they
The Pearly Gates
Would have said
No
Right now
I am not sure I believe in Pearly Gates
Religion is a whole lot in the Bible it don't you remember how
All the time
What I want to say is
You can tell a person by sort of how much they stick to their conviction
And Alex
One of his big convictions is the globalist the running the world Seeker
Another one is Vicky
He is a good Christian man
And
Religious conviction
In his car
Conception the way he presents it
Is one of the most important things to him
Defining
And the idea that he would so easily go against
Very literal
Very clear scripture
I am deny God
Just because he doesn't want to die cuz this guy isn't worth my honest
That's a great argument
Jesus said anything like that
Someone wants to hurt you wasn't worth telling the truth.
He said this guy Jesus isn't worth my
Basically what I mean spiritually
Commitment
Did you ever did you ever hear that one
And one of those is that that shall not lie
You are not a good Christian
Is that is your mind
You're hungover I don't know
But at the same time well when I'm hungover I definitely didn't about whether or not I would tonight
The other thing I loved that moment when you realize associative talk
About lying
I got a f****** fan
Well that's the s*** that Joe Walsh
Tweeted out where
At least he's honest about lying
Shut up you fallen so far as that
Eagles
So
We just got
Has not been dragged down by the
Who is without a win
Cast the first
So this next
Clip is
Alex is still hungover
You know the adrenaline of doing this show hasn't really helped out but he's found something else that might
Might be
Super male vitality
Brake Force
And some little mouse around here is eating my brain Force
Intelligent but open it up and it was
Envelope
Wasn't punching punching a steel door
High School
Furniture stores in Denham
Girls getting frostbite
Breakfast
Cake spongy
Is not minding the pain
Pain don't hurt
Weird
Superman
It's a little
If you're watching the video he's staring off into the middle distance
Sometimes pain is been part of you so long
Who's there
You're revealing a lot in this hangover
That's crazy
Both of you impress Girls by
High School
Telugu stories
Girls
I know his in the breakdown
Cuz he f****** banged out 200 girls before he was 16 so I don't know what's going on
Texas women
Apparently is all it takes
Everything is bigger except their self-esteem
Causing a lot of Texas I only went for half
Don't mean that at all because I don't believe Alex the story about it
If it were true is that many women
Deemed
The two lower
True
Bristol weather
Not Vegas
Boy
Beyond the humanizing of it with me like that really sad end
Old man
With
Joe Biggs
In order to impress them
Are you telling the stories on the show to impress his audience
With his masculinity
You might think he's been sort of made a fool of
You might think that
He doesn't be as another clip about people who have been made to look like fools
Russia
It's
This is part of a larger
Globalist operation
In the final
Prosperity and John
Got them taxes cut the spending
Call welfare folk start working stop
We did
The first
I know some people that it
Anybody throughout American History For Whom the
Prosperity engine did not work the first hundred fifty years of a country
Close-minded narrow Focus
Also the Great Depression
That's whenever it stopped I can't think of any reason why the prostate Prosperity engine so-to-speak was turned off
Could it be because it's
The goddamn
Yeah
And you know why the Federal Reserve exist
I can't think of any because
Before the Federal Reserve existed first of all the value of the market
Was so volatile
Everything was up
Stabilization
Before anyone could make their own money
People could just make money
The payback
With whatever
No it doesn't know it doesn't look very disorganized way to run a country
We will also be everybody
Redeemable at
Disney World
150 years of Art
Black people wearing
Yep
Women couldn't
Vote
And you can hear them
Yeah I was totally cool
Men and the family ruled the world
I'm children
We're forced
Into work
Prosperity
Twin slaves in children
The Chinese were forced to build the railroads
A lot of them died in the process
Without that's productive there was a lot more abusive foreigners than just that
Do you know
Might have had the best
Time
For the first 150 years of America
Weird
They probably
Yeah
It's weird
Weird I wonder if there's a lot of
White nationalist
Built
Around
Go back to America
And
The alarm talks about help because he embodies that sort of
Sing
Prosperity
Ignore criminal government look
Stupid government is way better
Absolute
Like quite frankly because we know what's going on with his mind
But this is taking a
Horse pro-russia
Like before sweetheart
And you might think immediately following the money bomb to write
You might think that I'm
Selectively editing
Staffing like
Oh he was talkin possibly about Russia before and I just
Was leaving it out no
We've talked about some
Pro-russian stuff creeping in
And now
It's just
The entire Tiger shows are about Russia
They're being good
And
I don't know what to make of it
Because here's the deal
We keep coming to New conclusions about what the f*** happened in 2015
Because we didn't come into this
With a like
This is what happened and we're going to prove that it happened
Went from
Fucktrump
To I loved her
17th and with each new piece of evidence that were finding
It changes the way we're looking at
Heimlich
When we found out that the money bomb was coming up right at the end of the fiscal year it became so clear that he's in finance
Cancel Crisis
He's a financial strain
He needs to try
Keep water out of the shower
Needs to bail some water out with that million-dollar money Bop
And we talked we thought like this is going to be at
Or even before that we thought
Do the first debate is going to happen
Alex is going to be like
And that was
I thought this was most
Two months past Trump
Now he's just article
Sleep Russia Kik
And I don't know what to do
I don't know what to think
To me I'm starting to think
Did you a little bit about that
I'm starting to suspect
That Trump
Is not as important
To Alex
As we might have been thinking
I'm starting to think that maybe
Trump
Was memes
To supporting Russia
Holyshit
Okay
And I don't know if that's
2 crazy
Alright
Vetting
Man I just can't
Hear me out on this
Okay I'm going to need way more than just
All the s***
Yeah yeah I am going to be more than all the s*** we just
Here he refused
Alex
Support of Putin
Clearly predates his support of
Yes true
So that's one
The people that Alex Jones
Spoken about already
In or invest
Navigation very positively
Who end up being involved with the Trump campaign
Jeff sessions
Who is clearly involved
With Russia
He's clearly involved with
The crime in general Flynn
Who is also involved with
Yes
So
Those are the people
But he has already spoken of as
Gyros
They're the ones who end up getting involved in
Trump's campaign
I mean I just don't see how that
Canby
Because
Straight up
Well if he's telling out America to support Rush
That seems a lot
Maybe that'll help
So
It
His primary objective is fighting these imagine Club
Yes
Right he believes the Putin is doing
He believes that Putin is
Essentially the only enemy that is against
The globalist international
Kicked out of the
Everybody thinks he won't go along with the global
Right
She can't outwardly support Putin
You can't do that
He can't turn his show into an out-and-out propaganda Fest
For Putin
But what
He would be probably
Subject to some investors
Well yeah.
And at the very least you would think
The Patriots
You like
Lovett or leave it
The same thing
So
I think on some level
Whether it's honest
Or whether it's sort of
Coerced by some sort of third-party
There
Keep spit balling like what could happen
And I recognize that this could be wrong
But the way my mind is looking at it at
Sickly
The way our speculations have gone right in the end
The truth is all of our speculations have been partially right
Yeah that's always possible never know
Just like the end of Clue
Everybody
Express
So the way my mind is looking at this now is I think there's a
Is a decent chance that someone behind us
Seems maybe someone whose name rhymes with
Rodger Krohn
Was convincing Alex
Is fighting
The globalist
But he is
Globalist
And
That Putin
And him are on sort of
Inasmuch as they are against
The globalist
Therefore Alex
Convince his positive feelings that he has about food
Call Donald Trump
Okay
Cuz that would be a much more
Acceptable
All of these narratives
Is it come from Russian media
Becky's clearly
Probably not get him
Afoul of
Presupposes that he actually
Does believe
His own b*******
In the global
Right
It's hard to say
Right flick if
Even if he does
Believe in the globalist
It is
Clearly an amplification
Should have that on his
There's no way you genuinely
Set the globalist
AR
Des
What
Expensive is the powerful honestly at this point I could believe
I could believe that no
He is this f***** up off
Off-air and
Miserable
Music complete
Conversely believe in
Amplifying it
Seaweed
I still contend
That with what I know of Alice
Which admittedly is nowhere near as much
So I could be missing the forest for the tree
I don't know
But
Is it to me if there has to be somewhere along the line
There has to
I don't diss
Agree I think there's probably some money involved
It's possible that could still be a piece
Could be things like we talked about with when Joe Biggs went to the Trump rally
They saw that there was a massive untapped Market
But do seem to believe in a lot of the weirdo libertarian stuff
Might just be more intrinsic
Be more like
This dude got a big swinging dick and I'm ended
Whereas Obama is
No control
No you're missing your missing tooth
Okay
The reason that the Russia thing is there for him
Is because he believes Russian media
He believed the stories that come out of Russian media about how
Putin is secretly trying to defend Chris and dumb
He didn't actually blow up these apartment building
I all of this
Eventually the good guy in
In Syria
To the strfkr thing because
There are so many anti-American
Medias
That it can't just be that he likes Russian media
Because their anti-American Russian media is really
Good
Like they are
Slick in their wealth
Yes
Most
Convincing propaganda Outlet in the world save for
Maybe ours
Pretty good propaganda here
Well I mean
You look at North Korea maybe their values are high but
They got a handle on everybody
Troubling
But I don't think that their propaganda is nearly as exportable and people on the outside or absolute
And it's very clear
With North Korea how much Kim Jeong Hoon
Kim Jong-il before him
Word
Where is
How is it not clear that Putin is an oppressive
Again I think it's that there he believes recipes
What I think that is a big part of it
Because we're seeing all of these narratives
They clearly are rooted in
Straight out of
Russia weather it be
Or that just Rovia
The source that we talked about the other day
The Russian
Infowars
So I mean of course you would see like
Is like like
You know that I see they're similar to me now I like them
I don't know
And I want to be clear I want to be totally clear
Hypotheses
Speculation
I'm not in any way saying that Alex Jones is or ever has been a rush
I'm not saying that
I'm saying
It's possible you're the liar
It turns out that the
Like we need to send a v FBI a hot tip
I'm if you investigate Alex the whole thing comes down
I'm
Starting to think
Maybe that's
True for the entire Russian investigation
There might be
Some Creedence today
F******
Masturbatory for me to say that is a guy who hosted Alex Jones podcast
I don't think that I don't think that at all the only way to take down Trump
He's with us
Alex Jones is
Incredibly
Unguarded and dumb
A lot of the time
We provide
24-hours of evidence of
Himself everyday
On the air
And it's all on
So I think
I think there are
Indications in clues that you can pick up from that
That you probably couldn't
From
If you have a question
Concession with somebody
It might not
Providers ruffolo
I've just put them in front of a mic
Over for 3 hours
Or just leave them to their own devices
And the whole system comes Crashing Down
These f****** douche
Out
Donald Trump jr. needs to get Alex and Rehab if you wants to survive
It might like
We hope
So if I can if I can say
To think with specially would like
I don't
I was just stretching my neck I wasn't
Know that the thing with the thing that crashed
Give me about whether or not anything will ask
Is what just happened with Tamara in Brazil he was caught on tape
Bright
Not being investigated for corruption
Literally you can hear him admit
Too bright
Right
But the Brazilian Congress
Just voted
Keep him as present
And because they need that
He cannot be arrested
Under those
Perry illegal charges
Do to me
The idea of anything bad happening
Donald Trump
Is
Entirely around whether or not our Congress
Actually gives
And right now I'm
I'm leaning towards no
I don't look like oranges
Fusions are going to
Protect us
It looks like we're f***
Yeah
What is like what
Like Dave
Today is just
Gotten
Grainger
He's just getting processed I think a lot of stuff going to move pretty quickly
I know but I think there's going to be a lot of
If you might accept a portfolio
Wasn't leaking well in the white house with a firearm
Well f****** of course I'm going to do it now I would not be too surprised if that was
Also I want to say that
Just because
I don't think anyone's necessarily pointed this out maybe someone hasn't haven't seen it
There's no
Goddamn way I would believe that Anthony scaramucci was not
F****** leaking stuff to cernovich and Alex Jones
Hundred percent
Stuff from him
So is walleye Crusade against leak
Is it crazy
Why do you think certain it's the truth with all of these people are against
Only what they're again
If it helps them
Even if
I'm against leaks except for the leaks that help me out
Right like it's always it's always the it's always the
Even though you do
F****** you guys are
That's
The operational
Play Books
Yeah
Freaked out a little bit
Cuz it's investigation is going into weird places that I did not expect it to go
I never would have guessed
That before he supports Trump
And months after
This investigation started
He would just
Violently ramp-up
The pro poop
Rhetoric
That's why
Especially knowing what we f****** know now
This is how aggressive Russia has been in there
Kompromat
Campaign or whatever it is intelligence agencies have come out and said on record
In Congressional testimony that they first indicated
Russian
Either Media or
Persuasion campaign
Which would be right around this.
I think that Alex is falling for Stuff
I think that is a piece of
Highway Bears out over the
Section of our
Investigation on August
October 3rd
He was just like
Never spoke about Putin again
By the police
Stop today
Not as much
It's a good idea to bring him up at
I was just reading about how he's not a poop
He's not pooping attitude comes or Worse threats like that
But the more
The more you protest too much
It's like
I mean
Every time he has to reiterate
He's not a puta
Is worse
Is the Trump Tower
Exact same s*** that they do
Hillary's 30,000 emails
Bright
Obvious
Pro-russia campaign that I'm dealing
People should be taught rhetoric
So you could immediately tell the what about
That that people use to deflect from
Argument
They're already off to the
Yep
Your house is not in order
F*** is going on with you
Your wild
Also
Does it still hurt
I hurt all the time
Pain just becomes part of you and you know what else should be a part of you
A visit
To our website
Dollartree.com
What's the word transition you've ever done in your entire life dad
I think I've done worse though I'll be honest
I can't remember.
A life
Visit to our website it's not the choice
Disagree with the president
There's a lot of
You can follow us for more great transitions go to iTunes
We just got another review
Sweet River review
Let us know how you feel about Danza transition game is tight
Also you cannot follow us on Twitter and knowledge under
Underscore fight or just knowledge fight on
Facebook
I can check us out over there
Got to do a long conversation with someone who
Entirely sure
Why not
Wheelhouse
Unverified Facebook account just like
Ideas about Alex's
Trajectory and I appreciate the,
Conversation
But also if you'd like to support the show you can buy going to knowledge buy.com quickly support the show button
You know anybody was got a business
Who wants to advertise
Message
We should we should really try Court some sponsors
How do you do that
I don't know
But if you know email Audible
Is why we're bad business you and idea anyway
F****** old ass dude
Googly eyed Muppet looking
What is
Decorations
Situations website
What is anamorphic
News.com
He also doesn't know how to hang a picture
And sells overpriced
Lecture series on CD-ROM
Go fuc yourself
Is it Rappaport
Yeah it's Rappaport
Sit-up
F***-you classic
Alexandra Thurston color