Air Jordan 5 sweat it
I have great respect for this knowledge B B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Alex
News on Wednesday of this week episode came out
That I was on of
I was very nice
To have a chat with her
It's been awhile since we've gotten
Sit down and talk for a bit
Yes you wanted to I have not talked about my mortal enemy Alex today
So yeah it's a it's a lot of fun nusret it was great
210 at the chat I didn't come out I will. Very funny
Comedian credibly Talent
We talked a little bit about how we met
I don't know if we met but the first time I remember ever seeing her was at a place called Jackson
Yeah a little bit about that
Good
Yeah I think the funniest thing about her for me is that
It is it is weird to see somebody that you know is
Is a small-time comedian you know
Coming up in Chicago and you look up to her
And then a few years later she's in a birdie commercial as be assholes
Yeah. That was an unfortunate week
Continues to spoil
What about the New York Times article
About us and
Thursday undue amount of attention paid on where we went
Reporter once a town
So it's delightful
Spot is a bit of a Twilight spots
The bright spot is my partner
She is going on a retreat
Set my alarm for the next 3 weeks
Get together with artists
Grown ups
Adults
And then
Just starting the s*** out of the woods and painting
Check with Toad on her lick
Lips
That's very cool but she's going to be gone
Few weeks the first time we've been apart for like
Years yeah yeah you're going to go nuts
Going to lose your s***
Great for her I'm around so
Obviously we can
We can hang a little you can move in
I can't do that at all this furniture
Is a gradual process
Applied for wellness checks with a little sure Flay every couple of days make sure I eat
How do wellness check but it'll be like binoculars outside of your window
Yeah and then we're fine
Sue Jordan today we have an episode to go over
Talking about
July
Which is the Wednesday episode
From this weekend
Big news
Yeah big news app
So we got to talk about it naturally Trump
Declared
Is bread
That didn't happen
Not good but there was some big news
I will get to it before
Looks like a little over to say hello.
Elmo robbery was awesome wasn't it
The name Alex itself is a red flag never met one who do me dirty thank you so much
Thank you very much
I heard you and Jordan on behind the Bastards about the rich
Eating Christianity and needed more of Jordan in my life Jordan don't stop
Screeching thank you so much
Sure
So thank you so much to a from Sweden says death awaits you all with nasty big pointy teeth you are now
Technocrat
Natalya brilliant someone
Sodomites
Has a Caribbean
I don't want
Jesus Christ
Jordan legacy
Okay well here is what we talk
Breaking live now
It's not that Alex started with t n a
Suburb of Atlanta Georgia the Georgia guidestone
Skyhigh at least a third of the satanic structure
Towards the left from the pull-down Monument monument and I will say that
Agree with whoever did it because we need that he will end up us there
What
Fashion letter
Mother's Farm
We need to be there to expose their plan
Reduce the world population
So this is dumb
The guide
Need to be standing for people to remember that they did exist and to keep a record of what was on them
We have TV
If I were Alex I also wouldn't be thrilled that someone bombed them but for completely different
Conspiracy world
These are super important as a monument for the globalist who built them
Specifically where they are so they would survive the coming
Cataclysm
These were meant to be a guide
Made for the Post apocalypse
What's a collapsed people
Who need to rebuild
Society in essence distilling down the lessons that we learned and weren't able to put in practice
Is before
We destroyed ourselves
Given that this is the point of these stones
It stands to reason that if someone would have bombed that it would have really provoked a response from the globalist
This will be no small matter for them
And when there is no
Swift devastating counter move
It's going to look really suspicious
Like no one gives a s*** really is going to be like
I mean
It's fate
Kidtastic the idea of the the conviction of the person who bombed
The Georgia guidelines somebody who really
Really believe me it's Satan
Yeah I guess so I guess
But on the other hand
Carved Stone
What do you have difficulty
Replace them
But so he's just he's just going to wake up the next day and everybody's gonna be like
Is interesting at their back
And nobody cares
One of the big mystery surrounding the Guidestones is about who paid to have them built
In the first place but that wouldn't even be an issue for they're rebuilding
The person who had them built using the pseudonym RC Christian gave the monument to Elbert County
Then it's become a massive tourist
Attraction
The motive for the county itself to rebuild them
Is pretty clear given that the
The bombing of the Guidestones essentially would be eliminating a thing to brought a bunch of Commerce
Did this otherwise not very interesting contact
Not much going on there but the Georgia Guidestones Obispo
Point Yacht
My feeling on this is a little bit mix
On the one hand
I definitely don't care about the Georgia
I think it's a very interesting thing that they were created and they Christian managed to keep his real identity obscured
Through the whole process although
Alex and the conspiracy
Community of decided that they have proof that it's Ted Turner
Property damage is a political statement is not really something that I have much of a problem with generally
In this case I think the political statements being made his hollow and meaningless but I appreciate that humans weren't targeted in
This one
I guess we got that to say for it
Can't go wrong there
Beckett's
I have my feelings getting a little mixed up
I don't necessarily have a problem with property damage
I do think this could be a scary harbinger of what's
Succumb
The celebration that's been seeing the conspiracy communities after this bomb and could easily translate to attacks being carried out on
Other imaginary globalist monuments and institutions
And I think a lot of those things are
Just be proper
So I guess my take is that it sucks that Elbert County residents are probably going to have their businesses hurt by the decrease
Traffic outside of that I could take or leave the guidestone
I worry about what this could lead to a zit
Feels like it could embolden
In the type of folks who want to carry out domestic terrorism against
Imaginary enemies
Overall I just feel like it's really sad
Adults acting like
This means anything beyond somebody blowing up a tourist
Attraction
Give me some kind of like
Spiritual importance is really embarrassing
And I feel really bummed out scene
Adults Pacific Northwest
Giant Paul Bunyan
Huge
Cuz it's cuz of the
The story of Paul Bunyan he was a big guy
Pickaxe
Announce not all that
This is like if somebody
Blue up Paul Bunyan cuz they were like if that dude comes back
He is going to lay waste
Easter this land
So we got to take
Tiffany's out right now make sensory
We don't even know what
Can't fight back against that we have to let it run
All week
We can take him down
Yeah it's like blowing up the world's largest pecan
GEICO roadside attraction is removed one
Ford and mile further down the way and I don't think like you should trivialize
Bombing episode
I might have some misgivings
About like bombing a Confederate statue
Or something
Just because I think bombing
Is generally be a little unpredictable
Yeah I mean I'm not a bomb guy
So I don't know anything about bombs but from what I've seen enough
Everything somebody tearing down a statue
Feels a little different than bombing something here's what I say
I say we can bomb any mom Newman
So long as it is moved
To The MythBusters lot further
They are the only people allowed to if they're still
Safety salute it'll be fun to watch
Alex has some details about this bombing that are not correct
You can see
Georgia
Stones English portion has been blown up
It repeats it in
But
12345678
Different languages
Sanskrit
English
Open away from face portion
English speaker that is angry
American
So Japanese is one of the languages
Make such a big deal the idea that the English portion got destroyed
And it's probably cuz
It's not true
The Guidestones include the same text
In multiple
They're four slabs of stone and eight languages
So they basically have one on each side
These languages are
English Russian
Traditional Chinese Arabic
Hebrew Swahili gindi in Spanish
Three of the four slabs remain standing after the bombing only one was blown up
And if you look for images of the rubble
It's very clear that the slab that got blown up was the one that had the message written
In Hebrew on it
Oh my God I was really I was almost like
Who is Fitz Russian maybe that has
Hebrew
That's a Hebrew on one side and Arabic on the other
Fortune because if he acknowledges the fact that it was actually the slab that had Hebrew and Arabic translations on it
Possibility that this was actually motivated by other maybe anti-semitic ideas come up
Prefer to ignore that because
Is it kind of come
2 closed
Touching on how his worldview and his characterization of the globalist
For essentially just based on a piece medic troops from history
No that wouldn't
Be good and definitely not in a story with the stakes of the Georgia Guidestones wouldn't be the way he wants
What's it like finally
Confront the fact that everything he does is
I don't know if there was any importance to which
Was blown up
What if it's
In the world we live in
We don't know
Yeah
It's the Hebrew 1
It's automatically suspicious
She's just got to where we are
Insisting it's the English one
Absolutely
I don't know
This is not really understand
These stones
Infowars.com
Local
Depopulate the human
Population
What a weird thing
Digital photo
There
And
Endorse this time
But I certainly understand whoever
And it's the middle of nowhere
Lavash
Side Road by cornfield
It was obviously blown up in middle of night
Appreciate
Guessing
About the motives
Yeah that's fun
We've been over this a bunch of times these Stones do not say to depopulate the planet down to 500 million people
The point of the stones are to be a guide to the population that live through an end-of-the-world type scenario where
Humantay to bottleneck
Advice to a new civilization
Which point the world's population will be less
Than 500 million
And the stones are just saying that they should probably shoot for about that level of population to maintain
A balance
With nature
Also bombing this Monument is not civil disobedience
You can agree with
Doing it or not but it's definitely
Vandalism at least and possibly to mess
Disobedience
It really does refute magic dominator
I think it would have to blow it up with a spell
Didn't see any debris
Are we did
Obedience is something like a city where you put your body somewhere and refuse to obey with Apple
Least telling you to leave or refusing to cooperate with
The police
Enable exit solitary and State
What happened in Georgia is a bombing
That's different
You know no-one was hurt
Yeah if you blow up a cop car that is not civil disobedience
No that is blowing up a cop cause a little bit beyond
Whether or not
You
Agree with the reason someone engaged in that Adam sure like I wouldn't have said
Burning of the police station
Last year I wouldn't have said that that was civil disobedience
That was taking a step in the right direction
I got to say
It is not consistent
I don't think he's sincere
Appreciate
Least
Verbalizing
But he doesn't agree with this vomit
That level this is not the right mood to make
Sympathize
Type of Foster
The process of doing this
What are we going to do when they're killing us to the poison shot
The GMO Foods
Cultural satanic
What are we going to do with it
And the New World Order
Bill Gates
Population
Talk about it exposed
They do that all the
Pretty much
Constant YouTube videos of people at the Georgia Guidestones doing like a look at that TiVo
Put something up in March of 1980 and have me believe there's any magic
It's a big part of Alex's like it's in endgame
You can't it's the beginning of everything
Reagan can't be president while magic is happening
Betty's powerful inside Stone
Also Alex is like really going
Pretty full-on into assuming the motive behind this person
Make an obvious
Leap
Do like well there's some problem with the
The conspiracy theories that surround
The Georgia Guidestones
Hard to believe that there would be another reason
Have to like
Recognize that there could be
Total and it could end up being some sort of a Neo-Nazi
Precise with this person you're making a pretty big
But you might not want to make
Later that might look bad
What I'm hoping for is that this has the wackiest possible outcome you know like whenever the
Impersonator impersonator with the I want that
That this has nothing
Things to do with anything other than
The frame somebody
Or just someone is
In the area and they had a bomb that accidentally lit and they just juggling
Black one with a skull and crossbones on the
It's like Mario with a baba
To go off
So we don't want
This is not a false
I'll tell you that
Early stages of ants never actually Target
The New World Order the gondola
This was a right
Monument being blown up
It wouldn't even be on the news
Totally
But because
This
Schedule Dish Dish
Obelisk
This
Colt marking
Population for death
Because this
Is a
Logo
Spiritual
They are going to go
Absolutely
Can't believe it
Yeah it's not a false flag be completely meaningless an arbitrary definitions that Alex had today
For what is a man
Are you busy easier for me to
Use as a story if it's not a false flag
Makes more sense
See no way that you can
Live in the cognitive dissonance of it being this
Harbinger of Doom that is
Put there by the all-powerful globalist
And also you can just f***
Can blow it up
You can't just f******
Blow s*** up
But nobody like you couldn't have just been like oh s***
Boom Jesus Is Dead solve that f****** problem like you can't just blow magic up
You can't have it be like this super important thing to the globalist have someone blow it up and then
There be no response would be over by now if any of Alex's work
Ordered the entire state of Georgia with
Begone
Just I just to get this guy
That would be it would be like if that somebody
Was it
We really were in The Book of Revelations
People had just been raptured
And somebody just shot the Antichrist and everybody was like
Oh s*** I didn't know you could just do that and then it was over
The guy would not have just been able to drive away
I don't know maybe a lot of Alex's ideology and worldviews dumb
Could be
So Alex
Gets real weird
Because key thing
This is like
It's not a false flag
I don't agree with this
But I like seeing a blow up
Take it upon himself to deliver a message to the bomber
Good excellent it's not good that safety
It's not that good
Call for desperate measures
But in the balance
Whoever did this
I would tell you
Probably watching
Disappointed
Encourage you
Bright bless you didn't hurt anybody
Y'all she chose the time to do it where you wouldn't hurt
And I
Out of character for my people
Stand Down
Weird
Strange
Thing to say about the proud boys who would that be
Stand up stand by as like that
For his call
Just be cool for right now I don't know
I respect you also his like
I'm not I'm not mad at you
I'm just disappointed energy
It's so infuriating for a bombing
Big a big dad energy
You listen you wrecked the car
It's it happens to a lot of people and I'm sorry it's a little bit different from
You
Blew up the Georgia Guidestones I get it we've all been there amongst us hasn't
He was without a bottom cast of the first bomb
Obviously
Alex is comfortable to being like
I'm pretty sure you're letting me you're clearly one of my audience
Alright
A boy
I think that this
She's probably going to be a case that will not
Take very long to solve
And what have you stopped
No additional
Think of it you'll be standing by
In prison
Before hurt for a while they released a statement from the mad bomber what bombs
Is it midnight that was a little bit weird
Concert with it LLC then
Chair face Chippendale
So
We got we got open phones.
First-time callers long-time collars
Disagree people
GradeSpeed
We don't screen your calls just have a clean phone line
Now we're hungry cable and tv stage
Can't have the
370 + radio station
Now which is
Almost
What he was
I don't think that's the case
That's not the Arc of his his
His popularity
We'll check back in on this at a later time but I do not think that that is accurate at all
Cartoon character that he's going to
Compare the bomber to and it is not the mad bomber
What Bob's are busy
It is not a great one.
I think you chose the wrong character
Georgia Guidestones blown sky-high
Was there this
Mater
Poured everything else
Well-done are they scramble around like
Bunch of chickens with their little
Satanic heads
Shut off
Find out exactly what happened
What's coyotes defining characteristic is his
He blows himself up and blowing up
What is the Georgia
No
No no
Eat the roadrunner
I don't know what that would have been metaphorically in this case
But yeah you wouldn't
You wouldn't compare
He does have Bob
No no that is
But he orders them online he doesn't like make them from home true and again
They don't work sometimes but even then they are very small and just turn his face black
Work ironically sometimes
30in that they are off
Running when there is no ground beneath
The other thing is that
No one
Is running around like chickens with their safety shut-off
I don't know if I've heard anybody be like
Oh my God what
Yeah one of the boar
Curaleaf
Notable thing
It is simply a thing everyone has noted
And that is it. Good but someone bombed the thing obviously but yeah
Big deal either
Kind of a notable events Meadowlands like this strikes at the heart of
We like the Georgia Guidestones themselves going up it was just a notable thing
They died today live
What if
A blue I'm up if anybody would if anybody
Would behave like a
Toon character in real life I think we know exactly who it is
So
Alex has a bit of a I guess
You know there's a psych meds narrative
About
The Highland Park shooter
It's been going around
Marjorie Taylor Greene
Thrones
Some business or at
And this is
Is extending now for Alex
Cuz we have
The
Psych meds
And also
That sweetgreen
Alex's
He's going Reefer Madness on
Remember
10 years ago warning Joe Rogan too many others on air bed
Weaponized marijuana
20 30 40 times stronger than what they used to be
Was linked to schizophrenia
New York Times
The dish new weaponized marijuana
The crazy people
I have known
Personally
Three people that worked here
A massive pot smokers who went
Crazy
Was a reptile alien
He still works
Another one thought we planted microphone to their office
Was Alton Bay office Jerome
Completely normal
Totally insane
Marijuana
I would I would argue that there is a real selection biosphere
Three people who worked at Infowars went crazy in it would definitely weed
Paranoid ways.
Very own brand
Lizard people hate someone spying on me and Alex's the devil
For somebody who worked at Infowars
To think that there were microphones In Their audience in their in their office or they
Little lizard person considered
Is constantly on the show
Regularly
Everyone else being the devil someone being like maybe you're the devil I feel like these are all just manifestation
Very normal paranoia that would be
Pretty normal in Alex's
Crew I would also say that if
Figures like Alex
And Joe are saying that
Recently
People I know have been reacting very negatively towards me
I think it's cuz of weed
Maybe you're an a******
Yeah also for Joe like
I mean some of his friends going crazy on the weed
I think that also has a selection bias
He chooses f***** up people to be friends with
Most of his friends have been hitting
The head repeatedly a lot
Yeah
Alex Jones
Used to not have a good filter at the people that he likes to spend time with
Also
I love the idea of The Joe Rogan
Has come out against weed while he smokes
Constantly on time during the show
His whole brand is we all
Smoke a lot of weed
Also you just
Went on my
Mike Tyson's podcast
I did mushrooms mushrooms
Gummies
Calm down
Call Mike
We'll see what you need to understand is that Alex has a reason
That he uses weed sometimes
And this definitely doesn't sound like someone has a really serious problem
I have tried marijuana
The longer is not ringing when I get
Time of the year
And about a year ago
People said well yous don't have the right strain
I tried to give her strength
Let me tell you some
The only time I've seen in my life
What's smoking
Marijuana
You Feel Fine Foods
And all the sudden
Really
Cialix
Many times but other times you felt crazy
So this is bulshit
No that's that's
I'm going to
Stop drinking by smoking weed here's what I need
To do replace one addiction with another
Yeah that'll do it really troubled times in my life has been the way I thought
My hangovers are too bad I'm in college right
Becomes more prominent
My way
But yeah
Alex has a
Adults
18 lb what a weird thing to happen perhaps I just replaced one
Compulsion with another
Yeah this is
Pretty
Dumb
Maybe not dumb but it's
It's the disordered kind of
Thinking that is it
I like it's pretty common among people who have a
I just can't handle
Watching commercials when I'm 15 that are b******* where it's like
If you smoke weed you're going to
Kill your baby and put her in a microwave or whatever and then be here 20 years later and have people
Still be saying that ship when it's f******
Legal sets
I think that Alex was a big libertarian
Smoke your weed kind of guy
Earlier
Because it was in opposition to the mainstream consensus that it's kind of becoming
Google and it's
Then I'm not that big a deal
Flipping and becoming a reformat
Missguided
End
Be a conscious effort
To be interesting
And I also think that it might be completely unconscious just oppositional defiance
But he has no access to he doesn't realize he's even doing
The 100%
I could totally see either of those because
In his personal life
He would smoke weed at the end of
The show
Or if some celebrity with any celebrity was around
What is it
Crystal meth
Couple times
Yeah we know that that's a good beach Behavior. Beach Drive
Not for Alex
Solo
This all leads to talking about how I crimbo Primo the Highland Park
Smoke that weed
Psychiatric
Whatever
Works
Whoa
Living on Cloud Cuckoo
Cuckoo
Wild who's cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs cuckoo for that Cocoa Puffs
That's what he was going for for the popcorn Cocoa Puffs to you didn't go for those big nugget
So Alex can't prove that cremo was on any psych meds
He's just taking
Comments for Marjorie Taylor Greene is proof that he was ignoring stuff with no proof
Mtg's a pretty bad Source on this stuff
Considering that just after the shooting
She posted a photoshopped image of cremo on Twitter trying
To push the psych meds Theory
These people have a king
Conclusion and Willy
Accept any fake evidence to support that
A conclusion they should be doing is gathering information and allowing to guide them to a conclusion
They don't do that because they don't care about reality
Their job is to
To distort reality so it leads people to their predetermined
Conclusion
Cremo probably was smoking a bit of weed
Sure
We all are
I'm not
I don't enjoy it no not much but still sometimes like no not really anymore
Edibles gummies.
Would be like
It's not like you'll be like all I can't believe anybody would do this or I wouldn't take this if I didn't
Feel like I sure sure
It's normal
Yeah yeah
But it's not
Eddyville
Because everybody loves
Drugs are great you know everybody loves it is interesting how Alex never talks about his speed
He drugged you
Eddie comes back from break and I think you might have had a little visit
Dr. toots
Send them up
In charge of a goddess
Great
Carlton knock out the park last night.
Break I'm out of here
Have a little vodka
Is Vibe was weird
Tucker Carlson
Comes back and
Clearly trying to build more conspiracy around the island park
Shooting
Now he's folding in Uvalde
Intuit as well
Predators
He's antifa
Are some of the postings
Where he did
Home screen
For you
Right now
Dehydrated
Supporters
America
Attacks of July 4th parade
Wonder
Uvalde a young druggie from a family
What limited means somehow manages to buy about 5,000 spaghetti weapons
Does David King
Family
Exclaims
None of that
Is anything Alex
Establishing any in any way
Address as the as of man or woman
This guy's that is definitely
Something that can be done seen
Mission Impossible
Yeah but it's also possible that people can be in the performance
And so our people can
I'll be
Yeah France
It's all possible
One does not purr
Preclude the other Alex is acting like there's only one thing I mean I just
It's just so fun
All all in services like
You are even pointing out like always there's this
What's going on
Family of limited means
Let's spend money a lot on
It's like
Pointing out all the red flags that should be looked
It's very simple that the problem isn't the s*** you said
16.
Preamble it's in the predicate
Stuff that he's saying that are sort of distraction are you
From
That
Is just stuff that is based on s*** talk yeah
Like right-wing should talk
Brutal so Alex
Skip back to the Guidestones
Some calls
And this is just not
This is not
True
Review
The Georgia guide
Headstones
This morning
So I don't want to be pedantic and I don't want to be a dick about this quarter
Of them were blown out there were four slabs of them was blown up
I don't care about misspeaking but Alex's setup 3rd
A couple times
And this is a problem because
This should be something that he's studied
He should be very familiar with the Georgia guidestone himself
Adverb
When he was going around at the stop the steal stuff you went to Georgia and they went to the Guidestones
He should know that there are for it
If he cares
At all
He does not
At the very least you should know Japanese isn't on any of them
I give my all
It's true all symbols that are English symbols
Might as well be hieroglyphics whatever
Anything that doesn't look like a letter is anything that's not one of the original 20
6 get out of here
So I just find that be a problem
Anyway the colors seem to have
Pretty consensus view on this
Brilliant
Actually a brilliant thing they did
Sent out some texts
And actually a few of them didn't know what they were
It is bringing
Thinking about
It's raising awareness
So this bombing is
It's good because it raised awareness
You know
Do you know what's
Interesting
Is
I think
This is
A terrifying thing
To Alex and
The far-right
Not because of any kind of like bad
Turbo back or anything like that
But because
If people actually start going after the targets
But they often
Sensei are focal
If they continue doing it looks long of the UN building or something even more esoteric nonsense
It's whenever it's just the weirdest s*** out in the woods
Do you know and they just start blowing up even more obscure s***
And nothing keeps happening
Fright eventually they're going to be like
I guess none of these were that important
Spray or you know there is a guy who bombed
The Georgia Guidestones
He gets in trouble
In the same way you would if you
Blew up
Something else just like a
Or whatever
No not some kind of day like
He gets the death penalty or it doesn't become some kind of a thing like
The awareness of the Patriot community in the aftermath of the Oklahoma City bomb
82 not that kind of
Scale no it's just
Treated as
The crimes that it is
I mean what if it went in Smash
The skull with
Call monitor whatever
And it's like this is a demonic thing that they
What did I do
I would be out of a second
I don't think that
Picture of me
The point is that's not what that's not a high-level card
Girl stupid
Is my is my overall I mean like
From
Be
Motivation to bomb
The Georgia guidestone
And someone showing up with a gun,
Or not really
It's not that big of
A gap it is
You know definitely one is a massive threat to Human
Life and safety 100
And that is very relevant
I don't really believe that there's that kind of a
Discipline
Abang Alex's audio
To show the kind of
Of concern
Person who bombed the guidestone
Absolutely
And I think that that could have the effect of making people take a lot more seriously
But yeah I think you're right
No it's
There are just other things that people are treated like it blew up a thing
Going to give you a fine if you go to prison for
A year or two years touring up a bomb
You're like yeah yeah
It could definitely be like
The devil be mad something bigger than like a six-month
Probation
Happy because the brain
Lisa in Florida Lisa what's your view
Point of view you don't want people to go getting violent and
I wouldn't want to see that either
So I get what you're saying but
I don't know I think
Because it gets
Talking
Gets people talking
Bad news
This is
I feel like this is rapidly getting out of Ali
Control
Well I think this is still within the Serta territory of what his take was
You know like this is
This is not something that I would encourage but the
After effects of it maybe
Something paws
Raised awareness of
Evil sure sure
And this leads Alex actually have like a little bit
This theory is
I know guns will you
So they can't scream it out gun
Military police
Nazi swastika
Yeah so it's probably local military police
Okay
So but I mean
Then is it okay if there's like a
Jesus statue in the middle of nowhere like that they put up
I think they would treat that a little bit
I think that actually would be more f***** up
Seriously
Religion around the Georgia Guidestones
And their imagination that is a holy site
You know
So in the my imagination that puts it on par with
In Texas there are like Recreations of the
The Easter Island
Yeah and
I'd be hurt
Yeah that would suck
But why you blowing up the Easter Island said what if there was some extreme Easter Island races
Or what if there's gold in those hat could be pause
You got a crack them open
There's candy inside
Monument
Total
Proof of what's going on
Amanda
Attention race
I'm not sure I tend to agree with you that
Blowing it up is not necessarily apposite
Russell anything else you like that
Yeah I just
Is my girl products
Miracle
Is America product take that X2
So it's not proof of all of evil plans of the globalist
Or whatever but
Maybe it isn't
The good thing
Fine
Things that someone should make a documentary about the Guidestones now and I would say
It's too late by the time you're done with that everyone's Eyecare
There should be another documentary made about the door
Go out there and show him and
Agenda behind
And promote the living
Most people don't know about
They're going to now
Boy now they do know
All about it
It's called
7 million people butt
How hateful is it
The bombs have been calling for killing 7 billion people
I'm just super racist
White supremacist
What do you think
Absolutely
Written all over they should probably aboard another 60 million
Children just to make this
You know what I mean
Well said
Very well said
They are just terrible it's Ark
Yeah it always comes at a weird time and you're like
Why did you even add that
Yeah
Well it's because you want to minimize the other very racist things
That job
Happened in your world and you support
It's Jews maybe they just blew up the
The Jewish would what a crazy think we I mean he's really hope that isn't the case eventually
Hope it's not the case eventually
Some very hateful Angela to this that you were pretending
Isn't the part of it
We'll see I mean I think until the purge
Person is caught
Until
There's more information it's a really tough
To tell if
This is just a simple conspiracy riddled mind
Who takes
Upon themselves to blow up
Effigy
Aviva
Or if there is
Some meaning to the
The fact that it was
But Hebrew what I think they want to do in order to catch
This guy who's clearly a match
I think what they're going to need
To do
Is
A sting operation
They're going to have to build their own Guidestones in maybe Iowa or something
It'll be too hard for this master criminal to resist
He's going to help make another 40 years
It's worth
Nerve
Right away
Come on Duke
Amazon
This show
25 minutes
Wow she has been exposing the statue of War threat of nuclear war
Everywhere
The Georgia Guidestones
Georgia
Dog weird to live in this imaginary world where Congress
A big
Deal
It is such a big deal that you have a congress member on your show and you open the interview asking
I think there is a way actually if you were a sincere interviewer to ask the questions they called me because she
District in Georgia
Kind of relevant to her
But it's it she could be
Anywhere still open
Hey that would be could be the
This is a Nutty thing
Introduce each other this is somebody's in Congress
And this is her take
Boise
Around
The world a shot heard
There in Georgia
Thank you so much for doing something about January 6th
Economy will talk about
What is your take on the Georgia Guidestones getting blown sky-high
Appreciate about you
As you bring up the issues that a lot of
Regular normal
What you being sarcastic what just happened there
Research
As you know like you
Completely
The globalist
Agenda and again
Population
Control
I just heard the news
Probably about
2 hours
About about
And I
I think it just shows where we are today
People are done with globalism people are not going to go along with the new world order the liver
World Order
What does the difference between this is a symbol of the globalist people are sick of the globalist
So yeah you're good blew up this symbol of evil
F*** man Congress this is nuts
Yeah
Yeah like what like what next
Blow-up blucifer
The outside the temporary Airport
Let's go let's go
Dig underneath
Spaghetti
That be fine with me honestly
If instead of blowing up the Georgia Guidestones they were like f***
We're going to do it and they just got a s*** ton of machinery and literally dug beneath the Getty and found nothing
That is not going to help
Because the demons that are under the Getty only are like
Spiritually visible
Is trolls still be there or down there no
Marjorie brings up the 4th
For July shooting
And she said something really dumb
The July 4th tragedy
Is heartbreaking
Imaginalis
It's that there was an entire month of Friday
Braids
And festivals and drag queen story time
Christian nationalist
Shooting
Braids
The 4th with her hashtag
And in terrible language against our Independence Day on July 4th
Is Margaery pretending not to know about the 31 Patriot front members who arrested
Sit in the U-Haul truck heading to riot at a pride event in Idaho
It wasn't in the US but in Oslo two were killed in 10 injured in the attack on
Lgbtq
Tiki Bar
Just before the pride parade was set
The begin
Is Margaery pretended not to know about these suspicious pattern of drag queen story time events that have been targeted by groups like
Proud boys
Disrupted with
Violence and
Threats and specifically events that have been posted about and promoted by the lives of Tik-Tok account
Or how in Baltimore two separate homes were the target of fire attack
Because of their pride decorations
One of them having their pride Flags
Specifically burned
Or what about the
Bi-State violent over 250 anti-lgbtq bills
Being introduced by state legislatures at least 24
Which have already passed
Marjorie can come off it with this
S*** he's just making a ton of assumptions about the Highland Park shooter in his motivation
Hyatt order to make herself more of a victim in everything
Match he's pretending that he coordinated an escalating
Intimidation and violence
Directed towards
Just didn't happen
Also do not forget
This is a member of Congress
Who just said maybe the bombing of the Georgia Guidestones as part of a war between Good and Evil
Picture of the Highland Park shooter
In order to push her auntie medication agenda
She's a piece of s*** who should not be taken
Seriously
On any level
Any level
Well said
Thank you
Much like that color for curly hair
Exactly like that, she can f*** off
Anyway she has some demands
About the Highland Park shooter
Robert Kramer
And this guy
And I started demanding it immediately
Release
He doesn't get a ride
We should know
Exactly everything
His arrest record
Hospitalization records we should know
What drugs he was on recreational drug
We should also know what
Prescription
Ssris
You can see the sky
Clearly messed up
You see these are the rule of law people
Super concerned about people respecting a lot also a very serious concerns about privacy
That's why Marjorie doesn't seem to care about determining they Primo is
Guilty before he's been tried
He treated as if he were guilty
Before being proven
Incel
He's guilty before trial to her because she believes that there's some utility for her in Act
Sing that way
She doesn't give a s*** about the fundamental rules that our country operates on this is all just a
VR games
To her
I let me explain the game that she's playing here
MTG knows that these records aren't going to be released
Or at least there's a very low chance that they will be immediately
So she's setting herself up to
To score points
Pretending that this means that these records are being covered up
He's talking s*** about something that she knows is a non-starter because it allows her to
Do basically nothing and act like she's some kind of intrepid
Truth-seeker
The second reason she's doing this and it's just in this needs to happen now
Is because she
Keenly aware that our audience has a not exist
Send a tension span
As the investigation progresses and
Gets the point where cremo goes on trial
A lot of that information that she's after will be readily available but by that point
Her followers won't
Care at all
Not even a little bit of moved on to being mad about some other thing that she's pretending to be on a crusade about so that
Station at that point is of essentially note
Used to her
She needs to make as big a deal about this as possible now because she won't be able to use it for anything later
If she G stands about this idea that he must have been on psych meds now she's after which is
Is the demonised med
And it won't even matter if she's right or not that
Cremo was on meds
Even If eventually it does come out that he wasn't on any it's still won't matter because all her audience will remember
Is that she made a big deal of how suspicious it was that you wasn't being given access
To all of his personal information
This is
Trick and people who play games like this they can't be trusted to be in positions of public influence
Also let us not forget that her underlying premise is also incorrect
I thought there was no causal connection that they can demonstrate
Gene psych meds
And carrying out shooting
In fact
A prospective study published in the journal of clinical psychopharmacology
In July 2021 sought to look at the connection but
Psychiatric illness
And my shooters
They looked at 35 Mass Shooters selected
Because they were the ones
In this database of 115 Mass shooters
Between 1982 and 2012
Who had survived
After their she has much more of like availability of information about
A nation was
Between 1982 and 2012
People who had killed four more people with firearm
They found the 28 out of 35 had psychiatric diagnosis
Forehead non
Have three there wasn't enough
Information to tell
From the results
Their analysis
None of those diagnosed
The psychiatric illnesses were treated with my
This talking point
Marjorie have is b*******
And it causes harm to people who need
Mental health care
Makes people
More reluctant
To seek
Treatment
And get the
Help that they need quite frankly
Monstrous
She should be very same for selfies doing actual
No there's
There's
I mean there's really only to like
She makes a lot of money doing nothing
With a lot of stuff
Well yeah but
Just just
Taking a lot of steps
To do nothing
And then it's just
A f******
It's a celebrity trolling
Demonizing psych medication
And doing everything to protect guns
You are why mass shootings happen
I mean it's the exact same thing with like the you know we talked about
I think was on our last episode with the unfortunate and tragic case of the migrants who would match
Policies that Alex seeks to
Put in place make incidents like that more likely to happen inevitable
The policies that Marjorie seeks to put in place
As it relates to psych medication would make people
More likely to not get
The kind of treatment that they need and make
The possibility of
The violence whether self-directed or outwardly directed more likely to happen.
It's f***** up
Yep she's just talkingshit it's just somebody who's kind
Patrolling with the
The troll damage
Serious
Congress
Yeah
Yeah I mean
You can't
Reasonably not know
This information by
You can I think it's unlikely
And I think
The studies and stuff
The information that she would be having to be relying on our things like
Stuff produced by the church
Church of Scientology
Glow like
Yeah you have to understand
At the foundation you're standing on his flimsy
And that means
What's that
You know
Don't give up
I think that it
I was mentioning earlier
They have a conclusion that
Seeking support as opposed to looking at information and letting that lead to a conclusion
It's me it's backwards
Well I mean
The problem I feel is that they
He's done the truth-seeking and now they're deliberately lying to
I think that is Jen
Generous of you to assume they went through that much of a process
So Marjorie sucks
And and we know Alex
We know that it has led
Nearly 100%
Beastmaster shooters
And they may be a combination with recreational drugs
Other serious issues
But also know obviously
It would not be
The full story to say that everything is
Perfectly fine with
With the state of medication
Obviously there are
People who
Should have access to medication who do not
Whether it's Financial reason Insurance reason
There is that
There is overmedication in some sectors
In some meds
The Profit motives
There can be a little bit of searching for help with your bariatric
I think there's a widespread awareness but maybe there could be more
Have the dangers of
Falling off medication and abrupt
Police stopping taking it
These things are real
But they're being some of it is being hijacked
Yeah no stopping your medication rupley is more dangerous than not
Taking medication
Probably
I don't have to quantify
Cuz you kind of have to like
I can't counterfactual I mean a situation is very dangerous
It should not be done outside supervision
We are
There are there are legitimate things but these aren't conversation
Cuz they're having
They're having
We're willing to watch
People die
Borderline everyday just because we get our
So I think Alex has realize that when he trolls everybody talking about how Marjorie
You should be present
Gets a lot of attention out of
Course I'm so he continues on that game
You're really the example of what they
Everybody sees that
Trump DeSantis
In the system
I think you would be told better
And be a better candidate for president
Would you take a VP slot with either one of them or
You're just a smarter smarter than both of them
I do believe that's true
MTG president here
I honestly don't think that she would pull
Well at all no
She wouldn't be in Congress if she wasn't dead Republican
Plus
Yeah honey whatever I District
Opposed
Tigris Atlanta have
I just like crazy and
Incumbency
I advantage
Which is
Crazy by the grace of God let's say in Congress
I don't think that you would run well
And the moment
People started listening to her talk
Oh man
Made a lot of assumptions about Trump
Bing
Some people like people who talks
Oh no they do they love people dancing we underestimate that a little bit and that you would have a lot of mileage in that
Sure but I mean even Trump
Didn't say like
You know the Georgia Guidestones it's okay if you blow them up because their source of evil
She said that sort of diplomatically
That's what you said
MTG
President baby I love his
F****** brown-nosing for no reason other than just to do it like she'll talk to him
You should be present cuz she'll talk to him
He's totally being serious
Do you want me to back her right now
That's what he wants to
I just say we LeapFrog the whole time
We can't really do that but
Speculating
About that but you know people
Like both of them for a lot of games
Juno
And he should run for
For president
Yeah Alex
I get that you had yourself a little bit with the Strategic flexibility
What about you had a global exclusive
Yeah you don't have a global exclusive on a maybe he will maybe he won't
You are claiming that he will it's a lot easier to play this game after the fact when it does now
Congratulations on being wishy-washy
I feel like that's just lazy
Yep
So marjorie's out
Off on her way to run for president
No doubt and Alex has a weird sales pitch
Show me project
So busy.
Order for project
Hoverboard at Roosevelt month behind
I have spent
Literally 56 hours a day just trying to get the
I just noticed
But man
What you need
Just get the product
We have delivered so much we have done so much together this is the Tempest. We're so close
What you need the products we've got
What I can do
Broadway
I can get out of here
About plugging
I didn't worry about trying to unmask
Tour I am out of
Important point
Put your phone in there
You cannot piss in their face better than spread the word about Infowars
Infowarsstore.com School the big July 4th special running right now for a few more days at the 75% off.
Low cost
It's really it's really interesting cuz I think that
There may be some truth
To that there is no better way to piss in
In the face of the globalist then promote Alex's because
They only exist as the
Cobra to Alex and whatever you know
Batman imaginary bad guys the rise up against
So yeah the only way to stick it to them is to
Funded the imaginary opposition to the like no matter what I do
I will never be able to stick it
To the Captain Planet villain
No
Unless
I lost the site
Captain Planet kind of like an augmented reality game
Microtransactions but there you're buying Alex
Cuz pills
Yeah I imagine it's the same kind of psychological a dick
Shinto
Terrible
Yep wow I don't think there's a lot of irons in the fire either
No I think he's got a lot of irons that are getting burnt
I could do with so much money I love this notion
Into this like
Back in the day I didn't have to worry about plugging
Really you certainly still do it a lot back then
Back in the day
But you didn't have to worry about plugging your worrying about it you're just doing it for fun
Cuz you're doing it a lot still
Stopping time
We have gone back
All the way
Y2K my friend
Scatter Marjorie leaves
And
Thought
Biggest thing is the Bringers of death
Jeff are allowing China China and Russia
And Iran are going to hold
Military drills
Down in South America
Make sense
You can allow them
One of these days here
Absolutely
Look like we are in the middle of it
This is communism
It's the worst communism I've ever seen
Really
Look up anything like
Why communism
Late-stage capitalism
I also thought that
Chinese land invasion was supposed to have already happen
Based on Mike Adams
Fiction
IAAI
I'm really struggling to understand
What do these people believe
Will happen
If Biden allows China to attack us
Like
Okay fine
You believe Biden will allow China to attack
What is that look like military
Are you really trying to tell me there's going to be a land War in the United States with China
There's going to be a Normandy Beach
Well I just going to be at South Carolina
Quit wrong OSHA
Stacy managed to Jamaican
Through Point Beach on Normandy because they didn't have
F****** drone Automated machine guns and also bombs that could be flown from anywhere
I think this is unlikely but
Again it's a caller talking
That is true
So here we are
So you get back to the Guidestones
Caller actually has a really
Good point
The Alex realizes a good point
In the middle of this collar bring it up
And it should have been
Something that Alex thought about already
My view about the guides
Opposed
So what was chiseled into those Stone
But we all have a right to say anything we want
Call no no no no no
Just for saying s*** dammit
Constitution is toilet paper to me remember
Does constitutional
Afforded to every citizen should be waived entirely just because I'm willing to say that
One person obviously it will never be turned around and used on me. Here's the good news
But
Realizes that this is a dangerous point for him
Because he's this free speech Warrior absolutist
Course but this color doesn't know what he's talking about
So we have a right to say on privately-owned stones on it
Privately-owned land
Property rights
And Amendment
What's the First Amendment
Protect
All American to go onto private property and destroyed
Privately
I agree with you
Take a note
Guidestones worked on private property
RC Christian gave it to Elbert County so that isn't private property sent its cover
Owned
It's very all that would have been needed to take down the Guidestones would have been
The County Commissioners getting
Petition
And following some legal channels to get them removed
That never happened because they were helpful in terms of bringing visitors to the area which help local businesses
Care enough to try to get them removed
It's interesting that these people don't really understand Free Speech Dynamics
Either side of the coin
This absolutely
Could have been speech that would be subject to censorship
Because why
Because only lunatics think that it's some kind of an evil satanic
That's why someone had to blow them up
Because they couldn't get their way through the appropriate channels
That's really what happened
Again
You can't
Just f******
Comptroller your way to defeating evil
Okay if you could just be like hey okay we've got 15 votes so
Evils taken away then it's not really that evil
Right
I mean like this this this is something that if it was
A problem for the local community
Any of any point
Who's actually good for
And in the ultimately yeah
I think they should leave the rubble Epix
Because that's going to up the tourism even more honestly they should just
I don't know rebuild them but like imbue them with magic or something they can have a
The new conspiracy theory bombing
By the globalist cuz they forgot to imbue that purr
Particular tablet
They blew that one up and then they
Took it all.
Demolish the whole thing
But
The bomb itself
I took out that one naturally
So you're the dumb caller
I want to talk about how the human race saved life on
Planet from
Tropic CO2
Depletion
All right cuz
Planet
And literally
The old fossil fuel
What's fun
Man can't we all just be like
Okay
Whatever you believe about climate change
We just got to let oil execs not be
Be there anymore
You know like they they're your ideas
Lying there f****** Paco
With billions of dollars
Whatever you believe that's fine
Look at the billions away
From them no no no and then we can put it towards
Anything you want that is not America take it away from them
Blowing up something in a private lawn
Anyway here and
This is really kind of
Exactly what we've been talking about is the
Sort of danger
Of
The blowing up of the guidestone
And
Also
Wouldn't
Really
Change anything
I think the only thing that could make me
Satyr would be a
Somebody
Somehow gets into the Grove and take some moloch
Before the average treat this
It's July
We went for no violence but it's
Terrible idea
I know how I really
That would really
Today
I am I pretty
Joking around
Hey guess what is private property
I was bringing up
I mean this is the kind of conversation that is inevitable
To be had in these
Groups
And that is like oh yeah let's
Take down more
Like I said the thing that I eat is worrying is
It will not
Have the discipline
Generally not hurting other
People
This is LARP
Except larpers know their LARPing so they don't
Actually shoot Fireballs at each other with like
Flamethrower
You're having a good time
Haha
This doesn't
Fireball
No real reason to know the dangers of this stop with EPP
One person who he inspired to show up at Bohemian Grove heavily-armed
Like him he should know the danger
Yep and that's why I would have
Preferred if there was a more full throated
Condemnation of his bombing
Not some kind of I respect you
Standby I mean that's crazy
This is dangerous it's
I've been a little bit
Flipping you know because I don't care about
Georgia Guidestones
Yeah but at the end of the day I do worry that the way this was handled
By someone like Alex is only going to lead to more
Potential
So far the world has not
Art stores
DF
So whatever you see something that makes her go but also has a bomb
That means that there's going to be something probably later that makes you go Ohno
Yeah
I hope every night
No problem
I'm scared of Bob
They're not dead
I just
You know I just don't understand why you would hold and explode
Real real explosive
The carved faces on Saturday of the mountain to make presidents
Explosives that is
Is it true you are not wrong what if you're trying to cross grape
Lots of space in the short amount of time you can blow up nuclear bomb
Bomb
Just fun
Yeah those are Fun Time Explosion
Fair enough
Will you come to the end of this and
Guidestones are gone
And Alex's
Is this A happy and
Marjorie Taylor Greene sucks
Let me tell you how little I've paid attention to the Guidestones
I genuinely thought they were like well I mean
Still got three
And they just left them up I think that
If I recall
You didn't know about them
Before the show
You learned about them on one of our Epic
Today like I thought that when the guy blue on them up they were like well wishes
Clean that one up and
Decided it was too much of a structural Danger
Absolutely
It's not really
Front and center of anyone
Midas maybe the Elbert County tourism people
He's going to have to go for the wrist
Yeah you got to pick up the spare
No way
See how this resolves though like when they catch the guy
Or gal
A person
What their motivation was
What kind of
I hate Stone
Yeah it's Rodger Stone it is a stone it's a
Yep yep
Yeah we'll be back on Monday Jordan
But
Creamy summer is going along again for their generosity
Support of the cause
Ice cream updates on there of course there will be more I don't want to speak
Specifically yet
But they're exciting things
On the horizon
There are irons in the fire that aren't I
Oh no but thank you all
Yeah so we'll be back
Website.com
We're also
We are on Twitter that analogy underscore fight not go to bed Jordan up will be back but until then
Dzx Clark
I hope you all have a wonderful dreamy creamy summer
And now here comes
What the sex roll
Alex