Air Jordan
I have great respect for knowledge b b
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
Exit
Alex Jones
Jordan question for you sir
That would have been fantastic
Tweets about 10 or so so I figured I would
I will try and get it out in front of it
It was good tennis morning in reality my bright spot is over this weekend
Made a rare public appearance
Able
To I was invited to Jared Holt
Sweating friend why do Jared Holt
Next time
Play I've not been
2 wedding anniversary long time
I also
Lockout
South it was a nice time
False
Always nice to
60 people in love
What are you laughing
I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry there's nothing funny about that it is always nice
My bright spot is yesterday
At the airport and I was later on
She landed
Or the landing is good I like that everything was fun
All the magical spells I kept to keep her here they are there only proximity-based
No she's going to care after this but they also maybe these spells I helped
Airplane lamps
You know
It was it is interesting
Because it was basically like that say was the
Closest I'll get to sending
A child this summer
Okay do you have all your stuff is everything packed and ready are you going to be okay don't miss me too much
You know that whole thing do you have an emergency number solutely absolutely I'm ready
She's happy having a great time and I'm alone
It's good news
For everybody
Hey alright
Today we got episode
To do
Situation in Sri Lanka
Naturally
We've got the obvious estimation
I got to be honest
Sri Lanka are not countries that are that important to Alex
In the past
It is not been
Major
Movers and shakers Within globalist
2 conspiracies
And I don't particularly care what his take on
Any of it is at least I'm not like
In a Mad Dash
Do Define
Yeah I'm fine without that
Yeah I mean what are you going to say it's all an attack on the globe
Probably I mean
I think the only interesting thing I would be
What's his take on the homemade
A gun
Oh that the adjuster with homemade guns are those against the rules because they
Take money away from honest hard-working
Gun manufacturer
Think that his take would have to
I think I've heard him talk about like 3D printing and stuff
He has to be in favor
Because otherwise you would be like
Making a commercial necessity for the existence of your right to
Defend yourself seem to be the case
Craft a spear out of a stick
For self-defense yes you can buy
A sword or spear you can make a shiv sure
I spell this is the second event that is an interesting conversation that I think the Supreme Court will
Eventually
Undoubtedly is coming soon
It turns out
I may I made a little bit of a
So
Boxcar Willie Nelson Mandela effect
Me a message
I don't know I don't have a ride
Person
How's it going every name on there so
But
They reached out and asked
That
We do an episode
For their son's 18th birthday
Naturally it was
June 23rd
That was
Yesterday
I mean
You're recording this
On June 22nd
Nope we're going to do this we're going to pull it off then we recorded I don't know when it'll be released
We're not we got to own up to it
Reach Out
Plenty of time in a tree
Maybe too much time in advance
And I said I'll make a note make a note about this
It's your son's 18th birthday and the council cannot say no to people who ask
I'd so I did make
Make a note and
I lost it
I also told them
Time to send a message
Tips to remind me which they did
Control
Did not see the message
But hey we're only a couple weeks
Let's just remind everybody it is just the two of us in it that means you
That means it's just
Yeah
And sometimes
Email
Sandboxes
Are completely destroyed
Them
We're late
But I want to wish you a happy birthday to Boxcar Willie Nelson Mandela effects child
Of course
Say a very excited that you're going to register to vote
Very very fun
I wish you the best
Don't buy a gun
I'd so
We had a request
To do this episode about the day that this child was born
I am so this would be June 23rd 2004
And
That is what we're doing today
Happy 18th keep them someday
You turned a team just in time for Jules to be outlawed
Welcome
So this episode is actually pretty
42in
It's interesting that this was randomly
Chosen episode based on this
Because
Stuff very much worth
Sure I'm so I'm excited about that but
I would like to
Give a happy birthday message
And the only way we know how
Jimmy someone life is giving someone death
You can say that
Life is death
Happy birthday
Let's
Begin here on June 23rd
Here is why
This is
A fortuitous
Episode trust a cover
Maybe coming on the show
He of course is the father involved in the Ruby Ridge standoff
Yeah whose wife and child
Jaguar killed by by the government
Also
It's just a
B of A
Nutty guy
It's too late
It's kind of difficult sometimes
To disambiguate
The tragedy that happened
And the mistakes
Egregious mistakes
In some respect
Text that were made by the government in terms of carrying out
Thing
Also just
Not a one of those standoffs
It's usually not cuz you're in the best place
And then when the government murdered your family that usually doesn't like improve things
So there's a lot of can argue that a lot of really shity stuff about him
You know obviously there's the
He was hanging out with the Aryan Nation
Compound butter
Illegal weapon
That he
Was probably
Deeply anti-Semitic
There's a picture of him
I bet you
Can find where he's wearing the shirt
Potatoes
Just say no to the Zog Zionist occupied government obviously
Geology of that just
Defies
Killing his wife in
Yes family thing is the real problem here
Like I get he's a racist piece
The s*** but don't murder his family
Do you eat from my understanding of in my looking
Sing into the
The events of that standoff
It's not like the government came in and there were like haha we're going to kill your family
A lot of
Worst case scenario situation
That ended up
Spiraling
Handwriting
What happened
People who did
I'll kill people should be off the hook
It's not as cut-and-dry as the
Murdered
These people
To portray it premeditated murder
We've talked a bit about the the Ruby Ridge situation and past episodes
And so I don't want to do
Too much on it
Halo
Talk about this
For half an hour
But
It's
Wild
To see Randy Weaver
Appearing on it
Infowars that's not something that I was aware
I didn't know that he was
Like somebody
Who would go on Infowars and Alex were acquainted
I guess I could have assumed that in
On some level
I don't know if I've ever heard like I knew that Alex had worked
Early on in his career
To try and help rebuild the Mount Carmel Church
The Branch Davidians
But I don't know if I've ever heard Branch Davidians on his show
Right I knew that he supported Randy Weaver and
The ruby-red Scituate
Is obviously a catalyzing and radicalizing moment for a lot of the right-wing
I didn't I did
Didn't know that he ever appeared on
Surprise I was it did he did Randy Weaver make a ton of
Media appearances
Following like
I mean like
Afterwards for sure
But like over the years did he
He continued to have that
I think he probably did make a
A number of them but I
It assumed that they be like
An ABC documentary about
Not 26
Surprised
I'm surprised
To hear my divorce because I think that his standards would be higher
Ono Island
Just not a great place to go
But I think that the reality is that
This interview is most
Happening
Cuz
Randy Weaver's got
To work
He does mention
The next stop on his book 2
To work
A Mexican restaurant on
Some Highway outside of Austin
Play Castaways it's in Texas
Can't figure out which one it is cuz there's multiple of the time I restaurant on that Highway
I do spend a bit of time trying to figure out take a left at the but it's the one with the corner
Got the mountain on it not that McDonald's it's basically that
An appearance at this makes
Chicken restaurant
Going to give a speech
But he'll answer some
And then everybody's going to have a nice day
Okay
And then also I guess calling
Morganton Ford
I'm surprised to her was not so successful that I found out about
Because this Mexican restaurant situation
Something's very promising towards it's her the career
I think
Book Nevada Mexican restaurant
I get some
I can get to the burrito and here about 2
I ran it open my got of a Mexican restaurant for a long time so yeah I've been there buddy
Didn't go out
Didn't go well
I went to this because I didn't either I've completely ruined the surprise that he
He does end up showing up
Because Alex is trying to get him on
He does in fact
Appear
Wildside
I'm over selling
It's
There's a couple things that are like what
Wild might be
So Alex is mad at abl
Good you'll never guess why
What's my name
Yeesh
Camera reviews
People I mean
That is
Is an interesting way to be like we don't want to be anti-Semitic
Ozark cast
Obviously I mean no the part where I
The part where I was making wait no
Anyways these people
Oh boy yeah that's that's a mess
And then the other thing too is that like
The obvious can play
What's going on is
Shameful
What is mythica
Complaint is
The Texas GOP part of their platform is this
America is a Christian Nation
That is
Troubling
For groups
Spit or non-Christian
This country is about us not you we own this nation and we allow you
U2 live here
Exactly yes
Conflating that with the ideas
Things that you're Christian
What is antisemitic
Which is not at all what anybody is
Is it starting
He's using this sarcasm in order to create a straw man
To argue against because I actually position
Any actual complaint
It's being made
Ate something that he acts
He can't argue with
No no I mean
The fun part is that just because you say something in a sarcastic
Tone does not mean that you are also admitting that it is true
You know like
Oh
I liked
To see the sun outside
Like no you do why I don't understand why you're being sarcastic about that you don't like
Jews thank you
One of the things that I think you're going to see and I noticed
Descendants episode in particular is it was one of his like
Major rhetorical Tech
Is this sarcasm
Being used
To create a straw man version of an argument
That he
It's the only way out for
There's no other real taxi
We can use
Covers of story this is one of the big stories
Of the day and I honestly think like
It's alright this is an annoying
But I do
Really know if it is
Like Alex thinks this is
Police state
River
Riverton Wyoming
Carnival
Peter
Determination
So
Look I mean obviously if you're camping in Yellowstone
Or a lot of national parks
Leaving food out
Is dangerous to other
People attract bears
Yeah and other animals
That could
Cause harm
People in that swai
Seriously Alex can minimize the
She left out marshmallows but
Like you could get someone to
It's something that
There's a reason that ruhligs
Just that but it's just like the very basic level of
Engaged with
The world that you live in it you can go to
To the Yellowstone National Park
Carelessly throw away food as though it's nothing
Then
The f*** you
You know
You go to jail
F*** you
Yeah and that's the reason there's a fine
Real situation is obviously some there was some
Sort of
Miscommunication
And somewhere
Something happened
Where to pay the fine
But it didn't go into the system or something
Clerical error of some sort
She went on a cruise
Saw the warrant when she came back
And now the judge is apologizing to her
Insisting that they figure out what went wrong
The prosecutor is saying hey
What's letter goes
Can clear up this warrant
Like obviously yeah
Maybe she should have
Some sort of rest
Institution from the state like
Here's a
Couple thousand dollars
For your trouble
Or something
You f***** up
But this isn't
Police station
This is an unfortunate circumstance
I obviously feel for her I right
It's annoying to be caught up in something like this
Pictures of Deadpool
Why is this a big story for him right all right
I get that at
The same time
Who the f*** is putting out warrants for a $50 fine
I bet it's a warrant they would never be served of course now that would only come up if you get arrested for something else
Or re-entering the country
So what we really have
How to deal with Heroin
Once again is our border patrol is out of
Whatever their out-of-control Customs and Border Patrol
Even if 2004
Control debate
Is
I have close to a non-issue as an issue can be
ITune
Think of the situation that she had
Like I said
Big headache
Probably put the bad into your vacation sure sure
But
Everything
Seems to have gone exactly right
Bright past
The point of that into
When Alex says
It goes on and on
Whenever he stops reading a story
Well no
That something has come up in the reading of that story that contradicts what he'd already said I got you
He explains
While he's reading
That custom
Sometimes runs
Warrant checks on people re-entering the country evening Cruise Line
And
Earlier he had said
They run background checks and face scan you when you go on cruises
And he contradicted that and that's why you think I'm going to bail on this
Before I contradict more vitamins
Right I got you
That makes sense
I'm not I'm not horrified by it in terms of a police state
Yeah I mean it just seemed like the judge should have looked at himself and then looked at them there and been like
We are here which means somewhere in the system
Any system that whines up here we just need to fix from
The start
Apologize exactly exactly have dismantled the entire legal system along
But that might just be me
Yeah I think that's
For this correct it could be
So we have a movie coming out in
What's
It's a movie that has excited about
Okay
Expect that I Am Legend
Truth about 9/11
I like to be saying that Michael Moore gives bad Solutions and all of his illusions
Self-promotion
Are you promoting Alex's s***
Yeah yeah
The screening
Fahrenheit 9/11
I'd get them to
How do you mean
Get them into my Revenue stream
Recruit this is a perfect recruitment ground bracket right
So what's going to happen
Okay
So
Michael Moore is like we need to let the Democrats take over America that's a terrible idea
He gets bad solution
Sprite we all know that
But what
You should do
Go to an actual business
And ask for them to
To print out business cards for a place you are unaffiliated with
In order to give a message to someone who has never wanted to hear it
And then give them a business card that they're going to throw away
Probably so he is asking you
Do politely
Throw dollar bills at a stranger and the stranger could have
Did you least use the dollar bill with the
Oops of
Getting them into Alex's information space
Better than if you print up a goddamn business card I bet a lot of people to do that
Bill marketing
Mia
What's going on is this
This is like
Trying to escalate
I promise
Yeah but you know you have the premise that introduced by Fahrenheit 911
People to go around to the yellow not only that but
After all these people refusing repeater
Annoying
And also
Counter to Alex's
Very consistent positions about Michael more about how much he hates
He's useful right now right
Because 9/11
My brand
And
He's allowed in
In theaters
It is a little bit like if Alex
Went to a Alex was like Hey listen go to this Marvel movie
And whenever they play the end credits
Boston with your DVD of our post-credits
Avengers endgame
Collin Avenger
It would kind of be like if Brian stelter
Made a movie about
Covid
And then Alex wanted people
Promote a movie
But listen we've had a lot of disagreements in the past but this is going to partially wake up a lot of people find
I can somehow profit off this
Go to see everything I believe is malleable and negotiable
Playing the trailer for Fahrenheit 911
What are the trailer
Bringatrailer
It's just Alex recognizes the radicalization potential there's going to be a certain amount
How people who go see this movie that are emotionally affected and invulnerable State when they leave the theater in that
Is an inflection point that is a point where they're malleable enough that you can get them to think like
What is the planes were remote
Control
That's why I
Recruit at bus station
When you get off the bus you're ready to join a cult
That's just the case for everybody
You're not supposed to look
You got no choice
You just want to get away from whatever's in the bus now essentially
So leaving all that behind us Alex's workgroup
Matt Drive
We get to something that I think is is one of the
Great things
News about listening to Alec
What's in the past
We get these little slices of life
He's a little
Pictures and glimpses into what his life
Was like
Early on
Any makes a claim
About his high school years
Think this is possibly true
I want to make a cup
School
About 12 years ago
District was doing
Echo testing in ER
Classroom setting into the guys
Every senior at his high school.
Clockwork Orange
Call man
That is nuts
We get Bronson on the phone he interviewed everybody
I feel like that might have come up
All right I think unless he went to a
Completely wacky
High School
What you did
This absolutely did not happen hours upon hours of
Electrodes
MTV scream stranger things went to that high school he was there with 11 he wasn't he wasn't going to these
You were always close they had every single
Every single
Senior at their eyes tried open and they do watch
Flashing screen
That's why I can't
Was the debate over
So another explained
A lot of
Glimpses into Alex's life
About Alex's dad okay
None of this matches Alex's other bio things
As for the told him all this future sup
And let's not forget that his dad had to move from Rockwall
Because Alex
Got in trouble with the
Police but he insisted were selling drugs
Nine racketeering operation and they threatened to kill Alex they didn't
Leave town
He's not not you fit 18
This is bulshit
Yeah I kind of believe
I believe this story insofar as it would make sense as to why he's committed himself to a life of
Gryffin cry
Can do become a school teacher you going to be broke
What you should do
Grift millions of dollars from people duh
Be a criminal if you want to succeed in the lawn first
But also if you just wanted
Three criminals be a criminal and that's
The way to do it legally because they haven't outlawed it yet
This story is b*******
Considered in the context of
Alex is all of his other stories
So how naive is he at this point are you a criminal Alex
Legally has to say yeah
You better believe murdered multiple crimes in this time.
She was 16 you know like a crime
Prime
I love this
Assistant thing with Alex that is
Everybody who
He runs into his friends of his dad or whatever
There is a highest level the top Ranger Federal Marshal Intex
Nobody's ever just like a middle manager at a bank
Oil producers in the country Mercedes
Oh yeah
So
The top person
Coup
Actually how you would rank people involved in Ruby Ridge
Randy Weaver's probably the most
Stooges member of that event
And he's on
Now
Thanks Alex glad to be here and I watch new one
What's new Under the Sun
Well what's most
Probably what was important to him 10 years ago and that's
One World Government
So it's important to remember that talks about one world government
Cycling to some
American Spirits 8 theories
Yeah reason to know that
With the
The world of
Ruby red
The entire story
What Randy believe
Actually
On some levels Alex doesn't know a lot about
Alex is very much
Created a Randy Weaver in
His mind
That Brandy Weaver believes without
Believes
Those two shall never meet
All right and I imagine that Alex heard Bill Cooper talking about Randy Weaver Ruby Ridge
Assertive
Flip some switches in his head
Ruby Ridge at this time is already lore
It's already not even a real events
So much as it is
Is the story of the event happened because of
The
Waco
The Oklahoma City bombing being fired
In some ways because of those events right
And if it does become a larger Ark
That
Specific
A33 pill
You know you don't remember Horace Grant
Contributions in 1991
You just remember Robert Horry
So here's another thought
That Randy has
And it's going to be too late
They're going to be sorry
And they really should get
Defensive offence
Join our side
End
Police officer
We better get up get out and join our side
Wow
Wow I'm not going to join your side
No I mean I mean
Is is Randy Weaver about to read
From the Turner Diaries on
Conair is that was about to happen he doesn't get that far. The Bookies on tour for
Talking about how everybody at his school got Clockwork Orange
It's part and parcel of this
Weird narrative he has about the government forcing everybody
Need to get on antipsychotics
Which
Talked about here a little bit
As we know this happen
Yeah the government years later
Forcibly drugged with antipsychotic
People who get diagnosed with conditions
Could be helped by psychotic
Forced to be on
Nope nope
Yeah they have as of yet not eliminated either droogs or milk
Both of those still in full Supply
Full disclosure I'm on
Where is very long time
What kind of medicine not because I think they didn't
And work because
I was just going to going along with talk
Therapy ingestion
Wasn't taking meds
That would have
No one
Pressured me in anyway that's the weirdest part all too often I remember is like it's easily not be on meds
You should have at least
Any Triumph I would have I would have been fine with that hate Maybe
Triumph
Nobody ever gave me that it's so weird the reality of Mental Health
As compared
To the version of it that
Existen Alex
There's like they're going to test everybody
As if it were.
Possible to
To test everybody
Diagnosis is not like
You can't just take
Blood be like
It doesn't work that way no it's
Are nothing but the other thing that I've been doing on Fridays I've been talk
Talking to people outside of our showing their experiences with men
Old watches magicians Isabel
I know it's really really interesting because everybody story around this
Regardless of whether or not they
How to diagnosis or whether they're just
Like suspicious or they've done talk therapy or tried everything
All unique
And none of it has ever been like
People work
Clearly helping
Get the help I need
Incredibly uncommon
A lot of vehicle
Also
That there's an under understood
Aspect of this
Particularly for people like Alex
That is it
If process
Like if you're not engaging with it and
Working absolute it often
Will not
Leeds
Any kind of
Progress
It's silly
Sing is silly
Anybody would listen to him yell about how the government
It's going to
Forcibly
Screen everybody somehow for mental illness haven't forcibly drug everyone psychotic
Is
Is Ludacris I mean anybody
The f*** is this guy's problem I don't know about something else
You know it's not
It's not real
Yeah then the fact that this is from 2000
Forgives me zero hope 2040
Not not feeling good about the future
Kinds of attacks on Psych
A Masjid
G
In the present and Alex
Of course is still banging this drama although he's
Clearly has no real G now I don't know Reelfoot
Imagine if
At this time. In 2004 he's
He's banging the drum for people getting help
More people getting the f****** help that they need well I'm going to just say this and I can't prove this obviously fit
Working theory of mine
That is the reason the people like Alex
And Marjorie are so opposed to mental health care
Is because a large part of their base
Probably me
They need some kind of
Probably be
Be in these communities
If they were receiving appropriate Mental Health
Yeah and I would lose their audience
And the market that they make money off of
Were people
To take their health
Right eye I mean
You know somehow that sounds cynical
You know the idea that these these people are willing to
Perpetuate and exploit
Pains of people who give them their trust
Implicitly
Play N total
You know that's Annika
I'm going to go even worse Ivan
Think that they
Mass shootings are good
A business
So how cynical do we got a cynical are we going to treat this
I think I know
Join you slightly as long as we provide the caveat that I own
Think any of that is
Just process
I don't think it necessarily is a thought that like shootings are good for our
Politics and I don't think I don't think
Think that Alex or Marjorie are like
Attack psych meds because
The people in our audience and leave them and we would lose money if people got healthy
I think that is a conscious
This thing but I think on some level
Part of the motivation
Intuitive understanding
Yeah I don't think they're in like a
Lounge with a fireplace
Snifters
Brandy going how can we destroy the Vino but
It's their amazing kid in some ways it is there
So Alex gets back to the story about the woman who left marshmallows out
Yellowstone
Wendy Weavers take on this
Don't tell me cursive
It's not good
No criminal record
You know I didn't
See that article
It is so
Anymore
The first thing I tell people to do Alex
Get R Gun
Get loaded
People with
And if somebody wants
To come and give you a $50 ticket
From marshmallow
What litter or whatever
I'm afraid.
Is marshmello
Finish ticket in.
Get out of my face
Real quick seems like a great idea with a gun
For trying to get a ticket for leasing food out
Which could attract
There's another
Edibles and beer
Bowser
People enjoying Yellowstone
If that's your solution for a $50 ticket solution I don't know if I want to hear your solutions for
Any other problems
Variations on one idea
Brandy's head
Is a
Hey here's the ticket you left food out at walk walk away
Away
You're under arrest for a massive felony of threatening a Ray Wright with Wright
Find out all forest rangers can
Control animals and there we go
Everyone is now
BAU
For something that you did that is against the rules
And now we're turning it into a life-or-death situation with the
Loaded weapons involved
Mayonnaise and then she got mayonnaise can I get to take on this real quick
Just always
Just always have a loaded gun
Yellowstone agreeing to the conditions of that like
You are in the wrong
If you eat food out
Are you I mean this is one of those big moments where I would like everybody to understand
You are less important than Yellowstone Park
As an individual
I am more concerned with Yellowstone Park in the long-term
Boutros Boutros
You exist
In the conversation of the park
In the context of the other people that are there
You have a responsibility both to the nature and to
Everyone else was
Just as much of a right to enjoy it as me
And
Yeah I do I don't understand this being presented is tyranny
As much as it is just
A formulation of making
I'm sure everyone is
Respectful to each other
Obviously it would be great if
You didn't have to worry about people leaving to wear out but I do need to punish
Real people
Forget melda's leave food out everybody's going to get eaten by bears mean it is it is like
Can you imagine
Narnia had tourist adjust B
Garbage everywhere people throwing garbage at mr. tumnus
Space like that's the way I've always thought of national parks is like literally I'm going into a magical place
Well if it louder is they might get something better than Turkish delight
Maybe there's an upside
So this the spirals out of control and
Reveal something that Alex really doesn't want to
I wouldn't.
The ticket
Yeah you tell me about it
Scary
You know what's scary is these people
I thought I think
Dragon growth
People think the way they do
For sure was a
Freshman High School
Alex is really wanting this to look like
A joke or a metaphor but it is not helping with that conversation turned to the
Wrong direction sell faster
At this point still trying to Brand himself as
Different not that David Icke and UFO type
Aaliyah it cuz he
He wants that like
Credibility of like
He's like how Tucker for a long time
Or even just this week
To distinguish yourself from something that is a touchstone
Is silly to crazy
At this point it's the alien stuff
Documents
In the Bilderberg Group
And yet he doesn't want Randy Weaver this large figure the page
Patriot right-wing movement
To be honest show talking about how he
You seen UFOs about something with a kid
And he believes in Aliens and maybe that the people in charge are actually alien
Yeah
I have to pretend that it's a metaphor a joke
It's not
You can't
You know if you're blindsided by it you can't turn it around
Until it's too late
You know the moment he said people don't think like that differently there aliens from when I was growing up here like
Okay that's fine
That sounds great you know people are different and then he's like they're aliens you're like hahaha
Nothing I can do now LOL I disagree I disagree
The weather out like when I grow up I think they're aliens
You need to immediately say hi you said it might be like a brandy
Conversation
How's the kids Bento s*** no not like that
Talkabouttd
Do pivot the conversation right hard
Because
It's so silly
For you to allow it to go into like
How's the UFOs my whole life
Really wants
This to look like a
No I'm not
I am crazy you know we are the naughty ones
Alex
Accept the fact
Big Lots
Okay
It's not joking doesn't have the chops
For that yet
He has been like Randy is being like
Facetious and sarcastic with the yeah we're The Crazy Ones
He wasn't about the aliens
Play all of it as joking in
No but
Get out he gets off the subject
As little damage
Just possible
I guess
I just
Ivy
It's hard to go from
What's your take on this
Cruise thing
Shoot people
What's things like now
Aliens are everywhere okay alright this is Uber is going to be at a Mexican restaurant we can figure
Where it is interview for everyone involved
Another really bad ass by
Oh no
I enjoyed
I don't get you
Shortwave radios
Several years ago and I never I still can't get the
Starting to work there in Jefferson Iowa
I cannot pick up
Good speakers
Talk show host like you
Yourself
Yes it is
Ohio
I'll try it
As far as
Don't know anything
What's wrong with Iowa
Couple times nice state
I never enjoyed
It's fine it's I bend
I don't know why you need to fire shots at it though Alex in particular
Sure sure
Why I should say I have been looking
Through Alex
His current radio Philly
Play it's open doing a little bit of checking in on that
I can say with
Confidence in Iowa now
0 stations in Iowa stations in Ohio
Four letter states are not going well for Alex these days
Might be 0
I think there might be something like outside boss
Not Cambridge download
It's a has I just as much of a presence in Iowa as he did in 2004 that
So yeah it's
Give you tickets at a national park
You got to talk to the aliens
I can't figure out how to hear you on the radio
And also I'm speaking into Mex
What what a smorgasbord of all the things that shouldn't be going
Yeah you know it's interesting cuz
Turn on the episode and I hear Randy Weaver is going to be out of my kisses
Huge
Pretty big deal
Is a diamond in the rough we randomly stumbled across it
Zoe
PT
Colon
Slash
Switch Lite
Is it forward slash inspected
Can you put in the address
You have to hit enter
All right don't forget the right.com
We've already noticed a couple times
Is this sarcasm
Alex is using
And it really is incessant
It is essentially his only rhetorical.
Well I don't know I just
Good
Don't like small confined areas is
Especially if I'm locked out of my guess
Yeah well not me they're not
Laika
I prefer Verbal Intercourse bearing back in
Imports but if they want to get
My face is a gun I'm going to meet you
You know I'm saying
Also they come to me with a ticket I have a gun
You have clearly decided to respond with a gun
Not all not all my numbers
I think Alex uses this
Sort of
Technique
A lot
Over the top on this episode
Maya the English teacher that I cried it with a
Helping me become a writer
Doing that whole
He used to tell me that sarcasm was a
The two of the Wii
To which I said Sarkozy
And I wish you could be any more of a teacher we became friends until
It's I mean I think people use it as a way to express that they're on
Uncomfortable without feeling like there we
You know Soul sounding like that
I don't mean because I don't mean we can message rat mean like they're not
They're not
Being dominated in some way you know like
I'm still a person of equal standing with you even though I feel like I'm
Not doing well in this
Situation
That got it
A little easier than
Kind of more creative
Cleverness
Alex Penza and his conversation with Randy
And
He's plugging
Here
This feels right
Before I do
And I'll read all the news article
I got to find that break down a 1984
What's the f*** you going to spend the rest of tonight like really trying to find
And then secondly the
Her point that here is that
This is what he should be doing
He should have his website that has a subscription aspect to it
And you know why he can't
Don't want to pay for this s***
We couldn't get people
Go to subscribe to his content
Because they don't want to they bought it for free they want to passively
Engage with a to be like
Look at this guy
You gallon gallon things I like
Righttime
Maybe I'll buy a pill
Southpoint
Alex's tricked me into thinking I need
Right it is it is a little bit like his
Pill business's success is actually a reveal that his content is worthless
You know
I think there's something to be
Be sad for
You know
Providing your content
For free obviously that I'll be in many
I-i'm
I'm big into
I think this Alex just
Wouldn't be able to get anyone to give us
You can give this stuff out for free
And get enough views on it
Terms of anybody being like
Oh yeah
I'll go in for this I'll get us some
Directions to his website
Clearly doesn't move the needle
He couldn't do that anymore that's
Kind of sad
Yeah because this is the model
This is
This is the model for him
Everything that he says little f****** blowed somewhere
You don't need him
Nope nope
Nope, don't need his pills
What do you need from him why do you keep going back to him
Cuz you're in an abusive relationship
Ship with a weird cult leader
No you're in a social relationship with a weird cult leader
I thought we were in the morning
Yeah I just I thought I find
Interesting
Vaped this was there and it could have
Ben what he
He does yeah
Buddy
Just now pills
Play this is even after like x with gold sales and
Stuff right now
You still involved at Anderson
B
Maybe he just really dreamed it
At this point that is content was valuable
Well you know maybe this was a situation where he saw that maybe this was the model
And if he can sing
Succeed at that witch
Which is what he's trying
To do that he can succeed
And then he realized that his s*** is s***
I'm so he started walking
Yeah it may be
Do you still
That's true
Water filter
Sponsor on
But it's
This person to answer the phone
I will be the person who talks to you yesterday do a little mini infomercial
I don't know I just think it's like
Obviously if it works
He would still be doing it
If it made enough money
This would be the way he operated
And whether it is because it wasn't enough or because he is
Driven by greed
He moved on to something that made a million
Could very well be that we're leaving out the intense possibility that
He was
Successful at this business model.
Yeah but not
Billionaire
And that is to me indicative of somebody who's not driven by
The supposed mission
Yeah but he claims to be on because
This is a perfect
Microwave
To be able to disseminate the information
Support base
That is organic
From the audience
And still not have your boss
And mop
Poison people with iodine with monsters monsters
And then back yourself into all kinds of weird
Narrative
Based on
What you support
Yeah that's that doesn't seem like you know he was building the very walls
Even then
That contain him now
Randy Weaver says
He doesn't so Alex is another Gaston
Actually this
God was really revelatory for me because it helped me realize
Why
He was doing that stupid
Clockwork Orange
Narrative that led into everyone's going to be
We forced check cuz it was all just setting the table for this
I'm just grateful Allen
Having me on
So now
Great because
This show has structure
This episode has a meaning.
Structure
That makes
Sense
It's all bulshit
But it makes sense
Yes now he has this b*******
Story about everybody being forced to be on antipsychotic meds medication
Psychologist
Doctor breeding
Story serves
That's why he
He's covering
There is a narrative structure and art
He's Park
Talking about this lady who had a marshmallow out at Yellowstone because he has Randy Weaver on
These are stories
That are meant to connect
The guest
He has on
They are setting the table laying the groundwork for these guests
And whatever
Propaganda narrative bulshit they're going to bring to the table
Make it more easy for them to have a jump off
Point something in the news
To be a touchstone stone for them
It makes sense business
Discraft
Yeah yeah I mean
Repeat it so
Add for us to talk about it
But this is how you would produce a show
Yeah because I listen to so much of his show and
Often times these
Sweetly bulshit
Off the Wall White
The f*** are you talking about this story
It's not connected to anything
And in this case
It makes total sense
Two stories that are off the wall
Meaningless
Why are you talking about this
It's because of your guess
That is leads me to suspect
Use production and crafts goes into it
And he's covered
Bring the story to be
A gift for this
Easier to interview
I am a cancel until you just had
Covered some
Bulshit story that means nothing
Wait
Was that I don't remember
I was trying to figure out if you got to give it up
The Somali pirates who is
It was an it was capped
Ben Phillips it was later released posed to be him right
In the movie
Developer interview
What was it like
Well I'm going to be honest
I got to give it up to the Somali pirates on this one
This guy doctor breeding
When is an auntie meds
Psychologist that believed
He has a philosophy that is
Wild
Colts make better horses
Or something and so it's like essentially
The the
Argument is
Hey let your kids be nice
Yeah
Crazy
I think
Bit of something to that and within reach
I think you know you do have to understand the kids make mistakes and
Act up in Waze
Is that like
Maybe as an adult you like
The f*** but
There's also
The emotional distress
So they could be manifested through kids acting out
They should be taken much more seriously than just
Hey kids will be kids
See this is why you don't want people like dr. breeding using idiom
Sounds like a wild Colt
Let's make better horses
Is because on the one hand you could say oh well this means giving
Children's ability to run free
Will allow them to become better if you know
Adam the other hand you could take that as saying like
Listen if they die they die
God gives us who wins and who dies well I mean it's kind of Scott Adams
Open ComEd
About to have you have to watch
Kid become a
Killer Hornets
Kill them
If he dies he dies
That's all that's all I know
You should have a gun at loaded with you for any time somebody's like wild horses
No problem
That's how you spell problem
Channels off
Yeah that did go a little bit of rice
To become
Yeah
Yeah but I think I'll so you know this
Kind of Illustrator
Of this
Long-standing inconsistent
Stream and nonsense
Opposition
Into public school
Existed
Just just
Anything that
Challenges
The legitimacy and not just that
Of their world.
Even if it's just like
Hey baby
Don't pull a gun out on a ticket you know like even if it's just that they're like
We go back to this again like with the opposition to psych meds and stuff being
Detrimental to Their audience
Retention
Same thing with
Education is detrimental to their audio
Pretension
Don't hold up to the experiences that you have
Live with
Public education
The people you interact with
The
I'm not being under the influence of your parents
At all timer and they can kind of have an eye on you being
Being able to
Create
Through a social
Structure that dust
Include
The oppressive religion of your parents
It's being pushed
Latino party
They like to have that can
Control over children
Schools going to be
Kids in beds
Being experimented upon
That would be almost preferable
And it's nonsense
It should work on that screenplay there's still time cuz this has not happened
Oh they were aliens come on get out of here
Also this
Caller calls in
He's an interesting story about school
I don't know what's going on here but I found a story in
Weather
I pick the kids up on time
Hayward
What it called when you go in like the whole school goes I have a big
Meet up in the cafeteria and what else
Giving out there getting out
No anything
Educational
You notice they are when Alex said it's a 17 preschools the guy was trying to correct him but it wasn't
What's preschool making up details
Yeah well he
Right right
Like we live in a society where it's
Promote
Powers an idiot
At mediocre people don't even know what they
I didn't even think about it
And I look at on the
Look on Aaron and who the kids
Show the picture of two kids
Working together in spine
Play right now.
On the fence
It shows us Dying Light
Blue jeans
Shirt and a construction
Is happening
We need your help
What
I don't know what this is about but like
I could see some
Kind of
Like
It's something being misconstrued like it being an observational exercise or something like that
Like you know
Having kids
See something and then be able to describe it right something Brave rather I see that being an
Occasional exercise of some sort
But also to the premise of like this being anything groundbreaking
Like using it the whole thing from like 1930s magazines of like Spike it's being in the
Invisible ink in the back of the magazine.
Things will be total rip-off Caesar not
Real X-Ray glasses
Ivy something that's been popular among
Kids for time immemorial
Hard to B hard to be like all those 30s adventure stories of those kids didn't have any
But that's why there are like constant stories about like
Harriet the Spy
The archetype of
Team little kid defensive pedia goddamn Brown
These things are are popular for a reason it's because kids gravitate towards that
In the same way they like
To play
Pirate
So what would it be
Flexible spike it it would he be happier if they handed out like a Hardy Boys novel where they did invest
Notice notice what does I really thought he said
It's my kids though so I kept thinking it was the Robert Rodriguez movies
Starring Antonio Banderas and his like
Can you really be that mad at this movie
I think the timeline might be off
Come out yet I don't know
Look
I also don't know what this guy's talking about because he
He seems to be saying that they gave them microphone
There's no way they'll be cost-prohibitive there's no way they're giving microphone
Kids giving them those like old-fashioned song Michael have the little Echo
Start just like the tube with a little ice cream cone on top
Did you ever have those
So it's like a little microphone cream Coronavirus
Is plastic
And it has like the little microphone top on it
In Oaks
And it was hollow inside and when you spoke into it the sound with echo in the chamber and it would come out like
No idea what he's talking about
Anyway
Read one last clip
He does not still believe he seems not to still believe this
I don't think this is s***
It's been over four billion dollars in
Strongly connected to
Bush senior Bush
Jr in St Louis
Political appointees
Wow
Schizophrenia is real
That's a man who's been told he is
Bentley accuses people of being scared
He throws it around just as a pejorative
4 people
I understand you're trying to do is frame something
These drug companies of created
Condition
Or whatever
I don't think
That Alex actually believe
I think this is
Indicative of him
Just talkingshit
I need something that serves
The s*** talking that he's doing with Doctor breeding until he's making
Like I claim those
Responsible
And audience
Maybe some of them
Here then be like that isn't real
Maybe some people in his audience have people in their lives been diagnosed or themselves
I'm hearing something like that it's not even a real thing
Right they can be it can be pretty irresponsible pretty dangerous
Yeah I mean
The thing with that is
Once you start cutting away at what is and is not
Based on whatever he decides
Then it's it's all up
You know like if he gets
It's this AOL schizophrenia is not real just cuz I get
Get to say it he can say that anything is not ready but mental illness
That's just not real you're just wasting all of your time on that you know you understand that's parcel of the position that he's at
Giving himself in his profession because Alex is the Arbiter of like this Secret
Information that he's able to
To decode
From the globalist
He in essence
Is positioned himself as someone who gets
Dictate the terms of reality for these people listening
And the way he does that is so irresponsible
Call ended the way it manifests
18 things like this schizophrenia isn't even real
Is abusive
Yeah for the position that he's put himself in
He feels no
Responsibility
To take care of
The people that he is put into the position of like
They get there
Experience reality through him
Totally and if you're if you hear that the only responsible thing to do is like literally stop everything and be like okay fine
You don't think schizophrenia is real what is real and what is not let's go down the DSM f******
4 and then you can tell me what you except
Doctor breeding doesn't even do that he's not he's not stopping out
Looks to be like well
Like I understand you have some grievances with maybe you're going a little far here for once in our lives
Let's team up
41 in the positive column
As we allow the 1 billion served in the negative condo
Tell Colin to keep going
Batman sounds
That man is dead
We got attacked by a literal Wild.
Well you tried to give a Randy Weaver ticket
Didn't go well
Yeah
So this
This is this is
Interesting also
Doctor breeding
Necessarily like
Some kind of a
Large
Popular
Important prevalent dr. Shetty the guy in Austin who Alex's friends
So prestigious
The most prestigious Guyana like Austin Top Doctors in the world
You know very
Fortuitous
Use that word already
You're not hearing this interview with Randy Weaver was is wild
Eye-opening
Subway's crazy it's a big event in terms of Alex's
Like me so's
You could say
Glad we were able to
Find it this way as opposed to waiting until we die 2000
Right
Through 2003
I am I am also glad that much of the myth around with me Randy Weaver you can
Easily B
Spell B
UFOs when I was
15 believe in a Zionist occupied government
He sees UFOs constantly he will kill you if you
Savior
Seems that the prom
Happy Birthday to happy birthday
Boxcar Willie Nelson Mandela effect
I really hope that you did not tell him
We did not achieve his birthday gift
And you just let it go and hope no one's to Hope I did send an apology message that I had missed know I'm talking to him
I'm hoping you didn't tell your son
Oh yeah
From my understanding
Message
Did not get to the
Good I'm good so this is going to be even better to be a better birthday present off cuz you're going to know that you're
Dad cares so much about you that he would contact the least reliable podcast in the history of the world did
Right and then we drop the ball
Wrecking Ball
Many more to you
5 - 8 Jordans
Emilio Emilio and bzx park I hope you all have a wonderful dream agreement
The sex robot
Alex
Birthstone colors