Damn important I sweat it
I have great respect for knowledge by knowledge
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Worship at the altar of Salinas like a little bit about
Jordan
Barbara Jordan
I've mentioned
On the podcast
Already
That I've been moving some stuff around in the apartment to make things fresh
I had a big part of the
Was to create
An insulated space
Use for a particular reason
I am not here to tell you that there is a plant Warner
You may want to watch
Subway
H-E-B coming back
Deep into growing plants
Right before the beginning of the pandemic
I'm but I was deep
Into the Green Thumb territory and it was a great hobby it really did a lot for my mental health
And I just felt great
Love these little little green things
And unfortunately there were two problems they came at me in a pincer attack
Was that I did terrible job was watering
I didn't really understand what I was doing
Right that ended up the
Leading to me getting rid of all of my
It was a very funny situation how many bugs there it was off
That was coming at me was
That I had
An inability to grow a lot of things
Is based on a concern for Saline
Because a lot of things are socks
6 cats
And even beyond that things that aren't toxic to cats
She would find a way to f****** and eat
She would eat my plants dated me
Yeah she f***** up a lot of stuff to ya-ya so I have rearranged things
In such a way that I have an isolated space
But I can keep Celine out of
And
I could be more careful with the watering right
And I'm very excited
Reignite
Right I mean I have been trying to get you to start your own hybrid hydroponic grow room for a long time because
This obviously is going to last that much longer. You always want to see man
Hey man can I get an eighth of potato
You mix potato new mix toad
You got yourself a meal
But man I think you just need towed
You need a. Growing weed
Keep going to The Dispensary you want to try and like I said smoke
You can turn into a bong if you want
Tutuapp
Cross-pollinating Escrow in a thong potato
It's got a little coating on the inside of the North Pole
Whatsyourprice
Looking for coming bong potato
No right bright spot near the I'm riding your coattails on the video game story
Yeah yeah for me I'm finally into the three houses Warriors really enjoying
I don't know if I am but I'm very lonely and I'm taking a lot of fictional characters on x
Expeditions right now Partners out of town so you got to do what you got to do
But I am really thinking about what Mercedes is feeling about
So I know I'm not cheating on my wife but it doesn't put his face always
T8
This is the problem 3 hoax
You know people's feelings about
About politics sometimes these anomalies Expedition
Actually this this will revisit this as the cut you off
We have an episode
So Jordan to do today
Mostly covering
The 11th and 12th of July 2022
Hey love it's really f****** stupid
Buckle in for that little sex disgusting and some of it is really really stupid
What we do
Business on that list and say hello
New Wok
Oh you're almost through all of it thank you so much and I apologize
Scuba Steves father
Fitness Guru of occupied Texas long may he gay
I think I might have said this one already but just in case I didn't
Jason Matthew love your wife KY thank you so much you're now if I was wrong
Also the wife's name might have been KY
Next game Studio baby Adams
My wife is getting tired of me warning her of the globalist thank you so much
And finally
Lorenz Hellman Gloucester thank you so much
I was going to come back I see what you're saying this person
Do what our favorite houses are I just figure we do a little
Little little breakdown a black Eagles person shooter
I've I've started with the blue Lions both times
And they're the worst
Yeah you you kind of
But you gravitate towards
Being unsatisfied by like royalty
Also also a generational power you want to live with in it but you want to be bought
Bothered by delivering in it
Enjoyable
Dimitri's essential
The B is not stopped and I do appreciate that happening
Royalty
Information
But now the gold mines Charming seemingly Carefree they don't have a lot of baggage going on
Everybody else is crying and weather
Tragic backstories and family and s***
Carter's just having a day I find no spoilers
The story in the three hope
Yeah is annoying that sounds about right to I'm having trouble
Experience
I just like the eagles I think they're
Characters of better bernadetta
Sucks
Well if you like Huber we are Friday
That is my challenge shy strikes me as a weirdo
Let's stop talking about fake characters
I'm trying to reach across the aisle to today tonight
I love it
So there's a couple of out-of-context drops that I'm not going
For today
I'll play them later
Today Show
Friends family neighbors are liberals
Black people put the Liberals coming up to Alex
You're right we're wrong friends families
A bunch of liberals
Coming up to him saying
You're right we're wrong totally sounds right
So we're going to start I told you were going to mostly be covering the 11th and 12th
True
Alright we're going to talk
At the beginning of this
About a little things happened on the 10th
Rights that was Sunday's show and Alex
Start the segment here in a little bit of a mood
But
I want at all I want
Injecting six-month-old baby
When they're poisoned Travis.
News
System
And doesn't protect
So we're winning
The fight
But they've already killed millions of people
Preparing
They're far worse all you saw
You just
Lives
Beta test
Now our enemies are going operational
Control
God is holding our hand
God has his hand on her shoulder with guardian angels
So real
Zillow realtor will tell you all about it
Totally Rudy
Operational information but just
Want something
This is 100% real
You don't need me to
Tell you that anymore
Can't talk about stuff cuz I don't want to give the enemies
Operational information
I was like it whenever he's not talking over the song with anything
It feels like
He suddenly started talking
Into the song like
Money
You belong to
Honestly I think you need to do a wellness check on Alex
Anytime he's coming in for break with Lana Del Rey
Because
It usually is a harbinger of something
Trailblazer
And this case is no except
So thank you for joining us live Sunday broadcast
That is literally
In Defiance
At least psychopathy these demons
You're doing
Roblox
Cell block
Where I Wanna Be
I just got to turn
What's the name of the goddess
Because it again they will
Billy got indirect me
Because we haven't
Nothing
But success
Nothing but Victory it has been
You
The viewers and listeners
You did this
That's why
I just cut finger off
ShopRite on airshow you
How much I appreciate you and what you've done
Beginning
David Mann
Is it reminds me of what he had on his desk
Talk about this
Is very quickly bulshit background
I do
Think I mean
Obviously
This is a desperate attempt
Hook Line & Sinker
We've talked about this a tiny bit off air
There's an escalation aspect do this because generally he has talked about cutting off his finger for sure
He has not brandish
That is true he's got a dagger that is nice
It is all little bit weird man
Also
I think that you can tell from
The listening to it
Exactly this it's right
Yeah that comes out of
I've been out of nowhere
I feel like maybe
Weider's there's a Twilight Zone episode to be had about
Alex
Like the devil appears you know whatever however
He does in a Twilight Zone episode
I'm just
Forces him to do all the things that he says so Alex accidentally says I'll cut off and then he starts to sweat
And then
The devil looks
Slowly chops that finger off and it fades to Black
Holy s*** that was a good Twilight Zone this is the sequel to Liar Liar
The Twilight Zone version
Horror movie version of Liar Liar
Amplifying
Everybody bizarre display wraps
Talks about cutting off his finger
Said he's not going to do it in any goes to calls
That's basically out of this guy
Amanda schull farming
Appreciate you and what you've done
Nothing
You
I change the word
You have stood up and
You have turn the
You
You've got that
A very
Bottom of my heart
You got my
Full commitment
Real people
Friday all day salmon
Because they know
Shout out to them
Justin Elser to match a lot to them
Zaino
Finger off to prove that
I say that Alex is a f****** liar and a fraud and as evidence I submit the past 5 years of my life represent
About 700 podcasts
But demonstrate
The lines that he sells and more importantly
Only the specific strategies he uses
To push his dishonesty
Alex
Please feel free to wear buttons that
I wish I wish the story of The Boy Who Cried Wolf
What matter
But then I think about it more and then I realized that
That's not how the media and Alex work like Alex says he's going to do something outrageous
And the media reports on it
And it's like the boy who cried wolf except it's like if the boy who cried wolf
Gave the media 20 bucks every time he cried wolf and they're like
I need twenty bucks today so I'll get ya all know he's crying wolf this time for sure
Unfortunately symbiotics
Things sort of you know because it's an easy story
Alex
Brian said some dumb s*** that's pretty funny I don't like him
57zz easier than taking the time to
You know maybe go over some of the content that he's and it shows that is
That that sucks yeah and it is it maintains this
Like there's maybe a hope that you can tell yourself it's like 10 people will see this and realize he is out
And it doesn't it doesn't
It doesn't have that effect
Holding onto hope that people like oh my God he is
He is not a trustworthy source of information he threatened to cut his finger off
I just don't I think it's
Unproductive
Yeah it's work earlier in the podcast
I would have a
Cover Alex over and over again
Too many too many
Too many
No I don't mean you know the boys
Give them 50
50 bucks when he cries well if it doesn't
50 bucks whenever they point out he's a giant bucket races
True
Hard to go back to the boy cried wolf
After you like
This motherfuking racist piece of s***
Only cries wolf all the time
Civilization
And they're like not will take fifth
It's not newsworthy that Alex has once again threatened to cut off his finger
It is newsworthy some of the other s*** that he believes in F
Is is
This problem
So we jump in here on July 11th
And I Alex has a
Hot take
Sri Lanka
There are massive
Riots
Government building hours
Find a visual saying
Death to the New World Order
Bill Gates
Downtown
Sri Lanka
Dutch
Countryside
Texas
They're saying it in Chile
And Venezuela
Over the world in Brazil leading the charge
The best leader come out
National level
Don't say
Wow
Apparently the Sri Lankans
Yeah they were mad at you
Halo
Wow okay I just don't even engaged other than to say stop it
Bolsonaro
The best leader national leader in the last 50 years
I guess that's
I'm trying to see where the cutoff is there
I guess Andrew Jackson was before that
Ragnaros best
Right yes
Fellow
Was that he likes
Truthout
This Broad
Nation point
Patient zero of Liberty
This audience
Tucker Carlson
Otherworld
It hurts to watch Alex embarrass himself like this throwing his support where he does but it's
I would love for Alex
Specific thing that bolsonaro orbon have done to make him
Support them some vague b******* like they stood up to the new world order or they resisted the Takeover
They hate carslaw
I got one
Mostly just because I know for listen
This dumb show that Alex has no specific
These dudes are just know what they
What their policies
I mean I imagine if you could he would be like
Well both
Bolsonaro accelerated the decline and infect destruction of the entire Amazon rainforest
Dooming the planet to further
Describe how the planets those Forest grape
More CO2 in order to save the world
Narbonne
Beat the s*** out of journalists on The Daily
So that's again
Right on there
You know First Amendment
Yeah this continuing fetishization of Tucker
Alex needs to wake up and realize that Tucker doesn't like
Tucker defends Alex when defending Alex is a useful props for him to use to attack his Target
But he does not give a s*** about Alex
Illustrate this point here's a clip of Tucker attempting to argue that his great replacement conspiracy theories
Actually aren't all that crazy
How many
That's so casual for Tucker
Racism when he's
Confronted with it it's second nature for Tucker
To attempt to claim The High Ground by into
System that his racist theories are solid
Hey based on real stuff I'm like Alex Jones
Who's racist theories are crackpot s***
The dynamic here is very simple on one level and then there's a little something underneath it that makes it a little bit Messier
The simplest
Is that Tucker just wants to differentiate himself from a symbol that all right-thinking people can agree is insane
And that is
The things that Alex Jones says
Trope
Escape goat
Yeah the more complex thing here is that
The theory that they're discussing the core of the great replace
Conspiracy theory
Alex and Tucker agree on
Identical
Alex yells about the great replacement Tucker yells about the great Replacements so in order for Tucker to really get away with
His kind of dogs that he's attempting
He needs to clearly articulate what it
He's about his great replacement Theory That's So factually based
Scholarly
In what aspect
Alex is great replacement Theory make it turn into crackpot Raven
Tucker can't do that because they have the same thing
Siri and it serves the same political purpose for both of them
Belief in the great replacement theories is to attack your own position which is why
Does this dodge the way he does
The same s*** that he does in order to use Alex as a punching bag in an attempt to bolster his own credibility
If Tucker were to be engaging honestly and he believed what he was saying
He would give
This same defense of his replacement Theory being based on fact
And instead of attacking Alex
He would say and you know who was way ahead of everybody else on this
Alex Jones
Lauren Southern with her documentary
If you truly believe this s*** and he needed to bring Alex's name into it
PewDiePie
The people who were preaching this gospel long before Tucker realized it was profitable
He doesn't do that because to him Alex
Isn't that ideological forefather
He's a puncher
Check bag at a property
To use to maintain his shaky grass pump public respect
Debility
Offended
I'm sure he's not though because
She knows that all the people he interacts with her self-interested backstabbing Liars
And nothing outside of the accumulation of and exercise of power really means anything
Chinese flag
Once you start looking
Can boot there's no what are you going to complain about the different Taste of boot
Helix movie kind of hope that like
You
You hope that Alex Wood
Feel hurt
By somebody
Clearly being like
You're a f******
Ranting lunatic I'm going
To use you as an example of the thing I would not when I'm being accused of being
A racist Theory
Now you're so smart
You're so smart
That's such a smart idea that's what you got to do you got play the Smokescreen
I totally like you you me you really love me you realize the image of me
In the world
You can use me as a shield and it WI a diesel bus
Really really f***** up is that
Alex
Even five years ago
Used to be that
Things that push the Overton window
You know
Because he was so out there the Republicans could
Take a more extreme position but they would still have to
The moderate in terms of that
It feels like now it's just a smokes
They all say the same thing Alex says another like while we're not like I like sounds like
No no you're there man you don't do that anymore
It's December gray Alex is like a focus
Kind of
You can get away with
See let's let's let him test drive some of this s***
That is that is such
I would describe it as exactly the way things are going
That's a bummer
So Alex spends a lot of time talking about Hunter Biden's iPhone
On this episode
Hunter Biden's nice
Looks like his father
And we cannot show you this information
Legal
Obviously
Him in bed
As trophies
We cannot show you
We will not show you
Quite frankly after I looked at some of that.
Stop looking at
Last night
Because never in my life
And as a journalist
I'm a pundit
An analyst
I also am a journalist
Look at it I will not look at it that's okay you could stuff man
That's fine
He doesn't
It's true so with this stuff I really feel like it's gotten to a point where the police should just arrest Hunter Biden
Alex can try and get a charge 2
Sister stick in court
If you can prove his case harder to go to prison
Alex goes to jail for definition of defamation
And malicious prosecution
There needs to be some steaks through this cuz it has just on except
Here's the situation as I
Someone on 4chan claimed that they'd hack
Hunter's iCloud and released a bunch of stuff from it
Go to pictures and videos
Hunter with
Is Kraken sex-workers
Okay the authenticity of the material isn't fully confirmed which is actually something we should be careful about
Is it does appear that some of it
Is previously unreleased stuff
At least according to motherboard there's an article there they
Claim
But in situations like this because of the really dicey origins of the stuff being put out it can be very difficult
Difficult to know what is the genuine product of a hack and what could have been slipped in along the way
So I don't
No
What to
Do about it
Has more authenticated by
Respectable Source other than
Some weirdo 14
I'm confused about the whole Hunter Biden thing to do people care
WeCare do the bank I think I think that is some people is a positive correlation
Between caring about Hunter Biden
And stuff and
The Durham report
Yeah they were the only people that care
I mean
ICare inasmuch as I think
There seems to be a problem Maybe
There's a personal you know what it is
Mine no problem
No
I think that if
Things were
What Alex's describing it would be a problem
Everybody else to take care of
From everything I understand this is outrageously sensationalized
Describing that
Look I just
Growing weary of Hunter Biden stories
First it was his laptop now it's his iCloud.
The Jacob Wohl is going to announce
That he got his hands
On the graphing calculator
F****** sketchy s*** on it even the even more simple you turn that upside down that mother
Biker is dirty
So I I just I mean I don't
I don't know
This is a crime
Tired of hearing Alex say stuff that doesn't go anywhere and it's disgusting
I mean honestly and I just don't care it if
If you had him on one of those strong man things where if I hit the thing with a mallet
Hunter Biden would actually go flying up
And his head would hit a
Bell
I still wouldn't care
I just don't care
I don't care about him
Nope so
Alex and his mom
Yeah
There's something's going to happen
That is never going to get that titty again
Nope
My mom's really smart person
Biden was installed here in Africa
She said mark my words I've said this many times here we go
Told you this
They're planning to kill Biden as a false flag
Change the subject
My mother
I also think of right-wing
Common Sense thing
Your family sounds f****** annoying
So yeah Alex is both
Take that the other guy
Jill Biden
Is a false flag
Man what a dinner conversation this is the only way that Hunters iPad story is going to go away
False flag kill Joe Biden it is kind of fascinating to think that like
When I sit down at the dinner table with my family for like Thanksgiving or whatever
You talk about our lives
Even if it gets to politics or something like that
We're still talking about stuff grounded in reality you know
Legacy games to me they would Alec
Does that and either sitting around the table
They're all just in a writers room just tossing out bit
So just like
Okay here's what's going to happen all right
The North Koreans are going to... And that's how we know it's going to happen and you like what are you talk
I'm picturing like Alex's mom pulling him aside and then I got a Hot Chip
Yeah but Alex really thinks is going to happen
He's not predicting
So I predict
Prendela mine
Common Sense thing
The weather building a shop that they're going to kill by
I really think so,
Before the midterm
Who cares about the birthmark
Probability in the next 120 days
October surprise
Yeah that would be a
Surprise in October okay
So if you get this I mean this is the way this s*** works with Alex it's like I'm not pretty
I'm predicting that the globalists are going to do this is a 90%
Please just give yourself up
Back exit Escape Route when it doesn't happen
Although I'm gonna feel real dumb if
Is false flag
Next couple months
I still won't feel dumb
I refuse to feel dumb if he's false-flag murdered
Fine
Qualify
Hopefully I do think that what this is
Representative of an indicative of is that Alex is responding to the idea that there is such a
Fever Pitch
It's growing with
The thing
Things like the January 6th committee
I think things like
The continuing covid
Situation
There's a pretty good chance that someone might take a shot at 5
And I think Alex knows that the people who are ideologically
Very much in sync with him
The doj puts on their big boy pants and actually charges drop with a I mean any number of the crime
You know that they proved he did
I got really excited because I thought I might still have the outside play
How did my iTunes
You know people are going to start
Putting putting bullets in Long Rifle
It's it it seems like it's not a zero possibility and I would recognize that to his preemptively creating
His storyline
It's going to happen but also by.
Help them
I wish you harm against by there any of these people
I want to be tried and put in prison
Process
But I've already determined the
So do process but it is
Arteriogram
Methodology the poles
Democrat
Always baked into the falls
But now Biden is polling in
Biden approval rating six historic
Believe me
Awaits
Before but also these poles are also
Yeah there's still super fake
They're faking
8 hits
Still Rick Lowe
That's their idea
Of how to do this are likely playing
Embarrassing
Listen he's hitting 185 you going down to the minors man there's nothing to say
It's over
We got to save face with an all-time low
It's going down
Does it matter
Wow yeah it makes sense though when you really think about it
No it does
Know each other
Subway
We got to we got tacos energy crisis
Texas
Again
And
Refuses to understand how Texas
Power grid works
Following
Bilderberg Group
And public relations arm
Screw
Operator blackouts that was months ago
They're not allowed to use coal
Shut down most of those plants
It's fine if they don't
Prison time
A year-and-a-half ago
Add
Joe Biden
Who just got that office shed
No
With three!
This is just straight-up pathetic
41 Alex is completely lying about
Pretty much all of
The details of that blackout
But if you zoom out he's actually also lying about the entire reality that the blackout existed in and there's a
Good reason for him to do that
Texas power grid failure is an indictment of his ideology
The reason they were outages like the ones that happen Tracy
Is back to a deregulatory is disconnected from the two major Countrywide
One so they can avoid any federal over
Alex needs to lie about everything related to this case because if he doesn't
His listeners might catch on that those blackouts were tragic
And deadly example of political ideas are bad
You won't go to prison for having a coal-burning power plant there are plenty of them in Texas
It is pretty sad but honestly the alternative to lying here is Rekha
Hypnotizing that deregulating be power grid in Texas was a
Really dumb destructive idea what Alex can't do without admitting like
Hey my guys were wrong
Yeah
Listen
Okay
If your
Like a big solution is
Burning coal
F****** get out of here
YouTube Fargo
Where is
Sing The Jetsons Antarctica
That wasn't why do we have energy that isn't cold
Nicole is Magic Man
Top country
It's all clean
Complained
No nothing
There's tons of really toxical as well agree we should use the Clean Coal first
Alex thinks Clean Coal is a different things in Kohl's
He thinks it's a different like
To a Subway
Thanks feels better too tempting to make coil cleaner
He thinks that it's a different Rock
Different mineral
Energy source
Within its Heyday was f******
Horses
It doesn't
For now its 2020 to come up with the f******
Music
Not Cole
Look I understand
Cowboys
I understand where you're coming from but I also think it's
You're distracted from the Psychedelic speaks of Clean Coal is difficult
Which was the Noid
Which was the point
Just calling it Clean Coal but
The reason that I'm stressing it is because he clearly has no idea what he's talking about or
Is audience for the sake of big big Cole
Scrub it down that's what I mean
Just regular cold
But I scrap it down first all that dirty
Is you also have to use scrubbers but Clean Coal is like
You know how do you see the chunks of cold shoulder black
Write these ones are like grey
The clean their clean
Alright
Hello
Completely come on
Our sweet pedantic saying this little bit more about the the power
We know the place they run we know their scams
That was the power operators months ago
And now
They have come out
Grid operator potential rolling blackouts today
Issues call for voluntary conservation
That's right you got to conserve
Because they cut your power your learning in this great transition
No more Heating in your houses
The government will give you a place to be warm
Two groups like ercot are making these sorts of announcements because they know that the alternative is to connect the Texas grade to the interstate
State infrastructure and that's
Something that
Is heavily conservative State isn't going to go for
They would rather die and have rolling blackouts then to give up his imaginary sliver of Freedom that they think
Do they have from the Federal
A solution that would help with the problem is categorically off the table so the way to live with it
Is the ask people to voluntarily limit their energy intake
This is not build back better or the great reset this is conservatism enact
Heidelberg Germany they didn't say the people could
Heater own houses
That's enough to scare the audience
The German government is concerned that Russia May restrict
Gas supply the comes into the country and this would create a
Huge energy
Crisis come winter
This is a potential merger
That may come up months from now so to prepare for that possibility some cities in Germany or setting up heating Halls
Where people can
Can go to make sure that everyone has access to a safe warm place to be
Oz intentionally misreporting the
Story because the cover
Sincerely would reveal things he doesn't want the audience
It's to realize
First be potential for this German energy crisis has to do with Putin restricting the supply of gas that flows
Country
The audience
Supposed to think that the globalists are meddling with energy not the guy who Alex
To protect is fighting
That would really suck up their heads
Second the story is about the government setting up emergency centers to save the lives of vulnerable people should
Worst case scenario comes
The pass
I was present this as a government saying that you can't heat your home and you have to
Independent Big Brother 4
Because if he didn't
People might ask
Like why are you opposed to humanitarian efforts to make sure the people don't freeze to death on the
Mistreat another hop
The simplest
Humanitarian effort
You don't even need to talk about the
It's
Undaunted f******
There are heated things
Cuz it's fun
King Cole
That's how it's just the same s***
God dammit
Yeah just more centralized in like a Hall that's dedicated to even more importantly then
Deregulation is why they're having the blackouts in the conservatism being
It is also that the people who run ercot are billionaires
Who make even more money
Whenever you can't have power
If it's if they lost money
For a moment
They would come out and they be like holy s*** guys we really f***** this one up
It'll give us a little bit more profit if we're
Good people may be true for the the companies themselves the workouts actually
Does the electric electric reliability Council
Cheerleader
It may not be them that has the harsh profit motive
Necessarily I'm sure they're not at all captured by those energy
Companies that would be
Fair enough
To be hyper
Clear there are other factors at play that
Relate to why
Babies energy crunches
Are happening but a large amount of the burden
Could be taken off
Bye
Not making your
F******
Entire electric grid
Independent
In order to avoid Federal lovers being stupid
Stupid
So you made a really good point about the idea of Alex's enemies getting a fair trial
Fixated on that
Broadcasting worldwide in defense of human Liberty we are the resistance
From enemies foreign and domestic
Alex Jones humanity is getting off
My body
I am so proud of the people
Sri Lanka
South Africa Nigeria
Humanity
The blinders off
And the globalist are going down
But we need
Is Nuremberg to
World trials
We need him convicted
And we need a break their necks
But only once
They've been given a fair trial
Which will be so fat
The Farris trial anyway ever
For the world to see
Full HD
Ladies and gentlemen yeah so like there is a trial for Klaus Schwab
America
I don't think that's fair trials
Did we lose our stolen and Charles.
Think anybody should be allowed to
To talk about
Sri Lankans
A Sri Lankan group
Break into your home steal all of your s***
Live in your pool and then beat you to death for being too rich
I don't think Alex gets to be like congratulations srilanka
Cuz if his house was there
He's dead witch house
Exactly
Yeah also go fuc yourself with this idea of Nuremberg to you should not be in favor of world Courtney
Alex
Quartz he want
Americans to put this
Skort
On the world
Look for them to see
I mean I guess that is probably what do you want
But you shouldn't
If you don't want to One World Government don't argue for world try I mean I do feel like what he really wants is for us to put stick
6 steaks
With dead bodies on the border of the United States
Klaus Schwab Bill Gates and all that
Beware globulus
Know what he wants
Is 4
People
Kill them
Look for him to keep this flimsy veneer of I like the rule of law don't hurt anybody
Anyway so did Alex
Larry does again
US Secretary of State
Around the world
Masturbated
By the Russian aggression against Ukraine
1% of it
No it was
Tears ago
Play Shine On
Paris climate Accords
Anime
30%
Really happening
You will eat some bugs
Dialysis is making
Shut up signed onto the Paris Accord back in April 2016
The Kyoto Protocol
Since 2002
The information Alex's providing is just made up to
You can go to the Sri Lankan government's National livestock statistic
6 page and you'll find that the number of cows has been
Been steadily increasing year-over-year
The professional numbers for 2021 included in approximately 2 million liter increase in average monthly milk for
I guess I could just say whatever you want
Provide no evidence for it
Expect his audience
A nod along with it cuz
That's the game
I mean
How do you even
Come up with
They just killed half of their cows
Whenever the truth is they have more cows
How do you do that it's because the stories of
Sort of revolve around ideas of emissions
I get that responsible farming thought process
Sri Lankan
Livestock sector is mostly made up of smaller
Operation of course
And those are less
Damaging in terms of
Environment
Olympics
So
Look
We need
Coal-burning
No
Why cold cuz they're good for trees I swear to God
Done with it
Coal power plants are good for trees
So my trees and plants
Directly downwind
Coal Power Plant
Grow much faster and healthy
Carbon dioxide
The bad guys in FernGully aren't this evil
Play pump carbon
The exact opposite is actually with most studies
I found fire power plants are
Pre bath in the surrounding area
Likely due to a combination of air pollution
PH level and nutrient composition of the soil
Sometimes
Alex's example there about humans walking around in CO2 and being fine is actually a really good argument again
Against his own position
No one is saying that we need to get rid of CO2 in
Hi early because that's stupid
Obviously CO2 exist as an important natural process
However
Excess CO2 has really negative consequences on these processes
And there's plenty of evidence that our actions have increased the levels of CO2 in ways that are danger
Alex is human exam
Just walking around
Their CO2 in the air
And if you're fine
Generally because it's a low enough level that there isn't a problem
However once the air becomes more concentrated CO2
It becomes really dangerous to breathe
At about five percent composition you may end up with some respiratory problems and it could become serious but the real issue
Is when you get over 10%
Hey which point you'll likely have convulsions you could end up in a coma and you might die
When you get higher than that you're in a situation where you'll probably lose consciousness
Free quick
If someone with a mask
Isn't there to help you you'll die
CO2 super dangerous to people in the levels are high enough
But it's a normal not dangerous part of life when the levels are in
Check
This exact same principle applies to the lottery codes
The mad if Alex is so certain that CO2 isn't dangerous to people
You should do a livestream where he goes into a room
Where the CO2 levels are like 30% so we can children have seafood
I'm I'm waiting for the day and I don't think it's
Going to be that long
You remember when that a****** brought us
Snowball in
Congress seems like C climate
You know I'm waiting
Waiting for the a****** to come in with a jar of CO2
Unscrew it and then release it into there and be like
Zc02 doesn't hurt any of you today and I just idental happen
30% CO2 what I mean is
Take there to drag him out I just want a demonstration of him passing out I don't want to die
I just think it would be funny if you had a lot of hubris
Like when me and Kyle waterboarded himself
No he didn't
The paperwork and everything
Paperwork yeah
Amazing
Any day now
So Alex is a guest
The guy was running for congress
I also used to run
On the football
Feel okay
There is an incredible Herschel Walker
This country
Primary
Tyrone Davis in is Going to Be Our Guest for exploit
I didn't realize until I set it up that way that'd believably have been Herschel Walker
It's not okay Davis is a former football player who's getting into the political scene
So he's running for Arizona's 4th District and the reason he's got Alex's attention is that he recently
Very extreme Pro AK-47 campaign
Stevenson is 15 candidates in the GOP Primary that's taking place on August 2nd
The primary candidate isn't running unopposed
I'm going to predict he loses
Knowing nothing else
Arizona's 4th is a republican + 22 District so whoever wins at GOP Primary will get elected
But that's still pretty big hurdle with
The field of five
This is a really good strategy for these friend Infowars ask candidates
It's troubles me that they're taking
You attacked the primaries of Super Save GOP disc
You're probably not going to win but there's a
And if you do
Is a cakewalk into conquer and Youth
The Cakewalk.
Stay in concrete you have the incumbent
So crazy
This is the only way lunatics like the sort Alex loves are going
To get into office so if your political strategist your best bet would be
Cook's partisan index
Just focus on getting insane primary candidates
In most of those heavily.
District
And then the more airtime you get them in Congress
The more cover they give to the insane Republicans who at least talk
Like people I mean
On some level if you're even just like a
Playing with fire but
If you're just remain
Rino Republicans
That would even work to your advantage
Maybe don't do too many of these primary
Challenges
It does it does work to your van
I mean
It's not hard to
To see how the unintended consequences of this strategy are going to come back and bite them in the ass but it's all of
But most of them will be dead by then so they don't care it's us who are going to be bitter
Let me ask which is
Would you like to know exactly what it's going to be like if Davison goes to Congo I would love to
Now you out here like
When I get in here I'm going to wedge war against these evil
Evil people
People don't understand this what America needs to wake up and understand right now
You need to wake up right now because your sister five churches
And pastors are not going to come to the rescue they are not involved
In the spiritual battle
You need to understand that
Evil is
Evil
In America does not understand how evil is because they think that this is some kind of movie
This is a real evil takeover and they coming to take your children from you
They coming to take your wealth your life and everything from you right now
Hey man the guy you're talking to thinks everything
Movies are real
So also what you just described
The government coming to your home taking your children your stuff and then your life
That sounds like a lot a lot like a movie
Yeah and also I mean
Wants to go to Congress
Wager holy
You know cuz that's how you want government to work
It's not so what happened first
So here's how it goes what happened
You want somebody
Probably Young
To really fill their brain with absolute
Garbage nonsense and then later on like a Manchurian Candidate they'll appear from nowhere and spout back bulge
And then there's a good chance that
Your other bulshit people are going to go for a go f****** cares
Look
I don't want to leave
Luckily I don't think
He's going to win the GOP Primary but if he does
Bad stuff
Hey man this is a complete War
The spirit that was with God he saw God he was created by God he watch God make the stars and the
The planets and everything
In the Bible says in Joel that they rejoiced when God made all of these things that he was The Sovereign Elohim
But these papers with the God and saw him and knew him as God but yet
Build against him
What you think
People just stayed in heaven or was just between the pages of Genesis and exodus evil is prevalent today and it's in
The Democrat Party at we have to stop at right now
What you're right I mean they're at war with us that they admitted War they are just shutting everything down
Cancel Bible demons
Yeah
What is the
Democratic
Parties
The devil should pick
Oh that's true Democrat more effective
Oh wait
Democrat devil
Righteous Republican
Right there
Involve the human brain breaks down
I agree it also this is scary s***
Like this V's ideas that are being spouse
Essentially they like biblical demons
Still walk amongst the Earth and they are at the Democratic
Yeah I think a lot of people would be scared if they knew how many people truly believe
Yep
My point
Is that bad
You know
I don't want this guy to get in
Because
Here is how you can support
Go to Jerome pecans.com go to get involved
I'm raising up an army of two to four thousand people that are going to knock doors make phone calls
Share my content make memes memes are very important right now
And a very powerful make fun of the left laughing to make jokes out of
Take my video and share it make a mean mother
We are going to go after them and we going to wear them out they don't have a sense of humor
And laughter really wow
And share this content
Send five $10 to my campaign send $20
Tell people to donate because the the GOP isn't fun to me they're not helping me
This thing I started
What is that $3,000
It's I think it's
You don't have to go up Alex it's I think it's like 58
$58,000
People will just
Realize you got to spend your money to save your money
American
Hey man this is a complete War
Against demons who now live inside the Democrats and they've been around ever since the Bible times at watch God create the Stars
Yeah yeah you need to make memes to boost my campaign and give me money
I mean it is amazing
It is a maze
The even with the
Devils
Help
All Obama could do is get a watered-down bulshit healthcare portal pass
That's with with the Devil
Yeah God damn
So drone leaves
We get some calls
This call made me sad
I've had conversations
Stuff that you're spinning
Well yeah
Between these things happening our government is run by C
Panic pedophiles they have their signs
And they're trying to bring about
Play the second coming of Jesus Christ
This is why we think things are bad now it's
So much for your eyes
Why are you mad at him
I just get really sad whenever people are like people think I'm weird
Especially ever even weird
Yeah I mean that's Gunn Patrick that's a consequence of believing in all this weird stuff people are going to treat you like you believe
Advice
To anybody
Before you read between the lines try reading the lines
Oh man the lines are usually more important than what's between them read those lines
And then if you read the lines you might find out that those spaces between them racks
Spaces so you can read the line
Is it Eerie between them then it's
Dutchess black ink all over the place
It's stuff in between the lines often is really an art of analysis and assessment
But you need to know the lines
In order to know what your analyzing and assessing
22 skip that
Text app
Is really like thinking that you
You can do a 900
Before you can stand on a skateboard
Listen you need to get good at standing on a skateboard before you're going to even do a kickflip
If you're doing Shakespeare in the park
Don't improvise A Midsummer Night's Dream don't do it what are you doing drunk Shakespeare in the park
Then maybe you are a
So so is he
What kind
Really want to thank you and your show and I have
To tell you that
I take
Religiously
And I never used to dream
Now I dream
Constantly
What's me up
They're so hard
NFL brother
What are your folks working adventure adventure nothing we promote as a fraud
It will change your life
Text Adventure
If you went to your doctor
On anybody like Lissa
Said I guess I feel good
It makes my dreams hurt so bad I wake up
I mean he always dreamed you just
Is remembering or maybe the dreams are more Vivid now substances and some chemicals that
Count to
Make you have more pronounce
Is there caffeine in
X2
Battle
Didn't cut a clip of his supposed talking about EX
Do and make some soup virile and like is a boner pill again
Wasn't supposed to be what
Superman
Are there all boner pills
So Alex gets back to his prediction that is not
A f****** prediction
Don't say it's a prediction really feels like if he agrees with the prediction then that means he is all Talladega cannot predict
Biden's going to be
I believe
It doesn't mean it's going to happen but
Believer
I said that 34 days
Barber shop
Trump said I'm going to run in July
I don't know if I heard anybody covering this
No
You didn't it was a
Worldwide
But I don't think I heard anybody covering a
Discovering it. Even after he said so
I think we just made fun of them
Is planes done repaint American flag on it
Just talked to talk to for people to talk to Trump
They said yeah he's going to announce in July as early as
Monday
I said hey
He's aware that for most least reliable people ever
You didn't do it
Rodger Stone no
Their moves
And what would help them get rid of this liability
Blame it all on him
Criticizing
Bad
Makes perfect sense
I don't
What is my mother
A year-and-a-half ago
Set my alarm to family dinner see the medium
Another going to kill him
I'm just telling you now
A sweet potato
But they can watch it
You know
Delaware
We're not behind that
We don't support that we're on record
That's all I'm getting
Do you know something
Do you know of
One of your weirdo friends talking about killing Biden when he goes to his home
Sounded weird
I don't know
I do I do think that there is just like this
FedEx
Relationship with information
But if you pay attention to Alex's show you start to recognize over and over again
And that is exactly what he's
Sort of lashing out about In that clip about how people took me out of context and said that I was going to
Forthright
Yeah what
A gun out on the 4th but also
Nothing means anything
He's going to get killed
Before the midterms
Not predict
90%
Not going to happen
Eventually when it doesn't happen he can complain the beep
Contact shirt
Checks
Here's what we're going to talk about
Statistics
Okay if you claim that something is 95
Percent likely to happen
Is 90% likely to happen he's right 95%
All right so if you're right 95% of the time
Then that means out of every
20 examples
You're wrong one
True right
So
If you have less than
Five examples
And all of them are wrong
By what measure could you describe yourself as having anything close tonight
A lot more things than we have so far
And here's another piece of unfortunate news for Alex
If you have been right about 95% of the things of the past
But you have not
That has no bearing on
Your future prediction it is how that work be wrong 100 per-cent of the time moving for
Yeah you do not ever have more than one in whatever chance on a roulette wheel
So you can't like
Get more chance
So we jump to the 12th
And Alex is in a
A good mood
Wow the worldwide Awakening
Against the New World Order has eggs bloated
They're flying the Gadsden flag in Argentina
In Venezuela
In Sri Lanka
In Eastern Europe
In the UK
Right here in the United States and Canada
The Chinese are writing and taking over
What time is party central banks the same things happening
Other countries Dutch farmers are torching
Turn off the energy
Enemy
Play Gwar
Power outages
Launch by Russia
Okay
Alex Armenian the Dutch Farmers had burned down a factory that was owned by Bill Gates
That made synthetic meat and that's part of what he's a ranting about it that's not true
There was an online grocery service Distribution Center in the Netherlands that caught fire but it wasn't owner-operated
So once again Alex is approximately as good a source of information is your grandpa's Facebook feed
Some triumphant music
That's nice and fun
But there's a reason reason
It's not that Litany of b******* right is not the Gadsden flag being
Flown around the world
Countdown
Was
Like
But it's part of the proudest moment of my high school career when you saw a rest
Master development High School fight song
Was the final countdown
And we will play it March
Band Style
And then after the football games
We would go and we would kind of huddle right near the door and we
We play what we do you know who played double time
Blasting that song as fast as we possibly can right
So what night
I was playing in the football game
And I got a pretty serious concussion
Right but I also played in the marching band so after
The football game
I put off my drunk
Walked over there
I f****** killed it
I had a concussion
My proudest moment of high school are proud of you and I'm super happy about it so it was
You know what I'm remembering and I miss was that
I miss the times when Alex would play fight the good fight by Triumph
You know like
It's like I hate to say this because it involves your proudest moment of your life but I think that The Final Countdown to little bit hacking
High School
Life let's not go to what bar songs a little hack
It's a little bit
F***** out
It's play too much
But I haven't heard of double time by marching
I think that fight the good fight by Triumph is
Enough of like
People don't listen to
On the rocks
Stations all the
The time
You know
I don't know I feel like
I feel like Alex
You should bring back dry up how does how do you make Triumph field about
Comic I don't care
You don't think so cuz I feel like they have to get like
Triumph is good for me to poop
Somebody would do that
I think that anybody
Was going to a Triumph concert now
Your rights day baby pass the
Robert Smigel Joker
Of my
30 is a pair of Nike wheeled nerds
Real Transformers
They don't want to insult their tomorrow
I think the reason that Alex is in a good mood
Venusian zinncredible
Let me give you just one example of this and I'm sure they'll take it
Audi covering this morning's Jackman
But Alex is war is
Ugliest things I've done
And I
Really promoted it yet
And it has gone once it went on pre-order 2 days ago
Thousands of films you can pre-order
Number for
Ladies and gentlemen
Just behind Top Gun
Jurassic World
And the Justice League
We pulled past Elvis
God facing Noland
Freedom
I mean those Jessica
In the top
We are at number for headed to number one
As usual
So I guess there's a lot of pre-sales for this documentary / Puff
It's coming out at the end of the month
I guess that's big news so much so that Alex needs to open the show with it
Weird
So I can do to the champion Narcissus
It's really remarkable how about him
Over performing in pre-sales
It somehow evidence that the globalist are going down
Just that guy who gave Alex 8 million in Bitcoin
Since the film's the film's Twitter if you do it only
6700 follow
I know it's not like it's setting the world on fire there's not that much anticipation for it
Haley's book becomes a bestseller and you're like okay well if you block purchase iris flower
You go to the dollar store and there's a thousand of them are
So I wanted to learn a little more about those documentaries
John IMDb
Apparently a guy named Hadrian belove is one of the primary producers
Hadrian belove
Yeah that mean probably doesn't ring a bell to you but he used to be the executive director of cinefan
An independent leaning theater in Los Angeles
2017 email circulated that accused him of engaging in a pattern of sexual
Harassment carried out by beloved as well as other board members
Chamblee shutdown
Permanently with the board releasing a statement quote
The damage caused to the organization by the conduct of some and the crippling debt now facing the cinefamily are in the
The board's View irreparable
I don't want to go out any details but
It seems like this is a shity dude is behavior heard a bunch of people and pelvis Troy movie house that had been in business for a deck
I can see that guy making a documentary about Alex for sure
Another producer is John Isom
Who isn't the same John ice and men who killed the dude like a year ago but if you Google his name
That other dude comes up
Wild
Also produced Amanda Milius Is 2020 Trump propaganda film the plot against
The president
You can't say all vocal
Immediately after that I was like
This guy
Also killed a guy like that can't be how it goes
Also seems like somebody who would make a documentary about Alex
Movie Howie like in the early days of Studios whenever these guys would get together and
Make Ben-Hur that's the type of s*** these guys are up to
Right there's no Robert Evans Easter of them on this project
The other producer is Philip Hancock whose other credits include the plot against the president
Upcoming documentary about John McAfee called wack
I feel like I can guess what the angle of that one
It's going to be
Hancock also worked on the series called the witness project
Told stories of people who escaped for
From communism
The point is this team suck
Subjective
One of The Producers is a disgraced former member of the LA art movie scene and the other two are people whose resumes are just
Trump propaganda and anti-communist short
I'll still watch it but it's absurd to pretend that this is
Is anything other than something that the glamorized and rehabilitate Alex
His Public Image
Which is why he's promoting
Also I can
Count the number of no-name ass Comics who went to number one on iTunes when they released an album
None of these metrics really mean that much on their own and often they're pretty useful as a tool to make something look more popular
That it actually is and I would guess
What that dynamic
Is somewhat
At play here
Listen I'm not saying it's not important but I have intro'd far too many of my friends with
Their album went to number one on iTunes
For me to believe that it is a
High honor
Those sorts of charts don't
Numbers of gross downloads for a rehab
There's not a lot of
So
Alex
You know he's
Said that he has an octopus
Just before the history
Also during the deposition of his corporate representative
Add to that note
Does come up again I'm sorry what
It's going into the prisonplanet.tv archives are now free to the world
Clips
And again
Ago when I
Called for operation
Freedom really fear that
Yeah
Now they're afraid
The clip is from 50
18 years ago
They clearly haven't been that of
Nope
Not really I think maybe more just sort of like
Annoyed until 7
1976 starts to really be associated with
Violin
If you're talkin about 7076 in terms of like looking back on the founding of our country share
Hey Anjo appreciating history
I get it that's cool
Becomes a rallying cry
Like Alex uses it as right
It starts to be
Become something that is a little bit less
I appreciate our country in the freedoms that it's based on
And more we're going to do it again yeah it is a little bit like
Most of us look back on 1776 and we imagine you know something and they look back on it
In that imaginary way but in the spirit of the
The true 1776
Insofar as they're a bunch of slave-owning terrorist
And that's kind of their their jam
I also
Like
Stewart Rhodes
Desperately just
Wanted to be a
F****** soldier in a revolution
Yeah like that
That's what he wanted to be and Eve
Play that it for
For quite a while
Alex wants to be the guy who's like
Yelling
During the revolution
And unfortunately
Things of a rodent
To the point where they
They're kind of giving their wishes
Civil War reenactors
So look
Alex Hales about 1776 or maybe an entire sect
Fourth is
Is
You're either 1776
Are your 1984
Baby
All day long
What
Her boy
So yeah it it's it's
Weird it is you know that that thing that happens when you say a word over and over again it is its meaning
What happened as I was listening to him yell 1770
Also I really
Really just
Degree with a dichotomy of you can either be 1776
90s guy I'm like
The Gutenberg
Bible Gaza 4022 guy because I live in
The presence there is nothing else except this moment
But there always was this moment of the past
This is also this moment
Oh no paradox
Plural
Betty White
Jordan
Alex Optical office
I remember that vaguely about that a little bit at the beginning of the show
I want of the reasons is
Recovered it even though it's
Obviously a desperate
Publicity
Is the things taken
Call the 12th
And
Finger off
No he basically just admits that this was a troll
People
Need you to bow down.
They need you.
They need you to go along with them
Thousands of times that played the Corp
Right
On the Sunday show I was doing it
This is archetype.
This is satire
Stop saying Ark
Illustrative
But if we could defeat
The New World Order
Find me simply cutting a finger off
Blood spilling
Doing
To show the listeners and viewers how much I have
Appreciate them
Willing to give up my body
In the fight
Why would I not
Join the mafia
He didn't even say that stuff you didn't say it was that tire
Because he says that all the time
So at no point did Alex say that what he was doing with threatening to cut off his finger was
It was meant to get attention by trolling Tubidy
It was really obvious to me that this was his goal because he's a transparent con man but if you were a person who liked his
Show and thought he meant anything he said
You would not take this as a publicity stunt or satire
You would read this as an
An expression of his sincere feelings of appreciation for the audience
Sacrifice that he's willing to make
The defeated imaginary items
Obviously Alex was just trying to trick Publications with wider audiences than his into writing articles about him
Misrepresented what he did
Which is another example of how the media always lies about
That's one
Hammocks at play here too
The first is that Alex probably knew that the January 6th committee was having their hearing on Tuesday and the topic of it at
Announced as the connection
Ministration extremist groups that Alex is deeply entwined with
I don't think this is the case but I don't think it's impossible that Alex would try to do some kind of a media stock to attempt
How to control the narrative is about him
Do people be talking about him threatening to cut off his finger instead of his clear association with a bunch of really suspicious groups
Score charged with seditious
Conspiracy
The second thing
Is much less speculative and more
Alex is trolling the media to get attention
That is true
But this Cuts both directions
When Alex was talking about God and how he would cut off his finger as a tribute to his amazing audience
He was also trolling his audience with his performance of sincerity
That wasn't sincere at all but it was meant to be
Experience as if it were
Alex has gotten himself in a certain position where in order to pull off dump licity stunts like this
You have to exploit the parasocial connection he has with his listeners
And make them the ultimate butt of the joke
Anyone wrote an article about this was playing into Alex's
Plan but the real idiot here is anyone listen to Alex do his whole Act
And took it to mean any
Oz business model relies on a really uncomfortable intersection
He needs to appear sincere enough to convince his audience that he would do something like cut his finger off so they can
Feel that level of commit
The fight
Which is code for
You need to give me money
Essentially no access to any media that exposes his content
To nuada
His Radio reaches non-existent he's not allowed on YouTube or social media
He can get his audience on banned. Video but those are people who are in the already
They're already in the pool
In order to Lorde new people into the web
Do you need the audience to recruit or he needs to hijack other people's media
Which is why going on Rogan is so important
That's why he's heavily promoting this documentary
NYU does s*** like pretending to be so committed to fighting the globalist
So you cut his finger off
Other people would write stories about him
And tequila
Get them talking about him
In places you wouldn't be talking about otherwise we got high with Ty
Alex's on the ship
Before he's even threatened to cut off fingers
Before because he's not that
Creative
It's pretty f***** up any of that big ass knife at Arm's Reach while he's doing his show though
Very sad and I mean this from the bottom of my
People need to ignore this kind of unless they're able or willing
Discovery in its full context highlighting
Desperate nature of these cries for attention
Because here's the thing to remember
Without anyone covering this.
It's no longer a star
It's just a sad loser threatening to cut off his
His finger in front of his captive audience
And no one caring
That's the way it should be
Because that's the reality of what this is
Yeah yeah
Yeah I hope those people feel bad
Everybody involved
Should feel at least a little bit of shame I really think that I understand what your job is but
You should feel shame if you got at least by Alex Jones this bad don't know if it's actually that bad of a fleecing like I do
Don't know if you saw that concrete of a game from that attention
Didn't work out the way Alex wanted it
Because here's what he had to do neck
Mediaite
All of them ran the story
Last night today
It's in thousands of Publications
Is mentally ill
Finger off
Manisha
No I said
Joseph
We cut the balls off
In the UK and European 11 Canada New Zealand Australia
You're old
Because the government convinces them there a girl
Little boy has their penis cut off
Penises
I'm going to get up right now
I'm going to cut my penis off
That would be stunning and brave
Alex
Continue on from his finger cutting thing into his normal transphobic bulshit
He just took some
Calls
This is just Alex attempting to escalate the police
The Beast.
He's high on pulling off that first one so he's trying to double down and apparently no one
I'm scared this time
This is legitimate lie like a kid getting a bunch of attention
For eating a bug trying to get more attention by eating a bigger bug and then too late
The people really aren't into watching people eat bugs they were just laughing at him
And now the joke has run its
Of course Novelty Ohio
I'm a say this too much
I am special and this episode but this is absolutely pathetic
It's so transparent A desperate in this one work
So poorly headline on his website
Alex now threatens to cut his pee
Penis off
Adult
It's been a long time since I thought about
Kafka's the hunger art
But I am really getting that Vibe here
Except
In kafka's way he was kind of turning it into a sort of noble situation
You know suffering for ones
It's a little bit different but if he'd cut his finger off then I would actually go with it yeah
Text drops that I couldn't play it
The beginning of the show
I'm going to cut my penis off
Here's the other one
Penis
Those are to be sampled again sooner or later
Technocrat is going to hear that
Boy
Anyway this is all just nonsense that he transitions into
The publicity stunt
Detention
Theoretically gained from it
I've been trying to reach
Contextualize the whole idea of cutting off his finger versus cutting off his
Is dick
I'm going to get up right now
I'm going to cut my penis off
Would be
Host
What I say I'll
Cut my finger off
To show you how much I appreciate you
And a flip-out
Oh my God
Liberal
But Joan says
You cut my finger off
Call Ironman
Oh no not you know I'll do it so
Is a child trying to impress
Absolutely
Hey man you know it I'm that kind of crazy dude that's why you keep me around
It's so desperate but like
The desperation
Really the reason that it hits that nerve or whatever is
Is because the desperation is covering up the reality that know you would
Absolutely not and we know it I don't care whether you cut your finger off or not
It's D
Beef cutting your finger off is a way of discussing your ultimate commitment
Do this fake cause
That's right that you've dedicated your life
You're not really that committed
Nothing to do with whether or not you cut your finger off
All you have is anybody called you
You make me very sad
You know I do it
Hold me back
Colby-Jack
I'll be back if I if you guys were holding me I would cut his finger off
Totally
So we have one last night but I was talking about
Cutting his dick off
So it's all over the news
Associated Press is everywhere
Jones
What About Us
Oh my God
But it was
Little children's balls and penis has been cut off is good
Carrabba's bad which way is it
Nice illustration of how Alex teaches is audience to accept incorporate bad thinking pattern
A relationship with
Information
The purposes of this explanation
I'm going to translate Alex saying supporting cutting kids balls off to me
Supporting trans people existing
Because that's what he's talk
He's framing is disgusting a defensive but at the end of the day he's not literally talking about cutting peoples balls off he's talked about any
Any kind of trans affirming activity
When understood of the proper context is dichotomy makes no sense
It's not a matter of not being able to have it both ways
These are unrelated
Good things
Easily support trans rights and also think that I was probably
Shouldn't cut his finger off
Reason that
Interesting start was cutting your finger off is because people who are unfamiliar could be like
Maybe that guy is crazy enough to actually cut his finger off
There is that level of
Perhaps it's in the possibility of possible rain and also I don't think anybody was like oh Alex is bad
For cutting his finger off or he shouldn't cut his finger I don't think I'm cut his finger off
Honestly I think ever
Everybody who saw that headline
And has any familiarity with him to be like
No not this ends with no finger everybody's time
For sure so look me up a larger picture is it
No I was saying I was
Shouldn't cut off a
Finger
The media article that this was that was what the root of this is basically
It's just a transcript of what Alex said on his Sunday show with this little intro
Controversial radio host Alex Jones
Took an alarming route when making an impact
Speech about his appreciation towards his audience
That's fair
Yeah weird
Google is it cut your finger off it's alarming
Jeff said he had a knife
There that is alarming but also that's how you know is a pre-planned dumb stunts
I actually choose to believe that that night is always there
That's fair I just underneath the skull
Think that there is something
Weird about this predictable
And sad
The way that I was just trying to make transphobic lemonade
Out of this
You know it it's
It's it's
What's
What's what it is
What it is is just that point that you made it
Trans people
Existing
He's using this kind of example as a way of making it
Visceral thing for people who don't have any trans people in their Library
Always brand
Your kids balls off it's something that's like
Disgusting
Anybody
But doesn't mean like oh if this actually happened
If somebody says they're trans
That's what he's going to assuming that's what is priming is audience to assume and that's the
That's just exist
I'm let swimming be totally clear about something
Is there were trans
Person
Oh they're doing the radio show and they said
I'm going
Going to cut my dick off on air
ABI would be upset by that
No even if they said I'm going to cut my dick off during the
The commercial break that would be upset I just I mean
Unsanitary
Adapt that's not the surgery either it's not a f****** nice
It's not like they put an iPhone a hot plate and then they're like well we got to solve this problem
Alex take some calls
After this
Has come to a close here
This color is a little bit confused I can clear it up
With a lot of people
Early College especially they just don't care
They don't care what
I'm wearing a shirt
It's usually the only people that
Respond so I was thinking maybe we should like
Megafon live video or Patriots you know
Just blast
Highlights of Infowars clips
Out in public
Some areas young people are awake
Younger people been talk to me
Jellyfish to not care
Yeah if young people that are the problem
No
Is almost entirely
Cold
The new young people are responding well to do yourself
Because young people
Don't buy into this
Load of s***
And the solution is not to force everyone in public to listen to
To Alex's insane disgusting Rambo
Yeah I appreciate anybody who can
Find
A
Soul
Boiled down
Cause and effect
Problem
And still with
You know that is there
So many times where everything is confusing there's so much information that doesn't necessarily have a have any of
Effect on things but you feel like it does there's so much nuance
You're not sure what you're supposed
But every now and again something is
Boiled down to so simple that it's a yes or no question like a real
Solid binary
And he's still with
Amazed
Amazing
I like that the solution is just like well people don't like him for
Let's force them to listen thought process that's exactly what he is
Taught you to think
Now people are not watching the panda video down and prop their eyes open
It does Alex does presented in the Innocence though of like
You're doing
Good these people are are it's not that they don't want to listen
Right
Get that moment then they're automatically convert
Not like
If you play this at high-volume people are going to attack you
Sooner or later there will be an attack
Packed out
The 25 year-old lamenting
Jerk with Alex Jones isn't more popular
This rally and I'm surrounded by Nazis I really don't know why there's so many Nazis at this rally
So crazy
Is
I mean I've been to that I've been bummed out by some of these calls so far
It's called bums me out on a visceral level
Josh Josh
You for taking my call
It's a real honor to be on
Michelle
But
But I really wanted to talk about
Was Klaus Schwab
And how he is
Making masks
And his little
Mind game offense
And I'm just
Not going to
Stanford
Josh how old are you
I'm an eleven-year-old info Warrior
You f****** with us Josh
Black beautiful Josh how did you find the show and what do you want to say to
Millions of people right now
I found it because my dad watches it
Interesting
And I
And I find call Schwab
Barry
I don't even know but
I just really wanted to get that off
Call Schwab
Making of
Making us
I know you don't mind
Car shops making us
Puppets in his little mind
Is in fifth
Great when I was 11 the main the main villain was f****** Shredder
Okay letter is a problem is not a problem dr. Wily
Years old
Outlook
It's it's it hurts your brand if you're Alex
And you say
I appreciate the call I can't talk to an 11 year old
You're not you don't have the intellectual maturity or just be
Like you can't possibly process the information that
Is being put forth on the show
He has a responsibility to do something like that
He can't take a call from an 11 year old is complaining about clothes Swap and be like all this is
Beautiful
An eleven-year-old doesn't know what the world economic forum is
11 year old probably has difficulty understanding
Other countries forms of
What you say
It's not even it's not even just that maybe
He does know that those things are at
Nothing but the ability to comprehend
Woody's that they exist in the ecosystem that all this around this is impossible
And you can even
Hear that in the concrete way that he's expressing total this is a line
Klaus Schwab is making us puppets
It's in his little mind game
That is a concrete sentence that he is either
He's repeating
Or is the way that he's able
To save it
There is an abstraction around the ideas
It's really really f****** inappropriate
I feel bad for this kid and
Remember the other content that's going on in this episode Alex just got done talking about I was going to cut his dick off
This is not okay for 11 year olds to be listening I mean it really does feel
If it was our show
That we
It's okay call from 11 my first
Hey excuse me tell your parents never to let you listen to the show
Maybe when you're an adult and you can make your own
Choices but otherwise
I'm mad
You should go spank your parents that is what we should be doing right here
Inverse banking my childhood should come full circle
Nah
So we won last call here and this guy
Daddy is about Georgia
Wanted to let you know
Smoke and mirrors
We got stuff
Still
The Albertson Granite Association Vice Pres
Albertsons mayor Daniel Craig
Your name
Yes you can
1 years
Again
The governing Authority dollar King County's who owns that land
Downey weather
And tell them
Capri bill that's literally all it would take
But the reason that they're saying that is intact on the community and the reason they would want to rebuild it is
Of course because it brought a ton
Of traffic
To the area
Business to the local
Accounted for a lot of the town's Revenue
Quite frankly I don't know why anybody else is going to Elberton
George
So there would be very high motive
4 people
To rebuild them
I did not suspicious at all today
Based on his whole presentation of like this isn't the right thing to do
Chuckling when he says that can't wait for someone to blow them up again
I'm right
Yeah but
Kind of like
So
Political terrorism
You're trying to intimidate a group that occurs
Sure
This
He's trying to intimidate the global
Right
This is an imaginary group that does not have
Exist
Is it is difficult to intimidate
San Jose
That is currently very difficult
To do
I mean
I would argue if I were lawyer
Normally
Normally I'm against
This however
If if
We can eliminate all of our other conversations
And turn just the Georgia Guidestones
Into the ultimate proxy war
Between conservative ism
And progressivism
Just never ending
Arms race to build and destroy those very still while the rest of us get to live our lives
I think I'll be great
But I don't think the progressives have
An interest in rebuilding them in Elberton done
It'll be a war between the Elberton Business Association
And conspiracy weirdo
Yeah that is the problem with my plan
You could make it a proxy war and that we are at siding with Alberton and they're siding with
Discount america
Plus Albertsons
Of the other side is in prison
Right round
Jefferson Davis
This is Dad so he can't come back
About his ancestors are still alive
Come to the end of this and I think Alex heard you yell
Cut his dick off
To literally
It's becoming a more common
Rallycross
This is a bummer I mean Lord is a real bummer
This is not like on the level of some of the other
Publicity stunt
That have worked in Alex's advantage
Some of the other ones we've seen
Obviously was like
Call Mike
You should have better instinct
Because of the the nature of
Giving
You will
To this
Exposure fire
Needs to operate
Without the artificial inflation from people
Posting
These little videos and talking about him cutting his finger off
Without all that
It's a
Publicity stunt without a stock
It's just
Us going look at how sad this is
And that's
Great
For the world that's the best way to do it yeah you know what wasn't like a big cycle on Twitter
Alex throwing a hatchet at a camera on Christmas Eve
That's good clean fun
I demanded okay
Here's here's my
Demand of the media
Okay alright
The next
Time Alex threatened
To cut anything off
Everybody publishes one article on every page which is just
If you don't cut that off will never talk about you again
Yeah that's that's
Steaks on there
I don't care I don't care if he does or doesn't
But somebody eventually has to decide okay or every headline has to include Alex
Engages in a
Pathetic 100%
Yeah Tim in the headline every chance you get
A upsetting
Fairy thing
Really wants people to look at him if you know it's a publicity stunt
Then York
Play sit in it
That's just the truth because your headline cookie but instead of
I suggest that there are some people who still don't quite understand fully
You are not
Knowingly playing into these.
I would just wish that everybody who's in a position to
You put out an article
Would learn that lesson is that
So this oxygen
Feed this publicity fire
Won't be there anymore
And it'll just be sad Alex drunk
Only throwing hatchets on Christmas Eve
And we can all have a good time
Oh man I hate it when are solutions always come back to learning and the woohoo that's not good
There's four ways to
That is true none of them are listening to us apparently apparently not
Indeed but until then
Before we do it.
There's also some controversial
Reviews on the movie Summer on the GoFundMe
Then also you don't have to see these controversial reviews
But I don't know there's just controversial reviews
About supposed to really controversial one
Right now
Are you click on it
What's up
Bananas
Great
Not about Jenny's flavor
Buttermilk Milk Bar flavors
Anyway look forward for that
Dreamy creamy sauce
And now here comes
The sex robot