I have great respect for its knowledge B
Knowledge
Knowledge fight
Nike.com
Groundworks but the elders Lane and also talked a little bit about Alex Jones
Question for you my friend
Today
My bright spot today Jordan
Side braids
My aunt was in town this weekend for dinner
But she was
Flipping the bill
Went to Morton
The steakhouse almost got a Sunday there legendary Sunday
Mccreamy summer
I saw them walk by with one and
There was no f****** way I was
It was like a fishbowl massive
You should go there just for that
Bright spot is
Polar
Self
Haha and I tried it and it is
Really honestly thing
This would do numbers
In the year of the seltzer
Haven't been around it is a pink Apple lemon
Flavored seltzer
Entities
Honey Honeycrisp apple
I'm fascinated by this pink Apple m
Plus a Honeycrisp apple
No pink Apple and lemon not pink lemonade and apple but I mean the Apple before
Pig lady
What about the kind of apple I understand people
I know exactly what I'm saying
Pick up the phone
It's so good
It's a refreshing
I believe you
Oh my God
I like apple juice
Too sweet I also paid little bitter
Bright sometimes you get at a bar
Little stupid little too sour
This is right in the middle
Nice sweet spot good stuff
So good
Alright probably 97
Make a few ways but it could be better
Right
I think Loki might be the best
See if that's recency bias I'm going to have to say that you're not
Just start over from the beginning Andre taste all of those up
My bright spot
What is a Dragon Ball Z
Vu my friend
As we progressing
I'm clearly regressing into a childlike state
And I was like
What am I what do I need to do and I realized
I needed a soap opera
Dragon Ball Z is it's just like professional wrestling it's a soap opera
With fight
Scenes from time to time
It's all about the build-up and then the fight is actually kind of boring honestly
Edibles
The formula is
Non-stop this a commitment
Formula
So staid and boring
Then it's almost admirable
I'm sorry I'm barely paying attention I'm really trying to figure out a way to make RuPaul's Dragon Ball races e work
No
Can't make it work
It's not going to happen there's a pond in there my friend I really wish there was but I think he I better Minds than you
Giving themselves mad trying to fight it I've seen the best
To make this pain
Well I'm glad you're enjoying.
So Jordan today we have an episode to go over and I'll explain all about it
Let's say hello.
Does the new Wok
The look of confusion on the waitresses face at Olive Garden when I tried to order the Lionel's ferlinghetti thank you so much you are now
Ewok
I'd like to do punch up on this and meatballs
That's a little bit better in a workshop talking about your jokes
That's the meatballs
Live tonight it's.
Pizza in The Bachelor Squatch Trio thank you so much you're now about siwa
Sorry about this one a little bit late
This is a Happy Father's Day
Father's Day
Narc
Funko thank you so much
Thank you very much
So first
And Luke loves Josie and both of us love this podcast thank you so much
I'm a policy
I have
Risen above
A little breaking for me
And then we're going
To come back
And I'm going to
Start the show over
F*** you
I got plenty work for you but
At the end of the day
F*** you and your new world order
She rode in on
And all your s***
Maybe later on West Broad
Maybe I'll just be gone a month baby
I'm Yours
Walk out of here tomorrow
And you never see me again
Really what I want to do
Back here again
Apologized
To the crew in the Lester Chester
Was legitimately having breakdowns on air
Better tomorrow
Never will be a never was
So
Today
Jordan
I'm sick of Ali
What is bulshit
The publicity stunt ship from last week
Just very annoying
Really drains you
But simultaneously there's not a lot of other
Very good Outlet
Still looking
Jim Bakker dry well
I don't know where to go with that go back to the forest on that one too many times
Boring boring Lake
Wasting my time
Justin
Until I realized there was something that I had been meaning to do for awhile
And that is
Go over
September 11th
What's 2001
Oh my god do you know how funny that is
Because of the did you see the picture going around apparently
ESPN Yankees
Red Sox
Oh that picture funny super embarrassed
A little bit of timing
Here's the situation like
One of the
Reasons we haven't covered this already was
Was I
Have access to the audio initially when we first started this
Cafe
That was a limiting factor
Actor Eminem as we go further into
The podcast
I kind of thought like I will save this right this for something and
Stupidly I was like
What's up with her like we do it live or do it live on land
Gradually that felt like
That's never go
Going to be a good idea
I don't know an argument could be made that a professional podcaster might have done this for like episode 700 as opposed to
I really don't understand
Why why have we numbered are episodes in the first place it was a bad idea either of us remember
It's just for people to have shorthand for like it was
You do it's like putting a piano your your pulled into the numbers game not
Exactly
September
Importantly number episode
During the day
Write a letter we're going to be talking about
Then on what
Today we're going to be covering Alex's
Evening show
These back on air from 9 to midnight that night
And so obviously there's going to be different amounts of information that he
He's privy to different things will have happened right
Into over the course of these next
Couple episodes
What's we will
Experience he's immediacy and he's like a little time to simmer
I'll see if there's any differences will see
We will see how this goes
Texting him being correct about Saddam son still being alive
That's
Doesn't come out
Made it to go forward to this
For now is it also we're going to be in Austin going to be
Doing a bit of like
Present-day coverage of Alec
It feels like let's
Let's have some fun while we can
Where to be doing plenty of present-day Alex
640 wires
Super informative
In the way that I kind of like a lot of the
Botanigard show to me
It is theirs revelatory thing
Cuz when you go to the Past
What the f*** are you talkin about
Runner-ups not as much of that in the present-day so
In the present is supposed
Was too revealing
Can you believe this
Smoke them all you got them
I'm feeling I got that we live
Here we go here is how Alex is starting off the show and I will say that this is about exactly what you would expect
He's recounting the events that have happened
Uphill
But he gets on arrogance out
Released 5 years wow
Oklahoma City to Waco
Has been government action
I need versus a pre-tax
To bring you and your family
Martial law
Breather using
Couture Arabs in allowing a druid
Or this is for complicit
Complicity
How will the federal government
The evidence is overwhelming to bring you up to speed on what
What's happened
Add to a 8:50 a.m. EDT plane hits World Trade Center 920 FDIC
At least one plane
Hijack
9:30
Eastern second jet crashed in the World Trade Center
Plane hits Pentagon 945
Official said at us airplane
World Trade Center building
All u.s. building
Things in Capitol Hill evacuated 1013 1015 World Trade Center
South Tower collapse
Report explosion at Capitol
10:30 us Congressional leaders Top Cab
Beneficials movies
Anchor
Another hijack plane
Reported 20
Minutes south of Washington
DC second tower North collapse
Hijack plane crash
Pittsburgh PA officials
Investigating another hijacking
For the plane headed towards d.c.
Federal Building
DC have been evacuated so
Airplanes are in the antler finding bombs
Stools
Cracks in the World Trade Center
So here we see the way Alex opens up the show on 9/11
Then there's a couple of things that stick out to me in a pretty serious way
The first has to do with the end of a clip where Alex says that we're told there other planes in the air and they're finding bombs
The school
Uclear in the statement at this point
They have no idea if the things that are coming in or Acura
There's an understanding that the immediacy of the event
That's great the fog of uncertain
The end that's not something
The feels the same as how Alex operates
Today
The second thing I found really interesting is that Alex's take on this is exactly what
You think it would
Immediately this is declared a false flag it has to be because that's how the globalists are going
To bring in martial law
Happen
There would have gotten worse since
In terms of surveillance
Police militarization
To martial law
These are the objectives of this false flag
Because they're the objectives Alex
It's always immediately declares to blame his imaginary
Periphery tragic event
Sakura's in this just
Sing with that for sure
The third thing I want to point out is that Alex is already declared this a false flag
He knows literally nothing that will eventually appear in his documentaries about 9/11
All of the real or imagined anomalies
In order to build his case
This is critical
Because it really does illustrate how he arrived at his conclusion long before seeking out evidence
Which is not a good process
I guess what I'm saying
Is it Alice if Alex knew that this was a false flag hours before building
7-Eleven
Then he shouldn't be able to use Building 7 in his explanation of what makes
If the argument
This was a false flag
All the evidence he should need to present Hast
Has had prior to his determination that this
The false flag
Girls that evidence is no longer really evidence necessarily released its suspicious
Just that it could be trivia that he sought after
To justify that
Conclusion that he wanted
To push
And I think that description is really app
If you look at the
Conspiracy theories that were pushed in films like the Alex produced loose change
Which is also produced by Infowars
Employee Jason bermas
Aka the info Warrior
You start to get the picture that this was the
The process that Alex world was using to deal with information
That documentary had to be re-released Multan
Bull times because things at the Fillmore debunked
To the point making their inclusion in the documentary embarrass
For instance
It's in various incarnations of the film Flight 93 was originally shot down and then it was diverted to Cleveland Hopkins
Airport
And then that entire storyline was edited out
The Final Cut
It's important to keep his dynamic in our heads as we experience the way Alex covers Today's tragedy
He already
Has a conclusion
And he's trying to find Justin
Vacation
Conclusion whether or not
That justification means anything or is he even real
You have quite a response there though
I mean.
The new have you seen the new edit of his 911 movie
I've not it's just him gone
NFL all the embarrassing part was left behind all that's left behind
This is about me
Yes I know that the World Trade Center is literally still on fire but I told Kyle
That is amazing to meet you know
Pretty shity like
In the present day
You hear him do s*** like that for a mass shooting and you go Jesus Christ that's f***** up
Yeah I know
What you feel like that's with 30 years of being a giant piece of s*** under your belt
You know that right out the gate
On 911 he's like
Called it story
Yeah
Insane Psychopathic narcissist serial killer level s***
911 and being it's cool
I remember the teachers being very
Somberg there was a tonne of like
A lot of
I just ate
Feels really absent from Alex
I mean this to is
Like
If you listen to the episode of like Bill Cooper after a tragedy
I believe
I think it was the episode
For Columbine
That you can
Confined
And he's crying
About the tragedy and
How he feels are these families
I got the kids
You know a lake
I don't want to
Bf5 Bill Cooper he's an a****** absolutely
Recognized on some way that there's
The people are hurting
And it's okay to hurt
At all
No he's an absolute psychopath like there's really no way to describe them other than a complete psycho
Can an hour and a half after the planes hit the building
I am he's
He's on there being like done it again
Wow
That was amazing
There were high school kids
In my
Leaving prayer circle people who weren't religious were joining
Unlock the door in there people in circles like all the sudden there rip rained all kinds of Gods
I recall that
Dude the school the high school that I went to they
Basically made a thing goes like if you want to go home you can
Yeah but if you want to stay at school all the rest
The classes for the rest
The day I just basically going to be weird
Work through like how to process what happened
Weirdly I had a psychology class
Bad afternoon
Actually kind of failed with like
Dealing with trauma and like
I think I think there was
A lot of that process
LOL
This is not that
No
That's amazing really weird to fix it like I was in this
Class
Talking about Lee everyone's opening up with her
The feelings about this and like
Some people had family who lived in New York
If you're talkin about their fears about it absolutely not being able to contact folks
Simultaneously in Austin Texas
Alex's recordings this
Board for
Alex
Thank you so he
Talking about who he's got
How to talk to the
This is
Pandemic
This is one of the biggest stories
Alba last century and now in
First century
We're going to have Dave on class enjoyed finally joining other Genesis host at want to wish
Limbs
In New York
That's coming up at this break
Is cell phone hold
Jim right we don't have a landline for in the landlines aren't working too well
The pleistocene
Sort of
No
Recognizing the gravity of the
The situation I suppose sometimes
There'll just be like some weird anti-vax
Fake talking point. Traffic is the biggest story of his wife
Is recognizing that fact is the biggest thing by century
Great you almost expect him to call Steve and Steve is in New York City
Call Jesus Alex you didn't even ask if I was doing alright
I was I wasn't in the building but I'm next door malak's this isn't going to make sense but you've got a call Leo zagami
Bench for his guest is shallow
But there are no Heavy Hitters that he can get on the show
Just others
Gcn host
And this
Jim Wright guy who's a personal friend of his who is
They are and saw the attack first
I think he's
Married
To Alex's sister or something like that shares a familial connect
Said he's a friend of his
He doesn't actually meet Steve pieczenik until 2
2000 to 12 years
But it seems strange
But he couldn't get likes
Steve Quayle or Joel skousen on
Some of these Old-Timers who are like
Real anti-communist weirdos be Loosely connected
Did the gcn folks they would later be his standby experts like Webster Tarpley or Stanley Monteith
Reven Alan Watts
Not Alan Watts
This doesn't mean anything but it's something to know none of the good weirdos are around at this point it is just
Whoever else is associated with dcnr is friends with Alex
Yeah is it that so much or is it possible he tried to get in contact with them and they were like
Do you realize that
911 is happening right now
Cut this clip
Because there's they're psychos.
I think if people recognize that Alex
Was a useful
Place to appear then right
Then I think they would probably make time
I think that Alex is a useful place
To appear at this point
He does mention
Benton Capehart
Who's the guy who OKC Oklahoma City conspiracy theory and
Farmer General
Airport
Development that sounds true
And at 1
Point his producer says that
They're trying to call him and they're getting a busy signal Alex
Announces on air
Stop trying to call Ben 10
Have his phone number
Larry Nichols gave out his number on air
Now I'm in this place where I'm like
Is there a is there a heist
Putting together a crew moment for Alec
He's like
Walking into Webster Tarpley
Bar one time and just like looking at him across are just like
It's time to get back on the horse you know I kind of assumed it was a borrowed be Big Jim Tucker
That's what I was thinking of an alcoholic
From a glass of whiskey neat
Denny's like
New York
It's time for another job
A ride horses to Bilderberg
It needs to happen
So Alex has some
Evidence that he points
To build his case that this is a false flag
Can you go to infowars.com you'll find some
Aberdeen
Sun where the
Joint Chiefs of Staff
We're going to blow up
Civilian airliners
Attacked Marines
Guantanamo Bay
Army company
Disguised as Cubans
A bomb Washington DC
We have a James Bamford
Story
Best selling author for 2020 executive
With the CIA and NSA documents
The past wanted to blow up civilian Airlines wanted to bomb Washington
Wanted to shoot
How people in Miami is
The pretext to invade
Cuba
In 1962
Infowars.com
Mainstream
Later
His head was blown off
We are becoming
Society in 2000
This is Operation Northwoods
But he doesn't use the name
You mentioned it multiple times
But I don't know if he knows the name
Or if he just doesn't
Trust that the audience will know the name
And understand what he's talking about that is interesting
Has that be I mean
Clearly
I didn't know about it
In 2000
A White Wave wouldn't surprise me if that
Spit particular thing gained more prominence awareness in the greater
If you're going to talk about this
And you know a lot about it
You might want to give people shorthand they can use to look into it
A little bit easier than
I guess
I'll try and figure out what
Land JFK turn down an operation Northwoods it's a little bit easier to
Look into it that is true
I don't know if it's a negligence or if it's
Just Alex being a
I could be could be anything
Could just be he's Green Man he's not he's not that he's still young he doesn't know everything yet.
Years and hours of study to put in 15 hours a day
Same amount of effort
How many beats
He could make if he was coffee
A total of
16 Beats
Is the number he could bake
So I look
I think
Alex
Doesn't have
Have a great evidence
Here's a little
But more evidence
Back in 1993
What's in the New York Times October 28th
Rainbow bomber
Crane betrivers
And allowed that bombing to go forward
They got caught
Telling him to like Obama
She was worried about
Ben cream for
What am I saying I'm saying who
Who stands to gain from this
Who has the motive
So prove any of this stuff about the prior bombing
Another World Trade Center
This all comes
Comments made by Ahmad Salaam
The FBI who had a fuse inside the group
But that was planning that bomber
Small concrete information the FBI was aware that a bombing was being planned but they weren't aware of the
The specific details
After the bombing salaam recorded conversations between himself and the FBI where he made claims like that the
Bomb was cooked with the supervision of quote
The bureau and the DEA
But that's not something that's been substantiated
And it was widely investigated and reported
Impressed at the time committed admitted to committing perjury and also
Flying a bunch
For instance he admitted that quote when he met his wife he brags falsely that he acted as security for the president of Egypt
This is from an article for 1995
When the LA Times began working with the FBI in May 1991
During that time he said he lied to an FBI
Bragging that he knew Libya's leader moammar Kadafi and a rock's president Saddam Hussein
Military anatomic capabilities of other come
In addition to that he lied under oath while serving as a state witness so his credibility isn't strong enough to serve as the
Firestone have a conspiracy that the government did the prior bombing or Dynamite
This is exactly what you want to believe so he
Critically accept whatever information allows him to justify the
Conclusion he would
With or without ever
This is basically his whole game
What we got
Yep
Here's my here's my feeling
Okay
It's
You lied to the FBI
And they believed you
That's on them
I feel like that should be the rule
For the FBI's you should be able to you should know you're the FBI or the CIA
The FBI or the CIA and have them go
Sounds good to me boss and then get to work
It's fanciful the way you think
I hold them to a higher standard of being able to at least look into whether or not a liar is lying to them
Weather whether or not
4 alive
I think that it is indicative of your credibility if you lie so that's more
Mypoints
Killer only got caught because
He said
A disc
To the police
Part of the conditions of him sending this floppy disk to the police
Was that they had to promise not to trace
Until they did absolutely. I'm just saying that the
Play I should take responsibility for their own f******
They should be like Oh I'm mad at this guy I'm sure that guy committed perjury.
A fair world and just
Shouldn't be able to be punished for successfully lying
To feel that way if you successfully lied to the FBI venue will Nikki
Trouble anyway
Food delivery
Want you to the statute of limitations I feel like that's important
That's great I'm glad we had this policy has a number that he's going to put on the percentage
This was a false flag
Media
Able to get him via his cell phone
They're on the scene a month
Please be praying for the dead and dying
Yeah you sound sincere
Babylon
Create something like this
I'll tell you the bottom line
98%
Orchestrated
Control Bonnie
I've been telling you this was going to happen 98
Percent chance
Hi
Trinity
Boilerplate for him it's
Do you know there's a little bit later we can already see the kernels of it
Feels like a little bit autopilot here on 9/11
I mean other than like
I feel like he's excited
You know he's like oh s*** 911 this is a big deal
The amount of audience
Probably does this is a very early example of the tragedy is good for business
Kind of situation here
Yeah I definitely think so
It's cynical man
Yeah it's really Bleak delivered to this this image of
Wolf yeah
It is it is always interesting to me
Whenever he's
Adding like
This modern-day Babylon wear
Like
He saying we haven't,
You know he's saying time
The government did it to us
If we hadn't created such a shity society then the government would have done this to understand
Push and pull exist in the present day to like destroy us
Go because we have abortions
Stream Christian right
This this
Like
Notion that we deserve this punishment that's coming
That the punishment is almost
It's like a holy
And the unspoken part of that is
Everybody else that there's that punishment
Right we are The Devout who will be the remnants binocular 5 this
This holy punishment
Hold on to those thoughts because this
A rollator
Explicitly the feelings are already getting
So
Look Alex had some other stories
In addition to stories that he covered
About the
Becoming of
Realized
I should probably stop saying look
But before every Clips appointed me as well
Digression
I'm getting a little self-conscious
About that out of nowhere
But Alex has some other stories that he was covering that he feels
Possibly perfect
Everyday
I read news stories today
They were telling you that
We're going to be hit by terrorists
But it was going to happen anytime give up your ride
I've been telling us we're going to get hit by an
Anthrax
Smallpox
The API
Report on a secret meeting
Stop the heads of the
The media
Was fake news cast
They produced
I'm back
Gianna Jun
What I predicted 124
Going dead from anthrax
Martial law
The term used
I'm not saying this
Going to happen
But they've been preparing for it and they
Haven't seen
It's going to happen
It's a little interesting to note that Alex was in a decent ballpark here in terms of talking about smallpox
Anthrax
I don't necessarily give him credit for protecting anything but it was a topic that would become much more relevant to the days after 9
It's not surprising
After a giant terrorist attack you would be concerned about another attack happen
Putting antibiotic agent would be a really devastating second hit
So if you're the government you'd want to be safe
Thus after 9/11 discussion about the
Agent since they are
Pretty common
Accessible and Dangerous Ones
But you'll be worried about terrorist
Getting ahold of end-user
As for why I was talking to bunch about these things
Before 911
I have a few theories
The first is that in 1998 the military made Anthrax vaccination man
Natori
2000 with a very high-profile case
Eye of major Sunnyvale
Who refused to take the vaccine
And was ultimately discharged
From the service
After this base embarked on a long journey of trying to sue folks about the vaccination if you consult some of the
Contemporary material
It really reads a lot like
The talking points about the covid vaccine
Today
For instance here's a bit from the washing
The Post article about Sony's lawsuit against the FDA from May 2001
The suit seeks a court order that would require the FDA to treat the vaccine as anak
Experimental drug
Such a ruling with me
I mean the military could no longer without informing
To be clear enlisted person still have the right to informed
Toby policies in place where refusal to accept something will violate the terms of their
But these are not
Killed
Don't sneak up on them
Behind
Going to spend the next twenty years in the brig
It's just like oh I mean
Yeah we get it
And if that's what you want to do that's dumb but I mean you're just fired by that's fine why would we not want
All of our soldiers to be immune to a possible weapon
Cuz what if
Dand
So this is a going I'd like you hear that same thing like the emergency experimental drug
Kind of language that is mirrored and echoed
Entirely 20 years later
This is essentially right now it's his wheelhouse this story
So I would guess that the odds are very good
But he was following this
Entire situation in creating exaggerated narratives out of it
Which would make Anthrax a really hot topic on his show in the anthrax vaccine now they want to force it on you
And honestly maybe it wouldn't have been relevant to most
People until after 9/11 gives the appearance of Alex talking
Think about this whole lot
Rite Aid package
Because he was
Hey Matt hey
Niche
Area of focus
Guess for instance
The military and tobacco
Oxidation
He will have that kind of information to other people
Just wouldn't be aware of it
I'm so for the meeting of the media and the Joint Chiefs this took a little while to sort out what I think is going on
Pretty confident about this 2000
Tabletop tabletop exercise where they simulated biological terrorist
Attack that you smallpox
The agent in the fictional scenario
This with a lot of the details that Alex was talking about and some of the participants in the exercise included members of the press
Like Judith Miller from The New York Times and Mary Walsh from CBS News
It also included people had policy experience taking on the roles of people in important government position
For instance David gergen played the National Security advisor
Although he was not
General John student
Chiefs
In the scenario
And unfortunately high percentage of Alex's narrative
About reality come from selectively misrepresenting things that people do
In scenario exercises so I'm going to bet that this is where he's pulling
Yeah that's
Steph lockstep enough for me
Totally
Other examples
My point is that at first glance it feels almost impressive that Alex is bringing up how he's been talking about smallpox and Anthrax
Prior to 9/11
Knowing what we know that these will become Hot Topic
Pics of conversation in the coming days
But it's not really
When you take a moment to ask yourself if there's a reason why
He would be talking about the subject
The time
Almost always you'll end up disappointing yourself when you realize that he's basically been doing the same week bulshit for over
Does really
Kind of deflating man it is
It is
Like
It is like just seeing
It's just a giant mass shooting to him it's just a bigger mass shooting with property damage
Eight like he doesn't have any emotion towards this Beyond
Feels very emotionless and that's who is a little bit robot
You calm down
You've got a deep inner turmoil I can't calm down
I'm going to give a tiny warning before this nightclub because there's some discussion of
You know some of the
Bodies
Carnage
And he does that so graphic
He doesn't really he's getting the report from Jim
His buddy
Who was there
Yeah
There's only one reason that I really want to play this clip
And it's to give
One example
A couple times throughout the show
Alex seems to have a bizarre preoccupation
With details about the p
People who jump
Oh okay and I find that super distasteful
Write because that detail as like
Vocativ image
Terrifying
And it's straight out of a movie
Yeah
Here here is that
Skip ahead if you don't want to hear
Assertive
Recounting of
Details
Tell us where you work what you saw
The Rundown
For this audience exactly what developed
This
Morning
Add 28
The first plane slapped in
I slammed into the south at World Trade
Directly across the
Straight from the World Trade Center
Sunriver
Cancel 9 or so
I actually saw
Vibrating in some of the neighboring building
Cherry bombs
Call Ty
Workout
Pappadeaux
Setup point server number
Are people lined up on the 5th
Watching One World Trade Center burn
You could actually see
Were they on fire
Getting the details
Anyway
Necessarily think that there's anything to like horribly graphic but there is
The preoccupation that you
Contrack
I felt like it was
Was worth mentioning
Just that is
Response to it is
His hearing about people falling
Yeah jumping and he asks
Are they on fire
Tell me more gruesome
That's so
Weird
Trying to get a Faces of Death
Story
I'll just like
Oh man yeah what else is going on always it was there a foot flying to like all that's so gross.
More information view game by finding out if they were on fire
Oh I mean well you get to
Find out if they were on fire I don't know how it changes The Siege
It's very weird
Because it feels
Kind of exploitative in
Engrossed
Yep and I thought it would be exploitative engrossed if I played
Like the number of him
Fences that that
For like
Talks about people falling gross stuff
So this guy
It turns out
Yeah it's not only Alex's friend he also went
College
Implosion
I've ever seen in my life
Straight down
71 monolith
How could
Bonner
In the upper floors you say one playing at about 200 floor the other day
Route to 75th floor
How does that cause
The building
Completely collapsed
It looks like there was charges
I just got to believe that was also charged
He's just
Guessing this
Straight up you the guy who is
Only on the show because he's a friend of all
Alex
And he is not April
Professional
Structural engineer
He turned on CNN is an expert for them so we could go on Alex's
Or are you just going to do a favor for your breath
Saturday
Structural Engineering
You may have had a degree
He said he studied at the Masters level
Which to have a master's degree
I don't know what that means
But I'll give you maybe an undergraduate degree in some kind of engineering that means he knows something I'm not.
I'm not necessarily going to take
Alex's friend who may be studied engineering
Oh
Well there must have been Bob
Then I'm not going to throw this out at you
Anybody who within the span of under 4 hours
Can suddenly decide that they placed charges around the bottom of the World Trade Center without anybody noticing
Well
That is somebody I don't trust
Well I think
You could talk
To somebody
And they could say it was surreal watching them go down a bit
It's like they had bombs or something
Casino time to
Deal with what you have experienced
How do you say
The closest corralero
I can think of to try any processed was it
Controlled demolition
That makes sense but you're on Alex's show Wildflower doing a credential of I'm a structural engineer
Nydia yeah
Yeah that's not me and
Some dude in a bar going like interesting that's cuz I remember I saw one of those on TV
It's a little a response
Alex is like
Phuc yea
This is government
What you have just told us her
I saw those build
Collab
You were right there I was watch
Watching it on the news
They wanted massive death
So you're saying as a structural engineer
You
Are witnessing this
It is collapsing
I'm in both the structure
Pictures only place
Charges are sober
Is that what you're saying
T.i. Alex is taking this and he is now
A professional structural engineer
We are going with
This is a 98% now man this is one
Hyundai I despise whenever you get asked
Still yes or no question
And you answer with something
Sing wishy-washy what are you talkin about
You know of course it didn't
What are you doing
I think it's a weird thing on out to show because you know that no matter what you say
He's going to make it a quick unequivocally they like
This is 100%
Digicel structural engineer
I started the Masters level because I was
Picked out of college by the greatest structural engineers in the world
George married but no one has ever even heard before I'm secretly Frank Lloyd Wright
Frank Lloyd Wright
So Alex is just pushing
It's pretty hard when he's going with actually
Do you see how the government
Could stand to gain to bring us
Release date from this happening
I'm not even going to go there I have no opinion on that
Tell you the facts I said
Terrorism
Martial law
Hitler burning the reichstag is a
Protection declare martial law
Ridiculous
For five years I'm just so glad that
You're alive
Have you had a chance
To talk to your wife
I have Alex
A jarring turn I'm so glad you're alive
Said it with no gladness if his voice whatsoever so this is approximately 15 minutes into the show
And it's still
Chaos and New York at this point
In the day
It's honestly hard to express exactly how distasteful it is to hear Alex covering the story This Way knowing what people were living
Through
I understand that he pretends
Vdx the way
He does because
Smarter than fighting a larger
Your evil entity the
It's pulling the strings behind all world events
Coming on the air at like
11:15 on 9/11 and rambling about the reichstag fire and trying to get your guests
Who's Justin
A friend of yours who worked in a building near the World Trade Center to agree with you that the government
Probably did this
Is a b disrespect
Record while after 9/11 people respond to any joke about the event by saying too soon
Intelligent people can disagree about what is and is not too soon to joke about a trash
The aristocrat
Categorically undeniably
Snow soon for this
They're joke
What's better too soon
But this is not busy
Is not never
Soon or late
Just don't do
Especially
I mean evening
I was trying to put it in my head like maybe if you do subscribe to this worldview
This doesn't have the view of address
Even if it's a false flag
People are still dead.
Knowing what we know now we know the number of deaths was and I will say that Alex
Believe that to be
Much higher
I think a lot of people myself included I thought
There's no way that possibly couldn't have killed tens of
Alex
Stew in his head
Believe this to be
Do you know much
More deadly than it was still bi
This way
An indication that like okay if you're arguing
His conspiracy world
Do doesn't make him see this as a tragedy that's
That's macabre
I don't even know what to think about what that kind of worldview would do to your
Ability to a
I really don't
And then imagine
If you have that worldview and you assumed that there were tens of thousands
The Dead
And then somebody's like
Don't know
The real number is actually much lower it
I bet he felt disappointed
I wouldn't want to I would want to speculate but
That's so dark
I think the only way you can go about the only way you can go about it I guess is
To just be like
F*** it's awful that
These people died
But I have to transmute that in
Anguirus
The globalist because they did the
You know that's
The only way you can do it and I don't even really feel that no I feel Highfield feel like
There's an increased
Anger that is being sublimated from now the pain or a vegetation
Excitement it's easy
There's a little bit of
I got a lot of eyes on me
Sure.
Yeah I told you so I've been finding love is a good too I told you so
It doesn't it doesn't
Feel-Rite
So this doesn't feel right either
The amount of time between
Imploded
Could be evacuated
About 45 minutes
Like they were giving them
Time
To evacuate again
The grid
Engineer
Area you're saying your most
Beautiful image
Implosion you've ever
See Nana
Absolutely what is that voice tone is just
Bizarre
Spock and then also you noticed he's like trying to build up those Prudential
Trying to really stress the
The credentials cousin
This is gone from a first-hand account from a friend of his
Into a store
This is now something he's going to try and rely on as like
The day off structural engineer said that they were bombs in the building
Is your friend talkingshit
Things were a little bit loose
Oh totally
Do you know I think
I think that that part of the mythology is something that you hear a code in his show in later years
It is it is such a like
Don't get Orwell all this friends kind of know this like
Drop
Something that makes you a little bit
More than just a regular layperson in there
And Alex will immediately run with it Beyond
Reason
Hope that you're if you were friend he's friend
You know that
Maybe you'd hope that you'd be a little careful
You would think
But apparently you don't maybe subconsciously they want to make him happy
Maybe now
So we have some early misreporting
Aircraft Landing the boat
World Trade Center towers they have
Praying for everyone
We have another plane
Smashing into the Pentagon
A part of the structure has caved in
Being reported
Another one slammed into the
Pittsburgh PA
Airport
Run outside
International Airport
Just Dance US Canada
Mexico borders have been
Shield that is martial law
Gentleman
You can see hear some preliminary reports that Alex is Aaron that are not correct
And in some ways this is stuff that's expected and you can give him some leeway
On some of this
However the Tonys using is completely different than at the
The beginning of the show where you said that there were reports of bombs in schools but that may not be
True
Now things have a much more factual delivery from Alex but what he saying
Is the same unreliable fog of immediacy
The plane in Pennsylvania didn't hit the airport and I don't know if that was something that was even widely reported in Arab
Gypsy some kind of miscommunication Happening Here
I'm not going to be a huge dick about
The other piece of information
Is a bigger
The US Canada and US Mexico borders were not closed in response to
Security was tight
As one would expect
But the fact that Alex is reporting that the borders are just sealed is definitely not
Correct
This again would be something I wouldn't be a huge dick about because
I think that it also seems like
The kind of information you could
Here and it makes sense on a day like that
It's also understandable as an errored some sort of the miscommunication I can say they're clamping down on security and you should
Misinterpreted or whatever
But then Alex says that next sense
That's martial-law ladies and gentlemen
Ceiling borders is not martial law
You may think that a state
It's in martial law Woods
Fuel their borders but it's not a defining characteristic of Martial law at all
Why would you seal your borders
I mean not let anyone in or out
Wilshire but that does
Doesn't make sense in the long term
Nope
Martial law is something that needs
Be invoked
And it involves the military taking over governing and law enforcement operations which traditionally are held by civilians
Princeton's in 1954 Russell County in Alabama had been consumed by organized crime to the point where
Corruption
It made the existing political and law enforcement apparatus essentially a rogue and a t
Culminating with the deputy
TV Sheriff assassinating a candidate for district
Who is seen as a threat to the racquet
So the governor declared a limited martial law where the National Guard came into controlling
Clean things up
They're obviously more messy
Incarnations of martial law
Principle is the same
Martial law requires that the civilian authorities are temporarily replaced by military authorities
And sealing the Border does not qualify is that at all
This is a big deal because
I really don't think Alex understands the concept of Martial law at all
I think he just uses it as a scary buzzword to evoke negative feelings in the listeners
But it often does
Don't seem relevant to the things he's discussing at all
Marshall are supposed to be his big thing like his main topic of expertise and I don't think he even understands it on
Basically
Really
He wants to just say like
Totalitarian
Say it has to be Marshall I can't because she wants to see you scary
Like he's still expect
He thinks that
Biting could be president during martial law you know like
You know like all of those things
Match up with marshmallow
Biking
Could rely upon himself General ahead of the armed service
I understand I understand the technicalities there but I mean
You know what I mean
He just means that there is complete and total control over what you can and cannot do
Not that
The military is going to run things slightly different
No I think I agree I agree but I think more
Specifically I think
It's just a catch-all word for like
When cops
Are doing things that make me uncomfortable black masks as martial law
But you this is martial law
They don't
Give you their names and back
Martial law
In fact
You could ask if you could argue that some things
Could be
In hindsight should it ever get to that point
Step Sports
Martial law
You don't know at this point necessarily that's
BEP.
The conclusion
That all
Tigrett so gym
Has another little
Piece of information that I find fast
Right now I can tell you a third building that's across
About a 56
I Can See Fire Through the Windows on a bout
5260 story building on fire
As well do you know the name of that build
It's one of the World Trade Center buildings
Something like that
Is Building 7
In the World Trade Center complex there were a bunch of buildings but it's important to understand their relative sizes
1 into were the Twin Towers which were much taller than the other
Building 3 is the Marriott Hotel in was 22 stories tall
Buildings five and six were Nine Stories till
Building 7 is the one that Jim is talking about
For sure given that it was 47 stories tall
And Jim mentioned that he's on a boat on the Hudson
A bit of figuring out his vantage point
Eddie had to have been a little bit more time
Geo locate where he would have been chair
I don't think that any of the other buildings
Would have been visible to him
Other than Building 7
Based on where his view would have been
The other ones would have been
Obscured by a
Fall beginning at approximately 5:20 p.m.
Phillies 5 hours after this call
The conspiracies that Alex will be pushing later characterized the Fire and Building 7 is insignificant
But here on Alex's own show he hasn't eyewitness
Is an friend of his
Reporting that the whole side of the building is smoking
Alex probably doesn't remember
This part of that conversation
And it doesn't match
His later
Later information base
Despoiled by your own friend
Terrible yeah it kind of makes Building 7 female less like The Smoking Gun
Tony vallot it seems more like the smoke
King Garden
It's a smoking building
This is not a time for ponds
Anyway Alex has another Gaston
Heavy Hitters
Harry thank you for holding
Ensure
Tom
You been covering the stuff for years you know I've been on your show predicting this
Warning people
I put out press release
Places on it
This was going to happen and take my ride is your take on all of this
Brownfield
But you know
Alex believe it or not it did not Shock
Very much
Cool wrong with these people I don't know
The dairy Brownfield is a seventy-year-old radio guy from Missouri who hosted the show that's described as
Agricultural news
I think it's less of a show like
Breaking news about growing corn and more like news that's tailored towards the agricultural community
Except I'm not sure if that's the case
He started something called the Brownfield Network
Which still exists
It's like a news distribution service
You go to their website
It's all about Farm okay
When I Was preparing this episode
Is quote rain comes at
Optimal time for Illinois farmer
That's Farmers singular
This is an article about Sanborn who was thrilled that it rained because it helped his Bean crop
This is the top headline on
Website
I mean yes oh of course he's not surprised that 9/11 happen
You know
Pass to someone else's
Maintaining the Brownfield
Like
Indicative maybe of the news who's putting out Daddy's
Rain helped my b
Twist
I was really expecting you to go the opposite direction
I was expecting that agricultural things to be some sort of like smokescreen at you don't like
Americans for Prosperity you're not really surprised I probably was right wing weirdo conspiracy
A fair amount of it might have been like
Weevils are actually robots from the government Maybe
This old man out of Missouri is apparently someone out
Had to get on to get his take
And apparently he does not give a s***
A gives a s*** but he's like I'm not
Surprise
But here's the thing
There's big
Dairy has to bring
It's Jerry but if I could be
Like milk
A big news that he has
Bring Alex's attention of course already knows about this
My original plan today was to talk with Charla
Hazel Burke
And
I called her she was one of the individuals that didn't know a thing about this
Listen to my contacts
Need to change our program
And she just called back
A moment ago
She said that her husband
Friend that's a Belgian of the Belgian
Businessman
And he stole in all of Europe
Pull up the news that two men
Passports
Entered into Afghanistan
Sandlot
Today's
Citgo
He says this is all over here up
Not here in the United
You heard anything about that
Yes
Yeah
This is about Ahmad Shah massoud
Masood was assassinated on September 9th
2001 by men who had fake Belgium
Passports
All of the details are lost
Totalitarian Alex
Who just want to fudge details in order to prop up there
Predetermined
Conclusion
That everything is a conspiracy that only they can see through
And there is no correcting of this there is no like it comes up again later
To Belgian
Why not into Afghanistan
Got to do what you're up to talking about it but it's censored in the American
You guys have to have this wrong
Shouldn't you have
A real good sense of something
Alex response you with
Yeah
I guess that be a big
RedFlagDeals if you feel like
Horse confident about what I'm hearing
My instinct is to say yes but I know that this is stupid so I'm going to go with
Barry has a bottom-line
What is your bottom line analysis what's Your Gut level
Feeling on all of this who do you think's behind
Well
Telephone number
But what
Earlier in this showing I have had 1000
Sometimes on the air I read the back
And I'm real referring here to the holy scriptures
Lindsay on earlier this
Going to see what he thought
Couldn't
But that we know that we're going to have I one world order a new world.
We know it's coming
We know the Antichrist
Standing by
I don't know
Certainly don't have the power
To clean all this mess up
Make it
Currently the Antichrist
Standing by
Jesus
Proud boys
Could be could be a woman as well
I have to save it
I guess for dairy
He
Gummy he died at like almost 80
Yeah
The new world order did not come
To being the devil didn't come back
Nope
Pretty like
I think I'd be disappointed
Furious if I spent my entire life predicting the Antichrist is coming and then I just
Died
Like it was fine feel empty climatic
Words would have been like
To be like I guess I'm the Antichrist panel
Like you got it
Maybe an action movie Antichrist
This
Not going to work
So
Yeah we've got
Alex's body
We got Dairy
Again Alex has another guy
Let's go to Ted Anderson owner of Genesis
Communication
Resources
Very upset about all of this
My testosterone level
Glowing just like yours are out there
Ted Andrews
God bless the server
For providing
This network in a place for people to get accurate
Information
Financially
Well obviously there's a lot of
Crazy mixed-up
Emotions going on in the Auto Mart
Right now
What's the World Trade Center that is where gold and silver trays in
In the United States
Is the largest market
For gold and silver
I was
Trying to be
Ghoulish
With my exaggeration but I expect
I was way wrong
I was not ghoulish enough
No no
Nope
Hi
Crack I think there's no bottom I'm convinced there's no bottom
And it just keeps going
Just keeps going hit those floors
Men's shoes
Try this song
Forsyth
It's very amazing to me to watch this happen I've never experienced this
Three years now that I've been in the business
For the mark
Actually been shut down like this
And I won't open up at
Until further notice
Shield
Troops Federal Protective
Control of downtown
Cities under
Security Arrangements
Well obviously Alex
A major concern
As for the p
People that are sitting there
The paper wondering what's going to happen
And hopefully the market
Disabled
I can get out with reasonable cost
Well there's a
B of a stamp
He going on here at
Midas resources
Even calling in on the 800 number
Please be patient we got a lot of
People working them
But
You will not you will be
Taking care of
A lot of people are looking to have gold right now with the
Shut down obviously
Play the United States
To be much tougher
Buy the stuff
Not every
Not every year
Not every Ops
Anymore
So if you are calling and do that
Be patient
You responded to also hit me like a semi truck
Obviously we should be concerned and I thought he was
Going to say about those words
On 911 I'm not finish it with listen to Grossmont Center because that's
Third on your list we should be really concerned about the people who are stuck invested in paper money
What is the number one thing that we should be concerned about is some people are just too
Quit right now unbelievable I I just
The sauce
What is the I mean
Wolf
One Tower goes down and you think
Lot of people are going to be stuck in paper money
Yeah that's what I thought that's what I thought
I need a tire open
Ivy
Cheese's
Stouts
That's grim
There's just not enough lightning
Furious that people believe in God cuz I think if we all just believed in Zeus only
Then maybe we could get one person
Struck by lightning bolt
Whenever they pulled s*** like this
It's
Amazing
A words fail
Irish Times
Because this is like
You know I mean
Without mincing words 911 is what made Alex is
Career
Are you going to listen to this show with on the day of he does not
Seem
That concerned
About
Gathering accurate information about what's happened
He is all over the place
He doesn't seem like
Lucky's emotionally
All that affected by what's happening
The guest
AR
Weirdo Farm guy
Friend who he gets turned into the biggest
Structural engineer in the world
And his gold guy
Does not great
Yeah these are these are three certifiably insane people
Well four of them obviously but one of them
Well beyond that point
Insanity history people
Saying those things
Astonishing
Jim you could make
Some argument
For being less complicit
Cuz there were opportunities that Alex gave him to double down on some of his stuff
I do believe
But you know Alex
You probably would know his tendons
You know that you're
Essentially doubling down by Nas
Not pushing back
Oh yeah
That's good advice. Get out of paper money
I would tell everybody make
Make sure you got your cars
Pull up gas
Make sure you got plenty of
Food
Does water filters
In the martial law stuff starts cranking up I'm going to go to
My parents house
So you're leaving
The country
And you're taking my little sister out of here now
Senior
School you're getting out of here and you're leaving
Now you're going
Now
And I'm going to stay here and I'm going to fight for this
Country
Or anybody else
Jerry Brown
Alright
Did you bet I will
This is a great day for me
Terry has
Nothing else to do
Fantastic time I already watered
Wow
Amazing to me how these people handle emergencies cuz they have no concept of scale
And reaction
You know like you do
Covid there's only going to be lone survivors and then 2 weeks later they're like well I'm not dead yet so this isn't even real
At the Twin Towers is gone we need to run get out of this country you got to get gas you got to go Frozen
Water yoga
Give me nice
Bored by it already what are we doing tomorrow
We getting we getting Thai food
So Alex is just
Humped though about Buddy
Look at this about
Fighting this is I just had a weird feeling
Infowars.com for all the updates and all the news
Larry
Beer and we're not going to let him get away with it will be black
That's gross
Wow
Doesn't like it's indicative of the
The town there isn't any
Concern
Or recognize Judgment of
Acknowledgement of loss
Acknowledgement
People who are listening are probably going through some s***
Acknowledgement that some people are scared confused
Do people in New York you don't know you haven't gotten a phone call from them you don't know where they were that day
Subway with
Filled with
Dustin Shay you don't know if they've got beat yet
Disrespect
Well honestly I don't know whether I
There's a lot of other words
Just keeps coming back up there's a lack of
Respect
Dude
Reality
Notion that we're all
Experiencing something together
You know yeah maybe I'm to collect
Activists maybe I'm a sauce
Berlin that way but
I just wanted I find it abhorrent
4 weeks
There was no news organizations
Who would begin to speak this callously
About
3 years
No mainstream news organization would ever dare make
Joke about 9/11
This dude
F******
20 minutes
Twin Towers falling
Is like this is a great f****** day for me we got martial law going
Non everything isn't
Pretty f*****-up
So I know that
You know in 2008/2009
When we've been listening to some of those episodes
About half of the police are waking up
Good people in the army or Waking Up
A little bit higher numbers there
About half
Of the military and the police are woken up that's great
Police
Are woken up 2001
Don't let him give you a police-state out of it
We have the power
The American
People
Police agencies in military
I know that 75
Isabella Perry
Is awaiting what's happening
About how
The cops are
We need to pray for the people that have died
Our house go out to
The family
And I would just bring her on the airlord
Heal our land do that
Just landed the hill we don't want to be
Parts of a needle
Our country
To be brought back
And please.
We pray that no biologic
Have the government
Predicting what happened
Fox and ABC
You seen the last month that I read
They talked about 1
God doesn't need citations from Fox News
Weird
Wow Alex
So when
You pray to me
Now I wrote it down
Long time ago
So you should really know this by now
But.
Don't also be broadcasting your opinions about bulshit to other people
Very specific relationship between you and me I'm glad you're you we do it that way okay I believe
I don't remember the exact verse but there is something about like when you pray on
Toomey's provide sources
Peter the letter to the Thessalonians said
You should start a pirate radio station and really start getting into it with people you know what I'm saying like correction
I believe it was
Copic apologies
Gross that's really f***** up
Interesting thoughts
I was one of the people
That cuz you're going to have to go whenever watching
2K was
You know what they're trying to do
I'm sorry what
Believe that this was
Going to piano
We were going to see some
Sing of this nature happen
At the turn of the century
Maybe I'll even on New Year's Eve
But that was too. Just
The pretext for them to put in their female bunker
Control grid
Why didn't they go ahead and do it
That night
Because the world was ready
Also bladimir
Put that just taking power Yeltsin it
Disappeared
A lot of power jockey
What's going on
But I still believe
The plan
If they had four wife
2K
Wow
Highbury alright
Okay so here's
Here's what I gathered from that
Whenever Y2K was is not an
Unacceptable thing to say
It's in the name
And that but it was it was kind of a long stretch for people like them
Yeah that's true
58 could have been
Tournament 2020
You have decided
Whatever happens after you've decided that white
UK is the plan
If that's part
Well I don't think
I may be perfectly honest
I haven't listened
Come to the entirety of dairy Brownfield
Lowe's catalog
New new buses
Farm Report
No would but I don't
Prior to Y2K he was like they're going to blow up the Twin Towers
So he's just sort of retroactively being like
This is what I thought was going to happen
Also you have to understand
Grassroots
Basic
Nuts and bolts level chair
This means
This is what the globalist or planning to do
They didn't do it
So now they did it
It is
A hundred percent
Conspiracy
It somehow
The brakes on a
For some reason whenever you want was jockey for power
They couldn't get things up
Two-speed organization is lacking
Kind of sloppy let's just face
There's no way around
Receive
Groundwork
It's a it's an assumption that's cooked
Into every conversation
It's silly
So
Sounds very familiar
They have the feds taking over
Central areas of downtown
Cities in
Capitals
Confirmed
This is the New World Order
And look for the next
He wait to say we
Turning our guns
So the terrorists don't blow up
It'll be something along those lines
Only big brother
Trans the game
Also I was thinking about this
Disney keep saying that like only big brother it stands to gain
I kept thinking like you do Elsa
You
That's why he's excited
Obviously I don't think that's a motive
Forward
Alex doing 911 or something
The game greatly from behaving the way he
He is
As as we're listening to that so like
I don't know
If I were him I
I would be
Thinking very
Very little of my audience
If I were stressing
Akebono kind of ideas
Apply
Who gains from turning this into a conspiracy
Conspiracies
Once you start doing that though then you're just never going to come back
You know who's who's benefiting off of
This sandwich that I'm about to
Is it me or is it Potbelly
I bet it's Potbelly I'm at Potbelly's put evil should inside my sandwich and they're going to kill me and that's
Because they don't want the money for me going back wait a second
Who benefits from me by in the sandwich Terry Brownfield
So Alex picks calls
A little bit of a temper
I can't believe somebody would call
I can't believe this
Can I listen to it every night
Adam Carolla and dr. Drew where my guys
Unfortunate Nightside but I love that show it made me
Me feel very
Comforted
It felt like
They're people who are struggling with stuff
Fans
Yeah you're not as alone
Even if
Making fun of everybody
And being a little bit meme
Really funny way
On 911
I think even the day after
They
Just took calls about what people wear
And you know like just opening up and being like
These kinds of fears and anxieties that you might be feeling our normal totally
And
You know we're all in
This kind of together
And it was really
Meaningful man
Alex doesn't
HD
Opposite
It's like it makes it worse
Yeah
Kohl's makes things worse
I really
I find it so f***** out that Alex would take calls I know that's unacceptable to the first one
Subway
Okay
I just listen to me for a second
Place
Oh God Revelations
Right now
At this very moment
What happened in New York now
If you take the airline
Read it to us
It's it's huge
Is lots of words
Yeah yeah
Dad is too long
What's happening
Is exactly what's in there
If you take the airlines out of it and you take the
They didn't know what planes were revelation
They didn't know that this continent existed
Any of you take that
They'd never heard of I don't know the world
He was going with if you take the airline
He'll get into this year as actually
Numerology
Here are the flight numbers
Play
Flight 77
White ones
It's like 33
Number is aligned
All of us are obsessed with
Okay you take these numbers and you add them together
And you get a total of
Take two
+ 9
Is 11
Bus 6
Is 17
Revelation
It describes what
I have no idea if it's
Coincidence or whatever
Still the numbers are there the length
Is there so this is stupid but it's also not correct
Be played
Are you saying is 33 is actually united 90
Which ruins Alex's number riff
Panda basically screws up his own weird
Cryptic math videos
Pull off here
Either way this is a great use of time
On the day the world
This is
This is bad like
Alex should have cut him off when he started doing that
Absolutely this is not like
This isn't something that you should
Humor
I mean
How do you not just letting sir sir
Sir sir stopping topless right now sir and make things make sense
You can't
Because that's what your whole thing
It's just that this is a different
Nord unhinged or more detached from reality
More obviously detached how about how about I'm going to throw this out at you sir
If God speaks in order of operations addition and subtraction
Then go f*** yourself
I don't even want that
If you are right
I'm rather more stupid devil than a god whose like 2 + 4 is 6
6 - 33 and that's where the Devil comes in God to saith unto me please excuse my dear
I got that X
Parentheses OnePlus and you moron
Yep
I find this very depressing
Partially because he's got the flight
Yeah that really sucks with his whole Revelation testing
Suspend because
The thing that he attached
Are you took from earlier
Wow okay so we entered the city is
Describe
Going on right now
What are we doing here to 17th number qanon
Wow you're right
Also it was very is talkin about a small town in Missouri named Sandy
Call Noe
It's just a short mention it doesn't mean anything
I'm sorry
On this show
If there are things better
Even slightly perhaps
Not
Tangentially related
We're going to have to make a
Fine I'll find a plate on the next episode of Derry Saints
Thank you very much
All right with this
Cuz whenever Y2K happened or whatever alright we knew
That's all I got
Those buildings went straight down John what are you
You see happening there really gearing up
I don't think we can accept one with expected I don't
Make of all of this stuff
It's up
So what are you going to do
I'm going to clean my weapon man I'm going to clean my weapon
Don't you do that anyway
I'm afraid to go but I just want to go by myself
Oh my God
These people
Precise
And
They ought to be ostracized
And everywhere else
John I appreciate your call we don't know
If the government did this
We know they did the other way
We know who Sam
The game
Final
Ladies and gentlemen I'm not going any
Any payment center what about you
It's legitimately nuts to listen to this cuz it seems like Alex is in many ways on autopilot
This whole song and dance here is so cookie-cutter that it almost doesn't seem like you need to be awake
To do it
He already said that he believes 98% chance of government did this and then later said the government did do that
This caller is saying things that get into violence
So how it's a little bit
Who did this
Wink wink and also I'm not going to let them take me Ohio
It's really the same couching type of presentation he does all the time and it's really weird to see it being
Deployed when talking about the
The biggest event of his life
Which happened a few hours earlier
Yeah weird to say this but I don't
Give a strong sense that Alex
Cares that much that
9/11 happen
I don't think he gives a s*** at all
It's weird it is one of the weirdest things that I love all the things
That I was expecting Alex
This is 911 episode to be
Apathetic
Was not one of them
I think it
It's more cynical than apathetic
There's definitely a line of apathy that goes deep vein
White
But look
He believes that it's the cover
He's already said that it was
But we don't know that for sure we just know that everything that would point
To the government means the government
And you know there's one person
Saddam Hussein
Why does government ever put him in power in the 70s
Why was our big buddy to fight Iran
Why was giving the chemical biological weapon
Houston
Through this and there is a chance
Saddam Hussein
I want that country note
Buccaneers why
Didn't they
Take Saddam out
1991 I asked you that question
Fair enough
So I guess he's into blaming a rock sooner than George W bush
That's that
Themes
Really not like what I would like to present himself that he would be nuked immediately
Don't want you to be emperor of anywhere Ayr response why would that work out well
At all like sugar
You recognize the amount of Civilian death that would cause
The pointlessness of
Of
Of that response
Like that's
Bucked up
No people don't know
You know
I think we need to go back
Everybody being
Really really terrified of nuclear weapons like the bombs and schools like they did
Covers
Instilled into children
Way more afraid of nuclear weapons
Apparently our
It's it's a
A lot of that stuff was so silly that it becomes mockable
You know you might have a tendency to
Take lightly
The affair
Modern weaponry
No when I was researching for my book
I found out that
Most of the missileer course not most but like
A massive chunk of them
Are always high
At the people who have all the computers are from the 1980s like
It is
Verifying if you look Morgan
Crazy it's crazy
People still using Punch Cards
To control nuclear weapons in 2022 with bananas
And they're doing ecstasy
It's pretty cool
Hell yeah
You got it so Alex takes another call and this guy is a little bit of a longer clip it wanted to play
Sort of.
This guy disagrees with Alex
About some of the premise
That he's coming
Forthwith
And this
Foster's Alex to a point
That he ends up making
Of totally bizarre claim at the end of the
Go ahead bill
But I don't see you first
That's my opinion
Healthcare
Second wave
How
And act like this
With the illegal in
Immigration in the
I think it's going to make people read
NYU legal immigration
Checkpoints today
Heartland
But then I dropped the borders wide open and porous and then advertising how open we are
The terrorist attack
So is a grand Prime
No question
I think the People Get Ready
Refocus
If you have a really tough
Modifying
I really don't
Martial law
It's already
Dental emergency in NM
States
The normal response to a major issue I mean
So you are you in the military
Okay
We support the military
We don't know who's done this
But are you telling me of some of Bin Laden
Could coordinate
All of these
Leesport
But telling you that there are lots of
How many country
Mercenaries going to fly a plane into a building
No you didn't let me see
I believe that there are enough
Tentacles by organization
World can have enough points
I will say this
A good chance Europe to be behind
Esther Rolle
Euro
Right now
And a half months
Yeah but your railroad has decided that it's
Like he's so thrown by this guy but
Impune imbibing a even in the military
Do like make him.
Appear to know anything
I guess
You know what
The road at the attack
Symbol of the economy
What do you get hearts at all makes
Send it is a little bit like
If a blindfolded kid
Kept trying to hit a pinata and eventually the pinata
Couldn't break it
I told them they just hugged
So like that's what happened there he was like well I guess
I guess I just believe Europe killed everybody then
Let's find a you don't agree with the crazy stuff I'm saying so I'm going to say something
Crazier how about that how you like that how do you do it
We're doing a nuke Europe now
I love
I love the response at
I don't think martial law going to be I love that for any any question like that
And I really don't think that they're going to ban
Cigarettes
Yeah and there's also two things that have already come up that are interesting
Counter-arguments to the ideas that Alex is expressing
The first is when Jim was on and he was talking about how there was a long delay but
Between the
Crash
The buildings falling right
Giving time for Chevrolet
Evacuate
Bring up the point that like it's almost as if there would have been time for emergency
First Responders to be there and they were the main target of the attack to believe
The diet is
A nefarious
Plan of
A terrorist organization
Takeout firefighters I am
Please write infrastructure people as opposed to
Adjust civilian death
That is an exam
By Alex how that would be a motive not of the globalist shut up
2nd Viscount caller is bringing up the idea that immigration would become a much larger issue
In the wake of a foreign terrorist attack
And it sure did and that would not be in
The interest
Of the globalist
Does Alex has presented them
Because they want all the immigrants
Become a
Exactly into this
Stick from a motive stamp
And this
Also isn't
Fully examined right
Lingering hanging questions breister ignore
And let me throw this one out there at
Osama has already attacked the World Trade Center
And not just that
He is incredibly Rich true has connections all over
Over the world
He is infiltrated most terrorist organization
My guy was saying that there are groups of mercenary tendrils and Jeff
I think it would happen in Alex's mind is like
What are organizations that I
Vu
She probably higher
Kind of like what he's saying
End up going down this road
Travesty
There is a fissure is internal
Struggle
Between the new world order right now
Germany runs the EU
They swarmed and dilation of the u.s.
Oldest country
What's panda
Muslim terrorist Bank
It's in between our government
Frank Lampard
PowerBlock
It runs a lot of our news
Wow that was so fast
98% sure
I'm leaving towards to you
Dude I had a weird phone call and now I take it you didn't
98% sure your update
Yeah
At amazing
Who's Europe
Did Germany install president Germany
Germany for the deaths of the United
Everybody
Sure
But I have no idea
Don't know
This is whiplash
I could not have been less prepared for this is why you go back to the past
Never really expect I got T-boned by Europe
That's what's going on Jesus
So one of the things I think is really fun about this broadcast
Is that Alex is like
Juggling gas
Traffic jam was on earlier
Recovery was on earlier he comes back
Jim's back now
Alex's upgrading this banter
About the EU
Listen carefully to the way he expresses
Did you ever think you'd see this
In the United States
Not really didn't
The one place we haven't
A10e over
Insulated
The EU
Now they're rolling out in the currency
It's already clean
The Distributing
Middle East
Financial Center is brought down
We've been into Wars of Europe
Getting analysis
By which I mean
10 minutes ago
Tossed out the idea Vu randomly minutes ago I talk some s***
Analysis paralysis
You heard me talk s*** and then they were like wait a second and I looked into it
The Heritage Foundation is it called my cell phone
We're getting it at like there's more analysis on the ground being done right now outrageously said somebody for me
Belgium to see if the stories true
Russell's suspiciously silent
Brussels has yet to respond
Did you do 911 comment from Leo zagami as of yet
So Terry is not in hiding females back
Gotcha
Farms at flight 175
From Boston to La has crashed
6 passengers at 9
Crew members
Emergency Personnel at the
The theme say there are no
No survivors
Why are these airplanes crash
Do you have any idea
Now is this a plane other than the for that
Went into the Trade Center in Dubai
Independent Burger
Into
Into the Pentagon
I don't have any idea
Well we know they've got fighter jets scrambled everywhere
So they could have shot
And I will probably never know that's
These guys have nothing to say
And this is not good radio
You have a guy who's running late to do the wheat report giving Alex updates on stuff that neither of them have any car
Context for so
I can do it instead of sorting the information out Alex just dismisses it all the way by saying
Probably cancer
Piercing will never get the truth about this
It's legitimately pathetic
United 175 was the plane that hit the South Tower or World Trade Center
R2
I believe the dairy is getting some Intel ra3 the
Crashed but the number passengers
That you besides actually matches
Is 175
So I don't know what's going on
You might have the number wrong or there's something we got missed
Translation
Either way this is a pointless dissemination of
Correct information that only serve
There's two kind of boring annoy Alex
Yeah this whole National tragedy pretty well all
This was the first time I honestly related to anybody on the show
Whenever he was like
I don't know what's going on I was like that is the first legitimate
Acceptable phone called wild to have
The dairy has where it's like why are these planes crashing
It sounds stupid to us now but
No I wouldn't I wouldn't have known that they were hijacked
Absolutely like obviously that's an assumption that you can make but like
Yeah there is a reason for at this time of day for dairy to be like
I don't know why they're crashing I don't know what's going on
Human resilience I can think of right here too much because I think it is normal
Serve to help
Radio show that supposed to be disseminating information
I am screaming in this scenario I'm screaming I don't know what's going on so I'm going to go to the news
For information about what's going on
I do not want to go to the news
And see me screaming I don't know what's going on and then Alex ways to 10
At the conspiracy ever know
So Alex got that caller
Downs talk about numerology
Really wish you didn't
Going to get into a little oven
Attack somebody level
Entire country
In Florida.
Education
Speeches
The president's crap
Schedule
The first reports
The facts on New York
Came up on
The board and said the
Stands for judgment and 11
A disorder
Really
And it shows how the global
Everything is 33 everything
7-Eleven
All of these
That makes sense
That doesn't make sense
Look at the flight now
That's not accurate
It's not one of the flight no
What's 7-Eleven
I-77 and 11 is the number of minutes that you wait
What was the 7-Eleven wasn't a flight number
It's 9:11
Right
The store
Yeah
What does that have to do with
I couldn't get anything to eat 7-Eleven
Brutal brutal Flamin Hot
Nacho Doritos it didn't have the cooler Ranch
I know brutal
I wanted a donut
So Alex has more bad prediction
Then we can see nuclear war with
Wood in the day
We covered
No.
Israel very upset saying Iran now has
Nooks and the missiles
Deliver them
It's just supposed to be
Could be the beginning
Armageddon
I hate to say that but we certainly have the ingredients only Terry
It looks like it does
We say time and time again once you read the back of the book
Beginning to see a difference
Picture and you look at the overall pick
Definitely say we are in the end time
I believe it's right as well Alex
That doesn't mean that means
You see what I mean
Glacier
Not good
Is there
He's good I want
We we are excited
MP idea of
Possibility of nuclear war kicking off tonight and this being Armageddon
I just want my sensors
Did his apocalyptic version of
Cher
Can we have one National
Or world
Or even local tragic
That is not
Evidence that were in the end times
Just one
I just don't want to know that we're in the end times
Every single time
How many enzymes are we going to be in bad on my end times
Yeah there's a limit
Yeah so I had this really interesting
Thought of a way that I would like to talk
Talk to Alex
If I ever were to
I know that he has a lot of
Evidence
That 911
And he has a lot of videos that he's posted or inside
There's a lot of videos that has posted that are like smoking
Gun evidence
Get the title of it right
I thought I would I would bring up
I like to talk to you about this article
Smoking Gun evidence that 911
Inside Job
What is this about
Smoking Gun what is it about
Guarantee
Like he would guess wrong
100 articles
Or even like a Smoking Gun covid is a killer
Which Wich Smoking Gun
You never get it right I would just put them in a room
Where that
Ever had
Did the floor covered in guns
And
30% CO2 and then we could
Really get to the bottom of all of his issue
Casino
Is CO2 good for you
Turn.
How many floors can you have how many guns can you have on a floor that's another question
So Alex and Dairy
This gets back to where
You were talking earlier about how the
Seems like they looked at this as like a righteous
This is where like
It really gets into that
Really messed up
To them to this next to this next
So
Again you have to have studied this
Absolutely
People don't
Damn this I caught world
It's been an Esquire
The Press Democrat
Mainstream
San Francisco paper
Spell National Television
Is in Europe
I snuck into caught world leaders in black and red robes
So why are you offended by us talking about how we're Christians and how are
Bible tells us
What happened in detail
And we're cookies
Dance around
Molech
How many world leaders are Warm Springs
The devil we're going to be
Our judge that is the bottom line with your agreement around
Absolutely that's what I said earlier today I think I'm headed to three times on National National radio
That it's difficult
For me to pray for America today
I can pray for God
And I can pray that
The people going to be saved as they popped
Wake me up
When our own
Children
Cannot go to a public
American
Stand up
And sing God Bless America
America I think the fetal tissues part of it I
Pretty
China giving them the Olympics when they kill their political test
Pissed off.
So bad
GoPro to the home now. All of murdering we're doing to our own children
Yes
The drugging of them aboard
We're being judged
Jennylyn
Beginning Ali
Societies are always judge
They have 10
And they will continue to be
Since you guys are exactly right I'll leave you alone
Thank you Darren
Blessed is the nation
Chicken that has been that believes in God you know
And cursing is the ones that don't
Yeah so 9/11 was
Political Punisher
From God
No different than like Pat Robertson's kind of s*** people
Rightfully
Throw this out at
Okay
Did you ever notice how God is it
Exactly as dumb as the people talking
Sing About God
You know like it is so crazy
Crazy to me that we can hear Alex Day
I want
And then we can hear him talk about his God just
Milking people whenever he feels like they need to be so crazy
Interesting other sort of branch that goes off
These thoughts sure
God is
Right and God is
You know infallible
Answered
Judgment
For the political decision
You disagree with
If he's doing a 911
Right
The kind of implies that
You want to do that
4 things
Things like
Abortion
Yeah it is almost like the people in those playing the fights
Spiritual flying into those buildings
Justify their behavior
Almost exactly the same way
You just justify their baby
How crazy is that are weird wrinkles but it would be you
It's right so maybe.
That's right I forgot this show is
Absolutely I don't know what happened we were Ninety Acres that shows the government now the EU
I'm happy
Convinced it's going to be Swatch by then
Got to be the squad
There's only one hero for us and that's the
So there is a
This is dumb
Warriors
Ever been an attack
On American
What
And never was attack
Not true
Yeah we had some
Agents
The New York comedian ever covered that they said
I don't know
Pearl Harbor dum-dum I was going to say you realize that that
Big
Attack
The biggest attack
But literally anybody could remember before this point
Yeah
Those big huge ears on American soil
But I guess there's some
Kind of maybe Alex
Doesn't look at non mainland
America
Define
If we're just going to make arbitrary rules about f******
Everything
Part of the United States
I understand
Also the f****** earlier bombing of the world
Hey remember that one
Anyway Harry should learn more
I do appreciate any times
That's only what I can remember and then you can just be like we learn
Go go find more
Sodus Point Alex reset
Recaps the news in case you're joining late
I just don't know what to say to any other
Sing about
Fort Wayne
10000 people anime
Collapse
I hit my lard
Passenger plane
Plane hit the Pentagon
Large portion
On fire
And then outside Pittsburgh
PA
One slamming
Shot down by
My Fighters
Swarming everywhere for carriers
Have delivered their payload of plane
Out into the air
And we got
Jets scrambled everywhere they're flying around here
Texas right now
About us
And there
Declaring civil emergency
Major Capital Cities
Why would they be flying over off
The jet
Find mine
So this is interesting because later on part of Alex's
Conspiracies will revolve around why didn't they scramble jet
Right reporting
Four things have deployed their payload in
Inskeep
Personally saw fighter jets
Scrambled over Austin
So
I guess you just forgot about that he knows that he can just
Reckon it whenever he feels like
Really comforting thought
How to be able to relax
Listen I'll just
Say that this is different like you don't even have to fix it in post you know it's like you you do the show
Says something and then yours is like I tell you it didn't
And that's it and that's why
Basically like
If you are doing a sitcom
And like it's episodic every episode is a new set of circumstances
Consequences brightness are the carryover
You can't carry something
You get to choose
What is reset and what is it
F****** jarring breaks my brain its narratively untenable
Just not Payette
You have to passively
Or else
You're f*****
So this is really a
Bad call
Pierre Alex takes a call and it really
Kind of pissed me off
Immigration policy is flawed
You're able to get in this country
And pray you and your family biometrically
It's a scam to get food is already putting a man
If your
Big reveal that Alex mostly just talks out of his ass
Hear the caller suggest that borders should have been closed a long ago so they could keep immigrants out and Alex agrees
But earlier Alex was erroneously reporting that the borders at
Concealed in response to the attacks
And that was
Was martial law
Sealing the borders up is good when it's a part of Alex's xenophobic
It's bad
When is the theoretical part of a country respond
Terrorist
You can pretty easily see the flaws in Alex's thinking and how this lacks any real can
This clip is actually worse
When he's ripping around with this collar about how bad immigration is Alex's that the government isn't going to close the borders because they
Just want to track and trace your family
But we've already established as a
Confirm piece of Alex's reporting that the Border
Have been
Concealed
Which is part of its Being Framed as part of the martial law takeover
That detail with Alex's coverage is now inconvenient for his more
Complain about how bad immigration is
So you just did
This is how information works and Alex's world
Something could be presented as a fact in order to scare the audio
It's about how the police state is here
And then without any explanation
Opposite
Can be presented to scare the audience about immigration
To recognize here is
The claim anthem
Negation of the
The claim which is to say reporting
The borders are sealed
And also saying they never would close the border
Wide open
Serve the same perp
Which is why it doesn't matter to the audience that are contradictory
And on the surface would make out with the show in Cohan
Both of these Center on the list
The white conservit
Christian American listener in general
Pettit centers them as the Vic
If the borders being sealed
Because bats martial law in there
Argon to put you in a FEMA camp cuz you're conservative white Krista
In America
If it's the border is never going
To be sealed it's because they want to solve
The problem
A foreign terrorism by tracking and tracing your family instead of stopping
Immigrants from coming in
Into this country
Both of these ideas that Alex is pitching satisfy the emotional need to be under attack
Vaquitas audience
Are addicted
It doesn't matter if he's things make no sense because they're not meant to
The emotionally resonate with the thing
Did people come to Alex
Is
Really really
I don't know if it's
Because the intensity of the event that he's covering but
Will become so clear in stock
Contrast
That Alex
Simultaneously be reporting
That the government is seal the borders
And it's martial law and we should seal the borders
Because otherwise
The Conspiracy to
Attack
Mainstream America with
That's nonsense
If I were in America
And I would have closed the borders right around the time of the First Crusade
And then saved yourself a lot of f******
In trouble
I find this
To be honest f
It is really illustrative
And I think the
You can you can learn a bit
About
How to process a lot of the ways that other narratives that seem weird on his show why they're there
How
How a lot of this is navigate
It Centers The Listener as the
The aggrieved one the one who is put upon
By whatever the larger
Conspiracy is
Some of it is some of the funk
Conspiracies is to make
Things
That are complicated makes sense
Forgive some sense
Comfort Inn
Chaotic world but some of it is also
TubeMate
Do you feel like
To just educate you into a friend
To always be in a fighter
Your flight mode with your adrenaline
Glands f****** pumping into your brain
Give
Excuse for why maybe you're not as happy as you wanted for sure because there's a
Firozi
That centers on
The identity that you are
Massive excuse for why you believe that they're coming
Going to kill you and all you're doing is
Sending him money
And it's a rationalizes fairly extreme politics because the alternative is submitting to the people who already
Play going to kill you
He's got to vote for the lesser of two evils
Anyway
Text clip
This is this
Is the
Core of what
This becomes
And it's just
All Housewives
That's on my website mean
Mainstream news stories
Chinese military in the Panama Canal
The threat is a housewife
That has an old revolver
Closet
Mr. Brownfield in the comments thanks
Call Wally
Not really
I tell you what I have a meeting downtown in about 45 minutes
Play better golf
Passion
You know that guy
Irresponsible
It's 9:11
Crazy
Yep you got to go
Answer
Just needs another bro to come in
So Ted comes back naturally
And this is Bisquick was
Depressing
Because
It start
With
Giving voice to
Very
Futile
In this entire show
Concern
And Humanity
Israeli Express
Domenico's
Are you going away like I am in my heart goes out to
The People First
Thing every night I just
Well there's your second appearance so
Family member
Caught up in this thing
You're just
It's mine bought
Tragedy
Kurds
But you do that
The financial institution you know that those two
Two buildings are worth it
From Men
Amount of money
Dahlia invest
Doctors that will put you to put the money behind that for
Particular thing
In the financial industry
Freezers no question about it I mean
Basically
You don't billions of dollars at
Just been lost within a matter of
Right as the
EU Europe
And then delivered
What you know but that's one of the reasons why a lot of
People get in the Gulf
All because there could be gold sitting in the basement of that building and I have
The gold still valuable
Oh God
Yeah
But I mean on one hand
It is
More empathetic
Lake van
Or at least begins more empathetic
Make then pretty much
All of this show so far
But it got it it goes pretty quickly to financial conversation
Some of that I think is why you just wouldn't want to have him on
On that
I think that's the world keys
He's in
Processes the event
Is it is my livelihood in my entire life
Is based around
Commodities Trading
In precious metals and currants
I mean the
They're god-king
On the day said now I have the tallest building so yeah I was
Kind of wondering if that would come up on the episode that would be that would be really a knot on his day show
I think that's why you just I mean I understand Ted's your boss
The runs all the companies in
And stuff but like it
It's not
It's not necessarily
It looks tacky
Okay
Unless your show is entirely Financial base
Or if you have a segment like
10 minutes of every hour is the Ted corner
The Ted Talk we could have branded that before have gotten their way earlier
That makes some sense
Sure we got the financial minute with Ted
But this is
This is this just look
What's gauche
Bumi
Away
Was
Won't someone think of the land
Please
Someone please think
Of the land law
Who are the most
Agree
Amber Reeves
That was f***** up
Here's what God
Here's what
And that's why you buy gold
Even if even if
Put gold at the bottom of the World Trade Center
You can dig that up that's still valuable if you are selling me gold
Under the Twin Towers
Yeah
It's not good
You could have used an example like a pirate ship
Using the image of the tragedy in order to
Promote the value of the thing you sell
And that sucks
Anyways
Yankees Red Sox
That sucks too
The other thing that I was thinking about Tuesday like
Okay like
Obviously this looks bad and is gross
Yeah
The same time you do have to
Except
The people who own the building
The busy
That were affected by it
It's naughty naughty
Bowels not the time
No
It's not the time
You you handle accounting issues
Days later now that said
The gold
Underneath the Trade Center is
Shock
That a human being could do that
Yeah
I would never ever in a bit I can promise you for his creative is my mind may or may not be
Never would have gotten to here's my sales pitch
That's right
To write
Like what do you think I want to show on 9/11 was like you couldn't imagine that it was Moses at
No I would never in a million years of thought
That he would have said
That
That's amazing
So here he goes off air after a few more pointless calls
And here is our last clip
From Alex's show from the day of
I mean do you think any Arab country would really do this I want to be turned into a parking lot
I never give ever going to do that they would
I believe in you was involved in this
There is a fissure there is a tick
Tectonic power struggle
Right I don't believe that
This was done by the
By the Arabs
So we have
At the end of Alex's
Broadcast day
For his daytime show
The conclusion that the
You was probably involved
So this is
I mean like honestly it's hard to some this up
Because
So weird anyway
You kind of expected to be weird
Okay of there's unfolding information
But here's the thing it's blowing my mind
The unfolding information does not affect the broadcast
That much
It's at all a couple of things that Dairy brings to his attention some of which are not accurate at all so
Accurate
Outside of that there's not much like
In terms of update
That are being Incorporated
It's kind of
S*** talking
Yeah yeah I think I can sum up the episode pretty well
And it's
+ 175
Team Plus
Well actually - 93
Because they got that one wrong
Well actually
-60
Cuz they got 33 right
So that puts us at where do I have you been
Keeping track of this
No but I like where you're going with it all right
Okay
So
98% chance
Inside Job
It was the government for sure
Now it's the EU probably
So weird much like Alex will be taking a break
He goes off there and then comes back at 9 that Eve
I will be back on Wednesday to go over
What strange Wilson still vu
We deserved it
God knows
Jordan
Play website
It's knowledge right.com
Ross on Twitter go to bed Jordan
But until then
Omnia I'm Leo idzi scarred
I'm Terry Brownfield
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color