Damn important I'm sweating
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
What's fight.com
Alex Jones
Jordan
Damn do you know what my brights
And I went and played tennis earlier this afternoon wonderful
Good-o
Blasted until that I was like well I'm going to take a little sit-down I could see that I feel like she
Probably is a person who has about a million talents
That like you just don't
Expect 100%
Every everything you accidentally click and go to it like a knife throwing
In place
That I know I threw knives for awhile whenever I was in college and you like what
That's what she called
Texts being good at skill
I know I
I think we were pretty if we were on a pretty even-keeled better way of bragging
Where she was just
So just teasing you like it wasn't even hard
Well
As many people know I have started to grow some plants
And
Couple of cucumbers coming up couple of seedlings
I also have
Some grow bags with potatoes
It needs potatoes to grow at all potatoes and general myself
I just feel like there's something weird about putting a potato on the grill
I'm expecting something very weird I was just in there
And I was looking at the soil and little buds
Are coming up out of the potato
Like out of the dirt
Borrowing from the Spud
So that's really exciting
It is fun that sometimes you can really like take a step back
NSYNC
You know I bet a long time ago somebody just threw a potato and then a bunch of potatoes grew wherever it landed
Like that whenever the land was
Was filled with
You threw a potato and potatoes would show up I had like a little compost
Thing going and I had a
Make a pinto bean a baby I'm not sure what it was
It was in
The sprouting
Whatever like garbage and it's still sprout
It was I was not to look just coffee grind Center
Like it just
It's so funny how so many plants are like I get there
It's just no way to make this grow and then their tongues where he likes
Yep
Something they also. Get away from me to is Alex Trebek
Segway
Are we go into part two of our examination of his
Which is 9 to midnight and
You haven't listened to the first one go ahead and do that because
Babe this prereq it better get better
Think about it at ready for a weird ride after we left after we were done recording and I'm just like
In my head I really don't believe if you would
Told me
20 years ago if you would
Showed me the broadcast
I would not have believed it was happy
I came up to you and I was like hey Alex Jones is that the EU 111
Order to help strengthen the euro
Observation I guess
Absurd
Yeah yeah there's a lot of a lot of surprises going on
Well I'd say put first
Get into any of that
Text Beach Journal policy wonk
Next
Alex's Journal policy
This is
Too late
Little bit
From Arkansas
Alex
Kirby's Return to Dream Land thank you so much
That was well done
I'm so before we get into the episode proper I wanted
Just to give a little bit of apology and clarification again
I use the term Afghani to refer to a person on the last episode of night is incorrect
I was unaware of this about this and I appreciate the person
Correct me on that it just
I don't know why
I guess I
I had no idea it's Afghan
Is the term for a person
Afghani is monetary unit that was
He's just completely in my blind-spot I have I have heard people referred to in that way
Contacts
Extend places where it didn't seem like it was effective
I'm so I guess I had just assumed straight up told me I'd like
I would have told you that I swear I heard people say it on TV like a few days ago like I have no idea
I'm glad that I didn't appreciate learning more though
So I look
I decided that if I was going to do this episode here covering Alex's shows on 9/11
It'd be important not just be the only way that I experience
The tragedy
I was alive when this happened
Of course but it's been 21 years and some of the memories have faded
If you wildly incomplete for me to approach this and just rely on my own memories and Alex
This is bulshit
I can read documents and reports but those are a little bit sterile an unfeeling one of the unexpected things about
What does morning show that we covered on our last episode
Was that you didn't seem to have a human response to the attack
Though he said it was the most important day in like a century
The show didn't have a feeling that conveyed the gravity of what people were experiencing
He took calls and people were crafting
Conspiracies out of bizarre numerology
You got gas
But they are people who
You know work that affected or they were trying to sell gold
This all felt like a huge disrespect
To the people who were living through hell pushing there
Experienced to the side in order to use it
Good for your own purpose
And I wanted to make sure that I held onto a little bit of the severity of the subject or cover
This is a show that's meant to be funny and entertaining so it's easy to put on that facade of not taking things too
To seriously being like
Glib
In order to make sure I held on to some semblance of perspective as I dealt with Alex I decided it would be helpful to also watch
Various news outlets live coverage
Of the tragedy so I watch
Hours
An H
Live
CBS
Local Fox affiliate
Of the day
I am.
I believe you
I was telling you that I'm a bit tired
A lot of that was during the day
I think I'll just do 911 a couple times because there's different channels
Part of it was I wanted to get a sense of like the information space that Alex would have been living in but he got on air
At 9 p.m.
Innocence of
How the media was
Covering it
You're so much of Alex's entire point
Anything is drawing Broad
Conclusions from how he feels
The media is doing other people's report
Choose the keeses
Imagined or not right media and pretends that there's a directives and marching order at the globalist
I'm so something that I felt would be kind of important was it
Experiencing a bit of that and luckily
You can find
Pretty much full coverage videos on YouTube
Pretty well-documented day
YouTube channel that has a lot of very important days
Like just straight news coverage
Check out so I watch too much of that
Some of that will inform some of the stuff that we get into today but I'll give you the CliffsNotes version
Version of this
I want to show is really bad
Terrible
We rightly criticised the media for a lot of sensationalism and there are tons of other problems with the big Networks
For the most part
And I am not
Does they seem to handle a lot of coverage fairly well
3D
Impressed
Bye
The coverage
As events were unfolding
Yeah there was a there was a respect for what was happening
There was a restraint in leaping to conclusions
Like the CBS was the first one I watched
And they took forever to eat
Even admit that it wasn't
An
Right you know they had a real resistance to
Using terminology around terrorism picture weave there's not enough inform
Formation coming in
We know this is a tragedy but we don't know who's really found
It didn't
But with how I remembered how the stories are told
About 9/11 was that
There really wasn't
A like
Hard finger pointed at bin Laden
Intel
Quite a bit later
It was it was it was fun things
No I mean in the evening there was sort of a consensus coming around that like
It's probably him
This is a good suspect
Read the story that
We tell is that like
Immediately they said it was Osama bin
America isn't the case
Oh no the Palestinian group that took responsibility for it initially conversation
Is this
Credible taking responsibility
And then
Brought up as a possible person because
He attacked
Predict the future
The possibility of State actors
More of a conversation about possibilities
I was I was kind of surprised
Experience at cuz I thought I'd go back into be like so much better
Talk like straight out
Yeah baby. Super
But I really had
I thought of in the past but I don't
Like my memory of it I didn't
Remember people even throwing around like
Here's who did it at all for awhile like for at least a couple of days or so for me is just people were like
Wow that was f***** up
Terror you know like the whole thing they've they didn't actively put a name on it
For a while
Yeah and I think that a large amount of
The coverage
Instead you fine
That I was watching
More with a human end of it
Then
The who did this
Although as the day went on certainly there was some conversation of
Who did this in
People made were
I didn't see as much racism
Violin
Got a lot of people for blood
Remember happening right away at there was a former Secretary of State who was on CNN
I got my boo who it was
Eagle bird
And
He was like
Look
We got to kill somebody
Whether we can prove they were directly
Connected or not we got to go and kill somebody
Oh boy
That was what's funny about Alex
Saying we got a Newcomb
I'm at earlier episode is that I do remember being briefly a fairly mainstream thought
People would like Bandy about like okay so what do we do
Do we nuke him
What's that kind of thing
It's a visceral reaction that you have
Like a punch that's coming
Interesting was that that was part of Alex
Response as well
He likes to pretend that he's above that kind of not be that emotional response
Centerpiece and he doesn't
1 expand
Nuking some f****** country
If you can't possibly be in paperback even if you
You proved that their government did 911 you're just going to kill someone
I mean essentially you're declaring war on the earth not on
Enough
Yeah and
So here we are
That's where we'll be more along the way I Kira
But here it we start Alex's evening show and familiar tone
Alright ladies
It is 9/11
September 11th
Ambli
Numbered days isn't it
Amply
Allowed
Throughout the
Early morning
Hours
I have
Been one of those lone voice
Job fair warning
You about Deborah
Sponsored
Terrorism
So there's again like in Iran
Immediately show and that's
Bizarre
I was already I was prepared for it I was like I know right at the gate he's going to be like look at how right I was
It's it seems like one of the most important things that he wants
Distress
And to me
That seems
I am a prophet of Doom
Follow me for I have predicted what has befallen us
So Alex has been watching
In some of the local and national news
And he has
Some word
I have the latest
Information and then I went
Away from
The collapse World Trade
I'd centers an world
A total of 5
Instead of collapse
Totaled
Burn to the ground
Collapse
Rump Shaker
Leaving local
Rock song for that
Wrong song
Fours and
Baltimore Sun new book
Us tariff
Casually listen to dead people in u.s. newspaper
Indignation
Information your calls coming up
The local and national news outlets are used to demolish to build
That is just made up
I'm not sure if it's accurate to say that five buildings had fallen
Partially because I just don't know what the definitions were using our
World Trade Center 12 and 7 definitely fully collapse
Building 3 4 5 and 6
But also non World Trade Center complex buildings that were destroyed in the attack
And it seems difficult to precisely quantify that
For instance the Saint Nicholas
Greek Orthodox church was destroyed by Falling
Debris
I don't know
Discounted in Alex's
Piano Factory
It's a particular
But I just don't think it's five buildings as an accurate count regardless of how you define
I know that Alex seems to also the still not know the name of operation Northwoods
Or want to say it
Or something
Strange there is a key
Consistent
Use of that name
Where is now it's a buzz world
He loves operation
Not on 9/11
Well I mean that is the most respect
Yeah that's about as good as we're going to get from babe I'm assuming
Yeah
So there's some things that Alex is just wrong about your butt again
I think there's a number things that he's wrong about that are
Totally acceptable
I'm very understanding
At least five
Towers are down
Two of them the
Fourth largest building
On the planet
Upwards of 20,000
People are dead at least
Those cowards held
50000 people
Got a lot of them haven't gotten to work yet they're on the
He's posted 851 that purse
Passenger
Whiners
Smashed into the South Tower
His number is higher than a lot of the numbers that were being thrown around and other news outlets but
I understand that feeling and I understand that sense of
Like I said
You know
You look at something like that you can't imagine it
Killing a million
It is like it was a bit like seeing Godzilla knock down a toy
Power and then being like there were only a few thousand dead near like
I mean I know that's a tragedy that's horrific
I really thought the entire f******
Area was going to be
What grounds do you see the videos of people running
From the debris cloud
The way that the debris cloud like
Enveloped them exactly it's it's it's unthinkable
That
You know you wouldn't
Assume
For sure
Is like 20,000
At least
That's a little bit stronger
Yeah but I get it
I don't feel like
I want I wanted to include something like this and
Whenever
Wrong about but he's right
To be wrong numbers he probably shouldn't have thrown around that number that high and definitely shouldn't have
Confirmed at least but
If you to see if you would ask me I've been like Basher 20 30 40 that sounds right
You know I'm not here to nitpick
Alex I'm not here to be like haha you got this wrong
Because I could
With that
But I would much rather spend my time on stuff like this
I'm in the towers began to collapse
I have one of the designers
Chicago Tribune
Chang this is
Impossible
I've been trying to get ahold of General bitton Parton all night with his
This phone has been busy
Perpetually
We actually had a structural engineer on the
The show today
That is not how buildings go down
You can see here already that Alex is claiming that he had a structural engineer on his show this morning who said it was a demolition went in
A friend of his on
Who'd studied some Engineering in college but now working in a financial sector job
The way Alex is seeking to solidify this talking point is for the perception to be that the guests he had on was a purse
Work professionally as a structural engineer
Because of that perception strengthens the illusion of his claim
Where is presenting his guests accurately would reveal how flimsy is s*** is
Also this article in the Chicago Tribune
You can find it it has the headline
Engineer shock
Spy Towers collapse
And nowhere in the article does this supposed co-designer claimed the way that the Builder
Wings collapse
Was
That's a claim that Alex's inventing from thin air
Just adding
The article discusses how less Roberts
Send one of the structural engineers of the Trade Center
Hey given to talk in Frankfurt Germany a week before the attacks
And it brought up the Builder
That the buildings were designed to withstand an impact
From a 707 jet
This is likely an accurate statement but it's being published in the Tribune not as a direct quote
They're actually quoting an engineer named Joseph Burns who was at the conference relaying Roberts
Sims words
The article literally says quote
Burnsed Robertson did not elaborate on the remark
The buildings were designed to withstand a crash from smaller planes like a personal plane or even up to a 707
But the Jets on 9/11 were
Bigger and Mater
I think one of the real
Alex is doing this is because he's not very creative
This this game is a
Creative
We can see in present-day every single mass shooting is basically the same
They want your guns
Who's the guys on psych meds
Incel
There's basically just bullet point
City applies to each new shooting regardless of the actual details
Have the real situation
He did the controlled demolition secret bombs in the building
Conspiracy with Oklahoma City
And he has another situation where buildings were destroyed that he needs
To turn into a
Conspiracy
It only seems natural that he would do the same thing over a
It's so much easier
You're for him particularly because
Whenever you making any kind of
You may need to just say
Like they did in OKC
And Guardians is prime to lend whatever Alex is saying more credibility
Looking at Alex's Behavior here on 911
And I really don't feel like
He's doing anything different from what he always does
He's got a conspiracy archetype that he's working with and he's applying it to the current Hot Topic
He has a guest whose expertise of being exaggerated in order to bolster their claims
He's got headlines that don't say what he
Sports they do
It's kind of dark but
I mean I don't really get the
The sense that this is much
More than another day at the office
Just for him
I mean I am assuming that in two or three days his friend is going to be the top structural engineer in New York City
The most prestige one of the most prestigious the financial sector
I know what he
Why can't I see the trick that he's doing
Already in this episode and it's not that
What he's doing is he's going to try and create
A bifurcated identity
Okay so he'll have his friend who was a financial analyst who was there was a first-hand account
Another
Reply will also be a structural engineer but it's not he
His friend it's his other friend
Implied that they're two different guys
Structural engineer and also I had a friend right
First hand account
So that that's a smooth way to do it then you never name that structural engineer
I need outside point out that he is actually a financial advisor
Who may be undergrad
It's like when somebody is an expert on MSNBC and then a few years later they show up on Fox Business with
Completely different special
What are you
Here we see
I mean look
This is just
I had to
Sit with this clip
Yeah it really frustrated
And I was actually the local KLBJ radio
When I get another structural engineer on from Texas A&M who did part of the analysis
Back in 1993 for the First World Trade Center bombing
China Fish wouldn't happen
And then the host City yeah
I was watching local news this morning right one and happened and then about 20 minutes later
30 minutes later when the first Tower collapse
The reporters were panicking
Explosion on the bottom floor
And the sounds were picked up by the audio.
Hyperspin machine is in overdrive just like in Oklahoma City telling us
The truck bomb outside blows out columns further back and blast them off
Wing Lee at the bottom making rebar
Concrete
Disappear
So you can see from that clip what I mean by the OKC stuff
Alex wants to wrap up his talking points and references to OKC so in order to even address any of his
It feels like you have to completely re-litigate all of his conspiracies about the Murrah building bombing
Before you do so
And you don't have to do the
This is a distraction tactic
Alex is employing
And it's totally okay to just ignore it for now
It's not relevant to the question of whether or not bombs took down the World Trade Center to talk about his
His ideas about
Oklahoma City
I want to track this story here that Alex is telling an illustrate to help with
Prophetic the level of sourcing he's using is to make the
This point
Alex was listening to a local show on KLBJ where the host said that
He had watched an unspecified local news show
Where they were saying there was a
Floor of the World Trade Center that was caught on the audio tape and now they're scrambling cuz there's a cover-up
Cuz it got caught to the sound oh no
This is useless
Even if you wanted to check on the
Let's claim what would you do
Sereno the Jeff Ward
What is the KLBJ host
TV station was he watching
Pretty much every local news station be running National coverage since so many of them are NBC or ABC or
CBS affiliates
Like I watched a fair amount of the news coverage
To me at all
But because of the vagueness of his claim
No matter what I say Alex could just Retreat to the claim that I just did
Watch the right videos it must have been on another Channel
I can definitely say that reporters
We're freaks out when the Builder
That was because two giant skyscrapers were falling and dust clouds are racing down the streets towards them and everyone was essentially run
For their lives having difficulty breathing
InstaCare
Here it actually is Alex's
One of his baby mama sees Nico
Who was reporting live
From
New York
And she had actually taken up shelter in a school
Running from the building
Things falling
Mika Brzezinski
Is downtown Macon
Hi Mika Brzezinski reporting from
PS 89 it's at it near the scene of the collapse of what we believe to be the
Number one of the World Trade
Center CBS News correspondent Byron Pitts we were coordinating our
Cruise-in
Crowd of people near the corner of Murray Avenue and the West Side Highway
When the collapse occurred and literally
Looms
Smoke
And gases as the collapse happened I'm sure you're seeing in the video
Began to roll or way and that is when the
The crowd went wild people just
Began to run
Our live truck shutdown
Crews were running reporters were running people running in the cops
Literally were just waving their arms saying go go go we are inside the school right now actually inside a small
Ballroom
Trying to stay clear of the crowds that are trying to get out of the way and also the evacuation of this school
School officials here are trying to get everybody out of the building in an orderly fashion as as quickly as possible
But again there is
So much confusion out on the
It is literally
Chaos out there we've got a short timeline here
School right now
Is
Is now putting on the intercom
Where kids
Need to go
To assemble W classes
Your chamber street they're trying to organize
The closet
These kids out of here safely is
Possible right now we're dealing with
The air
Because of the plumes
Smoke and gases Byron 2019 a weedeater
To move quickly
Because the
Smoke that was rolling our way in the debris is well
It's very thick and it
Could be very dangerous
It was already a chaotic situation
Before
The collapse happened in this is
Just piling up
More dangerous damage on top of what was already a very chaotic
Situation
I'm not sure any other reporters were too concerned with the b******* games Alex plays considering many of them were huddling in a class
Kids are trying to figure out how to reunite with their families
And everyone was worried about poison air
I don't feel like
This is
Alex being
Now I'm going to go ahead and say that yeah
Listens pretty bad
The previous clip
Doesn't look so bad
Comparison to this
Makes things look real f*****-up
The part about the engineer from Texas A&M presents the same
Problem is Alex's other sourcing issue
The details provided cannot possibly be sufficient to trace down this claim
I went to the Texas A&M Structural Engineering Department website and they have 15 faculty members listed
But you can see how we're no closer to knowing
I could go through all of these professors resumes and find nothing
Think I dwell what if the person I was talking about his retired or died
Hey guess what there are multiple reports and official reports that have been made
About
The 1993 World Trade Center bombing
I can go and find them and
I have so many of them
They don't have
Professor from Texas A&M
I just didn't find the right report you really dropped the ball on this one dad
There a lot of built-in loopholes to the to the details that Alex rattles often protected from
Attempts to make people proven naked
Like that no Texas A&M professor said that
Sore that the local news clip
He claims he heard a local radio host
Talk about doesn't exist
And he does that because he couldn't do anything else
He has to force you to do something impossible to prove him wrong
Because if you were forced to establish and defend his own claim
He will fail every time
And if you
If you get him to stay on that he'll be like but what about the Oklahoma City bombing
And that will try and get you to start arguing about the OKC bombing
So then you're already forgetting what you were supposed to be arguing about
Which was 9/11 the first
Once once you're not allowed to
He just pulled this tract
Balls everywhere just like anything shiny to get you away from the point
I think this is a good example of that
You're watching
My mind
Control unfold
Whether the government was involved in it or the European Union as they roll out the
The Euro this parts
Ashley Gold back
Trading above $2
Osama bin Laden
The 80s
Why is fam
Still bill
Are military bases in
Saudi Arabia
Weiser family
The Border
Satellite
I want to know why we didn't take Saddam out at 1991
50 miles
Downtown Baghdad
What is reached the phase of Alex's reporting where he asks a bunch of distracting questions that he knows the answer to
Yep GIF under been locked because he was fighting
The Communist enemy that you wanted people to fight
The bin Laden family get a lot of
Construction contract because they're not terrorists
And they run a really big
Construction Enterprise
Terrorism is not like it runs in the family I hear color
Sleeping with the Iridium satellite thing it
It's just people who are doing business who happen to be related to a terrorist and aren't
First themselves
In order to claim that this is nefarious or any of the stuff is nefarious
You need to provide some information other than
Say it like
I mean it's like I want to know why they let Osama bin Laden
I need to know why that man was allowed to go to college
You can't
Also as for why they didn't kill Saddam
You got me I don't really have an answer.
Honestly
Why you say probably a strategic reason of some sort maybe I don't know sometimes it's like who they decide to take a shower
Giada and who they don't is
Is not as
It doesn't make any sense
You know we're going to try and kill it we're going to try and kill this this leader
But this guy
We're not going to do that
I'm not sure what's a calculus went into that
So I guess if we want to get distracted
A good way for out I cannot talk about 9/11 on 9/11
Who do we kill list
Keep coming back
To this because it's
Seems bizarre to me
Alex seems to have no idea
Anything about operation Northwoods except
A blurb
From this Baltimore Sun article
That includes
Mentioned
Operation Northwood
And it's wild
This is from the
Baltimore Sun
Posted
Since April on infowars.com
Him interview James Bamford former 2020 executive best-selling author
On the puzzle Palace on the interstate
And of course his new best-selling book
Kill New York Times bestseller list
April
Body of Secrets
A900 page
Us
Military leaders proposal
G2a secret plan to commit Tierrasanta
Blank Cuba
Create a pretext for Invasion the Oscar
For your new book about the National Security
How do I support that spilt bag
Adele
No but I don't support
Becoming Fidel.
Fightful
And the main headline is
Secret
Human race
Pretext
New York Times
She seems to think the name is Cuban Invasion pretext
It does seem that that's what he said called I think he's misreading
What what appears to be a book review maybe that was in The Baltimore Sun
Of a book that he totally read half of already
Already
Promise he doesn't have really any handle on much of the details outside of what would be in that book review
It does seem suspicious doesn't it does
Especially considering
That
You know you're supposed to be this person who
Would consider a document like that one of the most important things
Absolutely
Furthering your cause of spreading
Totally
You should probably know that thing inside and outside backwards forwards
I don't get the sense that he does pretty sure he has no idea what the name is because earlier it's like maybe he forgot or he
Pull it right away this is hours later
You should I mean you could have even looked at you could have read the article in the between tribe organized organized
He does hit the surface level of Northwoods
Really hard
Casualty list
That means blister
Dead people
A US newspaper
Bridgewood Plaza helpful wave of indignation
MMA in Memphis
We can pick a passenger ship we can blow up airliners
We can attack one tana Mobay in the Marine
They're using Army dressed up
Cuban
I mean they're here in this article
Quotes from the documents
Confirm wanting a blow-up airliner
Now it was signed on to
The Joint Chiefs of Staff
The Secretary of Defense
And Kennedy
Despite all his evil
God bless his soul
No way
CIA
Don't remember if
Yeah that's a funny story
We've talked about operator
Operation Northwoods a bit in the past and you know it
Not without
Describe
Staff
Not an actual
Attacker people
These will be fake
Pretend
People not actual dead
Got Diane really did a lot for Kennedy I think if he had lived he would be remembered as a realshit president but dying
Billy gave him a lot of
A lot of good Buzz
Really
It leads
People to
Come up with reasons for his death and a lot of them end up
Assassination of a president obviously would have to be pinned on the bad guy
So how many must be the good guy someone killed him
He was one of the Assassin was a good guy and he saved the world
I mean never even condemned we never even address that possibility
Get me Doctor Strange
So
This show my man
This is a real
Is it no
And I warned you on here
This show is not a game
This is not entertainment this is information
And I warned you over and over and over
Forget to call washing
And we know you're behind the terror
I do have to tell you how often do grocery store today
This morning right what happened
Get something
Everybody a noun
Alex we know you're right the government blew it
Maybe the EU doing
Wow
What a time at that grocery store
Everyone's like I have Alex alright hero of 911
Autocorrect might be the EU
Sharkboy be too crazy even for f****** nuts you nothing
Oh my God
Alex
This is too hard of a swing for 2001
Two Hearted
I don't not popular enough for
The f****** abuse of saying
If you had called your Senators more
911 wooden
Have happened
There is a little bit of an undertone of that
There is an undertone of that
Yeah everybody had listened to me harder
This wouldn't have happened
I think it's one reading of that there's another reason the kind of goes like we tried our best
You know like no matter how many people called
You know you can have a clear conscience because you could
Possible but it ain't no being generous
I'm going to lean more towards the ungenerous interpretation
What's about to happen is unthinkably offer
You have to
Are you at the dispenza events this week so far to the generous
In order to understand how bad this is
And whatever ill feelings you might have about dinner at 4
Blaming his audience are not calling
They are
A pittance compared to what's about to happen
Caught wind of
The fact that
The people onboard hitbox
Steve
And solution is the same solution that he has for everything
I'm somebody
Arm the pilots
Windows exploding Air Marshal ball
Any of us can buy
It'll go through about an inch
Something but nothing more
And put an armored bulkhead door on those aircraft and I'm hearing these guys
Supposedly
Planes of paper
The box cutters
He pulled a box cutter on me and.
Mommy I take them away and broken
Don't brag about how
Mister tough guy but
Sounds pretty rough
So they can obviously this machismo this I would f*** this guy up chair
That's to be expected
She has a real Macho problem
But where this takes him
I think is
The angle that he's taking with this in his neck
Clip
I was I was disgusted
I just walked over and grab it maybe I'm stupid
School
Tackle
You got piles in a Plane full of people
They supposedly have box cutters how do we know this
The former Clinton administration people was on board
Wife
Longboard at aircraft
Call Pomona
Phone to cell phone
And you believe that do on a plane with man enough
Complain to somebody got a box
Are you believe that they would fly A10
The 500 miles an hour that thing was moving
Pothos planes into that building
I got a bridge I want
Want to sell you
Score we're getting there is punk
I can't believe that you had hundreds of
Sheep on those planes
He probably shut around me
You can't kill me with it go ahead and cut me I'm coming in
Maybe a double-edged
Stiletto style dagger
Patty more deadly the person
Any man would do that any
Woman would do that
So there's a lot of uncertainty in terms of the details of exactly how these hijackings white so I'm not going to dip too far in
Into that pool but there's something I think it's important to point out
On the evening of 9/11 Alex is getting on his nationally syndicated radio show and arguing that the people who
Who died on those hijacked planes were cowards
And not big
Strong boys like him
That's completely disgusting
Years
Years after this
After 9/11
More than a decade
Mark Wahlberg would say the same thing and still people be like that
F****** awful I think monster
I'm not
Really caught up on all of Mark Wahlberg's comments but my understanding is just that it wouldn't have happened if he was there
I don't know why but somehow that's kind of okay because that's not
Impugning the people who are on board as much as it is elevating yourself which people were
Rightly criticizing him for
Sure Alex is doing both
Alex is elevating himself
I'm calling everybody else coward
Are not man or woman enough to do what is human nature
Right on the day
Day of their
Find this gross I don't know how to
I don't know how to live
Did I lie
I've never been in a hijacking
Situation but I think I can imagine some scenarios where you would
Think it was a good idea to attack the terrorists who taken over
For the plane
For one thing it's unlikely that you'd think they were going to crash the plane into a building
A lot of hijackings are done to hold hostages for financial gains or to spread political messages
And I can see thinking that you might survive the ordeal like they might just landed
Cuba if you have a knowledge of
Playing the history overtime you're like
S*** there were actually a lot of hijacking
Kings for a while and everybody lived
Pizza Heist type of
Hijacking
Used to make the situation worse
By trying to fight back
You could be increasing
That the plane crashes
And you or someone else is killed
Right now
In hindsight
It's easy to see how the people on those planes were essentially do
But it seems so unfair and disrespectful to take this kind of tone
Particularly less than 24 hours after the attacks
Alex's soul
Gross it's the it's that impulse though that they all have the people who are like this tragedy happen
Can give somebody a gun there
You do give a teacher a gun in school like all of those thing
It's because what they're really doing is expressing their fantasy of give me a gun let me go back in time end
That situation
So I can personally be a hero
Right because I know everything that would have happened so I can be the winner there
There is a bit of that there's absolute is it self-aggrandizement if you are saying give teachers a gun to protect
Students you are saying
I could
Protect everybody if I had a gun
That's what you're really saying
And that's what he's saying right there I can print I can fight off a tie Jacker I can fight off a terrorist I can do it all just
Just put me in there
I find it less
Abhorrent
To say I could do these things
It may be right
It's maybe an expression of narcissism
It's maybe wrong
It's definitely not the time for it to the negative
No
But I there is something different about it being
Presented as
I don't believe
This story because
Any human
Who isn't a complete pile of s*** coward
I would have taken over the plane from the hijackers
I find that to be a
Like
It's A Bridge Too Far Man been played are here for you
Maybe he was just thinking
That's a hopeful
Yeah
Let's get a look at them under oath let's see what he says
That would take some calls
And one guy
Michaels in
And now it's wants his take
But unfortunately he does not give the right to
Trying
That's juices take a little bit to the right place
Kim in Virginia
You think happened here today
Well your gut level from all the others we brought
Here
Down here before the Sabbath
Predicting it
And all the others we've been collating
Oh well
It could be
People have probably had most of the
Money and
Probably around
Yeah but who stands to gain from the
Something where is senior sales here and we really Hotel
Who stands against
Washington the market sorority and floating on Friday and Monday
They were already talking about
Spending Trading
But even more than wife
There is a fissure in the New World Order
Reported by our
Scholarship
Fisher
Dr. Coleman dr. Kaufman
Dr. Monty
General pardon
We're talkin about
Doing right now
Stores and Banks
Yeah man
He's really pushing the EU did 911 on 9/11
He's pretending that he's getting this analysis from hold these people I mean he is not getting it
He said multiple times on the show he can't get ahold of Bret Hart
He's perpetually busy
So now you telling us that this guy is giving him information that there's a fissure in the globalist camp
And that is led to the EU
911 I would say
First of all f*** you
A letter first second
Why should I have any faith you're dumb dumb friends have any idea if the
Globalists are getting along I mean
Because they do they give us weekly or globalist us
There's a Maxim magazine but just for Global
Haha
I think this is dumb but it is really funny to see Alex
This guy to say eat
He's really into the EU
So we're watching the destruction ladies
I don't know who did it
Was it Ben Laden acting alone
20% chance
What is this government
30% chance
Didn't you seems 98q and her operatives
Shakopee
Or Brian control subjects
50%
That's my analysis
Frankly I've never been wrong
I wish I was wrong everyday
Congratulations your wishes with gray
Every single day
You have
You do not need a genie
Earlier in the day 98% chances are government
The globalists right in our government
So Alex earlier in the day
His buddy
Who was Aiden at our nearby
Witness the attack
Maybe he had him on
And it blossomed
Into a
I am so just for good measure Alex has him back on
So the EU did the
Controlled demolition
I don't know what I don't know why your pictures
So Jim is back
Alex has new bomb evidence for him to sign off on
Now
Jimmy
You have a degree in engineering
And without me even prompting you and your wife called me
Here at home
We got the interview of that post on the website right now
And said that
Let me know Alex Jimmy was there
And then
She gave me her cell phone number we got
You were literally walking
Charred bodies
They were piling up
You
Wander Over Yonder cord said
Punjabi rapper
Scene
Now I'm hearing all local and National radio
And we've heard reports
This morning it was a reporter out front is one building
Another one
Smoking
The first one
You'd explode in the bottom
Airporter jumper cover
The structural engineer who designed
The building is
Chicago Tribune
Just out on infowars.com of the viewers Phylicia
Would like to see that
Shangri-La
He designed it
How to take out the 777
What time is it
Time does chop't
The top of the building off
Strong building
Instead you see a perfect
Falling
Nnn
As the top
How what were your,
Agreed
Person is structural engineering
Play one of my
Colleagues
Who's also a
Construction engineering
Weave
Watch the time in both of our,
The building
Chick-fil-A
Eminem
Straight down
Which
Is very hard thing to accomplish
Structural steel building
Because the
Steelton
So we listen to the morning show and at no point during those interviews was Jim walking through burning corpses that were
Piling up
That's a disgusting grotesque and exploitative image that Alex is painting and he should be ashamed
That was his instinct
To do something
But in this clip you can see the larger game that Alex
Who's playing
He's got his Structural Engineering expert back on so we can lay out this new bombing evidence
Billy Gilmour. Loaded endorsement of the
Conspiracy
Ideas
You can tell so clearly how Alex is listing this stuff off for gym
I'm as if to explain
For him
What he want
What's Jim to say in response
Yeah
I went to essentially trying to exploit his family friend here and he's doing it
Using intentional misrepresentation to sources
A meaningless references to things
He claims to have heard a local radio guy say
How about a local news
Allegedly saw
It's
Yeah I mean this is
The way you talk
Is like this is the type of coaching
Can you do off
Are Nares sounds natural when they actually sent you the s*** that you want them to or it's like in an interrogation
Gation room if I was in the room with him I be like
The lawyer
You're not under arrest you're good you're good
So I mentioned
That there was a little bit of
A repeated thing about
The idea that bodies were burning
Inflaming and
People jumping on fire in
He's still on that tip
And I think that there's something
Admirable
Knowing nothing else about Jim Wright
Inmate
He does try and moderate this a little bit
Germany
Nobody
The people coming out of the building
Weavile
Exaggeration
Building but we we did
He is at least
Trying to not play along with the plan
Was Alex's s*** Betty's
Clearly
The exploited
This kind of
Feeling of like
But maybe this guy isn't so bad
A part of it comes from this clip
Anything else you'd like to
Add
Samurai
People that are building
It's better trap
Alright Jimmy Ryan I really
We appreciate you joining us
That's the first time that that kind of concern has been voiced and Alex's response
Okay fine moving on dickwad way to get me nothing like
Look at
Look at what's being said
Jim is pointing out that some people are still too
That's an awareness that Alex's listeners wouldn't have
He's not reported on anything like that on the
The circumstances on the ground the
The human tragedy
B b
Because it's not important
No and it's not his
Movie it's not as movie of the person walking through dead bodies in the flames in the wreckage and there are no serve
Survivors because if there are no survivors you don't have to worry about
Helping people that years of to worry about Klaus Schwab well I won't know about another twenty years you got
What is the big bad guy in the world
Start saving and helping people in
Well or at least have to explain why they are not concerned
So six more calls
And he gets a guy who
Brings up an idea that Alex will take two
Quite a bit and I'll be sure and that is
No
Planes remote
Control
Complicated
And I just wonder what the chance
You know there's a technology
Aircraft
Operate totally on electronics
It's funny you bring that up
Jim
Arjon
That's okay
Did you see on my website the fox say
Television piece about the
Second
The X-Files talk show
Text control of an airplane
My computer and tries to crash
Kid in the world
Trade
Spinner
Ketchup's like
Governor keating's brother white writing that book final
Aldehyde
3 years before the Oklahoma City bombing
Where he mentions mister
McVay
And Liang burpee
Federal Building
They like to brag don't they
Yes the other Technologies
Is there the satellite
Turn place
To look the lone gunmen episode doesn't prove s*** but
It's the kind of evidence that Alex really loves blows people's mind what
And that book bag you could have easily put in the mix
Tails after the fact
Publix
Three years prior that's all Oklahoma City
Conspiracy Lord antrax
To pretend it is
Hello tushy
Basically
Nothing
Right it's exciting that nothing
Yeah
So you didn't
Pieces of nothing
It is a little bit of
Like proving 911 was fake by
Pointing to a Mandela effect
Of the Berenstain Bears you know and they're like
See I got to be honest I'm convinced yet and I mean well it's if it's spelled differently then then I guess you're right
Samantha
Blue my mind
Tonka
I could not have been prepared
I told you we had wide open
We're about to go back to John
Kingsville
Whitening
Missouri Cindy
In West Virginia
Perry Oklahoma darilyn
Texas and other
But coming up in the Box
510 minutes
The song it was in the world
Financial
Center right next door to the world
Expect
Gas is my
Friend
Joe Rogan
What
Call Robert
No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No No-No
Do not tell me
That Joe Rogan was on Alex Jones Show on 911 9911
Okay I need more
Showing up
I guess it's kind of different because Richard Belzer was on but they the Boston bombing
But that was just a coincidence he was there and then he decided to stick around cuz there was a bombing happen
Is Rogan coming on because there was a bombing and he wants
Talk about it
Why do that why do we why isn't isn't known
What is he talking about it I feel like I've talked about his friendship with the night of 9/11
No
You always remember where you were on the evening of 9/11
Why is this I wasn't ready for that
LPR
I was expecting literally any I was like
Ready for the Newton I was ready for anybody but I can't believe it
1 Rogan to Newsradio Rogan
Now this is a few years after that it is a fact
This is yelling at people
Rogan
I don't know the
I don't know
Do you make this up
I tried to refuse I believe
You have gone back in time and forced me to mend together if I could manifest by our life
I would not do that
Please don't
Alexandra has basically convinced himself of his own
Conspiracy
I'll get on the phone
Today was recalled
Interrupt your son in Senate
And avoid
Concerned about what happened
Hear from us right now more than ever
And are you letting them know that you smell a rat
I don't know what I thought about the building
Obviously
Structural engineer
It sure did
Yeah
Because of shape
The Columns at the bay
So none of that's real I mean right had a friend of his who knows a little bit about engineering
Amateur engineer which is not
Sure I mean unless he's a train
Model train guy
You could probably build
Maybe so
Yeah you got that
Congratulations that's not much to go on Chicago
Great
Well it's confirmed
There's nothing here
There's literally nothing
But it's loud nothing
And it's interesting nothing like the lone gunmen
Beyond the thought
The impulse
That a human being would have
Think after her
Hours after two planes
Took down the World Trade Center
20,000-plus people are dead
You call
Lindsey Graham
To tell him
That there were charges on the bottom of the building
Because I misread or I didn't read a Chicago Tribune article
And then Alex says
They need that now more than ever
Yes
Right now
That is the first thing that are exactly
They'll never do anything about it
If it weren't for this guy
So Alex is just misusing
Sources and s***
But
It's also intention
Large passenger plane medium size
World Trade Center
Designer
How the towers
Is saying
Is impossible what happened
Only shape
The bottom could cause that
That's what he said
Kevin boots
My brother-in-law
Do I know
Very well
Who is it
Investment guide
That works in a pint
Towers of it explode
He was an eyewitness
Several hundred yards
Countdown
How we got the Pentagon
Attack
You simply would not act like this if you were a sincere person acting with honest motive
If your goal was to deliver the facts
Or even the facts as
Do you see them
You would not mess around and fake your sources like this
This isn't sloppiness this can only really be the product of intentional deception
Giant manipulations that Alex is trying to pull off in that clip
The first is the way he discusses the Chicago Tribune article
The engineers who designed the World Trade Center didn't say that this was impossible but now Alex is saying that and
In language that makes it sound like this Source included them saying
That only shaped charges could do this
This includes that as an extension of his sentence where he's relaying the alleged comments from this engineer
Anyone listening
Would obviously think this was Alex
Continuing to convey
What was
In this Tribune article
In reality it's just Alex making s*** up
If you read it
Then there would be quotation marks around a certain spot right and then it would be a, and then his editorializing would continue
But if you're listening
Intuit you don't know where those care quotes are everywhere you go
This isn't something he's doing on accident
It's to make his s*** talk appear like it's reporting
The second thing is that Alex is doing is the
He's characterizing his interview with Jim Wright
You can see in that 40-second clip he mentions talking to Jim
Twice
But he's trying to make it seem like he's mentions are about to differ
People that he's interview
What Mansion is a family friend who was a first-hand witness the other is a
Structural engineer
If you were just trying to recap for anyone to and again
You wouldn't
Resent things this way
He mentioned the structural engineer that he had all been lies about the Tribune article that talks about his friend who is an investment banker
First-hand Witness
The two characterizations of Jim's interview are separated because Alex is hoping to disconnect these ideas
In his listeners mind in order to make the narrative stick
Easier
The first-hand witness Jim Wright news an investment banker
Current trend of Alex's
Should be something interesting that happened on the show but ultimately it should be forgot
All Alex wants the audience
Remember is that there was a seemingly very knowledgeable structural engineer
Who said that the building had to have had explosion
There's no way would fall
Alex does this kind of s*** all the time
In his deposition for the Texas Sandy Hook case
There was a particularly good illustration of this same behavior
Mister Jones before we break
I'm asked you about your
Your statement about what
How big
Then you said that
School investigation
Who were the who
Another group
Southern jobs
Anthony said that in addition to those two
That
School safety Expo
Who was that
Righttime in all of these
This is one of Alex's very common tactic
6 World take one piece of information obscure it and then multiply it into a bunch of different
Places
Pieces of information to create the appearance
30th so much more evidence than he actually does
His deposition just said that Wolfgang halbig it been threatened it would
Seem like
A very specific incident that relates to one person who is also harassing victim
Family member
Alex is rhetorical magic the Specter of staple
Lewis School investigation expert
Am school safety experts that have been threatened
The appearance of a
Giant coordinated effort to intimidate
The people who would be in a position to challenge the official narrative
Of what happened at Sandy Hook
This is an effect
Tool to use because if you are paying close attention or you
If you haven't listened
Somebody episode where berries things
Are alleged to have happened
You may just passively accept it outside
Katana details that he's working off of
Well that's definitely not the case
You assume
That he has this structural engineer professional Defenders the first
Are the same person and he's not a structural engineer
It helps it helps that you're listening to it on the radio otherwise you would have to like if you were seeing this in real life
His friend would be wearing a nice suit
Investment banker salary
And then Structural Engineering his friends would go behind the curtain
Put a little cap on a must
Fashion be like
Dear friend
Yeah on the other radio you get away with that a lot easier
Write in pencil like in the same way that Alex wants this to appear like there's a number of things
Not just Wolfgang halbig wine
Brightright
It's that appeared because the actual reality sucks and it doesn't work for him
The actual reality of his interview with Jim right also doesn
Work
And so he has to obscure it and create
Multiple tendrils that he can use for different
Things
Out of it and that's something that he does a bit
And that's really difficult
The trace down
One of the
It's one of the tactics but he uses that it's
It's
It requires
Having listened to a ton of his s***
That's where this is coming from
Kind of self-contained
To some extent
You know like he's referencing this thing to happen
Earlier the day we listen to that episode
And so like that help
Make that
Crackdown easier
We think they're like
I'll never be able to know what the fuc
He's talking about you know this is one of the things that I think is probably the most
Common and may be useful tool of media literacy at all is just understanding what people
People are saying when they say
You know like you read any number of different things about any number of different things
And they're quoting experts and the people who are they're quoting
Don't trust
Pope
Conditionally truck
But not whenever Alex
So expert
Pixelmon
News radio station
You do the space episode one time he was well he did destroy ever
Joe girelli
Pokemon
Joe Rogan
Alex
Here to go to the Hollywood
Perspective
Good body knows all about
Joe Rogan
Popular
Ascend Decatur
Host of Fear
Scott's number one rated
Show on
Anodyne
I'm just really excited about how
Hey Alex
What's going on man
I don't want to sound like a dick
Because I love Newsradio and I think Rogan was great and Israel but you're kidding yourself if you said he's one of the top guys
Eyes on that show
It was an ensemble casts
Fast but you're high
If you think that he was on the varsity level of that ensemble
Maybe I actually sat down and thought about this
For quite a while
Best 6 banana
Yeah you think so yeah
What's a Foley and Phil Hartman or tied for first
Right below the 100% is amazing Envy Lake
The clump
Of the top
The Ensemble
Then there's the people who have
Like storylines that
Pretty consistently Vicki Lewis
And you have Jimmy James Stephen Root
A man underneath that you have
Khandi Alexander
And that's cuz Candy Alexander
Brutal underused shooter
So been somewhat underused used
Exactly the right amount cuz anymore and he would be exactly like Rogan which is annoying and really bothersome to me
Barry Hospital
An argument can be made that he has
But
Yeah man Stephen Root is sneak
Watching news radio then
I would not have thought one
Stephen Root is going to look better
30 years later he's going to have the career that maybe I envy the most out of anybody ever
He's a solid at Candy's amazing
6 memorable moments certainly one of the
All time
Not many Beyond.
He's he's part of that just talked about shaft
That is true like a
B12 be you big strong refrigerator
Refrigerator
So messy
Yes
Somebody somewhere but
Come on
Hot guys
No.
I mean Phil Hartman
If you if you even breathe without saying Phil Hartman and Newsradio in the same setting something
If you said Andy Dick was one of the top guys
Is on I disagree
I disagree
Matthew is featured
Constant
I understand stuff going on with Matthew
Anybody
Well I will admit
The way he fell was pretty spectacular yes he knew how to fall him and Vicki Lewis
They were
The zaniness
If you need that right that Dynamic the chaos episode
That one
The complaint box I got the complaint box
What is the greatest episode of TV
McCain of course absolutely
Or the smoking
Left news radio talk cuz we got to talk to Rogue
So
Alex
He started out the morning show
People to know that he predicted this Easter
Evening show talking about how he predicted
That is going to start off this interview with Rogan Kelly Rogen
I predicted that do you know I was predicting this
Tell me all about
Well now you do predict that
The government is doing
Thanks buddy
Let me know
You don't believe there's people another country that they hate
Oh I know there are but I know this
MSNBC
Ben Lawton
Comes home to roost
The CIA ties are only the beginning
MSNBC
I mean he supposedly had CIA
But that doesn't mean that he didn't like
Get angry when he was work
I hate America
What's the CIA
No I hear you now.
They're saying it could be alright
There's
Anybody
And my question is why
Take back that night
D91
If I had more time to prepare this episode
How to make a Supercut of every time Alex reads that line about Bin Laden coming home to roost
It's been probably a hundred times he's used it and he's never actually
Discuss the content of the article or how
Glosses over about how about the 1993 bombing
And optically that's as good as any evidence so whatever
Alex throws that headline at Joe is the most common sense reply that been on may have been working with the CIA in the
Past but to think that he's still is would be
Alex should disagree with
But he can't really support his own argument so he just
Gives up on that point
Essentially wind
How many moves on to his next talking point about how we should have killed Saddam and taking over Baghdad in the last Gulf War
What's going on is that says a few conversation pass as Ops
To distract the audience from realizing that it is a dead-end and Alex has nothing
To say about this article that he
He's constantly bringing up
Hibbett store
Sweetly different subject
This is disorienting if you're taking the conversation seriously and think there's a coherent
Going on here
I want to sing that he's been predicting this another government
Uses these kinds of events to accrue power which Rogan agrees
At this point in the day there's already some talk about Bin Laden being responsible going on so Alex trots out this article from 19
To demonstrate that he's correct
Did they even if bin Laden
I do still.
Do points out that this.
Prove that bin Laden
Is working with the CIA
Which is at the Crux of what Alex's suggested by bringing up that article
Simon Alex completely crumbles
Talking about Saddam
This is not a normal or rational conversation or interview path
Because it's neither of these
It's an attempt to get Joe to
Mirror Alex is talking point
Which failed in its first attempt so Alex tried another road
Yeah it is
It is
It is interesting to me
But he didn't immediately bring up that the
The EU did it
Because the EU is the most likely
50% over
Both Iraq
And the government Logan is no people at the grocery store
Hey man I'm hearing
Germany did it what what are you thinking the EU today or just to launch in this currency Germany
Open coming for us
You know
I think that Alex's
Baby wants to ease into it a little bit
That you don't want to throw that it Rogan right off the bat blow his mind
Joe Rogan I don't know maybe he thinks that Rogan will like
Capital of
Are you kidding
I can't deal with this reality
It is it is funny because Alex talk
Makes you feel like he's going down in this hedge maze you know where he's turning down this corner is like well
Nothing there something to go back around that
I put if you listen to the totality it's more like
We're in the Hedge maze
And he's just creating bulshit as you go along and you're trying to get to a conversation
And there's nowhere to go it's just amazed
Yep
That's about it
So Alex wants the the Hollywood respond
2 what's going on
Apologize in advance there's a slur and here are slur coming up
What are your friends out in Hollywood
Tell people are freaking out I mean
This approach
People assume that ever
Everybody of Middle East
Spell racial slurs
You hear it everywhere from also
I've been here in camel jockey
Stream radio
Sad
Lakes that border on
Definite slurs I would say that they are
Put Jordan terms for
Is a great euphemism for
F*** off work
So Alex so yeah if you really look at the Joey's criticizing
The media
Perhaps more so even than a large
Percentage of the media that I watch
I don't
There was not that much
Awesome
But not as much as you might expect
I think we need to Newcomb
That's what Alex said
Immediately
There was less of that except for that secretary
Got to kill someone
That was a outlier in math
So you were
You were like a why won't eat
And if you just wait a little while we would have gotten there alright and your theory might have been
Joe what about the
But you run by the German
The rolling out there
New currency
Globally
The dollar
You know everything is about
Currency speculation
Financial Center
Destroy the dollar
You think that this was Europe
Attacking America
The Destroyer
I know that in Davos Switzerland
They were going to be pretty
The dollar was going down
Fight going on
In the news an hour
Until we have any evidence
Everything else is just
Speculation
Joe my point is we have to
To ask
Who is behind
Responsible
Stream media there out there
I think that Joe is responses alright
You know cuz there is a
What are you talkin about clearly doesn't believe
Clearly doesn't agree and usually polite in the pushback
This is irresponsible speculation right
I don't think that that's the tip
Listen
We're already
The problem
Is that need to be solved
Happened way before we get to Joe giving anybody a lesson in ethics in journalism
I'm not going to complain about that you're something that I was surprised about I mean person I was surprised that you
Allen second I was
Surprise that was listening to this
I think
The Joe Rogan
At this point
Is who he thinks he is now
In 2001 Joe Rogan is
He's self-perception in 2022
Cuz he he can push back on our
Yeah if it doesn't go well
This interview
Goes bad
That's nice
On 911
That's
Boy all the joke
Then I won't make
It's really surreal to know what's about to like we're about to
To discuss and recognize that this is the evening of 9/11
Just
When we were doing our last episode of scenarios are so
Big
You know
Vas
The universe is you know yet you think about the pale blue dot
You Know Carl Sagan talking about the pale blue dot
Carl Sagan would be like f****** no way is Joe Rogan showed up on 9/11 what the f*** are we talkin about it
Shut up
About this
Telling everybody right now if Alex was doing his show in like
Pearl Harbor happened as Milton Berle on to tell him like Hey,
I'm down
South America what is wrong with you
Absurd
Alex
He's not like the,
Companies want to kill people
Joe pushes back on some stuff Alex
Cuz throwing out
It looks like
Playing outside
Well yeah well I'm
I mean I can't say I'm glad they did it but
Cost you a lot
Then I guess it was the right
I mean
Call Giselle
So I care about him
You don't know
I'll just tell you,
Cool because socialism is what
You know a lot of
Education
People want they want
Share Wellness
Scary
I think it's ridiculous
The ruthless
Dictatorship
In the newspaper
Yeah well
I've heard that
What was that yeah well I've heard from my own mouth many a Time
I guess if you were hinging
Your conspiracy and your rebuttal to my point is they called him Uncle Joe
Well
Okay
You're On Solid Ground moving on then
Yeah
I think that Joe
Appears to be far more capable of critical thinking is to be
Far more able to hold his own
He has a centered grounded position of a thought
He's not going
Be bullied by Alex into a being like what maybe it is the
Bu holyshit
I think that's the lesson we're learning don't get old everybody gets old windup sucking later on
I'm pretty sure even back then I would assume drugs
For thirty years is messages green maybe one of the drug
Bugsy did did it
We'll never know which you don't think so
How would you judge I mean we don't know if
Toad with
Again
It's not the same
Snorting totally awake until you like toad is not a culprit
Here
USA DMT
Now I don't want to say that either
Feel like he's got to have Donuts
Honda of Lake
Other weird things that no one's ever heard of like chemicals
A mental chemicals and stuff
I'm going to say it has nothing to do with drugs
Number one drug that would cause something like this is surrounding yourself with yes-men and people like
Alex Jones consistently reinforce your position regardless of whatever it is that you are saying
That's leading you down to a lazy thought pattern because you never have to try that's true
Cultivating a full of people who don't challenge
You in terms of staying
Not some kind of a critical path
I think this is
It's probably corrosive
If you'd just done drugs and not become famous I think he would be a better person
If people still made him own up to hosting The Man Show
Orbeez
Boy that's weird
Rogan
Is not play
Playing ball with Alec
Looks really bring up something that Joe can respond to and be like
I feel like
Why don't know about the Communist dick
Haters right there just some of these socialists ideas like
Medicare Social Security I do like he's like which I think they're f****** stupid but whatever those
Smart people does educational people does talking about like
Whatever that is
I was just realizing that like this is not going to work
So I'm going to have to Blindside him
And so he tries to with the Northwoods.
Scaccia
James Bamber
Performer 2020
On different Networks
You have a plan
Pretext
Chain and not Tom Bowman
This is Baltimore
New York Times
They wanted to quote casually listings numbers of dead in u.s. newspaper
How they wanted to blow up passenger airliner
Animo using Army
Dress-up is Cuba
As a pretext
How Kennedy
6 months later
His head
Sloppy joes
How you responded I do your web.
Read the stories and hear the clip
Well you know I've heard
Any million
Number of
Series on now
How Kennedy was assassinated
Now
I suspect
One of them out there is true
Why I suspect
The government probably had something
I do with it
As far as
But you're not even
The joint
Just got signed on to it
Sandwiches already realize that Joe is clearly not in favor of declaring that the globalist Dorothy you did 9/11
And I was just no argument
Had to make that they did season
He knows that Joe isn't a pushover in 2001 and that he has his own celebrity
Like the other guest has had on
On 911
That's Tuff
Because if he starts asking too many questions about why Alex believes the things he's saying or what
Poopy has bass Electro Bass
It might become clear that Alex is just make
Shut up
So Alex Goes On author
This clip is him putting Joe in a completely unfair and unwinnable so
Situation
He doesn't think the government necessarily did this in question to Alex's idea about a possible motive
Instead of arguing that point Alex throws operation
Jojo
Know about this document he's never read it so this conversation
Have to happen
Entirely on Alex's terms
Or not at all
Except so I can't have this conversation
The latter option
Is more responsible but also wasn't super productive in a radio interview setting
Plus if you know Alex you know he's not going to respect
Now you just going to have the conversation anyway
Alex's forcing Joe to engage with something he knows nothing about which
Supposedly proves that the government had plans approved to do it 911 back
The 60
So from an optic standpoint
Alex is making it Jose responsibility to debunked this document
Before they can even really begin
To talk about the actual Madrid
Which is impossible
Sometimes whenever moving the goalposts isn't going to work for you
What you have to do is switch to
To playing highlight
Right so you're like a football is really hard I'm not going to do that s***
Highlight is Buddy that old Thomas Jefferson quote figuring out the answer
That's when I change the question
Has great Thomas Jefferson
This is what I was doing is in essence the same thing he does in terms of using OKC is cover
For the 9/11 Pompeii
It's an attempt to force someone to complete
Need some other task before you get to the real issue that you're supposed to be talk
About
It's like Alex is an NPC in a video game sending you want to fetch quest in the middle of the main mission
What is a poorly designed game
So you kind of know that once you finish that side quest they're just going to send you on another
It's going to be a long time until you get to the main mix
To take a lot of patience
To have any actual conversation with Alex
Who's going to keep throwing out oh no I need an amulet if we're going to
Go into this right for right after the f***
Write the noise
You don't know what my Kennedy conspiracy theories
My conspiracy theory is this
You know
No no it's even worse
Oh boy
That is disseminated
Conspiracy theories
Because
They don't want people to know how easy it is to just
Murder the president
Like honestly if you look back in American history
There's been at least
Should have been murdered president
That were murdered
That's true
Twice
Two guns jammed in his face
Add blown off to Roosevelt Roosevelt
Gone Ronald Reagan
Out of here yeah those were those were not sophisticated plan do you do not need a sophisticated
You can just shoot them
There's a dude
Obviously it's not that it is not me
Complicated process
But you can hear you can hear it in Joe's voice to he's like
It is there so many things there so many moving Parts there's got to be a
Complicated
Plan behind it
It's got to be that Ocean's 11 Heist
And it can really just be a dude was out of those other ones were
For what it's worth I mean even the let me there was some planning in conspiracy involved in the lake
Assassination
Not like all we got to get Russia involved yeah
That is interesting
I mean I don't agree I don't believe your premise is actually doing interesting to think about how
There's an expectation that that has to be the most Byzantine thing
Thinks that it should be really really hard to assassinate the president of sell it if you look back in assassinations that worked and didn't
All you really need is the hotspot to try and maybe the chips will fall where they may
Well I'm going to need you to go on Rogan while we're at Austin and ask him about that.
I think that's a good one
So look
Alex
Can't handle this in
Alex has some thoughts about Hollywood
Then unfortunately Joe is in Holly
What does this do for our image
Oriented country what Acts
I don't think Hollywood ever
Should be in a position
The take Antioch
Chen's whatsoever
Hollywood is about Eric
Payment and making money
In Ohio Hollywood
Find prop things up at
A lot of federal money
Stop
Are they really
Hell yeah
Yeah exactly
All the free equipment
What to do in WhatsApp
Takeout
Highly doubt the army
Take out I think
They do probably
They can't have the army
Call Terry
You dinna
In a poor way
My God displayed
But
Give the money for them
It's also good
You have to realize
Watch a movie like Pearl Harbor where
The kids join the Navy and become Heroes
Kid
Might be just the push
Did they need
Get him into the armed service
Yeah I created
Glut of people 1
Playa 14
Where's my Top Gun
Yeah but Alex is arguing against his own point I'm confused as to why Alex thinks
Statistics a conversation he's having
Crumble lady tried to make a claim Rogan is like
Nada
Eczema
He's got a bag of candies at he's just throwing them at Joe Rogan like this one taste good
Good
Let's see if the media taste good
And what media is there for
Funny
Altars in anyway
Was that mean
Tiring attract
The people to work as news anchors
Aura
Using up the soundtrack or doing whatever the hell they have
This year
Before
Okay blocked onto it as a point of focus
And then suddenly
Ucbh
We are in Jaws
It's all about
Right now what it's worth
Is a Terrace
And whatever is work
That is working
Did you just say
Spell immediately
Agencies
You know any short that people get
Ridiculous
I know all the tea
People behind me shows
They don't care about
They want ratings
18 to 49
That's what'll be on
Yeah but you do Mad TV and Newsradio and host Fear Factor
The number one show in the mansion
Anchors
Your face but there
Group meetings that are now
Publicize
Calling for what
You like that
Well we know Ted Turner of the uni
Coming come on
Katana gives a lot of money
What Alex's
Not being able to handle like what are basically simple rebuttal
This is bad yeah this is an embarrassing show
Lizardman going like
Hey come on that doesn't make that much sense and
To mean to Joe cuz he is the host of one of the top rated
Did shows in the country
Yeah
It was a huge
This is weird to think back on that fit like
Yeah it was winning its time slot
Yellow people so they would eat Bugs Bunny everybody who is Ever making fun of like all the Petro
Rock fat is like man
Fear Factor is way worse than that s***
Yeah it was a phenomenon
But yeah like
I think that there's something really interesting going on here and that is the
Cuz Alex can't really fight with him all that much without risking
The Friendship of really famous guy
More important than gold
Yeah I can
These things out
Vicki supposed to say
It's like obvious way Alex has no rebuttal
For this
Hennything is
His arguments are flimsy and bad person he's making up these people who
Are controlling things and going to Bilderberg
This stuff
And because of that
You just have to give up on all these points
Keep arguing without revealing that he doesn't have a second step
Did this argue
Even really a first-set based on
He doesn't have
He doesn't have enough feet to step with
And it's really depressing I mean first of all
I know seeing Alex this this
Not great
But then seeing Joe this
Able
To navigate this territory and like obviously
He didn't ruin their friendship he was able to give voice to
Steve counterpoints to what Alex
Was saying and show a little frustration while he's doing it not let Alex just
Get away with whatever nonsense he saying
I think maybe part of that Dynamic is videos on Alex's show
Yeah
If he's on his own show
Do you want salad
Stupid
Don't get crazy I get it out
Really benefit
From Alex's
Oh man
I just don't know how you live
Today we're talking about it was 9/11
Correct
This is happening on that day
I don't know what that was that for a little bit
Are working today
Is such
Nothing to say
On 911
It's really weird because it's also in the context of that like why is everyone talking about shark attacks
Yeah it's a media it's applications for whatever
Wow that's a little different when there was Wyatt's tiny bit
Well I mean I feel like there would be a real you'd have to be
Really bizarrely disconnected from how humans work
In order to be like why is it talking about terrorist attacks today yeah that would have to be insane that would be an insane thing to do
Well Tara said text her what's driving money now is that understand
Critical of
People talking about sharks
I agree we kill more sharks and they kill us and they're better this one's different
Different Berry dip
So Alex really
If he knew what he was doing it all
He would just
Bail on talking about anything that has to do with the media or the entertainment industry
But he can't
For you the Roll-Up.
Message Department ride
Scripts for Law and Order
Undone
Wednesday
80 cm
PCMS
Admitted
Part B
Scripture Law and Order in order
New one
Why Law and Order
How about you
Can you do with keeping people in line
You know
Proceeding for the judge
Shabazz
Violation
I didn't write it
Would be more than happy to read it but
Do I read it
People who run television
Illinois Lottery
Who run
I know the guy who invented
Who Wants to Marry a multi
Chamillionaire and all these other crazy shows are on television
And despite what people think of the motor
Funny shows on
For you know what
Logic randeree velour
Reason
For evil reasons rather
These people
Why would ABC have anything to say about Law and Order being How It Was Written
On ABC ABC is trying to
Law & Order got a scoop on their NBC Rivals right about how they're letting
The government right there shows 8w
Good thinking about making Dick Wolf
The Attorney General
What he's what
What Rogan is not allowing for is the possibility that the government was writing the scripts because W had a pretty
Particular things that he liked Law and Order to do you know
Listen we find out now everyday more of what the queen is doing extra judicially
Jesus said he's influencing laws and s*** they're getting away with murdering animals on their ships doing all that white
I couldn't W be like Hey listen I want the next storyline for Law and Order to be I think that's
A reasonable thought
You're thinking it's the doj is making requests
Taylor entertainment for the president
Is do it being a nefarious just 100% a man going like
Law & Order the headline sound
More entertaining headlight cover
More power for less important ship you're not wrong
But yeah Jose I buy in that s***
Alex
Drawn to this topic
But he should avoid it I just
Stop
Evil
Girl putting
You know this is a guy walking by watch
The network
In a grander scale
It's variety shows
Reality shows
Whatever it is
Detergent
Charlie's crazy notion
Did the government
Do you know what using
Is ridiculous
I'm here
Deep inside the media
I Fear Factor
Okay but I'm telling you
I don't necessarily believe them
I have the new stories here
Maryland
TV tonight
Jamie to give up our Liberty
We should give up our liberties
TV tonight
The little bit I thought jarring because Alex needed to retreat to safer territory for him
Cuz I'm buying it has expertise and he's in those World Geography
If you being self-deprecating even with like
I know that that's my job that's why I have a show
Like it's interesting
Tell people they want to watch me yell at people
Atlantic help sell Prada
He's not disillusioned about like totally
Crass materialism
Explanation of what team
I hosted clubs for years that my job is to sell drink
And so
Like
Alex
Handle
He doesn't have enough
To go on
We transition over to safer territory which is like Avatar
Are you on CNN
Again we're in this situation where I can point that out and Alex can tell you like almost been on another Channel and we're back where
Where we started
It doesn't really matter though because this was just something Alex throughout the
The change of the sub
Realized he was losing this government controls the media stuff
And yeah
Who at whatever
Yeah Alex really isn't used to his quote-unquote experts
Using their expertise
Combat him
He doesn't appreciate he's like never know you're not supposed to act
Actually be an ex
I'm just calling
Okay you're the host of Fear Factor
I've been in these rules I've met these executives
The host of Fear Factor
So
Joe
Joe in Hollywood is it
About manipulating
Perception
Why are they so outraged
Play against the shack
Paddling Michigan
What do you mean
Good question, on all of them
Did you stop there
Control 24
47 turning your guys
Information Hollywood
Hollywood
Relationship
Like how Rosie
Perfect
You know why
A Hard Day's Work
Have a beer
Fair enough
All right yeah I love that moment Pharrell
Alex though
I love
When he's a victim idiot against the Second Amendment
We talkin about that's no example
You know how they're all day Outta control control with a second amendment hatred
Everytime I look at the TV I feel like they don't like the Second Amendment
Whenever there isn't
Two guns on screen Married With Children
Problem in less than 30 minutes via some sort of
Communication as opposed to a gunshot
Sandwiches losing ever
Circles around him with
Minimal effort
Really don't have to work that hard
No it's Alex really needs to basically discredit Joe by giving him a
Terrier motive
All I can say to all them
Smart guy
The New World Order
You're doing very well
Call sister
You know your show
Compared to all the
People drive to watch
This system
So there is this idea that he's within the system that you have to say what you have to
To say to keep your corporate overlords happy globalist
Hollywood System
Agreeing with me a hundred percent
That's really not fair
Why even have the conversation then
Like what's the point
What makes the roadrunner and Wile E coyote relationship interesting is that the Roadrunner is very very
Very fast
So
The coyotes attempts to attack at our
Scaled
Correctly
And that's the darkover complication is what makes the problem is right
You wouldn't watch the show if it was the Wylie Coyote
Versus turtle
I'm Turtle wasn't moving very fast
And Wylie Coyote still blew himself up
You know you could just
Step over
And grab the turn
You don't have to paint a whole extra Road on a
Brick wall you know you can just I would say that that Dynamic is part of why this isn't Elektra
Radio
For me in a way that a lot of these interviews are
Because you see Joe
Being His Highest self
Yeah sort of
I don't actually know if I can back that up there may be a better version of him somewhere
Represent yourself on Infowars
This is V best way to do it and if you're going to represent yourself as Joe Rogan
This is a good representation of him compared to every other version of him we've seen
Very very Joe Rogan e as opposed to more Alex Jones
So Alex just is going to just do whatever you can
Nonsense
What we're walking a very slippery slope
With trying
Protect ourselves
And you know trying to make sure the government
Take personal
Joe I agree with you
East Germany
Reese's go in I have
The photos of the video from the LA Times
They're firing
I mean that is not America
Uniforms in Black
Do you watch her
They were driving
Germany
No this happened
Lost Laura about it
The guy's house burning down
Capc
The shootout
Well I mean what are you saying
Military coup
No the police
Jelly Time
Black
Discriminate
Reese's
To go
They're in the neighborhood
Shooting up the wrong
Townhouses going
And then tried to frame
This guy they killed with
Well I I didn't read that I don't know what that stories about but
What does that have to do with
You know the government taking away our liberties by
By blowing up
Chocolate candy
When you do
The Black Eyed Peas
I'm not totally sure what this has to do with the larger topic or what that response even was but it makes sense confused by Al
Alex throwing this new story Into The Mix
Cuz it's the total non sequitur
Alex is also lying
About that situation that occurred in Santa Clarita
Please arrive to search the home of a guy named James
Alan Beck
Who was a felon that the authorities had learned from Neighbors who were worried
That he was
He can't do
And there were some reports that he was going around impersonating a police officer
From my way time
Deputy
Also nicknamed Jake Kardashian
Was among scores of officers
To flock to the scene
He was shot and killed within minutes of arriving
Alex's Dojo that the police shot their own officer and then frame back which was reported in the LA Times which is
Absolutely
And it's a necessary lie because if Alex discussed the situation at its real form
He wouldn't be so black-and-white and would become much harder for Alex
To use for stalking
Black open fire on the officers and killed the sheriff's deputy police returning fire
They were a bit unprepared for this turn of events
And shot a number of rounds into the adjoining house
So no one was
People whose house was shot in a suit and they were awarded $200,000
Daliso get some restitution
Through it all
Text continued shooting
Probably
Thousands of rounds
He had a huge cache of weapons firing at news helicopters it was just a huge mess
He shot at people for hours until the police tried to shoot a tear gas canister in which may have started
The fire
While the fire burned Beck
Continue firing his guns until the roof
Wow
Well there's criticism that can be made
Of the police and ATF
Response absolutely they
Preparedness
Vibrate
There probably is a sub license
Things to be learned in the post action
For sure
But because of
Who does Baseline similarity that the situation has to Waco conspiracy theorists latched onto the event is being the same thing all
He got a fair amount of news coverage but really wasn't that big of a story outside of this extreme right-wing media Circle
Alex
It's mostly just because they used it as a reminiscent thing of Waco
And that's why Joe has no idea what he's talking about but seems like a giant
I can see that discrepancy
So I said some positive things about Joe but
Time for that to go away I just don't necessarily agree with
His perspective
And we find out Iraq
What should we do
Absolutely positively without a doubt
I'm all for
Reading the world
Food and the United States
We can prove Beyond A Reasonable Doubt
Joe do you want to stay with us
What
So
I think that obviously
I get where he's coming from
He also earlier
Describe people being kind of warmonger eat
I don't know
I understand the
Feeling that there is a need for war based on a terrorist attack like
Like that
I understand I particularly that evening
I get it
I don't know if I agree
Fully because I don't think
Solve the
And you end up killing a ton more people
Civilians now if I understand correctly it's not
It doesn't seem productive are you trying to say that so far up to this point
War does not seem to have self problems
I would say
War
What is it good for even one step further then might you even be saying that for
It is war itself that led to Osama Bin Laden to committing these terrorist acts in the first place
Thereby meaning that if we were to start another War only
Guaranteeing that yet another Osama Bin Laden several years will come by and blow up something else are you saying that maybe this is a
Recycled that happens over and over and over again that people stupid is like Joe Rogan and
Good God
Did something like that
What is a good
Absolutely nothing
Say it again
So
JoJo you wasn't listening to Alex's show earlier
Because he
Critique something that I likes did earlier
Boy
I didn't know they were doing this and like
I'm sure you've heard that gel that
People call them
Cell phones
Hijacking
Box cutter coming
And now my comment
People like
Fight
Kennedy Airport
These pastors
Security
Tell them hey we're going to crash in the World Trade Center
Joe I mean
The courage of the
People on board
Situation like that
So you could judge
All of Joe Rogan
Criticisms about the media in response to Alex saying that the media is doing something
Are criticisms of Alex's memes
Far more extreme versions of it than Joseph probably seeing other place
Mentioning
Like Alex
Is
Definitely advocating for bombing a rockmore
Then early that's conversation that's come up a lot more
Hear that he has at this point on other anywhere else
Nobody else is even talking about Iraq yet well I mean included
I can hear you got to kill somebody I don't think anybody was on the Nations tip
Like let's have let's
Let's throw this on a f****** government it's weird it's weird to have Alex eventually become this guy
Who's like
Anti Iraq War
I know that become such a piece of his identity and he's
Really
Very much
Like
Maybe that's the garage if they did it
It does appear that the only
Only thing stopping Alex
From being the cause of all the things he complains about is that
He wasn't there to make the decision like
If he was there too
Complain about the Iraq War he was there to make the decision he would have bombed them
He can't complain about this if he was there to make the decision he would have done that well complain about the power grid because if he was there
Well I think you would have bombed Iraq if he could prove that they did it
But proving things means nothing to Alex are we go so I think
If you were in a position of power he could very easily prove whatever you wanted to prove
If it was
Speedy and towards whatever you want
Man that is almost
Word-for-word what someone did
So Joe doesn't want to see the UN
Take over the US courts
The great sure
Also Joe's
Dewar's are bad
BJ's credit
He doesn't seem like the concert
They're going to take whoever it is a from a Bin Laden or whoever it is
They're going to put them under the international criminal court and all the people in the United States of America are going to say
Oh isn't this wonderful
Now I've got a couple other 10 the criminal court is not allowed jewelry
You can't face your accuser
Double jeopardy
Install
30 years lot of trial
Do you support
Well I'm out
Support you know any
I don't support the Constitution
People
2%
Tax
Conceive the getting that high
There's a lot of things
They're in our constitution
People
We need a rule of law and
Republic
That tax thing isn't what I would have gone with as an example but the
The point stands
I mean you could have gone with slaves
Sherp
There's a recognition that the constitution is an imperfect document
That's for boating
Very very weird ears
You know what the Constitution.
Yeah that is
Yeah
So this next clip Jordan
Yeah it's a bit
This is a three-minute clip that's not good
They get into it
Interested
I got to say
I admire Rogan
For being able to
To have this conversation
I do not admire him for doing it on 911 really am struggling again with this
Okay I'm fine I'm
I'm just I'm removing the fact that it's 9:11 on the day from my you should try I can engage with this as
With the understanding to get through it otherwise
We're having a spirit
Debate tonight
Joe is not
Depending a new world order
Heelys
Tell because he's not here everyday Joe
Covering
Got you and I know you're my friend and I love you and everything
Do
A lot of discharge
You do yourself a disservice
You're absolutely positive about that
I think by saying that you know the answer to everything
You make the whole notion ridiculous
Aggressive
Is a lot of disinformation by our own government by the media
Answer to okay
What are the only place
Is
Hella proud argument
LeapPad gel I'm here to tell you
You right now
He is
Quads more narrow
Receptors
Allen cocaine
70%
Does 50 hits
She's very damaged
Open children
And I've had the neuro
Scientist
The cover it
I read about how they're putting cancer virus
Vaccine
Across-the-board
Why cancer
Is exploding
I'm going right down the line on all of the
Nausea
Sit there and say I
Answers
I don't drunk
Why do SWAT teams
People's houses
Out of the military
Superdrug
Send
Magazine
I've interviewed former
CIA officer
Oklahoma City
Bring me unexploded bombs out of the building
Former head of airport
Nadia
How far we slip down into it
So you're telling me I'm doing a disservice and it's not true
I think you're doing yourself
YouTube
I think you are
I think you're really really confident guy and you got a lot of
Someone who will
I agree with you on that
I agree with you
When you have proof
I think everybody admires that I think it's a fantastic
When I think
Is when I think you use something is based on speculation
You to use something that
May or may not be
Beetroot you stated
Absolute
But any intelligent person listening
It's all booked this is a pretty
Gay evening
Critique of Alex
I also think it's too generous
Yeah that that like I think you take things that are speculative and you act like
You're convinced of
Yeah that is
A pretty
Deep cut
Because I
Think it's very active
It's 100
But the problem that I have is when you limited to speculation
And things that you are fully convinced of because he's
Bring up lying and making things I was going to say
Joe
Who is is doing him a disservice
Because
He's not acknowledging Alex's
Greatest Talent
Which is lying on command about anything anytime
For no reason
Or whatever he's rattling off a bus
Topix
Absolutely all over the place early
Organize them a debunked
Do the things you do this for me in order to
Substantiate your claim
That he
Is convinced
Things that are fully proven or whatever
But he's thrown out
It's like
Alright man
Buena Vista
It's it's child
It's a way of arguing that
Is like
It is the way that people who don't want to do homework argue
In a group project
Where you're the person who does all the work you know
It's like
Everything that they do is just saying a bunch of s*** at you
And you're like God damn it now I have to learn about this
Now I have to learn about that have to learn about this not to learn about this man
And he's not learning
Anyting
It's all on you
So Alex
Brings up like some of the
Books
And what have you and broken is really convinced
Book sources cuz I look sometimes
Dumb
I've read more than one who brings up one Dumb Book
Behold the pale white horse
Information
The government's having alien bases on the Dark Side of the Moon
There's a lot of books like
70% of our land
October 8th
They took over 7
United States land mass
Yes
In what way where how did it take over
Infowars.com
Interview
Congressman Ron Paul they signed over the country to the UN sir
And the national bar
Chicago
Tribune agrees
Okay
That's why it's so unfair to have a conversation like this with somebody on a radio show
She's not at all talking to you at all not even a little bit hear what you have to say is a meaningless what he's doing is
Posturing for the listeners fostering and then at the
But he's being a very unsuccessful
If you're paying attention
He's also just trying to throw you off absolutely throwing out these things all over the
Play
Possibly have any idea what he's talking about
2 + t.r.u.
You look less grounded in the criticisms that you're my
If you are Rogan
It's basically like you're having an argument with someone you're talking about I don't know
Interest rates and then there are actually little people
What
Sure
Did you know the UN has 70 70 70% of Americas
Fine
No they are getting rid of juries
Yes I only no response
SoJO tries to just reprimand Alex for like
Being an a****** well his inability to accept that there are things
He doesn't know
He does have that ability
I meant Alex does with you expect
The e x like a little baby
We didn't
That's why this is happening regardless
We don't know who it is
All we all heard it was
Initial reports they were looking
For Islamic fundamentalist Terror
Oklahoma Joe's
Everything
You even said yourself
Stock market
So we don't know yet
Map directions
I guess I don't know anything I'll just
We don't know who
But she's going
Hi Samantha you and I never gonna be alright
F*** you Jesus Christ
Iceman
Not saying that
What does the worst
The worst person
Listen to talk to
Just the worst sojo's making a fine point and bring
Backup do you like
Why do you sing the terrorist attack is the result was not punishing other terrorists in the past
When first of all you think all of those past terrorist events are fake
Exactly
Maybe you did this to Despicable I speak to roll up a gyro correct
What the f*** are you talking about you're on your way there if you don't know things and that's okay today
Let's give up our freedom
How about that
What I want to do is never come back here again
That's great what a prick only Joe it's Dave mad at Alex prayers everyday since 9/11
Call Josh
Sneakers
That was
Jose 9/11
There was an opportunity
SoJO leaves
Don't leave on terrible terms another still fully expect but there's definitely between
Did not see eye-to-eye
Emotional day but apparently heard neither of these guys is it is
Grogan was given definitely a good bit of
Recognition of the
The loss of the tragedy I may not have
Got those clips
As much
I think it's more interesting bit
Did they have this fight tonight 11th 911
I just
Don't
Understand
Everytime I come back to the thought like oh then you know what we do and have done for a long time
Surprise
Joe Rogan and Alex Jones got into a fight on 9/11
You know how we've done this thing for five years
And the only thing that I could say that would really make you go
That's probably not ever possible
Is Joe Rogan and
Alex Jones got into a fight on 911 I think that's one of the one of the wonders of
This of this
Space space whatever it is that Alex's doing it's like
You can do 700 episodes of this and still be like what
No
I want to scream
So
Predictably
Yes and now I have access to take
Control at Meredith
You know I sit there and I watched
And it's the same thing with our
Neurotic
Military
Bought a good day
Number one TV host
Play just can't
Can't face the system
Dinner with Joanne steps
Take later
Hosting live right now
Website
I know you don't totally believe all the
Come on tell me
He just he agrees with a lot of them
Play just can't go all the way I'm at
A problem
Damn and you just can't face
It's not man enough
Two-faced things the way that I do
What could you buy
Possibly get
Out of a relationship
Ship with a person like Alex
That justifies
Everything that he's done
I mean look I used in college
I used to hang out with some people that maybe
They were a little bit annoying but they usually had weed
Maybe that's what
What's going on you didn't have that they came to you for
And then you were like
You're my best friend
Yeah I don't know I mean
What is
Like
Imagine
The Alex is like
In like interpersonally so generous
And caring
And like
Gives you the perfect birthday gift every year like I can't imagine what it is that would
Make somebody
What's up with this s*** if Alex had like
Pulled him from the bottom of a lake
While he was
Drowning
I would say you get a couple of years out of the actuary
6 1/2 year old Lake
25 years of friendship
What happened
I think Joe probably stopped listening after he got off
Didn't hear Alex talkingshit
Cannot listen to Al
Blissfully unaware of anything that Alex does for a living
Must be that has to be almost I think
Baby there's a contract
They signed Bowman Alex started doing the show
Don't ever listen
Don't ask me any questions about it and work day Joe our relationship is successful because you have just created an
Image of what I do in your head face reality
You imagine if
Alex had come back with Joe you do yourself a disservice
Creating the people around you
Giving them a higher sense of
Value towards yourself and generosity from their spirit
Yeah who's doing a disservice now a******
To threaten to cut you like a pig
Phoenix children
We're going to have a psychically abusive or 25 years
Crazy
Very sad
Alex more calls
Used about that Rogan appearance
Call Kevin Booth my body and talk
Call man said I want to come on this guy's
Number one
What's on television
I say we're friends
Jojo
The show
He just can't believe all
He believes a lot of
The best killed
Kennedy
Stuff like that you just can't go all the way
He doesn't want to admit that
Picturesque
Hollywood Life
Jeopardy he's a coward he doesn't want to give up the
Trappings of Fame in the glitz and glamour of
Hollywood
If you wants to hold on to that
What
I mean
Angels mine
Does he think
That Alex
Is criticizing him in the same way that Joe is criticizing
Alex
When he says
Your pie
Relying on conjecture and b*******
Like this Jose
Take that is like a legitimate
Criticism
Cuz that's a f****** dirty insults
Horrible a personal attack on you
Essentially it's saying your character is such
What's that you value
Material and selfish
Pleasures over saving the world
Joe's a nice guy but he's a rich prick like that's what you're saying
How is that not a defensive thing to hear
He knows a lot of stuff
Amy probably has a suspicion that
What I'm saying is totally true
But
I mean Tiffany even then
You're reading your
In your conspiracies
The top executives
Are the people doing the thing and we know that Joe Knows those people now you are saying that he
He's too much of a coward to stand up to them why aren't you just taking the step and going
He's part of the system he doesn't listen to all because he'll talk to her
Years he'll be right there almost ready
Over the over the board and save the devil
Running things and we have to have a holy war
So we have one last clip here and
I think this is a good example of Alex
Doing eggs
Exactly what Joe criticized
10-4
Dodge do we have Liberty
Society
Now we're not about to give it all up
We're going to strike back whoever did it
Hello as I think we know who did it don't we
The New World Order
I think we know who did it
98% certain it's the New World Order EU Iran Iraq
Whatever Germany
One-hundred-percent certain it's the new world order
Wild
So what a day
Wow
What
F******
I don't think there's any way you could
Necessarily expect
I think
Content-wise
The morning show was
Wacky
Yeah and all over the place
I meant this
Was something
I just
You know
You can take
The day off
Can't you take the evening off you already did a show
You can do it yeah you can just
You can just say no
Do you have a choice
There's no need for you to do another 3 hours if
An hour plus of it is going to be arguing with
Joe Rogan
This is disrespectful
This is disrespectful it really is happened by myself if they made this like
10 years later as a hey what would it be like if we did a show on 9/11
Disrespectful things
To do
Oh man go Boston go New York that's what it's
Jesus Christ I mean the Mind reels and
I really have anything to say I think he's episodes speak for themselves
I think that like as much criticism as you may give the media which is deserved
A lot of it is very deserve for sure
Nobody did a worse job than Alex
Alex
Completely with
Lyft on every count
I wish
He's 9/11 coverage
This sucked
It was disrespectful it was
Was disgusting
The way he focused
Largely on the
Grotesque images of Bernie
Bodies and people jumping
And himself
On the way
Essentially called
The people who died in the plains coward or not taking back over
Jesus I'd just abhorrent
Behavior All Around
The
Value I think
Think of Watch
This and seeing this
He's but you do see a very
Concrete example of the beginning of that
The bombs in the building narrative you see what it's based on
You see it the friend
Who becomes a world-class structural engineer
Ucv Chicago
Tribune article that's being lied about it
You see this
Apocryphal local news story that he heard a local radio host talking about right
Then in you see these
Pieces these disparate pieces coming together
That you know five years later are going
To be presented
Not as what they are
Like
The world's top
Structural engineer came on and gave me an
A schematic
A breakdown with all of the equations about how this was impossible
They did that Chemical Testing
You know all of this in
Yeah it's
It's going to
Use what Alex's conspiracies are
Core
This is what they are
It was all there in the beginning
There wasn't anything there to begin
It's
A whim
Yeah the most
Real thing is probably Alex and Joe fighting
I mean yeah
Yeah that's the only thing that it felt like Alex actually gave a genuine s*** about
Being threatened
Reality
Yeah I was not being
The person who's who's the
The smartest person on the on the show
Wow
Jordan yes Dan this is been a ride
F****** rollercoaster my friend
But will be back indeed we will for another episode at a later date
Cameo I'm Leo I
Ndzi
I'm
Dairy
Brownfield
That's it Brownfield
What the sex robot
Holding
Alexandra Thurston color