Jordan
Knowledge fight
MoneyGram
Alex
Acknowledge fight.com
I love you
So folks big big developments
India in the world of Alex Jones
This is a bizarre way to start the show but here here's the reality
I'm sitting here and I'm recording this
With no Jordan
I am
H mere hours away from getting on a plane and flying to Austin Texas
Where me and Jordan will be enjoying enjoying seems to
Make it sound like fun we will be
Participating in and observing
The
The trial that Alex Jones is going to be going through
But unfortunately I can't take any time off because
What happens here
What happened to your on Saturday
But does Steve Bannon release a f****** episode of his war room show where interviews Alex
In order to promote his stupid documentary
Alex's War
That's all I feel like I've got to talk about it but there's no Jordan
It just leaves me to think
Where have all the good men gone and where are all the gods
Where's the StreetWise Hercules
Isn't there a White Knight
Hope all the fiery feed
Play the night I toss and turn. I need I need a hero
What is this
Discover heaven
Robert Evans
Wow magically to life
By the power of music
By the power of Pat Benatar apparently Benatar mistakenly thought with the one who
Did the song but I told you to sing it and Pat Benatar style anyway
And here we are here I am
Summon
Well thank you thank you for answering the call
Of the Bonnie Tyler call for a Hero
I appreciate it we're going to be sitting here we can talk a little bit about Steve Bannon having Alex on
I understand you you covered Bannon a little bit in the past yes
As he was known in the krassensteins children book children's book
Because he was a squirrel that lifted Donald Trump's hair
Those guys were so created an American that was
Yeah
That's really what cancel culture took from us
This
We lost we lost the krassensteins
And life has not been worth living for a single second
Nature has not healed
Are they active improved social
Do we know if they're on the other they must be I can't imagine is given
If I were Trump I would
I would definitely I'd give them a verified account
Great for him
If I were Trump I would make them collectively my vice president
Absolutely
So beat you give me he sucks we can all agree on this right I mean
I don't like him
And look here's the top because one of the things I hate most
Right we can all agree
On team trying to be better people that it's not
Not good to make fun of
Somebody for their appearance when there's so many things that have nothing to do with therapy
But
Looks like something a British /
He looks boiled
He looks like one of those
Unsettling puddings that the bridge blood sausage I'm not a good enough person not to comment
It looks like it like a half English breakfasts
Yes exactly he looks like a blood sausage
In some sort of blumaan
Dina's
Coalesced into a baby
And unfortunately
It also happened that he was like
The person who had access to the most money in the deepest understanding
Of what the internet had changed about human social interactions
Circa 2000
14 ish
And he made a lot of Haywood
Plugged into other folks who could do something with
Do you know that sucks
He's very smart
He gets
You can find
Packers won this
This week from Christianity
The day that
Largely silly but makes a good point of highlighting the thing about banning that
That's important
The understanding he came
To about
The fantasy
World
People like to live in and there's a bit he goes on where he's like
You imagine this guy Bob
Who's the f****** account
Bob.
You know some f****** mortician has to make out or whatever
Funeral regrets make up a 5 minute
Funeral
But imagine like
Online Bob's got this
Big digital presence in My World of Warcraft or something
This great warrior
1000 people show up in the internet tax
We like
Celebrations his heroic Deeds at all this
What would rub Bob
Identify more as what identity is more real than anything
Banning came to aesthetic
You can provide people with these kind of like
Provide people with an outlet for their fantasies that allowed
To feel like
Whatever
Weird little communities
Fantastic
It worlds that got involved with online are impacting the real world
Do you like make them
If you can make them feel like what they're doing online matters
You can build them
A chance to feel like a hero
Through doing nothing but sitting at their computer
You can actually get quite a lot done
And I'm not I'm not explaining it super Wild
Bannon
Translated that into gamergate
It sounds like he could just be studying a lot of Alex's s*** to I mean like convincing the entire audience
That look they're just their fealty to him and
And I was supporting it show
Is a fight against
This established
Ben Powers
There's a lot of white van in gotha
It's just old fascism right like that whole thing is is pretty old-fashioned them
What Bannon
Did that was
Clever
Was well.
Berry effect
Probably too
Sitting on your ass and like harassing
People over the internet
Like that was the thing that he
You figured out kind of be gamification
Of like
Fascist
Militant
In a way that that
He was the first person to really lock it down
And it is never it is always been to his benefit a potent force in American politics
Well
That sucks
Otherwise I would have
Describe it a little better but you get the point
Yeah I think it's a during covid brain you did a fantastic job
I'm too I heard that Alex was on
Abandoned show
And I almost fell out of my chair
I didn't mean that
What's your immediate response to hearing that I mean other than like foreboding
Did it seem weird
If like
If I had the power to
Prey in an air
That's that would have been the spot
Well you're never going to get them cuz they're in that pandemic War Room bunker
You have to assume you need one of those
Does bunker Busters
Fox informed me about when we were going out
Saddam
Yeah I've never listen to Bandon show because
I don't I don't have time or the emotional energy
But I did I listen to this episode and I was shocked
That they're like
Their theme music is kind of
It's got a little bit of a rat
Flair to it
And it's about how like
We're going to take out the cccp and
We're going to be there until everyone's dead
It's a pretty bizarre vibe that they got going on
Apparently
If you go by the theme song it's mostly about hating China but that is not what I took away from from this
The screening
Best viewing
So Alex is on
And
It's the it's it's really bizarre
Because
These two
I don't know if I've ever heard of them
Interact
Huge figures in Trump World
And I have some awareness of some beef
A witch make this
Just seem even more unlikely
I'm so I was really excited to tune in and see what we would find
And turns out I think a lot of it is a press tour
For Alec that documentary Alex's War
It's going to be coming out
I don't know if you watched any of the
I've seen the ads for it I don't like the
Bad and who again I think has a
A pretty canny understanding of like
What's a product
Road to go down propaganda lies I don't like that he sees turning Alex into a college celeb
Money in Thai
Yeah and it's it's it's either something bad about the moment right now or a sign of
Desperation between
The both of them
That's kind of how I'm
I'm seeing the ball breaking one of those Direct
Desperado be asleep there is some reason to Hope
Like I don't want to be all doom are here
Because like
Banda MS
Actually might do sometime
In the very near future
Just got convicted this week as we record this
On two counts
F****** around with Congress both of which
Prison for up to a year
And
Then
You've got like
Alex who is in the finding out stage of all of his
Court cases so sure
I feel like they're their circumstances of
Pure desperate enough that it's like let's see what we can do
You have a little bit of juice I got a little bit of juice let's make a cocktail
Or something
I don't know that I I have
Yeah
I wish I had more hope
That it was
This was like
The dying gasp of a wounded animal rather than
The step one in the eventually seeing billboards with Alex's face on them in Times Square
Yeah that is that is worrisome because you have something of a brand rehabilitation in some
What's going on
You know you have
If documentary
It's seeking to obviously in some way whitewash a lot of Alex's
Quote-unquote mistake
He's made in his career
And you have Bannon who like
As much of a
Fringe figure if he is
He is on a lot more radio stations
Then
Did you expect
Cuz he's indicated with that like America's Voice or
Whatever the
That thing is called
They've grown substantially
In the
Yeah and Glenn Greenwald was hosting that question and answer thing or earlier today about
Via about Alex's documentary
There's there's a lot of fear I don't think billboard in Times Square but you know something
Yeah that's not great
So let's jump in here I want to play this first clip for you this is this is the here where band
Bringing Alex Indie setting
Table
About that about his feelings for the center
John's crazy socks
Conspiracy theory guy's a nut case you got the grants and all that
What they miss
Is it this guy's ahead of the curb
So many different top
Of signal.not noise
He's one of the the the
The really the leader
In describing with transhuman
Ism
Is it
Dangerous and what's
So that there's a there's a code that goes through a bit of this
Episode
Signal not noise
Which seems like just kind of the Weasley way to say like he's wrong about everything if you listen you is going to be constantly
Wrong about stuff
But if you look at the big
Big picture you could kind of
Yeah
I guess that is an interesting way of like
Bannon's phrasing of the Alex Jones
Was right kinda
Yeah it's it's signal is right there's a lot of static
You know you throw around a lot of bulshit
We wrong about everything but
Yeah yeah yeah
You can trick yourself into thinking that he knows things
He's right about the time
And then at the end you can hear him bring up the transhumanism and that's because I think that banning just one
Wants to be like
Alright
Look there's a lot b*******
There's a lot of dumb stuff but Alex has been saying that they're going to put robots inside you
For twenty years
Which I guess is fair
I mean that is going to do the mark of the beast the chipping of people and stuff is a that's like the safest
Big scale future prediction to make though is that like they're going to start putting robot parts
Course they are
Like yeah. They is in like
People are going to like increasingly do more body modification
Like we have throughout history
Yeah people are already doing that like themselves there's DIY
Stop I have a chip in my hand that has a business card on
Like it's just a thing people do cuz
Meet and they're bored
Yeah some people put magnets in their fingers
I don't write you can use his hand to open the electronic locked his front door
Wow there are people who do it if it's not the government that's doing it
But it is it isn't it
It's a trend that could progress into like
Some kind of a like
Robot arms
Or something or it might not
Who knows
4 years
An app forever
Science fiction writers they did they write about like
You know these these questions of what does it mean to be human
And obviously this is going to be fertile territory for it
So confusing theorists TalkBack
It's safe
And that's that's why Bannon wants to
Like really Center thing
Is there
I think that's a good move on
I think it's smart
To do that instead of
Stupid s***
About
The EU doing 9/11
Well that I do
You think that was EU
Yep yep yep yep
Bournout
A lot of people don't know this but Osama Bin Laden and Angela Merkel
Same person
Whoa I've never seen them together
That is true
And you know I have this baby
Exactly right
I was thinking about like if I could
Feed Glenn Greenwald one question to ask
Amad q-and-a session
It would be
Who is the head of the EU right now and what is their position called
I bet he couldn't name
Even swap it out with a um
Who's in charge of the um and once had positioned called
That's always like the actual thing if you were if you really cared about interviewing Alex is like a credible journalist
Ask him a basic question
About like fundamental facts
Reality
Like
Who is running like
How does the how does the eu's like economic system actually work like who makes dislike our decisions like voted on
Ron and stuff
You know
Any any kind of like very basic reality question he's just not going to be able to answer
Doesn't understand any of
Like it we can rattle off
Facts about like
The year that something happened or like the name of some document but anything past that
If he was a smarter propaganda
But there's also two little facts
Ticket learn that can make him better at that like the fact that like a big chunk of the eu's economic Administration
Is done in the building in Berlin
For the luftwaffe
Hermann Goering Sophos
It's the Germans keep repurposed
If you wanted to make a conspiracy out of that
And he knew like three facts
It's about the EU he could actually put something together but he doesn't
Dammit Robert this is going to be on his show in a week
If it's too good
I'll just trying to help the man out he seems to be having a rough one
It's it is tough times
Shannon plays the book the trailer
For Alex's documentary
A number of times
And there was one little clip that stuck out to me
Emma play that here real quick
Alex Jones said the Sandy Hook shooting was claimed the lives of
20 children was fake
Did the New York Times get in trouble
For consciously lying about wmds then led to a war killed tens of thousands in Conflict now
I think he's playing a little fast and loose
I with details about that cuz for one I don't know if it's fair or necessarily to say that the New York Times
Pause the Iraq War
I think the whole argument is that they like Bush Administration was planning to do any of it like
You know they belong predated
Maybe some sloppy reporting by the New York Times help justify it certainly was
Made it easier for them did not
But I think it'd be fair to say did not use the kind of journalist
Gregor they should have
But you know who else didn't use the kind of journalist
Regulation of the Iraq War
Glenn Greenwald
Who support
I would have Alex I would feed him a question to ask Greenwald about that
Yeah and also the New York Times in 2004 issued like a huge apology about their car
Calvary
Judith Miller was the
The main
Person who's making the most
You know high-profile
Errors with c
And she got forced out of the paper in 2005
And
As she work
In any meaningful way in journalism son
There are consequences for these folks just Alex doesn't care
He doesn't know
And
He just makes things up
They were reporting portal
She makes things up
Little bit of a difference
It is there is a difference between like
I don't know
Yeah yeah there's a difference I guess when you when you start to
Compare the consequences the size and relative influence
The New York Times makes me
Thank you could probably argue that their failure in the Iraq War
Did more damage than a lot of the stuff Alex
Pakistan
I think you definitely could in terms of scale for sure it's a different point
But I think that's fair
When you try and get yourself off the hook for your behaviors by being like well I didn't cause a war
I don't know if that's meaningful
I don't I don't know
Still bad
Savannah gets around to introducing Alex here
And
Here here
Get here was
What I thought was going to be like the beginning of a really exciting in her
Alex thank you very much
About this movie
A great filmmaker made the
This you're interviewed for
But other than that
It's their film
It is
Documentary Robert Mueller
These tablets were they always lie
But I've seen some horror films in
A bad light
An Android lockers I mean a real person just like you
But it's hard to come on here Steve
It's hard to come on here Steve
That's exciting line
Now
The reason that was really exciting for me was because I know that Alex
Heat Steve
I am sure he's he's repeatedly as I've learned through your show at active
Deaf
Almost constantly
For years he's a scapegoat that I went to his used to like try and get Trump off the hook for things
It's all I got really excited and I decided that I would put together a compilation
Of Alex talkingshit about Steve Bannon
I heard Manning was Forrest Gump for leaving but I didn't want to put out Rumors by to get that from the White House tours
Now the president
I was on your show a couple of months ago and I said that
Steve Bannon
What's a complete sociopath
And eventually he would
Trapping cell
It is lies
And it's collusions with his colleagues
I am for the indictment conviction and prison
Steve Bannon
The reason is very simple
10 in is what we call a self-promoter
A nicer term or a different term would be a BS artist
He just sits there and it sits back and watches
Is it a blow-up Lighthouse political
Likes of you
Watch Opposite distance
Outside know it's dandruff
Ketchup stains
Illuminati with money after he died
The Godfather Liberty Movement
CBS and running around Minato the FBI
Fawning and agreeing
With the Russia investigation
I've taken over the light and Steve Bannon
New problems but they don't surprise me
Because we know definitively
Contradicted his testimony at my trial
Our work and which is great
Adopted by Banning Banning didn't come up with all this
Movie screenplay writer
Okay they wrote a screenplay off the show
Telesto pissed they got all the phones tapped they know
I'll still listen everyday
Okay
I don't know if you know this but this is first-hand from the people involved
Steve is working with Mike cernovich and Jack Pacific now
I know people who were working directly with them
And they told me their goal was to destroy
You
Steve Bannon
Trader
I don't like Steven man and he's done some nasty stuff you bear false witness
Rodger Stone
Hindsight is 20/20
I can say is this
Michelle Damn back
Sociopaths and Psychopaths
And
Weak people that have been abused themselves they got do it to other things but they're they're owed something
That's really what it is
I think band is kind of one of those want to show everybody that he's the big man
He's the top guy he's the leader he's in control
Overthrow everybody around him so he can feel like
Hawaii
Yep so I mean it's pretty consistent
I hope he does his Steve Bannon voice in this interview
What's
I hope he asks him about that plot to destroy Alex that the Paseo bacon crnkovich were working on the fan
Frank talk about Steve Bannon Plata
Destroyer
Sure orders effects chatting after a football's game
Or what about by Steve Bannon perjuring himself in order to get Rodger Stone locked up
They said that's definitively that the in Infowars lore
Steve Bannon lied
Rodger Stone
Yeah but given how much money Stone was costing Infowars are we sure Alex thinks that's a bad thing
I mean if the North Korean boats story headstock
I think Alex would want to see Rodger silenced in some way
Taken taken
Him to prison
Also I love the idea I was going back through some of these banding clip I didn't realize that Alex had suggested that he
He was a sociopath
Who had been abused
That was why he was on this Power Trip
Particularly
Flare the empanada
Alex
Yeah yeah
I agree
So when I heard him say it's hard to come on
I was hoping like
Alright
We're going to air it out this is going to be great
Years he's hated Bannon
But of course
Aegis
Precedes
The kiss bannon's ass
In a way that is
Just embarrassing
I think if you listen to the end of this clip
You'll hear Steve Bannon himself being embarrassed by Alex's behave
But it's hard to come on here Steve
David margiotti was a brain
Able to do and you've had the most courage
I'm anybody out there
Standing up to the January 6th Broad and Everly
Bring America back
It's hard to come on your show
And and then talk about myself Heritage surreal
With
What you did not backing out of the committee
Add
Them and their kangaroo court and how they wouldn't let you cross-examine people
I'm patient 3-ring lawsuits run by democrats
Baymont in Travis County that
Rick Perry and Tom DeLay
That I'm not allowed to say I'm innocent at my trial next week that starts
You cannot say you're innocent
You cannot say it's rigged
And you can I mean it's insane
I'm posed to sit there and not talking and not say I'm innocent
This is the end of America so they can destroy Steve Bannon
Alex Jones they can destroy you so I'm just
I'm not gushing here
I'm gushing because
Literally we are in the arena
And I
And you would have greater love I got to say they are so scared of you
And an admirer of your work
And I have going to really really push people in a taxi and stuff to tonight
Because they're wrong and when they do they're buying into the global propaganda
So I am really
This is a big bucket list being on your show and I'm I'm so proud of the fact that exploded
Everybody talks about I'm at the grocery store I'm at church
Everywhere
Almost everyday
I really love your style of Steve Bannon did you see this you see that I don't get like envious I feel good while going to sleep at night
Next week least ybanez out there
Can you put together
But here is the reason I want to have you honestly felt but the films of Powerhouse
House film
That's that's you know you spent
2 minutes talking about like how
It's your dream to talk to this person and they're your hero
And then they just sort of like
You talk about your film
That hurts a little right
I mean
It's not that what you want
So what you think about what you think about this turnaround
Well I mean it it seems like the thing Alex always does
Which is that he's capable of having a wide variety of opinions largely negative
About other people who are prominent
Until those people are willing to talk with him for 30 seconds
At which point they become his favorite person
It's like what
It's how we can go from threatening Joe Rogan's children
To talking about how he's leading the
The the
I don't know whatever the the
Devolution
The human mind
Your second only to Tucker
I never friend
It is I he hasn't done that with Tucker though right
I'm going to guess that like
Cuz obviously he's got back
Danforth on Rogan basically everybody
Has he ever said bad s*** about Tucker
Yeah back in the day back when he was like more of a neocon bowtie guy for sure
Kind of
Crossfire days Alex heads
Until like it didn't come up often but I know that there was
A little bit of distain between them
Tucker dude like
You came on Infowars once or twice and it wasn't like super hostel
But it definitely was not like
This guy gets it
He knows everything it was more like
Alright I'm going to talk to this neocon for a little bit
I will see if we can get it to wake up
MN
He wouldn't show back up
But yeah I know I think Alex knows better than to threaten
Tucker
Tucker's way
Way more of a hold of the you like
Weird
Trump is like guys
Yeah
Well I also think he's
Kind of
Scared of Tucker
Like most
Then maybe meme
Reading some
What do you think he's scared of Tucker doing
Like
Labeling of a globalist
Yeah I mean I think he's definitely I think he's definitely aware that Tucker could
Could do damage to him
But I also think more than anything he's scared the Tucker
Chris going to render him
Whitney irrelevant
True I see kind of I feel like there's a little desperation
And how he praises
Tucker
That makes sense
I mean you know the man better than I do
But that's that's
That's just kind of what I
Yeah I think so I mean as much desperation as there is an
I go to sleep at night comfortable knowing that if I go to jail Steve Bannon is out there
You know it's
There's desperation all around
And some of it is
Like a recognition of being able to siphon publicity
And then yet some of it is
Probably in
Recognition of his
Is obsolescence
How do you spell obsolete since the internet
Really picked up as much as
The dead like
YouTube
Largely
Hindered his his Stranglehold on
My gatekeeping
Conspiracies
Tucker gets to the
To the the old folk
Says things
Really
Softly he brings extremism into a a
A digestible paragraph
He's just actually better at doing Alec ship than Alex ever
What you make City makes it easier to swallow
Did you hear from like all the the Nazi types
Andover like Tucker
It's just doing our s*** better
You hear that
And not message boards
From time to time
So
Here's Steve Bannon embarrassing himself severely
The point I don't think
People get about
We do it the worm and I person
Because I followed you
4 years
Is that
You're not just a man of Ash
Actually
The guy that sell Turbo
Saying hey
You know I'm liking the first tank
And we'll drive this
As
Much in his importance that leadership
The true
Thing that you've done
Which is
Stunning
If you look at the evidence of that in the facts
You are one of the Great
Thinkers
That is very where you got to go back
The Revolutionary
Regeneration
Yeah man
Alex is one of the great thinkers
Of our time
Politically
Culturally
Spiritually
Musically
You've got me Randa rannigan man
Oh no
Found a pretty dope cover of Hungry Like the Wolf by Reel Big Fish the other day with love now he's at on a
I will I will cut it in
Splice it together for you
Is that new
That Reel Big Fish cover
But it's it's axilla
You can find it on on the YouTube sin the Spotify
Where they just became basically like a cover band
I mean I have not
Caught up I don't know when they'll most recent of their albums was but they've definitely got a lot of covers
I mean that's guidance that is the natural journey of every great Scott
Yeah
Because the secret of music
That that's like at the core of
Of all the FEMA creation
Is that every song is better as a stop
Yeah everything is better with butter
Streetlight Manifesto to the cover of Such Great Heights that is
Very very fun
Mommy like Less Than Jake became a cover band
In fiery Reel Big Fish has become a cover band
Like Me First and the Gimme Gimmes we're the ones who got it
ATM out the gate a cover band
Anyway I saw the rice off Mighty Mighty Bosstones at Riot Fest last year too depressed
That was right before Vicky parrot
Became an anti-vaxxer
I don't think anybody needs to be listening to The Mighty Mighty Bosstones after that George Floyd album they put out
Isis was before the fact
I think I hope
Yeah it definitely was before I was aware of that
So Banning
Love's
Infowars
Amy loves Alex
I don't know if you'll believe this Robert but
He claims that he listens everyday
You believe that
Yeah me neither
But here here he is saying
You know people that watch your show know me over the years
4 * The Economist
Oswego through that's
So I'm a I'm a huge
Believer in
Information
And I go to
The yobs
Infowars everyday
In Fallout
You know why
Ahead of the Curve
He's been
Demon eyes
Conspiracy theories
Right
I got to tell you
This book The Great reset in the war for the world
Left in the mainstream media are going
Going to have to sit
Get there
And we got to
Forestdale
Responded
This book is that in
No Force necessary I mean I'm not the left nor the mainstream media but I'll
The end of this book
Coming out
I've heard Rumblings of this and there's been there's been talk of it but
Alex's apparently coming out with a book I think it's getting rushed out because
There's a bit of a blitz going on right now and
The timing is not not suspicious
In terms of his
Israel happening
Starting on the 25th and going
Probably until the beginning of August or so
You on the 29th
You have his documentary coming out and then his book is supposed to come out in early August
I think there's a little bit of a like
Let's have something else to talk about
Kind of vibe going on
There's a couple things I have to think about this book
The first
Is that there is
0% chance that Alex wrote this
Yeah I mean he's too rich to write a book write like
That's not the problem that I would have
I don't know if you can write a book by skimming
But like I think I think you have a really rich people will have like ghostwriters
Write something
Or or or whatever but like
Alex is so f****** lazy
He couldn't write an article on his own website has a team of people to do that
I have no faith he could Emmett the last book he wrote
Inferior
I'm not even sure if he wrote that one was like
15 years ago we wrote some night like a 911 book
Probably like Jason bermas rotor or something
What would I wouldn't be surprised given him being the guy that he is if
If you'd like if he does a lot of like
Dictating that's how Hitler wrote his book
You know
Some people some people have too much
Get like to walk around and talk too much to actually write a book
And so
Those people have their their their Rudolf Hess or their whatever gyro talents
Well I if that's the case I can't wait to read it
Because the
Who sang who could transcribe the nonsense
That Alex is going to have have
I've thrown out I mean
Does the syntax
Is going to be revolutionary
I think that
The great the great English professors
Will struggle to deal with
Alex's
Run-on sentence
Hemingway-esque run-on sentences
I predict
Yeah I think that books going to be dumb it's just about the great reset so
Complaining about Klaus Schwab and
But Noah Harari guy
Yeah
Sapiens right he's
I mean the Futurity in Dushore
Kind of boring
I'm going to guess that your assessment is not going to match Alec
And in this forthcoming book
Yeah I don't know I thought it was kind of boring
Like most books that Barack Obama recommend
I don't think I've ever read it I don't
I don't know I don't I don't gravitate towards
The genre of
Futurists writing
Too much
Like I would rather
Futurist
History of
Hominids
Okay baby I'm just categorizing it wrong because that's like what he is
You're yeah you were thinking of so that I have not read this book he wrote another book called a homo Deus
Yeah that's I think
Business future
Okay that's
That makes
That's me that's the sort of
Cubby hole that he existed without so I just assumed like pretty much all of his career revolve around that
Fear this book is going to suck I'm sure
But I'm excited for it
I will definitely do a
Protracted series
On it as soon as it comes out
And that turns out to be exactly what Bannon thinks I can
Do
I tell you what let's hang out we'd love to keep you for one more cigarette
If you want Steve is awesome
Okay if we got Alex Jones the book
Is the great reset in the war for
For the world
This is Ace
Seminole
Madeline Peltz
I dare anybody to go
Read it
IND
Jeffy the rapper
And the deconstruct
Major work
Bye-bye
Major
This is not intellectual
They're accepted
100-percent I accept this
I know that I'm not cool like Media Matters
But I will I will handle
I'll handle this Bannon
And I'll get back to
I would
I think there's a pretty good shot of
You getting on Steve
And if that happens
You're going to need
The plunge the dagger of telling megiddo
Into the glowing spot at the base of his belly
In order marked by a ketchup stain that will finally bring the Kali Yuga
I I was looking at this guest list I think I fit right in a mean you got like jakpus obok you got an owie
Packers close friends
Ritual. We ate at the same restaurant once I mean that was a child
That molestation Dan and I just thought it had pretty good pizza
But hey you know we're at work work clothes
Robin Malone
Sonic just outside Columbia Missouri
It's a mess
That places
It's haunted for sure
I'm so distant
This interview is
I'll be honest there's a lot of content in it that would just be
Really
Pointless and
Boring
For like anybody listen sauropod
There's like
You know Alex will throw out things like why the future doesn't need us or
Eco science by John P holdren like I'll throw these things out as if he's like making an extra large in it but
It's just sort of scattershot reference
So I don't particularly care about that too much
I want to focus
On how sad this is
Alex
Hates
Steve Bannon
Banning has never acknowledged Alex
And hear the two of them
Desperately try to out
Complement each other
This is two men brought low
Towards each
Well you been through this President Trump's been
And what they do is
A populist
Play fear
What Americans
American
Popular
Shut that down
Medina Ice-T band
Donald Trump
And I'm not trying to
That back the league
Make your property
Pick-A-Part I am because
You're respecting her also
Better intelligence background of
Dana was a blind Trust
Potawatomi
Trump successes
And I'm not
Trump
Because I think
I like Trump you have
Have a
It was Bernard Charles said only connect
You have a way of connect
With the working class
Tree in the middle
That is very powerful
I mean what am I guilty
They're actually
I mean
Incredible you have a way of connecting
Trump.has awake
That
Is their biggest fear
The biggest fear is
Is the
Education and Enlightenment The Awakening of that army of what I call the army of the awake
And they will take
I think Tucker and I are
Farhan backup
Because you want Trump have a way
Connecting
A hard connect
With that
That is
You can't coach that
That's a god-given
Do you have
That's where the car I don't want
What were they trying to do right now they've done everything possible
So the
You got this nice Vibe of
You're awesome
You are drunk or on the same
God
Given wavelength
Connection to the
To the the
The real Folk
Common people
You understand your this organic connection
And I would I would suggested maybe it's the
Him and Trump are like they live in the fraud
You know they live in that that manipulation so much
Vets
That people connect to it
More easily
That could be
Part of it
And someone like Tucker. Really
I was trying to think about what
Like what connects Alex to
Two common people
Like what what is it
He's been in media for 20-something years
He's a millionaire
You have multiple home
He lives in one of the liberal enclaves of Austin Texas
He is friends with celebrities
He's having Steve Bannon tell him that he's
One of the great thinkers since the revolutionary era
Runs away from his fans when they confronted about the street
Because they scare him
Like Blackwater security everywhere like he has a tank
There's nothing he didn't hesitate text
I think you did but that was that was just
If that's who that's similar to what a lot of Americans are dealing with having cell there
Extraneous out the tanks absolutely
I wish more people were selling their tanks
Steven I might be able to buy one but
You know you said something is second ago
About what connects Alex to Common be
And I know what you meant by that but now all I'm thinking
Thinking about
Is Alex getting together with Ben Folds like Shatner did
And doing a cover of folks comedy
I think Alex actually could knock out of
The park
If
Alex does lose everything
We need to get him a record deal to do a Shatner type out
Yeah exactly
But also very Lounge
So like in between songs there's got to be a little bit of banter
You know you got to have some kind of word
I mean the other option is to just have Alex do an exact
Perfect
Word-for-word replica of Shatner's album has been
So like Alex's
Singing that song about Shatner finding his wife dead in the pool in about being the washed up
Star Trek start
I feel like you can talk Alex into doing that he hates Shatner now so like
Backup
Try to do a better job than bill
F****** perfect
But
I think Alex has beat I mean you know Steve Bannon is complimenting him quite a bit but I think he has the potential to be
Like Paul Stanley level
Stage banter
Kind of guy
Like really make it make it its own thing he could decode
Revolutionize the art of
Saying dumb s*** in between songs
No absolute
So we got one last clip here
It was not very long enough
It's just kind of vague
Puff piece
Promotion for the book that's not out and doesn't have a release date
I am the documentary so it's basically just that
And
When this episode comes out I'll already be in Austin
For the trial
And
Here's him Alex telling ban in about this
Everything Alex is saying is total b*******
This is just
Offense
I have
The Motions in limine infowars.com
Call the judge's order
The first of three
Ridge Sandy Hook trials where I've already been found guilty I've been
Defaulted
When I gave them everything and more which they used it as a boy
Blueprint
Find nerdy bankers
Platformers
And the judge
Put in the order for the trial where I'm guilty
But I cannot say I'm innocent
Says word for word
Anyway
Murderer
Call dead bodies in my basement I would get up and say I minutes
No I am guilty
And I can't cross-examine anybody
And I can't raise the First Amendment
And I can't say that
Order to have this trial
Or I'll be held in contempt
She did a million-dollar fine a month ago
Court Appeals
One day a million dollars
And I'm out of money they finally run me to ground
I paid a million dollars
On Monday
Literally bought the company that like $3,000 in the bank
That's okay
This is a real war
If you mailed it
You stole my phone
Understand why you want to show people this is veritas
Which particle
They hate barbecue in the family way
They hate Donald Trump
They hate me because
We are populist we are we love the people
The people get that they
See if they can feel it and gone through
And they don't want them to have
Spirit
And destroy us
That's their symbol American people Trump always said
Look they got to get through me to get to you and it's totally true
We have decided to stand up
Love America
Heroes we just can't
Rollover
Soho they see us standing or no
And smashes they can do it and
This is not my rights are being robbed
Dial
DC situation we are all having our rights
Stolen
Say I'm innocent
And can't say I'm bankrupt
Campsaver three trials coming up
Literally
She says we can say almost nothing
We have to be there
And so
That's where this is
Criminal
You just stop talking
Don't like him
Comparing
Him
After
Like half a decade in the court
Having to pay money
For slandering the family
Dead children
To being a right
I really I just I dislike
I don't think
I don't think you should be able to do that
I agree with you and he Compares that use that comparison a lot and I
I will say that I don't often
Included on our show because of it being
Usually of an obviously always a benzos
Yeah also usually even if you tracked the thinking it didn't make it doesn't make sense
A lot of the time
Conceptual standpoint
Important things to remember here beyond that too and that is one
Bannon chose not to do defense
He could have done he could have done a defense
He did.
All of the stuff I like to sing
Are the products of his decision
He had every possibility to be able to raise the 1st Amendment
Defense
He didn't do it
Teacups find a million dollars because
Keep kept sending incompetent corporate representatives in the judge
Ran out of options
He can save that boo
You know the trial is a like a staged rig thing
He'll be taken out of court probably held in contempt just like
Anybody else in a courtroom would be
Like this is he's not special there's no like special victimhood here
It's the product of his choices
Because
He knew that if he went to trial he would lose
If you want to try all he would lose and it would be
Embarrassing
But
If you just decided not to participate
Losing by default
And this would be the situation we were in and he can be like always only I had my day If Only They allowed me to
Defend myself
It's all just b******* the same thing parents doing the same thing Rodger Stone did and his trial
Like all of them don't defend themselves in the in the time when they are given the opportunity to because they know it all
No way to defend their behavior
So their only defense is
Stretching it out as long as possible I guess and hoping that
Once again the system
Does not actually
Penalized
Away like
Uno Spano probably get a weekend
Can a f******
Resort
Yeah it's hard to fault somebody for thinking you won't get any consequences based on the lack of consequences
Usually yeah
You just kick your feet and kick up dust
I'm kind of just hope that
Eventually you'll have some resolution where you don't have to reveal more information
They'll be more destructive to
Your industry
That sucks
So I'll be in Austin I'll be watching the
The proceedings where Alex is not allowed
Bring up the First Amendment
Is not allowed to call it a show trial
You can't you can't believe that he's innocent because he's already been found guilty suit
It's irrelevant to the case so he's lost by default
There's no there's no
This what I do
I wonder if Alex will actually show up to the court
That's something that I'm not sure about
Does he have
I don't think he physically has what
For him to not show up
I would imagine there is
He could just send his lawyers
I don't I don't know I don't know he doesn't have to testify or anything I don't
Yeah I mean if he doesn't have to I would have to guess he's probably not done
Right
But then the attention
Possibility
But you can say s*** outside the courtroom
Well yeah I guess there's that like maybe it'll be worth it for him to show up outside
Or two shops
He can go outside
The courtroom at
Keep it a f****** impromptu press conference at his custody hearing
A couple years back
Oh God yeah you know I had forgotten about that okay well we'll see
I could I could see him doing like a little rally outside the courthouse
Or something trying to
Promote
His stupid documentary
Yeah we'll see we'll be posting episodes
Throughout the time they're in Austin
Trying to find some
Some relevant folks to interview perhaps in
Trial updates
So well be fun
Robert thank you so much for joining me
Do you have any any closing thoughts about to visit
Disgraceful
It explained
Number one
Thought is that it's worrying that Alex and
And Steve are getting closer together cuz those really aren't you worlds that I like being tied closed
However
Steve Bannon is is really dangerous and I worry about him a lot
And Alex Jones
Is
Has a mr. Magoo likeability to
The trip up people around him and get them into terrible terrible trouble
That's true
So possibly this will go well
More than anything Dan
I'd like people to listen
To the Ben Folds William Shatner album has been
Particularly the cover of common people
The chatter does on
Is it it it
It Fox
I understand next week you're going to have a three parts behind the bastards
About
That album
It is
The bastard of that album is that I can't stop
Singing it
Is have everyone around you
God label you the bastard for
Incessant leasing in common
Well they're going to label me the bastard
Cuz I think Shatner said some
F***** up this
I refuse to read any new news stories about Shatner it doesn't
Okay then he's an old man and will be dead soon
It's fine
I'm unaware of
Anything past him going to space that is where I checked out that was the last thing I needed from him
Fulfilled your your narrative Arc
And we got
Yeah I sent him a letter the other day saying you're allowed to dye will
You let him go I let him go I let him go
That's big of you
Well we should. Let ourselves go
And wrap this up again people can find your podcast behind the bastards
Fantastic
Shoe
Thank you
And thank you for summoning made
What the power of song
I am no longer in need of a hero but but thank you for being one for me
We will talk again soon
Yay
What a what a fine interview that was what it was but a lot of fun too.
Talk about how stupid Steve Bannon is in
Oh wow he's talking to Alex Jones God Kenny can you believe it Celine
Meow
I know you did
Keep it quiet and I have to pretend
Meow for you just going to kick back with a nice
Nice Radler here just a nice
Treat myself you know I'm going to be taking this trip I I deserve a little bit of a kickback
No nice nice 2% beer
You know that's about that's about what I want right about now maybe a little bit
Hey Mark Basinger
For sure I mean I was just about to enjoy this nice beer that's a really just lemonade but
Want to have a chat with you
You know what
Even Keel you know heading into the
4-year buildup of the most surreal trial in American memory that's going to be watched by the entire world
I'm really chill about
Yeah it seems like it you got it you got a laid-back Vibe I have to be honest I do not feel my radio theater that I just did
I'm very self-conscious of Yeti better than the fur
It's nice to talk to you I know that
I'm going to be
Recording this on Saturday evening I'm going to be there in person tomorrow
But I wanted to sit down if it was it was it all possible and thankfully it is
To talk a little bit about what people can expect of the
The coming trial it's actually it looks like it's going to happen
There's no more bankruptcy stunt yeah
Yeah I'll be looking you know what to expect tell me I'm I'm waiting bated breath I'd love to know
I expect a dry heat
There is there's no way to tell us about that
I'd like to say
Tonight's plan coordinated a bit but I'm dealing with one of the most unproductive
People in
Gosh
In living memory
Yeah who knows what's going to happen
I think I know how it's going to go down
But you know
I mean
There's a there's one thing that is B you know the preparation and the the law aspect of it in the trial
And I I just I think I think you probably have your ducks in a row in terms of that
The thing that just blows my mind is that you know we have
This this case is starting on Mondays 25th
And then on the 29th Alex is releasing his documentary
Oh well I mean
Take a break
The trial of the century Casino
Jesus
Yeah he's like really trying to steal Focus I don't know
Glenn Greenwald
Like right on the
Really this is your best attempt
Grab publicity after I've been absolutely smoking you in the entire Global media for 4 years
Come out with the guy
Cell movie in
It's the guy who almost got Snowden arrested and you're going to like it really
A green Walter that involved in the documentary I think he was a gun-for-hire for that q and a butt
Ridiculous
I was watching a little bit of that earlier before we started chatting and the director
I was sitting in between Greenwald and Alex
And she had her head down for long stretches of time
Seem to not want to be there
I'm not sure if I was reading too much into body language but
Can't blame her
Dogs get fleas
Regional thing or not
Yeah I know
I feel like it's good
If he's burning time doing
What's going on over there man it's a mess
And then when they walk
Look I think of
Expectation
They're they're going to garbage like that and we'll see how it goes
It kind of went play was
Let me know
Right exactly if you know anything about the suit
What you can predict is that anything you think is about to happen
Not is exactly what
What's not
Did the one thing I do have to say about though it's like
Set the Comfort I have going into this
Is we have a trial judge who I know is not going to tolerate nonsense
I think we've been waiting for you
Jones
Courtroom theatrics aren't going to be in Dish
Some nonsense judge
You need to see where you're going with this
That's not what's going to happen
That I had that I wanted to run by you and that is actually came up earlier I was talking to Robert and that is that
Do you
Know if Alex is actually going to have to be there
I was thinking that there's and there's an entire possibility that he wouldn't even need to show up like a lawyer is good just
Conceivably show up right
Is I am starting to get asked
When is
The entire world who's and attention to the sting
Tim will expect his trial
Part and parcel with what this is
Right kind of anti-climactic for anybody who likes Alex if he doesn't
Right
Or whatever that shot is butt butt
Jury at some point
Regardless
They're going to want to see Alex Jones on the standings
And whether that happens or not
Control of that necessarily like that's not a thing
Cover
Decides he wants to kick back into society
Trout
I can't
I don't have
Enso Wheels but you don't really need to have him
Like testify or anything like you do with no reason that you need to call him to the stand to make your case
Look at this point
The default judgment that resulted to us
Is wow
Climax
Meaning
Doesn't mean a damn thing there's not like you were going to walk into this try on people
Defamation
That was already decided like that's done and like
Where you going to do is press
Wait
There's not I don't want to put it to
In other words what I want to say is my aunt's at this point
Like it's not
You can you can say all you want about how you perform in a trial that's going to be
Amazon me and respect
As far as what I can do to those poor people in the box with the decision they're going to make
This is purely about
Press play and let them react there's going to be 12 jurors and they're trying to come up with a number
As much as I in my
Personal life in a rental
I have a lot of
Shaken faith in our systems and institutions one
Bible Otto
Cynicism
I guess it's how you put it at built up after seeing how juries relaxer
Sometimes
But one thing I can say
This particular truck
This particular droughts
There's never been anything like what Jones did
This is what we would call in-law a matter of first impression
I think this is nobody's going to have to do this is the first time a drink enough to look at this kind of comics
10 years of somebody torturing
Erin Burnett children
They're going to have to come up with number of what it's worth
And whatever number they come up with
Is the correct
Number
Not either party in this courtroom I am convinced is going to have much of an effect
What they decide that correct number is they will be faced with what is basically Undisputed facts and they will
Face
The same
Controversial National outrage that has consumed part of the country for so many years on this
They will come up with that number
At this point I put in the hands of those 12 and a lot of stuff to press play on
Based on these depositions stuff that we've covered I imagine just
Seeing the reaction of people to the lot of that be amazing
One of my most rewarding things I do on this case is for the first time when I show somebody
A
An email a piece of deposition for a clip of diarrhea
Runaway
Right right exact
Or you know some of the people that you're going to be seen at this trial and I'm going to give kind of like a
You know okay so I know your viewers love the deposition episodes
It's baffling to me but yes
Because
If you listen this deposition Strider on YouTube the rather dry
Horner whatever but like the analysis y'all do in between questions
I feel like we should just become a deposition cast
Exactly
Is there's going to be a bunch of deposition testimony Clips play at this trial
But they've never seen
Really
Bunch of new stuff
This this raises the question
After the trial are there going to be a bunch of deposition that will be public that weren't before
Cuz if so
They have not seen
I heard because of the different rules up in Connecticut
Damn yeah
I have never heard
Chris Maddie
I never heard that
And we've seen a little bit of the transcripts that have
But you're going to see a couple of things in this
When is the one that everybody already knows a small
And we're going to be hearing from her is the corporate representative
And then you're going to hear another deposition from the nobody's ever heard of
And that's Robert Jacobs
Jacobson was the former video editor for nearly 15 years at Infowars
And he will test
Sue very very surprised
About what
He knew and did inside of it
That smell be fascinating because he's already said some pretty bad stuff
Public
NN I'm being careful confidential depositions that will become public at the moment
But there are Robert Jacobsen is good
Testify by deposition that's going to be a very surprising
Deposition for a lot of people
The other is I know a lot of
People know from The Saga
Infowars reporter
Nobody's interest Crockett
Yeah I'm believe me that
Barry
Entertaining
They did
Wow and I'm tell you I hope that does becoming a fully public cuz we're going to be playing but the entire thing
Thing is as rewarding as you might expect it
It is
Really something
To see that man
He's a police officers dream because you ask him one question the answers
Sex offender
Getting stuck by God from seeing some of his interviews that he did back when he worked it in
Infowars it seems like
Out this guy I'll talk
Another
Another surprise guest will be a dawn Salazar
Nobody
I don't want Salazar
Is one of the chief Riders at Infowars on Sandy Hook still like a major
Figure they're I don't know if I've ever seen his face
Exactly
The theater for a little while
And then once we mentioned it he stopped for her guts up Twitter
So there was something sneaky going on there but
I don't want to see this because like you know
I don't want to put this on you at all because my personal perception of him
Is he seems like a s*******
I don't know if
The deposition will
Will color my feelings at all but he seems like one of the worst
I will describe him or in terms that the
Describe
Deeply irresponsible and malicious journalists at every step
That is so diplomatic
And then the last sort of surprised that they will be is
But our case
Broke down in tears for what he did
42r self
Bye to your phone
He is going to be appearing as Lafferty
She was also
From there
Do we have a lot of people and we'll have a lot of people at trial
We have experts to fully disclose so I don't mind telling you
True that we're going to have
Fred's
Longtime editor of the Austin Statesman testify about journalism and the standards of care he's now University of Texas
We'll have Becca Lewis who thing is our Twitter
One of the foremost
Tom batters of misinformation out there
Top-notch a media researcher
Define a lot about
Spread of invoice message
Also have the therapist use treated
Onion Scarlett's Instagram Sandy Hook
And as well as a doctor who is a forensic psychologist you is
Published in the field of denial of trauma
And he's going to talk
The variety of enforcing Floyd's
I'm so it's going to be
You know a lot of people were kind of worried coming into this if it just being a damaged how are you going to get the full measure what happen
Absolutely will
That we're going to be going through the entire story
Everything kind of deprived of the
Dial itself
You know there is a need perhaps for the jury that's exciting these damages to have
Some of that
I am in this contact
16 Oak
If you talking about like what
What you're saying a number for the damages he should
Have an appreciation for what the damage
That was Don what you know stating for their arms to the plane
Do also be awarded punitive damages
4 to address the wanton malicious conduct
And it doing that to have to really consider how bad was it
Yeah we're going to need to do a deep dive
Do what they do when they do it
And I think
You know even for knowledge fight listeners
I think it's going to be deeply surprising for them
Dashew volume
That they
Subject with
Yeah I'm out that they tormented people
Nmd the absolute
Ava T of knowing
What they did was wrong that the people they were talking to her crazy
It's very shocking story in one place
You don't even for me somebody who's
Pretty well-versed in this when I came down for the deposition seeing some of the materials
Was pretty surprising for me
Like I can be as cynical as the next guy and for me there was even a
I want to see benefit of the doubt but there was a
I I don't want to assume the worst until you know you see some information some of the
I guess some of that is public as it was in those depositions but like
Who is Wolfgang halbig emails some of the the indications of awareness of things
It was pretty eye-opening in its you know I assume there's a lot more
There is a lot of surprises to come
And I'm it's going to be quite a show let me ask let me ask you a question here
You're talking about surprises
You talking about Infowars employee
Dude where you able to track down
Batman Jakari Jackson or my gal Lee Ann McAdoo
They're the old Ivory people
My friend
I have searched high and low I have uncovered
And I must report to you
But they are like the Snows of yesteryear
Gone from this Earth
Well you know I guess
Will you know it may be best to let them let the
Actually I think we're involved in all this
Lien has not made much of a video
You know like there's just going to be videos of her and Rob do
Talking about some of the most vile stuff is Super Bowl choir was actually the bird
Children
I mean
Yeah I remember that from some of the time I was going back over that that period of their content yes
Yeah it was a little disappointed
Well as lockers appointee
Yeah it's going to be I mean obviously I don't want to say this is going to be fun because it's not but it will not
I can tell you that
It will be cathartic
And
In and very interesting to see how it plays out
I heard you say that he was going to have for the show so you can come try
Let's see if he does that let's see if he does that be Barnes that he's thinking about Susan
And it's like literally Alex Jones Roatan
David Barnes botched the case and please don't do XOXO
We got rid of bards
What a stupid show well I mean the code the code for that is Barnes botched the case
Which I wanted him to do and now I'm blaming him in a meaningless way
Ever done is a light
It's just disgusting
How much they just Levi
The courts really do believe it's true that like
Stay away from
Get that whatever
Right
Cost of these things like if you don't show up in that courtroom to face me bad what the
Yeah
He just for that for the
But if he doesn't show up
Yeah
4 years to look at man in the face in the courtroom and say you're going to take
He doesn't do that
What kind of man is he
Yeah that's something that gets really lost it and I think it's intentional in the way that Alex discusses the k-select
How he's so jammed up and how it's like
A show trial for him in like
The reality is
Him trying to invalidate
All of this is invalidating the family's right to have their day in court
And the flip side of that is that would also be his day in court
I like to even further emphasize what this means for the families
Right and I don't I don't mean to be overdramatic sure
Is that
When you have a plate of who is his actual injury when doing him and Scarlett actual injury
Is the denial of their trauma
Great is the denial
Bendy Vindication of a jury verdict
Is not just about Justice it is
Medically necessary
They need to have the smoke they need to have
A public Reckoning birds recognize their son was real this was bulshit what he did to them was bulshit
Like this needs to stop being the Legacy to be how they've indicated the legacy of their child not
Yeah
That doesn't really happen
They can never heal like this trials not even
That's his most important function
I'm going to get a lot of these parents if he doesn't come in there and face
The antidote to that negation is affirmation
You know
On some level yeah
Well I guess I don't want to keep you all night so cuz we could talk some quite a while
There is there any other like important points you want to you want to get across to her
Yes
Thank you everybody out there and knowledge fight lands
Yoyoman real like you was really nice
I don't know
Is the best fanbase in River encountered my life
Passionate and
Supportive
If any of you reside in
Trials open at your Courthouse
Come on down
And then make yourself seen there and be a part of history and see it all I would love to see you there
But just you know if you can't
But also leave me alone leave me alone and socially awkward please do not approach me
Or any of that
I will spray you with a spray bottle
There is a live stream
Of procedure
You need to find it
All you need to do is go to YouTube
Inserts the 459
District
And you will find the courts YouTube
You know
Tweeting support and do whatever you can to have
The community cathartic effect
We need right like you have to do
And just keep us in your thoughts and
Pretty soon we'll
Will be at the end of this long journey
I don't know what kind of angles are the cameras in the courtroom will have but if you if you look you might be able to find any
Easter egg
Of this guy
Wearing a Hawaiian shirt of some sort
Yes
Of course
I don't know what that I'm going to Iowa
It's going to be ex and I don't know what it's going to be
Yeah
I look forward to seeing you and I look forward to this process working itself
To it's a conclusion
Enza
Hope I hope everybody comes out the other side
A bit better for it except for our
Absolutely
Thanks so much Mark
Best of luck
Saudi Saudi forever my friend amen