Knowledge party.com
I have great respect for its knowledge B I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Need
Knowledge fight
Everybody welcome back to knowledge fight like just sit around in a hotel
Show rooms in Austin Texas
We worship Selene from
Alphardy
Saw today
What are we
We do it yes it's a very serious question
Get back to this in a second but it was probably
Talk about right spot
Yes that's a good point Dan
Bright spot today but bright spot is
I was around the
The s***
Today after going to the trial
Yeah and I wanted some food
And I've nothing in the hotel room so I ordered jack-in-the-box
There's no Jack
The Box in Chicago now it is something that is beloved of me and my friend
True love a jack-in-the-box
Cuz there was one like on the way to St Louis there wasn't any
Columbia either
Answer was like is real
Need to pull over and go to the Jack-in-the-Box
Ghetto
Tacos not good doesn't mean that when the heart
Wants What It Wants
Liking garbage
But yes I got that I got some
Some of the Jack-in-the-Box tacos
They showed up
Worst
Worst delivery experience
There are different
Your situation was maybe a little tougher but
I get the Jack in the Box
There's no sauce for the tacos
I am so I thought
Myself
Going to be disgusting
They're already
Disgusting but the sauce makes them
Edible
Right
The soldier through
And they were still pretty good
So yeah that's my price
Significant break in the Box tacos were not ruined by being
Sauceless
Give me my bright spot is
Boy it's been a long table Kate of s*** for me I've been really enjoying Tweety
Think about the trial live stream
Literally nothing else has been good so far
I've been hit by a truck. Had to run around this whole f******
Ringtone for THC
Soundboard
That doesn't even f****** work half the time
All you got
Because I think people might be
Confused first of all
The soundboard issue that
What you're talkin about is
We brought a small soundboard
With which to
Record and did not realize until we got here that did not have a USB connect
Could plug into the
The laptop and I couldn't play Clips through it
Now that's going to do a lake
We can throw that into Barton Springs
In honor of Oz
Alex this one's for you
Then
You got a replace
Another one that has a USB connection and we cannot get it to work
3 hours
Plus
Earlier trying everything I can figure out to I do it so
We recordings this here
But we can't play any clips
Not our fault
We have to take the blame cuz
It's not anybody else's
His fault but it is is just bad happen
In Stamps Shore
And I had a fun episode
Really ready
Need to go but I guess we just have to ruminate on
Are serious Austin so far
So you got hit by a truck though
T-boned
Or like going over
B it was it it was kind of a weird situation we were driving in a f****** Park
Parking lot and my Lyft driver I mean
My Rideshare driver sure
Absolutely
In the in the parking lot
And I was not paying attention whatsoever I was like hey I'm happy that this guys moving cuz I've been waiting here for a while
And then all the sudden I am smart
Passenger side door
Because we got T-boned
Buy a f****** lawnscaping
What are those
Huge ass like
Or whatever they're f******
I'm called now I feel bad about saying you didn't get Tebow
I mean he was it was like he was going
1520 miles an hour
You know so all I have is a giant lump on my head I didn't have a seer
Concussion about to go to the
Which you made me you're going to make me feel your head
I received
I was going to make
Certainly suggest
Do you think there's a possibility that this bump on the head is what
Is causing you to live tweet
There are so many possible things with the bump on the head
Could be responsible for supervillains
Shitposter shorty
What you hate dad
Play the path
What is a plural noun
Me what I be Matt Taibbi
Except
We're here we're in Austin
Danzig
2 Days in on the trial at this point would recording this
At midnight
Cuz I couldn't get these recorders to work we're doing great
Doing so good doing great got it on Sunday
Yep
Monday was the jury selection
And we we happy
Thought or the belief was
Initially that we would be able to go to that
And hanging out at the courthouse
But
We're not able to
So instead
A bit of that on the the old livestream
Didn't allow any media into the room during the
This is what I heard from other
Media folk right
The only ones
Not not trying to
Pretend that we press badges or anything
I did put a little sign in my hat fedora
Yeah it was like a little sign on your pump
It's so a little bit to uneventful I think selection is
Kind of an arduous process there's a lot of repetition
Yeah kind of get a little bit in
Insight into some stuff obviously but
It's not
The Flash
Yeah it was interesting to watch
The jury select
TuneIn full
I just
Because it appeared that
The defense lawyer was absolutely willing to give up
Every bit of their strategy in every single question
It was literally like
Hey
What if I said I want a judgment of $1
Who here it was a virgin auction like
That's what everybody's maximum amount would be
Obviously
Seems like a question should be able to ask
Yeah that's that went on Monday
Let me ask you this when you were watching
Specific
Did you find yourself poem
For any jurors
Like honestly really for them to be on the jury but
Absolutely
Play there were a few
You people who gave
I'd like
I mean
Gave responses
That were impassioned
We're empathetic
We're caring
And where the absolute wrong thing to say if you ever wanted to be on this f****** jury
In your life you know
Like somebody was
Describing restored
Justice almost
And it was listening to that I was like you're gone by
Get out of here you know
Yeah yeah
I think that kind of fun cuz you couldn't really see
See the people until you just had their words
Yes judge on
Face of a lawyer unhappy
It's like the dating game
Do you know where you'd have Bachelor number 1 2 and 3 behind the screen
Juror number one
I would have preferred a game of guess who where we could have just
Slapped off the people who'll be
No glass
Is your door wearing a
That's me
So close
BBQ
How to get to barbecue which was
Find that was my first and last food in the past 3 days
Heather on the other hand
Jack in the Box tacos
Barbecue I got some donuts tomorrow morning
You're doing better than me but I think I could outrun
This is the best I can
You can run
That's good enough
So yeah
Today
Was the beginning at the open
Little bit of
Eyewitness
This time how did you feel about Mark's open
Yeah I thought so
I mean look here's the thing
When you talk about the opening
Segment
That were made in this
This case
I think you got to look at both of them at the same time
Because I pay
Obviously you could just say that Mark
Opening statement was good
In order to understand why it was good
You really are
Have to look at the other one which was not good
Amazing Alex's lawyers opening statement was not good
I'm at work
Reasons why is first was kind of Meandering
It wasn't very well delivered
Mark had a
Sincerity behind what he was saying a pesos
But
More than that
There was a narc
Yes there was
Is a
Story essentially of like
Here are relevant pieces of information that fit into
What happened
Right and that was really missing from the defense
Open
Opening statement which was just kind of like
Apologize
1 this is an Alex's fault
Even if he did say he did it and we heard him do it
I know you saw those videos but he did next
Say that yeah
Three come on he apologized that does
Doesn't count and for its again everybody else's fault but Alex
Sue them
Opening
It certainly included for the defense was the notion of you got to watch the video
Oh yeah
That came up a couple times
Conflicted relation
Chip with that because
I do think you do need to generally
But you might have to
A lot of times
There aren't there
What is context it's amazing
From
Short section
The video
You are Alex
And you demand people watch whole videos
No one has the time in their life to do it now and if that's the standard of being able
The judge Alex's intentions
Like nobody except me you would be qualified
To have an opinion on what
You did right
Maybe that's true
Which means
That yours is the only opinion that counts
I think we've already established a lot but you understand someone would just come back to me with like all you didn't watch this
Standard of something that you're missing
Emancipet
That's difficult
Because I think some people
Can be done Dirty by
Selective attention
Cherry picking
Wingstop
I think that's the case
At all not just that
Button
Mark's opening
He played a clip
We're Infowars clearly
Edited versions of
Clips together
Deceptively
To avoid playing the full clip
So Alex
Is
Guilty of the things that he blames everybody else or not
Well thank that clip that you're talking about is the one where Owen Shroyer is
Talking
About mr. hassling
Two clamps
One of dr. Wayne Carver and one of one of the other parents
And they are edited in such a way as to make it a
The pier that they're saying
But they didn't see the kids and there's no what right right
I'm so
The issues
I don't think anybody can demonstrate that Infowars edited those video
They may have come in house
Deceptively edited
It's still their fault for not finding out what the context is
But yeah maybe they didn't do it then
Make the videos but if you're the ones who play it on Infowars
While saying that everybody else needs 200 full clip
Yeah
Point stands just wanted to
Clarification
I'm talking legalese now so we showed up prior
To these these
Opening statements and I had a nice
The front row
Reserved
You have to go to the bank
Because I am a bad boy
The sound a little bit
The first thing that happened when I sat down to the back after Alex walked in
Well I was going to get to the hell okay thanks for ruining the dramatic reveal
No cir so I sat down
I sitting next to Sebastian Murdock
I was there very very nice to meet him
Do just do it there's this
Beard Buzz of like
Is Alex going to show up right cuz he wasn't there yet wasn't there on Monday exactly it played sick
Yeah it was something
And
Just kind of a a feeling in the air of
Is it going to show up
My conjecture had been
Just you and I talked to Robert about it a little bit on the episode that we did
Alex was going to show up
And he was going to make it
He's going to be a dick
Outside the courtroom cuz he couldn't behave
Like a dick inside the court
Correct
That was kind of my theory if
He did show up
But we didn't know he was going
Until we're there were hanging out
Habitat power business
NYX Alexander
Gross shalaby f****** jacket The Man based on his appear
Do you need something
I'm insulting him based upon respect
Bright bright
Look better than
Not good now I sweat through a shirt
That wasn't very attractive at all
I don't have respect for
4 quarts so that's fine with me
Yes that's in a position where you have to
Wear an undershirt
Alex walked in
I was in the depositions I've been in a room with him
Before right
And
I I don't know what it was like for you to experience him in the
The Flash for the first time
You know it was
It was
Very similar to what you described
When you met him for the first time
Which was
Like
You should know who I am
I'm sure I know I know
When to
Boy this is
Really that's
Yeah you are a disappointing motherfuker
You know what was super weird
I'm surprised by how little the atmosphere in the room change
When he came in
You know like I really doubt there was a part of me that expected like
This Electric
Thing was going to come in and bright
I was I was just kind of a dude is way too much
Security
6 total
Is bunch
And outside well after you would laugh
Alex was doing a little bit of a small press conference that said he had some other security guards she's one of them
May have had a fake must
What is unclear
Earlier in the day
Alex shows up
Beyond just like the atmosphere of the room not really changing and if
You showed up what about that
Beyond that the other thing that I was
Really struck
By was
How
Few people were there
Really not many people I say this
I say this at risk
Of sounding
Conceited
I think there were more knowledge fight fans there than out
There were
Three or four people who came up to us and thank you for saying hello it's nice to meet you
We're not here in any official capacity
I didn't see anybody
He who like
Appeared to be someone I would recognize from Infowars world
Like one of the other reporters
Like
He had
He could have just had like Harrison
Smith Wait out of the hall or Savannah Hernandez it maybe do an interview or something Harrison has to wait
Car windows rolled up
If he lives if he lives if he dies he dies
That's Alex's snake-handling
It was it was
Not
Pact
Really at all
And that was surprised me a little bit
I thought that
I mean
I don't know what I
I thought but I figured Alex would have some kind of a fan face
First off the first thing that we thought was
Get there early cuz we don't know if there's going to be enough room
What you know there was
Led to your room
Now
A lot of people were like
Taking up more space Maybe than they were some people like
At least a few people with
Equipment yeah I like cameras or what have you sound like
That takes up more than once
But yeah yeah
I was baffled by that
I think that's sad for him
I don't know maybe he maybe he would actively not want any of his fans in the courtroom on
My account
All the truth
That he's not allowed to lie about
Well pennies he doesn't have to talk
You know he's not like
You think he's going to be up on the
Fast and hitting getting
Debased
Or anything but I think
I have two minds about it
One is a dink
If I were him I probably wouldn't want
My listeners there either
Not necessarily cuz what they would be
Be exposed to
Because
Wiggle around
Because of like
You know that
They're going to not
Be cool
You know like they're not going to be people you want to meet
Probably Brown
For people who like him
They're probably going
To Yellow
1776 on the court
100% And that would be
Bad
I guess my mind is
Maybe that would be good
Maybe they'll be what you'd want disruptive
Entirely
And have somebody else do it that you want
Take responsibility
That's true
Do you know
I guess
Although that may really Prejudice the jury against you if one of your fans
Bust out
Just going
I think if I were on a jury I'd be like
Bad guys bad guy
It's me if I was on a jury
That
This person is very
Believes
In America
That's what I read in their followers
But yes yeah
Opening statements like I said I think we agree on this
One good one bad
It reminds me of relative
You know how if you're both
To the speed of light
Time moves slower so you know if
You go out at a million
The light-year away
You know I meant come back
Everybody you know is two years older
And you're still the same age really
Right
That is similar to the opening
Mark went to f******
Andromeda Galaxy
And this dude Doug himself like
PowerPoint presentation with some clips and contacts and all this
Alex's lawyer head like a board to write on
Psychopathic
They wrote slowly on
Excruciating and most of it was really just
Like
Here is a stretch of time
And then
Sixteen-year-old emeritus
Hillary
Are we here
Yeah but here's a really bum meow
So when we got in
Decorum initially
There were
Some props
Alex's lawyers
Had some profit
Right in the gate
One of them was a board
That said something to the effect of like
Infowars coverage of Sandy Hook
Cuz 1/5 of 1% of
They're covered in then there was another thing
That was like
I think it was
Going to be velcroed onto the big board
Find glass in order to demonstrate the
Unveiled because I was sitting in the background
Is baby allowed in court
So I didn't get to know what those this was excluded
Did as being something that could be presented
I think for a number
Jackie
I understand it it was not like if you're going to say that you have to be able to demonstrate right can't demonstrate the
If it was
One-half of 1%
But here's why I'm pissed off about
I wanted
I wanted those Pro
Got they would have been
Chicago though
The judge needed to disqualify those
This is a courtroom in real life
But
I mean those are not going to help.
Defense
Big Board
That they had the big sign
That I did get
To see a little bit of Vic
Cuz they was unveiled Prix
And it basically looks like the McDonald's like
Over 500,000 hours sold
Like
Kind of thing
To make a big deal of like
He does a ton of content and this much was about San Diego
Right
I've been alive
Like a million hours
Only two of them I spent murdering
Yeah
All about you
I want those
I got to find
Tomorrow morning we're going to I'm going back to the courthouse
Figure out the sound
Go to the courthouse
I'm trying to find their dumpster
See if it's in there man
In the courthouse. What else would they do with it
We're going to throw a soundboard right next to it everything like
Marc's
Car is in there the 10
Fake mustaches in there
Oh God
The opening
Statements
Go down
Queendom there's a recess
And
We all everybody exit
The court Alex goes out before
And as we're exiting
You can see that a little ways down the hallway
Which is the only way to
To leave this courtroom Alex's posted up in front of
Some cameras is yelling about how he got jacked up
Now
Jordan
Ever the
Besides you decided that you wanted to interfere
Yeah I was just listening to this
Bulshit and watching these people in a courtroom protect
Him
And his ability to say nonsense
On camera
Child be allowed to bear
They're going to come get me
Play I need to yell at
Motherfuker
Sure
So instantly
After I said something
The court officer
Just walks up to me get the right in front of my face real close and goes
And it's like f*** you
Will do whatever I don't think it was that intimidating
Are there
Ocean
Is intimidating
Because you are trying to make it time
Think that I I I see both sides of this
I get where you're coming from and I think
Scale
But in the desert of the individual like
Actual real world of it
Like we're there it's a disrespect to the court what
He's doing
And you'd be adding to it
If you
You yelled at him so I'm glad that I'm glad that
Calmer heads prevailed
Myself strategy worked
Which was behind him
Until you're there
On Fox 7 right
Insert myself in some entirely where's Waldo ass
In the background photobomb his business conference
And so are you know if Alex watches himself on the news he's not going to see me behind that works
Okay
The shots
I watched a little bit of that
We were both
Well I will tell you this my mice
Sweaty pits
Prominently featured and it many
I also got sidetracked with
Bill walked by
A reporter at Matt's
Price of
A lot of lot of Halo
That happens
And
I thought
For sure Alex's
I thought like okay he's done his
He's going to leave
Right
He ended up staying
For his own opening
Safe mode
And
The judge
About doing
What he had done in the hallway
Rightfully and maybe
A little late
Toward maybe I should have been immediate
I'm not going to be late is the story of this trial
Well
You know I
I think what you're dealing with somebody like Alex
You got to give as many benefits
Served out as you can
Because
The argument is always going to be there
You jammed this person up
And you got to cover all your bases to make sure that those things are
Flimsy appearances that could be knocked out
Super easily
But I think that if your zodiac is like some kind of an awareness about Alex operate
You can't do many press conferences would have been like ground-rule I mean we're on
Year what now he did that during his like
Custody hearing
This is what he does
Anyway not be allowed to give an a
Prompto press
Front outside lights.
If he's going to be a giant
I think I should be allowed to do as well
Was basically told to leave work
Not like I'm going to leave I'm too sweaty
Man extreme anxiety is not fun
Realizing that weed isn't legal here until you get here
Yeah it is it is weird to have extreme anxiety and
Treated it
Successfully with
THC for a few years
And then just all of a sudden people are like
Know your meds are illegal
Like oh
Okay
I guess I'm just going to sweat my balls off in this
Courtroom
Somebody about how I know it sucks
Weed illegal here
Chicago
Here too if you know someone
Or if you go get Delta Ancient Man
I've been doing THC for too long to believe that Delta Liu
Suck down an entire Vape cartridge
Delta 8
And I was part of your sweater
No no no that was
And told a cut it out with this b******* shenanigans
And
I regretted Maybe
Spain
Before the 2nd
In part because that guy is opening
It was pretty boring
To come back
Come back to the hotel to do some work and watch the
The stream from here
And you missed out on me
You had already left
And out
Side
Outside of the courtroom
Alex showed up
Outside
Write in order to do another minipress.
Because you told me he was totally can't do one in the room
And so he did it out in front of the courthouse
And he put on that like Infowars bumper sticker over his mouth wow then just took it off
Basically when he realized that there was nobody out there
There was nobody what a message he had no fans hanging out
There was no press
Here's what the Press was
You had
Sebastian
Georgia Post
You have Liz Williamson from The New York Times and then by the Bennett
More security guards than there were press and fans combined
True it was
So sad
Because Alex was holding his is like little thing you could
I was watching from afar
And I could tell that he was doing his
They will not let me defend myself right then he realized
The reporters were people
A little bit of a
So then he posed with his lawyer with a bumper sticker over his mouth
God
Pathetic loser
Yeah that he took off that stuff it was
Hilarious to watch
Because there was such
Impotent
Showmanship
Who's the showman without a crowd
That
Was fun
Got it somebody had played
The curb themes
Songwriter
That was what I was saying I wanted to do instead of
Yelling at Alex was just put on the Cantina theme from Star Wars and dance around
Just dance around behind him
Oh my God
Yeah
I think I
I thought there was something really sad about that
Yeah but then
It kind of hit me that
You know that electric
That you didn't
Winfield when he walked in
Into the room
I know.
Splits
You could kind of get a little bit of that sense
When he was in front of those key
Yeah there was there
It wasn't
The vibe in the room didn't change
Because he didn't
Turn himself on
Yeah like he can just turn himself on
Randolph and whatever if you just
I'm here I'm just catatonic
Or whatever
He's a vile mean
After the I don't know you couldn't
You couldn't see this be
Because you left
The courtroom
But on the feet
After the opening
Sing the lawyer essentially said you know
I think we've got half the jury
Because he's amor
Sure and then
And then well I listen to him talk
You decide
And then Alex
He wasn't optimistic those props were going to fly
That's true
I meant Alex looks directly at the feed camera
And then
Gives it
Finger guns
Straight up
Double finger guns and laughing
Like
Wow I feel like if it wasn't Alex Jones and it wasn't in a courtroom
I could kind of dig that
Yeah I wouldn't I would have appreciated it more if he had done that to the judge but I think that would have gotten him a charge now let me sink
Now what
Yeah
Yeah from what I understand from what you were saying that there was a bit in
A bit of things
You can see in the feed cuz they didn't realize that their mic was on
We're still on because you can hear half of what they were talking about hopefully not anything like important strategy-wise
I mean there were some things where if you
Really
Dug-in in like tried to
The catch
Cuz you can hear just like little bit
Bits and pieces of
And there they were
Some things where you're where I really did think that
I don't think they want this
To be public
Brunswick they want this on the street
Transitory feel about that to that cuz you're not allowed
How to record
Any of that stuff ever have clips of the
Anything
Yeah
It's 1 in the morning
Now
Because I was
Sort of
Ballpark
Working it when I said
We have to get to the courthouse tomorrow morning
And I'm excited about that
That would be more witnesses and I think they three is going to be
No more interesting
Victim
Alex probably won't be the
And I think that'll create less of a like
Severe discount
Well the judge
And the lawyers were were very clear that Rob is supposed
To be there tomorrow
Well-liked
He is supposed to be that we will see if they will do as you
If so
I hope he's wearing his Kangol hat
Yes I wonder how tall he is in person
I wonder if the room changes when do
What is do it like
You don't know it but he has like
Just just
Animal magnetism like everybody's
Music holy
Watch out this is like a young built
Quinton walking into the room he can
Breaks out of snacks
Search wailing on
Hopefully you get this audio fixed
Because
I would I would like
To be able to place
Some clips we're going to do our best
I don't feel like we're at our strongest when we're
Just relaying
We're we're having
We are left
Stat just relaying
Until I think it feels a little bit different since but I'm
Which is not to say that Clips are any sort of
Crocheting
So much as it is
We're just not practical
100 episodes in yunos kind of have a have a rhythm have some things that are you stupid
I think the audience has become a
Custom to I agree
And they'll be back
But yeah
You have any any other thoughts about today
Experience thus far I will tell I will tell one story that
When Alex walked into the courtroom and its security.
Detail followed
Yeah yeah
Two of them went and stood at the
The back of the room
Right next to me where I was sitting in the what I'll call up
And
I looked over and I saw their their earpieces and I was like
Oh my God are you guys out
Security detail do you want to sit next to me
They did not respond
And then went and sat over on the other side and just started
Talking amongst
Themselves that every now and again look
Looking back at me like I was a threat
Very scared
Is not happy about it you are sweating so much trouble already
Where I'm not supposed to be unless I'm going to go to
Jail that's the way I feel
Think of it usually why people are there
So in my head I was already
Going to be accidentally convicted of Alex's crimes
And then
Former Blackwater motherfukers like
Former Blackwater
The house is fun but that idea that you like
Man
I screw up
This is all going to be about me
Pictures of elaborate trap
To God it is nice to think that I'm
Jordan you're so ridiculous
Me
Sweet sweet intersection of narcissism and anxiety
Quizlet
My name is George
So
We have a lot
To enjoy over the coming days in a week
There'll be episodes
Probably more regularly than normal but also
I don't want to
It all depends on how good you are
I know it's on his way
That is
The issue coming down to me
So hopefully
I will for once in my life
Step up to the plate I certainly hope you're not sick like
He struck out
Brutal but we have
Glenn Greenwald and Alex Jones doing Q&A
I'll get that, no yeah we got Alex's War
The documentary about Alex coming up you got it we got some probably can have somebody with some folks
Here are some folks here why not talk to him
Maybe I'll find Rob do tomorrow and
Be drawn in by his Charisma get a job at Infowars it happen
Sit right next to Alex and you'll keep him
We're getting sued
That's your job it's just a bite him whatever he says something scary
I feel like
From a monetary perspective that might be worth it for
Several hundreds of millions of dollars
Depending on the judge
K.c. price is not cheap
No
Look like someone who you want to buy
Anyways
I guess we'll be back
But until then we have webs
ND we do it's knowledge right.com
Amigo I'm Leo on dzx Clark
I am right behind Alex I'm standing right there don't turn around
Alex