Goddamn important
I have great respect for its knowledge B
MoneyGram
What's fight.com
Hotel room far away from talking about Alex Jones
What's up
How do you feel about your desk cuz mine's broken
OU in your hotel yet
No I did not walked in there broken
Hey I don't buy it
Fair enough but what you write about for today by breaks a Jordan is the good people at Nora bar
How did Evan Louisville Kentucky Louisville or some people pronounce it if you're ever out there the best karaoke
A bar that side of the Mississippi Heroes of the day I swear to God you don't even know
We had
The more technical problems going to put out an episode yesterday Thursday Friday
We have two heads
Fun stuff to talk about bud
I could not get it done
Really f***** up it was
It was looking good
For a minute
Emma and it all just fell apart it is a proposal to call this a war because we did win
A lot of battles battles
Sometimes were we were so close and that those battles over the appearance and feeling that we had
Goodwin those battles overthrow Charles
Then I get it
Like the war ended with
He's not wrong attorney
Proprietor of rebar
Be not help Ranger John
And he helped us out hooked it up and now we've got our
Equipment all set up and I'm not touching
Goddamn
Honestly think we should move a little bit further away but I could be in the other room
Worried that there's going to be some kind of a like electromagnetic field that I give off the
Personal 11 Cruise outside they're putting out of the MP
If you are in Louisville
Anyway what's your bright you know there's no bright spot brighter than finally getting to do this show.
William
We are
Recorded almost
Central shows yeah pretty close is been a little bit like edging
Butts
Like if edging was with knives you know like it really really hurts and now to be here talking to you
You
Spectacular and knowing that we have a thing in front of us
Yes
Jordan today. Here's the old six that we find ourselves in
Quite honestly I forgot to get to walk shout-outs and I think I'm not going to don't worry no offense we have been
Jumping through a lot of hurdles
Spoiler alert
It's almost midnight till what time it is in you don't want to know when we had
You don't want to have any idea no no keep that to keep that s*** far away from you and let me deal with it
Let's Pretend so Jordans today we are going to be talking about
Alex is war
The new documentary that has come out
Comes out today
What how did you possibly see it on some people have accused me of being a witch and let's just say that
Did you see in your crystal ball and watch it from a discharge gave me a vision of this documentary when I was four
It's raining right
I'm helping him support So bolsonaro regime
I'm watching of this thing and
On this bad boy
The comes out today
Accurate 100% I assume well here's my first thought
Oolong
It's 2 hours and 11 minutes
Max Rim that baby up Max actually if you're doing the theatrical release these people sit and watch Alex with that
Long I was well
I will let me tell you this right now Dan
When I was in the courtroom today
People watch Alex's show for a full hour
How did you think they did
I was watching the stream of that
And they I mean
Your tweets about one of the jurors who was writing notes
When I saw him when I saw him writing
So diligently he like really cared and then it one moment you could see him stop and you're like yep
We've all gotten a realized I don't need
Weird
This
This is going to be something and I will say actually interesting Lee contacts drop from
Documentary of some of my feelings about this documentary fairly well
It's always something
Pretty close to to my feelings I think you are
Is that a deepfake Shallowford
So like I said this thing is too long
There's a lot of problem
But
In advance of this documentary coming out there no one to bring this up there have been some people who have maybe Sho'nuff
You too many of their car
And discussing this documentary
Some of these cards have been a little difficult to interpret they were
But they were shown all the same
Glenn Greenwald who agreed to do an embarrassing Q&A event
At the premiere of this film where he interviewed Alex
As a promotional event
For the movie
We're going to cover that Q&A on our next episode so I'll leave some of my more specific thoughts on the side for a moment
And then you had Matt Taibbi
Who posted it
Diculous post on his substack where he appeared to just want to scold people
You think this documentary is bad
I honestly don't know his full argument because apparently the full thing is behind a paywall and he can f*** right off with
But you get the point
Just from the free version
This is one of the more particularly pathetic passages in that
Pre Trump era it was understood reporters weren't supposed to avoid ugly or scary topic
We were supposed to Dive Right In
And they didn't the non-judgmental manner of doctors figure them out
That was the job but somewhere along the line it became too taboo to ask the usual why questions about the likes of
Or Fortune Surfers or the subject of Moyers new movie
Alex is war Alex Jones
And a while you were reading.
A scolding people who aren't engaging enough with monsters tell ubm's his free section with this
Quote
Journalists now aren't supposed to look too closely at their motivations
And most don't
Wearing in in curiosity like a badge of honor
Moyer look
Referring to Alex Lee Boyer director of this documentary
Years ago where are we
To put capitalism
And I was like man
This guy's got some thoughts and much like Glenn Greenwald
He shoot himself in his mouth
Haven't watch this documentary I can tell you that if Taibbi isn't getting paid to write that he either hasn't seen this film or
He's one of the stupidest assholes on substack
And that is a deep roster of stupid assholes
We'll see through this exploration that this is not a documentary that asks why at any point antiques
Even a concern
The why is entirely constructed by the subject of the film
Alex himself
When you have somebody who's a huge liar and the reason he's divisive is because he's a hateful liar who lies all the time
It's kind of irresponsible to produce a documentary about them that skirts the issue almost entirely
And if it's even addressed at all it would just be Alex saying I'm not a liar which is been taken is
There are no dissenting voices
There is no other side presented at all outside of random people on the street yelling at Alex
In short Snippets of TV host to making fun of him which actually aren't included to provide any sense of balance their there
To inflate
The image of Alex's Noble
Kyusha this documentary sucks
I will save that right off the top of your and I make no bones about it
I'm not trying to
Pretend
To be a
How you be a neutral Observer here's what we need to do we need to bottle you up for another few like before
For our next episode we need to make it impossible for you to record anything so that you're all of your Fury and
Passion and rage
Goes into writing about Matt Taibbi bulshit
Man you are a f****** Dynamo by I don't want to
Go that direction understand intimately
Albert like this
These supposed
Freethinkers like taibian Glenn Greenwald congratulate themselves for Having the courage to support this film is des
Disgusting
Zeidman's gold people for not engaging with what is pure and simple and exercising whitewashing and rehabilitating the image of a
Strategically released at the time of his Sandy Hook trial's beginning
Is an inexcusable activator malice
Or intense delusion
I can accept that it's possible that they think this film presents a very nuanced picture of Ali
And then maybe they are acting out of a place of severely ill will
But I have to say if that's the case
Then they're guilty of the very thing there scolding everybody else about
Not engaging with difficult subjects
The only way to think that this documentary
Experience days
Just showing Alex as he is
Would be if you have done zero investigation on him
It's simply except the frame and gets put in front of you on Quest
Running late
Having spent more than my fair share of time researching the topic
I can say with absolute confidence that Greenwald and Taibbi and anybody else who's not a full-on infowarrior or right-wing
Xalatan says that this documentary
Does a complicated unfair picture of Alex
They're a coward who's afraid to look at Alex's he actually is
Or they've been tricked
Book these people who are trying to rehabilitate Alex's image and make fun and portraits of him more mainstream
Using whatever credibility they have
In some
Perverted exercise of like oh you guys just can't handle dealing with this person who
Google you're afraid of
He's saying things that are dangerous to your your worldview
F*** off
Don't 700 episodes on the cloud
Let it be known
That this
Will go down as one of the most
Righteously Furious weeks
Of any human beings
In the history of the world between you mean Mark Etc
This s*** is
How are we in this room janumet did you hear that the fire department was called earlier today
Oh I was taking a nap and I was woken up by them saying everyone can come back in the building
And I was like you know what this is because I'm
If I were Alex I would say that it was Alex in the info Warriors trying to smoke
Side of the building
McGee said about Chantilly Virginia when he was staying at that hotel pretended that is under attack
I'm going to sell
Say to myself
Neighbors 2
Want to say that
That incident where Alex pretended that the globalist
I'm going to make a lot of points of things that aren't in heat
Also the time that he went bullhorn Bilderberg
And I Canada
Nope not in that they play that no
I know
Here is the beginning of the film and it starts with a One-Shot
Alex
Staring at the camera a much younger man
Hello
Imallexx
Number radio and television
And for many years I've been exposing
The criminal act
Other Global Elite
Also known as the New World Order
My research has
Stop
Militarization of police
The attack on America
National
Destruction of private property
The family
All of these
Institutions
Destroyed
Before
Established
And create their ultimate dream
A1 world
Government
Documentary begins with the clip that was originally the intro for Alex's film Dark Secrets inside bohemian
Grove
It's kind of fitting because although Alex probably shot to prominence mostly through his 911
Conspiracy activity
One of his earliest publicity stunts that he pulled was the whole charade of Bohemian Grove
And what is this documentary Alex's War but another
Publicity stunt
There's a thematic resonance that may not have intended that is made by putting this clip at the start of this
It links Alex's bulshit from his early career to the b******* he's in the middle of trying to pass off and sell you as
As you watch this documentary
In the same way that he intentionally lied about the circumstances of his troops
To The Grove in order to manufacture a false reality that affirms his worldview
This documentary is literally nothing other than Alex Lee Moyer allowing Alex to use her to do that again
Present-day holy dishonest portrait that creates a false reality
Alex's idiotic worldview is affirmed and shown to have been right all along
Based on literally everything of his documentary
Can very confidently say that this is not what Moyer was going for
But it's interesting
If you want to overanalyze it like a lit major
What would you call it like the incidental irony
Stan's wherein you know
If you were making one movie
You could play this clip
But if you were making a movie about that movie you would play that clip and then play like a
Cut over it where it's like
Wrong
Yeah yeah
In this film that kind of have that
That feeling to it
You didn't mean this but it's
That there's an accidental thing here that's being coming across
A little bit like
A little bit late works you watch you watch the documentary about
Cheap Trick
You know and it's like it's so cool that they're alive and then you watched
The Behind the Music in this like
They did a lot of drugs in there all day
You know it's like that kind of feeling oh no
And then things
So the documentary itself starts with some Glamour Shots
Basically of Owen Shroyer at
The steel rallies in November
ABC
And does people yelling at him and what have you in it so it's a good time
4 Million Man March Madness
Business ain't opening to Swan Lake
Did you know that
Dog begins with a bunch of shots of Owen dramatically yelling into a bullhorn World surrounded by a
Haunted security security in the courtroom
Interspersed are shots of people yelling at the Trump fans more less meant to signify the threat of antifa I guess
Justify the ridiculous amount of bodyguards every Infowars person has
Panera Pub
Also this is where the film introduces
It's framing device
The film begins with footage from DC from the Stop & steal protest that happened in November 2020
Would you may recall is the endpoint of Owen stupid Caravan
This is presented as 72 days until the election which will be how all of this is understood
The documentary is I'm sorry not 72 days till the election inauguration
This documentary is a countdown to the point when Biden is set to be sworn in with the flashbacks to point of Alex's career
Ronan in order to I guess pad the runtime
Or something
One and two ecos without saying with their huge chunks of Alex's career that are complete
Completely ignored by the
This film for instance there's no mention of his highly disgraceful Boston bombing coverage
There's nothing about Jade Helm there's nothing about Y2K
These things are countless others
Aren't included because if they were mentioned it would detract from the illusion that this film is trying to construct
X
Like about Sandy Hook are meant to be seen as the rare occasions when he's met well but got something wrong
Looking at the broader picture of Alex's career with to easily reveal a different pattern
Which really doesn't serve more or this documentaries purpose
Through this you see lies that Alex is presenting
And they're being delivered by Moyer with
Literally no pushback and no other perspective being presented at all
At other points there are instances of
Full on deceitful framing that isn't
Entirely the product and how more decided to edit this film
They are intentional choices that could have been made by the director or could not have it was they were making the film
It was up to them
I'm going to do my best to be sure to delineate the differences between these types of deception because
It's important to recognize how this product is actually alive that Moyer and Alex are
Collaborating on
Creative
Whether or not there's actually
Make me look like I've got a giant dick
It doesn't matter
Creating that through both of their right
Alex through lying and Moyer through
Directions
Yeah but here's the thing
Alex is just doing what he always
Does he's a narcissistic liar so what would you expect him to do other than to lie to create a heroic masala
Ology about himself
Moyer on the other hand is pretending to be a documentarian and almost everything in this film is alive that she's tell
Going through framing for a live at she's letting Alex tell
In choosing 2% without any question or any
Suggestion even of any doubt
She is an Essence responsible for all of the dishonesty in this documentary either through intentional choices
Or negligent filmmaking
And I think that will be borne out through the process of our conversation here today
So I'm I'm hearing
That maybe
Is not a good cat
No I don't think so I don't know I don't know all that much about her
Other than tubing on Infowars a bit
She made that a couple times just like
About her documentaries
She on this show that that should alone by itself be like
Oh well then this lady is a month
Western Wear like well we got to find some other credits
The Brute fuse bad
Yeah she made that incel documentary
She was there at the Greenwald kubaneh
And
Hung her head looking at her lap most of Alex's interview perfect
Anyway so it goes on to complain
A little bit
Just dramatic
I had been here since
Since the fake pandemic
Everything shut down everything's locked down
Businesses reported up
Can't even go get breakfast
Pinata wear face mask
Quarantine
What a communist country would look like
Socks
What the Democrats to turn America into Italian
Weird
Doesn't want is a country where his access to luxury and Leisure Commodities isn't anyway restrict
He is essentially translated that into being with Communism is so when there's a temporary shutdown of some businesses because
Cuz there's an active it's killing thousands of people a day
The only way of experiencing that is to say communism
He can't go to the water park so America Has Fallen tomorrow or something
Which is weird cuz I kind of had the APA
Experience most of the liquor
Liquor stores didn't deliver booze until after the
The pandemic so now I feel like you know there were some pause
I'm not saying there were no
Smooth
If they say
Praise God for small beer
So it's important to understand that a lot of the understanding that alexanian floors ideology has of Concepts like ominous
More freedom are painfully superficial and they often revolve around appearance
Princeton's Alex
Constantly talks about the police taping but police and black ski mask
Switches anaesthetic characteristic
He doesn't
Reno tacos frequently about what behaviors would be associated with the police state like
Police determining law and acted with impunity to mete out Justice because
They'll be way too complicated and what it actually does happen
He's generally in favor of it
He doesn't usually have a problem
By maritime law are allowed to kill and execute anybody who'd
It makes
If you think
Real
Not soft
What about if you think realsoft about it.
The optic
When is describing could easily exist in a capitalist country there is nothing that would be stopping that
At the core of the point that's being made is I don't like the bad and scary thing and then they're just naming that thing coming
When is Amore in Alex's case
Multaq martial law
They're basically just signifiers for like
The sign that had whatever on it doesn't matter
Yogurt
I think it's pretty bold of this documentary to start out with Owen complaining about
Emma continues
But I do take it
Tacoma d.c.
Fernanda
Troy
Destroy monuments
Destroyed
Bartender
Churches
And then when we come to town the group of people who have never burned
Never looted never ride it never done any criminal activity
They shut down the whole city
January 6th
We can't go into Park
But the last
Solution destroys they get full access all of it
They get to put their product Capital as follows
America loading Patriots come to town and they shut this city down so
Pretty pathetic in DC I'm not going to lie
Tell me he's talking he's talking about like the left destroying churches in like
Bright around this point I believe is when his buddy Enrique tarrio is spilling black lives matter Banner from
Church and burning it
Yeah and getting arrested
So it should be proud boys
Pick are pictured in this documentary with Infowars personality
It's wall-to-wall
In the first 10 minutes alone Owen a scene with the head of the proud boys Enrique tarrio and Rob do as a chat with
Ahead of The Oath Keepers Stewart Road
Lumi calls brother
You know the wire had a lot of
Former convict
In the show
It's interesting that this documentary has a lot of
Future condo
And not presented as
Dicey weirdos
Stereo and Stewart Road
Is our leaders of groups or participated in organized planning prior to January 6th and stamp charges to dishes
Put their actions attempted to stop a certification to the 2020 election
I don't think any left-wing Grupo in can name has done anything close to that level of rioting
And the leaders of both of those groups are his
Friends
Yeah that's going to be tough to argue around calm the f*** down
These groups do all kinds of Street violence and destruction
Super inconvenient for the Infowars narrative so it's never happened before
Anytime a right-wing or militia group has done something it
Either been purely
Self defense against the left who actually the real problem
Reality has to be constructed this way because if you don't do this then you'd have to distance yourself from these groups and marginalized
The violent wing of the movement that you've constructed
How much would never do that because he needs these group
He needs them to continue to engage in Street violence and hostile intimidation and they need folks like him and Owen to Justice
The fire to their audiences
By pretending it's only the last that ever Act
Text that way
And this is only considering the group
That are literally in this documentary and Friends of the subjects
You could Branson's up to all sorts of far more militant right-wing groups from the Patriot front caught up
Down the line
You and you'd wind up with the picture that the right has a substantially greater problem with organized rioting and violet
Worse than any leftist community
For the Specter of a
FIFA could ever be saddled with
Well what you're forgetting is the absolutely violent left
This group it came about whenever Crayola
Put
The the peach
Cran as
Skin tone antifa
Granteva yeah I'm going to I'm going to live with that one I'm going to call home that's by
My friends and family are going to know about that one
To change the mood I should tell you that there was a guy who was walking behind oh and it just point it was wearing the Trump flag as a shot
Fantastic
So
That's fine
Scott's 20 and being interviewed in a black
Cowboy hat
In a hotel room
I don't know about we live in a great world
I don't know much
About cowboy hat sizing
But it feels too big
Stupid I'm not a neck
Expert
Chemically neutral
Prospective you say
Can you sing covermade is corrupt
Lights 90%
People are dying
Do you think
That mainstream media's
Again
Happy birthday
But green
Saddle you can convince people
Chianti music
Otherwise Alex Jones will differ
Retired
He would have said that the new thing that replaced the mainstream media was lying to them
If you got Miss wish in 2008 and Ron Paul have been elected president he would have done his whole deep State thing back then
Finding Traders everywhere in the Paul cabinet
I suspect the reason Owen laughed when he said Alex would have retired Longo's cuz he knows that's not true
Portable chair
Yeah you hear the music swelling there and because
This is the point in the documentary about 7 minutes and where we see present-day Alex for the first time
This is a choice
This is a hero shot
With the triumphant Crescendo and Alex being flanked by tons of people Marching In d.c.
This is a decision that boiler made as a director to introduce Alex this way
It's almost like he has arrived was like
Let's put
Patton in front of this giant American flag the director had trouble idea that that would make people think
Oh this is a patriotic mat
Yeah no clue
Yeah I would say
Not too great not great for
So this is Alex's second
The first was an intro to him as a
Concept
With the clip
Of Alex from darkseeker
This is meant to instill the message that he's been talking about the same thing for his whole career and he's been prophetic about all this
Stop
The second doesn't enter to him as a person
Evie exist
Hitman Vindicated
Leading agile
Crowd no longer the outskirt Outkast on the
The fringes of society
I have to stress this of these are filmmaking choices
This is how Blair wants the audience to see Alex as he's introduced
And that would be totally fine if this film question that presentation at any point
But it really doesn't
Right
This
His glorification
Right Right Alright problem
I mean it doesn't get more
How how do you live with
Yourself is a question that I've been asking a lot like
As I've watched shitball make argue
Forever now
Wonders
Who's at
How many times have I said there's no bottom
How many times
And yet I look at his brazenness and I think there's no way that's
You know and so with this kind of s*** it's such the same thing there's no
Wait
This is real
Yep we're living in fake town
It's a good thing you brought up something to head to do the trial because we
You will have a trial update on except
This documentary is
Today
So we have
Owen
Introduced
Talkin we have Alex
Triumphant
Man
Leading a charge on the street
And then we get another character and that is
The man with the Kangol hat
Rob do I was hoping for Aragorn
Nobody has
You have to be able to
Adapt very quickly to Everton
I did an interview with couple guys
At one point is
Infowars
They're like very kind of
Apologetic
Annabelle
You going to crowd
I'll show you the most popular
He's the most
People know who I am
Bigger
More
Fedex.com
How you get up
You're going to get moved on the field
And that's what he does
I think I was probably does carry the ball about 4 yards everyday but the problem is it for a really long time he's been
Not heading towards
The endzone he's been like going for yards toward the sideline of any changes Direct
Again
He's been out of bounds for a really long time is what I'm saying
Oh yeah Rob's metaphor is stupid
Answers Rob do himself shown here in his trademark Kangol hat
He got this job through Craigslist which is fun but invite
Experience most of the
The talent on Infowars get their job through winning a contest
Like Willy Wonka for bulshit
I guess
Behind the scenes folks are all just answered the wrong vaguely worded Craigslist ad that doesn't say Infowars on it so you can trick people
Belinda possibly working there
Cuz most people wouldn't do that you know my aunt was on Who Wants To Be A Millionaire did you know that damn I ever said that before
I didn't know that
To do the questioning part
But she did describe to me constantly the
Experience of like
Answering Who Wants To Be A Millionaire questions as the audition
I meant getting the audition and then so on and so forth
That was a more complex
And difficult process than becoming an Infowars
What I mean is
Is fun is they like
Rob do you got his job the same way I almost got
Scammed on a clerical opening
And I answered an ad for a histology lab assistant to my position
In 2009 and I'm still getting him right right right
Going to be my roommate but only if I sent him a couple thousand dollars because
Is he needed
Money to move in with me and he couldn't afford it at the time but it when he got there he would have paid me twice
As much so
You know I almost thought about
But I don't think it was true
Probably not
So here's where Alex comes in in earnest
Speaking to the camera
Laying out the
No no
Everything
That's the way the universe works
There are
Eating forces
That bar
Trying to dominate
And everything
The general public doesn't realize her under
Cremation
Operates
In the info
We call ourselves
He's a performance
So this is as close as you get to any kind of counter point being made at all is just a little little
Slivers of
TV host
That Alex is like so look there's
War around information
That's how we got our name
Isn't that cute
Everything's it reminds me of the whole movies
The thing between Brendan and Coach mcguirk weighs like
Everything is a prison
Brandon Brandon everything's a prison
School
Prison
Our Lives
Friends like this conversation
Prison
My buddy Ryan back and I started comedy together
Columbia and
Always remember is that I had to believe that LOL comedy is essentially an argument
Or a flight
So many good sketches kind of involved people having an argument
Trying to make this point to Ryan
We ended up in an argument though Bike by pauses.
All you have to do is show them Monty Python
Dead bird sketch
And you're like this is,
That's what
Is tonight is the only sketch
Ever existed the only one
So these clips
The TV host
Continue
On his website Infowars
House what many would say our offense
Paranoia for
Somebody who's traffic
Some of the
Tickets
Extensive
Clown
Animaniacs
Media person
Hundreds and hundreds
TV reports
Every major
National program you
Publication
Your mom
That's when you're over the target
Yeah I mean this
This is
An ocean that is going on challenge that all of these people are making these criticisms of Alex
Because he's over the target when in reality most of those clips
That he played where people making
Accurate points about him
Yeah it's it's like
It's just that notion of like you know they laugh at you and then you're right you know that that goes at Gandhi
Laugh at you then they're like watch out for this dude and then they murder you or whatever
Sometimes people are saying that you suck and you're being an a******
Because you suck and you're an a****** Alex is sarcastically saying something that somebody else's
Said that's absolutely accurate
Oh Alex Jones is a racist and you like you can say it sarcastically but still Drew
It doesn't really affect my feeling or whether or not
Exist otherwise we all die too
Well
Alex has a thought on that
This was maybe my favorite part of the documentary
Fairly early are they show Alex behind
He's doing his show
Automatic goes to commercial
This is all
It's no 100%
This is so fake
Rockview comes running in
No Doubt
Did I've ever seen
Galatians
BMO
It's the one by
Violence
Artifacts of protein
He's about to f***
What's that laughing
Well we got to go get them oh my God this mRNA
You're telling me a text protein only
You f****** s*** roll man
Man
Wow Unsolved Mysteries is like
That is the
The greatest
Re-creation anyone's ever
It's a fun fantasy
Open unit even if it were real it's not productive and I don't see anything getting done
But there's no way I believe
That this happened
You know what I feel like I feel like watch this show as much as I have
He is
Like
Drinking or sweating during the breaks
Right he's not doing any like more information on these stories I'm about to rip about
I hate to bring this up because I don't have specifics and I don't remember names and I really don't even remember where it's from
However this documentary does
And it is one where the documentarian gets really close with a bunch of people who committed genocide
And then later over time he gets so close
But eventually the people who committed that genocide agree to reenact
The genocide they committed on film
Right
That is what this documentary should be not like
Have you ever considered genocide is awesome
What about that
Yeah there's some editorial choices that I take some
Serious issues with
The revision of Rob do running and it's so f****** funny is yelling at me another name of that.
No I'm not
I don't remember either exactly
So I
I take some issue with this
Alex
Start discussing his earlier years now this is the
The portrait of a man
He brings up some of his reading history
And I think that this is actually like
Fairly accurate at the end
The river
Where we jumped it before
You recognize Where You Are
High School
Osborn a small town
Reading comic book store
678 years old
What's fun but as soon as I was reading Julius Caesar
It was like this
What is Julius Caesar
When was everything from
All formed
Keep didn't know what it meant
He just kept looking at it
This is Alex's work process
Yeah you know what I mean I don't think there is a more real
Sort of explanation of Alex's information base then
I read science fiction and comic books
And I really love them
And then I saw smarter books and I stared at the
So I skimmed them
And then I pretended this is
You know
Reading it is very similar to what I did I read the Sandman comics and then I look
Looks at hieroglyphic
Fixing I was like well clearly I understand them now
Listen to that album by hieroglyphics
They now know how to read that
OVO amazing
I can't remember any other members
Anyway Alex had some more books that he read
There's a fee
I got really stuck
I totaled or the death's-head
That twice
Kissinger
Timeline
Encyclopedia
The occult
Cover to cover
By Gary Allan
Pretty much accurate
So you may notice that Alexandra really like books about World War I books
You probably think about that
More importantly he's very clear here that he read none dare call it
Conspiracy at age 12 which he knew was accurate
Because he'd already read all this other material which raises the question
What other material
He was a child reading all these history books it didn't actually understand
He was skimming s*** and then he read none dare and decided this comported with his studied worldview so it must be true
I would suggest this is all bulshit
And the reality is that none dare resonated with Alex because he was brought up in an insane John Birch
Society household
In the book Matched up with what his dad had taught him was true when he was much younger
Another important point to bring up yours that Alex is saying that he read that book
He definitely didn't read Carroll Quigley tragedy and hope before that point
Which is why he approaches quickly book solely through the lens that he internalized from none dare call it conspiracy
You'd already consumed the John Birch Society propaganda prior to seeing the actual book
And I strongly suspect that he's never actually even read tragedy and Hope
It's really long long we talked about it extensively and that's longer than the amount of time he's attempted to
I do believe that he's read compulsively about Nazis will say this
I will say this
In that clip
If you'll
The only person
Read the only author whose work he's red
Who has not
Been party to or actively committed a genocide was none dare call it a conspiracy
I mean I think that Gary Allan was pretty in support of Apartheid
Have the power to do it you know like haeringer
Genocide Hitler the road
Vision government's rule true but nobody was like
Let's make him an international sex symbol for no reason
Do you know what I'm saying
Yeah that's true I'll give you that much
So
Alex
Like he just read the
These books got
Got this
World
Expanding
People in his life who helped them peek behind the curtain
Stuff without a central South America after
Vietnam
I actually think that is true I think his uncle was now I don't I don't think I don't think you're wrong that's what he's funny about it
Yeah
My mom that had friends that were
San Francisco
Psychedelic research
MK Ultra
My dad and Friends
Cashless Society the plan to bring up the
Family at all this
Grew up seeing autumn
Behind the scenes
You could refute this clip by confronting Alex with his own words
Or with other pieces of information that are publicly available
For instance you could say that Alex's dad didn't have a friend that was in the John Birch Society
His daddy been a member himself since College in a given speeches at JBS events
It wasn't background noise that was the operatic score of his childhood
Or you could bring up various versions of this stuff that he's pulled on his show over the years
Like what his dad actually a CIA dentists
What about the part where his dad was the smartest boy in Texas in the global
Just tried to recruit him into their depopulation
Conspiracy when he was 18
These are things that I was bringing up in this documentary because this is a forum where he's kind of wanting to be taken seriously and that's
Sound like a guys making s*** up all the time
Because he knows that there's a
The chance that people who don't
Already like him will listen or watch room
Of these book
Books from the John Birch Society and also John Williams wrote The Imperial March
For the John Birch Society and I read all the science fiction books that I should have blurred with his number of society books
Just turned it all into
Some people would say
So Alex gets further into his life
Those younger life
And there's there's just
Straight up
Problems
With this towel
Outside
Texas
Whataburger
National TV
Lived in Rockwall
Dallas
See like a famous preacher
Rolls-Royce
Stop
Prostitutes brass
We would go to her party
You see the police
Pull up
Off-duty uniform income in in
Shelbyville drugs
Because
It doesn't sound real
I bet it was
Alex tells that story all the f****** Spotify
He's one of the very few stories about his younger years that he tells constantly in mainstream Outlets because it allows him to protect himself is
Somebody who
Sniffing out corruption
From the youngest of Ages
Here's the thing though
On his show he tells stories about the super-rich people all worshipping the devil and then trying to lure him to join
Them in Satanism by offering him sex with their daughter
There was a real serious devil worshipping problem in Rockwall that Alex was on the wrong side of
They wanted to recruit him desperately because Satan had communicated to them that I was going to be very important
Forgot the plans in the future
We notice from Alex is telling of his Youth and this raises an important question was that
Did Alex tell the documentary crew this
If he did that it's safe to assume that he was self-censoring because he knew that if he said that s*** he would look like a lunatic
He did say that stuff and we're decided not to include it
That means that she's censoring her own subject to protect him from appeared to be as insane as he actually is
I can see it going either way but the fact that this aspect of our to self mythology isn't the dress deer is it
Itself inactive
Censorship
Obscuring the reality that Alex creates absurd fantasy stories about himself
To satisfy his narcissism and amuse his audience
Keep them impressed with his exploits
Write this b*******
Alex's story if you allow that
To stand right question it is somewhat
The central problem of our era
With Alex Jones which is that
The we can get the
Distracted by the effect
We can get distracted by the
Cause
We can get distracted by the effect
Before the cause that led to the effect
But the reality is that the
Cause before all three of those
Please everyone involved is insane and we're all wasting our time with the others
If that makes sense to you it does I mean like
Yeah it's
It doesn't not resonate it's convoluted sure it's not great
Yeah
But I would still some more stories about his younger days
He's also hit very familiar themes that we've heard before
Dallas Cowboys
Fight
Extremely vile
Extremely Loud
Shot
Travels
Cars
Change the movie
Episode Alice was crazy
Rebel Without a Cause
You better learn to kick some ass
Fighting
I got quite a few times
I would support judges
Hospital
Dinnerly bad
And those words
Because
Victim
Wright also doesn't match various versions of Alex's violent fighting years that we've heard from various
Sources including Alex himself
For one thing Alex's story has always been that he uncovered a conspiracy
A secret drug-dealing gang within the Rockwall Police Department
And because of that the cops threatened
Kill Alex if he didn't leave town
This is why is dad moved them to Austin according to his consistent telling of it in the past
Why so different now
Possibly because his other stories completely absurd and no one outside of his audience would ever believe it for a second
Possibly because Alex knows that this documentary is meant to region ton indoctrinated audience
It'll be bad for business if he scared them off of his normal bulshit
Allowing that to stand on question is not up to the job of making this documentary
Either through negligence or biased she's allowing Alex to contradict himself and not address
That's bad filmmaking it's bad storytelling and because the audience isn't made aware of this glaring credibility problem
Alex has
It's an act of sanitizing and presenting Alex inaccurate
And it's dangerous because the audience
It could be
Susceptible to that can you imagine
If in the Glenn Greenwald
Qna Glenn was like
Alex
Tell us about the time that you was a
The fifteen-year-old
Uncovered a drug-dealing ring
Within the police department of your hometown
Tell us more about that in the documentary
What are the greatest stories I think I've ever heard and it's a part of your whole knitology about being a guy who's not afraid to stay
Stand up to power at a young age
That's what
Turn him onto the idea that power is corrupt and all this stuff yep
And now you just left Rockwall cuz he got in a few fights
The f*** is going on here
Also Alex Memorial probably should have asked Alex about all the people he claims to have killed
Couldn't hurt to ask about how he constantly talks on air about how is mostly black people attacking him when he was younger because he was white
Any of this stuff would be super relevant to presenting Alex accurately because
The awareness that he constantly lies about himself
Is very relevant to a documentary where the main source of information about Alex is Alex himself
By not addressing his credit a credibility problem in any way
Alex is allowed to be seen as a credible narrator
Which is a choice
That motor is making
How about how she directed the film
Maybe because
She wants to lie for Alex or maybe because it's easier maybe she's lazy
I'm surprised they didn't have the quote where Alex says
Is that no black person has ever
Experience racism from white people more
Then he is
Experience racism from black people
Surprised that didn't make it to the
To the documentary that one seems really
Like foundational you know these dreams
Dissonant depictions of his younger years may seem like water.
Down versions of the stories he always tells right
Kind of mint
Trick people into thinking that he does not have complete bulshit artist maybe you can listen to him and it's not
Not really is not really as insane as people say it is currently this
Documentary feels like a massage for Alex with a happy ending
I think I'm putting it delicately and and mildly
Far more than that it
It's filthy
It's the first time I've been mild to you it's like it's like a month at a hedonistic swingers real
Resort
Fehlig unfailing you god dammit
Oh no
Goddamnit Bohemian Grove
So Alex Goes To Georgia cuz he was looking
How it went down to Georgia looking for an election to see you
So when he went he went to Georgia I wasn't on his regular show
And water things that happened was he went to the Olympic rings statue
Shoot a little video about it all out
Downtown Atlanta Georgia
Sandra
Bye
Hitler absolutely did not design the Olympic rings
They were designed in June 1914 by a French dude named Baron
Pierre de coubertin
The reason Alex is confused is because Leni Riefenstahl made a documentary about the 1936 Olympics that involve going
Going through Greece and making a prop that look like an ancient object resembling the ring Sim
It's 1984 Robert Barney Sports historian found it
They mistook it for an actual Olympics
Symbol not knowing it was a Nazi propaganda film
So the association with the design and the Nazis of the product of one mistake and sports historian
Propaganda film
I'm willing to bet that Alex got it from the ladder
Pienso Que
Kind of just making up the part about Hitler designer
That's
Silly
I'm sorry but
If I told you
Third degree of the Olympic side would you agree
Also I believe that that Olympic
People is there because of the bombing of the Atlanta Olympics
So I also not a documentary about the Atlanta bombing
Of a relatively
Long f****** movie too long
Yeah so this is my second favorite part of the documentary
I'll explain the guy on the street front-loaded it
They might
So
Guy on the street outside the Olympic rings
And
This guy is chill as hell he seems pretty cool and Alex tries to
I don't know what point you're trying to make here
You don't hear yet
But we've
Okay make it answer
Everything holder
Good
It's hard to assess what Alex wants to say but based on the words he's using I think I get it
He's arguing that Hitler designed as a logo but it doesn't
Stanford Nazism so even though it has a bad history it's now good so we shouldn't tear it down
This is actually him talking about the statues of Confederate generals the people wanted to take down but he's making a convoluted
Good point
He doesn't think the Confederacy was bad
So the history of those statues isn't bad
Alex
In what way is something like a Confederate generals statue become a symbol of something good where is in the past
It was bad
I don't know how like
Bedford Forrest
Has now become a symbol of something good
Well well well
Burnside
Now we got sideburns
Confederate general
No idea but I'm going for okay I don't know if you want I don't remember
Ambrose Burnside suicide he was on
I'm going for it
Also third problem Hitler didn't design you
That's really the Big Brother favorite my favorite part of that clip is just the
Cleat
And perfect logic
Of the person responding to it where it's like
Hitler design this flag
Sweet
Bad flag let's get rid of
Oh we taking it back and now it's a good thing
Sweet
That's awesome it's a good thing let's keep it up so you don't want to keep it
Man I'm confused
Figure your s*** out
Okay
Goodnight
You don't like
You also want to keep it man figure your s*** out and then
Come back to me
Volkswagen was founded by the German Labour front which was a Nazi organization back in 1937
The existing labor unions have been raided their leaders killed and they were taken over by Nazi groups and belabor front began
Hitler absolutely did not design the first Volkswagen cars although he may have made some suggestions as to
Little design features
I don't care who designed the logo because you know he has that artist
The past and also
The original design is way different than it looks now
It's a notably missing be lines around it that look like a swastika
Swastika.
So it's hard to say if Hitler invented highways
Because I don't know what Alex means by Highway
Using some definitions if a really stupid client that Alex is making
Like there were highways like the ones we understand that predate Nazi Germany so that point doesn't stand
I think I was just misunderstanding that Hitler was involved
With the construction of the Autobahn
Hitler created the Pony Express
That's what your middle or invented mail
Cool
Maybe I should have done a better job of reading all those Nazi books he loved his kid
Superbad
So Allie Alexander is here in Georgia
Holly Alexander in a movie
Purporting to be positive or they'll kind of have to because he was a big part of Alex's trip to Georgia
Troy.
So you're going to include Georgia at all it's going to be hard.
Well olly Alexander
Coordinator
Stop steel movement
Together
Critical juncture
Tell folks all over doing
High Noon
At the Georgia state capitol Alex
Patriots
A marching and we're telling
Stop
Certify
Kind of like you did
Yeah stop doing certified
2 affidavit
So while they're in the Statehouse they are in Georgia
Somebody else who's along
With
Alex
And Allie
Has an idea
And that is essentially like 8 we're already inside let's just not leave
Aan idea that his
Has never been tried
Before a protest history
Is it ever happens it's a peaceful noncompliance
Here's the valley has to say
We're inside
Let's not leave
Listen to me.
Jacob all the ideas
Decide to fly
Listen to me
Stop Steel
Official GameStop certification
I'm just talking out loud
Fascinating for two reasons
The first is that what Ally is saying is that you don't get a say in what the plan is
He's the brains of you hillbillies are the bodies
This isn't the life there's no democratization of ideas
It's a hierarchical system or Ally calls the shots and you follow
That sucks
And I can't believe that didn't piss this guy off and it's funny to watch Alex try to smooth things over
I mean
You know
It just doesn't get better than being like
If we let the hillbilly set the rules we're going to lose
Is the country I don't know if
If you know
Cool
Dior
Leading no but that's a lie I hear he's an elitist with that like
Better than all of those people very people that he pretends
He's supporting overalls are slightly cleaner obviously I'm of higher status
Second thing
So weird that is documentary really tries not to point out that Nick Fuentes is right there with Alex and Ali
No Spotlight on the Holocaust denier buddy that you brought along to Georgia
No shout-out for him no scream time let's just pretend he's not there
That's another editorial choice that motor is making
Because recognizing that Fuentes was traveling with Ally and Alex
Is way too much for this documentary driving
Explain tween on indoctrinated audio
It's inconvenient to the portrait of Alex's it's just ignored
Be at the little baby Nazi isn't there
Explain to me how they could fit that in in a 7000 hour documentary
There's no way there's no way you just it said look
Even Avengers had to cut
Some stuff yeah I know you know what you do make a good point because they needed to fit in important things like this from Florida
Bucket list
You got five kids that says you shouldn't have any
Oxy Udonis
He peed on the Georgia Guidestones would not be happy with that
Alexandra pissed on the Georgia Guidestones
Oh my God
Of course
Alex's urine mixed things explode
We don't have evidence that somebody else blew it up but we do have evidence
Alex
Heat on it I believe there was a car that they sell.
Alright
Alright so your point is fair maybe someone else just ignited
Exactly. Then accelerate
He tried to smoke a cigarette a little bit too close went up big night the night before
Bottle whiskey
Alex Reeves from the side one of the
Guidestones
This is in a foreign language
This probably isn't defensive
I mean it is
What
I don't actually know who he's trying to offend
You're right
My mom
Tupac Makaveli
Their plan is called the Great reset
Operation
Agenda
Public um playing
In the name of world peace of stopping hunger
Practice shutdown the world economy
And will cause massive
Depopulation
This is
The most
Dart
Savannah Cardiology
Ever B
Here's an interesting question of a documentary filmmaker could have asked
Hey you're saying this agenda 2030 thing is the blueprint for how the globalists are going to kill everyone but isn't that exactly what you
You said for like the last 20 years about Agenda 21
Is it possible that the whole thing was b******* and then in 2021 you know Agenda 21
I came around you needed a new thing to pretend was the plan to kill everyone
Inquiring minds journalism all of that I mean I guess you could just say
Alexei all this s*** unquestioned event agenda21 never
Comes up that's another option
Yeah well I do feel like
The direct
You can get away with this
Mainly because
The first
Peoples that I
Think should be offended by Alex
His impression
Are All Star Trek aliens
And then we get to regular human people
Do you know like there's a bunch of different alien races in Star Trek that would listen to that and be like
This is unacceptable Behavior we got to get to Captain
Singkarak we got to deal with this quick
Because
Is this is f***** up
Yeah I don't I don't know I don't know what Alex was on there
About but
Don't
Not good
Alex gets into talking now but his early media days
Embark on another flashback
And
Here's some bolts
And it was very classical liberal
By that I didn't know if I was Republican or Democrat
Things I liked about both parties
The average real liberal
Like new law health food and was anti-war
What's free speech and seemed really inform it cool
For a while I want that job
What's the temperature
TV
They're like rock and roll shows
What Christian shows like
Old ladies doing exercise shows it was and it was everything
Like we don't care what your speech
I saw it was local poker
They were talking about New World Order
World government
So some people might think it's shity for you to bring up that abortions
I hope they don't accept that attract what I would say to that
It doesn't come up Alex doesn't bring it up normally I would say personal business
Whatever no big deal listening to Alex that he is presented that as a
A pivotal moment in his life
Yep when he realized he needed to get his s*** together and fight the globalists after his dad told him stop killing my grandkids so
That should be a moment that is a
Impactful enough nature
That it should come up in the retelling of his
His wife
They're based on the details that he's given here and it doesn't it's suspicious enough that you are going to argue
Do to me that a man can tell the same story for 20 years about his Origins
About abortion and s***
And then gets
To go into a documentary and just to Omit that as though it never happened
And that he doesn't have to deal with it
Then
We don't get
To talk anymore
Weird
So it wasn't the classical liberal any he didn't have like he liked the life when he was
Younger
And if he had complaints about the right-wing they weren't far right in
This documentary is allowing Alex to present himself this way on question because it doesn't work for their purposes to treat him
Extreme right-wing ideologue
From early on in life
It's far more attractive to presentable somewhere that's kind of in the middle and licked all sorts of political ideas pretty
Who's driven towards the right by the
Stream fanatic on the left or no longer Free Speech they don't like health food
Above the left-right paradigm
This is a decision that boiler is making because she wants to make her subject more attractive to a non-exclusively
Extreme right-wing audio
It's a deception by omission
And allowing Alex 2% things on
Challenge
I mean look here's the here's the bottom line 2
She has every right to do that
If you want to make a documentary that is a puff piece nonsense b*******
Indoctrination
Whitewashing and sanitization
Of Alex Jones
But I'm not going to put up with it for a f****** second
Right that's fine
I can do this
Go to pretend that this is some kind of a like
Middle-of-the-road on
Just let him tell his story thing
Is nonsense
Right now
I agree with
But honestly stip
Bulate that
She can do this in the world that we live in now
And not one that is good
And well we don't need to argue about what the limits of good or bad are on
Feature etcetera
I think we can both agree that
This is bad
Sylveon
Yeah yeah
You're going to see it you see here another editorial choice that I think is really glaring and that is the swelling music accompanying
Alex's decision to get into covering conspiracy theories on the New World Order
You can hear the feelings it's intended to to be a laid there
The clouds are parting and Alex sees his
Half
That's not something that's being conveyed by Alex's words
It's being stressed by the musical choices and directorial decisions that Moyer is making
Because that's how she wants the audience to see Alex
There is a moment in a new hope that I hope every single human being on this planet remembers where
Luke Skywalker
Is on Tatooine and he looks at the two suns setting and the swelling John Williams music play
Plays to a point that
If you're not inspired by It Go fuc yourself
That is what she's trying to do here
Alex is not Luke Skywalker
Also based on your misspeaking I just thought of a socialist Star Wars characters Luke Skywalker
Somebody who else has a bit of a worker comes in now
He's a former friend of Alex
I guess they're still fresh
Pecos Way Back
We are descendants from Davy Crockett
This is myself in my wife
And if you go all the way over
My 4th great-grandfather was
Nathan
Ethan Crockett which is
Is the brother of Davy Crockett
In my 5th great-grandfather was his father
Man lot of Davy Crockett
Who is Mike Hansen
Very few non-current Infowars employees who's allowed to
Speak in this documentary
He was Alex's original cameraman way back and was a long for their fake infiltration of Bohemian Grove
There's a reason he's included as a talking head in this film and other folks
Art and that's because Alex
It's still
Very beloved
To Mike Anthony loves Alex
He has a huge room full of
Pictures of Alex and archives of all their stuff including the shirt and shoes that he wore
When they went into the Grove
Full disclosure I want those tapes that he has but the difference is that I want to create an archive of Alex's career that could be used by Reese
Deconstruct Alex's body of work
Mike has a giant shrine
Priebe know it in a Bill and Ted situation
You are George Carlin coming back from a perfect Society being like okay
If I get this s***
And take it back to the future
Then we will have a successful world
So Mike is in the spelling because he's a voice that can say that Alex is not only great now he's always been great and I would
No because I was there
Including this voice and not other voices of people who were there and are now critical of Alex's an editorial choice
On Moyers
Part
She doesn't speak to other people who are there when they went to the Grove like Jon Ronson or Alex's ex-wife who didn't go into the Grove
With them but was along for the trip
The selection of voices that are allowed in this film
Is curated to create a particular image of Alex
And people who are actually critical of him and know it would threaten that image
So they don't take
And that
Is her choice
Yep
Clips of Alex from early early on in his life
And this one is weird I don't know this is a weird thing to keep in
Yeah it's Alex Jones baby
Serious
Today
We're talking about how they got us
The body
Bobby Front Page News at Fuzzy's
Seller said something race
Even though he's an old
Fat rice
Who cares about old fat race
Something about an awesome
Man
Asian
African American
He's worth probably hundred million dollars
American
Bro
Strange disease earliest video of Alex's minimizing racism
Hey
Who Among Us
Cannot go back in
In time
20 years
And say to themselves that yes
This is a country divided and it should be okay to be racist towards tigerwood
Who Among Us
Right
This is
Years before Obama allowed us to be racist towards the president
So it's so weird to look like oh 1997 was Alex doing saying racism is not a problem
The country is divided 1997
I don't know if anybody's ever heard that
Sure
Right now
We're here at the Alfred
4 p.m. building
In Oklahoma City
The site
April 19th
Bombing
And there's a lot question
A lot of fun and
Answer questions
Like why is the media ignored
Seismograph
Report from the University of Oklahoma
Logical survey that show
Two distinct
Explosion pack
Why have they ignored
The first one reports people on the ground as what
And I'm not sitting here claiming to have the answers
But I know this
They don't want you to know
They're keeping something
From you
They've done at 8
Intimidation of witnesses
The covering up evidence
This is Charity at work
One way or another
Either
Exploding this terrible tragedy
Or they were actively engaged in
Yes
Federal
This clip is just Alex being Alex man he's got a conclusion and he's going to accept whatever have cooked pieces of information you can find
Find a justifier
We talked about how the two explosions and seismograph thing is bulshit back on an episode about Bill Cooper so I'm not going to get into it here book
Working with Alex's doing
He's got an inaccurate piece of information he doesn't fully understand and he's using that lack of knowledge on his part to insist there
Must be a
Conspiracy
Because of this inquiry
Direct information there to possibility
Either the government did this or they're covering up who did because they let it happen
There isn't a third possibility to him
Never considers it mats
There's almost always the correct one that's what he doesn't know what he's talking about and he's wrong
Yeah this is the same s*** with this Sandy Hooks.
Hold it was based on incorrect information that he decided to accept his true
So he could claim there were anomalies with the shooting that would justify him calling it a false flag
You can pretend that the government has used in mass shootings
Pushkin
Control
He's kind of a one-trick pony and that one trick is being wrong
Yeah
Behaving flimsy justifications to rationalize being wrong
Man
You're right
Sometimes it sometimes it would be nice if I had something insightful or funny to say but sometimes
It's just like
Yeah
Let's hear the truth happened about that what a weird thing to have late
You know I think that on one level
Hey it more competent hands in a actually
Well put-together documentary
I have stuff like this
And you could juxtaposer
With stuff about Sandy Hook
And you could make the point
Even without grilling Alex too hard
This is the same s*** that he does all the
The times
That documentary
This one does not do this
That is not that documentary The behavior that he's displaying in Oklahoma City is
Looked at as
Good
I mean a softball interview
Proves Alex is a month
It is only a tee-ball documentary that allows Alex to exist the way he does
Yep
I was like what
People documentary second now that you get it it's
Super good right yeah yeah it is late the way you were saying it made sense to me I got the price you were trying to
T-ball
Mike
Anson had some words about Alex
Wasn't very popular back then
You were out there is
Pharisees
But Alex made it
More popular because
He was well
Spoken
Professional
He was found like the Dan Rather
Conspiracy theory world
People
People information
So weird how this documentary doesn't even mention the existence of Bill Cooper
It's not just kind of pretending that Alex didn't completely idolized him and pretending that he wasn't
Figure in the anti-government conspiracy world
Bill was already the conspiracy Dan Rather
Alex is a big deal that's fair enough but it's a little much to pretend he was this much of a trailblazer
Recognizing the Bill Cooper existed
Hertz the ability to create the image
That this film wants to paint
And that is that Alex
Entirely went his own way and created this
This whole thing out of his desire to tell truth
In Alex's War
Alright are you swallowing in Bill Cooper's wake
It is
Yeah I mean they didn't bring up father Coughlin
They didn't say that Lord haha They didn't say that like Wolf Blitzer was the Dan Rather of
Of not being Edward Armour Road they didn't say all of those things there's no Keith Olbermann
City Hall
There's always talk about whenever people say that he's a racist and that is like
Clan
Right where I really interesting
When
We were rebuilding it
The Ku Klux Klan come down to Waco
And Alex and Ian
Bullhorn
Guess what Alex was Bullhorn in the clan but it was really more about being defensive about Waco
Disagreement
With the clan so much as like a
I want more attention than the clay and I have baselessly decided that you're all fed
But like really that contact is actually fairly important
When they came to Waco when he was trying to be the guy who's rebuilding the Davidian Church
He's not bull horny McLamb no other times he's bull Horning
Anyone who takes attention from him and it's the Klan is the people who take the attention
Anybody who might
Attract a right-wing Patriot audience
That could steal
Yes yes
What you might call a power struggle right
There's often audience because they're trying to take my
Yes
So I will get Alex and the present-day here talkin a little bit
And this is just so f******
Can stupid
The general public are like
Babies inside the womb
I don't even know what's going on in the outside world
Inside their mother
What's going on
Mad scientist
Trying to steal the future
Probably before they're even born
I'm outside I got out
I'm not totally blind
And I'm powerless
Stop
Even though I can tell people was coming next
It doesn't matter that people just still
They can't deal with the magnitude of
Understand
Yeah these people they put shadow puppets
That's how it works but also the allegory of the
So that's
That's cool
Yeah you know but
I'm real proud of him for having
Kind of
Almost learned a thing about the past that maybe he can relate
A little bit one of the most basic philosophical
Maybe your first class
If your school block you don't expect
To know the first principles of philosophy
Fine
Fair enough that is true
So there's more of the past
Things about Alex going to Bohemian Grove
Alex
Of context
Deadpool costumes
Spectrum down an ISDN line 280
Million listeners
Alex place
Bohemian Grove
Pitmasters
To control the world's government
Thanks the media
And the United Nations
The clip of Jon Ronson
From the secret rulers of the world
Displayed I'm not talking to himself
Right there is
Video
That shows like b-roll
Shows of his interview on C-Span
Lied about what happened to provide growth
Play the audio of it at all right there's no dissenting opinion everything is
Just reinforcing Alex's
Perception even if there are things that are very clear indication
That you should have access
To the information
Get makes you responsible for
Pushing back on this other.
Right
It's fun that the jet
Text position of
John and Alex
Makes you think that the British
But then Piers Morgan comes in later and do it
It's not a bad
Navigate to 2001
Hello ladies
Gentleman
So glad
Join us
Jay
For this
Wednesday July
25th two
Broadcast
Open the glow
The globalist want to bring down and they will use terrorism
As a pretext to get it done
So this is his prediction
911 show
Yeah and this documentary is pretending a Bill Cooper doesn't exist so there's no reason to explain that Alex just stole this prediction from Bill
This whole section of the film is a really long greatest hits
It's of Alex's career that's meant to paint him as a
True Renegade
Going against popular
Need to tell the truth
About these tragic events
It covers things like OKC Waco and 911
But it's just surface-level s*** like Alex saying this thing is a false flag and then Alex in the present-day was a boy that sure was a
False flag
It's meaningless
It doesn't talk at all about the details of stuff like how Alex up the EU did 9/11
Then we have Bohemian Grove in there but you don't really have any mention of reims
I'm going on C-Span discussing how Alex
Submitted to in the day he was lying to his audience about everything
It even worse
This documentary just ignores so much of Alex's career that doesn't fit it's mold
Like what about Y2K
Three larger what about the Boston bomb
That was part of his career and
He got it
Completely wrong
That was an event where he managed to send Dad but dondi to disrupt a press conference at the authorities were holding to inform the public
Book about the situation
While the bombers were still unknown and on the loose
The public was living in fear in patandi was just yelling Infowars.
Cam at the police were trying to
Call the pub
You can make an argument that his coverage of the Boston bombings in like the top five point of his career that
Bear mentioning
Hazel Mission here is glare
And the reason is because it doesn't fit
Do you really get to Hero
Play Bedford hero
The selection of what to cover and what not
The cover is an editorial choice
Whitmoyer is making
Because these things are at the building blocks of Alex's mythology where is things like him being an idiot in gleefully
Exploiting a terrorized City isn't necessarily good optic
Sandy Hook will come up because it has two
Yeah but it's presented as more or less the exception that proves the rule and even
More
But poorly presented and we'll get to that later
It's like the one blemish on his otherwise spotless record
Do you know Alex actually is human
Despite all evidence to the contrary Japanese concept of the flaw that makes something perfect
Yes every mundala
Of course of course
Is Roth naturally
From the past all of these like Oklahoma City
Waco 911 and
Some of them is
Mildly interesting but not really at Stephanie's gone over head nod
So what's your point of addressing it interesting and unique situation
Once again
No one has seen this
Or the people who haven't seen this or unfamiliar with Alex
Have no idea what's going on
And most of our listeners
Would be in
Incredibly bored by us telling that
Regular people
Insane information
Basically the
V
Points of
These things from the past are
Presenting Alex's
Activities surrounding these topics in the most generous and
Thoroughly
So
Get back to the present
What do you know
Alex is a
F****** hero
Call Priscilla
Much of the discussion of the past is framed as things Alex did being on Pop
He got fired
Recovering her Waco
The stories here recovering 911 is a false flag
Punished for telling the truth but he kept soldiering forward
It's important to understand that framing is a critical piece of this documentaries editing choices because
When you now Flash
Back to the fall of 2020 and Alex's at the stop the steel rally
He's having everyone yelled at they love him and all this witch
Is meant to be experienced
In contrast
With how he was treated in the past
This is visually telling the audience that Alex was right all along
And though he suffered hardships
At the end of that road the people realized he was right
This is b******* and it's not the impression you would get if his tour throughout his career treated his career accurately
Did not like an embarrassing puppy
If you saw him fumbling around and saying horrible racist s*** or
Insinuating for months that the bath party were being reinstalled in a rock or arguing that the
The EU did 9/11
We're doing in same s*** about Obama's birth certificate or is Ebola bullshiter
Pizzagate for slandering the head of Chobani
Or have you thought that Obama was a secret Muslim trying to use FEMA to turn the us into a caliphate under Sharia law
For all the times you can sister the Ron Paul is going to win
The GOP Primary
Then you wouldn't see that's mascot to the present day
Disabled
If you understood the clear picture of his career you might see the people yelling out. They love him is
Pitiable people's been sucked in by a con man
But because this documentary only seems to care about
Representing Alex is a really solid information guy
You see the people flocking to him it's meant to look like they finally come around and recognize that Alex is great
This is a choice
Made by the editing
His being gone by Moyer
There's a reason that the discussion of Sandy Hook is separated
From all of this pasta
Because
That's not supposed to be seen as actually part of this
No no absolutely not
That was
That was a blip
That was a
Worst
Rick listen Okay do you remember how that one time the United
It States was running these drills
Right
And they didn't notify Russia of it and these drills would be very similar to ones that you would do
If you are launching a nuclear attack
And Russia because they didn't know that the United States was about to or was not
Going to launch a nuclear attack and only knew that these drills were happening
Decided that what they needed to do
With launching
An actual real nuclear attack
And it was only because of the efforts of 1
Heroic man
That they did not shoot those f****** missiles right
Do you remember that
Nobody even remembers it
Not that important
So Alex
Presentation of him
Sucks
It stinks
And it would not really be possible to achieve
Eve without very intentional choices being made
Absolute being presented
No I mean what how
How is it that we have trouble
Will sleeping at night Dan how is it that both of us
Caffeine alcohol on your part
Dental in Balance Shore
I don't know Patrick
Here in the fall of 2020 and Mike Flynn is giving a speech
Speech speech where Trump flew over in a helicopter
Bucked up
When human rights
McCall's by the media like I've been raked over the coals by the media but my mom says
Sticks and Stones can break my bones but names will never hurt me
Ensenada
Before the media
The New York store
Service to this country
Oh I'm sorry that was a different quote
Was so close
Next president of the United States is Donald Trump
The visuals of this are terrifying
People are looking up at the sky is Trump flies over in the helicopter there's a shot of Mike Lindell looking up like
He's going to cry
There's this beautiful operatic music
Indicating an almost religious experience
The people are having a looking up to the heaven
Moyer toes to play that music underneath his video which gives a very pretty
Nuclear tone essentially the people who view Trump is there saved
But
This documentary doesn't give you
You any reason to think that's a bad thing
The subject of this film is the biggest Trump supporter in the world who cried on air about how we die for Trump
There's no voice in this film that's critical of Trumps of the music
Doesn't really come off as heightening or highlighting something that
Is being commented on
It kind of just
B and the film is treating like
It's bats okay
Yeah this is
Really disturbing I mean the scene itself is disturbing
And then the directorial choices that are made here
Presented in a way that I find
Under
Yeah yeah I remember watching Apocalypse Now I hate that I'm making so many movie references but we
We are talking about
We are discussing a movie and we are discussing a person who's making a movie and a person
He's making a movie like you would make a Hollywood
And so
If I was discussing the scene in Apocalypse Now where someone were to say
I love the smell of napalm in the morning and I were to play the Benny
Hill theme song or
My town
That's alright that's our theme song for the week
Play Feels Like It
It also hasn't been a week dad's Fair
So Alex is at this rally where everyone is culturally looking up at the sky at Trump flying over and there's a moment that
Really disturbing
It's a woman who's trying to climb over a fence
To get a picture without
That clip suffers from the same problem as the last one
Inside this field there's no reason to think it's weird for someone to be comparing Alex to John the
This film is essentially justifying that conclusion by choosing to show what it shows
A woman climbing over a fence to take a selfie with Alex and compared to John the Baptist should be a shocking image
But it should be troubling but in the
Context of this documentary
If you accept the story as Moyer is telling it
Why wouldn't you think that Alex is John the Baptist
He's basically been right his entire career and persecuted for telling the truth about what was coming
Because that proof
Threaten the power structure
This documentary allows Alex
To bring themselves so unquestioningly that it makes sense that this woman views Alex's way
Honestly it would almost be weirder if she didn't
That's f***** up
So when we leave now taking in
A bit of Alex
Hero in the present
Vindicated for all the past
I all the past
Turmoil in trouble
And now we jump back to the
And we get we we pick up here where Alex is
Discussing you showed up at like
A convention
Ain't talkin about how like none of these candidates are good
We're going to leave it at that
Thanks very much
We'll be back with more dingleberry
A few minutes
Of course the floor is empty but they're here and let's beat we be accused of not hearing all voices we cut you off a moment ago this
Texas radio talk
Infowars.com
Candidates are cousins
This is Claire the military-industrial
Was intimately involved
The commission
Complete fraud
We're losing our
Both parties are
We don't wait
Troy giving up Liberty
Only gives us tyranny
It does not give us accurate
But everybody
Wakes up to this
And realized
And Constitution
Everybody should investigate
And find out who's really behind it
Reichstag
Thank you for the planet.
Alex
Going to be a crocheted that's going
Or do you want to be
Multiple jobs
We're looking for
Somebody
Control
Gear
And
What do this
Refuse Fox News
Right before Glenn Beck
They would have article
Fox News with fox
Flashing back to the past
Again but it's important to understand what
Track where on
This is the track that leads to him supporting Trump which has to be contextualized by pointing out Alex's Renegade individual
Melody throughout his political career
Here is talking about a bush and carry both suck
You know it doesn't want to be a part of Fox News
They conveniently ignore is
Constant support for Ron Paul's candidacies because why provide context when you can
Just pretend that Trump was Alex's first love
This is the section where Sandy Hook
Come up because this documentary wants Alex's coverage of Sandy Hook to be understood in a very specific way
Which will discuss when we get the
Also
If Alex has ever taken one of those job offers at Fox
He would have lasted about as long as Michael Savage did it MSNBC
Ship can so fast
He can't play ball
If you do you want
To say with
With the 20th of 20 hindsight
That he knew
What was
What was happening
Is that
He
Spoke
In short sentences
Confidently
Loudly and quick
And nobody knew with that time that that's all you needed to do to dominate the entire American conch
I would argue that sometimes
It was also run on
Well you are not wrong to give the appearance of like an overabundance
Really just killing time until you figure out what the next sentence here's what I'll say I'll say and I want to try and describe it
This way like
Back then
If you were to take her
His words
You could put it into like guitar tablature and you would have
Clearer idea of why people enjoyed it
Then you would if you listen to his words
Do you know what I'm saying yeah
Yeah it might be more rhythmic
Jack Byrne
Exactly tabs
Definite
Call and response history to it
Is the history of bat
Baptist preaching of effective
Of course
Of course so at this point Alex's rejected these deals from from
Fox News he doesn't want to support
Buschur Carey's salute
He's a rogue
Just like us not
Advertising for
He's out in the wild no one he's no one's
Person
But he's also in Waking Life
And so here's a little
It's going to be
Pure something
Creativity
I don't care about Hollywood
My goal was
The band movies my goal was to
Embraced by all that
So I mean like
No mention of Star-Lord
Yeah you were supposed to get there you would have gotten paid before then
How does it not coming up
More than Chris Pratt
This is just meant to be like this rejection of
Of the the mainstream or whatever
There's a world where Alex shows up in Jurassic world like
Dial is a Raptors
A blue you and I are friends
Now come on now
Blue Raptor
Everybody blue
I do remember the other rappers named I did
Open new watch the first of the new ones
I was curious
Yesterday it was fine
So
Alex doesn't like Hollywood
Gates West Coast
Cool
Charlie Sheen was the only
Party
Creepy
Week
Spiders
My soul
Truly on the planet
It resides
Onalaska
He might have just been jet lag
And then also like
You shouldn't be saying if there's a devil
I mean
If there's a devil should never come mere Alex
Yeah pretty stupid
Text my heart
Because that's
Fundamental to his exact
Existence
That is fair
You know it's almost like
Controlled by the Christian devil
Feel like
If your fundamental issue with the globalist
Is that they are
Controlled by the literal Christian
Skin devil
That should also be the centerpiece of your duck
Does that seem feel like I'm not being crazy no no you're totally right
Shockingly little
Interval variable is the cause of all of my problems
No certainly not that very little of his religious fundamentalism at all
News coverage and Topix
Praying on air
You know the thing that he doesn't do
Liberal
I forgot it was our fault they loved a lie
Back window bush
Correct
Oh no
It's fair to say that
The Liberals
Nothing you hear the background that belly of the Beast they played the video of him the Rogue and running around in their push mask
So that was what that was Fighter video
Did the crazy guy in Austin
And that Obama came in
Then at the end there is the Obama Joker thing
Classic radio hits
Blanca
That's available in Street Fighter 11 I think
Welder
Continuing this Narrative of persecution
Chad sticking to his guns
I am behaving like a principal
Like I was the same
Liberals loved me because I thought I hated George Bush but I also write it up, and then they stopped
Above it right
And so you have this path that is being walked
And they flash a clip Up
Of Alex talking
About
The operational lockstep document
Back in 2010
You want both know he wasn't I do know that he was
I mean I'm not even worthy to be bringing you information this powerful
And I hope that you pay attention to
Because I've had chills
Since last night
This just confirms
Everything else
We've already research
Yeah but he's covering the document that is now known as operation locks
It wasn't known as that in 2010
The video that's used in the documentary doesn't come from the original show
But Alex did
The graphics that uses are similar to those in this little Sizzle video that Alex put together on his website
In the Alex Jones
Prediction section
It's meant to show that Alex Jones is right about everything
That's not great to imagine that instead of using primary sources might rely on a propaganda video made by
Infowars
Designed specifically to pretend that I was predicted covid over a decade ago
I probably wouldn't do that
I don't I don't know why I would just use the raw video of Alex from 2010 cuz it's available obviously
Okay I'm going to tell you this
We all watch
But there was a point
At which
The defenses lawyer
Argue
That
The plaintiffs
Making them look
Dumb
Was in fact
A sanction
By the court
Wow right
Now the podiatrist
It's an interesting
To the judge and the judge said back
The only person who's making you look dumb as you
Yeah the only person who can make you look down as you have your choice
It feels like we're here
Does that make
Yeah yeah yeah the only person who can make this documentary as bad as it is a person who made this documentary and I have some
Choice word two hours worth of
So Alex is talking
Asus motherboard
Open 22
And no one's allowed to go outside
They're going to 0 to a trillion miles an hour
We were in the war
Trillium Eisenhower's not possible
That's where my study of his
Aaron's
Because whatever it is or tune into it
Beyond by now
Alex is very frequently talked about our God is giving his visions of everything that's going to happen and that he's a psychic
I'm going to guess that he didn't say that because he doesn't want people who don't already like him to know that he's that nut
Also this is a more recent thing but it's
It's still part of this descent into the past based on him predicting covid back in 20
We're still on that track of Alex being a renegade who has no team
Who the Liberals like because he was criticizing push and then
They stopped liking him when he attacked Obama
That's the main theme of the section that were in
Or the river that were in as Alex would that would put
I am
Frustrated by the
General Vibe I'm getting that
This documentary is Menton
Entirely to rehab Alex
His previous five years of being a
Far-right
Jobs into returning to some sort of
Pre obama-era above the left eye
Bright Peregrine paradigm
Version of himself
Is that what I'm hearing ball I mean I think that's probably one of the goals they would like to explore
I think whatever positive interpretation that becomes of Alex after this is what they're going for
That would be a defensive for me to ascribe to them intent
Because that would suggest
Competence on some level
As good as holding him broke is what it is
He just wants to be good so it's so can go to heaven
Alright I'm so pasta politics
Kid Perfect
Willie
Freaked out loud
Trying to do
Not really.
My wife was God
And I want to get out of the
Fathoms to get real bad
But you were lying lying
I told my son 3 years ago
Unfollow me shutdown song
Is isan everything's over the there's no going to college and that's why I spent your education fund on taking the trip to California evil is
Place on Earth so I can do mushrooms with Mike Tyson
Can you talk about that's all
The f*** out of here with this overly dramatic nonsense
Slug
He tried to smoke his son because he
He thought his son was a toad
After smoking toad
What happened
He was just licking
What does we have found out that's just not how you get high off
Alex's on
So we're through this past of Alex's
Political
Rebellious misses your life and so we get now to the point where he yells at Piers Morgan
Pierce
Why don't you come to America
Do you understand
Suspicious Anna tab Center this is the subsequent
Time when Alex showed up at a Morgan event
Not interested in talking to a man I bet there's no recording of that and there's no way to hear any evidence
I wish I had the time to go through all the archive because
Listen to our show
Bath or
He is I think I think you played it on his shift but I wouldn't ask anyone ever
Do that
So now from there we jump to Trump
Crop top
And
Look
Trump just latched onto what Alex was doing man
The real quick
Obviously the point of this is going to be that he was yelling Hillary for prison and then Trump took that and is good lock her up
But Alex said that he stole Hillary for Prison from somebody's like buffer
Forsake her that he saw
Answer this person is actually responsible for from somebody who's anonymous
Cuz they can't argue against
That's how it work that's a great point
Paradise motel
Banner
Trump tapped into the same populist
Anchor
The same Papa
Worcestershire
I've been tempted
The whole takeover fail
And now
Who gets to talk to the president
Who gets to talk to Supreme Court Justice
Alex Jones
He was a nice guy
Gloves off
Twisting stuff sometimes for playful like
Joke
You like every newspaper run today to yards
Every newspaper
So in case it's not explicit enough here is Rob do laying out that Alex is responsible for Trump being
President
Alex Jones
Matron
Whether anybody
Believe it or not
Spirit of America
He loves it
So here is where things
I would say
Become entirely onyx
Talking about how
You know he basically was what Trump
Surviving off of
Trump liked him
Dropcam on his show Hillary started to get mad at him
And he was going to happen
Huntsville crime
Be the president
And that in raids
The permanent
Bureaucracy
That we know of
The people are so awake I mean I'm not kidding every
When they saw that
They're like oh
He stopped the crazy guy on the internet
Now if you go back
That we could get it
Now we got it
Destroyer
I'm really upset I'm having to be honest
This is no exaggeration the last wave at any self-respect
FileMaker recover the subject matter
Sandy Hook is not coming up as an instance of something really really bad that Alex didn't his career
Something that people are only mad about because they needed an excuse to attack him because he supported
Trump
This is a choice that Alex Moyer is making as a filmmaker
She didn't have to include the Sandy Hook outrage is merely the result of people
Needing to justify hating Alex Joe
I went to Sandy Hook coverage isn't even mentioned chronologically because of the context of this documentary
One thing isn't his coverage
It's the way people got unfairly mad about it because he like Trump
There's no counterbalance to this depiction at all
This is an unchallenged position in the film which is editorially supported by the way that Moyer has edited this
If she thought that Alex's claim was it all dubious
She could reach out to one of the Sandy Hook parents to discuss how they were trying to get Alex to stop this s*** long before you cared about Trump
Or if you wanted to give the impression that she disputed his claim
She didn't have to structure and edit the film to comport with Alex's narrative
Again much like with the John the Baptist
If you believe what this documentary is presenting
You have no reason to not believe that
People are only mad about Sandy Hook because of Alex
Supported Trump
The story as it's told Lee due to no other
Conclusion and that is a choice
That is a choice
Being made
In the creation of this documentary
Unacceptable
Hugh
Recognize
That this is intentionally being
Not released
During the Sandy Hook trial
Makes this
Outrageous
Justly offense
This is unacceptable
I don't know what the f*** you think you're doing but this is
Typing
Causing PTS
I mean is that
What you want to say
I mean part of
Part of the problem
Is 1
You
Set everything
That needs
To be sad about
That is
That is it and anybody who tries to
Counter or even add anything to that
Is wrong
There's a reason that the discussion of Sandy Hook as the one thing that Alex f***** up
Isn't included in the timeline of his career and all these Greatest Hits because it's a prop
In order to justify why people
Are so angry at him it's because they like that trumpet make
The pick through his career to find something they could
Could be mad about
Yeah
F*** that
That's like
Ion
Understand
That this is an argument that's going to be made that it's like I'm just presenting him the way he is you make your own
That's bulshit
There is a Judgment Day
You as a filmmaker are making by presenting this information that way
That is not an unbiased oh this is who he is this is how it is no f*** that noise
Yeah
Still fine to make this documentary I'm not saying
You should be
Silence
Store like
You shouldn't be allowed to make a second battery or anything like that silenced and then we'll talk
But you can do can scream over it if you want the former silence.
I don't think
I don't think like
You should be allowed
To do this but
You also
Should recognize
That what you're doing atkore is
Malicious
It is unacceptable and
To see what other b*******
She's going to do in her career
Yeah
This is the kind of documentary that if January 6th have gone the other way
Would be looked at by history as hell any reefer
We would look at Nazi documentary
Can't believe it January 6th didn't go that way and so
We have a couple years
Until we look at it that way when you bring up January 6th
It does
Pullback
A little bit
The View
If it was an alternate routes Jones on The View
I know that
That one is very narrow
No I'll try and I'll try and keep this short but
By bringing up January 6th
That just require you to kind of pull back from the Sandy Hook
Situation
He's absolutely monster
And then you pulled back and it
Further
Even that you know like
No means my minimizing what he's done
To the families of story
But also
Overthrowing in tonight in entire country
That's also pretty big
Sure you know and
And to a certain extent whatever the point is made that
Trump wouldn't be president without a lie
Which is debatable but there is something here's what I'm going to say about that
When we talked about nuance
1 weighted
View that
What is by
Math just very simple
And the fact that we are very capable of talking about nuance
But when we talked about it we're not able to really get to the fact that
If
Alex is
20%
Responsible for Trump
Becoming president
Then he is responsible for Trump becoming president because of the market with 20%
That were not able to really deal with right now
Even to make your point further like there's no way that we can create a counterfactual real
Place where Alex is earlier career didn't
Exist in the parts of it that involve the Tea Party of coin he helped start The Oath Keepers right
And all of these things like the ripple effect
So these things from further back in his career
And how many of those haven't told direct effect in getting Trump elected
So I think it is
Kind of fair to say like
Check in whatever sense
Right
Could be seen as somebody who helped push it over the hill at very we I mean you're absolutely right
The problem with the word nuance is that we all understand what it means but if
You try and Kwanzaa
Safayet
You're f*****
Yeah yeah but the larger point is vasectomy
100% I'm sorry for trying to like tangential
You know what I'm saying
Yeah I was just talkin here a little bit about Sandy Hook
And he said something
Not good
I am not
Sandy Hook
Big events
The internet was questioning
Minion Amelie's
Some of which turned out to not be real anomaly simovitch
Were still unsolved
Which one
Good question
Which one's Alex trial tomorrow
No
No we will get some reasons that you question Sandy Hook we're legitimate
What what animal is which one
Dumb dumb
Fortunately you said today some reasons that they Quest
Sandy Hook were good idea yeah I guess that move
I guess that's their position good luck
6 good luck
So they play some clips from the deposition
And I will say we don't play the ones that are meaningful
But
Mark and Bill both make out of here to this document rape people grilling out
Is right there is no mention of the fact that this deposition that they play of Rob dues is the one where he's there is corporal represent
What that mean no clue there is no mention of any of
The discovery issues or any of the bad behavior that Alex's
Carried on in court
Of the abusive practices
These clips I believe are used
To make it look like
The lawyers are bullying hours
Can I say one thing before you play the F bus
Can I say one thing yeah right
Daria was asked
Today
Why did Rob do leave the company
And what she did not say was what I think we all secretly believe
Is because
He would never become the corporate represent
224 Infowars again
Underoath
And that is why Daria is sitting in that stand right so I thought the reason was
He's tied up in a bunker
That could be there is also another possibility
That works he's in the freezer
I was watching the Picker answer was he decided to move on
From this Mortal coil moment that I am existing
Know how do I hear some clips
Mistake or not mr.
Anderson Cooper was in front of a blue screen
The only reason I would say it's not a hundred
Percent because somebody asked him if he was there and he
Video
Video of a guy asking him
During a taping of a show
You said hey were you at the
The funeral has no I wasn't
Right she wasn't
Active
Recently
Your lawyer said
There is no.
Dispute
The Sandy Hook tragedy
He was real
You stand by that that's
What you would Minister
Yes
Appearance of the badgering Hammond like it
It's it's 8:00 it creates the appearance of
Like Alex is a victim in this whole thing
There's no wreck
Recognition of the fact that it is the parents
Who are suing him
There's no recognition of what they've gone through
It is
Hayirli one-sided presentation
He's Sandy Hook legal troubles
Which again are presented as only the result of people trying to
To find something to be mad at him about because he's Sports dropped this is
Stupid
I've watched
Far too many true crime documentaries
To hear a clip of somebody saying no
I saw that in a video
And if they don't follow that up
With the video
Then you didn't see
See it in that V
Video
It's tough to documentary immediately shows that video
Yep
You think
It seems like that's what the dude the plaintiffs are doing
So Alex
Is a baby
He likes to do is whenever people are like really f***** up stuff about Sandy Hook and your behavior wasn't
Probably
You know over these people some money for defamation what have you
That's what he thinks people are asking him to do what I've asked you baby
I'm fine with that I'm not going to say you should be back by then
We accidentally take a
Hard left turn the episodes of how not to cover Alex
The okay
But put me in prison for Quest
Okay
Pull the trigger
Absolute control
Thanks pointing out the permit
And this is where we find the source that God made
Difference in the New World Order
Alex more than indeed music piano sound
Alex sound
People like this song in the world
I let that go on as long as I did because I wanted to illustrate that they play almost the entire Bon Iver
Parody videos Alex
Because
Anthony most like
For him
Yep
That's fun
But also he doesn't know him that song they don't have permission to use it
So I was thinking
Hey this is a copyright strike right here
Like no joke I don't mean to tell Tales out of school but I got in touch with the guy who
They used your
Chip in this documentary I know you didn't give them permission
Have a copyright himself to that song
So is Super Deluxe wants to
I want to put a copyright strike on this they are more than welcome to
Viacom
True
Maybe
Better is
Is just fun tonight we smash cut forward to the January 6th
Era
Enzo January 5th
Owen on the evening they all got together in the documentary film
Maker was like why are you burning this black lives matter flag and he was like
Because it's so great
But it isn't
Evening of January 5th and it is Owen
This must have been just before that I wonder if the document
Was there and saw him burning a flag or just didn't
Go along for those anyway suspicious
Odd
That could determine
2020 election
Supporters and Patriots
Rndc
Yep that's where we're at
Some speeches are going to happen that night and also we're going to go burn black lives matter flag
Antifa
Nose kranti
They were still on that
The cranberry juice absolutely
So here's Alex on the 6th
There's a good bit of
A video of south on the 610 and what have you been here
Boiling people up with all the exact
Same
Rhetoric and the ideology that
To everyone storming the capital
Give me give me the rough cut
Of this
Entire documentary without the music
Look at it
I won't change a single scene
And all I will do is change the music
And you will hear a completely documented at completely different documentary probably could play Soul Coughing I don't need to walk around
Run in circles
And you would listen to that clip
Listen to I reread you be like oh yeah this is a f****** moron for
Simple this is a music made by music entirely.
Which almost warms my heart because I love music some
You know what I would like to see
Was that replace all of it with a Cantina theme
So now that Alex has led this March to the Capitol
Things go bad
Remember
Harrison talking about the capital is falling appreciative Takin Over
Leaving
Some things that
Might be important
Yep okay
But here's Alex it's angry while happy with it
Beloved
Trying to get people to stop
Rioting
Stormy the capital
Right
There's one point that I want you to listen closely for because Alex is not getting anyone to listen to him and you can hear ali-al exam
Hey Pryor chant no alright
America to stop people from
Taking over the capitol to get rid of the illegitimate government that you believe is taking off
Over the country
Don't know if chanting USA is going to really calm people down
But he tries
Dear every creative person that is ever exist
Do you remember that
That time when you were like
Here's what I'm going to do I'm going to put into the section of my create event.
Where
Somebody in America
Tries to calm the crowd down or change their minds by just
Randomly chanting USA you remember when you were going to do that and you were like
That might be
A step too far you were wrong
Wrong
Kitchen work
Record around the other side
Mark Harmon
Could be explored interesting Lee by a different doctor
Commander even this
And that is Alex being unable to
Control the monsters he creates
He has done his part
To create the exact situation that unfolded on January 6th
And here he is yelling into bullhorn unable to stop people from doing the thing
He's pretending he doesn't want them
Yeah and that is a kind of sad picture
And it's very similar to the way that he's unable to stop his listeners from harassing
Sandy Hook parents
Stuff like he created this atmosphere he created this thing
And even if he does
Like eventually say
I'm sorry
Able to
Stop the ball that he started rolling down the hill stop these people from
Diet wanting to take over the capital after you have yelled into a bullhorn all day about
One from you it is an illegitimate and we need to take back our country
You and that you have no power over the monster you created
You have the power to rile
Pull up and create this atmosphere
The your info
When it comes to
Stopping
Yeah it's it's partially because you don't actually want to stop
Yeah I mean
So this
What this reminds me of
Is despite him being a horrific terrible shity person
In the book
Speaker for the Dead
Orson Scott Card
I had a character who was
I mean
Essentially living out an Alex Jones fantasy
So he built up this
Mob
As as one would
Describe it
And the waitresses
Goes through it is that
Disguising
In control
This situation
He builds this mob together
And he pulls it
End
Then
Without his ability to
Control it
It becomes a thing
It becomes a
General conscious
Despite the fact that it's a bunch of different
Separate individual human beings
It is 1
Ma
And then
He'd be made the character he is now the enemy of the Mob characters
Like oh this is a bad idea
And tries to go
Hey Mom
Let's not do this
Guess how it
Yell at Alex's honestly lucky that the mob
Turn on him because in that environment him, everybody knows
Photo stop
Either he's telling us not to do the thing
The natural conclusion
Everything he's been saying for the last month's absolutely
We've talked about it how many times but it's like just cuz you split in
Infinitive doesn't mean you change the meaning of your sentence
You still shouldn't split Infinity you Jamie
It's just bad right
It's a thing too badly do it.
Alex now
Poorly good leader
What
That wasn't bad
So Alex now
Had to deal with the fact that
5 + 1
Although he still in denial about it
So now we're on his show
Forget to the day of the inauguration and Alex announces the death of America has either whiny little titty baby
From the Frontline
Of the information War
Alex Jones
Ladies and gentlemen it is 0 hour
January 20th 2021
The 46th president of the United States
Has been installed in a giant
I am Chinese Joe Biden
Looking like a
A corpse
With fake
Hair blowing around
Actually Jim Carrey
Wonderful
W76 he's really say it died
January 20th the year 2021
Very dramatic
Very very dramatic
I mean in some ways he also has said the capital has fallen you know just with a different
Tone
The capitalists as much as
It's the same as ever
The capital was in the hands of the Patriots were a very short. Of time
Waverly Tire Schrodinger's Capital cuz it was up for grabs
And then we observed
So I guess
I mean if you want to be
Like
Kind of
I don't know. One
I mean in all honesty there is a part of that that is the Republican argument against
Trump losing the election is like
If you hadn't counted the votes
We wouldn't be here
Here's the here's one reading of this documentaries Ark
That I think is
Not with a intended but
If you want to be really cynical about that sure and ignore all of the music
Syracuse and the entire structure of everything
You have
Basically Alex's career he's this guy who everybody looks down on because you won't
Compromises views and he tells the truth no matter what it cost him
His job because
Waco and all these station because of 911 in his liberal fanbase cuz he wouldn't
Except Obama shrew in all this been finally has indicated right in the lead-up to the 2020
Alexa, stop.
The Steel stock price
Finally a man
Because of trump who is seeing
The guy
He's been right all along and we were foolish not to listen Bro Hymn
And then he has this call Natori moment on January 6th
And he is completely unable
To stop the crowd
From taking the logical Next Step
His rhetoric
Which actually doesn't serve his purposes very well
It doesn't end up working and then biting
Is President kind of like a
A deflation
Yeah it's almost like all that stuff you was right about really didn't matter no
Cuz Trump lost
Easter 2020
And that you weren't able to overthrow the government
You know it is a little bit like
Boy
Sucks to be input
Yeah it had the politically especially it like in there
Partially because there's nothing
Behind what he say
If you're better on the bone and therefore there's no protein
If you were
I understand what you're saying
With your boy your metaphor because I just don't believe you are enough
But but it is it is a little bit like
While his speech is going on
Right before the end whenever nobody pays its
If you played the Benny Hill theme song
Same thing
Come on we can't go back to that well too many times it's in a Cantina
Find the documentary
Closing with
Alex
And his son
Outshooting
This is the end this really humanizes this is hate
Image of him and his son shooting guns
I've been having some family time
I meant this clip and
With a really wistful clip
From Alex
No
Refuse it's the wrong message
He really just needs a space where you can
Can Roman be free
He's like
Buffalo
Iraq
27 years
How is it going to
My fear is a
Failure not of death
They could kill me anytime
Hope I can do the best job I can to
Maintain doing good work in the future
However long that is and I've already
Had a great life
Rayman Rabbids
Is the
Setting
OneAmerica
Or is it Rising
People that are well-informed
So young Alex's monologuing over video of like a really beautiful sunset Picture Show
Yourself
Not only that you haven't learned this
You burned the opposite
Disgusting
Yeah absolutely
One last clip
If you wear that thought
Severe the shot of the sunset and then this is Alex coming in
With The Parting Shot of the documentary
The weirdness I've seen in my life
The bizarre happenings
Incredible
Discoveries that I've been
Blessed to be part of
Truth is Stranger Than
And that's not because I'm out
Because of
Time
Happy Wheels
Incredible timer
But really my personal best moments of my life
NetSpend
Understanding of timelessness
And those moments in eternity that are
Those are
Emily Eliza
Of
Infinity
And also when I did mushrooms with Mike Tyson I remember when Amitabha Buddha said shoot me in the f******
Kingface if that a****** talks about me
You see the stats
You know that's not exactly how you
But they're going to be
A Goldie in Eureka
Better for everybody
You know it's really painful
Do you make mistakes
Children hurt people on the way but
You're doing it
From a place of goodness
Do you forgive yourself for that
Process of being
The body injury
I want to die
It's
The right now in this hotel room it's a fairly good hockey ways and productive for me to die
I mean what am I going to do what is better than
How to say
I think
Ending the documentary with Alex expressing forgiveness for himself
I'm really grateful that I'm allowed to be
Not responsible for any of my actually.
Offensively indulgent
And you know and here's How This Ends
Yours have the sentence in a good world
Animal House
Freeze Frame
Words
Saying Alex is on the lam never seen again
That's as good as we can do for this documentary
So if you're making this documentary doesn't end like that
Then you're f****** done
Done on the release date of this documentary Alex's in court and his lawyers being a complete ass hoe
Cool gas
Yeah congratulations
Can you fuc yeah man
Unbelievable
This documentary sucks
I mean I guess I could have just summed it up that way I put in a half hours
How many more things we need to talk about from The Trial update
What have you
I think I think a lot of people are probably interested in following you on Twitter your live-tweeting
I mean that's fun and silly and I have
There's a little more context to like talking about what actually happened
I totally and I'm going to be honest with you what I'm what I'm trying to do is just Infowars info
Sprite like
I'm not doing a good job as a journalist in any sense of the word you cited a source
When I told you about the Saint Rose of Lima never not give you credit for telling me
So your journalism is alright I give credit where credit is due I am credited Eugene mirman when I stole
One of his jokes
Today man of the sea
Have
If you have a thought
It is it is quite simply that
Mark
Is
Notification of a documentary
All of these infinitive
Mike's emission of the documentary
Is
What if
You made a bad p*** movie
That was just
Two and a half hours of somebody
Gradually
Ever so slowly
Poking at a limp
Is that is that work for you
Does that is I feel like I've known
I just said I'd like to drop my ear metaphor
Fine I think that this movie
Yeah it's a whole
It's kind of excusable
To a point
I think the wave
But you talked about Alex's
Career in terms of like
Oklahoma City
If you want to portray that it's kind of mythological in this Fall's version of it whatever you're creating this me though so
It's supposed to be said it's Corso if you're going to do that you're going to do that and whatever
I think
The framing of Sandy Hook
Is just something the people are mad about because he supported Trump is a nun
Excusable
And
Editorial choice
That these documentary filmmakers are making
Threatened
I think they should be deeply ashamed of them
I think that anybody who watches
Is this documentary like quick Glenn Greenwald
Or Matt Taibbi and they don't come away with the same
Kind of conclusion
I think
That they
I've lost it
Yep I don't think it's possible to watch
Documentary
Hey you know what it's responsible to
Choose to make this
Like
If that's why people don't talk about
Yeah right
I mean look
The problem practice documentary
What's be wrong about things
Currently and loudly
No I don't think that's going to work for us
We're going to Haiti
I don't know I keep I feel like I'm hitting my head against the wall trying to make a summation other than like
This sucks
It sucks
It's bad I think even some of the
Stop is
Confusing
Some of the musical choices
Not the ones that are like really tacky and the crescendos that are like
Overly dramatic
Some of the other ones are
Very weird to pause a couple times
Cuz I thought something I got pop-ups
Started playing music
Right right right
Pick some of the filmmaking itself is actually a little bit bad here's another thing
Breaking Dawn
Is like
What about all of Alex's friends
Like what about
What about pechenik name one
What about like all of these gas
But he's had all over the years who are complete lunatic
The Nazi
Adjacent guy who was his Bilderberg
WorkSource
Credits
A Spaceman in his book above filter
What about these
People like
Chrisley
You're missing a
Big part of it
He's story
If you don't recognize that a lot of his information comes from
F****** wackos
Right but what you're missing
Is that this is actually
Okay and I feel like I now
Understand the
I've come to the conclusion
That what this documentary is about
Is
That's a man
At one point in time
Is he a chosen not to do a Rush Limbaugh on Fresh
Couldn't find
The Vespers choir
And instead he chose one Beth it is it is it is a classic poetic
Tale of a of a man who can
Go down to pass there's a beauty to that it is
Gorgeous
So we'll be back with another episode I think I think the next one probably will be
About the Glenn Greenwald thing
But we may be able to also have a court recap in that
Cuz we can maybe make it a bumble episode or something record I would be shocked at how much
We record
Absolutely
We're leaving the livestream on like the courtroom
Everybody can just occasionally listen to us.
So I will be back but until then
Super late so I'm to tell you
Go to bed Jordans no I have to get this app out a couple hours
Yeah you know Saturday Leo I'm dzx Clark
It's always something
Alexandra Thurston color with your trip and I love your work