Nola.com
I have great respect for its knowledge by now it's like I'm sick of them posing as if they're the good guys
Knowledge fight
Hotel room and worship Selene from afar and talk a little bit
Alex Jones
Jordan is just like
Getting
I had such high hopes
Of being able to get an episode about that documentary out on the day it was released
And I thought there's no way I'm going to be able to
Perseverance
Stick-to-itiveness
Whatever you want to call it
Persistence
We managed to do it and I'm proud of us for it
Although a presstime
No response from Glenn Greenwald
Bora or Matt Taibbi
Nothing for me
No soul searching
Nope post unsubscribe haven't seen them be like
This is why we're examining our life
Is not one
I want a question why I didn't think it was weird that Sandy Hook came up in the context of why people are mad at Alex
It's just because of trump
Oh yeah
I am glad that we were able to do that
I I think that there is a
Such a whirlwind of Alex going on right now that it's so easy for things to get lost
And that seemed to important
To the larger body of like
Alex apologia yet I wanted to make sure that wasn't missed
I forgot to bring up one very important thing that wasn't
Documentary
Recent Wars
The most important
It wasn't in the documentary the crowning achievement of Alex's wife the culmination of his career
Warriors
Not in the document everybody here
It's you are right Alicia it
No mention of like Cleon skousen no no
Anyway what's your bread back on yours because yours is very magnanimous and sayings
That we got it done
Stayed up late until 3:30 or 4 this morning
You worked all the way until 10 a.m. this morning when most people they would have said hey
3:30
I'm just going to go to sleep
I'll do it tomorrow and then then the episode of going out at 9 p.m. at night that's not how you f***
Workday at the I don't want to go to bed until a task is done even if it's
Possible
Fight like hell to make it pop
More like 6 Central Time
You know people really rely on me not to be like
Hyperbolic
Actually you know what Jimmy Buffett says
Then I am somewhere
I have found something that I think will be a
A bit of fun
For folks still a little bit more
Impactful.
Not as hard as the the trial
Not as hard as the documentary Greenwald
I still off in the horizon
Going to do that soon
But we're going to have fun
This is an amuse-bouche
But also one of the things that I wanted to do was
Take an opportunity to
Do it take talk a little bit about the trial itself and how things are going on and
Give folks a little bit of a recap cuz obviously
That's
Step something on Friday just
After the case
TGIF
Same
David mentioned Philadelphia earlier
I'm hungry
I feel like you've been either keeping a real a real watchful eye on this case
I think so
I mean there I did I did go back because I read I read a lot of what I wrote
Today and I think that I could be making all of this up
Like if you read through that
That is a made-up there's no way that any of that is real based on a real thing I'm clearly hallucinating
In my hotel room after we recorded until 3 a.m. last night that must be what happened today
Thank you that were the case you'd have a lot more people responded to your tweets with like I'm worried about you because I'm watching the Stream
This is not at all what's happened
Well
I'm worried about you but not for that read
12 shirt
Dana par for the course
No it was
Today was I mean
It started
Good with Owen being a piece of s***
Who is trying to
Owen was trying to be like
That Stonewall witness where is like
You know I don't know if you and I don't know if you can prove I said that you know he's trying to do that whole thing
Pressure but everybody annoying until he left
The Jurassic
The jurors asked him to question
Is that where it was quite funny
The story of today
Is the jurors questions as
As time went on
Yeah right
They started off being
Very
Simple and
Then by the end of the day
They are wondering who is and is not a lizard person in the courtroom
Nobody was not aware of how this this
Does working out when you have the witnesses
The jury is able to record questions
That the judge will ask them
I'm right and people can object to the question
The judge can say I'm not going to ask that that's
Ridiculous
Too hard
But yeah
The progression of these questions has
If you're Alex
Skorys lawyer
You cannot
Feel good about something
Is the way that they are open
Yeah yeah it is it is hard not to think that the defense is like here's what we're going to
We're going to Red Pill these people
And those questions near the end of the day I have got me thinking that the opposite is true
Well actually we don't know tone
Are you a lizard person we could we could be totally missed
I wish that were to possibility but I will put it at maybe 15 20%
I feel quite I feel quite low odds
And then we then we played some depositions Rob Jake
Demolition crack up the Kraken
But dondi's deposition
Which was so funny
And listening to him talk
About how much he loves Infowars and how close he is with them and how they're his favorite people
Depose next to Dari be like I don't know if I've ever been
Ben-Hur to put on day before my birthday
Absolutely love my daughter money like it's that kind of made me a kraken plushie
It was it was that
I'm laughing about that but at the same time there is a pesos to that because
This guy is being used by
Play cannot absolve him of any of these things probably on his own
But he's being egged on and
Directed in some way and
Validated and probably told by Alex that you're part of the family and all of this
And it's going on a bed once it's inconvenient ending
Incredibly
Dammit
To be too close with patandi you immediately cut bait and
Never heard of her
Never heard of this guy is kind of sad
It is it is cuz he was
He was really expressing just various versions of like
It feels good
Get feels good to get a good boy from Alex
You know I imagined
I guess
The UPS
Swing of it is Oregon
Maybe the justice of it is
Because there is that little bit of pesos maybe we can feel okay that the Gandhi himself is not getting sued
Off the hook
Or whatever
I mean
It is it is a little bit like don't be done.
Deposition
Kind of makes him look to be more the gun and not
Somebody who is firing
You know
So it's like well I mean I know he's a person but also
He's a person shaped like a gun that doesn't think real well so that kind of a problem
Convince the Sandy Hook
Is a false flag or whatever video yelling at somebody about it and no one cares
Aldar there's not going to be second
Video
Keep going
If you have a platform like Alex's show like the Nightly News on Infowars
That's willing to validate and
Disseminate your content
And
Connect you with like Wolfgang halbig in right you know like
B
It cut its encouraging in a way
Again I don't know we can prove it but I would say probably
Facilitate
Pizza kind of makes
It happened it happened and that is what the afternoon testimony was almost in
Entirely about Becca Lewis
Spy hero to the
Squatch forever well I appreciate that
Did do a great job on the train
Sasquatch has no hearing
I will I'm I'm nominating her potential here over dishwasher
Artificial light
Understand
But she did a spectacular job explaining like
The difference between what happens whenever you post on Facebook and what happens when you post on
Infowars
And while it seems like it that's a very
G-Eazy thing for people to
To just instinctively grasp around
It is kind of complicated
Whenever you start getting into
What it is better
Memes to post on Facebook you know you get 100 shares or whatever and you think while I'm the meteor
Innovation
As opposed to
When Infowars post something maybe it says 100
But because it's Infowars it's on this platform
Echoes over there
And then because it it's like a spider Wester bution of the content
She made clear the better it was now they're getting that s*** yeah
Kind of hard to recognize now in 2022 and even over the past few years the different nature
Sure of what Facebook was like
Can 2012 2013 2014
Like it was not the same website that it is now wow I didn't even consider that but I don't think anybody can say
Fitted that I imagine that if they'd actually
Just been like okay
Let me show you who screenshot of Facebook in 2020 12 and what it look
I think that would be a very different question as well that's why I think so and I think
That it was it was the last
And unusable website
And more like it wasn't as much of a like place where people
In a grandparent chain emails
Basically be reposted over and over again
Confined to smaller spaces groups of people who hated
Gardening but somehow wanted to know
To your point
With the lake if you have 100 shares or whatever
And you're like the hundred people who are sharing it
Are people who have
Spigen audience of two exact you know it's
It's
It's a distorted
Image of 100 chairs and Route real like right
Well it's real but it's
It's not as impactful as
2 shares from
Bike
Tia Becca did a great job she was fantastic on the stand
And I thought it was interesting to watch the
The Defence try and do the cross
My God it was
Cuz it was weird
I don't even know how to describe that guy's
Performance today
I think that was
Today I really did feel like
Like I tweeted this and I don't want to repeat
Exactly
But
Today really felt like the first day that Infowars tried to put the system on trial instead of Infowars being
Cross-examined in like
Here's why you guys are terrible
This was
Shitballs first
The temp to be like
Here's what I'm going to do
I'm going to prove that you're a liar
I'm going to prove that you aren't an expert at all what is
Harvard Law School price
Stafford law school can you walk me through an entire statista
6 class holder
It was it was very much that it was like Alex's questions for somebody who actually knows something and they do now
Not sound good in a in a quart
No
To be a little bug
Over the course of the last
Few days do their bidding
Some things
They have gone on
There has been probably the biggest
Moment
Outside of the Rolling Thunder of darya's horrible performing
It went on way too long
Exhausting
But I think honestly
Most
Of that
Is stuff there
It relates
At least
Sort of
Tangentially to stuff we covered in the
Right and I don't know if anything happened in the courtroom that is more shocking than Daria saying
Chipotle
Is a image of Hope
Yep an expression of Hope
Yep and so
I don't want to dwell too much on it
Because
I don't know other people have talked about it. He was trending on Twitter
Things I think stick out are obviously the fight
That Mark
And the defense attorney
Been to course
Add a little little fun
Hey it's Jack
Texas Justice
I think I should have had to do with li
I think they might still and then
The other thing was Owen being we're going on Infowars and tacos
And the moment of him saying
That his lawyer had not told him about the rules
Of him being a witness
And not being able to talk to other women
And not being able to talk about the case
That was
I mean
If if there was a moment
That was needed to be like
This is
This is disrespectful
Like the bad guy
You know
I knew
Where we be
But still
I thought the
When the actual trial happen
And I don't know why I thought this I feel like a
The fool
Cuz I still had that thought in the back of my mind even though I knew here's what I'm going to do and expect the worst
It's still in my head I was like
At the
Actual trial
They will have prepared
Something hahaha
Nothing
I mean nothing prepared emotionally to be this Brazen I don't know if there is a way to prepare to be
I think you're born with this kind of
Involves whiskey
Cantina theme
Yeah it's so I don't know
It's interesting for me to look at it
I'd recognize that like
I think that there is a not-insignificant amount of our audience who are watching
The LifeStraw
Of the trial
And
To any discussion of something that would be redundant there is not
Is it a lot of
Outlets are covering the
The trial and some of them have a better understanding of law
100 opening arguments didn't episode the game out of believe today about the
The case ohyeah
I don't know
Are you
Feel that I'm at my best
When were talking about things that other people aren't talk
Yeah and when there's other coverage
Just things
I kind of feel like
We'll end up just being another voice
And that's not to say that we shouldn't talk about the trial at all
Are you talk about our feelings on it but
I don't have as much of an interest in doing like a play-by-play on it
Like I would with the documentary
At least until it's over
Well
The reality of it is
In our
Is that what is happening is they're just being forced to listen to
All of the evidence
Instead has been presented against them
Not not necessarily collected by but you specifically
Just that that's what our show is to
You know and there's
They're looking at it and the
That would be redundant
For us to cover it because it's the same stuff we
We have cover
You know they're just presenting the evidence that we've spent
Talking about
Finally
Dumb people's face
Yeah it's a little bit brief in terms of like
The court recap
Butts
Turn on Jordans
Twitter go to bed Jordan
If you want a lot of thought
Torrential barrage
Just bullshittin and we'll have more you know talk with some of the folks maybe have a better Insight on some of the stuff
In coming days
And what have you
The Jordan
I told you
With something a little bit fun
That's when we're going to get into today
I'm about
This out here on
On Friday evening like as I guess
Say defective Saturday episode is because why not we're here in Austin we can record to do those ugly want
Rules
And so we got to get this out
Because it's a it's a special time
For comedian
And that is
JFL
Audition
People just got JFL.
No today I think it was the other day
I don't know if they're one of your old friends
But somebody that I knew dad was friendly with
Chicago ever Maynard got new places
Pasta cat and so
I am great
They're great and I got in this this mood of thinking about stand-up
Really fortunate
Because
I'm banned. Video
Owen Shroyer released in 18 minutes that is
Owen Shroyer does a stand-up special
Yeah stand-ups
Did he get a chance he'll not because if he gets one and I have never gotten one I am going to be mad I'm going to be furious
You've never auditioned I don't think
Well every I'm nobody's ever even ask me that's how bad
Considered asking me so we don't need to worry about
The audition audition
Cyf
And it was
Painfully clear
Even going into it they were interested in seeing and I doubt the rest of the show right
You know the producers asked me to like
Be a part of that pattern your meeting was so f****** clear like
All right before people that have a shot
View
If you torpedo this f****** room yeah then maybe
Will consider it but like you don't really have a shot
Oh you came here with your agents
And we all came by ourselves
We're not going
Djfl are we
Nowhere
So this was at a
Bryson Gray
Rappers
Comedian
Flash
Public figure man I'll go figure
Real Renaissance
I call him that I don't know too much about him actually cuz I
I think that he lives mostly in the War Room guests.
Are you seeing him less
If I even remember to be on Infowars
But I'm sure he has
He's been on with Alex
Brightside
Yeah he's a guy who's running a little bit of a show
In San Antonio
In San Antonio have been there
On the day that we got
The wrong City
So this
Had
That's
Who else was on the Bliss
That night
There were two people from
2000 Buick
But not tonight D'Souza other people involved in 2008
There was that that Maga rapper did that song with Rodger
Stone stone is dancing
I I just don't do it you know whenever the Maga people have their culture
That they in
50 is something we might describe as rap
Or something we might describe
Humor
I just did I disagree with them on the prince
It's not rap for fun
So I'm done I be honest
Sickflowz
Well then I guess I take it back
The fastest rapper in the world
Methamphetamine lyrics god dammit
Here is
Owens
Introduction you got to come out of the Gates Strong
Obviously you want if you are
Someone who is
Maybe starting to get into the world of stand-up Niwot a little bit
Strong opener
Strong closer
You know the old the old saying you know your best joke is last in your second best joke
August 1st
That's the way you do it
You can tread water for a little while in the middle get away with it if you stroke
Strong close strong
So here's Owen opening
Did he
Snooze
Woo
So the tacos thing
That was that Jill Biden
Comment
About the
The Hispanic population is diverse as the bodegas in the Bronx
Brighten the breakfast tacos
Obviously the point that she was making
Not a defensive one right but boy was it
They got her boy was it got it
She should have
Reconsider the way she was
But yeah I mean I guess
It was
Pretty recent I guess
To Whitney did the stand-up special
Until coming out with a
Topical
Hey we got any tacos out there
Wolf
Yeah
Hey hey that's what they call you
I'm calling you that produced you and
Greeted you that way without performing the context Jewel that would give you the idea that I'm above that it was
It's it's so widely known within the displacement like you have
Explain
I need to explain to you
Man in our listeners probably
So yeah they know it's so well.
It's been that
Top headline at every right
Refugio Biden calls Mexican people tacos is absurd
I can't believe that I have no idea about that
Whatsoever and that's just the most famous thing in the right
Crazy this is also caution
Two people want to get it set up be careful about whether or not you think your material will age
Right Right Alright this is
This is tired so we left already unrelatable
Easier for John Stewart to like
S*** talk
Gaffes you know the late night shows
They talked the gas all look at the president he said this
You know and then it's gone tomorrow because it's a very
To throw away
Right you know you don't need it and if you're saying it out loud on stage
You should stop being on stage
Did make the news people talking about that
About exactly it's not like he was
Following biting around like everybody's lying about you but thanks for
Hanging out and having
Cancer with me
Yeah
GasBuddy
I was reflecting on it be I made reference to somebody being like
Precinct list three
I didn't realize it but what I was
Trying to pull up in my memory was that George W bush
Who's giving it like a press speech on a golf course
And that he was talking about like a rock
And now a watch this drive
That's right
Are you forgotten that that's what why wouldn't I was in my mind
Wow I take
Outside of all of the context of being George W bush and
Talking about Iraq
It's a pretty baller movie
God dammit yes it was like a science
Terrible terrible
Can't be president if you say that
That should be
Again I'm not saying that we need to make like big
Grand lies I'm saying that we should make more targeted very specific laws like if you say that to the media
You immediately stop being president
That arises from that is like
Was that an attempt to be funny
Or was that something that was just like
He uncomfortably said it and it ended up here
Amazingly disrespectful and very funny
Knowing w
The way that we all do after
Do they sell many years I imagine
I just really wanted to hit the drive and they kept asking him questions and Zoe weapon chili he lost in
Interesting what they were doing
And was like
I'm going to go hit this drive I'm the president
So he doesn't but the media didn't cover it but they did
Decides to develop
OfficeTeam a little bit of
Sicknesses that Biden hats
Not necessarily just a joke
Maybe
Joe Biden covid
Dementia
Arabia
Turn All the Lights Off
20 minutes
No but you noticed
Who stand up that I think a lot of people
Like
Right
It is a little bit like
Saying like oh I could
Just go sing the national anthem in front of the staple
Where you like
Sure maybe you know how to sing
You could physically do it
Yes but you don't know what the
The song actually sounds like until when you sing at your kind of layoff and that's
Stand-up has a music in the Rhythm and the end of vibe to it
And if you are singing a bad song
That's going to happen
You also don't really know what that you're going to feel when it doesn't go the way you expect yeah
Unless you've done it a lot of times that could be really disoriented
And you can end up in
Situations like we just heard there like he has no control over the audio
Is the Allen shootout
Just like I will say that I do like
If you if you weren't doing it like he was trying to do a bit
It's at the if you were asked
Accidentally or
Maybe even on purpose I get like that and that would be funny but unfortunately for like an Auntie, decent away
Absolutely also Biden went to those countries
Before
I was diagnosed with covid
Also we stop
UPS tracking and tracing way before
Never got it I actually but would bet that there has been
Some attempt to attract
King in Tracy
Given
O'Reilly
Yeah yeah yeah but the people that he has
Contact with yeah but yeah those trips that
Not after
Find canceled like a domestic
QuikTrip because of Coke
60 never outside
Wishing well
Covid
Manuel
I'm going to go Gray
Why
Yeah it's not that great but the structure of a joke
I like the low and then they just kidding it at somebody else or not
Babies of that that was a very that
What is kind of an interesting thing about the rights version of humor you know they have the structure of a joke but they just say something they believe
You know like
I don't want him to dive covid iwant him to die of cancer
That's what he said
And so he wasn't joking
Maybe but
If you just look at it from a purely
Comedic perspective
Mister Ed
Is the classic mr. X
Congratulations on you pulled that off
Kind of that is true that is true
Bow Wow
There is just a better that's
The punch adult that their punch shoppable joke though I mean you don't go from covid
The cancer
You escalated into a
Completely
Territory you know
We don't want to die if covid
We wanted to be hit by a giant rubber duck
You know you really push it
To be absurd might be helpful but I think there's something about the
The Revenant
Sound covid-19
I think I got to go with it
Sound is usable for humor much better than many of that maybe instead you should say he should be Brown
Caca
And it's not hard to punch up this joke
But he'd already established the cancer earlier so I think it kind of boxed in
The button doesn't have cancer
Clapter
Maybe I can
Thank you so much
Always he done
Thank God
Is it like
60 cents a gallon or is it what is it
I don't know
There's no context where there's no
What did Aikido put the same amount of gas in your tank every type of barrel
Yeah I mean
Is this a joke
I guess it is he's funny
He just thinks he's funny all the time
I would assume that a lot of his life
Revolves around people affirming that
A lot of people yelling you get them cut
Destroying stuff like that
DIA
I think that
There's any problem with this and that is that they
Complaining
The gas prices are too high for a very long time
And they're making fun of
Somebody achieving that
So that's a problem
The second problem is that does he not think that Trump has bragged about way smaller.
Reductions in gas price
I don't think you understand how he
I understand
No I know I understand that sometimes you want to just you know
Swing a big bat or whatever
Winter joke
Structural problem
The point that he's absolutely
I think what's what's fun about it
Is that for the far-right
Sprite you know how we
Comedians who are like everybody give it up for the troops in order to get a huge
The Applause break
For the far-right
Apparently you get an easier Place break if you're like
Biden is a Cancer and that's it
BB f****** hate what they see is like a virtue signalling in comedy in
Stop
What is that
No no no it's way different
Meme well I guess you could argue that it's elevated from
Pure virtue signaling because he's saying he doesn't have cancer he is cancer so there's like a linguistic
Twist using but it's
Elementary
Joe
I'll be only by
There's another
Jill Biden
No-oooooo we're talkin about
Hunter
Yeah it's
It's funny because he's horny
Now there's a strip club
How old is in San Antonio is there any reason to assume Hunter Biden would be
Any thoughts
Hey there's boobs in there
Let's put
These two together and how can I turn this into something that is
Is it going to let
Break ground in the industry
Yeah it really did
I really did
Hunter has come up
I have to say that I think that this next clip that he
This joke that he has about Hunter Biden
I think
He's as close as you're going to get to a good
Interesting
There's leg
To do some work on it I would recommend him hit some open mike okay
Think about what he
He's trying to say a little bit
There's some
Thing here
News
Car comes over the antenna
Sometimes
What's going on
Your
You're a legend.
What's the music that's a weird 12n.
The joke
In the act out of
I'm going to Best Buy in Victor
And gross it's disgusting
Tighten the B
Of what he was
Who's working on
The absurdity of a man going and buying a camera
To film his own criminal act
Yes yeah yeah yeah
The image of
That like why would you feel McCracken
Are the specs
So the camera like there is something there that you could chisel away at
It kind of
Barely funny joke
No context
Cuz what you got in your back pocket
Yeah. What you got
Compact in your back pocket on this
Rights as you can slowly escalated
Through that kind of prism
And then instead of being like a ruler to go look up to the whatever
You can be like
Wait
Are you Hunter Biden
That's what the you know and then it would be that would be a better life
I don't know whether to call the police or the manager is kind of lazy
That's something you would get out in like
The first three or four times you tell the DirecTV is not working
It was kind of like
Do I see you
Terrible good premise
Negated it halfway through instead of continuing whenever.
You can't do that you got to have the Rhythm you got to have the music like what you're saying to is
And that is that like
The shock
Of the the twist or whatever bring it to the inside writing
It isn't earned know me and it's not like
It's not what the foundation of the joke was raised absurdity and then you went
But gross
What time does no time to process
So there's more topical stuff here
They're fighting
Oppression
Racism
Heard
Look fat
I don't know like
What that is exactly
But like in the context of a parody of o n
That's a pretty funny Alliance
It is a funny thing to say
Cuz it's so absurd that anyone would ever say it
Only owenwood
In the context
Something that is
Commenting on people like Owen
That is a great line to include
Obvious very bizarre
Yeah if you dressed up in a knowing suit and said that people be like that is the funniest impression I've ever seen
Sacha Baron Cohen character
Professional
Victoria Saudi Arabia
Find
Call Stearns
Google
Historically been a sport that was built on exclusion
In order to play it you needed access to
The huge areas of land which are usually expensive
Access
Expensive equipment and is deeply rooted in segregation with courses be part of golf club
We could choose to it
No black people if they want to do until relatively recent
Things have gotten gradually improved with a sport but it's
Still got a ways to go in terms of inclusion
Anyway
There's a larger backdrop behind the phenomenon that Owen is
Is discussing what you eat
Pretending not to know about it is relevant to
Did something
Ejected this joke
Also
The structure of this joke doesn't really make sense
He likes it
PGA you like sleep because he interprets them
Lesbian listen to work
Soar accepting gay people while he hates the NFL and NBA because they're too woke
Saudi Arabia apparently wants to buy Gall sewing wants them by the NFL and NBA presumably so they wouldn't be so
Gay people
But there's really only two ways this could make
Make sense
You have to believe that the sport of golf was preemptively being excluded of people in order to coordinate offer from Saudi Arabia
Whores that golf was previously full of woke
But Saudi Arabia somehow got them in check
Nothing about golf change because of
The possibility of Saudi Arabia buying the sport whatever that means
So there isn't a hinged put this on to make
The joke
If they bought the NBA it would stop being woke
This is just not very well-thought-out material he's just saying
Then hey
There's a
Venom
Bigotry that runs
Through the Gulf
I like
Right there is a vein of wokeness that goes through the NFL and NBA
Write Saudi Arabia is starting their own golf
Series that up buying the
PGA or something
Writers getting their own lives
Series of golf event and so he wants Arabia to get into these other professional sports because he
Believes
The things that he complains about about Muslim culture would then be applied to any to be better
What he saying is that he would rather live in Saudi Arabia than he would live in the United States
Because the United States has to work in Saudi Arabia kills game
I I mean
I don't know how else to interpret the structure of other than he is saying that I would prefer
For f******
Sharia law to be the law of the land
NBA player
To say black people exist
At least he would like Sharia law to be applied to Spa
Sports bets
Baby
Yeah I mean was it what are you saying is like
Here's here's the problem right
NFL in a 2-1
That's why all of the openly gay players
Come out after they retire
Too much wealth
In the sport that's how it goes
So goddamn walk now it's naughty Arabia bought them
We wouldn't even need to worry about it would weigh
There is there are there are just like
Somatic
And I like idea based reasons that this joke
Pretty weird right
Especially for someone like going to be saying it right
But then even just from a structural standpoint it doesn't make sense like
What would be achieved by
Saudi Arabia
Buying a golf
If what I'm what I'm interpreting is that
He wants
Saudi Arabia to f******
People of
Anything that but
Straight white male then
He's doing a bad job of telling
A joke about
You know like I said from a from a telling the jokes
Standpoint if that's what you're trying to say
You going to have to write a better joke
Actually decent joke
It's simple
I kind of think it works it's Feller
I really respect and Greg
I really do hate
Oh no no no
That's a fine joke
Because of calling back
To Joe Biden interview on The Campaign trail with The Breakfast Club black if you have a problem
Deciding between him and Trump
Right
Apologize for it but like
Yeah that's making fun of something that did happen right
Maybe
Maybe the it could be Rewritten a little bit
I do I don't necessarily think of it like that's a Polish joke
Sure thing that he's trying to say like
These people are racist against Bryson Gray
Here I go for Joe Biden is the joke there and I mean on a scale
I know
Emperor for what this is that the find joke
Okay I guess I will get y a
Maga crowd would laugh at that
Run not be like what's
The joke
Here I get what the joke is
And why
If you're in that space you might think that's
Right right I mean
Okay
If I'm if I'm rewriting it I'm saying
You are coming dangerously close to
Not
Parroting the thing that you
You're describing but in fact
The thing that you're describing insofar as your
Describing a black person
Asthma in Black
Do do whatever it is you feel like
So you're saying
These people are criticizing him for this
And then you're doing the same thing
Only in a positive
So it's not really changing or or
Switching the premise around it's just like
I like
Deeper analysis that you're
You're touching on that I think
Could be there
Sure I'm looking at triviality of stamps
When we're on that level it works
Stuff like Biden saying that kind of stuff that's fair game that's what people should be lampooning if you're right
Play wingspan
Start
By all means
Yeah I know that's
Here we touch on Owen's getting it getting into the hot gun
Good guy with a gun
Situation that just happened recently
So funny
Indiana Mall
Animal
Very tragic
There was a hero
Place to go
Suggested
Get ready to do math
I don't want without t-shirt.
And they're sitting on the TV
Control
We forgot the joke
Yeah that's
Exactly like what
The
Right complains about
The left
Then stand up and
Stuff doing
Which is not being funny and just
Sort of virtue signaling
Lapoint yeah
And then just getting clapped
From the audience to agree with your point
You can hear people muttering
There was no lektor
He's doing the what is presumably an act out
Of this this liberal who wants
More people to die in the shooting
Control
Alright man just
Grimm
Well you heard somebody like whisper that's what they want this is a call and response
Pastor
This is not a
Santa Baby
If I were in this position
On stage
I might bail
I would have so that means I might get Hosta
Irene weave weave weave spoken at length about one of our favorite places to perform,
TV
Centerburg Windsor Garland
And there was a I will call him Infamous Man Who Would host the shows and he
Open by bringing out the worst headlines
You can think of
Hey just go like
Three people died on the street because it was too hot yet
Yesterday
But they wish they had an egg
And no one would laugh and it be like
Yeah that's what you deserve
That's this is horrific
That is what I heard
And what I realize now is that he was just in the wrong place
Superman
Had gone to wherever Owens going
He would be on Infowars
You might you might have a show
Yeah Google look up obviously is a tragic thing
Need to see but my experience with scars
Stripes was
Is a hostile place
Not always
The best time
But there was a very rarely a lack of reaction
Whenever most people were performing
Silence
When you're doing a l o yeah it's
8-bit that's terrifying
Is a performer
Did you win committing to like
Bad character that you're getting nothing
Not good not good
It's the silence that's worse than
The yells at least I can work with it
Are you watching TV right now with silence is what you've got to retreat to that like making Apple ID
Medical point to get Applause room and bring things back into a lake
Alright I'm actually
Here eliciting a response from these people okay we can
Maybe try again
Yeah
He stays on the
The shooting
Subject a little bit about Uvalde
And how's the market police didn't respond if I was writing the setlist
Might change it
Thanks
I have to tell you
Right here
Stephanie ruhle
Do you know about Stephanie
Probably not
N400
Prepared
What's the argument
Kindergarten teacher
Virtue signaling to Gunn sheet with like Army
The teachers but like
I guess if you're in that space and you really believe that arming teachers is the solution of
All of them
Disarm everybody everybody with a gun in their hands because you know it's going to take five minutes for the police to show
Show up even in under perfect circumstances
Fine whatever I get that that's your beliefs is right
But
I think
Just looking at it through clear and sober eyes
400 police not responding right
The teacher being on arms is not the problem
Right
Write this is much bigger
Problem that is a 440
No idea
The teacher is the teacher had just been better
Is what he say
Well if the teacher had had access to guns to be better
Sure honestly then you have to ask yourself why didn't
The teacher take upon themselves just be armed and basically saying that
If your students die it's your fault as the teacher and the inactivity of the police is not
An indication of a systemic problem
Right there over there working
But
Yeah I don't know I get
But it's
It's it's not that it's not thawed out in the way these other b r
It's just
The fanservice
I mean it's cuz I think he thinks there's
The turn he thinks that Saturn is
You say 400 police off
Officers and then you put it on the the single teacher
Do you know that's the turn
I guess yeah
And it's
It doesn't actually make sense it's it's more structured like a Norm Macdonald joke where the premise
And the punchline are the same
Sentence you know
But it's not funny
Because it doesn't make any sense
So I will get to talk in a little bit about abortion
The top hot topics
All over
About abortion
Protester
And we have a crazy liberals and a good comic references his own videos
Yes
Material so strong
What women are naked and they cover themselves
Tennis courts
Starbucks
Don't think that's going to happen
Used because
There's not really a
Joke other than calling to mind what
He now he wants to characterize
Abortion protester
And then the statement that he's making is I think their tactics
Are ineffective
There's no joke what he needed to do at the end there is like what
They should do is
Or something
Funny idea of what they should do to protest
That would get a message across
Or something or
Hi Tana parody of
I don't know
Whatever
After complaining
About these
Being ineffective
The audience
So kind of expecting a
This for hundreds of years how jokes work is if you establish
In the context of being a
Comedians that you have to follow it up with a punchline
Yeah of some sort other than like I think that's dumb
What I what I didn't realize really until just
Now is like
People who watch stand-up a don't do it
Right when they
They don't
Realize that the biggest liar
Comedian says is I don't understand
Like if you are writing a joke
When you say I don't understand
Because at the end of the joke
You will have made a point
Because secretly you always understood the whole time understand in order to watch
Play a dumb person
Play the movie you don't like that
I think
Obviously
Obviously a man but he doesn't actually understand what he's talking about so he's like
I'm killing it
I think then just
This is dumb
Like I think that stripe
And if you're expecting
To carry you on stage you are sorely mistaken
It works for Alex though we saw that
About a long time might work now
Deliworks
Brought that brutal
So we get to International affairs
Terrible it is
Terrible
Petlab
Stationary osisoft
What time is it
It's okay
Anything that they do it
Phoebus Athena stuff wow
Soldier Boy
No laughter they're supposed to work on things
And the comparison between the two of them immediately striking
By position
Contrast with each other you reveal how similar things are treated differently
For instance you can look at historical sentencing Trends between crack
And cocaine
Orson
Between white and black people who commit similar crimes and by doing so
You reveal a hidden truth about Society
Right that's kind of what I want thinks he's doing here by saying that went to close up
Does it it's good
But the problem with this
Is that these Arden Allegan situation
What own is referring to as the Keystone XL pipeline
This is a private company
TC energy that had applied for a permit to build this Pipeline and were rejected by Obama
In 2015
If you prove it and then Biden withdrew the permit
That's when he became president
Boil from Canada will still make its way to refineries in the US but it won't be done
With its pipeline that endanger surrounding areas
Allegiant all sorts of other concern
As for Putin
He's threatening to literally cut off oil supplies two areas of Europe that rely on that oil to provide essential service
This is not a matter of convenience and profit
Like with the Keystone XL
It's a situation where someone is actually restricting access
These situations are so completely different that Owens joke is
Confusing as a statement
And the only really at the way the distance
Be construed
Is funny is if you imagine that Owen is doing a carrot
Who's a parody of his own ideology meant to highlight how superficial
Their understanding of issues is and how they celebrate their own willful ignorance
But it's not
Owain is just dumb
And his understanding of this stuff is superficial
Any celebrates his own willful ignorance and
Expectant audience to applaud for it
You can really
If you understand that subject
It's being discussed
The only conclusion you can really take away from the point of that joke is
Is I like Putin and I don't like by
Yeah I mean I know people that
Think that comedians are stupid
And for good reason
We've earned it
But what
We do
Is
Pinkberry
Very hard
About what we're going to say on stage
Regardless of how old your intelligence is beyond that
So people who you might think are like
Enable to do long division
Are still capable of coming up with intense insights
Through this medium
Kissing on something very very well
An understanding it totality
Its totality trial
Such a large part of being able to deliver.
Basically what you're seeing here is somebody who's not respecting
The idea of doing stand-up
Have like
A joke like this
If you were if you thought it made sense
Did you went out to open mics
Tried it a few times
You didn't get a response
You might start questioning like
Why is does it not make sense
Is there something I'm missing about this
I might just order instinctually you try to figure a way to readjust
The things that you're saying to your at
How to tell the
The point that you think you're trying to make it a different way
To elicit a response from the audience
Because they would land on
I understand what you're saying
I mean just
Beyond
The more elevated ways of
Looking at how
What comedians write jokes
Here's a simple
If
You think you have too many words
You have three times as many words as you should
I mean he needs to get rid of
90%
It's much like with the documentary
Trinidad
So I hear about this bribery
I forgot that
You didn't
Anything that they do need a driver ASAP
Going one
Storytime show going on
Daddy
Anyway
Call back to the earlier joke about Saudi Arabia buying golf
Right which I admire him trying
It didn't really land as well as I think he wanted it to least attempt a call back which is
Second
Belts who is yellow belt level
Flawed premise
In this joke
You contradicting his entire worldview that is
Going to be Pride parades is an attempt to make kids gay
That is their whole grooming thing ideas
So you're negating everything that you say not on sale
Yes in order to I guess
Call people at Pride parades
Clowns expose is that
The joke is the joke
About
How's the people at
The pride parade are clown
Spoiled there's one point in that is the you couldn't get away with the stuff that they get away with
Which is just the victimhood and persecution complex expressions
What get away with what she
That's the way into the Joker
I see that and then yes it's not a sex thing there clowns you'll be afraid of clowns
Like clowns
And then
Guy at baseball
To gay I mean really that's you're going to say that you're
You've thought about this
It's your own Shroyer
Then after you thought about it
And set it on stage you decided to post this the internet so other people can be clear
The only reason I'm treating this this way is because it's labeled Owen Shroyer stand up special
Temperature
England
These are bits
Yep this isn't something that
He's just talkin off the Dome
These are at there's a call back
Back there
Joke structure in some of these things that he saying
Preparation
And that's why I'm freaking
Proper
It's why I'm giving you the business
Treating it like it's someone trying
Because
It is
Stay out of our fuckingworld Owen
If you want to walk in here you're going to have to learn how to write a joke
I would like to make clear that I have given it up on a couple of
Applications where there's like okay
This isn't like the vibe
This guy's not black cuz I didn't vote for Biden absolutely that's a fine joke the
Play the fancy about Hunter buying a
Camera to film a crack deal
Potential right I'm not I'm not saying none of this
Almost
You don't like it
You're taking a very good sport attack
Towards the way and this is how kind of how we treat
Young newer comedians
Currently as we both
Substance and up
I did my best to
It just encouraged anyone
From ever trying to to do
I focus on all the bad joke
I really went into your face I was like this is why this is bad I have no idea where you're getting the idea that I would
I wanted to hide from
Open strong Gallo strong
You can get away with a good deal of this Meandering nonsense in the middle if you come in with like
Just burning the house down with you and then a closer if you're closer is 10 minutes
And it's really good
You can do a bad
20 in the middle and you'll be fine
I guess week I would say that is open
Was weak cuz it was mostly that Biden cancer chunk
Yeah and I don't think that really played
Sounds
Consonant
That's what it's all about
Calvin and Hobbes map
Right that's not a
We don't hold false idol.
If that was on
It all my God that's the funniest thing he's ever said
Response from the audience of any of the things
Is any of his
Yeah no the problem is he meant it
That's why it's terrible sort of expression
It's like a someone saying
Look at the end of their set like
Let me be serious for a minute here except
Is a joke after serious
Again
Incidentally
The funniest thing that he's ever said I can't imagine a fun of your things
Then like
If aliens come down
To Earth
Anne askew
To take you to their leader you hand them the Bible what kind of insane world
View is that where you're like
Not only
Am I not
Think about that
But all of these people are going to
Clapping
Scream how great I have for doing that
That is a maze
This is this is Owens closer to and what is that
Accepted expression of virtue signalling to Christianity
Signal to aliens there is nothing
You should have done to take
To your dealer
There's nothing
About this baby is an attempt to being funny
Is just demonstrating your virtue to an audience and them applauding
In for it
This is exactly what
He has gone on ran
People on Infowars
Peterson's of the world all talk about this being
The cancer of the left and how they approach being funny
Healing humor
Bulshit
Version of all the exact same thing
Yeah I mean this is really really tragic
How's the traffic
Really bad I mean the problem is
The problem is
This is a man
Who is posting that video
Well someone
Well I guess he allowed it I mean I assume if I had if I had that on my wrecker
Every gone I would be telling that I would I would
The producers of the show
I have talked to producers of the show The Past who recorded it and I told them
Don't play this
Because I am embarrassed of how bad it
Listen to me in the past sure
Yeah
I think that a woman should have
Vicodin
Click click
No
I thought we could use a little bit of a momentary breath
Of something different than
The trial in the documentaries that Delight
Shop
I don't think it owns getting JFL
I agree but I agree I don't want to sleep think
Bass
Just on
Talent
And Merritt
That wouldn't even
Fly at a bad local show
In Chicago
Struggle to get a response at an open
Recognize
Is the hubris of doing 18 minutes
18 minutes
18 minutes and Dan how many how many producers stories do both of us have along the
The lines of somebody's like
I've got forty minutes of material of really want to go up on you show it is my first time doing stand-up comedy but
I know it's going to be great
This is that
Yeah this is that
It's bad hubris to not recognizing
Is something like box
Jackson has much as like it
Seems like a shorter time than it actually is
Like a 3-minute round in a lifetime
In the boxing ring is
Tough to fill
If you care about it being
Good entertaining for the people you're talking to
Exactly 18 minutes
Is a f****** lifetime
Answered
Destroyer Destroyer stand-ups has he been cut
Something else
Who knows when do now
Everywhere you can't
Turn away from us
Easley Texas freedom
Jordan
Back out Bujo
Omio I'm Leo I'm busy
Clark I hope you all have a wonderful dream mccreamy song
Robot
Holding