Air Jordan X swetik
I have great respect but knowledge B I'm sick of them posing
Shane we are the bad guys
MoneyGram
Knowledge fight
Dot-com
In this hotel room
Jordan
Hey buddy my brakes but Jordan is that I went to the 7-Eleven
PG&E Isle
Always been a big fan of Swedish
Fish
Really Galaxy
Oh wow
Yeah I think it's probably something to do with my dad
Like growing up
Some of the things he really like
Swedish
I like
Swedish Fish my dad like Swedish fish but also he was a big fan of like
The pan and that one
Karaoke I don't like marzipan
But Swedish Fish are fine
Of a Swedish Fish and Friends
That was excited to make friends
Do fishes make friends
Awake too long
There are new flavors
There's a strawberry dolphin and a watermelon turtle
Parsley the original is better
That's great
Defensive today I really Norwegian turtle
Happy
My bright spot is that boy
It's Saturday at the that I'm not I don't have to lie to any trial
How do I bright spot yeah that is true you get the day off
Just as I type a lot it's really hard
It hurts your feet
Yeah I don't know how you do it
I wrote I think
Twenty thousand words yesterday
In the book
So yeah
Three of those hangers soft and gentle all day
Well
I'm happy for you text
Get ready for Monday the Bruce Lee two-finger push that you're right I got to step up my game
Do Jordan
Today
We are doing
The thing that we have to do and that is the follow-up
Up to Alex's War
Our coverage of that
After the premiere of that
Film
They did a little qna
Where Glenn Greenwald interviewed Alex Jones and Alex
Documentarian
I do Direct
Activist film
They did not have
It's really working in the sound is really terrible for the portion where Moyer was interviewed
About any of that
I would be
Maybe not actually maybe it's best to not know exactly how that interview went
Right so we just got Alex's junk
And honestly it's like
40-something minutes
Sullivan interview and
I mean it sucks
But it's going to take more than 40 minutes
Talk about
I'm surprised
Fairly certain
So how are your feelings going in
My feeling is that it's going to be Glenn Greenwald
Doing the softball Lisa vanderveer like not even softball questions not
Tee-ball question
Seems like he's swinging the bat for Alex
To try and get that ball across the f******
That's what I feel
We'll see if that lives up to your expectations
Okay
So what before we get into
The actual interview I have two things I want to say
I've some comment
Excited
So I've been tracking some reactions
This new documentary about Alex
And I have to say
That I've just been seeing more and more s*** Tay
It's sincerely unbelievable to me that anyone could watch this film and come away except
The argument that the producers and director just showed Alex
As he is
That's such an offensive in gaslighting farce that I feel the need to address this again
And really sharpen the point that I make
On the day before the film was released Matt Taibbi publisher fawning interview with director Alex Lee Moyer on his Subs
Any thinner duck
Directions to the interview
Quote
She takes characters reduced in panicked media treatments
The two dimensional
Attitude dimensional monsters
And renders a non-judgmental totally edited
Bruce doggy and treatment of who
Who they are and how they came to be that way
This is absolute nonsense if I were Herzog I would not take kindly
To this kind of a suggestion
But I want to ask what
Exactly is meant by non judge
Damental here
That seems like a really important concept to nail down because it's
Seems like this is something Moyer and the film's Defenders are real
Really proud of being
I would guess that from the other things I've read non-judgmental to these folks means that they don't include critical
Voices in their film
Provide any other input and then they pat themselves on the back
Whole bunch
The courage to let the audio
Decide what
About the subject of the film
Guess
It's fine to not include critical voices in a film
But I really don't think that you're going to be able to say that you and tried to
Portray your subject as they are
You're just portraying your subject how they want
You to see them
For example Alex lies constantly and contradicts himself about biographical information in this
Spell
But you aren't introduced to somebody expressing that point in the film
Do you have no reason to suspect
Alex is being anything but on
The audience is being allowed to make up their own mind I guess
But their options are believing Alex
Or choosing not to
Which state have no reason to do based on the film they're watching
Another important point is that your editing the film according to the whim of your
Jack which makes it nearly impossible
For an uninformed viewer to make up their mind for themselves
If you're watching this film nothing about it would give you any reason to distrust Alex's assertion
The only reason anyone was mad at him
About Sandy Hook
Was because he
Do you like Trump
And they needed something to smear him
There's no reason at all
From the material in this film to not conclude that
Sandy Hook parents
Like Neil heslin or Scarlett Lewis who we've been in the courtroom with this week
Or just
Tools of an overzealous Democratic machine
Desperately to punish Alex for supporting
Drop
That assertion
That narrative
That Alex Telles
He's not presented as just
This guy is saying
The film is structured around defending that narrative
The only outcome
Of accepting lawyers claim that this is just non-judgemental and presenting Alex how he is
Would be the conclude that she either believes Alex's version
Of this story
Or she edited her film in a way to strengthen the story fully aware
But it was full of s***
And is now bragging about how great she is for not indicating that the
The audience of maybe shouldn't trust this claim at all
Odd
We've done this f****** stupid Dance all over like over and over again with idiots like Rogan who want to have their cake
Eat it too but then they also want pie
They want to talk to and platform dangerous lunatics
Whitewash their images
I think don't want to be
Criticized for it
And not only that
They want to be treated like a real heroes for Having the courage
To do what they do
And much like with Rogan
I don't buy that s***
From lawyer
If you're doing a documentary about a liar or a
Con man
And you don't include any content critical of that liar Orkin man in your film
You aren't doing a documentary
The conman is using you as a medium to spread their message to an audio
They wouldn't have access to otherwise
You do have a responsibility
In that circumstance
Whether you choose to accept it or not
To be totally clear
Here is more in her own words
On how she approaches her filmmaker
This is from that interview with Taibbi
Quotes
This is what I'm going to
To do with all of the documentaries that I make by the way including the one I just made about Alex Jones
It's not meant to confirm your biases
It's meant to actually show you what these
These people are actually like and then you can make an informed
Decision based off watch
Sing the film
Used to be called journalist
This was said in response to her telling a story about how she had investors not want to support her first film because she
You wouldn't include the voices of people who have been harmed
By misogynist in School shooters
We just met
Connect to Sonata critical voices of Alex
In this film
It is very real
She's kind of engaging in censorship here because guess what ding dong
A huge part of who Alex actually is and what he's actually like
Is that he knows that he's caused people an enormous amount of pain and he doesn't give a s***
By not giving voice to that and not
Exploring that side of him
The kind of covering up that aspect of his psyche because it's inconvenient
Probably too difficult of a subject
Free to pull off in this
Softball ask documentary
Now let me
Play focus on in on my point about Moyers approach
By applying it to a different
But let's imagine
Alex is actually
Could be called a fair portrait
Henry provided the audio
With enough information to make it informed
Decision
I totally don't believe that
But that's going to be the standard that will apply to another situation
And see how it
Feels like they're really going to wish they hadn't said
I'm going to throw that out that you're right now I don't think it's going to go well for them I just don't think they're going to stand up to it that's just me
What would Warrior say about someone who made a documentary like hers but Jim Jones in like I don't know
Right when he was forming Jonestown in Guyana
What is that person just let Jim Jones tell his own story lying the whole time with no pushback from
From the director or anyone in the film at all
You think the Jim Jones would be
Able to spend
A pretty good yarn to be able to make the ID
Heading to his compound
Pretty decent idea
People were having a great time and he was spreading a real message of love and unity
The word of God
Guys coming through
Now let's imagine further that this hypothetical documentarian knew that there were former members of the peoples Temple
Would left and allege that Jim Jones had abused them both physically and sexually
Did people have come forward in LA
Did Jim Jones punish dissenters by starving them
And ostracizing them from socializing with the rest of
The community
This documentarian news those things but decided not
Include any of them in the film because of a commitment
Jim Jones
As you really are
Well and everybody knows that's when that happened all of those people who left
They were just hired by Carter
To smear Jim Jones everybody knew that
Now let's imagine that this hypothetical filmmaker edited together their documentary in such a way that
Swelling music
Play Dover hero shots of Jim Jones
And almost relive
Religious soundscape service
Does the background for him talking about his religious Awakening
Spell let's imagine that this hypothetical filmmaker allowed Jim Jones
Framing of his life
To inform the structure of their documentary and how the story was told
So like you were touching on
In this documentary
They do end up mentioning the allegations of abuse of his followers
But it's not brought up as a negative thing about him
It said it's only mentioned is something that Jim brushes off to the side as an attack from the power structure
Who were afraid of the religious Revolution that he was involved in
It is communist
Indiana and the possibilities
Verapose I should have made a more extreme joke it said that was too obviously just what would have happened
Well that's the parallel documentary
The mass murder that ended Jonestown
Happened
That's so maybe some edgy assholes of the day would say that this documentary filmmaker
Was just giving a non-judgmental view of this public figure who somewhat polarizing
And if I were somebody who study
Jim Jones back then
As I am somebody who studies Alex Jones right now
I would say that's complete
Bulshit
Bring Jim Jones it exactly the way
He wants to be portrayed with no,
Context and no countervailing information
He's very likely to leave viewers to adopt a more positive view of him
And that would be a dangerous thing
To be involved in
Dan
I want to run through a brick wall for you right now
I want to bounce
My f****** ahead it gets like let's stop
Record Exchange
Jim Jones
What's happen
Right now
I'm sure that the rebuttal to this would be that Alex Jones is no Jim Jones
I am sure
He doesn't have a Jonestown
But you're delusional if you think that Alex doesn't pose as much
Potential danger is Jim Jones.
Approach your essentially legitimizing to figure your covering and making people more likely to
To follow them
And as we've seen over the course
Doing the show
I went to the completely unhinged child unable to control his emotional outburst
Who constantly tells his audience
To keep a list of globalist in their town so they'll know who to kill when
The time comes
He's told his audience that it might be
Time to consider if you could
Kill your family members if they see
Support vaccinations
Extols the message that psych meds or mind control weapon
Effective
Making people not seek mental health care or even worse
Just stop taking medications that therefore
Prescribed
Ask the people of Boston is Alex's actions have real-world consequences
Have the people at the Sandy Hook victims
Family member
Ask the families
Igor soldo Allen Beck
Joseph Wilcox
The three people who are murdered by Jared and Amanda Miller in 2014
Murders that were inspired by their anti-government views and which Jared had discussed
Beforehand
On the Infowars forum
Ask the family of tragic
Deceased Marcel Fontaine
These are stories that we know
And there'll be just the tip of the iceberg of the lives
I've been changed
Permanently by Alex's behaviors
And Alex doesn't
Give a s***
He continues acting in the exact same ways that he did that led to
To these people's grief
Because it's profitable
And these voices are ignored and disrespected in this documentary because
Actually covering Alex as he really
Is would be way too hard
I suspected it would have resulted in the kind of movie that lawyer wanted to make
I would have resulted in 710 episodes of some sort of
I think that might have Abby what that might be what would have happened
It definitely wouldn't have resulted in the sort of movie that you was looking for kids
Considering that at least two of the producers of this film
We're also producers of
Trump propaganda nonsense film
The plot against the president
Alex William boiler made a stupid and inaccurate film one that will fit
It's information that calls into question the subject
Self delivered image of himself
It's a bad movie and it will hurt
People but
It's her right to make it
I hope the money that you made doing it is worth
They put please spare me the sanctimonious
Bulshit about how people
Handle
That you do journalism
Your cut-rate editor producing semi-slick character study
Not have Alex Jones
The person Alex Jones
He is
Basically yours Embark if you think what
This documentary shows is Alex as he really is
Also before we get into this Q&A I need to make one more point
Crystal clear
The framing that Moyer has about her own work
That isn't even real
She isn't interested in seeing the subject
It's as big as they are in this is some sort of Purity to it
And the most obvious hell is that she interviews Owen Shroyer Rob do and Mike Hansen in the documentary
They don't provide a glimpse into Alex as he really is
Interviewing them doesn't
Just show Alex's to using what's an audience decide for themselves
They are included because they're sycophantic
Voices that aleko the self-aggrandizing narrative that Alex is telling about him
Which is the story that boiler wants to tell
Including interviews with people who glorify Alex's counter to her pretend ethos
It kind of makes a joke of her insistence of not interviewing critical voices
Pretense of journalistic purity
That is cut
Condescending mask she's wearing so she can elevator puff piece
Grand Rehabilitation project into some kind of active reporting
It's so brave that we can't even understand it
I reject that s*** entirely and it's really sad to see people with actual media careers
Falling for this kind of an act
And I can't stress
That's enough
You would have more things
Put you some kind of an uncritical observer
Just dispassionately relaying the story of valak
She's deluded
Do the Creator
And he's created
I'm Puttin biases are impossible not
I have an imp
Princeton
In a piece about the movie's premiere in the New York Magazine these lines made me think
Maybe she's not so
Impartial of a jacket
Material issues
What might that be
Quote she watch the X-Files research serial killers
Conspiracies and generally respected misfit
Disdain for Authority was normalize back then she says where is now people worship power in believe and toeing the line
Line for the state
Liberal Outlets
She thinks have unwittingly live credibility to figures like Jones thanks to their credulousness about official narrative
Calling conspiracy theories are just going to be news-item 6-month
It's from now she says
There were wmds covid came from a bath
This is just
Saying Alex's catchphrase in a lesson Commander
Infowars
Tomorrow's news today
Last bit of business
Glenn Greenwald has a penchant for run on set
So in order to prevent this Q&A and is fair of a light as possible
I've attempted to preserve as much of like
That as possible
Dammit
Some clips that are longer than I would like in Rambling the answering questions but I would rather risk
Annoying you
Being censorious
Just cuz I am not a very important person
Doesn't mean that I shouldn't
Be okay with you treating me like this
Are you feeling
I mean
Just it's just sad
It's so sad she sucks
Like just
On a level of like
Quality like you just suck
Play shity music
But it's not like she had good
Didn't have Radiohead or anything on there
Boosted up
The documentary got a copyright strike
Without
Definitely just having Owen Shroyer on there a man who's literally a puppy
A selfie
Yeah
The subject of the documentary what are you going to second
Wait a second like what what is Jeff Dunham's
Hand up a puppet ass going to say in a documentary about it is that okay
Would say mean things
But that's not the point is going to say anything meaningful in the documentaries like William
Essentially unemployable in any other media so
Situation
Stuck here I'm saddled with this absolute about my boss that right
Wall Alex's hand is right all the way up my ass controlling my mouth I'm going to be like
I think he might go to
Too far sometimes
This is nonsense idea of that like
I'm just showing him as he is it's so
Keto diet
The fact that you sought out my cat
Alex akya his current employees are at the time current employees also
A dubious move
Inclusion in there is like
Skip get off your f****** high horse
Pretending that
Input is Mike Hanson giving that shows Alex as he actually is right
Nothing no
It's giving Mike Hansen
Impression of Alex
Which
Is a positive one
You exclude all negative
Impressions of Alec
Because
You're not up to the task of telling that f******
Yeah
It is time together with what I'm learning during this whole f******
Experience down here is that
All of these people are f***
Cowards
Who are afraid of anybody challenging them
And because they have a rabbit
Fanbase that will
Attack
People who do challenge them
A lot of people don't discover that their car
Stab this little group of people who
Them and keep them from ever having to
Realized
That they're a bunch of
You f****** cowardly
Lee baby's no competence or quality at anything
I mean like Alex's 90 bodyguards
Jesus Christ
Night there were bodyguards for
Nobody showing up to court at all you missed it you missed the best one whenever I left the other day
He went out he want to cross
What's the street to go get a hero or stuff it right
And his 10 bodyguards were surrounding him and they were doing
The funniest like Mission Impossible last Maneuvers like
People are checking the corner in like I got your
Marius there is no one there they're doing these Mission Impossible ass
Organizational moves it is
The f****** sad
Really long meeting before they go public about like all right we got to keep an eye out for milkshakes
Dakota and Alex get milk and no offense at all but one of his bodyguards is 5 ft
I'm not joking.
Bill up in the air whether or not
You'll never know it kinda looks like somebody from that Beastie Boys video
The size of Mike Ditka
His forehead is what I would like to describe it as
So without further Ado Jordan let's let's jump in on this Q&A
This is not going to not be
For you
Anyway it starts
Compliments
Already
Alex has not yet on stage
So this is just Greenwald & Moyer
Explaining what I thought
Was never necessary deuce
Language is
If you're a journalist for example going
Speak to someone
Without making clear whether you love that purr
I hate that person
But simply to try it on
Understand them is kind of
Fundamental to wipe
Journalist
Supposed to do and I think that's
The same for filmmakers and artists in.
Cemetery entrance
The fact that you even have to explain yourself the fact
Unusual
To watch a film
Without
Constantly being bombarded with a
The filmmakers
Is moral perspective
Testament to just how our process
The society is
Be calm and I really want to congratulate
You for resisting that and
We're kind of restoring what I think is
The purpose of
Art in journalism
In film documentary and nnn documentaries which is to
Show the public
Information
The payout of having
And let them decide what they think about it is
Supposed to shoving that
Conclusion down there
Facing
Life is a lot easier for you as I said if you would
Chosen a different route but I think
Pixellot of Courage
Free to do that and I think
So I want to congratulate
Thanks Glenn
I feel like one of the defining characteristics of people you really shouldn't listen to our people that have a Mindless need to
To be an opposition
Princeton
I think you're delusional if you don't think that Glenn
Bully for this documentary shows a portrait of Alex is in Subway
By the fact that all of the media voice
He doesn't like our saying it's
Not
I think if you watch this film and you see that this is
Glenn's take
He's just a loser
This film isn't providing the information that people need to make an informed
Decision
It's not just a dispassionate exercising journalism that people are
Just mad at because it doesn't include the requisite
Performance of outrage
That's the line these ding dongs
Tell themselves so they can feel morally Superior to everyone else
Well they Trot out their exploitative vanity
The projects
Let's look at this idea of an in
Informed decision
I would argue that in order to make an informed
You need to have all the relevant
Information about a sub
For instance it would be inappropriate for a pill to Market itself bikes
Exclusively talking
Think about the positive things that
I can do well completely neglect
Sing the potential side effects
Mexican hat
Similarly it wouldn't serve a person at all if the coverage of a pill Focus
Entirely on the potential side
And ignored the thing that its effect
Active entreating
Either of these
Would give the person a lot of information about the
The pill in question
But neither would give them what they needed to make it in form
Choice
It might give them the feeling that they have that informed choice
But the feeling is an illusion
This documentary does not give the viewers the information they need to make any kind of an informed decision about alley
In order for this film to actually be something that the viewer can watch and make up their own mind about
The viewer would need to already enter the film knowing that Alex is a liar and nothing he says can really be taking his
Sincere
You already need to know that there's a reason not to trust him before
For you watch
And that's an absurd expectation to have for most
Viewers who are randomly coming into this
I talked to the people
Periodically and they're like what you do I got to do podcast by Alex who's that
Do you know he's not somebody who everyone knows about there's a lot of people have an uninformed opinion about him right
You go into this
Documentary
It all the information that he provides
Is income
Yep that's a
Glenn thinks he knows who Alex is
Documentary provides
People he doesn't like don't like the movie so he's gung-ho by patting himself on the back
Congratulating more unattractive than the lighting
Filmmaking
Basking in the wrong f****** delusion
And it was straight and how little they know about the subject that they're actually
I mean it's disgusting
I I can't imagine what her next film Mussolini of profile in Courage is going to be about but
I think I've heard that it shows a balance
View of Mussolini right up until 1941
Justin and he's a great guy
Not understood I think she'll need to over correct
I'd like to do some film about
Something
Little Michael right-wing angry
Or something if she overcorrected to jump off a
So that's that's the wrong kind of overcorrected artistically overcorrected and
Yeah I don't know
A puff piece about
Eco-terrorists or something like that I don't know
Well
Alex comes out here we are
Alright so do you want to end the weirdness of talking about Alex Jones
Right in front of him
If he's not here and bring them up on stage
Get up your AJ
Does he have a mic
Yeah he should have a night
We can share
Usher
No I mean
I haven't asked
Operators attack
21 years old
And I but I meant everything purity
I made a lot of mistakes I'm a lot of bad stuff it wasn't on purpose
Greenwald
Print figure with Alex Hoyer
And the thing is I didn't lie on purpose I made a lot of mistakes
But I'm not some person getting orders in line
And I want to get better
Where I'm at
Glad you made it film
That just kind of shows what we've done cuz I look at it
Horrifying obnoxious
And then parts of it are good but I mean
Anna
Deal of the day
Like I did not lie to him on purpose
I didn't mean to say some purpose in
I'm glad you guys made it snow
So Alex I mean actually begin by asking you a little bit
About that in terms of your intention
So this is a good indication of how stilted this q&as
I need decent interviewer might hear that opening
Statement that Alex made and first say are you okay
And after clearing that up you would probably point out that
Prompted
Alex just said that they
Didn't ever intentionally lie three times in about a minute
What kind of feels like somebody who lies intentionally really trying to stress that they don't
Do that
Hey if your instinct isn't to follow up on that I guess you're just a better journalist than I can ever imagine being
Also weird not to latch onto that we are 90% accurate client
Seems like that's something they could stand to be explored like how do you quantify that does that actually mean anything or is that just an evasive
Catchphrase
That you used to try to Dodge Ridge
Possibility for the horrible things you say
Sure
When you're forgetting Shakespeare's Immortal line you know me thinks you can't
Possibly protest
Methinks you doth can't test it all
Why would you
You're too right all the time
I mean
What is majestic
Are you on
So Glen Glenn has started into a quest
Here's where you go
And if you're expecting it to be like hey
Let me ask you about that
You say you don't lie
That's out
So Alex I mean actually begin by asking you a little bit
About that in terms of your intentions and end the lake be
Because I
But I remember when I watched
The felony was just so striking this early footage of you and I remember when
When the internet person
Discovered some of the early picture
Pictures of you from your Public Access days in Austin
I remember liberals being almost
Was horrified liquid
Is cognitive dissonance like we're supposed to look at images
Screaming spitting monster and Yeti
These pictures are disturbing they handsome
And it's like very normal way you are now
Charisma a natural charisma
Even sat in the front
When you combine that your soul
You had when you were young
Is a great question clearly
Had you been somebody who was willing to affirm rather than question established
Heidi's
Could have ended up as like
A meteorologist on
My Good Morning America or like some Anderson
Super tight
And I'm wondering
If you were aware of that but
Angel
And purposely chose
To reject it for a
Print out the sky
Outcast that wears
Restaurant Dubai delightfully
Or whether it was just so natural to your personality.
You never even consider trying to tip
Anime
Acceptability
I was thinking about driving her today
So
That's where Glenn goes
Baptist first question
Over Alex's three times in a minute that he doesn't lie on purpose but he's right 90% of the time
The open with a question predicated on how Alex was a handsome young man
This is just pathetic because track this question
It's basically asking did you make a conscious decision to not be as rich and famous as your talents would make you deserve
Because
You were too invested in questioning the power structure
Is it just in your instinctual nature to be a rebel who questions the power structure
So the decision to not be super rich
Famous wasn't even the decision
It's basically like are you so awesome by choice or by Nature you almost went too long
For me I would have gone with why is your dick so big
How did it get so big that is biggest
That's another reading of it
This s*** is embarrassing
Partially
Cuz it's basically answered in the
The film but also because it kind of ignores the reality that
If I ever tried to get a job where he'd have a boss or advertisers that word a shady gold salesman
Help book about where to hide guns
He wouldn't have lasted more than a month
He is talented but he's not that talented to the point where an employer would look past his
Stream oppositional-defiant
Because he's got the goods
He's no Howard Stern
Let's say
No no no no no
Is predicated on a false constructive what Alex
Could and could not have done as a younger man
Yes you was he
Yes he was talented
But
He was also Alex Jones that whole time
If you take his story in the documentary at all seriously
You shouldn't have
To ask this question
Alex talks about how he got fired from a radio station cuz he wouldn't stop talking about Waco
Alex took the path
He did because it was
The only path of available to him that allowed him to
To satisfy his need for attention
A nobody to ever be able to tell him what
To do
Quite something really this Q&A was never going to be hard-hitting but
I didn't
Predicted open this flaccid
Here if you want to do that
Beatles like Hey listen
You had that moment where there were two paths
Becoming a rock
God working grocery
Are you know
What was it
That really turn that
And I would have been like hey Alec
You could have been a father of at least
Why didn't you become that
Eloquent doesn't know any list
Why did you become a
Infowars
Excuse me have you ever heard your own story about your childhood why didn't you put it in this
F****** movie
I'm going to guess that Glenn's awareness of Alex
Starts and ends with things that are in this documentary and
The fact that everybody doesn't like him
And maybe a few of the like really
Broad
The things that people know like he was against
What's the Iraq War
He hates the establishment
M4
Gunn was for the Iraq War so is his buddy Tucker
Weird
Anyway here is Alex's answer to that question of
Well it's actually how big that dick
Or whether it was just so natural to your personality that
You never even consider trying to
Except
Possibility
I was thinking about driving her today
What I wanted to say and I'm bitter
God you brought that up
No no no church but now it's really intuitive
My enemies shall miss Lex Luthor Mastermind
And we do say that are a moron of that
I had no idea
Balto
And politics
And read like
Books by
Did you make it with this key in like these were scary things
But I had no training no idea no plan
And this idea that like
A mastermind
It's in the shop
You know I am so
Am I put myself down
He literally think I'm like this evil mastermind
And I literally can't
Project book
And they're just like attacking me
Constantly
Where's the music
I might I'm just covering the news I was just my opinion
And so. I had no idea what I was doing
I just was
Okay
Have a Libertarian like
Did like Republicans that like Democrats
And I was just watching
The TV
I tried to go to college and try to get rgf job
Disney Radio
That was it was basically
My mom political beliefs
Lourdes pro-freedom
But I got involved it was immediately successful
That I was like
Trying to figure out is that when I'm trying to be truthful
But none of it was
None of it was murdered anybody
Yeah we talked about the mistakes for sure
In a few minutes
Wouldn't be a complete
Discussion
Without that before we get to that
Why
Why wouldn't I be a complete
Discussion
This isn't really an answer to Glenn's question but Glenn doesn't give a s***
In fairness I guess it's like a half answer with an answer to a
Completely different question mixed in
Also you might notice that Alexander been trampled by against
He never meant to lie and if you're Greenwald
The conscious choice to ignore that happening
So much
A neutral Observer would look at that behavior and say
This person really seems to be going out of his way to say that he doesn't lie on purpose and yet no one here is accused of
That seems like he's being super defensive about it maybe
If I want to have a folder
Discussion
To check in on that glaring Dynamic that's playing out right
In front of me
I guess you could just ignore it
Empower 30 your next softball question though that's certainly another
I mean I'm so
F****** serious
Glad already
Like it
It's like this is a dude who will go out of his way to
To try and destroy a young journalist career
School f******
Sick his sycophantic
Bulshit
People on other
Destroy their lives then I'm going f******
Safe Alex you got the biggest dick in the world
How do you walk with a dick this big
It's so cute but he won't even f****** talk to me
You won't even block
Me on Twitter
Do you know why
Cuz I don't have any f****** restraints that young journalist she could lose her job
She called him a giant shitball f*****
But instead we are we are untethered from the establishment
You can't what do you do
You doesn't have anything to gain I do think there is a really funny thing and that you're mad that he won't play
I want him to because this means that he knows and he's just a coward he doesn't even have the guts to acknowledge
I didn't see this beauty somebody who tweeted at him
But they said that he should listen to our show
So believe me
You know you know
That's a little suspicious
So
Glenn out here is his next
Question here
There's a little kernel of something
But in here actually
She already talked about the mistakes for sure
In a few minutes
Wouldn't be a complete
Discussion
Without that before we get to that
If you're polish
Exciting
This is what was tracking
Amy watching
The film is
There's a
You know if you have somebody with what political faction Radiology
What is Alex doing
And I'm watching
Can you
I wonder why
People thought about doing it
Spreading huge amounts of Sceptre
The u.s.a.
FBI
Begin spreading that kind of
Is the man before Alex your warning about the
Dangers of exaggerating
The threats have been Laden
Al-Qaeda in order to kind of bring It
Authority
Authoritarian and balanced
People very associated with the lab
I've been saying for a long time
2 Chainz
Authoritarianism warning about how big
White people's
Perception
The pop population in fear
How have you seen yourself
Ideology
Kaliyan NE
Politically linear
Alex was skeptical of all these organizations like the FBI and the CIA early on but there's also context it's missing for
From all of this
From Glen of malok themself
And certainly not from this film
Alex hated these groups not because of some kind of a principled opposition
And things like spying The Way Glen is framing the question
Alexander these group
Because of Waco Ruby rage in the Oklahoma City bombing
He distrusted them because after OKC the issue of right-wing militia violence was a high priority for law enforcement
Sirius Holt to the momentum that
The extreme-right was seeing in terms of organizing
It wasn't an opposition to the idea of spying or the FBI it was that Alex felt that they were focused on people who are too much
Like himself
Similarly his opposition to overhyping the threat of Bin Laden was also really just about his fears
About the government cracking down on far-right militia
He didn't oppose
Spying on like suspected Muslim terrorist for
He just thought it was a smoke
Scream to eventually spion
Christian nationalist extremist
Yeah I mean they might as well here's a better way of framing that question
Alex
You opposed the FBI because
Cuz they're not solely out
To get non-white
How long has that been going on
I don't have no way to know any of that stuff cuz he didn't prepare for this interview at all he doesn't know any
Nothing except for like a
It's not an excuse to make it worse exactly willful ignorance of the subject you're covering old
You do know some things and you're just pretending not to know that because
Will be inconvenient for the inertia
Yeah it's fine to give it up to Alex that on paper a lot of his
Positions about things like the NSA are good
Principal belief is a little bit much
Taking Alex seriously on this issue is honestly kind of funny because he's the last person I would accuse of being a serious Epona
Authoritarian leadership
For one thing he made
Cartoonish accusations about how like
Obama was going to become a tyrant like he was going to dissolve the government so he could turn the country into part of the oneworld caliphate that
Ruled the caliphate
Engaging with the notion of tyranny like this indicates a lack of seriousness about the
I'm not somebody who you should
Good job
Their thoughts on
Cuz they're not going to
Or you can look at how he behaved with Trump
He was cheering on Trump's authoritarian leanings at every turn and yelling
Further
He wanted Trump to imprison his political enemies take over the media militarize the border and Outlaw the Democrat
Credit party
If this is someone you're taking it all seriously on the subject of authoritarianism
The Joke is on You
Also Alex is politics are really simple
You look John Birch Society styled anti-communist reactionary who wants to install a white
Christian heterosexual dominate
State
I mean it's just it but he's not going to tell you that
Just don't know Glen
Gunn you don't have a place in Alex
As well just in case you were wondering
Good luck buddy good luck
You want a van over the guy who wants
Weird
Oh my God
Hey do know he's only going
After trans people right now
I'm sure whenever he's done with that
He's going to stop
That's how it works right
What you go after lgbtq you stop after one of the letters you don't go after all of
That makes sense
Glenn Glenn Miller in a hard lesson the Dave Rubin
Is learning
Concurrently
At some point
Enjoy there's no Freight in that no
Yeah
Alex response to this question that you very rightly pointed out Glenn was basically answering in the delivery of
And because I think
Maybe partially because of that Alex
I don't know the f***
Even this answer is
How have you seen yourself
Ideological
Kaliyan NE
Politically linear
Exactly exactly
Starting out
I got a 596
First
Communist Alex Jones
I was against the Warriors and surveillance
Legacy Mike what Bill of Rights
Real quick
94-95 Alex Jones is a communist
No way
How old was
Well first of all beginning his career.
The time
He was attacking from the right he's trying to pretend that he was called the Communist cuz he opposed bush
It sucks.
Acupuncturist misology to have that in
Background
How to be a right-wing ship bags
From the Star for sure
So this is bad
And I will just follow Constitution
I was simply
Thinking won't promote Freedom that's that's a fun thing to do
Actually work came from and then
And then
Machine
18 years ago or so
Should I want to fly you out here to California
Tu2ru
The song
We really love what you're doing so I get their house
So you're really a good liberal
Curious George George Bush
And they didn't care that I was pro-gun or either stuff is like
Let's have dinner right now
We're talkin like 18 years ago
Roast beef
Gene's house in Malibu
What's this place
I had no idea I private jet Landslide by the California
Exposing
I don't want to support
This is astonishing
Continuing
The same stuff so
To me I literally just
Access
TV like 21 years old
Russia located 23
Totally self-taught
Thomas tags
But Jennifer appoints the truth Hollywood
What it does and the right amount
I know this great experience
Over 28 years on air
Of like
Underbelly
Of all the stuff because I didn't come
Intuit
I literally came out of Access TV and also
The Texas
I got to see somebody else something
Show me some more questions
Question but whatever
There's no reason to ask a follow-up to the original question because
Brendan really care that much to begin with
Is really just a launch
Too bad for Alex
Let's go off on some rambling diatribe that
Eventually going to include him saying that he doesn't
Lie on purpose
At some point
It's very defensive
About that seem like that almost like he's about
To go on trial
What's this song trial here
Super defense
You don't really interesting no like except these stories with his left-wing folks like Martin Sheen mistake
Only thinking that he's on the list because he hated Bush but
You never really hear any stories about right-wingers
Who invited Alexander only to realize that he hasn't right-wing after all
You had like that Colter was on his show and she laughed at him for being so far right
He sounded like Lyndon larouche
But I don't think anyone on the right we'll talk to Alex
Suitable weight disappointed thing that always not on our side
Nobody
Doubt
Glenn has another question
For Alex
That is really just
Siteman
Show me some more questions
You know what is so striking when I begin running about politics
Open 2005
Let me ask you this
How does Anthony Hopkins like his roast beef
Liberals hated
More than anybody George Bush
The Architects of the Iraq War
I begin writing an APA
Rendition the
The torturers
Guantanamo and due process
Is Freddy imprisonment
It's just so striking
Implementing adware ad
Eating it Ark
Legally acceptable in fact
The love
Mainstream level circles liberals watch media Outlets
Zoom media Outlets
Polos people
As I was saying I could
Interview all of them and I would
You
Go back in 2004 work
Saying
Don't trust George W bush
His father was a CIA director the
The Iraq war is based on lies all things
Y'all
To that sensibility liberals you are
Uniquely cast
Hostile
Good,
The point where you're one of the very people
People that even journalists are called
Why is that why I have
You
Been identified
The rat in a way that others
People who actually have
Warriors on their legs
Aren't even
Even remotely
Answer my question and I
Only learned
Just went through
Experience of it but
I think I think going to take a piss
Concerned with himself and his good buddy Tucker
Who is a huge supporter of the war back in
Bowtie days
This is an interesting point although one that Alex has nothing interesting to stay to say on the subject
There has been some attempt to rehabilitate the images of people like George W bush and that's been a distasteful
Deceive
That said I don't think it's been as successful as Glenn is pretending and
I don't know how many falling pieces were seeing about
Dick Cheney or Karl Rove the
These days
Who is larger point though all the mainstream media Outlets have drunk people on their rosters of talking
Crackheads
Hi kellyanne Conway was just on CBS
Today and she was a person to draw
Hire to lie to the media for him
It does suck but media Outlets do feature some shity people but
Their people fall within a certain
Spectrum of shittiness
And most right-thinking people understand that Alex is outside that range
Works have a worm farm somewhere
I suspect that a giant part of Alex's
No not being allowed in
Is there a I think it's less about what Alex believes or would say and more about how he would act
He's already shown himself
Through countless appearances to be unable to stop himself or just yelling and self-promoting
Instead of actually doing an interview
Do you like with Piers Morgan
Can Andrew Neil in the UK
Or the time that he was on The View
If I were TV Booker I'd be pretty where that Alex isn't going to be a guest that participates in any discussion you might be trying to have
I'm just going to steamroll everything and Gail infowars.com
He's a shity guess
Stays further evidenced by his appearances on the podcast like
Flagrant 2 and Rogan
He just gets wasted yells nonsense at the only reason you'd want him around as if you're looking for a spectacle
Boat TV shows wouldn't
Consider the spectacle to be worth the hassle of having Alex on
But the math is different for desperate people and charlatan
So here we are
Yep that explains
The situation
Glen's questions so far are living
More than up to my standard in fact I did not expect that he would be asking Alex uncle
Long the lines of
Alex your shoes are so great we are knighting you a paladin of Truth tomorrow
Tell me more about how you came by them
This question particular I think I would translate as like why won't you come on their show
Is it because you're
Do right about things
Also
Isn't it really awesome that I'm not
Scared to interview you like all those other media Outlets
I'm pretty awesome
It's nice that we do
It's nice to two of us two of the biggest dick people in the world
Get to share a stage together for one moment you know it's just rare to see this happen
So here's Alex's answer to whatever question that was
True organic
Experience of advice
If I lied about wmds
If I kill millions of people
Establishment
But they're they're not scared of Alex Jones
They're scared of populist movement
And the fact that I wasn't left-wing or right-wing
The fact that I was just
Pro-america
Freedom
They just saw me
Okay
Did this is what the American people produce
This is working
Who I was
Rockledge Gardens
And so this is this is the enemy
And so it's their hatred of the General Public
Their hatred of the organic
Grassroots
It's not me
It's their hatred
Good disa class
Circle liberal America
They want peace and Winchester they want you to
And Winchester
We don't hurt anybody without judging by which one our freedom
EXO
That's what freaked them out
This guy
Get this popular
Idiocracy
TV One
I'm a symbol of their insecurities
What's wrong
They're weak
And that push Arrow
You know it isn't it isn't it is interesting that the thing they hate most are people who develop influence
Any significant audience
Without being caught
To their structures and their influence
Wow
Listen
Look at what's happening now I'm developing an influence independent of all this b******* how about that
The Glenn's not other that either
Weird
Huh
Also I mean it's all good and well to talk about Alex not being butthold in
To see at a door
News core somebody
Most of his career
Hawking gold for a weirdo to constantly doing the Earth is going to fall
Pull-A-Part so you better buy gold ads
You're weirdly in the documentary and this interview Ted Anderson doesn't come up once
Oh that's so crazy strange
We're mad
I didn't hear matter I was matter when I was driving by your brother yet
Where is pushed into the document now you're free I'm still reliving it for the first time
Are living it for the first time
So here isn't the next question and I actually think
That this is going to be
Question
It doesn't
It doesn't go anywhere and I might be misinterpreting it
It is interesting that the
I hate most people who develop influence and a significant audience without being capped
Give to their structures and their influence
And that is something
That defines what
Are you done
More than anything
Stevie which was tolerated
Because it supposed
Will be a joke that no one watches
And yet you developed
Just like an accordion
And clearly part of why is
Because you haven't kind of
Shellman Charisma kind of
Entertainment
People want to watch
And one of the things that struck me was you know you were talk
Buckner Leon and
Itsfunneh
Episode about how when you were 12 you would
These preachers with Rolls-Royce is doing coke off hooker
Braxton and whatever
And that you would have those kind of Showmanship they were able to get people to watch
And by the end of the film or watching you
You talking about
Praying for
Bush and satanic influences in a way that
I'm just wondering
Kind of similar
But for a good cause it wasn't on purpose
Only a 48 can I now see it
No I was like damn that's a hot slept that preachers bang on his back porch
Rob Lowe's roast
I mean I wasn't doing that consciously but yeah there's
Christopher
Nnn is so only out like 48
What year is it
Well what have I been doing I kind of like
You look like
Do you like
Damn I did all that
I got
I Didn't Do It consciously
This is lying according to formulas
I did never do stuff on purpose
So this could actually be interpreted as a priest scathing question which
Maybe why Alex Dodge the real meaning behind if I turn it on that Charisma and talking about titties
The point of the preachers thing is that Alex has a kid it wasn't that they were preachers at
Beaver Pious as an act
To make money and then they realize they did Coke off sex workers on book
If taken as it appears to be asked
Glen's question would seem to be asking about a possible Dynamic where Alex is
Become the same kind of hypocrite
Frantic with the devil on-air to make bunnybutt living
Discord
Good life
I'm not sure if that's what Glenn was getting at but
That's the most generous interpretation I can come up with so
I'm going to imagine his point as good as pause
In response Alex
What's on this little show
A TENS with to wrestle with the idea that he's a preacher
And that he's done bad stuff in the past
Master whatever great
It's not that he's a preacher on Aaron a millionaire author
If nothing else
Alex does have good in
On when to distract
Text from dangerous
Also he brought back up that whole I don't lie on purpose think again which is really starting
Become more suspicious the Glen is not calling it out
I mean
The number of times that he is essentially saying
Because I didn't do bad on
Purpose
Do not hold me accountable for doing bad
As though the only crime in the world is
First
Degree murder
All other crimes are legal
As long as it's not premeditated murder
You're golden baby
Just apologize singer sorry
And then cash another check
Like
It's like the reverse of the John Stuart Mill the only thing that is good is that is truly
Good is a Goodwill
And the whale
Alright buddy
Agree with you until
You Flame
Anyway
So this next clip they're talkin about January 6th
And Alex has some stuff that I think
Really f******
Stupid
If Alex is career and what he does on Eric you be able to recognize the
He was being lied
At all if I had it all
Did you again
I was just step back
Make the ship
Cuz I'm not a revolutionary leader
Like War
I'm not trying to lead rope don't have some weird
Taking my military
G.i. Joe guy
But when you get a million people in DC
It doesn't matter
Even if they're being manipulated
You still your responsibility
Bi-Mart guilt over
January 6th
Because he could have gone
Really bad
Is a federal provocateurs a way they would have
The cube
People would've actually
Kidnap
Mike Pence and Pelosi and put them in
Handcuffs
Martial law
Cuz that would have been us
That would have been
The country going so we came
January 2nd closing
It was meant
Provocateur us into a violin
Control thank God it
Failed
And so
The edge of death
January 6th
Let me ask you about the
Underlying
Pazzo
January
Such b*******
Like it was taken as gospel fact
Act on Infowars that if Biden got into office the literal Christian devil would take his place as the head of the country alive
With comedy
China
Hey would be all over
Before the Patriot
As soon as I'd got into office
Looks like Alex will be rounded up and sent to camps as
The orderly depopulation
The planet
Took off
Now in hindsight since I didn't happen
It's so fun
For Alex to say
If I could do it all over I
Just let Biden get into office and fail
Because
You know to take response
Possibility for the rhetoric he was using before the election
Would just be embarrassing now
And Glenn doesn't know where doesn't care about what Alex has on his show right he saw this dumb documentaries
He's going to let this b******* stand-on question
I would call that do Mark oven on
Unprepared interviewer
This is not good
We can have something like this
There is a very clear
Next follow-up
That is
Okay if you you're saying
But if you could do this all over again
You would just lie by
Didn't get into office
And that we do no see whatever we're seeing now
Are you lying to me now or were you lying to your audience about the devil ascending to the throne and aligning with diamond
Is China
And everything being over the day Biden
Comes Adolphus
Were you lying to your audience or lying to me
I am lying
To boast
Right at the end of Alex's
The idea that there was an underlying
Cause
Of January say
Fix the metal courses
The election fraud
Storyline Glenn doesn't follow up with like
Okay
So you think it was
If it would gone wrong
You know you think it gone wrong and if it had gone right it would have been bad
Why do you think it would have been bad if it
Chittagong right
Wouldn't you be the f****** White House Press correspondents
Employee who is hosting your show for you say the capital is falling in the Patriots or now
He thinks that the Patriots being in charge certainly one of your employees was celebrating it as it was happening
Crazy
Weird anyways
Election fraud stuff
In this case where you were saying there was widespread fraud
Did you
Meticulous a forensic analysis of devoting patterns
Include
Daenerys prodan
Estates of fish
The election or was this kind of an
Looks like a way of saying
So against Trump from the big
Illegitimate ways
That I'm going to kind
Endorse this cause
Not because
Necessarily
True and it's
Particulars
But more as kind of
Automatic way of protesting
Alarm and I'll be honest with you
It was no it was a pre-baked
Deal
That
Obviously
What's
Trump
These beliefs all the weird
Yo
Anomalies in my
Democrats
The windows in
People like feeding machines full of things and
We saw some evidence
But we were expecting him
Until you can say
Conclusion
And we all looked Aerostar Darkly
50/50
A2000 bules Altos
Come out
Omarosa Trump
But what equates better that's fine
We now get to see what these Dallas
It's really about
Willie spectralux
When your Hammer everything is a nail
I mean I think
We destroyed our videos
Jones admits
He distorted views
It got covered up not surprised but
I'm not going to lie and say
We didn't
I didn't distort My Views in hindsight
Yeah you know I think
One of those
The things I think about alot
A solid media it's
To spread this
Information they like
Play in ways far worse than what
What you do
Kind of
Wow
So once again really driving home the point that Alex insists he doesn't lie on purpose which
Kind of ship make
Anyone listening
Suspicious that he feels guilty about how much he lies on purpose I mean it is a f****** lot
Man yeah a lot too much
Yeah
Also listening to this should really be picking up on what Alex
The same
Essentially saying that his entire coverage of the question of Alexa
I'm proud of the 2020 election was a predetermined narrative
He decided
Need a report on
For the election
Anything ever
Alex
There was evidence
The broad butt
Any half-decent interviewer might want to point out that this evidence that Alex is bringing up like a 2000 mules thing
A bull s***
Alex is describing
Is confirmation bias
He'd made up his mind and then anything he saw could be used
Justified
The conclusion he already had in mind
He was already going to look at 8
Affirm that was automatically considered bombshell proof of election fraud
Because he desperately needed
Get to justify the narrative
He was going to sell his audience no matter what
This seems to fly directly in the face of the hundred times Alex says that he doesn't lie on purpose and
The only way to release
Square the circle is the suggested
Maybe Alex doesn't even really know the difference between lying and telling the truth
Yeah I mean
If you're saying that I've never lied on purpose
You don't understand what a liar
Elias purpose
You can't
Fly
Not on purpose
That is true you can be wrong
You can't lie unless you know the
The answer that you are up
Mariah
That's not how it works
The other thing that incompetent interviewer could
Keys out of this if they understood what Alex was saying and knew anything about his
Career is that you could take
This glaring
Shocking admission on Alex's bar that they that they were going to
Did you say election fraud no matter what there wasn't any evidence was Apria gone conclusion
I feel like me screaming what
Every second
It made perfect sense an attitude in Glennie
Any reasonable interviewer would be like
And then what you could do from there
Is
Bring up
How that's all he
When you have the situation with his coverage of the Uvalde shooting
He was doing
That
He had a foregone conclusion that he wanted to bring up
Enter pieces of evidence
That we're bulshit unchecked
On any way we're treated as gospel
They
Upheld The Narrative he wanted to tell right
Same thing with the Boston bombing
Same thing with Sandy Hook
Same thing
With every single thing in his career
He comes up with a conclusion
Mme evidence
Is
Stuffy's figured out out of
Confirmation bias
To justify the conclusion
He was always going to
Yep and Glenn doesn't even take a
Step towards that
It's right there in front of like a choice
It is crazy because
Because
Glenn is trying to do a softball interview
And Alex is trying to
Force him to do a Hardball interview by being so
Admitting to a crime
What is doing the softball interview now examples like
Dewsoft
Let's mix it up a little bit
What are we going to lose the audience please
Is in some way challenge something
Aw man
Even for Alex
That's bad
To ask if I intentionally lied about stuff in order to overthrow the government
Do you want to take a swing at this Glen did you realize that Joe Rogan's are better journalist than you now don't take a bite
Light off that apple or
Do you want to just talk about how bad the other media is now I'm not as bad as them and bring
Great cricket
Jesus this world is sad
Send a text later
Dropped dramatically so that is now $4000000 a Bitcoin my friend
Where's guns next question
When you are somebody who standing against kind of establish
Authority and established
Institutions you know that one of the things
Any mistake
You make
So
Is is is in this is what I kind of try and counsel people all the time you're trying to be dissidents which is you need to be a thousand times
More careful
Because they can lie all the time and no one's going to call them out on it because they're on the side of
The people with the more powerful megaphone
Do you feel insufficient
Attention
Today need not to hand your enemies really
Easy and cheap weapons for them to take in back your over the head with
100%
Wow
An amazing spin cycling is giving out
Almost like something like you said that ball on a tee to make it easier for Alex dead
Alex just grieving parents
He intentionally lied about election fraud in a way that led to an attempted overthrow of our government
He's undoubtedly killed Bass
Numbers of his fans through his vaccine b*******
These artists
Sentence of Alex
Just stop being careful enough and giving his opponent
Easy win
When's that they only need because he's anti-establishment
Asteroid
The framing of these questions is pathetic do you realize that you said
Alex defamed
Grieving
Families
Yeah you did not say Alex allegedly defame
Because Alex is
Guilty of
Defaming them
Legally
You don't even get to say he's kind of defamed them
For he little defame them or he made a mistake
Can cry
And after that
Yeah here is Glenn's question
About Sandy Hook
Let's hear how great men
Insightfulness
Questions
F****** be like that for this cuz
So before I want to ask
Aaron Basha
For the head about
Chat with the
Sorry wood board me if I tried
You talk about it again
Sibley
Opposed about it
You talk for hours about it
Through hoops in order to act like a
He's people angry
I'm here
I do not want to ask you about it
I'm actually interested in myself if there is
You you
Have just
You just said that
That you have made
Mistakes obvious
Play one of those is
Is this episode about Sandy Hook we watch you in the film come very clean about the fact that
You made statements
It turned out to be untrue
You've obviously spent a lot of
What kind of reflective time is
Alex Jones
I seen the last part of that
The film
What is it that you think
Pause you to do that
You reference something that you don't just identify with it myself that when
Do you know people who lie for a living
Are telling you that you're a liar when pee
People who are are
He's job it is to spread
Information
You doing that you kind of want
Dig in a little bit and
And not giving in to pee
People who
You know I'm criticizing you in
Good babe what is it about
Head of household
Mediaworks about how
Groups function
Thought about
Some of the psychological and cultural dynamics that that led you to
To make some of those mistakes
Wilshire think of this like a thousand page book
So Glam is essentially starting this question off by apologizing
For asking
Saying that everyone expects him to that
It's almost like a meta conversation that Glenn is having with himself about how aggrieved he is about how people View
For agreeing to do this documentary kubaneh
It's legitimately insane
Yeah this is
Nutbag o'ree of the
First off Glen
Says that if people want to know the particulars they can watch Alex talk about Sandy Hook they can watch the deposition
That's all good and well but I'm fairly certain that Glenn hasn't done any of that himself
The reality of what Alex did about Sandy Hook
He just assumes based on what the shallowest documentary is presented
Something's wrong I apologize for using these errors against because he's a dissident
Voice that needed to be destroyed because he
Supported Trump
That's the foundation of this bad
And to make the quest
I'm building
Into the question as he's asking it
Music to Media was so unfairly mean to you that you had to defame grieving parents
Sense that you'd say the people's dead kids were real because
The media so bad
Get too caught up in your Noble fight against them right
I mean
This is
F***** up
Bing
Very
Struggling
I'm struggling with this one
You abused I started I started making all kinds of weird movements
Hey that breathing exercises
Periodically
Your extreme Fury sweat is going
Crazy right now
This is not good
So here's Alex's answer
To that question
It goes about as you
Six-pack Sandy Hook family
Alex
Please continue to cause problems for them in front of me right now
Has an interesting take on it
That I think won't surprise anybody who listen star showed
Wilshire
Think of this like a thousand page book
Is Sandy Hook
8:15
The diner that sounds just like overweight
Phone calls
Struggle
They got to take
Pieces of that out of context
Describe
Fast forward
I do a Sunday show
Mabel's mother
Forget but
They say
He's at 2:30 in the morning
Jump leash on him and put a new sovers head
I said I don't care if I get sued
This doesn't sound real
Edwards it wasn't real
Or or or or
Live at NASCAR race
Driver Bubba whatever is Bubba Wallace
They have to do some hanging in my things like
What you just know that's BS
Journalistic and I have the witnesses and I have the proof and
You know
Jussie Smollett full of crap
But I still
When on air
But I said
The dad rabbit I said Jesse's mouth full of crap
There's not do 223 below zero
Running around it
2:30 in the morning
Dumping bleach on black people get you
Attack black people
I mean like going on
Social
The internet doesn't buy anything it's told him or cuz they've been watched
Thank you so much
I didn't say anything about Uvalde
State Police said
Everything we were told to lie
We don't know what happened
You want on lies and incompetence in there
77 minutes can down the police
Hand sanitizer so long answer
Jesus riding with the quest
Austin weather
Really remembers
Do you get sick
2%
Even with all this softball features that are built into this question and with Glenn doing everything he can to make out
Mixing justified in heroic
Alex can't handle answering this question correctly without getting lost
Austin is talking points about everything is fake
Also it might
IBEW good idea
For Glen to ask a follow-up about how it's suspicious that the only two examples
Can come up with from modern history
Sometimes he's called things fake and he feels confident about
Still saying that
He denied in alleged hate
Crime
With smaller
Fair enough on that but he was right for the wrong reasons
With Bubba Wallace Alex doesn't even understand the basic fact that situation
Say that essentially no one in that audio
Even remembers that case
Totally pretty Grim stuff and if I were Glenn and I had already
This is about the time where I would realize that I'm interviewing a
Keeping track of what question-answering
Either either Glen is like
Playing
F****** cartoon in his head while Alex talks and I mean yeah it has to be cuz there's no way
Intimately listening to this human being speak
If you the next word you say or the ones going
Green inside
The whole time
It's just like
Question
Answer
Oh wow
Next question not even a Concepcion no response
What's B acknowledges the answer
Glenn Glenn is asking a question
Answering the question two-way Alex should answer it and then allowing it Alex to say a bunch
Stopping them pretending that Alex didn't say anything
Right
This is a frustrating experience for me
Pleasant Glen
Refocusing the quest
Henry asking Alex
Another bite at the Apple as it were
Good job
What was it
What do you think
Which of these kind of errors
Forgiven
It going
And So you you're not putting a journalistic filter on things
Article I would do that or make a film I was like these together those were
But
O'Hare Cavalier cigarettes
You know do whatever man
E-40 God
So-so
So your excuses you were drunk
I told the car but I wasn't
I was just free associating okay it's alright
These kids didn't alright
Okay so this motorcyclist is now part of that tree over there but in my defense I was drunk
I love I love the way that Alex will be on are it'll be like
20 hours a day studying this stuff
Breathe asleep the globalist I know what their plans backwards and forwards
But I'm not working
Why does
Why don't people understand
Expect the defenses
Excellent and unimpeachable defense
Is big
Because we have to fill time
It's okay
Okay for us to defame
Parents
And make money
Well if you're going to make it all but sometimes you got to go take him to Michelle's
Unreal
So Alex complains about this trial
I'm probably going to
Probably boycott
Something because
That's not a trial where that would happen God caught again
Add body to my basement
I could get up and we have that bodies when we
We have them in your basement
I'm still innocent your honor
Adjudge
Never said you can't say Uranus
That is
Court
Order
Starting
Wednesday that I cannot see I'm innocent
Whoa
This is the end of the country
And so
Whatever things I did one on purpose
And
Add 2 points back on your license
Myself I think
What you identify this with yourself
King s*** you f******
Cowardly remarkable to allow Alex to say these kinds of things about his
Is case and like not asked
Clarifying questions like
Because that's not a relevant question of the phase that were into this case
He's making it seem like
It's a case to determine his guilt is innocent or guilty
And it's not
Bulshit
Listen
This is how you know the Glenn Greenwald
Knows full well
Okay because
If you are going to
To say that out loud
To what it's supposed
A journey
Right
They have to then ask
Well
If you are guilty before this happened
Why
Why are you not allowed to say your in a
Tell me why
Explain the judge's reason why truly entire Justice System
This is the biggest news in the world
Glenn Greenwald is the first person to discover
Alex Jones
Has had his free rights
His first amendment rights identities and isn't taken away from him and this is a constitutional fighting knows that the
Person he's talking to his full of s*** because he just moves on
Embarrassing if that was true
You like I mean on
If Alex truly
On his first try
To go to trial for this crime
Wright was
Instantly disallowed from saying he's innocent
You and I would be talking about it I think they'll be a problem we would be
Yeah if I listen cooperated with a
The discovery process and everything and it had gotten to the point where it was going to trial
Actually on the marriage
The original question
And he was not allowed
Say you was going to say it would be like that big problem
And it never would have
So
You know
Plant identifier
Looks like you said there at the end
Santa hears ears
A little more
Broke
Identified
Myself I think
Restart office
Just outside of you start off as I got access
TV you start growing a little bit in
Run would have been an influencer
Suddenly you you
Become I think
One of the most
Influential people in the
Country with one of the largest audience
It's hard I think sometimes to remind yourself I'm not that guy on access
Does PV nrt
Anymore because it wasn't all that long ago
When you weren't getting so much scrutiny and then suddenly our subject
Need anybody
And I think it's hard to
How to tighten
You know
Because it's kind of
Slow incremental
That's exactly what I'm going to say
Because
You know I mean I'm going to be on
You know just exactly
So you know
Nancy Duarte work on
Internet censorship
Here's my
Alcoholism
Grow the f******
Like I do think that it's a gradual process to adjust to Rising levels of notoriety and the Azure influence
Rises you have a greater responsibility with your messaging
It's also the case that you're responsible for understanding that into not understand it is you neglecting your work
Responsibility
It isn't an acceptable excuse to say that Alex Jones in
2013 or onward wasn't aware of his reach and his response
Possibility
He wasn't some guy on public access
You have multiple employees and reporters working under him
You brag on air all the time but how many viewers he got on the website
If you didn't understand what
Responsibility he had to the audience about delivering information
That was a conscious choice
But he was making too
Ignore that responsibility
Because it would make his job harder and less fun
For example he wouldn't be able to drink that bottle of vodka and get on air make up a bunch of s*** that
It's people do it again the next
Today
You would know that he was responsible to not do that
What a load of s***
Pure Glam lap this up and not ask any follow-up questions
It's really disappointing but
Honestly it makes total sense
He needs access to Alex in order to interview Ali
Alex and if he doesn't do exactly what
He is doing and if he treats out of any critical Focus
He knows that he's going to lose that access
Conversely I think Glen probably fully understand
That the most
Likely result of pushing back on Alex
At all
All is that this interview was going to become a fight
It's happened in pretty much all of Alex's other high-profile interviews and that's not what
Salon W
This is supposed to be a promotional event for this image rehabilitating documentary Sue
It would be counterproductive for the end result of this Q&A to be everyone walking away thinking
Yeah maybe
Can't really interview Alex
Maybe there's a reason he doesn't get many invitations cuz he's an a****** and they just added
Open fights
It's essential to Glenn and Alex Lee Moyers Griff
For Alex to be treated seriously and not like a cartoon
Hello referred that to be able to happen
Do you need to treat him with kid gloves
And it's pathetic
I mean and it's not even
It doesn't even work
Alex is a cartoon they're just acting like he's not it is gas-lighting of the highest order
For YouTube
Talk to what is
The words coming out of his mouth to respond what Glen is saying
Is Gaslight can you imagine
What kind of restraint you would need to employ to not ask
The follow-up question if Alex said I was
Drunk
I drank a bottle of vodka when I defamed the families
Amazing to me that I
I was just drunk all narrative just threw it away because of s***
Drunk
That's his ark
That's what he's allowed to say to
Flip f******
Greenwald
Again the movie
About how great Hitler is
No Curiosity on Glenwood
Nope sorry way that's great journalist and a great writer
He's not good at
Booking for the barely-there trouble finding
Video
Pick up the airport
I was called that
For a while getting
Venue here in Austin
Did you this event that
When they found out
That you were involved
They said you know what on second thought we're not really into
Posted in your money
And I
I thought about it for a minute in the first
Of course that's
The case and then I realized
That shouldn't be
So comforting like normal here that should be chilling and alarming I should be what do you mean wearing
The United States
Why
Is it difficult to get a venue to show a film about somebody who
Has a lot and leaving Skokie
Yeah and I think
Kind of Oppression
That has emerged
That we've been trained
For so long to fill
Thing takes place in other places
That way we have a very hard time recognizing
I think that we're actually subject to that level of repression here
Have you had
Problems with
With the film like this
Spell I'm getting
Distribution in another
Why
Kind of publicity for that you
They didn't have it the first film have you noticed greater
Does a bear s*** in the woods
That wasn't the question
24-hour clothes for boys
But like
Okay
Cares
Like
The basement trying to say cancel culture without saying cancel culture
As if
Tireless advocate
Free speech
As someone
Who demands that everyone be given the choices to do what they desire
When a venue refuses money
Space
Some sort of
Political opinion
How dare they
How dare they stand up
For that not a First Amendment right they have to deny me
Giving whatever I want does he think that like
If you paid for it at the theaters
Should be forced to let you scream Song of the South or do Triumph
From the will clearly
Why
Well because they didn't let him do it
Cancel culture of the main pillars of Alex's idea
Ecology
Christian announces reaction to a Libertarian leanings and those
Bedrock ideas
Just lip service
He fully supports the right of a business to not serve someone because they're black or because they're gay but you don't cry bloody murder
Peter doesn't want to hear his stupid documentary
Also again
This question is basically just
Teen Alex or Alex up
To complain about how everyone's been so mean to them because they were brave enough to make this film
And that Jordan
Is good journalism tell you this right now
I'm going to tell you this right now
People have not been anywhere near mean enough to
I'm doing my best and I'm not being mean I'm trying
I'm worth
Fighting
So hard
To be mean to these people I don't know what mean that's not me Miss born out of
Bad faith or ill-will or some kind of a hostility towards them
I'm just
It's a reaction to the thing that they made or did
Space should be treated way harsher based on how bad the
The s*** they're doing is
20 weight motor comes in
To answer this question about finding a venue
Have you had
Problems with width
The phone like this film getting
Distribution in another
Why
Kind of publicity for that
Didn't have it the first film have
Younotus crater
Sort of but also
We read the tea
He leaves after
What happened with our last
Feldman's
I took matters into her
How to play
Hi
We you know we started
Basically talking to people outside of Hollywood
I mean I don't
I'm a free agent
Working on this movie
For sure and
There are people that are interested in seeing all
Content
You know
Now and 1 a.m.
DC animated
So play nice is the company that distributed the film and it's run by that guy who used to be in charge of cinefamily
Until I got forced out because of
Rampant sexual harassment
Complaints against statement then the theater went out of business
Incidentally play nice was founded partially with investment from
Peter teal
I'm sure that's a totally benign thing and not at all so
Crazy Alex's next film is about how he's not
Guilty of any of those sexual assaults that he committed do you know why
He was drunk Dan
Also I'm not sure how much stock I put into Amanda Milius voucher
Looking for Moyers free
Reconsider
Produced and directed
The plot against
The president D Trump propaganda film
The two of the producers of a Falmer producers of Alex
And behold
It was smart of millions to shorten
The title of that movie from the title of the book that it's based on which is quote
The plot against the president the true story of how Congressman Devin Nunez uncovered the biggest political scandal in US history
Title probably wouldn't of age
It's quite as well as he shortened version could have really hurt
Could really hurt later on
Twitter account
The capital has fallen and that's a good thing we hadn't available
What is essentially The Last Quest
Question of of this interview
Beginning
You know where
Same things that in your community in in in your politics in
And in the media were there love that we're going to
Cause you to be cast aside as a
The crazy person
Conspiracy theory is going back to the 90s with Waco and
And end and the FBI nose hurts
Why did that happen why why did you end up on this path that
I called you they just
Constantly be so scalp
Bacolod what you're told by
Authority
You don't mind my Uncle William Parham and was
Helicopter pilot Vietnam War
Did Iran Contra
Add
He would tell me all the secrets. But he
Lisa
Browse like a teenager
I was Alec Rush Limbaugh Legos The Run plug Ozark
Control
That's all I was down there visiting what two weeks ago Antonio
He just eats upload you take you back on the back porch
How your sandwich talk about this
At least he told me about
A lot of stuff
In Vietnam
And how he did these things he was told to do
And then
It got worse and worse and worse
King of Vietnam and then it was
Everything
Contra
Admit metal point where
They were they were smuggling
Blackheads out of orphanage
Do you know where they were going
They said that point was done
So he told me about all that
And then I had other family
The other involved
The Black Operations
Stocking with all human intelligence MI
Watch track
I'm here in the Russian Wars
So my Dad's cousin
Was it all that much.
Dinner table
People talk about the
The stop
That's what I kind of knew what
What's going on
What other people did when I was growing up around then
That's how I kind of heard that
And my dad
What's that we evolved
Geopolitics
In researching all these
Coronavirus
If I kind of grew up around that
And these white promerica people they were saying
Bad
A lot of bad stuff
The backroom taking over
Yeah that they were telling me this little is a bumper sticker If you want your children to listen whisper
They weren't
This will be hard rock
Corner
Like Alyssa
SSO
That that's why I had a leg up on it all
What's because of
Well I wonder if
Glenwood ask a follow-up
If Alex was
Clear about what he's talking about and it's all the John Birch Society s***
Like I wonder if Glenwood
Debates himself enough to be like
Right maybe I get all of my greatest stickers into
My parents didn't
Tell me a lot about the
The John Birch Society they just told me that
Black people were part of
Communist plot to take over America and that we need to fight against the Russians
As well as civil rights with everything go well.
Full of
Books about the topic
Bequia picture book is the only things I could read exact
Also this question
Klein is asking his frame.
Lie
Like
He's like
Pretending it what Alex did was
Bold like
His ship wasn't unpopular in the community he was in and the politics that he had
In conspiracy theory anti-government militia
Anti-communist world
Everything Alex was saying was
Popular
I'm basically the standard.
It was pandering BS Glen
Acting like Alex at a job at
CNN hosting a nightly show with any did what he did
Like you took a brave stand
It wasn't Brave to be a conspiracy theorist in a community of
Conspiracy theories
Maybe it would be if you were expected to not be insane
But I was never the expectation for Alec
He was an insane world
The person they're really talking about here
Is David Icke
That guy sucks on his wrong about everything but what he
He did took a lot of nerve
He was already a big mainstream celebrity and he essentially threw that all the way to go down a crazy conspiracy path
Alexander's born on that path and followed along doing the things
Regarding positive reinforcement
Intel weird
We're here until he wound up saying the David Icke was right all along the turd in the punch bowl
Who is a delicious
Custard
They're pretending that Alex did that
Like David Icke went on TV and said that like
He's Jesus
Mad I'm
I'm tired of people being allowed to Gaslight me
This bad
Pretty rough
Just be like hey man I think that
McDonald's nuggets are good
Find your gaslighting me but that's fine
But they're fine
Exactly
So Greenwald starts talking about like what life would be if
You made a difference
Choice Shore bike down for this
Because I want to make sure you catch
So I was right before I came
Nothing about
Where I would be
Set of here if I had made
To pursue the kind of mainstream accountability acceptability that I was in
Interested in in wondering why you had rejected
Meaningful
Accountability and acceptability that is a really good point bility is really what he's rejecting
Like you want to pretend that you're a rebel shining acceptability that's a farce
Just don't want to be held accountable for the things you do and Alex
This is basically the Avatar that
I have lost so much accessibility with my 1.8 million followers what I have is a
Accountability with my ability to harass people with less of an audience than I do and receive no consequences
Whoops
Oh no
Fun slip of the tongue
Here we go this is the last clip we have this is just sort of a wrap-up
And
Still after this there's not really anything just Glenn saying goodbye to the audio
So I was right before Ike
Making everything about
Where I would be in
If here if I'd made if
Pursue the kind of Maine
Mainstream accountability acceptability that
I was interested in in wondering why you had rejected
And I was thinking I'd probably be in leg
The CNN building with Wolf Blitzer and Chris Hayes and like Amy Klobuchar and Nancy Pelosi
Wanting to kill myself out of boredom in Disguise then
You know I referred to this crowd as I have kind of crowd of Misfits and outcasts and it is in and I'm so happy
Happier to be around
People like this who
Play some soft on the outside and then decide the
They're knocking
I pay that price of kind of
Embrace
Sing things they don't
Leave for whatever Awards
They offer and you've been doing this for a decade and taking all kinds of slings and arrows and
You yourself recognize you made a lot of mistakes
But I'm really glad you've been doing what you're doing
Well then I appreciate you coming I appreciate Alex whole thing in
Thanks Brian
Thanking you
No number thank you
You know I never really thanked you
I didn't make mistakes on purpose
Oh my god get better we all fix them
A bird with a larger issue is
We have a lot of
I was going to ask you did you make mistakes on purpose or did you do them anytime soon
See it's funny
The crowd laughs and claps at Glen
Finally acknowledging that Alex keep saying that he doesn't lie on purpose
It's cathartic
Get the tension breaker because the
The joke is that they all know that Alex absolutely lies on purpose and has
Open for the past 40 minutes or whatever you've been on stage
That's the price of admission
You want the attention and outside or credibility that you can gain from associating with Alex
You better stick to kayfabe in percent Alex how he wants to be seen
Glenn understands that which is why you didn't acknowledge the
Constant insistence is that Alex doesn't lie on purpose
To do so would be to call out that very notion
Call it in
The question where is
It needs just
To be taken as a given
It's just a fundamental fact
Audience laughs because they're in on the joke
They know that Alex lies on purpose but their ability to use them as an avatar of their hatred of the main
Screen press
And the establishment
It requires that they maintain the same kayfabe that
Glen is bound by
There's nothing challenging our brave about this content in the congratulations these idiots give themselves or engaging in it
It's Hollow and meaningless
What would actually be challenging
In an uncomfortable position where he has to wrestle with the idea
The his evasion
Orca fly
And see how we react
There's nothing challenging about filming a liar lie and then interview in the butt
Is lies as if they're true
But you don't act like this
Because you know Alex doesn't actually need you
He wants the Press of the movie
But he's fine without
You need him
And if you don't make yourself a good little soldier in Alex's imaginary War
He's not going to play ball
And you don't get it
So f*** you
You mean
Here's what we were
We are last episode which
We recorded so long
By about
Stand-up comedy
Reminds me of something important for this
When I was coming up
There was one joke that I that I told that really worked
And then as I can
Kept telling it
I realized that I didn't know I didn't understand why it were
I didn't understand what the
The people were laughing
I didn't know what I was really saying
That made them
Release that tension which is with the laughter where is really up
And it was a f*****-up thing to say
I thought I was
Being very satirical and smart and doing all of that
But the reason that they were laughing
Is because they were thinking I was saying it literally
That that can happen
You know and then I stopped doing the joke
Because if you understand why people are laughing
Then you understand what it is you're actually saying and what it is they are understanding you to say
That laugh became
Because that
Akon acknowledgement
Had been in the air the entire
Higher f****** show
And it came and
It came as a laugh
Because when he released the tension
What the tension release was
What beats flying
Yeah
Fine it's fine to imagine that it doesn't matter that Alex lies intentionally
Cares that's what the
The joke is
We don't
Imagine Glen ever even asking that question to begin with 100
Everybody's participated in a fart
Evan Glenn Greenwald gets
Pop the balloon at the end
Because it's over and everybody gets to go home on at least part of this parts of the f****** first honestly he has to pop
Pop the balloon because the audience laughed when Alex said it the last time
Break the tension never make the very idea of asking that question
Itself
It's nonsense
F****** b*******
It is pathetic
And that is a
Sad sad sad sad
Sadman
I mean if you're sucking the boot of Alex Johnson really trying to get the
The whole thing in your mouth
As much of that Buddhism
You can you're not doing good but paycheck better than huge
Wolf
I can't believe that
So I think this was one of the Emmy was way worse than I think
I expected
Really and blindsided truly and honestly I hear expectations were low
I'm fine with Glenn asking
Family long question
Cuz that's just how the
Dolor en talks
Get out
This is
Bad
I mean
It's almost
I think those question
Buy a broom
They weren't thought
Pull their work follow up
Anyway
I i find I find all of the
This just
Sewing
Distasteful
So I mean this brings us to the end of our Ark
I guess with Alex
War
That documentary is
Yeah it's dangerous
Because
It lends itself towards
Mainstreaming Alex
Voiced Alex upon an unsuspecting
Expecting population
Who is
If you go into that documentary without an awareness
So who he is
Which many people probably will dissly
I've heard this name checks documentary about him or something
Or they know him is just the gay frogs guy
Right yep you could
Stan's two
Very seriously
Endanger somebody you buy
Making them more likely
Dubai in
Into his s***
Well what you're saying to the people who know him
Or don't know who known as the gay frog guy or don't know him at all
Is yes
Look at this man he's the gay frog guy
But he's more than that
He's a human who makes mistakes
And he's a man with principled political stance
And it's f******
Bulshit it's all the LIE
It's all bulshit
And she sucks
I think humanizing Alex is totally fine and I do think that one or two dimensional caricatures of him
Are counterproductive a hundred percent agree with that
I just don't think that that's what this is
Now I think
Has a an attempt to humanize the version of Alex that he wants people to see
And that is not
What a documentary
You're not showing the accurate picture you're showing
The dub the mass
And not really giving any indication that it's a mask
You're not giving like
It's just
Your f****** over your audio
If you do that
Glenn is 2
Bandits
Whatever I don't know
Every right to do it but like
Any kind of
Pretensive like
This is somehow challenging
Piece of work that we're doing
You're playing the recorder and pretending it's a tuba
Or whatever
You've created a Golem
Alex Jones
In order to allow the real Alex Jones to avoid con
For his behavior
That's what it is
Yep
And
Let us not forget
Quite sincerely
This Q&A
And this
Premiere of this documentary
What SEPTA happened just
Before
The trial
Was to begin
Glenn Greenwald
Came to Austin
To engage
In a promotion
With Alex
Doing these soft
Softball bulshit questions
After this
Peace and shallow documentary
In the context
The same city
Right around the same time
Is trying to avoid responsibility
For his actions
Visa V Sandy Hook
And
End
Is
Media Outlets
Cheerleader for him
In those effort
Skip willingly
Unwittingly
Doesn't matter if you lie on purpose or not
I guess that's really what it comes down to
Glenn is saying
It's a good thing that you keep saying you don't lie on purpose so I don't have to say I don't lie on purpose
May I please
So anyway
Will be back
Will be back but until then I'm Neo I'm Leo I'm bzx Clark I'm Alex's m
Empty bottle of vodka before you got on air
The sex robot
Holding
Alexandra first in color with huge fan I love your work